<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:53+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레이니맨_Rainy_Man/우리_결혼해요/</id><title>레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 우리 결혼해요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:21:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:21:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%88%EB%A7%A8_Rainy_Man/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EA%B2%B0%ED%98%BC%ED%95%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 우리 결혼해요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[결혼해요 우리 결혼해요 <br>결혼해요 우리 결혼해요 <br>인생은 모르는 것 <br>완벽한 왕자님과 <br>결혼해요 우리 결혼해요 <br>결혼해요 우리 결혼해요 <br>어차피 막장인생 <br>사랑도 완벽해요 <br>지금 이 순간 내리는 비도 <br>세찬 비바람도 <br>거대한 태풍이 와도 <br>우리의 결혼은 막을 수 없어 <br>결혼해요 우리 결혼해요 <br>결혼해요 우리 결혼해요 <br>인생은 부딪히는 것 <br>사랑스런 왕자님과 <br>결혼해요 우리 결혼해요 <br>결혼해요 우리 결혼해요 <br>어차피 흐린 인생 <br>사랑이 해결해요 <br>지금 이 순간 내리는 비도 <br>세찬 비바람도 <br>거대한 태풍이 와도 <br>우리의 결혼은 막을 수 없어 <br>우리의 사랑을 막을 수 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)" label="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)"/><category term="우리 결혼해요" label="우리 결혼해요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레이니맨_Rainy_Man/난_마법에_빠진_레이니맨/</id><title>레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 난 마법에 빠진 레이니맨 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:21:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:21:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%88%EB%A7%A8_Rainy_Man/%EB%82%9C_%EB%A7%88%EB%B2%95%EC%97%90_%EB%B9%A0%EC%A7%84_%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%88%EB%A7%A8/" title="레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 난 마법에 빠진 레이니맨 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 마법에 걸린 레이니 맨 <br>지독한 마법에 난 걸렸죠 <br>태양에 버림받고 난 후에 <br>흐린 먹구름만 기다리죠 <br>태양아래 내게 다가온 <br>여자는 아무도 없죠 <br>난 태양을 피해야만 했고 <br>비 내리는 날만 기다리죠 <br>하루하루 비참함 속에서 <br>태양을 피해 헤매이다 <br>지쳐 힘없이 쓰러질 때 <br>써니걸 나를 <br>햇살 속으로 인도 했죠 <br>나를 원했나요 <br>내가 원했나요 <br>여기까지가 나는 <br>끝인가 봐요 <br>당신에게 난 <br>짐만 될 뿐이잖아요 <br>이젠 영원히 행복해요 <br>나의 햇살이여 <br>태양아래 내게 다가온 <br>여자는 아무도 없죠 <br>난 태양을 피해야만 했고 <br>비 내리는 날만 기다리죠 <br>하루하루 비참함 속에서 <br>태양을 피해 헤매이다 <br>지쳐 힘없이 쓰러질 때 <br>써니걸 나를 <br>햇살 속으로 인도 했죠 <br>나를 원했나요 <br>내가 원했나요 <br>여기까지가 나는 <br>끝인가 봐요 <br>당신에게 난 <br>짐만 될 뿐이잖아요 <br>이젠 영원히 행복해요 <br>나를 원했나요 <br>나를 원했나요 <br>내가 원했나요 <br>여기까지가 나는 <br>끝인가 봐요 <br>당신에게 난 <br>짐만 될 뿐이잖아요 <br>이젠 영원히 행복해요 <br>나의 햇살이여 <br>]]></content><category term="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)" label="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)"/><category term="난 마법에 빠진 레이니맨" label="난 마법에 빠진 레이니맨"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레이니맨_Rainy_Man/미안해요/</id><title>레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 미안해요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:22:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:22:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%88%EB%A7%A8_Rainy_Man/%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%88%ED%95%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 미안해요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[정말 미안해요 <br>나의 욕심 때문에 <br>그대의 따뜻한 <br>사랑을 잃을까 <br>두려워서 그랬었던 거죠 <br>미안해요 그대가 <br>날 버릴까 하는 생각에 <br>그대의 부드러운 <br>미소를 잃을까 하는 <br>두려운 마음에 <br>그랬었던 거죠 <br>이제는 이 마법을 <br>풀어버릴래 <br>그리고 그대 손을 <br>꼭 잡고서 기도해요 <br>저 하늘 높이 <br>하얀 구름처럼 <br>힘겹던 지난날 <br>기억에서 지워나가요 <br>미안해요 <br>나의 욕심 때문에 <br>그대의 따뜻한 <br>사랑을 잃을까 <br>두려워서 그랬었던 거죠 <br>미안해요 그대가 <br>날 버릴까 하는 생각에 <br>그대의 부드러운 <br>미소를 잃을까 하는 <br>두려운 마음에 <br>그랬었던 거죠 <br>이제는 이 마법을 <br>풀어 버릴래 <br>그리고 그대 손을 <br>꼭 잡고서 기도해요 <br>저 하늘 높이 <br>하얀 구름처럼 <br>힘겹던 지난날 <br>기억에서 지워나가요 <br>우리의 지난날들은 <br>비가 오고 어둠 <br>가득한 밤이지만 <br>이젠 모두 잊고 <br>이겨낼 수 있죠 <br>당신의 따스한 <br>내일을 위해 가요 <br>워 그대여 이제 <br>아무 걱정 말아요 <br>그동안 정말 <br>마음고생 많았을 텐데 <br>이젠 정말 마법에서 <br>깨어나요 <br>그대 항상 행복을 빌어요 <br>영원히 행복하길 <br>]]></content><category term="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)" label="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)"/><category term="미안해요" label="미안해요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레이니맨_Rainy_Man/남자들은_쓰레기/</id><title>레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 남자들은 쓰레기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:22:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:22:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%88%EB%A7%A8_Rainy_Man/%EB%82%A8%EC%9E%90%EB%93%A4%EC%9D%80_%EC%93%B0%EB%A0%88%EA%B8%B0/" title="레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 남자들은 쓰레기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[yech come on <br>What 하 하 <br>Let’s Go come on <br>이 시대 남자들은 <br>뭐다 쓰레기 <br>남자들은 꺼져버려 <br>시궁창에 빠져버려 <br>쓰레기통에 버려진 <br>찌꺼기같은 존재들 <br>여잘보길 돌같이하는 <br>짐승같은 본능들 <br>하나같이 머리통엔 <br>19금만 가득찼어 <br>워 <br>여자들은 남자들의 <br>하룻밤의 One night <br>two night 오늘밤은 <br>남자들의 제삿날 <br>지금부터 남자들은 <br>백해무익 해충취급 <br>내가 바로 해충잡는 <br>insectbuster F killer <br>남자들은 쓰레기 <br>쓰레기통에 꺼져버려 <br>남자들은 쓰레기 <br>쓰레기통에 꺼져버려 <br>남자들은 쓰레기 <br>쓰레기통에 꺼져버려 <br>남자들은 쓰레기 <br>쓰레기통에 꺼져버려 <br>남자들은 쓰레기 <br>쓰레기통에 꺼져버려 <br>남자들은 쓰레기 <br>쓰레기통에 꺼져버려 <br>남자들은 쓰레기 <br>쓰레기통에 꺼져버려 <br>남자들은 쓰레기 <br>쓰레기통에 꺼져버려 <br>]]></content><category term="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)" label="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)"/><category term="남자들은 쓰레기" label="남자들은 쓰레기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레이니맨_Rainy_Man/안아줄게/</id><title>레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 안아줄게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:22:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:22:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%88%EB%A7%A8_Rainy_Man/%EC%95%88%EC%95%84%EC%A4%84%EA%B2%8C/" title="레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 안아줄게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[따사로운 햇볕이 내리쬐는 날 <br>하늘은 너무나 화창해 <br>날아갈 것만 같아 <br>우두커니 외롭게 앉아있는 그 <br>당신은 왜 이리 슬퍼요 <br>이제 내가 꼭 안아 줄래 <br>그대 외로워마요 <br>내 손을 꼭 잡아요 <br>이제 슬퍼하지 마요 <br>내가 안아줄게 <br>따사로운 햇볕이 내리쬐는 날 <br>당신은 왜 이리 슬퍼요 <br>내가 꼭 안아줄게 <br>따사로운 햇볕이 내리쬐는 날 <br>당신은 왜 그리 슬퍼요 <br>다가가 내가 안아줄게 <br>그대 슬퍼말아요 <br>내가 다 안아 줄게요 <br>오늘은 힘든 일이 있었나요 <br>이제는 괜찮아요 <br>내 어깰 빌려 줄게요 <br>눈물은 어울리지 않아요 <br>이제는 내가 다 안아 줄게요 <br>]]></content><category term="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)" label="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)"/><category term="안아줄게" label="안아줄게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레이니맨_Rainy_Man/맑은_하늘/</id><title>레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 맑은 하늘 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:22:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:22:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%88%EB%A7%A8_Rainy_Man/%EB%A7%91%EC%9D%80_%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98/" title="레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 맑은 하늘 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[맑은 하늘 화창한 날 <br>왜 나의 맘은 어두워지나요 <br>햇살 속에 나의 자린 <br>그 어디에도 존재하진 않죠 <br>선샤인 샤랄라 맑은 하늘은 <br>우릴 기다리죠 <br>가슴을 내밀고 마음을 열면 <br>모두 행복해요 <br>샤랄라 라 라라 <br>라라라 라라 <br>라라 라라라라라 <br>샤랄라 라 라라 <br>라라라 라 라 <br>라라 라라라라 <br>맑은 하늘 화창한 날 <br>왜 나의 맘은 어두워지나요 <br>햇살 같은 저 여인은 <br>나의 맘을 이해 못하겠죠 <br>]]></content><category term="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)" label="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)"/><category term="맑은 하늘" label="맑은 하늘"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레이니맨_Rainy_Man/내리는_비야/</id><title>레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 내리는 비야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:22:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:22:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%88%EB%A7%A8_Rainy_Man/%EB%82%B4%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_%EB%B9%84%EC%95%BC/" title="레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 내리는 비야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내리는 비야 촉촉이 내려다오 <br>그녀들의 마음을 적셔 줄께 <br>샤르르르 내려다오 <br>그녀들의 사랑을 가져 갈께 <br>샤르르르 내려다오 <br>폭풍이 몰아치고 <br>거센 바람 불어오면 <br>그녀를 위해서 <br>어디라도 가겠소 <br>맑은날은 찾지마오 <br>비가 오면 내가간다 <br>내리는 비야 촉촉이 내려다오 <br>그녀들의 마음을 적셔줄께 <br>샤르르르 내려다오 <br>그녀들의 사랑을 가져갈께 <br>샤르르르 내려다오 <br>폭풍이 몰아치고 <br>거센바람 불어오면 <br>그녀를 위해서 <br>어디라도 가겠소 <br>맑은날은 찾지마오 <br>비가오면 내가간다 <br>내리는 비야 촉촉이 내려다오 <br>그녀들의 마음을 적셔줄께 <br>샤르르르 내려다오 <br>그녀들의 사랑을 가져갈께 <br>샤르르르 내려다오 <br>]]></content><category term="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)" label="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)"/><category term="내리는 비야" label="내리는 비야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레이니맨_Rainy_Man/랩_캐스터/</id><title>레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 랩 캐스터 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:22:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:22:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%88%EB%A7%A8_Rainy_Man/%EB%9E%A9_%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B0/" title="레이니맨_Rainy_Man - 랩 캐스터 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우기 우기 햇살 같은거 <br>넌 필요없어 <br>칠흙같은 어둠속에 <br>피어나는 희망 <br>빗줄기로 가린 <br>거지같은 태양 <br>we there is rain have a nice day <br>우기 우기 햇살 같은거 <br>넌 필요없어 <br>칠흙같은 어둠속에 <br>피어나는 희망 <br>빗줄기로 가린 <br>거지같은 태양 <br>we there is rain have a nice day <br>who i’m a 기상캐스터 워 <br>지금부터 오늘 날씨를 <br>소개할게 어 <br>창밖으로 화려하게 <br>쏟아지는 저 비는 <br>머리맡을 타고 흘러 <br>우리에게 얘길하지 <br>하늘을 봐 구름을 봐 <br>손을 뻗어 가려내봐 <br>손끝으로 가린다고 <br>멈출비가 아냐 <br>적셔오는 니 옷자락의 <br>빗물에도 <br>검게 물든 하늘의 <br>쏟아지는 빗물에도 <br>우기 우기 우기 rainy day <br>우기 우기 우기 rainy day <br>우기 우기 우기 rainy day <br>우기 우기 우기 rainy day <br>비를 즐겨 인생을 즐겨 <br>세상이 젖은 날엔 <br>넌 뭐든 할 수 있어 <br>비 없는 맑은 하늘을 <br>상상 하지마 <br>그냥 이대로 <br>즐기면서 살아 워 <br>새까만 구름이 걷히면 <br>그저 자리를 <br>떠나 내가 날씨를 전해줄 <br>날만 기다려 <br>]]></content><category term="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)" label="레이니맨 (Rainy Man)"/><category term="랩 캐스터" label="랩 캐스터"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_5tion/Break_Away/</id><title>The_5tion - Break Away - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:22:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:22:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_5tion/Break_Away/" title="The_5tion - Break Away - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[BREAK AWAY <br>Feel the 5tion <br>BREAK AWAY <br>밤하늘에 수놓은 별처럼 <br>영원할거라 믿었던 사랑 <br>Tonight we're breaking away <br>아직도 난 믿을수 없어 <br>BETTER DAYS <br>다시 제자리로 cuz you are gone <br>길을 잃어버린 아이처럼 <br>Tonight we're sailing away <br>파도하나 없는 오늘밤 <br>차가운 세상에 지친 날 <br>포근히 안아주었던 너 <br>이제와서 이별이라니 <br>Baby 믿을 수 없어 <br>BREAK AWAY <br>I can't live with or without you <br>잊으려해도 잊지못해 널 <br>BREAK AWAY 사랑밖에 모르니까 <br>hold me hold me 난 어떡하라고 <br>BREAK AWAY <br>I can't live with or without you <br>내 심장이 너무나 아파와 <br>BREAK AWAY 부서지는 추억속에 <br>멀어져가는 너를 보고있어 <br>Don't Break Away 날 놓지말아줘 <br>다시 한번 내 손을 잡아 <br>너 없이 살순 없지 <br>여기서 한발도 뗄수 없지 <br>여전히 난 너 하나뿐인데 <br>널 보내는게 너무 아픈 일이야 <br>고통속 니 흔적을 바라봐 <br>두뺨에 흐르는 눈물이 <br>진심인건지 모르겠어 <br>내 모든건 니꺼였는데 <br>잃어버린 Melody <br>BREAK AWAY <br>I can't live with or without you <br>잊으려해도 잊지못해 널 <br>BREAK AWAY 사랑밖에 모르니까 <br>hold me hold me 난 어떡하라고 <br>BREAK AWAY <br>I can't live with or without you <br>내 심장이 너무나 아파와 <br>BREAK AWAY 부서지는 추억속에 <br>멀어져가는 너를 보고있어 <br>BREAK AWAY BREAK AWAY <br>BREAK AWAY leave me alone <br>BREAK AWAY <br>Baby Feel the 5tion <br>Feel the 5tion Feel the 5-5 <br>BREAK AWAY <br>I can't live with or without you <br>기적 처럼 내게로 왔던 너 <br>BREAK AWAY 사랑밖에 모르는 날 <br>떠나가버림 어떡하라고 <br>BREAK AWAY <br>I can't live with or without you <br>내 심장이 너무나 아파와 <br>BREAK AWAY 내마음은 그대론데 <br>멀어져가는 너를 보고있어 <br>BREAK AWAY <br>]]></content><category term="The 5tion" label="The 5tion"/><category term="Break Away" label="Break Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤드맨/새벽_다섯시/</id><title>헤드맨 - 새벽 다섯시 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:22:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:22:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EB%93%9C%EB%A7%A8/%EC%83%88%EB%B2%BD_%EB%8B%A4%EC%84%AF%EC%8B%9C/" title="헤드맨 - 새벽 다섯시 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새벽 다섯 시가 다 되어서 집에 <br>돌아가는 길에 눈 이와 <br>송이송이 예쁜 저 눈들이 나를 <br>위로 해주려고 하는가 <br>언제부터인지 나도 모르게 <br>눈비 내리면 걱정부터 <br>이 순간을 그냥 즐겨보고 싶네 <br>나는 어느 샌가 아이처럼 <br>내려라 흰 눈아 내려라 <br>온 세상 하얗게 덮어라 <br>내일일은 모두 잊고서 <br>저 눈 속을 한번 뛰어봐 <br>아무런 고민도 하지 마 <br>언제까지 그리 살 거야 <br>아무런 고민도 하지 마 <br>니가 사는 세상 변치 않아 <br>노래 불러봐 크게 외쳐봐 <br>노래 불러봐 크게 외쳐봐 <br>새벽 다섯 시가 다 되어서 집에 <br>돌아가는 길에 눈 이와 <br>이 순간을 그냥 즐겨보고 싶네 <br>나는 어느 샌가 아이처럼 <br>내려라 흰 눈아 내려라 <br>온 세상 하얗게 덮어라 <br>내일 일은 모두 잊고서 <br>저 눈 속을 한번 뛰어봐 <br>아무런 고민도 하지 마 <br>언제까지 그리 살 거야 <br>아무런 고민도 하지 마 <br>니가 사는 세상 변치 않아 <br>노래 불러봐 크게 외쳐봐 <br>노래 불러봐 크게 외쳐봐 <br>노래 불러봐 크게 외쳐봐 <br>노래 불러봐 크게 외쳐봐 <br>노래 불러봐 크게 외쳐봐 <br>노래 불러봐 크게 외쳐봐 <br>]]></content><category term="헤드맨" label="헤드맨"/><category term="새벽 다섯시" label="새벽 다섯시"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SeanK/The_Way_You_Are/</id><title>SeanK - The Way You Are - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:22:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:22:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SeanK/The_Way_You_Are/" title="SeanK - The Way You Are - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘밤은 바쁘지 않아 <br>다른 가사는 나오지 않아 <br>I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU <br>THINK ABOUT ME GIRL <br>니가 날 어떻게 <br>생각하던 상관없어 <br>YEAH I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE <br>YEAH I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE <br>YEAH I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE <br>아직 확실하진않아 <br>YEAH I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE <br>근데 니가 맘에 들어 <br>자꾸 신경쓰여 지나가면 너는 <br>웃음 흘리고가 지나가는 너는 <br>난 그게 무슨 의미인지 모르겠어 <br>사실 알면서 모르는척 하고있어 BABY <br>I DON'T REALLY LIKE <br>HOW YOU DRESS BABY <br>I DON'T REALLY CARE <br>HOW YOU MAKE UP BABY <br>이번엔 기다리고 싶어 BABY <br>너는 다른지 알고싶어 BABY <br>GIRL ARE YOU WITH ME NOW <br>너무 나쁘게만 생각하지는마 <br>BABE ARE YOU WITH ME NOW <br>나도 불안해서 그런거니까 그냥 <br>기다려줘 너가 더 애가 탈때까지 <br>기다려줘 내가 널 더 찾을때까지 <br>기다려줘 너가 더 좋아질때까지 <br>COZ I DON'T KNOW <br>WHAT TO DO RIGHT NOW <br>I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU <br>THINK ABOUT ME GIRL <br>니가 날 어떻게 <br>생각하던 상관없어 <br>YEAH I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE <br>YEAH I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE <br>YEAH I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE <br>아직 확실하진않아 <br>YEAH I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE <br>근데 니가 맘에 들어 <br>시간이 갈수록 더 깊어져만 가지 <br>너에 대한 내 모든 생각들 말이야 <br>오늘은 좀 피곤해서 누워있어 <br>근데 피곤이 풀리지가 않잖아 BABY <br>I THINK I CAN'T MOVE RIGHT NOW BABY <br>I THINK I REALLY NEED YOU <br>RIGHT NOW BABY <br>더이상 기다릴수없어 BABY <br>너는 어떤지 알고싶어 BABY <br>GIRL ARE YOU WITH ME NOW <br>너무 나쁘게만 생각하지는마 <br>BABE ARE YOU WITH ME NOW <br>나도 불안해서 그런거니까 그냥 <br>기다려줘 너가 더 애가 탈때까지 <br>기다려줘 내가 널 더 찾을때까지 <br>기다려줘 너가 더 좋아질때까지 <br>COZ I DON'T KNOW <br>WHAT TO DO RIGHT NOW <br>I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU <br>THINK ABOUT ME GIRL <br>니가 날 어떻게 <br>생각하던 상관없어 <br>YEAH I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE <br>YEAH I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE <br>YEAH I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE <br>아직 확실하진않아 <br>YEAH I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE <br>근데 니가 맘에 들어 <br>I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE GIRL <br>I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE UH <br>I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE <br>I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE BABY <br>I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE <br>I JUST LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE BABE <br>]]></content><category term="Sean.K" label="Sean.K"/><category term="The Way You Are" label="The Way You Are"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SeanK/Be_Alright/</id><title>SeanK - Be Alright - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:22:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:22:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SeanK/Be_Alright/" title="SeanK - Be Alright - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'M GRINDIN' EVERYDAY <br>AND THAT'S WHAT I'MMA DO <br>아직은 너무 일러 잠에 들기엔 <br>난 매일밤 생각해 나의 미래엔 <br>WHO AM I GONNA BE <br>WHO AM I GONNA BE LIKE <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>후회하진 않아 갈 길이 멀기에 <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>돌아보진 않아 <br>매일 아침 나는 눈을 뜨면 <br>머리가 아파와 술 때문은 아니야 <br>BUT 행복한 일이야 아침마다 <br>내 미래를 꿈꾸며 <br>살아가고 있지 너는 어때 <br>MAN WHAT YOU WANNA HEAR <br>WHAT YOU WANNA SAY <br>내가 아직도 이 짓을 하고 있는걸 <br>손가락질 하는거 난 신경안써 <br>언제나 난 똑같이 이렇게 <br>I LOVE WHAT I DO NOW <br>I'M GRINDIN' EVERYDAY <br>AND THAT'S WHAT I'MMA DO <br>아직은 너무 일러 잠에 들기엔 <br>난 매일밤 생각해 나의 미래엔 <br>WHO AM I GONNA BE <br>WHO AM I GONNA BE LIKE <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>후회하진 않아 갈 길이 멀기에 <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>돌아보진 않아 <br>이젠 어느정도 지났지 <br>아무것도 없이 노래를 부른지도 UH <br>솔직히 말해서 <br>지금 돈이 되진않아 <br>평범한건 싫어 <br>I JUST WANNA BE MYSELF <br>MAN WHAT YOU WANNA HEAR <br>WHAT YOU WANNA SAY <br>내가 아직도 이 짓을 하고 있는걸 <br>걔네들 입에 오르고 내리는건 <br>어차피 한순간 뿐이니까 <br>IMA DO WHAT I DO NOW <br>I'M GRINDIN' EVERYDAY <br>AND THAT'S WHAT I'MMA DO <br>아직은 너무 일러 잠에 들기엔 <br>난 매일밤 생각해 나의 미래엔 <br>WHO AM I GONNA BE <br>WHO AM I GONNA BE LIKE <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>후회하진 않아 후회하진 않아 난 <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>돌아보진 않아 <br>난 가끔 머리를 굴려 <br>HOW CAN I BE FAMOUS <br>OR HOW CAN I BE RICH <br>난 자주 고갤저어 <br>사실 그건 그다지 중요하지 않아 <br>COZ I'M <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>후회하진 않아 갈 길이 멀기에 <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>I'M GONN' BE ALRIGHT <br>돌아보진 않아 <br>]]></content><category term="Sean.K" label="Sean.K"/><category term="Be Alright" label="Be Alright"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SeanK/아직_많아_Feat_Jewice_Lee/</id><title>SeanK - 아직 많아 (Feat. Jewice Lee) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:22:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:22:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SeanK/%EC%95%84%EC%A7%81_%EB%A7%8E%EC%95%84_Feat_Jewice_Lee/" title="SeanK - 아직 많아 (Feat. Jewice Lee) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[도시의 밤 공기를 <br>마시고 연기를 뱉고 <br>내 발에는 <br>WHITE VANS ON MY FEET <br>CONCRETE 위를 걸어가 <br>내 옆엔 내 팀 내 친구 <br>AIRJORDAN ON HIS FEET <br>WHITE WHITE <br>MAKES US FEEL FRESH <br>그게 바로 지금이지 <br>그래 바로 지금이지 UH <br>거리에는 온통 <br>향수 냄새가 진동을해 <br>그게 바로 지금이지 <br>그래 바로 지금이지 UH <br>저 여자도 같은 기분일까 <br>I JUST WANNA KNOW <br>WHERE SHE HEADING TO <br>I GO UP FROM THE BOTTOM <br>HERE I GO <br>YOU CAME FOR THE LOTTO <br>I NEED YOU KNOW <br>YOU LOOKIN' <br>FINE YOU KNOW THAT <br>JUST STAY WAY YOU ARE <br>AND BE THE BE THE ONE WHO <br>MAKE MAKE ME FEEL ALRIGHT <br>아직많아 GIRL <br>아직많아 <br>난 아직많아 우린 할게많아 GIRL <br>아직많아 GIRL <br>할게많아 <br>YEAH 우린 날개를 펴고선 춤을춰 <br>GO FLY WITH ME <br>Ima break you down <br>and roll it up <br>smoke you up nd pass <br>you round like a mary go <br>can't be wasting my time <br>on these hoes <br>If you aint gang u aint foe <br>drop a four in a two lieter <br>아직도 멀어 갈 길은 <br>그래도 같이 걷고 싶은건 너야 <br>thousand hoes on my dick <br>내 위에 원하는건 오직 너야 <br>But 아직 많아 <br>할일은 너무나많아 <br>getting this money <br>너무나 바빠 <br>널 위해 조금 더 참아 난 <br>무슨일 있어도 성공할꺼야 <br>I GO UP FROM THE BOTTOM <br>HERE I GO <br>YOU CAME FOR THE LOTTO <br>I NEED YOU KNOW <br>YOU LOOKIN' <br>FINE YOU KNOW THAT <br>JUST STAY WAY YOU ARE <br>AND BE THE BE THE ONE WHO <br>MAKE MAKE ME FEEL ALRIGHT <br>아직많아 GIRL <br>아직많아 <br>난 아직많아 우린 할게많아 GIRL <br>아직많아 GIRL <br>할게많아 <br>YEAH 우린 날개를 펴고선 춤을춰 <br>GO FLY WITH ME <br>ROLL IT UP <br>BEFORE THIS SHIT GET <br>TOO HIGH <br>I'M GONNA GET <br>TOO HIGH <br>YOU'RE GONNA GET <br>TOO HIGH <br>YEAH WE GONNA GET <br>TOO HIGH <br>I GO UP FROM THE BOTTOM <br>HERE I GO <br>YOU CAME FOR THE LOTTO <br>I NEED YOU KNOW <br>YOU LOOKIN' <br>FINE YOU KNOW THAT <br>JUST STAY WAY YOU ARE <br>AND BE THE BE THE ONE WHO <br>MAKE MAKE ME FEEL ALRIGHT <br>아직많아 GIRL <br>아직많아 <br>난 아직많아 우린 할게많아 GIRL <br>아직많아 GIRL <br>할게많아 <br>YEAH 우린 날개를 펴고선 춤을춰 <br>GO FLY WITH ME <br>]]></content><category term="Sean.K" label="Sean.K"/><category term="아직 많아 (Feat. Jewice Lee)" label="아직 많아 (Feat. Jewice Lee)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SeanK/Love_My_City/</id><title>SeanK - Love My City - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:22:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:22:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SeanK/Love_My_City/" title="SeanK - Love My City - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[BRIGHT LIGHT JUST DYIN' <br>MA HAIR BRIGHT <br>차를타고 올랐지 도로위 내 <br>신발은 YEAH <br>BRIGHT WHITE <br>IT'S ON THE PEDAL TO THE METAL <br>세게밟아 <br>부드럽게 미끄러져 <br>손을 스치는 바람처럼 <br>매끄럽게 미끄러져 <br>옆에 스쳐가는 이 여자들처럼 <br>WHY YOU WANNA LEAVE HERE <br>WHY DON'T YOU WANNA LIVE HERE <br>조금은 복잡한 도시야 <br>WHY YOU WANNA LEAVE HERE <br>WHY DON'T YOU WANNA LIVE HERE <br>여긴 조금 시끄러 <br>여긴 너와 내 젊음의 CITY <br>그 젊음에 술을 따랐다면 <br>잔을비워 아직 해가 뜨려면 <br>한참 멀었어 잔을 마져비워 <br>이 도신 가득차있어 기회로 <br>니가 뭘하던 <br>THEY DON'T GIVE <br>A DAMN' ABOUT YOU <br>THAT'S WHY I LOVE MY CITY <br>I LOVE MY CITY <br>THAT'S WHY I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE <br>I LOVE <br>I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE <br>I LOVE <br>OH FUCK EM BITCHES <br>SO HARD LIKE <br>I HAVE NEVER DONE IT BEFORE <br>NEVER DONE IT BEFORE <br>조금씩 술기운이 오르지 <br>밤이되면 나는 좀 바뻐 <br>이해해주길 바래 <br>친구들이 작별인사를 건네네 <br>내가 잠시 팔짱을 풀어도 <br>I'M NOT BEING SASSY BABE <br>YOU STILL POURIN' UP THOUGH <br>이 도신 가득차있어 기회로 <br>니가 뭘하던 <br>THEY DON'T GIVE <br>A DAMN' ABOUT YOU <br>THAT'S WHY I LOVE MY CITY <br>I LOVE MY CITY <br>THAT'S WHY I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE <br>I LOVE <br>I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE MY CITY <br>YEAH I LOVE <br>I LOVE <br>]]></content><category term="Sean.K" label="Sean.K"/><category term="Love My City" label="Love My City"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍은미/미움안고_살기엔/</id><title>홍은미 - 미움안고 살기엔 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:23:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:23:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%9D%80%EB%AF%B8/%EB%AF%B8%EC%9B%80%EC%95%88%EA%B3%A0_%EC%82%B4%EA%B8%B0%EC%97%94/" title="홍은미 - 미움안고 살기엔 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[미움을 안고 살기엔 <br>인생이 너무 짧아요 <br>백년을 간대도 <br>사랑을 하기엔 <br>너무나 짧아요 <br>눈감고 귀를 막고 <br>돌아누워도 <br>그리운 모습하나 <br>오늘도 그날처럼 <br>비를 맞으며 <br>슬픔에 젖어있어요 <br>그대를 잊고 살기엔 <br>사랑이 너무 깊어요 <br>하루를 살아도 <br>당신과 함께면 <br>행복해 질 수 있죠 <br>눈감고 귀를 막고 <br>돌아누워도 <br>그리운 모습하나 <br>오늘도 그날처럼 <br>비를 맞으며 <br>슬픔에 젖어있어요 <br>그대를 잊고 살기엔 <br>사랑이 너무 깊어요 <br>하루를 살아도 <br>당신과 함께면 <br>행복해 질 수 있죠 <br>행복해 질 수 있죠 <br>]]></content><category term="홍은미" label="홍은미"/><category term="미움안고 살기엔" label="미움안고 살기엔"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍은미/최고의_인생/</id><title>홍은미 - 최고의 인생 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:23:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:23:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%9D%80%EB%AF%B8/%EC%B5%9C%EA%B3%A0%EC%9D%98_%EC%9D%B8%EC%83%9D/" title="홍은미 - 최고의 인생 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[인생은 사랑이에요 <br>만남은 인연입니다 <br>이렇게 멋진 당신만나 <br>한평생을 기약해요 <br>살다보면 좋은세상 <br>웃으면서 살면되지 <br>사랑주고 안아주며 <br>후회없이 살아가요 <br>행복이 뭐 별거있더냐 <br>건강하면 최고의 인생 <br>세상은 오늘이에요 <br>만남은 기쁨입니다 <br>이렇게 멋진 당신만나 <br>한평생을 기약해요 <br>살다보면 좋은세상 <br>웃으면서 살면되지 <br>사랑주고 안아주며 <br>후회없이 살아가요 <br>행복이 뭐 별거있더냐 <br>건강하면 최고의 인생 <br>살다보면 좋은세상 <br>웃으면서 살면되지 <br>사랑주고 안아주며 <br>후회없이 살아가요 <br>행복이 뭐 별거있더냐 <br>건강하면 최고의 인생 <br>]]></content><category term="홍은미" label="홍은미"/><category term="최고의 인생" label="최고의 인생"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍은미/시작이_반/</id><title>홍은미 - 시작이 반 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:23:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:23:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%9D%80%EB%AF%B8/%EC%8B%9C%EC%9E%91%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B0%98/" title="홍은미 - 시작이 반 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[시작이 반이에요 <br>반입니다 <br>우리함께 뛰어 봐요 <br>나이는 숫자일 뿐 <br>상관 없어요 <br>다시 한번 시작 합시다 <br>백세넘게 살거라면 <br>지금도 늦진않았어 <br>세상사 인생사 <br>그 모든 것이 <br>마음먹기 달렸더라 <br>시작이 반이에요 <br>반입니다 <br>우리함께 뛰어 봐요 <br>나이는 숫자일 뿐 <br>상관 없어요 <br>다시 한번 시작 합시다 <br>백세넘게 살거라면 <br>아직도 늦진않았어 <br>세상사 인생사 <br>그 모든 것이 <br>생각하기 달렸더라 <br>백세넘게 살거라면 <br>지금도 늦진않았어 <br>세상사 인생사 <br>그 모든 것이 <br>마음먹기 달렸더라 <br>]]></content><category term="홍은미" label="홍은미"/><category term="시작이 반" label="시작이 반"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SCARYP/BLEQ_Feat_크림빌라/</id><title>SCARYP - B.L.E.Q (Feat. 크림빌라) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:23:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:23:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SCARYP/BLEQ_Feat_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%BC%EB%B9%8C%EB%9D%BC/" title="SCARYP - B.L.E.Q (Feat. 크림빌라) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Get your funky bitches <br>when I signed my deal <br>그날 밤 샜어 <br>내가 분출하는 <br>영감이 쌓인 만큼 <br>내 우상과의 대면 <br>이게 뭔 말인지 모르겠지 <br>난 맹독을 뱉었지 <br>black mamba <br>팔자를 그려낸 뒤에 <br>똬릴틀어 새긴 24/7 yak <br>yellow 피부 톤에 <br>황금기를 두번 <br>재현 하고 있는 팀 <br>존나 무시받고 냈던 앨범 <br>작년 한국 힙합 2top <br>명반 대열 fucked up <br>올해도 FURY 내고 <br>좆문가들 힙찔이 <br>평론가들 사일 rambo <br>매일 플로우 해 <br>꼭 왜 할 말이 많은 <br>L 다음 마딜 채워 <br>그래 매일 플로우를 <br>뱉어 내가 뱉어낸 <br>단어가 만든 <br>Gotham City 배트맨 <br>racks on racks 내 속엔 <br>또 다른 내가 많아 <br>의사를 불러줘 빨리 <br>aftermath yah <br>새까만 트랙 위 <br>검은 랩 머금은 채 <br>우리가 음지를 걸을때 <br>너넨 입 다물어 <br>bang damn 손을 떼 <br>you so wack <br>We so black <br>B.L.E.Q on this track <br>And we make <br>that bitch be going bad <br>We go H.A.M <br>We so kray <br>Racks on Racks <br>on racks <br>stack yo paypuh <br>cream villa 등장과 함께 <br>이 동넨 다 black-out <br>따가운 시선이 느껴져 <br>그럴수 밖에 왜일까 <br>존나게 dope한 새끼들이 <br>하나도 아닌 여덟 <br>이 구역은 이미 <br>우리가 먹은듯하지 <br>좆밥 새끼들의 <br>아우성이 난 느껴져 <br>I got skill 널 죽이는 <br>기술이 하루가 다르게 늘어 <br>이 정도면 내 직업이 <br>살인청부업 이라고 해도 <br>괜찮을 것같네 방금 또 <br>kill kill kill kill i’m sorry <br>no 우린 이 비트도 <br>죽였는데 어떻할래 <br>여긴 이미 흥건해진 <br>피로 까맣게 물들었네 <br>그 다음은 얘가 죽이지 E <br>but I done killed it <br>I' ain't into kill these rappers <br>But I ate them <br>단물을 빨아먹고 <br>몇번 씹어대 <br>걔네가 할 줄 아는 건 <br>내가 다 할 수 있는 것 <br>모든 색깔을 품고 있어 <br>Im so black <br>너넨 그냥 꿈에서 <br>나올때 야 여태 <br>방송에서 너무 많은 꿈들을 <br>심어줬네 <br>과연 니가 여기 <br>8년 뒤에 남을지 <br>모르겠지만 <br>그 때 넌 날 쳐다도 못봐 bitch <br>you so wack <br>We so black <br>B.L.E.Q on this track <br>And we make <br>that bitch be going bad <br>We go H.A.M <br>We so kray <br>Racks on Racks <br>on racks <br>stack yo paypuh <br>so 동네 양아치들 침뱉듯이 <br>I’m easily spitting ill flow <br>난 여유가 있어 전보다 <br>게다가 돈도 많이 벌지 <br>내 직업이 두갠게 <br>이 겜에서 핸디캡이 <br>될거라고 생각하는 걔네 <br>조던 보다 나의 로퍼가 <br>더 높이 뛰어오르게 만드는데 <br>어떻게 이게 핸디캡이라 <br>할 수 있냐 어떻게 어떻게 <br>백수가 되는 <br>래퍼들에게 나는 귀감 <br>이 되고 철되면 <br>꼬이는 여름 모기같은 <br>놈들은 여전히 <br>가사쓸 때 도움돼 <br>너무 좋은 먹잇감 <br>So Fuck all that shit 썩네 귀가 <br>얼른 랩접고 다 귀가 <br>조치 해야 할 필요 있어 <br>Q 할말있으면 해 <br>난 이만 <br>QUAIMO GOT A ENEMIES <br>생각은 좀 괴롭지 <br>아니 이건 뻥이고 <br>오히려 걔내들에게는 <br>필요하지 게보린 <br>쉽게 말해 짧아 <br>생각이 허나 너네 존재 <br>MY FAVORITES <br>다 하나같이 죄다 <br>멍청하지 정말 고마워 <br>MY 개복치`S <br>you so wack <br>We so black <br>B.L.E.Q on this track <br>And we make <br>that bitch be going bad <br>We go H.A.M <br>We so kray <br>Racks on Racks <br>on racks <br>stack yo paypuh <br>B.L.E.Q. Tiz bred <br>scary dope <br>Get your issue <br>funky bitches 우리처럼 <br>cream villa 4mc <br>1dj 2pd artworker 빵빵 <br>뭘하든 본토삘 <br>색깔은 존나 검정 yak <br>QUAIMO는 원해 돈과 <br>인기 명예 또 인프라 <br>내 소중한 친구들과 <br>MY TEAM CREAM VILLA <br>8햄 노래처럼 해낼꺼야 <br>믿고 기다려 조만간 <br>내 입에 달고살 <br>말버릇이 또 생기겠지 <br>ME GUSTA <br>ME GUSTA <br>그때는 상황발생 <br>모두 모두 비상 <br>값비싼 척 했던 음치 <br>랩퍼들 모아놓고 귀싸 <br>대기 맞을 준비해 <br>물론 난 뒤에서 <br>또 구경해 <br>B형 보여줘요 <br>형의 날렵한 턱선 같은 랩 <br>you know what i mean <br>난 알아 임마 <br>무슨 말인지를 <br>내 치켜세운 턱 <br>기깔 나게 뱉은 verse와 <br>긴밤 새워 화류계로 <br>치면 딱 30만원 <br>이제 내 가치는 내가 올려 <br>돈과 차트보다 <br>내 음악에 꼴려 <br>hold up 이제 날 <br>원하는 곳이 많아 <br>날 보며 돈과 <br>가랭이가 벌려지네 <br>]]></content><category term="SCARY`P" label="SCARY`P"/><category term="B.L.E.Q (Feat. 크림빌라)" label="B.L.E.Q (Feat. 크림빌라)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주연/내_세상이다/</id><title>김주연 - 내 세상이다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:23:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:23:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%EC%97%B0/%EB%82%B4_%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%A4/" title="김주연 - 내 세상이다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(지구가 좁으면 우주로) <br>(우주가 좁으면 미지로) <br>(가자 내 세상이다) <br>1절 <br>열려라 열려라 <br>내 세상아 열려라 <br>나도 한번 큰소리 쳐보자 <br>날아라 날아라 나의 인생아 <br>하늘 높은 곳까지 <br>사랑아 사랑아 내 사랑아 오너라 <br>당신이 내 세상이다 <br>불타는 태양은 내 가슴속의 정열 <br>내일은 전부 내꺼다 <br>지구가 좁으면 우주로 <br>우주가 좁으면 미지로 <br>가자 가자 가자 난 할수있다 <br>내 세상 내 인생이다 <br>내 세상 내 인생이다 <br>1.2절 가사]]></content><category term="김주연" label="김주연"/><category term="내 세상이다" label="내 세상이다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주연/운명_같은_사랑/</id><title>김주연 - 운명 같은 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:24:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:24:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%EC%97%B0/%EC%9A%B4%EB%AA%85_%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="김주연 - 운명 같은 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1절 <br>저 흘러가는 얄미운 세월 <br>그 누구가 잡을 수 있나 <br>바람같은 내 사랑을 <br>어느 누가 막을 수 있나 <br>당신 당슨은 영원한 내 사랑 <br>사랑한다고 말해주세요 <br>하늘 땅도 허락한 <br>운명같은 우리의 사랑 <br>인연의 끈을 놓지 마세요 <br>당신 곁엔 내가 있어요 <br>당신 곁은 내가 있어요 <br>1.2절 가사]]></content><category term="김주연" label="김주연"/><category term="운명 같은 사랑" label="운명 같은 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Raela_라엘라/쉬어/</id><title>Raela_라엘라 - 쉬어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:24:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:24:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Raela_%EB%9D%BC%EC%97%98%EB%9D%BC/%EC%89%AC%EC%96%B4/" title="Raela_라엘라 - 쉬어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생각이 너무 많아 <br>보내는 시간이 많아 <br>다 내려놓고 쉬어 <br>just let's it go <br>괜찮아 눈감아 <br>걱정이 너무 많아 <br>다 잘 될 거야 걱정 마 <br>다 내려놓고 쉬어 <br>just let's it go <br>괜찮아 눈감아 <br>잠잔거 같지 않아 <br>난 8시간 자야 괜찮아 <br>잠긴 목소리로 중얼중얼 <br>시간을 세다가 <br>밤새 고민한 산적해 <br>있는 걱정에도 <br>내 맘 모르는 햇살이 <br>내 얼굴에 번졌네 <br>매일 아침 씻어도 <br>맘은 씻겨지지 않아 <br>주변 사람에게 받은 <br>상처가 너무 많아 <br>인생 드라마 같지 <br>뭐 어쩌겠어 <br>맘 다잡지 뭐 <br>스트레스 풀기 위해 <br>뭔갈 사는 것도 사치지 뭐 <br>막힌 도로 위에 <br>골목길이 간절해 <br>내 앞날도 지름길이 간절해 <br>단순히 돈 버는 거 말고 <br>뭐라도 되고 싶어 <br>얼른 뭐든 직장이 아닌 <br>직업을 갖고 싶거든 <br>아침이면 밝아야 할 텐데 <br>내 맘은 밝지 않아 맑지 않아 <br>탁한 서울의 열기에 <br>오래 익어 냄새나 쉬었어 <br>쉬엄쉬엄 하고 <br>저녁에 쉬어야겠어 <br>That's all <br>생각이 너무 많아 <br>보내는 시간이 많아 <br>다 내려놓고 쉬어 <br>just let's it go <br>괜찮아 눈감아 <br>걱정이 너무 많아 <br>다 잘 될 거야 걱정 마 <br>다 내려놓고 쉬어 <br>just let's it go <br>괜찮아 눈감아 <br>오늘도 나 나름 <br>계획한 대로 지냈지 <br>헌데 요즘 그게 뜻대로 <br>되지 않는 시대지 <br>그냥 뭔가 하지 않으면 <br>안될꺼 같아서 <br>빈 깡통마냥 동기 없이 <br>괜히 숨 가빠 바빴어 <br>쉴 때는 치킨 콜라 <br>전화시킨 후에 놀라 <br>통장에 잔고가 <br>왜 딱 만원뿐일까 <br>돈이 줄줄새 짜증 나 <br>다 우울해 <br>다 집어치고 피곤하니 <br>침대에나 누울래 <br>오늘 아침 일찍 <br>일어났는데 설치는 밤 <br>괜히 좋지 않은 <br>생각이 번지기만 <br>그때 왜 그랬나 이불 킥 <br>근데 결론은 맘을 비우기 <br>좀 더 성숙하자는 걸로 <br>맘이 기울지 <br>꼭 자려 할 때 <br>생각이 많아지더라 <br>꼬리에 꼬리를 무는 <br>생각들 지겨워 싫어 다 <br>잠자고 싶어 맘이 <br>잔잔하고 싶어 <br>쉬엄쉬엄 하고 <br>잠 좀 자야겠어 <br>That's all <br>애쓰지마 흘러가는 대로 <br>서두르지 마 시간은 충분해 <br>신경 쓰지 마 절대 <br>누군가의 평가가 아냐 <br>그냥 시간에 <br>맡기면 돼 안기면 돼 <br>넌 여전히 <br>잘해왔단 걸 기억해 <br>다 내려놓고 잠들면 돼 <br>생각이 너무 많아 <br>보내는 시간이 많아 <br>다 내려놓고 쉬어 <br>just let's it go <br>괜찮아 눈감아 <br>걱정이 너무 많아 <br>다 잘 될 거야 걱정 마 <br>다 내려놓고 쉬어 <br>just let's it go <br>괜찮아 눈감아 <br>]]></content><category term="Raela (라엘라)" label="Raela (라엘라)"/><category term="쉬어" label="쉬어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CDC/Bitter_Sweet_Feat_김휘구/</id><title>CDC - Bitter Sweet (Feat. 김휘구) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:24:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:24:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CDC/Bitter_Sweet_Feat_%EA%B9%80%ED%9C%98%EA%B5%AC/" title="CDC - Bitter Sweet (Feat. 김휘구) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새벽은 어디에 있을까 <br>그런 새벽 말고 <br>편하게 잠들 수 있는 밤 <br>달면서도 쓰지 이 순간 <br>i feel good <br>i feel good <br>bitter sweet my pain <br>it's a ordinary day <br>나는 왜 <br>노예로 태어났을까 <br>하는 질문에 아무도 <br>대답을 해주지 않았어 <br>엄마는 병원에 <br>아빠는 없었고 <br>형은 삐뚤어졌고 나도 <br>그 뒤를 따라갔던 게 <br>너에겐 자연스러워 <br>당연한 일이지 <br>당연한 일이야 <br>돌이켜서 보면 말야 <br>노예라는 말이 적당해 <br>어울려 놀던 친구들도 <br>자기는 몰랐지만 <br>부모님 직업을 못 적게 <br>한 경험을 털어놔 <br>빚을 갚지 못해 <br>한쪽으로 찌그러진 눈 <br>혹은 말더듬이 <br>구걸하던 술주정뱅이 <br>이웃 아저씨들은 <br>전부 다 정이 많은 줄 <br>알았지 어린 나에게 <br>말을 걸던 그 이유 <br>대화상대가 없었지 <br>대화상대가 없었어 <br>양아치들이 피해 <br>다니던 공사장 일꾼 <br>창녀들을 실제로 <br>봤다고 자랑한 친구들 <br>어른이 돼보니 <br>내 나이 또래나 이모 <br>벌려서 번 돈으로 <br>먹여 살렸대 식구를 <br>요즘엔 등록금을 <br>벌려고 다릴 벌리고 <br>그 등록금을 받는 <br>학교 이사가 와서는 <br>더러운 이빨로 <br>여물은 과일을 베물어 <br>난 왜 여전히 노예야 <br>넌 왜 여전히 노예야 <br>전액 장학을 받아도 <br>난 왜 여전히 노예야 uh <br>청춘이란 단어로 <br>그냥 날 불러 부럽대 <br>막 주먹질로부터 <br>해방된 후에야 <br>make a withdrawal <br>make a withdrawal <br>넌 왜 부자의 탈을 써 <br>사진 속에서 <br>money with the savage me <br>한 끼 식사를 위해서 <br>남의 걸 쌔비지 <br>부모님의 두 눈 후비지 <br>make a withdrawal <br>make a withdrawal <br>난 왜 노예로 태어났지 <br>하는 질문에 아무도 <br>대답해주지 않아 <br>엄만 병원에 <br>아빠는 계시지 않아 <br>삐뚤어진 방식을 따라 <br>친구라고 칭하던 <br>한 명이 내게 말했어 <br>소설책처럼 보였지 <br>내가 살아있다는 게 <br>yo 힙합 해 <br>yo shimmy twice <br>내가 에미넴 영화를 보는데 <br>마치 니 얘기 같았어 <br>선생님에게 교재를 얻어 <br>쓰는 걸 자랑해 <br>사춘기가 지나곤 <br>견본품 표시를 까맣게 <br>색칠하거나 표지를 <br>찢어버렸지만 <br>그 말이 연하게 <br>쓰여진 속지는 <br>피부를 묘하게 닮았네 <br>새벽은 어디에 있을까 <br>그런 새벽 말고 <br>편하게 잠들 수 있는 밤 <br>달면서도 쓰지 이 순간 <br>i feel good <br>i feel good <br>bitter sweet my pain <br>it's a ordinary day <br>이젠 잘 힘들단 말을 안하지 <br>예전보단 나아졌어 <br>해가 쬔 바깥은 <br>달콤하면서도 써 <br>어느 순간 아름다워 <br>신께 만약 <br>전화해 <br>삶이 좋냐고 물어봐 <br>신이 아마 <br>대답해 <br>삶이 좋냐 되묻지 <br>어 좀 더 똑바로 보길 <br>현실을 직시해 <br>매순간을 넘겨서 <br>내 주머니 속에는 <br>끝이 보여 더 달콤한 <br>안락함이 들었지 <br>어 좀 더 똑바로 보길 <br>현실을 직시해 <br>매순간을 넘겨서 <br>현실에 물이 들어 <br>차갑게 식은 <br>심장에도 피가 흘러 <br>]]></content><category term="CDC" label="CDC"/><category term="Bitter Sweet (Feat. 김휘구)" label="Bitter Sweet (Feat. 김휘구)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공기남/그대의_편이_돼_줄게_Inst/</id><title>공기남 - 그대의 편이 돼 줄게 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:25:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:25:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%EA%B8%B0%EB%82%A8/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EC%9D%98_%ED%8E%B8%EC%9D%B4_%EB%8F%BC_%EC%A4%84%EA%B2%8C_Inst/" title="공기남 - 그대의 편이 돼 줄게 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘따라 그대의 <br>얼굴엔 먹구름이 <br>무슨 일 있나요 <br>하늘도 참 맑은데 <br>뺨을 스치는 공기 <br>다 너무 좋은데 <br>그 누구도 내 그대를 <br>아프게 할 순 없어 <br>나는 못 봐요 <br>꼭 내게 말해주세요 <br>나 그대의 편이 돼줄게 <br>내가 그댈 안아줄게요 <br>한걸음 더 다가갈게요 <br>아프지 않게 <br>손 잡아줄게요 <br>그대 <br>그대 눈빛을 보면 <br>달의 뒷면을 <br>보는 것만 같아서 <br>내가 더 불안해요 <br>그대의 그늘이 돼줄게 <br>내가 그댈 안아줄게요 <br>한걸음 더 다가갈게요 <br>아프지 않게 <br>손 잡아줄게요 <br>그대 <br>내가 그댈 사랑할게요 <br>항상 곁에 있을 거예요 <br>아프지 마요 <br>우리 행복해봐요 <br>그대 <br>]]></content><category term="공기남" label="공기남"/><category term="그대의 편이 돼 줄게 (Inst.)" label="그대의 편이 돼 줄게 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공기남/그대의_편이_돼_줄게_Feat_굿나잇스탠드/</id><title>공기남 - 그대의 편이 돼 줄게 (Feat. 굿나잇스탠드) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:25:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:25:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%EA%B8%B0%EB%82%A8/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EC%9D%98_%ED%8E%B8%EC%9D%B4_%EB%8F%BC_%EC%A4%84%EA%B2%8C_Feat_%EA%B5%BF%EB%82%98%EC%9E%87%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%A0%EB%93%9C/" title="공기남 - 그대의 편이 돼 줄게 (Feat. 굿나잇스탠드) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘따라 그대의 <br>얼굴엔 먹구름이 <br>무슨 일 있나요 <br>하늘도 참 맑은데 <br>뺨을 스치는 공기 <br>다 너무 좋은데 <br>그 누구도 내 그대를 <br>아프게 할 순 없어 <br>나는 못 봐요 <br>꼭 내게 말해주세요 <br>나 그대의 편이 돼줄게 <br>내가 그댈 안아줄게요 <br>한걸음 더 다가갈게요 <br>아프지 않게 <br>손 잡아줄게요 <br>그대 <br>그대 눈빛을 보면 <br>달의 뒷면을 <br>보는 것만 같아서 <br>내가 더 불안해요 <br>그대의 그늘이 돼줄게 <br>내가 그댈 안아줄게요 <br>한걸음 더 다가갈게요 <br>아프지 않게 <br>손 잡아줄게요 <br>그대 <br>내가 그댈 사랑할게요 <br>항상 곁에 있을 거예요 <br>아프지 마요 <br>우리 행복해봐요 <br>그대 <br>]]></content><category term="공기남" label="공기남"/><category term="그대의 편이 돼 줄게 (Feat. 굿나잇스탠드)" label="그대의 편이 돼 줄게 (Feat. 굿나잇스탠드)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강덕구/백년_고개/</id><title>강덕구 - 백년 고개 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:27:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:27:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EB%8D%95%EA%B5%AC/%EB%B0%B1%EB%85%84_%EA%B3%A0%EA%B0%9C/" title="강덕구 - 백년 고개 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1절 <br>길다면 길고 짧다는 짧은 <br>나그네 인생길에 <br>오손도손 정든 사람 끼리끼리 <br>웃음 꽃 나눠주고 살자 <br>힘겨울 때나 외로울 때면 <br>연인처럼 친구처럼 <br>거침없이 사랑하며 다정하게 손을 자고 <br>백년고개 같이 넘자 <br>1.2절 가사]]></content><category term="강덕구" label="강덕구"/><category term="백년 고개" label="백년 고개"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강덕구/짜증나게_하지마/</id><title>강덕구 - 짜증나게 하지마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:27:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:27:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EB%8D%95%EA%B5%AC/%EC%A7%9C%EC%A6%9D%EB%82%98%EA%B2%8C_%ED%95%98%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88/" title="강덕구 - 짜증나게 하지마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1절 <br>짜증나게 하지마 <br>우리 이렇게 그냥 사랑해 <br>당신이 사나이 이 가슴을 이해해줘 <br>지난 세월은 청산에 묻었고 <br>흘러간 사랑은 창공에 날렸어 <br>지금은 당신만이 소중해 꼬치꼬치 따지지마 <br>어렵게 뒤늦게 만난 당신의 사랑 <br>다시 잃어버릴 수는 없잖아 <br>자꾸자꾸 캐묻지마 짜증나게 하지마 (한번더)]]></content><category term="강덕구" label="강덕구"/><category term="짜증나게 하지마" label="짜증나게 하지마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강덕구/청춘_고백/</id><title>강덕구 - 청춘 고백 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:27:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:27:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EB%8D%95%EA%B5%AC/%EC%B2%AD%EC%B6%98_%EA%B3%A0%EB%B0%B1/" title="강덕구 - 청춘 고백 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1절 <br>인생이 뭐 별거이더냐 <br>사랑이 별거이더냐 <br>쓰러지고 넘어져도 <br>웃으며 나가보련다 <br>한 잔술에 털어버리고 <br>두 주먹을 움켜지고 <br>사랑도 명예도 <br>다 가지겠다 <br>사나이 가는 길에 <br>인생이란게 별거이더냐 <br>후렴: <br>한 잔술에 털어버리고 <br>두 주먹을 움켜지고 <br>사랑도 명예도 <br>다 가지겠다 <br>사나이 가는 길에 <br>인생이란게 별거이더냐(한번더)]]></content><category term="강덕구" label="강덕구"/><category term="청춘 고백" label="청춘 고백"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radiohead/The_Butcher/</id><title>Radiohead - The Butcher - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:28:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:28:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radiohead/The_Butcher/" title="Radiohead - The Butcher - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Beauty will destroy your mind <br>Spare the gory details <br>Give them gift wrapped for the man with everything <br>Though I lived a lonely life <br>I was confused <br>A butcher <br>I feel nothing <br><br>As it courses up my arms in position of the worms <br>Up, up through my heart and to my brain <br><br>I'm a big slab of basic combination cut out chopped liver on the block <br>My heart's still pumping <br>My heart's still pumping <br><br>He's a warrior <br>A warrior <br>Here's a little bitch coming outta him <br>He's a warrior <br>A warrior <br>Here's a little bitch coming outta him <br>Coming outta him]]></content><category term="Radiohead" label="Radiohead"/><category term="The Butcher" label="The Butcher"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radiohead/Supercollider/</id><title>Radiohead - Supercollider - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:28:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:28:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radiohead/Supercollider/" title="Radiohead - Supercollider - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Super collider <br>Dust in a moment <br>Particles scatter <br>Parting from the soup <br><br>Swimming upstream <br>Before the heavens crack open <br>Thin pixelations <br>Coming out from the dust <br><br>In a blue light <br>In a green light <br>In a half light <br>In a work light <br><br>In a B spin <br>Flip flopping <br>In a pulse wave <br>Outstepping <br><br>To put the shadows back into <br>The boxes <br><br>I am open <br>I am welcome <br>For a fraction <br>Of a second <br><br>I have jettisoned my illusions <br>I have dislodged my depressions <br><br>I put the shadows back into <br>The boxes]]></content><category term="Radiohead" label="Radiohead"/><category term="Supercollider" label="Supercollider"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laurel/Too_Far/</id><title>Laurel - Too Far - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:29:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:29:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laurel/Too_Far/" title="Laurel - Too Far - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Clench teeth, stare at the ceiling <br>I know how you feeling, baby it's alright <br>I don't want you just for the season, but you left for a reason <br>I couldn't see the end in sight <br><br>All star, maybe when we're older <br>We can try this over <br>Get a place with a view <br>Or maybe we'll just get lazy <br>Tell me, bitch you're just crazy <br>Wish I never knew you <br><br>We've taken it too far <br>Getting more than I paid for <br>But when you talk like that, it's all I can believe <br>And then I'm on my back <br>He says Shut up and don't speak to me <br>You've taken it too far <br><br>Been working you like a day job <br>But it's too much for the payroll, if I'm being real <br>He thinks I'm sweet like sugar <br>But I'm sick when we gonna call it quits <br>Maybe that's how I feel now <br><br>All star, maybe when we're older <br>We can try this over <br>Get a place with a view <br>Grow me up like a flower <br>In the city summer <br>So I can bloom with you <br><br>We've taken it too far <br>Getting more than I paid for <br>But when you talk like that, it's all I can believe <br>And then I'm on my back <br>He says Shut up and don't speak to me <br>You've taken it too far]]></content><category term="Laurel" label="Laurel"/><category term="Too Far" label="Too Far"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laurel/Hurricane/</id><title>Laurel - Hurricane - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:29:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:29:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laurel/Hurricane/" title="Laurel - Hurricane - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I said, baby, bring the weather with you, rage it <br>Driving down the south coast after dark <br>And I wonder if I'll ever see you again <br>You're painted in the pictures in my heart <br>But I try to play it cool cause we just got started <br>I'm only 22 and you're kinda loose but <br>I like how you are <br><br>Ay, ay he's a hurricane <br>I'm riding on the wind again <br>He's mine and I'm not worried, when <br>He's not around <br>Right back he comes <br>He comes back <br><br>I wait up to see you <br>And every time I dream I get to meet you again <br>It's like 24 7, honey love <br>There's a certain darkness to your soul <br>I really want to make you feel at home <br>Living in the city with you, baby <br>Saying life's tough <br><br>Wake me up with your rising sun <br><br>Ay, ay he's a hurricane <br>I'm riding on the wind again <br>He's mine and I'm not worried, when <br>He's not around <br>Right back he comes <br>He comes back <br><br>Ay, ay he's a hurricane <br>I'm riding on the wind again <br>He's mine and I'm not worried, when <br>He's not around <br>Right back he comes <br>He comes back]]></content><category term="Laurel" label="Laurel"/><category term="Hurricane" label="Hurricane"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laurel/Maybe_Baby/</id><title>Laurel - Maybe Baby - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:29:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:29:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laurel/Maybe_Baby/" title="Laurel - Maybe Baby - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't know what I feel about you <br>Wondering if I can be true <br>But don't what I'd be without you, babe <br>Moving through this sunny weather <br>Found it nice to be together <br>But I don't know about forever <br>Is that ok <br><br>So you seen me coming <br>And I've seen you 'round the neighbourhood <br>Ay ride it till he dies and <br>Here and now living <br>Would you be a forgiving if <br>I, I let you down, I <br>I let you down <br><br>Life moves fast, another dawn <br>And oh my god, he's like <br>I'm so in love with you <br>And everything's a little much <br>Found myself inside his arms <br>But maybe baby I'm just lost like you <br><br>Staying up to see the weekends <br>Tried dying just to know the feeling <br>But you just really care about me, hey <br>I guess we are pretty normal <br>Let's play it like a house and home <br>But I don't know if I can handle this <br><br>Walking in the park with you <br>I'm on the radio <br>It's like living a real life <br>Like play it nice for me <br>Sit in and watch the TV <br>But this life gon' let me down <br>And you just gon' let me down <br><br>Life moves fast, another dawn <br>And oh my god, he's like <br>I'm so in love with you <br>And everything's a little much <br>Found myself inside his arms <br>But maybe baby I'm just lost like you <br>But maybe baby I'm just lost like you <br><br>Your love enough, it feeds the soul <br>It's all you got to be make me whole <br>I'm living suburbs down and going crazy like <br>It's all got hazy and a psychedelica <br><br>Life moves fast, another dawn <br>And oh my god, he's like <br>I'm so in love with you <br>And everything's a little much <br>Found myself inside his arms <br>But maybe baby I'm just lost like you]]></content><category term="Laurel" label="Laurel"/><category term="Maybe Baby" label="Maybe Baby"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/큰숲크리스천스쿨/더_넓은_세상을_품게/</id><title>큰숲크리스천스쿨 - 더 넓은 세상을 품게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:31:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:31:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%81%B0%EC%88%B2%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%A4%EC%B2%9C%EC%8A%A4%EC%BF%A8/%EB%8D%94_%EB%84%93%EC%9D%80_%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81%EC%9D%84_%ED%92%88%EA%B2%8C/" title="큰숲크리스천스쿨 - 더 넓은 세상을 품게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[빛이 안 보인다고 실망하진마 <br>네가 세상의 빛이 돼줄테니까 <br>막막하다고 쉽게 포기하진마 <br>더 나은 내일이 널 보고있으니 <br>나는 장현아지 그건 당연하지 <br>내겐 훈녀생정 따윈 필요없지 <br>겁먹지 않아 두려워하지 않아 <br>날개를 펴고 당당하게 <br>하늘을 날아 <br>꿈을 위해서 어디로 가야할지 <br>알려주는 표지판 같은 건 없어 <br>하지만 괜찮아 걱정하지는마 <br>혼자가 아니야 우리가 있잖아 <br>넘어져 있어도 다시 다시 <br>저기 보이는 저 벽을 뚫어 <br>저 하늘 저 새처럼 날아올라 <br>더 넓은 세상을 품게 <br>이 세상은 끝이 없는 어둠 <br>각각의 빛들이 밝혀가는 중 <br>지금은 그 빛들이 <br>눈에 띄지 않을 뿐 <br>시간이 지나면 곧 보일 빛들 <br>이젠 그 빛들이 <br>당연하다고 여길 때쯤이면 <br>누군가는 또 빛을 찾아서 <br>한참 헤매일거고 <br>우리가 그 빛이 되어주는 <br>순환의 구조 <br>꿈을 위해서 어디로 가야할지 <br>알려주는 표지판 같은건 없어 <br>하지만 괜찮아 걱정하지는마 <br>혼자가 아니야 우리가 있잖아 <br>넘어져있어도 다시 다시 <br>저기 보이는 저 벽을 뚫어 <br>저 하늘 저 새처럼 날아올라 <br>더 넓은 세상을 품게 <br>라라 라라라라 라라 <br>라라 라라라라 라라 라라 <br>라라 라랄라 라라라라 라라 <br>라라라 라라라라 라라라 <br>더 넓은 세상을 품게 <br>]]></content><category term="큰숲크리스천스쿨" label="큰숲크리스천스쿨"/><category term="더 넓은 세상을 품게" label="더 넓은 세상을 품게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matthew_Good/Load_Me_Up/</id><title>Matthew_Good - Load Me Up - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:32:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:32:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matthew_Good/Load_Me_Up/" title="Matthew_Good - Load Me Up - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Picture yourself <br>Sleeping on a plane <br>There's something ticking in the overhead <br>And inside your brains <br>There's bodies in the water <br>And bodies in the basement <br>If heaven's for clean people, it's vacant <br>And hey are you know <br>And hey are you being careful <br>And hey are you luke warm <br>Hey ya you are <br><br>I'm frantic <br>So load me up <br>Whatever puts me all the way out <br><br>Picture yourself swimming in an ocean <br>A million miles from nowhere and the nearest phone <br>There's bodies in the water <br>Floating all around you <br>And all of them are talking, and they're comedians <br>And hey are you you know <br>And hey are you special <br>And hey are you deformed <br>Hey ya you are <br><br>I'm frantic <br>So load me up <br>It seems so practiced <br>Me fucking this up <br>Whatever puts me all the way out <br><br>Picture yourself at the MGM grand <br>Murphy's fighting Occam, you're in the stands <br>You're in the stands <br>There's somebody in the water <br>In the middle of the ocean <br>A million miles from nowhere <br>And they're alone <br>I'm there alone <br>So, so deformed <br><br>I'm frantic <br>So load me up <br>This seems so practiced <br>So take me all the way out <br>Whatever puts me all the way out]]></content><category term="Matthew Good" label="Matthew Good"/><category term="Load Me Up" label="Load Me Up"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matthew_Good/Lets_Get_It_On/</id><title>Matthew_Good - Let`s Get It On - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:32:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:32:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matthew_Good/Lets_Get_It_On/" title="Matthew_Good - Let`s Get It On - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[hey there bad seeds <br>let's get it on <br>i'll shut up and keep my end <br>let's get it on <br>our sycophanatic replacements are here at last <br><br>so impossible <br>the doubt in the everything, on everything <br>is so impossible <br><br>so load up and keep marching <br>the push is on <br><br>so impossible <br>the doubt in everything, on everything <br>is so impossible <br>down came your blackbird to suffer in my arms]]></content><category term="Matthew Good" label="Matthew Good"/><category term="Let`s Get It On" label="Let`s Get It On"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matthew_Good/Born_To_Kill/</id><title>Matthew_Good - Born To Kill - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:32:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:32:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matthew_Good/Born_To_Kill/" title="Matthew_Good - Born To Kill - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a big beat <br>You're spinning in my tv <br>A magician <br>The antidote <br>So I'm with him <br>Floating, loaded <br>Enough to be released <br><br>It's more than the less you say you do <br>It's more than the shot that gets you through <br>Born to buy into something <br>Born to kill <br><br>There's a big beat <br>You're sleeping in my memory <br>Like Satan <br>Lonely <br>So I'm with him <br>Floating, loaded <br>Enough to be relseased <br><br>It's more than the less you say you do <br>It's more than the shot that gets you though <br>Born to buy into something <br>Born to Kill]]></content><category term="Matthew Good" label="Matthew Good"/><category term="Born To Kill" label="Born To Kill"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matthew_Good/Suburbia/</id><title>Matthew_Good - Suburbia - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:32:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:32:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matthew_Good/Suburbia/" title="Matthew_Good - Suburbia - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You will come back within yourself <br>you can be art when we melt <br>and i will know what you were for <br>i say we're leaving <br>there ain't nothing here at all <br>another day, a week, the mall <br>and baby if I was in demand <br>you would be mind <br><br>someday this place it going to burn <br>is your whole life in there waiting <br>someday your head is going to turn and you'll realize <br>i'm missing, do you realize <br><br>you will come back <br>convince yourself you can stay alive <br>and wait for me <br>and i will know what this was for <br>and I'll say we're leaving <br>there ain't nothing here at all <br>another month, a year that's all <br>so you can tell them I'm coming <br>and hell's coming with me <br><br>someday this place is going to burn <br>is your whole life in the waiting <br>someday their heads are going to turn and they'll realize <br>you're missing <br>we are there]]></content><category term="Matthew Good" label="Matthew Good"/><category term="Suburbia" label="Suburbia"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matthew_Good/I_Miss_New_Wave/</id><title>Matthew_Good - I Miss New Wave - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:32:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:32:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matthew_Good/I_Miss_New_Wave/" title="Matthew_Good - I Miss New Wave - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Going to fly to Hawaii <br>get laid in a lawn chair <br>drown in a bathtub <br>fill it with cheap beer <br>i miss new wave <br>and movies about losing <br>or just the parts where it's a okay <br>see baby i got something right <br><br>the world is screaming <br>i miss new wave <br>and real intent <br><br>gonna drive to LA <br>get laid at the rose bowl <br>drown in a hot tub, fill it with models <br>i miss new wave <br>and hearing the scratches on my long plays <br>or just the part that sound OK <br>see baby i got something right <br><br>when the world is screaming <br>i miss new wave <br>and real intent <br><br>gonna die in Coquitlam <br>get laid by a golf course <br>that I never went to <br>well it's not a real sport <br>and I'll miss new wave <br>and watching you walk away <br>so go on it's OK <br>see baby i got something right <br>see baby i got something right]]></content><category term="Matthew Good" label="Matthew Good"/><category term="I Miss New Wave" label="I Miss New Wave"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/명왕성에버랜드/고백/</id><title>명왕성에버랜드 - 고백 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:32:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:32:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AA%85%EC%99%95%EC%84%B1%EC%97%90%EB%B2%84%EB%9E%9C%EB%93%9C/%EA%B3%A0%EB%B0%B1/" title="명왕성에버랜드 - 고백 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흔한 두근거림 같은 건 <br>별로 없는데 <br>분명 당신이 보고싶긴 해요 <br>딱히 썸 같은걸 타고있는 건 <br>아닌 것 같은데 <br>자꾸 연락하고 싶긴 해요 <br>예쁜 것 같기도 하고 <br>또 아닌 것 같기도 하고 <br>내게 손 내밀 것 같기도 하고 <br>당신의 마음도 잘 모르겠지만 <br>당신을 안고 싶어요 <br>막 사랑하는 그런 건 아니고 <br>그냥 좀 보고싶네요 <br>당신과 함께인 내 모습 <br>상상하곤 해요 <br>잘은 몰라도 나 당신을 <br>좋아하고 있는 것 같죠 <br>예쁜 것 같기도 하고 <br>또 아닌 것 같기도 하고 <br>내게 손 내밀 것 같기도 하고 <br>당신의 마음도 잘 모르겠지만 <br>당신을 안고 싶어요 <br>막 사랑하는 그런 건 아니고 <br>그냥 좀 보고싶네요 <br>당신을 안고 싶어요 <br>막 사랑하는 그런 건 아니고 <br>그냥 좀 보고싶네요 <br>당신과 함께인 내 모습 <br>상상하곤 해요 <br>잘은 몰라도 나 당신을 <br>좋아하고 있는 것 같죠 <br>]]></content><category term="명왕성에버랜드" label="명왕성에버랜드"/><category term="고백" label="고백"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이다윗/걷다_보면_Title_Song/</id><title>이다윗 - 걷다 보면 (Title Song) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:33:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:33:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%A4%EC%9C%97/%EA%B1%B7%EB%8B%A4_%EB%B3%B4%EB%A9%B4_Title_Song/" title="이다윗 - 걷다 보면 (Title Song) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[긴 하루가 지나고 <br>이젠 걸어야겠다 <br>신발을 꽉 조여 메고 <br>그냥 앞으로 <br>조금 멀리 돌아가 <br>그렇게 걷다 보면 <br>오늘은 달라 보여 <br>너의 뒤로 <br>여전한 너의 목소리 <br>오늘따라 키가 커 보이고 <br>여전한 너의 위로 <br>난 가끔 자신이 없는데 <br>너의 등뒤로 달라진 <br>어제의 연인들 <br>너의 뒤를 따라 달라진 <br>거리의 마음들 <br>너의 등뒤로 달라진 <br>어제의 연인들 <br>너의 뒤를 따라 <br>어디까지라도 갈래 <br>걷다가 걷다가 이렇게 <br>달라진 내 세상 <br>너의 뒤로 몰래 <br>괜찮아 괜찮아 이대로 <br>너의 등뒤로 달라진 <br>어제의 연인들 <br>너의 뒤로 몰래 <br>괜찮아 괜찮아 이대로 <br>]]></content><category term="이다윗" label="이다윗"/><category term="걷다 보면 (Title Song)" label="걷다 보면 (Title Song)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mayday_Parade/The_Problem_With_The_Big_Picture_Is_That_Its_Hard_To_See/</id><title>Mayday_Parade - The Problem With The Big Picture Is That It`s Hard To See - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:33:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:33:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mayday_Parade/The_Problem_With_The_Big_Picture_Is_That_Its_Hard_To_See/" title="Mayday_Parade - The Problem With The Big Picture Is That It`s Hard To See - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You don't have to go, I know I've told you before <br>I could never say it enough <br>And that's the whole point We could drive back to Florida <br>My home forever and you know it's yours <br>Let's see where we land or head out to sea <br>Hit the waves and don't stop and see where they take us <br>I was drawn to your light, now I don't even see it <br>I need you to find me <br><br>I said I'm sorry, but I wasn't sorry enough <br>To give back what you gave me <br>I got to you fast, but not fast enough <br>I know the reason you're always afraid <br><br>A decade of love, laughter and movement <br>With just enough struggle keeps it interesting <br>Once in awhile I find that old fire <br>The same one that got us here, I'm so afraid to lose <br>I hope I land where you'll always be <br>A place with some magic, let's see how far that takes us <br>You were my soul, now I can't even feel you <br>You said that you would find me <br><br>I said I'm sorry, but I wasn't sorry enough <br>To give back what you gave me <br>I got to you fast, but not fast enough <br>I know the reason you're always afraid <br><br>May you find what you need <br>In the darkest tunnel so deep down <br>May you hold onto me <br>Just at least another time around <br><br>I said I'm sorry, but I wasn't sorry enough <br>To give back what you gave me <br>I got to you fast, but not fast enough <br>I know the reason you're always afraid <br><br>I know the reason you're always afraid]]></content><category term="Mayday Parade" label="Mayday Parade"/><category term="The Problem With The Big Picture Is That It`s Hard To See" label="The Problem With The Big Picture Is That It`s Hard To See"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mayday_Parade/The_Last_Something_That_Meant_Anything/</id><title>Mayday_Parade - The Last Something That Meant Anything - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:34:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:34:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mayday_Parade/The_Last_Something_That_Meant_Anything/" title="Mayday_Parade - The Last Something That Meant Anything - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well I thought that we could sit around and talk for hours <br>About things I couldn't say to you <br>And things that we could never do <br>And this conversation has had no face <br>When the words take days <br>You can re write and erase anything <br><br>You know my heart so tell me honestly, did you ever really want this <br>Knows all these <br><br>And I'll borrow words from all my favourite paragraphs <br>To write a ballad while we say the things <br>We'd hope would mean the most to me <br>And each letter sent <br>I have found in the pages of hope for the days <br>When I feel like I've lost everything <br><br>You know my heart so tell me honestly, did you ever really want this <br>Knows all these parts 'cause my jealous heart can't take that <br>So I'll sing this song for every word that's come out wrong <br><br>But, I'll be OK Is that what you want me to say <br>It's called break up <br>'Cause it's broken <br>But I'll be OK is that what you want me to say <br>It's called break up <br>'Cause it's broken <br><br>Repeats <br>I'll be OK <br>Is that what you want me to say <br>It's called break up <br>'Cause it's broken <br><br>Singing <br>I'll be OK <br>Is that what you want me to say <br>'Cause it's broken <br><br>And you were just about to tell me <br>How you meant that you were sorry <br>And the nights we've spent <br>Have really meant the world to you <br>Let's not pretend I'm keeping track on every note <br>On every page the day she wrote <br>The cherry flavored kisses <br>Well, I taste them <br>Do you miss it <br><br>2x <br>I'll be OK <br>Is that what you want me to say <br>It's called break up <br>'Cause it's broken <br><br>Well I thought that we could sit around and talk for hours <br>About things I couldn't say to you <br>And things that we could never do]]></content><category term="Mayday Parade" label="Mayday Parade"/><category term="The Last Something That Meant Anything" label="The Last Something That Meant Anything"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mayday_Parade/Three_Cheers_For_Five_Years/</id><title>Mayday_Parade - Three Cheers For Five Years - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:34:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:34:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mayday_Parade/Three_Cheers_For_Five_Years/" title="Mayday_Parade - Three Cheers For Five Years - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I swear that you don't have to go <br>I thought we could wait for the fireworks <br>I thought we could wait for the snow <br>To wash over Georgia and kill the hurt <br>I thought I could live in your arms <br>And spend every moment I had with you <br>Stay up all night with the stars <br>Confess all the faith that I had in you I had in you <br><br>Too late, I'm sure and lonely <br>Another night, another dream wasted on you <br>Just be here now against me <br>You know the words, so sing along for me, baby <br><br>For heaven's sake I know you're sorry <br>But you won't stop crying <br>This anniversary may never be the same <br>Inside I hope you know I'm dying <br>With my heart beside me <br>In shattered pieces that may never be replaced <br>And if I died right now you'd never be the same <br><br>I thought with a month of apart <br>Together would find us an opening <br>And moonlight would provide the spark <br>And that I would stumble across the key <br>Or break down the door to your heart <br>Forever could see us not you and me <br>And you'd help me out of the dark <br>And I'd give my heart as an offering an offering <br><br>Too late, I'm sure and lonely <br>Another night, another dream wasted on you <br>Just be here now against me <br>You know the words, so sing along for me, baby <br><br>For heaven's sake I know you're sorry <br>But you won't stop crying <br>This anniversary may never be the same <br>Inside I hope you know I'm dying <br>With my heart beside me <br>In shattered pieces that may never be replaced <br>And if I died right now you'd never be the same <br><br>And I will always remember you as you are right now to me <br>And I will always remember you now, remember you now <br><br>So sleep alone tonight with no one here just by your side <br>Sleep alone tonight <br><br>How does he feel, how does he kiss <br>Let's sleep alone tonight <br>How does he taste while he's on your lips <br>With no one here just by your side <br>How does he feel, how does he kiss <br>Sleep alone tonight <br>x3 <br><br>I can't forget you <br>Let's sleep alone tonight <br>I know you want me to want you, I want to <br>With no one here just by your side <br>But I can't forget you <br>Sleep alone tonight <br>So when this is over don't blow your composure, baby <br>I can't forget you <br>Let's sleep alone tonight <br>I know you want me to want you, I want to <br>With no one here just by your side <br>But I can't forget you <br>Sleep alone tonight <br>So when this is over don't blow your composure <br><br>I can't forget you <br>I know you want me to want you, I want to]]></content><category term="Mayday Parade" label="Mayday Parade"/><category term="Three Cheers For Five Years" label="Three Cheers For Five Years"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mayday_Parade/Your_Song/</id><title>Mayday_Parade - Your Song - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:34:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:34:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mayday_Parade/Your_Song/" title="Mayday_Parade - Your Song - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You say that Gainesville's got no soul <br>Well that sounds like a good excuse for coming home <br>And all these Tallahassee skylines <br>They keep singing out a song <br>I know it's your song your song <br>They've been singing all night long <br>And this Galley Alley rooftop <br>Just keeps calling out your name <br>To come and stay <br>So stay <br>So stay <br><br>Stay and watch the stars come out and then the sun as they all fade away <br>I'll sing every song I wrote if it'll make you wanna stay <br>And then I'll say <br>That I missed you <br>And these words <br>They'll convince you <br><br>I poured through every song I wrote <br>Every line that I've cried every note that was spilt with this pen <br>And every line in every song, they all seemed to come out wrong <br>Until your song <br>And we'll sing it all night long <br>And this Tallahassee skyline hasn't changed <br>And while the view from every rooftop says to stay <br><br>Stay and watch the stars come out and then the sun as they all fade away <br>I'll sing every song I wrote if it'll make you wanna stay <br>And it'll say <br>That I missed you <br>And these words <br>They'll convince you <br><br>2x <br>And I could call you 'baby doll' all the time <br>And you'd whisper in my ears, you'd say, I missed you boy <br>So sing it over again, and over again, and over again <br><br>Still you'd say <br>That I missed you <br>And these words <br>They'll convince you <br>And I'm hoping as I kiss you <br><br>2x <br>And I could call you 'baby doll' all the time <br>And you'd whisper in my ears, you'd say whisper in my ears, you'd say <br>I missed you boy <br>Sing it over again, and over again, and over again]]></content><category term="Mayday Parade" label="Mayday Parade"/><category term="Your Song" label="Your Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mayday_Parade/One_Man_Drinking_Games/</id><title>Mayday_Parade - One Man Drinking Games - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:34:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:34:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mayday_Parade/One_Man_Drinking_Games/" title="Mayday_Parade - One Man Drinking Games - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And you said it would be funny to keep me hanging in suspense <br>Then I'd run over to your house and I'd scale the chain link fence <br>That borders your back yard and then I'd climb through your window <br>And I'd whisper that I love you as you fall out of your clothes <br><br>And we'd lay there in the darkness like the dream of you I had <br>Where we captured all the fireflies and we knew what time we had <br>Could be counted on our fingertips that almost made you cry <br>You let me hold you tightly as we said all our goodbyes <br><br>May I say I loved you more <br>May I say I loved you more <br><br>And it must've been an hour that I clutched you in my arms <br>And I must have said the right things because you instantly felt warm <br>And you heard my heart stop beating and you wanted not to cry <br>As your sympathetic whispers they told a tale of bad goodbyes <br><br>And you swore you saw me laughing, and I swore I saw you smile <br>And this time we've spent together was meant to last us quite a while <br>As I take this piece of you with me I'll carry to my grave <br>And knowing that for someone you're an angel sent to save <br><br>Keep breathing, my angel, if you go down I go with you <br>May I say I loved you more <br>Keep breathing, just keep breathing <br><br>Keep breathing, my angel, if you go down I go with you <br>May I say I loved you more <br>Keep breathing, just keep breathing <br><br>Let's drink to memories we shared <br>Down one to all the hopes and cares <br>Here's two for being unaware that you're gone <br>Because before too long you'll be a memory <br><br>let's drink to memories we shared <br>Before too long you'll be a memory <br>down one to all the hopes and cares <br>Because before too long you'll be a memory <br>Here's two for being unaware that you're gone <br>I said before too long you'll be a memory <br>I said before too long you'll be a memory]]></content><category term="Mayday Parade" label="Mayday Parade"/><category term="One Man Drinking Games" label="One Man Drinking Games"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mayday_Parade/When_I_Get_Home_Youre_So_Dead/</id><title>Mayday_Parade - When I Get Home, You`re So Dead - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:34:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:34:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mayday_Parade/When_I_Get_Home_Youre_So_Dead/" title="Mayday_Parade - When I Get Home, You`re So Dead - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The words are coming I feel terrible <br>Is it typical for us to end like this <br>Am I just another scene <br>From a movie that you've seen 100 times <br>'Cause baby you weren't the first or the last or the worst <br>And I've got to fill the blanks in the past with a verse <br>And we could sit around and cry but frankly you're not worth it anymore <br><br>Chorus <br>So say hello to all the boys at the top of this table that you're under <br>Lipstick lullabies <br>This is sorry for the last time <br>And baby I understand that you're making new friends <br>This is how you get by <br>The moral this time is <br>Girls make boys cry <br><br>and die <br><br>On any other day we'd shoot the boy <br>But your simple toy <br>Had caused a scene like this <br>Leave him hanging on the walls <br>Just a picture in the hall <br>Like a 100 more like a 100 more <br>Consider this as a gift as you taste him on your lips <br>And he's making you scream with his hands on your hips <br>I hope he's leaving you empty baby this is just a fix <br>For such a simple little whore <br><br>Chorus <br><br>And your name remains the same <br>All that has changed is this pretty face <br>So pull the trigger <br>It never gets closer <br>You want to start over <br>But never start over <br><br>Pull the trigger <br>It never gets closer <br>You want to start over <br>But never start over <br><br>Chorus <br><br>Say hello <br>Say hello <br><br>Lipstick lullabies <br>This is sorry for the last time <br>And baby I understand that you're making new friends <br>This is how you get by <br>The moral this time is <br>Girls make boys cry and]]></content><category term="Mayday Parade" label="Mayday Parade"/><category term="When I Get Home, You`re So Dead" label="When I Get Home, You`re So Dead"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mayday_Parade/Just_Say_Youre_Not_Into_It/</id><title>Mayday_Parade - Just Say You`re Not Into It - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:34:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:34:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mayday_Parade/Just_Say_Youre_Not_Into_It/" title="Mayday_Parade - Just Say You`re Not Into It - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In a show of hands, who has said these words before <br>In a show of hearts on the floor, who has ever meant them more <br><br>Well, I'll swallow my pride if you'll stay for the years <br>And watch me spin circles as I disappear <br>And hearts, they don't lie, they just quiver in fear <br>As you say <br><br>Tonight we forget everything <br>And we stay the night <br>If I was wrong, then I'm sorry <br>I'll stop this fight <br>For the night <br><br>And this empty space left in the seat <br>To my right where you should be <br>Says a lot <br>Don't let it say goodbye <br>Don't let it say goodbye <br>Let it say goodbye <br><br>Forget everything <br>And we stay the night <br>If I was wrong, then I'm sorry <br>I'll stop this fight <br>For the night <br>And this empty space left in the seat <br>To my right where you should be <br>Says a lot <br><br>And today I know that tomorrow <br>Will shine again golden and bring <br>Our hearts back home <br>And today I know that tomorrow <br>Will shine again golden and bring <br>Our hearts back home <br><br>And today I know that tomorrow And today meant nothing, 'cause you're gone <br>Will shine again golden and bring And I swear that this meant everything to me <br>Our hearts back home But my heart's not home <br>And today I know that tomorrow And today meant nothing, 'cause you're gone <br>Will shine again golden and bring And I swear that this meant everything to me <br>Our hearts back home But my heart's not home]]></content><category term="Mayday Parade" label="Mayday Parade"/><category term="Just Say You`re Not Into It" label="Just Say You`re Not Into It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Westpoint/Feel_October/</id><title>Westpoint - Feel October - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:34:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:34:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Westpoint/Feel_October/" title="Westpoint - Feel October - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I see the shadows on the trees <br>Everybody's leaving <br>I feel October start to rust <br>Summer's embrace I couldn't trust <br><br>I talk to myself when I have no one else <br><br>Weak forged promise <br>We lost permanence <br>No longer united <br><br>I'm secluded from everyone <br>They've all moved on <br>Save your silhouette <br>I'll be dead before dawn]]></content><category term="Westpoint" label="Westpoint"/><category term="Feel October" label="Feel October"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zeal__Ardor/Devil_Is_Fine/</id><title>Zeal__Ardor - Devil Is Fine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:35:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:35:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zeal__Ardor/Devil_Is_Fine/" title="Zeal__Ardor - Devil Is Fine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[little one better heed my warning <br>devil is kind <br>he come i early morning <br>devil is fine <br>he go by many names <br>devil is kind <br>we gonna go home to the flames <br>devil is fine <br><br>he gon forgive my sin <br>devil is kind <br>he promise many things <br>devil is fine <br>i can't do him no wrong <br>devil is kind <br>i see him before long <br>devil is fine <br><br>nobody gon show you the way now <br>nobody gon hold your hand no <br>nobody gon show you the way now <br>devil is fine <br><br>nobody gon show you the way now <br>nobody gon hold your hand no <br>nobody gon lead you the way now <br>devil is fine <br>devil is fine <br>devil is fine <br><br>little one better fins your way now <br>devil is fine <br>little one better find your way out <br>devil is kind <br>little one better run for your life <br>devil is fine <br>little one where you going with that knife <br>devil is kind <br><br>nobody gon show you the way now <br>nobody gon hold your hand no <br>nobody gon show you the way now <br>devil is fine <br><br>nobody gon let you go no <br>nobody gon hold your hand no <br>nobody gon lead you the way now <br>devil is fine <br>devil is fine <br>devil is fine <br><br>little one better fins your way now <br>devil is fine <br>little one better find your way out <br>devil is kind <br>little one better run for your life <br>devil is fine <br>little one where you going with that knife <br>devil is kind <br><br>little one gotta heed my warning <br>devil kind <br>he come in early morning <br>devil is fine]]></content><category term="Zeal &amp; Ardor" label="Zeal &amp; Ardor"/><category term="Devil Is Fine" label="Devil Is Fine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/브로콜리너마저/단호한_출근_Inst/</id><title>브로콜리너마저 - 단호한 출근 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:37:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:37:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A1%9C%EC%BD%9C%EB%A6%AC%EB%84%88%EB%A7%88%EC%A0%80/%EB%8B%A8%ED%98%B8%ED%95%9C_%EC%B6%9C%EA%B7%BC_Inst/" title="브로콜리너마저 - 단호한 출근 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[망설이는 순간 <br>딴 생각처럼 끼어드는 차들 <br>좁아지는 도로 위에 나는 <br>길을 잃어버린 것 같은데 <br>항상 출발해야 <br>할 때면 사소한 일들이 <br>마음을 걸고넘어져 <br>의미 없이 현관을 헤매지 <br>도망치고 싶은 날은 <br>매일매일인데 <br>돌아갈 곳이 없는 나는 <br>길 위에서야 <br>달콤하게 꿈을 꾸네 <br>단호하게 마음을 먹고 <br>출발할 시간 <br>아니 망설이지 않고 <br>움직여야만 <br>벗어날 수 있는 <br>정체된 이 길 <br>도망치고 싶은 마음을 <br>삼켜 봅니다 <br>도달하는 곳이 <br>어디인지 생각하기엔 <br>너무 피곤한 시간 <br>망설이는 순간 <br>깜빡이도 없이 <br>끼어드는 생각들 <br>도망치고 싶은 날은 <br>매일매일인데 <br>돌아갈 곳이 없는 나는 <br>길 위에서야 <br>달콤하게 꿈을 꾸네 <br>단호하게 마음을 먹고 <br>출발할 시간 <br>아니 망설이지 않고 <br>움직여야만 <br>벗어날 수 있는 <br>정체된 이 길 <br>도망치고 싶은 마음을 <br>삼켜 봅니다 <br>도달하는 곳이 <br>어디인지 생각하기엔 <br>너무 피곤한 시간 <br>너무 피곤한 시간 <br>]]></content><category term="브로콜리너마저" label="브로콜리너마저"/><category term="단호한 출근 (Inst.)" label="단호한 출근 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/브로콜리너마저/단호한_출근/</id><title>브로콜리너마저 - 단호한 출근 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:37:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:37:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A1%9C%EC%BD%9C%EB%A6%AC%EB%84%88%EB%A7%88%EC%A0%80/%EB%8B%A8%ED%98%B8%ED%95%9C_%EC%B6%9C%EA%B7%BC/" title="브로콜리너마저 - 단호한 출근 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[망설이는 순간 <br>딴 생각처럼 끼어드는 차들 <br>좁아지는 도로 위에 나는 <br>길을 잃어버린 것 같은데 <br>항상 출발해야 <br>할 때면 사소한 일들이 <br>마음을 걸고넘어져 <br>의미 없이 현관을 헤매지 <br>도망치고 싶은 날은 <br>매일매일인데 <br>돌아갈 곳이 없는 나는 <br>길 위에서야 <br>달콤하게 꿈을 꾸네 <br>단호하게 마음을 먹고 <br>출발할 시간 <br>아니 망설이지 않고 <br>움직여야만 <br>벗어날 수 있는 <br>정체된 이 길 <br>도망치고 싶은 마음을 <br>삼켜 봅니다 <br>도달하는 곳이 <br>어디인지 생각하기엔 <br>너무 피곤한 시간 <br>망설이는 순간 <br>깜빡이도 없이 <br>끼어드는 생각들 <br>도망치고 싶은 날은 <br>매일매일인데 <br>돌아갈 곳이 없는 나는 <br>길 위에서야 <br>달콤하게 꿈을 꾸네 <br>단호하게 마음을 먹고 <br>출발할 시간 <br>아니 망설이지 않고 <br>움직여야만 <br>벗어날 수 있는 <br>정체된 이 길 <br>도망치고 싶은 마음을 <br>삼켜 봅니다 <br>도달하는 곳이 <br>어디인지 생각하기엔 <br>너무 피곤한 시간 <br>너무 피곤한 시간 <br>]]></content><category term="브로콜리너마저" label="브로콜리너마저"/><category term="단호한 출근" label="단호한 출근"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로그아웃_LOG_OUT/사랑니_Feat_청자요_Tori/</id><title>로그아웃_LOG_OUT - 사랑니 (Feat. 청자요, Tori) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:38:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:38:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EA%B7%B8%EC%95%84%EC%9B%83_LOG_OUT/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EB%8B%88_Feat_%EC%B2%AD%EC%9E%90%EC%9A%94_Tori/" title="로그아웃_LOG_OUT - 사랑니 (Feat. 청자요, Tori) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[연애실패 한 두 번 <br>하고 나니 <br>두려움에 주저 하게 되 <br>그리곤 그저 <br>평행선을 그리던 일상 <br>달라질게 없던 <br>다 커 버린 성장기 <br>닫혀버린 성장판 <br>그 벽을 뚫고 넌 <br>하루하루 자라났어 <br>아이 난 또 내가 다 <br>큰 줄 알았지 <br>너를 보면 내가 <br>아이가 된 듯해 <br>조금 까마득해 <br>관계를 거듭해도 <br>인연에 끝엔 <br>아주 많이 아플 거래 <br>니가 점점 커져가는 <br>맘속 느낌이 <br>때론 감당 안될 것 같은 <br>기미가 보이기도 하지만 <br>이미 깊이 <br>뚝심 있게 내 안에 자라버린 <br>널 지킬게 나의 첫사랑 <br>니 가 내 안에 갑자기 <br>자라나서 당혹스럽지만 <br>아주 많이 기뻐 <br>Don't say that I'm falling in love <br>I need you I want you <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>자라난 사랑니를 <br>뽑아야 하지만 oh <br>아직은 이 아픔을 <br>참아 보려 해 <br>어딘가 비어있던 내 안을 <br>채워준 넌 지루한 타임라인 <br>속 달콤한 속삭임 <br>속에 점점 자라난 감정의 <br>상승곡선 곧 그 감정은 <br>어설픔이 앞선 <br>집착이 되었고 넌 날 피해 <br>안쪽으로 숨어버리곤 <br>속 썩이네 <br>빼내지도 못한 채로 <br>매일 앓아 이 느낌 알아 <br>이별의 전주 <br>가지런하던 일상이 너로 <br>인해 흔들렸지 흐트러진 <br>그대와의 약속이 <br>그대의 아픔보다 흐릿해져 <br>갈 때쯤 내가 잘못했단 <br>영혼 없는 말로 <br>타이르는 약이 습관이 <br>될 때쯤 다신 안 올 너를 <br>매몰차게 버린 <br>곧 찾아올 이별이 두렵지 <br>만은 않은 이렇게 한층 <br>성장한 나를 <br>Don't say that I'm falling in love <br>I need you I want you <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>자라난 사랑니를 <br>뽑아야 하지만 oh <br>아직은 이 아픔을 <br>참아 보려 해 <br>사랑을 알 때쯤 <br>사랑니가 난데 <br>그때 그대가 <br>머물던 나의 시간과 <br>이별 앞에 불안했던 <br>예감과 널 떼어낸 후 <br>허전한 감각 <br>다 끝이라고 생각했어 <br>지나고 보면 괜찮아 <br>지려나 겨우 몇 일하고 <br>끝나버릴 아픔일 뿐이겠지 <br>니가 발치된 자리 <br>남겨진 텅 빈 발자취 <br>]]></content><category term="로그아웃 (LOG OUT)" label="로그아웃 (LOG OUT)"/><category term="사랑니 (Feat. 청자요, Tori)" label="사랑니 (Feat. 청자요, Tori)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로그아웃_LOG_OUT/2시1분_Feat_MA_KVMA/</id><title>로그아웃_LOG_OUT - 2시1분 (Feat. MA$ KVMA) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:38:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:38:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EA%B7%B8%EC%95%84%EC%9B%83_LOG_OUT/2%EC%8B%9C1%EB%B6%84_Feat_MA_KVMA/" title="로그아웃_LOG_OUT - 2시1분 (Feat. MA$ KVMA) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 내 길을 알어 <br>너가 눈치를 챘던 <br>그대로야 for ma life <br>for ma mom and brother <br>이게 나의 사명이라 믿고 <br>계속 해갈 거야 <br>더 죽이는 작명 <br>Wassup <br>이건 낯선 주제일수도 <br>있어 너의 관점에서 보면 <br>근데 이건 오히려 너의 <br>이야기일지도 몰라 <br>그걸 노린 거지 난 고의로 <br>나에 대해 <br>plz talk about me <br>했던 날은 지났어 <br>나이를 먹었다는 거지 <br>나도 매일 다른 <br>생각으로 차있고 <br>그걸 해결하기에도 <br>벅차지 man <br>hey do it man <br>I'll be going err day <br>뒤쳐 지는 게 난 싫기에 내일 <br>해를 보고 잠에 드는 버릇이 <br>나에 뇌를 지배 했어 <br>그게 내가 사는 이유지 <br>난 착하지 않아 원래 <br>근데 난 천사일 지도 man <br>돌아가 돌아가 돌아가 man <br>돌아가 돌아가 돌아가 man <br>돌아가 돌아가 돌아가 man <br>돌아가 돌아가 <br>돌아왔지 다시 이게 <br>내가 버릇처럼 말하는 사실 <br>난 내 말은 지키지 <br>나의 왼손에 약지에 걸어 <br>세수할 때 빼곤 <br>안 빼는 반지는 그걸 증명해 <br>이걸 주신 분이 <br>나를 보며 천국에서 편하게 <br>쉬길 매일 기도해 <br>진심이 필요해 <br>so I pray god <br>두 손 모아 Amen <br>내가 필요했던 게 <br>절반쯤으로 줄어들 때 <br>그 허무함을 느껴 <br>더 배로 늘어가는 <br>욕심이 때로는 원망스럽지만 <br>그게 되려 날 성장시키지 <br>그걸 알어 깨닫고 <br>나서 다시 돌아왔지 men <br>아무도 몰라봐도 <br>I do it <br>play hard workin every day <br>난 착하지 않아 원래 <br>근데 난 천사일 지도 man <br>돌아가 돌아가 돌아가 man <br>돌아가 돌아가 돌아가 man <br>돌아가 돌아가 돌아가 man <br>돌아가 돌아가 <br>돌아가 돌아가 돌아가 man <br>돌아가 돌아가 돌아가 man <br>돌아가 돌아가 돌아가 man <br>돌아가 돌아가 <br>]]></content><category term="로그아웃 (LOG OUT)" label="로그아웃 (LOG OUT)"/><category term="2시1분 (Feat. MA$ KVMA)" label="2시1분 (Feat. MA$ KVMA)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헬로제이/예뻐/</id><title>헬로제이 - 예뻐 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:38:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:38:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%AC%EB%A1%9C%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4/%EC%98%88%EB%BB%90/" title="헬로제이 - 예뻐 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[예쁘다 예뻐 미치겠어 예쁘다 <br>너에게 매일 듣고 싶은 말 <br>수줍어하는 사이 사이 사이 사이 <br>누가 널 채 가버릴까 <br>스스럼 없는 사이 사이 <br>사이 사이 되고 싶은데 <br>어떻게 내 맘을 전할까 <br>너에게 달려가고 싶어 all day long <br>너만 보이는 두 눈을 <br>뭐라고 설명할까 <br>좋아해 좋아 미치겠어 좋아해 <br>너에게 당장 하고 싶은 말 <br>부끄럼 타는 사이 사이 사이 사이 <br>진짜 널 빼앗겨버릴까 <br>부러움 받는 사이 사이 <br>사이 사이 되고 싶은데 <br>어떻게 내 맘을 전할까 <br>너에게 달려가고 싶어 all day long <br>너만 보이는 두 눈을 <br>뭐라고 설명할까 <br>부끄럼 타는 사이 사이 사이 사이 <br>빼앗겨버릴까 <br>부러움 받는 사이 사이 <br>사이 사이 되고 싶은데 <br>어떻게 내 맘을 전할까 <br>너에게 달려가고 싶어 all day long <br>너만 보이는 두 눈을 <br>뭐라고 설명할까 <br>]]></content><category term="헬로제이" label="헬로제이"/><category term="예뻐" label="예뻐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Last_Dance/</id><title>Neil_Young - Last Dance - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:38:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:38:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Last_Dance/" title="Neil_Young - Last Dance - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wake up It's a Monday morning <br>No time left to say goodbye <br>Can't breathe <br>and the lights are changing <br>You can live your own life <br>Making it happen <br>Working on your own time <br>Laid back and laughin' <br>Oh no, oh no <br><br>Headlights <br>make it home by sundown <br>Feeling that the day is through <br>Return back <br>to where you come from <br>You can live your own life <br>Making it happen <br>Working on your own time <br>Laid back and laughin' <br>Oh no, oh no <br><br>You wake up in the mornin' <br>And the sun's comin' up <br>Its been up for hours <br>and hours and hours <br>And hours and hours and hours <br>It's been up for hours <br>and hours and hours <br>And you light up the stove <br>And the coffee cup, its hot <br>And the orange juice <br>is cold, cold, cold <br>Monday morning <br>Wake up, wake up <br>wake up, wake up <br>Its time to go <br>Time to go to work <br><br>You can live your own life <br>Making it happen <br>Working on your own time <br>Laid back and laughin' <br>Oh no, oh no <br>No, no, no]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Last Dance" label="Last Dance"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/The_Bridge/</id><title>Neil_Young - The Bridge - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:39:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:39:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/The_Bridge/" title="Neil_Young - The Bridge - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The bridge, we'll build it now <br>It may take a lot of time <br>And it maybe lonely but <br>Ooh baby, ooh baby <br><br>The bridge was falling down <br>And that took a lot of lies <br>And it made me lonely <br>Ooh baby, ooh baby <br><br>The bridge was falling <br>The bridge was falling <br>The bridge was falling <br><br>One day, when you talked to me <br>I saw myself again <br>And it made me love you <br>Ooh baby, ooh baby <br><br>And love came running down <br>Like a river on your skin <br>And you let me in <br>Ooh babe, ooh babe <br><br>You let me in <br>You let me in <br>You let me in <br><br>The bridge, we'll build it now <br>It may take a lot of time]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="The Bridge" label="The Bridge"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Dont_Be_Denied/</id><title>Neil_Young - Don`t Be Denied - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:39:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:39:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Dont_Be_Denied/" title="Neil_Young - Don`t Be Denied - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I was a young boy <br>My mama said to me <br>Your daddy's leavin' home today <br>I think he's gone to stay <br>We packed up all our bags <br>And drove out to Winnipeg <br><br>When we got to Winnipeg <br>I checked in to school <br>I wore white bucks on my feet <br>When I learned the golden rule <br>The punches came fast and hard <br>Lying on my back <br>in the school yard <br><br>Don't be denied, don't be denied <br>Don't be denied, don't be denied <br>Don't be denied, don't be denied <br><br>Well pretty soon I met a friend <br>He played guitar <br>We used to sit <br>on the steps at school <br>And dream of being stars <br>We started a band <br>We played all night <br><br>Don't be denied, don't be denied <br>Don't be denied, don't be denied <br>Don't be denied, don't be denied <br><br>Oh Canada <br>We played all night <br>I really hate to leave you now <br>But to stay just wouldn't be right <br>Down in Hollywood <br>We played so good <br><br>The businessmen crowded around <br>They came to hear the golden sound <br>There we were on the Sunset Strip <br>Playing our songs <br>for the highest bid <br>We played all night <br>The price was right <br><br>Don't be denied, don't be denied <br>Don't be denied, don't be denied <br>Don't be denied, don't be denied <br><br>Well, all that glitters isn't gold <br>I know you've heard <br>that story told <br>And I'm a pauper <br>in a naked disguise <br>A millionaire <br>through a business man's eyes <br>Oh friend of mine <br>Don't be denied]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Don`t Be Denied" label="Don`t Be Denied"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Love_In_Mind/</id><title>Neil_Young - Love In Mind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:39:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:39:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Love_In_Mind/" title="Neil_Young - Love In Mind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Woke up this morning <br>with love in mind <br>It was raining outside <br>but my love still shined <br>Kept me warm <br>till my plane touched the sky <br><br>And I've seen love <br>make a fool of a man <br>He tried to make a loser win <br>But I've got nothing to lose <br>I can't get back again <br><br>Man made rules <br>been holdin' back my love <br>Can't hold it back no more <br>Churches long preach sex is wrong <br>Jesus where is nature gone <br>What am I doing here <br>What am I doing here <br>What am I doing here <br><br>Woke up this morning <br>with love in mind <br>It was raining outside <br>but my love still shined <br>Kept me warm <br>till my plane touched the sky]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Love In Mind" label="Love In Mind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/LA/</id><title>Neil_Young - L.A. - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:39:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:39:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/LA/" title="Neil_Young - L.A. - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In a matter of time <br>There'll be a friend of mine <br>Gonna come to the coast <br>You're gonna see him <br>Up close for a minute or two <br>While the ground cracks under you <br><br>By the look in your eyes <br>You'd think that it was a surprise <br>But you seem to forget <br>Something somebody said <br>About the bubbles in the sea <br>And an ocean full of trees <br><br>And you now, LA <br>Uptight <br>city in the smog <br>city in the smog <br>Don't you wish that <br>you could be here too <br>Don't you wish that <br>you could be here too <br>Don't you wish that <br>you could be here too <br><br>Well, it's hard to believe <br>So you get up to leave <br>And you laugh at the door <br>That you heard it all before <br>Oh it's so good to know <br>That it's all just a show for you <br><br>But when the suppers are planned <br>And the freeways are crammed <br>And the mountains erupt <br>And the valley is sucked <br>Into cracks in the earth <br>Will I finally be heard by you <br><br>LA <br>Uptight <br>city in the smog <br>city in the smog <br>Don't you wish that <br>you could be here too <br>Don't you wish that <br>you could be here too <br>Don't you wish that <br>you could be here too]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="L.A." label="L.A."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Yonder_Stands_The_Sinner/</id><title>Neil_Young - Yonder Stands The Sinner - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:39:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:39:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Yonder_Stands_The_Sinner/" title="Neil_Young - Yonder Stands The Sinner - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, you heard about <br>the Great Pretender <br>I went to see him <br>and he's not the same <br>Down by the club <br>on the parking lot cinders <br>I was to meet him <br>and play his game <br>Yonder stands the sinner <br>He calls my name <br>without a sound <br><br>I saw his face in <br>the attic window <br>Yellin' down <br>through the broken pane <br>Sinner man <br>What you got to run for <br>Church bells rang <br>when he said that name <br>Yonder stands the sinner <br>He calls my name <br>without a sound <br><br>Well, I was about as scared <br>as I could be <br>I went and hid <br>behind the nearest tree <br>Peeked out <br>from behind the branches <br>Sinner <br>Yonder stands the sinner <br>He calls my name <br>without a sound <br>To get down <br><br>I guess you heard about <br>the Great Pretender <br>I went to see him <br>and he's not the same <br>I guess you heard about <br>the Great Pretender <br>I went to see him <br>and he's not the same]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Yonder Stands The Sinner" label="Yonder Stands The Sinner"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Journey_Through_The_Past/</id><title>Neil_Young - Journey Through The Past - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:39:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:39:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Journey_Through_The_Past/" title="Neil_Young - Journey Through The Past - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When the winter rains <br>come pourin' down <br>On that new home of mine <br>Will you think of me <br>and wonder if I'm fine <br>Will your restless heart <br>come back to mine <br>On a journey thru the past <br>Will I still be in your eyes <br>and on your mind <br><br>Now I'm going back to Canada <br>On a journey thru the past <br>And I won't be back <br>till February comes <br>I will stay with you <br>if you'll stay with me <br>Said the fiddler to the drum <br>And we'll keep good time <br>on a journey thru the past <br><br>When the winter rains <br>come pourin' down <br>On that new home of mine <br>Will I still be in your eyes <br>and on your mind <br>Will I still be in your eyes <br>and on your mind]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Journey Through The Past" label="Journey Through The Past"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Time_Fades_Away/</id><title>Neil_Young - Time Fades Away - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:39:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:39:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Time_Fades_Away/" title="Neil_Young - Time Fades Away - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fourteen junkies <br>too weak to work <br>One sells diamonds <br>for what they're worth <br>Down on pain street <br>disappointment lurks <br>Son, don't be home too late <br>Try to get back by eight <br>Son, don't wait <br>till the break of day <br>'Cause you know <br>how time fades away <br>Time fades away <br>You know how time fades away <br><br>All day presidents <br>look out windows <br>All night sentries <br>watch the moonglow <br>All are waiting till <br>the time is right <br>Son, don't be home too late <br>Try to get back by eight <br>Son, don't wait <br>till the break of day <br>'Cause you know <br>how time fades away <br>Time fades away <br>You know how time fades away <br><br>Back in Canada I spent my days <br>Riding subways through a haze <br>I was handcuffed <br>I was born and raised <br>Son, don't be home too late <br>Try to get back by eight <br>Son, don't wait <br>till the break of day <br>'Cause you know <br>how time fades away <br>Time fades away <br>You know how time fades away <br><br>Thirteen junkies <br>too weak to work <br>One sells diamonds <br>for what they're worth <br>Down on pain street <br>disappointment lurks <br>Son, don't be home too late <br>Try to get back by eight, eight <br>Son, don't wait <br>till the break of day <br>'Cause you know <br>how time fades away <br>Time fades away <br>You know how time fades away <br><br>Time fades away <br>You know how time fades away]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Time Fades Away" label="Time Fades Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ligabue/La_Vita_Facile/</id><title>Ligabue - La Vita Facile - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:40:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:40:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ligabue/La_Vita_Facile/" title="Ligabue - La Vita Facile - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Questa e la mia vita <br>Se ho bisogno te lo dico <br>Sono io che guido <br>Io che vado fuori strada <br>Sempre io che pago <br>Non e mai successo che pagassero per me <br><br>Questa e la mia vita <br>Se entri chiedimi permesso <br>Portami una gita <br>Fammi ridere di gusto <br>Porta la tua vita <br>Che vediamo che succede a mescolarle un po' <br><br>E ora che ci sei <br>Dato che ci sei <br>Fammi fare un giro su chi non sono stato mai <br>Dato che ci sei <br>Come io vorrei <br><br>Questa e la mia vita <br>Sono quello che ci pensa <br>Porta un paio d'ore <br>Una notte bella densa <br>Trattamela bene <br>Che al momento ho solo questa e poivedremo un poi <br><br>Questa e la mia vita <br>Certi giorni non si batte <br>Certi altri meno <br>E' cosi che va per tutti <br>Certi giorni poca <br>Certi giorni sembra troppa e invece non lo e mai <br><br>E ora che ci sei <br>Dato che ci sei <br>Fammi fare un giro su chi non sono stato mai <br>Dato che ci sei <br>Come io vorrei <br><br>Questa e la mi vita <br>Tieniteli tu I consigli <br>Io non lo capita <br>Figurati se tu fai meglio <br>Porta la tua vita <br>Che vediamo che succede a mescolarle un po' <br>E ora che ci sei <br>Dato che ci sei <br>Fammi fare un giro su chi non sono stato mai <br>Dato che ci sei <br>Come io vorrei]]></content><category term="Ligabue" label="Ligabue"/><category term="La Vita Facile" label="La Vita Facile"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Walwin/Let_You_Go/</id><title>Walwin - Let You Go - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:44:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:44:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Walwin/Let_You_Go/" title="Walwin - Let You Go - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This morning I woke up dying to kiss you <br>Your makeup on my pillow's making me miss you <br>I went from your bae to an ex in 4 hours or less <br>There goes another one I couldn't get right <br>But I won't let you go without a fight <br><br>I won't let, won't let you go <br>My eyes are red and I'm a mess <br>But I won't let you go without a fight <br><br>Well I guess my luck stopped from trying to call your bluff <br>But you know what you're like when you drink, yeah - you get rough <br>Pulling my hair, mouthing off about something that I'd done <br>No girl I'm not having fun, but that don't mean that I'm gonna run <br><br>But you ain't home tonight but I won't let you go without a fight <br><br>I won't let, won't let you go <br>My eyes are red and I'm a mess <br>But I won't let you go without a fight <br><br>I moved in with a stranger <br>You feel in love with a heel <br>My friends don't like you, but my heart wants you <br>Don't you know I'm thinking 'bout you day and night <br>So I won't let you go without a fight]]></content><category term="Walwin" label="Walwin"/><category term="Let You Go" label="Let You Go"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/High_Valley/Memory_Makin/</id><title>High_Valley - Memory Makin` - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:44:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:44:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/High_Valley/Memory_Makin/" title="High_Valley - Memory Makin` - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I will take your hands, put it in mine <br>Take that key, put it in drive <br>Drive all night, after no man's land <br>Draw our names, in the desert sand <br><br>No reservation <br>No no hesitation <br>Just you and me, memory makin' <br><br>Do you believe that, this ain't meant to be <br>Find all this feeling, confounded with me <br>We're dreaming, we're chasing <br>Memory makin' <br><br>Tonight's gonna be a , black and white <br>Burning so beautiful in my mind <br>So craziness <br>Gonna walk so badly, that it hurts <br><br>Baby, we're timings <br>You know, when we're timeless <br>Our hearts are waiting, on memory makin' <br><br>Do you believe that, this ain't meant to be <br>Find all this feeling, confounded with me <br>We're dreaming, we're chasing <br>Memory makin' <br><br>Bottle up the moment <br>Living like a <br>Writing our story <br>Yeah ehh, yea ehh <br>Bottle up the moment <br>Living like a <br>Writing our story <br>Yeah ehh, yea ehh <br><br>Do you believe that, this ain't meant to be <br>Find all this feeling, confounded with me <br>We're dreaming, we're chasing <br>Memory makin']]></content><category term="High Valley" label="High Valley"/><category term="Memory Makin`" label="Memory Makin`"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/High_Valley/Make_You_Mine/</id><title>High_Valley - Make You Mine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:44:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:44:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/High_Valley/Make_You_Mine/" title="High_Valley - Make You Mine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You were made to shine under Southern stars <br>Pure as the mountain rain <br>You're the love songs pouring out of this guitar <br>Sweeter than sugarcane <br><br>You've got my heart wrapped up like it's down in the holler <br>Covered in kudzu vines <br>When the night feels right I'm gonna come a callin' <br>I'm gonna make you mine <br><br>You're hallelujah, Sunday morning <br>All I've ever needed, wanted <br>Underneath this pale moon sky <br>I'm gonna make you mine <br>Yeah, I'm gonna make you mine <br><br>Gonna take you slow dancing by the water <br>I just wanna hold you tight <br>I'm in love with you so, miner's daughter <br>And I'm gonna make you mine <br><br>You're hallelujah, Sunday morning <br>All I've ever needed, wanted <br>Underneath this pale moon sky <br>I'm gonna make you mine <br>Yeah, I'm gonna make you mine <br><br>You're hallelujah, Sunday morning <br>All I've ever needed, wanted <br>Underneath this pale moon sky <br>I'm gonna make you mine <br><br>You're hallelujah, Sunday morning <br>All I've ever needed, wanted <br>Underneath this pale moon sky <br>I'm gonna make you mine <br>Yeah, I'm gonna make you mine <br><br>You were made to shine under Southern stars <br>In my arms tonight <br>I can feel the beating of your heart <br>I'm gonna make you mine]]></content><category term="High Valley" label="High Valley"/><category term="Make You Mine" label="Make You Mine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/High_Valley/I_Aint_Changin/</id><title>High_Valley - I Ain`t Changin` - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:44:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:44:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/High_Valley/I_Aint_Changin/" title="High_Valley - I Ain`t Changin` - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I grew up on the seat of a John Deere tractor bailing hay <br>Now I'm standing in the middle of a high rise city on a subway train <br>I'm sure jaws are dropping, small town talking <br>Let 'em talk away, I don't care, I don't care <br><br>I'm still gonna be the reckless wheel that kicks up all that gravel <br>I can feel the roots underneath these boots when I walk the road less traveled <br>I'm still the son of the back in them good old days <br>Yeah, what you see is what you get, no matter what they say <br>I ain't changing a letter of my last name <br>The way I talk or the way I pray <br>Carve the stone like a tattoo that ain't fading <br>I ain't changing, I ain't changing <br><br>I'm still make some racket, leather jacket, hometown proud <br>I'm still say the blessing, learn your lesson, watch your mouth <br>I packed all that up in the bed of my truck when I hit the road <br>No matter where I go, no matter where I go <br><br>I'm still gonna be the reckless wheel that kicks up all that gravel <br>I can feel the roots underneath these boots when I walk the road less traveled <br>I'm still the son of the back in them good old days <br>Yeah, what you see is what you get, no matter what they say <br>I ain't changing a letter of my last name <br>The way I talk or the way I pray <br>Carve the stone like a tattoo that ain't fading <br>I ain't changing <br><br>I like my tough love, red blood rebel heart that beats <br>Like the words in those old hymns that we used to sing <br>I ain't changing <br><br>I'm still gonna be the reckless wheel that kicks up all that gravel <br>I can feel the roots underneath these boots when I walk the road less traveled <br>I'm still the son of the back in them good old days <br>Yeah, what you see is what you get, no matter what they say <br>I ain't changing a letter of my last name <br>The way I talk or the way I pray <br>Carve the stone like a tattoo that ain't fading <br>I ain't changing, I ain't changing]]></content><category term="High Valley" label="High Valley"/><category term="I Ain`t Changin`" label="I Ain`t Changin`"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/High_Valley/Shes_With_Me/</id><title>High_Valley - She`s With Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:44:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:44:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/High_Valley/Shes_With_Me/" title="High_Valley - She`s With Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When the devil's knocking at my door <br>When I'm broken and I'm battle worn <br>Down in the valley, on my knees <br>Yea she's, yea she's with me <br><br>Ain't she amazing, amazing, out of my league <br>And ain't it crazy, crazy, she happened to me <br>She calls me baby, baby, hard to believe <br>That she's, yea she's with me <br><br>When my dreams are running out of road <br>And the world around me's turning cold <br>Anyone else would up and leave <br>But she's, yea she's with me <br><br>Ain't she amazing, amazing, out of my league <br>And ain't it crazy, crazy, she happened to me <br>She calls me baby, baby, hard to believe <br>That she's, yea she's with me <br><br>Top of the mountain and all the way down <br>When I'm lost and when I'm found <br>In the day, in the light, in the dark of the night <br>When it all goes wrong, when it all goes right <br>Whoa oh, I don't know what I'd do without her <br>Whoa oh, she's gotta know I'm all about her <br><br>She's amazing, amazing <br>Ain't she amazing, amazing <br><br>Ain't she amazing, amazing, out of my league <br>And ain't it crazy, crazy, she happened to me <br>She calls me baby, baby, hard to believe <br>That she's, yea she's with me <br><br>Ain't she amazing, amazing That girl, she's out of my league <br>And ain't it crazy, crazy, she happened to me <br>She calls me baby, baby, hard to believe <br>That she's, yea she's with me <br>That she's, yea she's with me <br><br>Top of the mountain and all the way down <br>When I'm lost and when I'm found <br>In the day, in the light, in the dark of the night <br>When it all goes wrong, when it all goes right <br>x2]]></content><category term="High Valley" label="High Valley"/><category term="She`s With Me" label="She`s With Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Makari/Melt/</id><title>Makari - Melt - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:56:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:56:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Makari/Melt/" title="Makari - Melt - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Leave me right here if you wanna <br>I would never weigh you down <br><br>Take all your time and go wander <br>But don't let them water you down <br><br>Ooo <br>So blue <br>Are you <br><br>Are you holding up just fine <br>In whichever city it is tonight <br>That gets the pleasure of <br>Your footsteps <br>Kissing the pavement <br>And your laughter ringing out <br><br>Melt like the ice in the summer <br>And you won't be sticking around <br><br>But for me there could be no other <br>I want you while I'm on the ground <br><br>Are you <br>Holding out like I am <br>For something worth seeing through <br><br>Are you holding up just fine <br>In whichever city it is tonight <br>That gets the pleasure of <br>Your footsteps <br>Kissing the pavement <br>And your laughter ringing out <br><br>I hope they don't change <br>Your mind <br>To make you feel wrong when <br>You know you're right <br>'Cause I'll be on your side <br>I could never forget <br>The way you made me feel so light <br><br>Are you always gonna be <br>The same person I met on the lawn <br><br>We spilled our guts <br>And your hair was long <br>And black just like the shadows <br>Of trees <br>Reaching for our arms <br><br>Are you holding up just fine <br>In whichever city it is tonight <br>That gets the pleasure of <br>Your footsteps <br>Kissing the pavement <br>And your laughter ringing out <br><br>I hope they don't change <br>Your mind <br>To make you feel wrong when <br>You know you're right <br>'Cause I'll be on your side <br>I could never forget <br>The way you made me feel so light]]></content><category term="Makari" label="Makari"/><category term="Melt" label="Melt"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan_Kinder/Close/</id><title>Ryan_Kinder - Close - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T08:56:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T08:56:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan_Kinder/Close/" title="Ryan_Kinder - Close - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Close <br>Like a little strap <br>To your shoulder <br>Close <br>Like you been <br>Since you slid over <br><br>Close <br>Like that sun is <br>To going down <br>That's what I wanna be now <br>Close, you know <br><br>Baby, we can fly high <br>Touching heaven tonight <br>Take it to a place we never been <br>Baby, we can chance it <br>First kiss, landed <br>Diving off the edge <br>Baby, going all in <br>Let it go where it wants to go <br>Yeah, we might not fall in love <br>But we can sure come close <br>We can sure come close, yeah <br><br>Close <br>Yeah, it ain't even <br>Close to midnight <br>Close <br>Don't even close your eyes <br><br>Close <br>Like your lips should be to mine <br>Ain't nothing quite like <br>Close, you know <br><br>Baby, we can fly high <br>Touching heaven tonight <br>Take it to a place we never been <br>Baby, we can chance it <br>First kiss, landed <br>Diving off the edge <br>Baby, going all in <br>Let it go where it wants to go <br>Yeah, we might not fall in love <br>But we can sure come close <br>We can sure come close <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah <br><br>Let it go where it wants to go <br>We might not fall in love <br>But baby we can fly high <br><br>And take it to a place we never been <br>Baby, we can chance it <br>First kiss, landed <br>Diving off the edge <br>Baby, going all in <br>Let it go where it wants to go <br>Yeah, we might not fall in love <br>But we can sure come close <br>We can sure come close, yeah <br><br>Oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo]]></content><category term="Ryan Kinder" label="Ryan Kinder"/><category term="Close" label="Close"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이달의_소녀/다녀가요_현진/</id><title>이달의_소녀 - 다녀가요 (현진) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:02:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:02:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%AC%EC%9D%98_%EC%86%8C%EB%85%80/%EB%8B%A4%EB%85%80%EA%B0%80%EC%9A%94_%ED%98%84%EC%A7%84/" title="이달의_소녀 - 다녀가요 (현진) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘도 어김없이 오게 되죠 <br>마주치면 어떡해 <br>조심스럽게 기다리고 있죠 <br>아무것도 바라는 건 없죠 <br>멍하니 멍하니 <br>바라만 보다가 가요 <br>멀리서 멀리서 나만 봤음 해요 <br>Hey you 내 맘 알고 있나요 <br>요즘 나 매일 어린아이 같이 <br>몰래 숨어 바라보죠 <br>You 내 말 듣고 있나요 <br>아직 나 용기나질 않아요 <br>말없이 또 다녀가요 <br>눈을 감아봐도 생각이 나죠 <br>이제 어떡하나요 <br>모두들 나를 바보 같다지만 <br>아무것도 바라는 건 없죠 <br>Hey you 내 맘 알고 있나요 <br>요즘 나 매일 어린아이 같이 <br>몰래 숨어 바라보죠 <br>You 내 말 듣고 있나요 <br>아직 나 용기나질 않아요 <br>말없이 또 다녀가요 <br>말을 하지 그래 절대 모르고 있죠 <br>놓치면 안돼 나 어때요 <br>너무 흔한 말 나오지 않아요 <br>오늘도 멍하니 <br>바라만 보다가 가요 <br>멀리서 멀리서 나만 봤음 해요 <br>Hey you 내 맘 알고 있나요 <br>요즘 나 자꾸 어린아이 같이 <br>훔쳐 보곤 달아나죠 <br>You 내 말이 들리나요 <br>아직 나 용기나질 않아서 <br>말없이 또 다녀가요 <br>]]></content><category term="이달의 소녀" label="이달의 소녀"/><category term="다녀가요 (현진)" label="다녀가요 (현진)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이달의_소녀/Ill_Be_There_희진_현진/</id><title>이달의_소녀 - I`ll Be There (희진, 현진) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:02:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:02:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%AC%EC%9D%98_%EC%86%8C%EB%85%80/Ill_Be_There_%ED%9D%AC%EC%A7%84_%ED%98%84%EC%A7%84/" title="이달의_소녀 - I`ll Be There (희진, 현진) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[망설이지마 Boy <br>네 눈빛이 Shake Shake <br>두근두근 대는 Girl <br>기분 좋은 Feeling <br>주저하지 말고 <br>내게 다가와줘 <br>니가 웃어주면 <br>Boy you rock my world <br>You rock me baby <br>핑크빛 World 그대와 나 <br>햇살이 물든 <br>아름다운 이곳에 <br>설레임 가득 안고 <br>바람이 부는 대로 <br>Boy you just give me your love <br>나와 함께 <br>Can you feel <br>24/7 I’ll be there <br>매일 같은 Day I’ll be there <br>같아지는 맘에 우리 I`ll be there <br>365 I’ll be there <br>시간 속에 I’ll be there <br>함께하는 우리 I`ll be there <br>Day Day 매일 새롭게 <br>기분 좋은 설레임 <br>네 눈에 보여줄래 I`ll be there <br>우리 앞에 펼쳐진 <br>시간 속의 Real slow <br>그곳에 멈춰진 <br>너와 나의 세상 <br>빙빙 돌아온 <br>꿈같았던 시간이 <br>지금 내 눈앞에 <br>Make me feel so high <br>All the time <br>핑크 빛 World 그대와 나 <br>햇살이 물든 <br>아름다운 이곳에 <br>설레임 가득 안고 <br>바람이 부는 대로 <br>Boy you just give me your love <br>나와 함께 Can you feel <br>24/7 I’ll be there <br>매일 같은 day I’ll be there <br>같아지는 맘에 우리 I`ll be there <br>365 I’ll be there <br>시간 속에 I’ll be there <br>함께하는 우리 I`ll be there <br>Day Day 매일 새롭게 <br>기분 좋은 설레임 <br>네 눈에 보여줄래 <br>I`ll be there <br>Ooh baby 우릴 비추는 Sunlight <br>I’ll be everything you need <br>I’ll be everything you need <br>Ooh baby 두근거리는 Moonlight <br>I’ll be everything you need <br>24/7 I’ll be there <br>매일 같은 day I’ll be there <br>같아지는 맘에 우리 I`ll be there <br>365 I’ll be there <br>시간 속에 I’ll be there <br>함께하는 우리 I`ll be there <br>24/7 I’ll be there <br>매일 같은 day I’ll be there <br>같아지는 맘에 우리 <br>I`ll be there <br>365 I’ll be there <br>시간 속에 I’ll be there <br>함께하는 우리 I`ll be there <br>]]></content><category term="이달의 소녀" label="이달의 소녀"/><category term="I`ll Be There (희진, 현진)" label="I`ll Be There (희진, 현진)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zara_Larsson/I_Would_Like/</id><title>Zara_Larsson - I Would Like - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:05:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:05:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zara_Larsson/I_Would_Like/" title="Zara_Larsson - I Would Like - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I didn't know that <br>I could want you so deep <br>As when I saw you <br>with someone who is not me <br>You got me playing <br>in a game that ain't fair <br>But you're taking me there <br>yeah you're taking me there <br>I can't help myself <br>it's human nature human nature <br>Who's to say what's meant to be <br>Why can't we be <br>on our worst behaviour <br>worst behaviour <br>When it all comes naturally <br>I would like to get to know you baby <br>Like to get under your sexy body <br>I would like to get to know you baby <br>Like to get under your sexy body <br>Under your sexy body oh <br>Under your sexy body oh <br>Under your sexy body <br>What would you do <br>the way you hold it like that <br>Looking at me to see <br>if I'm the get-back <br>Me and you boy <br>we gon' work tonight <br>to leave to leave <br>Yeah you're leaving with me <br>leaving with me <br>leaving with me <br>I can't help myself <br>it's human nature human nature <br>Who's to say what's meant to be <br>Why can't we be on <br>our worst behaviour <br>worst behaviour <br>When it all comes naturally <br>I would like to get to know you baby <br>Like to get under your sexy body <br>I would like to get to know you baby <br>Like to get under your sexy body <br>Under your sexy body <br>na na na na na na <br>Under your sexy body <br>I would like to get to know you baby <br>Like to get under your sexy body <br>Come take me under now <br>na na na na na na <br>Go on and go there <br>na na na na na na <br>Come take me under now <br>na na na na na na <br>Go on and go there <br>na na na na na na <br>I would like to get to know you baby <br>Like to get under your sexy body <br>I would like to get to know you baby <br>Like to get under your sexy body <br>I would like to get to know you baby <br>Like to get under your sexy body <br>I would like to get to know you baby <br>Like to get under your sexy body <br>Come take me under now <br>na na na na na na <br>Go on and go there <br>na na na na na na <br>Come take me under now <br>na na na na na na <br>Go on and go there <br>na na na na na na <br>]]></content><category term="Zara Larsson" label="Zara Larsson"/><category term="I Would Like" label="I Would Like"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/킬라그램_KILLAGRAMZ/Birthday_Feat_KidKat_Clean_Ver/</id><title>킬라그램_KILLAGRAMZ - Birthday (Feat. KidKat) (Clean Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:06:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:06:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%82%AC%EB%9D%BC%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%A8_KILLAGRAMZ/Birthday_Feat_KidKat_Clean_Ver/" title="킬라그램_KILLAGRAMZ - Birthday (Feat. KidKat) (Clean Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's my birthday <br>get turnt in the worst way <br>이런 분위기 fut that <br>It's my birthday <br>It's fire in the worst way <br>이런 느낌 I fuzz that <br>It's my birthday <br>KillahGramz pop pompeii <br>go and add some more of that <br>It's my birthday <br>23 like jordan <br>KillaGramz shit perfect <br>It's ma birthday <br>It's ma birthday ma birthday <br>오늘 분위기 좆 됨 <br>개쩔탱 기분 날아 높게 <br>따라 흔드는 고개 <br>고개 끄떡이는 리듬에 맞춰 drum bass <br>소리 쿵쿵 perfect <br>champagne pop pop pop pop <br>celebrate my errday <br>my errday <br>ahhh birthday <br>KillahGramz kill all day <br>Killin grams till the mornin' <br>oh shit make it heavyrain on checks <br>can I kill it till the world end <br>where the po at <br>우린 하고 싶은거 해 <br>하고 싶은거 하면서 부러움을 사 <br>till the mall end <br>we ballin MJ 23 y o flyin high 저 멀리 <br>말 안해도 알어 <br>오늘 밤을 새워 여긴 뜨거워 <br>hot weather like a fire weapon <br>reppin westside for the ever <br>이런 vibe 못 배워 <br>I'm just chilllin with this feelin <br>하늘 자유 배영 <br>It's my birthday <br>it's fire in the worst way <br>이런 분위기 좆 됨 <br>It's my birthday <br>it's fire in the worst way <br>이런 느낌 I fuck that <br>It's my birthday <br>KillahGramz pop pompeii <br>go and add some more of that <br>It's my birthday <br>23 like jordan <br>KillahGramz shit perfect <br>It's Ma Birthday It's Ma Birthday <br>It's Ma Birthday Ma Birthday <br>Ma Birthday Ma Birthday <br>Ma Birthday Ma Birthday <br>Oooh aite I do what I like <br>너희들은 저 멀리서 바라봐 <br>how we party like part of life is a <br>cop car livin fast no po po in <br>our pop pop 내려 <br>my life is a movie this <br>the fuckin intro to the birthday <br>of the true beast <br>이건 이제 겨우 beginnin 혹은 준비 <br>and I'll prove it <br>Killin beats like a murder freak <br>Po Poetic Minds fuckin murder beats <br>we on this shit like <br>it's a birthday errday <br>생일 케잌 매일 썰었지 <br>KillahGramz Popeye <br>bang bang bang bang <br>I'm up in this shit just doin my thang <br>나는 매일매일이 다 꿈같애 <br>이런 매일매일이 <br>KillahGramz birthday birthday <br>말 안해도 알어 <br>오늘 밤을 새워 여긴 뜨거워 <br>hot weather like a fire weapon <br>reppin westside for the ever <br>이런 vibe 못 배워 <br>I'm just chilllin with this feelin <br>하늘 자유 배영 <br>It's my birthday <br>Let's fuck in the worst way <br>이런 분위기 fuck that <br>It's my birthday <br>Let's fuck in the worst way <br>이런 느낌들 fuck that <br>It's my birthday <br>KillahGramz pop pompeii <br>go and add some more of that <br>It's my birthday <br>23 like jordan <br>KillaGramz shit perfect <br>It's Ma Birthday It's Ma Birthday <br>It's Ma Birthday Ma Birthday <br>Ma Birthday Ma Birthday <br>Ma Birthday Ma Birthday <br>]]></content><category term="킬라그램 (KILLAGRAMZ)" label="킬라그램 (KILLAGRAMZ)"/><category term="Birthday (Feat. KidKat) (Clean Ver.)" label="Birthday (Feat. KidKat) (Clean Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이건율/This_is_the_small_life_Feat_김지수/</id><title>이건율 - This is the small life (Feat. 김지수) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:07:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:07:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EA%B1%B4%EC%9C%A8/This_is_the_small_life_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%80%EC%88%98/" title="이건율 - This is the small life (Feat. 김지수) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가벼운 설레임 달콤한 불빛 <br>소소한 사람들 속 <br>노멀한 카페 마주앉아 <br>오고가는 life story <br>음 가볍게 뿌려준 perfume <br>살짝 걸친 my favorite fancy coat <br>내 입가엔 little smile <br>웃음 짓는 life story <br>내 안에 번지는 <br>so sweet한 향기와 <br>너의 눈에 담겨진 <br>oh 따스함까지 yeah <br>This is the small life <br>난 너를 미소짓게 <br>This is the small life <br>넌 나를 설레이게 <br>This is the small life <br>너와 나를 향기롭게 <br>This is the small life <br>small life <br>내게만 이끌리는 순간 <br>너만이 가득한 이 공간 <br>다른 모든게 특별하진 않아도 <br>You are my wonder story <br>내 안에 번지는 <br>so sweet한 향기와 <br>너의 눈에 담겨진 <br>oh 따스함까지 yeah <br>This is the small life <br>난 너를 미소짓게 <br>This is the small life <br>넌 나를 설레이게 <br>This is the small life <br>너와 나를 향기롭게 <br>This is the small life <br>small life <br>커다란 삶도 바라고 바래 <br>I wanna super life <br>작은 하루도 너만 있으면 <br>내겐 충분한 걸 <br>This is the small life <br>난 너를 미소짓게 <br>This is the small life <br>넌 나를 설레이게 <br>This is the small life <br>너와 나를 향기롭게 <br>This is the small life <br>small life <br>This is the small life <br>oh This is the small life <br>This is the small life <br>This is the small life <br>This is the small life <br>This is the small life <br>This is the small life <br>small life <br>]]></content><category term="이건율" label="이건율"/><category term="This is the small life (Feat. 김지수)" label="This is the small life (Feat. 김지수)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이건율/단_한번_Prod_by_노을_전우성/</id><title>이건율 - 단 한번 (Prod. by 노을 전우성) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:07:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:07:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EA%B1%B4%EC%9C%A8/%EB%8B%A8_%ED%95%9C%EB%B2%88_Prod_by_%EB%85%B8%EC%9D%84_%EC%A0%84%EC%9A%B0%EC%84%B1/" title="이건율 - 단 한번 (Prod. by 노을 전우성) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잘 지내니 <br>어디 아프진 않고 <br>오늘따라 너의 생각에 <br>안부를 묻게 돼 <br>기억나니 별거 <br>아닌 일에도 <br>함께 웃으며 항상 <br>즐거워 하던 너 <br>해맑게 웃던 너의 <br>모습을 기억해 <br>내게로 안겨 행복해 하던 <br>너를 기억해 <br>단 한번 단 하루만 <br>내게 닿으려는 마음이 <br>나의 욕심인건지 <br>바라고 바래도 <br>또 다시 바래보는 <br>나의 맘이 너에게 닿기를 <br>생각나니 <br>내 작은 버릇조차 <br>함께하자며 항상 <br>즐거워 하던 너 <br>해맑게 웃던 너의 <br>모습을 기억해 <br>내게로 안겨 행복해 하던 <br>너를 기억해 <br>단 한번 단 하루만 <br>내게 닿으려는 마음이 <br>나의 욕심인건지 <br>바라고 바래도 <br>또 다시 바래보는 <br>나의 맘이 너에게 닿기를 <br>너의 맘을 스쳐지나가 <br>나의 맘이 다 바래진대도 <br>단 한번 단 하루만 <br>내게 닿으려는 마음이 <br>나의 욕심인건지 <br>바라고 바래도 <br>또 다시 바래보는 <br>나의 맘이 너에게 닿기를 <br>나의 맘이 너에게 닿기를 <br>]]></content><category term="이건율" label="이건율"/><category term="단 한번 (Prod. by 노을 전우성)" label="단 한번 (Prod. by 노을 전우성)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이건율/내게_와줘/</id><title>이건율 - 내게 와줘 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:07:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:07:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EA%B1%B4%EC%9C%A8/%EB%82%B4%EA%B2%8C_%EC%99%80%EC%A4%98/" title="이건율 - 내게 와줘 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[두 눈을 감고 가만히 그대로 <br>내 안에 담긴 너를 그려봐 <br>아무 말 없는 내 안의 너에게 <br>살며시 조금 다가가 보려 해 <br>따스한 온기 해맑은 미소 <br>아직 내 맘 안에 선명한데 <br>내게 와줘 너무 멀지 않다면 <br>다시 한 번 너를 내게 담도록 <br>달이 지고 별이 되는 순간을 담아 <br>네게 말할게 와줘 <br>따스한 온기 해맑은 미소 <br>아직 내 맘 안에 선명한데 <br>내게 와줘 너무 멀지 않다면 <br>다시 한 번 너를 내게 담도록 <br>달이 지고 별이 되는 순간을 담아 <br>네게 말할게 와줘 <br>너무 서두르진 않을게 <br>넌 언제나 내 안에 있으니 <br>내게 와줘 너무 멀지 않다면 <br>다시 한 번 너를 내게 담도록 <br>달이 지고 별이 되는 순간을 담아 <br>네게 말할게 와줘 <br>내게 와줘 너무 멀지 않다면 <br>다시 한 번 너를 내게 담도록 <br>달이 지고 별이 되는 순간을 담아 <br>네게 말할게 와줘 <br>네게 말할게 와줘 <br>]]></content><category term="이건율" label="이건율"/><category term="내게 와줘" label="내게 와줘"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/황영원/잠시후면/</id><title>황영원 - 잠시후면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:08:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:08:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%A9%EC%98%81%EC%9B%90/%EC%9E%A0%EC%8B%9C%ED%9B%84%EB%A9%B4/" title="황영원 - 잠시후면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잠시후면 그대와 사랑했던 <br>그순간의 이별을 <br>받아들여야 하는데 <br>어떡하면 어떡해야 <br>무슨 말을 할지 <br>술잔을 부등키고 <br>오늘 하루를 지샌다 <br>잠시후면 그대와 <br>사랑했던 그순간을 <br>이제는 떠나 보내야 하는데 <br>어떡하면 어떡해야 <br>너의 한마디를 들을 수 있을까 <br>들어야만 하는건가 <br>떠나야 한단 사실을 알고 있는데 <br>잠시후면 그 잠시 후가 된다면 <br>이제 나는 너와는 없던 사이고 <br>기다림 <br>기다림일 수 없는 기다림에 <br>술잔을 부등키고 <br>오늘 하루도 지샌다 <br>너의 그 한마디 싫다 잠시후의 <br>어떡하면 어떡해야 <br>너의 한마디를 들을 수 있을까 <br>들어야만 하는건가 <br>이제 떠나야 한단 <br>사실을 알고 있는데 <br>잠시후면 그 잠시 후가 된다면 <br>이제 나는 너와는 없던 사이고 <br>기다림 <br>기다림일 수 없는 기다림에 <br>술잔을 부등키고 <br>오늘 하루도 지샌다 <br>너의 그 한마디 싫다 잠시후의 <br>잠시후면 그대와 나는 <br>어떤 사이가 되는 걸까 <br>]]></content><category term="황영원" label="황영원"/><category term="잠시후면" label="잠시후면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/황영원/오늘도_외쳐본다/</id><title>황영원 - 오늘도 외쳐본다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:08:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:08:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%A9%EC%98%81%EC%9B%90/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98%EB%8F%84_%EC%99%B8%EC%B3%90%EB%B3%B8%EB%8B%A4/" title="황영원 - 오늘도 외쳐본다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑해 오늘도 외쳐본다 <br>사랑해 이제는 외쳐본다 <br>사랑한단 말도 못하고 <br>난 그대로 헤어졌다 <br>사랑한단 말도 못하고 <br>그대로 헤어졌다 <br>나의 사랑 살다보니 <br>난 그대로 헤어졌다 <br>사랑한단 말도 못하고 <br>그대로 헤어졌다 <br>사랑해 오늘도 외쳐본다 <br>사랑해 이제는 외쳐본다 <br>소꿉친구 살다보니 <br>난 그대로 헤어졌다 <br>사랑한단 말도 못하고 <br>그대로 헤어졌다 <br>사랑해 오늘도 외쳐본다 <br>사랑해 이제는 외쳐본다 <br>우리 엄마 살다보니 <br>난 그대로 헤어졌다 <br>사랑한단 말도 못하고 <br>그대로 헤어졌다 <br>사랑해 오늘도 외쳐본다 <br>사랑해 이제는 외쳐본다 <br>사랑해 사랑해 오늘도 외쳐본다 <br>]]></content><category term="황영원" label="황영원"/><category term="오늘도 외쳐본다" label="오늘도 외쳐본다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/황영원/녹음2/</id><title>황영원 - 녹음2 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:08:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:08:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%A9%EC%98%81%EC%9B%90/%EB%85%B9%EC%9D%8C2/" title="황영원 - 녹음2 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 있잖아 일상인 듯 <br>스쳐가는 연인처럼 연인처럼 <br>연인처럼 너를 생각했나봐 <br>있자나 왜 그런지 <br>왜 그런지 미안하다 미안하다 <br>미안하단 생각뿐 <br>어쩌다 니 생각이 나면 <br>하루를 잠 못 이루고 <br>어쩌다 마주칠 일 없을까 <br>매일밤 서성였는데 <br>너 기억나니 그날 밤은 <br>하루지만 연인처럼 연인처럼 <br>연인처럼 우리 지세웠는데 <br>있자나 어떡하면 <br>어떡하면 미안하다 미안하다 <br>미안하단 생각뿐 <br>어쩌다 니 생각이 나면 <br>하루를 잠 못 이루고 <br>어쩌다 마주칠 일 없을까 <br>매일밤 서성였는데 <br>단 한번 만날수 있다면 <br>너에게 해줄말이 <br>정말 있는데 <br>단 한번 만날수 있다면 <br>너에게 해줄말이 <br>정말 있는데 <br>이제 그럴 일 있을 순 없나보다 <br>이제 그럴 일 있을 순 없나보다 <br>이제 그럴 일 있을 순 없나보다 <br>]]></content><category term="황영원" label="황영원"/><category term="녹음2" label="녹음2"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/황영원/녹음1/</id><title>황영원 - 녹음1 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:08:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:08:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%A9%EC%98%81%EC%9B%90/%EB%85%B9%EC%9D%8C1/" title="황영원 - 녹음1 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[수많은 인연 중에 <br>그댈 만난건 우연 일지라도 <br>그대를 만났다는 것 <br>우연이 아닐 인연이라 생각하오 <br>수많은 시간 중에 <br>그댈 만난건 한 순간 일지라도 <br>그대와 함께 할 지금 이 순간이 <br>이대로 멈추지 말아주오 <br>그대가 울지도 몰라요 <br>앞으로 다가올 시간 중에 <br>언젠가 어떤 날은 <br>슬플지도 모르죠 <br>그래도 함께 걸어가줘요 <br>수많은 인연중에 <br>그댈 만난건 우연일 지라도 <br>그대를 만났다는 것 <br>우연이 아닐 인연이라 생각하오 <br>수많은 시간중에 <br>그댈 만난건 한순간 일지라도 <br>그대와 함께할 이 순간이 <br>이대로 멈추지 말아주오 <br>그대여 함께 걸어가줘요 <br>음 음 음 음 <br>그대여 함께 걸어가줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="황영원" label="황영원"/><category term="녹음1" label="녹음1"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/황영원/그거알아요/</id><title>황영원 - 그거알아요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:08:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:08:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%A9%EC%98%81%EC%9B%90/%EA%B7%B8%EA%B1%B0%EC%95%8C%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94/" title="황영원 - 그거알아요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그거 알아요 <br>내가 널 처음 봤을 때 <br>보름달 지금은 <br>초승달이 보일듯 말듯 <br>그땐 좀 더웠더랬죠 <br>태풍도 지나 <br>벌써 낙옆이 <br>떨어져 있네요 <br>시간이 언제 간지 <br>나도 모르게 <br>나도 모르게 <br>당신께 반해 <br>잘될꺼라 바라지 않아요 <br>그저 말 한번 건네고 싶네요 <br>이게 사랑은 아니겠지만 <br>그저 말 한번 건네고 싶네요 <br>그거 알아요 <br>내가 널 처음 봤을 때 <br>택시를 잡고 <br>배웅도 해주고 <br>다음날에 만나 <br>예약된 카페에 가서 <br>멋있는 척 주문을 하고 <br>너에게 맘 고백해 <br>시간이 언제간지 <br>너도 모르게 <br>너도 모르게 <br>나에게 반했으면 <br>잘될꺼라 바라지 않아요 <br>그저 말 한번 건네고 싶네요 <br>이게 사랑은 아니겠지만 <br>그저 말 한번 건네고 싶네요 <br>]]></content><category term="황영원" label="황영원"/><category term="그거알아요" label="그거알아요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/황영원/만약에/</id><title>황영원 - 만약에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:08:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:08:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%A9%EC%98%81%EC%9B%90/%EB%A7%8C%EC%95%BD%EC%97%90/" title="황영원 - 만약에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[만약에 사랑이었다면 <br>만약에 사랑한다 말했다면 <br>만약에 사랑이 아니었다면 <br>잘됐을까 잘됐을까 <br>만약에 스쳐지나쳤다면 <br>만약에 그 시간이 아니라면 <br>만약에 사랑을 감췄었다면 <br>잘됐을까 잘됐을까 <br>만약에 사랑일지 모른 만약에 <br>너에게 상처 냈을지도 모르고 <br>감췄던 마음 그대로 묻어두고 <br>오지않을 만약을 기약한다 <br>만약에 사랑일지 모른 만약에 <br>너에게 상처 냈을지도 모르고 <br>감췄던 마음 그대로 묻어두고 <br>오지않을 만약을 기약한다 <br>만약에 <br>만약에 <br>만약에 <br>]]></content><category term="황영원" label="황영원"/><category term="만약에" label="만약에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/황영원/좋다/</id><title>황영원 - 좋다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:08:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:08:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%A9%EC%98%81%EC%9B%90/%EC%A2%8B%EB%8B%A4/" title="황영원 - 좋다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[유난히 비가 없던 <br>어느 여름날 <br>내게 다가왔지 <br>수줍은 보조개 피우며 <br>해맑게 웃으며 <br>내게 기쁨을 주네 <br>돌담길 따라 <br>달동네 계단 따라 <br>두손을 포개고 <br>너와 얘기 하는게 <br>돌담길 따라 <br>달동네 계단 따라 <br>두손을 포개고 <br>너와 얘기 하는게 좋다 <br>좋다 <br>]]></content><category term="황영원" label="황영원"/><category term="좋다" label="좋다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nelly_Furtado/Behind_Your_Back/</id><title>Nelly_Furtado - Behind Your Back - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nelly_Furtado/Behind_Your_Back/" title="Nelly_Furtado - Behind Your Back - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been talking about you <br>Behind your back <br>I've been telling people that I've heard things <br>If they ask <br>If we ease up and burning up <br>Well, it's a fact <br>I've been talking about you <br>Every chance I had <br><br>Is nothing bad, is all I have <br>It's just a chance to say your name, baby <br>Is nothing bad, is just a chance <br>Wanna talk about you <br>Behind your back <br><br>I've been talking about you <br>Behind your back <br>I know that talking is cheap <br>But baby, do the math <br>You were one in a million <br>And my whole heart's in half <br>Have is never conscious, it's a word I have <br><br>I've been telling all my stories to anyone that asks <br>I've been serving them up in a half empty glass <br>Don't go thinking I've lost all my class <br>When I'm talking about you <br><br>Is nothing bad, is all I have <br>It's just a chance to say your name, baby <br>Is nothing bad, is just a chance <br>Wanna talk about you <br>Behind your back <br><br>Is nothing bad, is all I have <br>It's just a chance to say your name <br>Again, baby, just a chance <br>It's all I have <br>Wanna talk about you <br>Behind your back <br>No, is nothing bad <br>Is all I have <br>I'm hoping you'd give me just a chance <br>If you came back <br>Another chance <br>To stop taking about you <br>Behind your back]]></content><category term="Nelly Furtado" label="Nelly Furtado"/><category term="Behind Your Back" label="Behind Your Back"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lo_Moon/Loveless_Edit/</id><title>Lo_Moon - Loveless (Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lo_Moon/Loveless_Edit/" title="Lo_Moon - Loveless (Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Crosses in the distance bells ring fast <br>Loveless in our shelter time will pass <br>Would you take a chance on us <br>Could you take a chance on us <br><br>Call out to the lonely with regrets <br>Loveless is your answer time will pass <br>Couldn't take a chance on us <br>Couldn't take a chance on us <br><br>Take my hand <br>In belief we trace our steps <br>Understand <br>No relief in silhouettes <br><br>Battled myself so many times <br>What I was isn't what I want now <br>We can seek denial and search for miles <br><br>Blessed love the love I need <br>Rolling drums the loveless bleed <br><br>Take my hand <br>In belief we trace our steps <br>Understand <br>No relief in silhouettes]]></content><category term="Lo Moon" label="Lo Moon"/><category term="Loveless (Edit)" label="Loveless (Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LeAnn_Rimes/The_Story/</id><title>LeAnn_Rimes - The Story - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LeAnn_Rimes/The_Story/" title="LeAnn_Rimes - The Story - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All of these lines across my face <br>Tell you the story of who I am <br>So many stories of where I've been <br>And how I got to where I am <br>Ohh But these stories don't mean anything <br>You've got no one to tell them to it's true <br>I was made for you <br><br>I climbed across the mountain tops <br>Swam all across the ocean blue <br>I crossed all the lines and I broke all the rules <br>And baby, I broke them all for you <br>Ohh And it's even when I was flat broke <br>You made me feel like a million bucks you do <br>I was made for you <br>Ohh <br><br>You see the smile that's on my mouth <br>It's hiding the words that don't come out <br>And all of my friends who think that I'm blessed <br>They don't know my life is a mess <br>No they don't know who I really am <br>And they don't know what I've been through like you do <br>And I was made fo you <br><br>All of these lines across my face <br>Tell you the story of who I am <br>So many stories of where I've been <br>And how I got to where I am <br>Ohh But these stories don't mean anything <br>You've got no one to tell them to it's true <br>I was made for you <br>I was made for you <br><br>Well it's true]]></content><category term="LeAnn Rimes" label="LeAnn Rimes"/><category term="The Story" label="The Story"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/INHEAVEN/Drift/</id><title>INHEAVEN - Drift - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/INHEAVEN/Drift/" title="INHEAVEN - Drift - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Drift, drift <br><br>When we swim, swim <br>Can we sink without drowning <br>And I know, I know <br>We've got a long way to go <br><br>Lonely hearts don't stay <br>I feel it getting lighter everyday <br>It feels like I'm drifting on a cloud with you <br>In another time, when me and you collide <br>I know I'll feel it soon <br>When this world ends there's dust <br>And there's me and you <br><br>Whenever, me and you <br>Whenever <br><br>Drift, drift <br><br>When we swim, swim <br>Can't you see that I'm drowning <br>And I know, I know <br>We've got a long way to go <br><br>Lonely hearts don't stay <br>I feel it getting lighter everyday <br>It feels like I'm drifting on a cloud with you <br>In another time, when me and you collide <br>I know I'll feel it soon <br>When this world ends there's dust <br>And there's me and you <br><br>Collide I know I'll feel it soon <br>Collide I know I'll feel it soon <br>Collide I know I'll feel it soon <br>Collide I know I'll feel it soon Whenever <br>Collide I know I'll feel it soon <br>Collide I know I'll feel it soon Whenever <br>Collide I know I'll feel it soon <br>Collide I know I'll feel it soon Hey]]></content><category term="INHEAVEN" label="INHEAVEN"/><category term="Drift" label="Drift"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Karmin/Come_With_Me_Pure_Imagination/</id><title>Karmin - Come With Me (Pure Imagination) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Karmin/Come_With_Me_Pure_Imagination/" title="Karmin - Come With Me (Pure Imagination) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know a place that I can go <br>And nowadays I call it home <br>Some argue that it's make believe <br>Oh if only their eyes could see <br><br>That the forest is full of evergreens <br>And that none of the stars are out of reach <br>They can shoot us across the canopy <br>Make your wishes and count to three <br><br>Come with me and you'll be <br>In a world of pure imagination <br>What we'll see will defy explanation <br>There is no life I know <br>To compare with pure imagination <br>Living there we'll be free if we truly wish to be <br><br>I know a world within myself <br>Where I don't need nobody's help <br>All of the flowers start to sing <br>And heat everything that's ailing me <br><br>I can do anything without a doubt <br>Paint the colors the world would never allow <br>Letting go is the only currency <br>Make your wishes and count to three <br><br>Come with me and you'll be <br>In a world of pure imagination <br>What we'll see will defy explanation <br>There is no life I know <br>To compare with pure imagination <br>Living there we'll be free if we truly wish to be <br><br>Come with me and you'll be <br>In a world of pure imagination <br>What we'll see will defy explanation <br>There is no life I know <br>To compare with pure imagination <br>Living there we'll be free if we truly wish to be <br><br>If you want to view paradise <br>Simply look around and view it <br>Anything you want to, do it <br>Wanna change the world <br>There's nothing to it <br>There's nothing to it <br>There's nothing to it <br><br>Come with me and you'll be <br>In a world of pure imagination <br>What we'll see will defy explanation <br>There is no life I know <br>To compare with pure imagination <br>Living there we'll be free if we truly wish to be <br><br>Come with me and you'll be <br>In a world of pure imagination <br>What we'll see will defy explanation <br>There is no life I know <br>To compare with pure imagination <br>Living there we'll be free if we truly wish to be]]></content><category term="Karmin" label="Karmin"/><category term="Come With Me (Pure Imagination)" label="Come With Me (Pure Imagination)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rebecca_Ferguson/Bones/</id><title>Rebecca_Ferguson - Bones - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rebecca_Ferguson/Bones/" title="Rebecca_Ferguson - Bones - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wish that you could see who I really am <br>It's tough being a woman in love with an unkind man <br>Cause baby I'd give you the world, in fact, I already do <br>And how do you repay that <br>Talk to me like I'm just a regular tramp tryna took you over <br>Have you even have a clue, what I gave up just to be here <br>Serve you with your steak and beer <br><br>Baby that's for love Baby that's for love <br>Baby that's for real Baby that's for real <br>And all I've ever wanted was for your loving arms <br>To wrap themselves around me and say <br><br>Hey girl, you're the prettiest thing my eyes have ever seen <br>Come and lay your bones down with me <br>Come and lay your bones down with me <br>Hey girl, you're the prettiest thing my heart has ever known <br>Come and lay your bones down with me <br>Come and lay your bones down <br><br>I'm not tryna play the victim, don't wanna go head to head <br>But boy I shouldn't have to stand in the mirror convincing myself I'm fair <br>Maybe that's your job to do <br>And maybe you should say I'm beautiful <br>Why do you wanna watch the set when I'm layin' right next to you in my own room <br>I feel like you don't even know I'm there <br>But I put a brush through my hair for you <br>Run my fingertips over your back real smooth <br><br>Boy I need love Boy I need love <br>I don't get enough I don't get enough <br>And all I've ever wanted was for your loving arms <br>To wrap themselves around me and say <br><br>Hey girl, you're the prettiest thing my eyes have ever seen <br>Come and lay your bones down with me <br>Come and lay your bones down with me <br>Hey girl, you're the prettiest thing my heart has ever known <br>Come and lay your bones down with me <br>Come and lay your bones down <br><br>I look you dead in the eyes and say I love you <br>In the eyes and say I want you <br>In the eyes and say This is what I'm asking for <br>How can you sit and stare at the wall <br>Do you even like me at all <br>Start talking 'bout making it better, it ain't that complicated <br>I just wanna see your arms around me, baby <br>Come and lay your bones down <br>Come and lay your bones down <br><br>Hey girl, you're the prettiest thing my eyes have ever seen <br>Come and lay your bones down with me <br>Come and lay your bones down with me Bones down <br>Hey girl, you're the prettiest thing my heart has ever known <br>Come and lay your bones down with me <br>Come and lay your bones down <br><br>Oh, I look you dead in the eyes and say I love you <br>In the eyes and say I want you <br>In the eyes and say This is what I'm asking for <br>Ooh, come and lay your bones down <br>Let me lay my bones down]]></content><category term="Rebecca Ferguson" label="Rebecca Ferguson"/><category term="Bones" label="Bones"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zipper_Club/Small_Town/</id><title>Zipper_Club - Small Town - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zipper_Club/Small_Town/" title="Zipper_Club - Small Town - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look at all the people <br>Heads are down and hands are up <br>They don't know where they should go <br>Leaving in the headspace <br>Hoping for a repay <br>Where to go, I don't know <br><br>Nowhere and anywhere <br>I got to get somewhere <br>There's somebody waiting <br>But they don't know I am <br><br>It's a really small town <br>With a really big body <br>It's a really small town <br>I'm a child in the space <br>I'm a child in the <br><br>Looking for the right eye <br>Can't see what my face looks like <br>Lost and bored, God only knows <br>Headed towards the freeway <br>In a wall I can't escape <br>All the roads look the same here <br><br>Nowhere and anywhere <br>I got to get somewhere <br>There's somebody waiting <br>But they don't know I am <br>Nowhere and anywhere <br>I got to get somewhere <br>There's somebody waiting <br>But they don't know I am <br><br>It's a really small town <br>With a really big body <br>The devil's come around <br>And tonight is the night <br>Tonight is my night <br>But tonight is my night <br><br>It's a really small town <br>With a really big body <br>The devil's come around <br>And tonight is the night <br>Tonight is my night <br>But tonight is my night <br>It's a really small town <br>With a really big eye <br>The devil's come around <br>And tonight is the night <br>Tonight is my night]]></content><category term="Zipper Club" label="Zipper Club"/><category term="Small Town" label="Small Town"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Afrojack/Gone_Feat_Ty_Dolla_ign/</id><title>Afrojack - Gone (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Afrojack/Gone_Feat_Ty_Dolla_ign/" title="Afrojack - Gone (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, Dolla $ign <br>Afrojack, oh yeah, oh yeah <br>Oh, yeah, oh yeah, woo <br><br>If I give you what you wanted, can you keep it off the record <br>And when I turn on the camera, tell me, can you take direction Perfection <br>You know the suite is presidential, you 'bout to get elected <br>Yeah, in the morning we can sip champagne and I'mma eat you up for breakfast, delicious Let me give it to ya <br><br>Two times, you know I love that, love that, love that <br>Thick thighs, you know I love that, love that, love that <br>Talk nasty, girl I love that, love that, love that, love that <br>Back up on me, I love that, love that, love that <br><br>All around the world, it's your turn <br>We can take our time, this is slow burn <br>Pop another pill, never sober <br>Baby, plannin' on leaving your life 'round midnight <br>Gone, gone, gone already <br>Baby we'll be gone, gone already <br>Gone already <br><br>In the morning we'll be gone <br>In the morning we'll be gone <br>You already know <br>In the morning we'll be gone <br><br>Baby I don't wanna rush you, you know you control the tempo <br>Yeah, bet you like it when I touch ya I do, blow your mind just like a whistle, official <br>No we ain't gotta complicate things, just keep it nice and simple nice and simple, nice and simple <br>That's how we do it, how we do it all day, baby girl you got potential If you want the info, I'mma give it to ya <br><br>Two times, you know I love that, love that, love that <br>Thick thighs, you know I love that, love that, love that <br>Talk nasty, girl I love that, love that, love that, love that <br>Back up on me, I love that, love that, love that <br><br>All around the world, it's your turn <br>We can take our time, this is slow burn <br>Pop another pill, never sober <br>Baby, plannin' on leaving your life 'round midnight <br>Gone, gone, gone already <br>Baby we'll be gone, gone already <br>Gone already <br><br>In the morning we'll be gone <br>In the morning we'll be gone <br>You already know <br>In the morning we'll be gone girl <br>In the morning we'll be gone <br>In the morning we'll be gone <br>In the morning we'll be gone <br>You know, you know, gone]]></content><category term="Afrojack" label="Afrojack"/><category term="Gone (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign)" label="Gone (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cherub/Signs_Feat_TI/</id><title>Cherub - Signs (Feat. T.I.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cherub/Signs_Feat_TI/" title="Cherub - Signs (Feat. T.I.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't wanna scare ya but I see ya <br>And I'm a big fan of your features <br>Just might be drunk enough to meet ya <br>My name's Jordan and I'm a Libra <br><br>So baby what's your sign <br>Cause girl you so damn fine <br>You say that you're a Gemini <br>And that's a perfect match for me <br><br>Damn shawty how you do that shit <br>Know how I love when you do that shit <br>Do it Do it <br>Blow my mind when you do that shit <br>Know how I love when you do that shit <br>Do it Do it <br>Damn shawty how you do that shit <br>You know how I love when you do that shit <br>Do it Do it <br>Blow my mind when you do that shit <br>Girl I can't wait to see you to do that shit <br><br>You make me feel like I'm a rookie <br>Box tastes just like some girl scout cookies so <br>You got me out here playing hooky oh oh oh <br>Cause I want it so bad <br><br>So baby what's your sign <br>Cause girl you so damn fine <br>You say that you're a Gemini <br>And that's a perfect match for me <br><br>Ohhhhhhh <br><br>Bankroll M Mafia <br>Slow down baby <br>At least long enough to tell me your sign baby, Gemini <br>Well listen up, you need to go around baby <br>Bring a friend if you want to, that's up to you though <br>But you know, I hate to be riding in a 2 door <br>With two seats, just you and me and tryin' to fit two more <br>But who knows Lets move on <br>And kudos to yo mom and you pops <br>Can't wait to give you some with the door locked <br>You lookin' at me like a Scorpio <br>Attitude like a Sagittarius <br>I swear if you let me near, Ima take ya 50 flows up bend your ass over on a tear <br>Ya got an ass like a dancer, tryin' to play it cool like a Cancer <br>But i'm the motherfuckin answer, no question <br>This how a Libra do it, hey let me see if you can handle wood <br>Now that you're you really should <br><br>So baby what's your sign <br>Cause girl you so damn fine <br>You say that you're a Gemini <br>And that's a perfect match for me <br><br>Damn shawty how you do that shit <br>Know how I love when you do that shit <br>Do it Do it <br>Blow my mind when you do that shit <br>Know how I love when you do that shit]]></content><category term="Cherub" label="Cherub"/><category term="Signs (Feat. T.I.)" label="Signs (Feat. T.I.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frenship/Run_Wild/</id><title>Frenship - Run Wild - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frenship/Run_Wild/" title="Frenship - Run Wild - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Run wild 'til it hurts <br>Who cares if we're gonna make it, oh <br>I like when it hurts <br>Just let it bend 'til we break it off <br><br>These feelings will expire <br>No no no, no no no <br>If we leave 'em alone, leave 'em alone, oh <br>Can we just fuel this fire <br>No no no, no no no <br>I need the rest to burn <br><br>You count for something <br>And we are far from nothing <br>And the higher we get, the less I let it go <br>The fire left you running <br>Let's ride these nerves <br>Until we lose another feeling, yeah <br>Riptide, don't swerve <br>Come sweep me up and leave the meaning out <br><br>These feelings will expire <br>No no no, no no no <br>If we leave 'em alone, leave 'em alone, oh <br>Can we just fuel this fire <br>No no no, no no no <br>I need the rest to burn <br><br>You count for something <br>And we are far from nothing <br>And the higher we get, the less I let it go <br>The fire left you running <br><br>Look what you've started <br>We were just loving but now we're haunted <br>Running, running, running away <br>Look what you've started <br>We were just loving but now we're haunted <br>Running, running, running away <br><br>You count for something <br>And we are far from nothing <br>And the higher we get, the less I let it go <br>The fire left you running <br>You count for something <br>And we are far from nothing <br>And the higher we get, the less I let it go <br>The fire left you running <br><br>Look what you've started <br>We were just loving but now we're haunted <br>Running, running, running away <br>Look what you've started <br>We were just loving but now we're haunted <br>Running, running, running away]]></content><category term="Frenship" label="Frenship"/><category term="Run Wild" label="Run Wild"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tungevaag__Raaban/Magical/</id><title>Tungevaag__Raaban - Magical - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tungevaag__Raaban/Magical/" title="Tungevaag__Raaban - Magical - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Been searching all my life <br>One touch, one look at my heart <br>Come take me anywhere <br><br>Where ever you are <br>Think I like it, yeah <br>Been searching all my life <br>One touch, you were healing my heart <br>Just take me anywhere <br>Where ever you are <br>Think I like it, yeah <br>Gimme your taste of magic <br>Gimme your taste of magic <br><br>Gimme your taste of magic <br>Gimme your taste of magic <br><br>Hey <br>Never let me go <br>We are We are <br>We are magical <br>Baby don't you know <br>We are We are <br>We are magical <br>Hey <br>Never let me go <br>We are We are <br>We are magical <br>Baby don't you know <br>We are We are <br>We are magical <br>Magica Magical <br>Magical Magical <br>Magical <br>We are We are <br>We are magical <br><br>We are We are <br>We are magical <br><br>That dressed up magazine love <br>Come see me through my veins <br>Where ever you are <br>Think I like it, yeah <br>Been searching all my life <br>One touch, one look at my heart <br>Come take me anywhere <br>Where ever you are <br>Think I like it, yeah <br>Gimme your taste of magic <br>Gimme your taste of magic <br>Gimme your taste of magic <br>Gimme your taste of magic <br><br>Hey <br>Never let me go <br>We are We are <br>We are magical <br>Baby don't you know <br>We are We are <br>We are magical <br>Hey <br>Never let me go <br>We are We are <br>We are magical <br>Baby don't you know <br>We are We are <br>We are magical <br>Magical Magical <br>Magical Magical <br>Magical <br>We are We are <br>We are magical <br><br>We are We are <br>We are magical]]></content><category term="Tungevaag &amp; Raaban" label="Tungevaag &amp; Raaban"/><category term="Magical" label="Magical"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jai_Waetford/Living_Not_Dreaming/</id><title>Jai_Waetford - Living Not Dreaming - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jai_Waetford/Living_Not_Dreaming/" title="Jai_Waetford - Living Not Dreaming - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Some things just never change <br>But we just can't stay the same <br>I'm running in circles watching you call someone else's name <br>And I know it's not my place <br>But my mind will never change <br>'Cause no matter what I do, I can't help running back to you <br><br>I can't outrun the thought of us, of us <br>Oh, 'cause when I turn around you're catching up <br>I, I can't help but think about love, 'bout love <br>'Bout love, 'bout love, oh oh <br><br>Maybe we don't care enough tonight <br>Take your fears and throw 'em to the sky <br>Whatever's wrong we'll make it feel right <br>We're living not dreaming <br>What's the possibility of me <br>Making up for time I spent with you <br>Tell me what you want me to do <br>We're living not dreaming <br>We're living not dreaming We're living not, we're living not <br>We're living not dreaming we're living not, we're living not, we're living not <br>We're living not dreaming <br><br>So, what's the point in taking so much but never taking a chance, a new romance 'cause it's a move you're scared of making <br>So, I'm not meant to be a sensitive guy who needs ya <br>So, stop pretending <br>I gotta be the kind to what will lead ya <br><br>Maybe we don't care enough tonight <br>Take your fears and throw 'em to the sky <br>Whatever's wrong we'll make it feel right <br>We're living not dreaming <br>What's the possibility of me <br>Making up for time I spent with you <br>Tell me what you want me to do <br>We're living not dreaming <br>We're living not dreaming we're living not, we're living not <br>We're living not dreaming we're living not, we're living not, we're living not <br>We're living not dreaming <br><br>We're too young to follow what they told <br>Oh <br><br>I can't outrun the thought of us, of us <br>Oh, 'cause when I turn around you're catching up <br>I, I can't help but think about, think about love <br><br>Maybe we don't care enough tonight <br>Take your fears and throw 'em to the sky <br>Whatever's wrong we'll make it feel right <br>We're living not dreaming <br>What's the possibility of me <br>Making up for time I spent with you <br>Tell me what you want me to do <br><br>We're living not dreaming <br>We're living not dreaming]]></content><category term="Jai Waetford" label="Jai Waetford"/><category term="Living Not Dreaming" label="Living Not Dreaming"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Mattrs/Bow_Down/</id><title>Louis_Mattrs - Bow Down - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Mattrs/Bow_Down/" title="Louis_Mattrs - Bow Down - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let me serenade, serenade you <br>Put you here, right where my mouth is <br>Been trippin' on, trippin' on you <br>All day, all day <br><br>Ladies and gentlemen, I did an experiment <br>But it backfired on me <br>I thought I could hit and run, but she's the one with the gun <br>Now I be begging don't leave <br><br>Said I bow down when I think about you <br>Said I bow down when I think about you <br>You make it, you make it alright <br>You make it, you make it all night <br>Said I bow down when I think about you <br><br>Been thinkin' bout, thinkin' 'bout you <br>I even drew a picture about it <br>You're kryptonite, kryptonite, you <br>I don't want to be stronger <br><br>Ladies and gentlemen, I did an experiment <br>But it backfired on me <br>I thought I could hit and run, but she's the one with the gun <br>Now I be begging don't leave <br><br>Said I bow down when I think about you <br>Said I bow down when I think about you <br>You make it, you make it alright <br>You make it, you make it all night <br>Said I bow down when I think about you <br><br>Said I bow down when I think about you <br>Said I bow down when I think about you <br>You make it, you make it alright <br>You make it, you make it all night <br>Said I bow down when I think about you]]></content><category term="Louis Mattrs" label="Louis Mattrs"/><category term="Bow Down" label="Bow Down"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frans/If_I_Were_Sorry/</id><title>Frans - If I Were Sorry - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frans/If_I_Were_Sorry/" title="Frans - If I Were Sorry - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'd crawl through the desert on my hands and knees <br>Rehearsin' my pretty please <br>Climb the highest mountain <br>If I were sorry <br><br>Shout it from the top <br>Swim under water until my lungs exploded <br>Walk into the fire <br>If I were sorry <br><br>I'd run a thousand miles <br>Wouldn't stop until I dropped <br>Wouldn't take a break to breathe until I got close <br>Enough <br><br>Then I'd do it all again <br>If I really had the chance <br>But I know deep inside for you it's just another <br>dance <br><br>If I were sorry <br>I'd give you all the glory <br>if I were sorry <br><br>If I were sorry <br>it would be a different story <br><br>If I were sorry <br>if I were sorry oh <br><br>I'd hold my breath till my face turned blue <br>I'd rob a bank and the post office too <br>Swim across the ocean <br>If I were sorry <br><br>I'd take a vow of silence <br>I wouldn't say a single word <br>Until you really heard <br>If I were sorry <br><br>I'd run a thousand miles <br>Wouldn't stop until I dropped <br>Wouldn't take the break to breathe <br>Until I got close enough <br><br>If I were sorry <br>I'd give you all the glory <br>if I were sorry <br><br>If I were sorry <br>it would be a different story <br>if I were sorry oh <br><br>Now did you ever realise <br>that your mistake had a prize <br>oh you threw it all away <br>'cause you're the devil in disguise <br><br>Now would you ever realise <br>the consequences of your lies <br>and would you save the falling tear or act as if <br>there's nothing there <br><br>If I were sorry <br>if I were sorry <br><br>If I were sorry <br>if I were sorry <br><br>If I were sorry <br>I'd take a vow of silence <br><br>I wouldn't say a single word <br>if I were sorry <br><br>If I were sorry <br>I'd be on my hands and knees <br>beggin pretty please <br>if I were sorry <br>but I'm not sorry, no]]></content><category term="Frans" label="Frans"/><category term="If I Were Sorry" label="If I Were Sorry"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lost_Kings/Phone_Down_Feat_Emily_Warren/</id><title>Lost_Kings - Phone Down (Feat. Emily Warren) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lost_Kings/Phone_Down_Feat_Emily_Warren/" title="Lost_Kings - Phone Down (Feat. Emily Warren) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This room's so quiet <br>I can hear the sound of silence <br>Right here in your arms <br>And I'm falling asleep to your heartbeat <br><br>It's just you and I <br>Shadows in the passing headlights <br>And I think for a moment <br>You won't let go of me <br><br>But suddenly that bright blue <br>Is glowing in this dark room <br>You turn away like I'm not here at all <br><br>Why don't you put that fucking phone down <br>Darling, so we could be alone now <br>Can't you just be here when the lights go out <br>Why don't you ever put that phone down <br>What could be so goddamn important <br>That it can't wait until the morning <br>You got me right here with my clothes off now <br>Why don't you put that fucking phone down <br><br>Yeah, the first thing you do <br>Is when I reach out my hand to touch you <br>Are you hiding something from me <br>Cause you moved when I get close <br><br>Oh, I hate that bright blue <br>It's glowing in this dark room <br>You turn away like I'm not here at all <br><br>Why don't you put that fucking phone down <br>Darling, so we could be alone now <br>Can't you just be here when the lights go out <br>Why don't you ever put that phone down <br>What could be so goddamn important <br>That it can't wait until the morning <br>You got me right here with my clothes off now <br>Why don't you put that fucking phone down <br><br>You're killing the moment <br>The window is closing <br>It's only supposed to be two of us <br>Put that phone down <br>Please, put that phone down <br><br>Now I'm feeling awkward <br>It's actually torture <br>You're making a fool of the both of us <br>Put that phone down <br>Please, put that phone down <br><br>Why don't you put that fucking phone down <br>Darling, so we could be alone now <br>Can't you just be here when the lights go out <br>And just put that phone down <br>What could be so goddamn important <br>That it can't wait until the morning <br>You got me right here with my clothes off now <br>Why don't you put that fucking phone down]]></content><category term="Lost Kings" label="Lost Kings"/><category term="Phone Down (Feat. Emily Warren)" label="Phone Down (Feat. Emily Warren)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Guy_Sebastian/Candle/</id><title>Guy_Sebastian - Candle - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T09:09:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T09:09:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Guy_Sebastian/Candle/" title="Guy_Sebastian - Candle - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm like ten thousand miles from you <br>And there's like ten thousand girls in view <br>They're try'na say they're with me <br>Get their drink on for free <br>Tryna get to my hotel room <br><br>Back it up, back it up, back it up <br>I ain't tryna do nothing, nah nah <br>Back it up, back it up, back it up <br>All I want is my woman <br><br>'Cause they don't hold a candle <br>To you, to you <br>You're my better handful <br>It's true, it's true <br>Ain't nobody taking your place <br>You're the only body I praise <br>They don't hold a candle <br>Yeah, they don't hold a candle <br>To you <br><br>She got that dress on to show her curves <br>And she came backstage to do some work <br>I knew when she said hello <br>She was ready to go <br>Ran her finger 'round my shirt <br><br>Back it up, back it up, back it up <br>I ain't tryna do nothing, nah nah <br>Back it up, back it up, back it up <br>All I want is my woman <br>My woman <br><br>'Cause they don't hold a candle <br>To you, to you <br>You're my better handful <br>It's true, it's true <br>Ain't nobody taking your place <br>You're the only body I praise <br>They don't hold a candle <br>Yeah, they don't hold a candle <br>To you <br><br>To you <br>Cause no one puts their hands on me <br>Like you <br>Yeah, nothing ever burns like your flame <br>That's why I ran and give you my name <br>'Cause they don't hold a candle <br>No one holds a candle <br>To you <br><br>Ain't nobody taking your place <br>You're the only body I praise <br>'Cause they don't hold a candle <br>Yeah, they don't hold a candle <br>To you]]></content><category term="Guy Sebastian" label="Guy Sebastian"/><category term="Candle" label="Candle"/></entry></feed>