<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:04:48+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thieves_Like_Us/Bleed_Bleed_Bleed/</id><title>Thieves Like Us - Bleed Bleed Bleed - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:31:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:31:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thieves_Like_Us/Bleed_Bleed_Bleed/" title="Thieves Like Us - Bleed Bleed Bleed - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Slow down and lay low <br>Against the rhythm of the time <br>I can't change, I can't hide <br>From the rhythm and the rules <br>And I'll say what I want to <br>Say what I want to say to them <br>And I'll do what I want to <br>Do what I want to do anyway <br><br>There must be someone telling a lie <br>There must be someone telling a lie to me <br>There must be someone telling a lie <br>There must be someone telling a lie to me <br><br>Live low or lay down <br>For the dollar and the dime <br>It's their tune and their game <br>You can only play to lose <br>I don't breathe for your money <br>Breathe for your money, breathe for you <br>I don't bleed for your money <br>Bleed for your money, bleed for you <br><br>There must be someone telling a lie <br>There must be someone telling a lie to me <br>There must be someone telling a lie <br>There must be someone telling a lie to me <br><br>Easy to cheat Easy to hide <br>And then you disappear <br>Easy to cheat Easy to hide <br>And then you disappear <br>Easy to cheat Easy to hide <br>And then you disappear <br>Easy to cheat Easy to hide <br>And then you disappear <br><br>There must be someone telling a lie <br>There must be someone telling a lie to me <br>There must be someone telling a lie <br>There must be someone telling a lie to me]]></content><category term="Thieves Like Us" label="Thieves Like Us"/><category term="Bleed Bleed Bleed" label="Bleed Bleed Bleed"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Now_Or_Never/</id><title>Halsey - Now Or Never - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:31:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:31:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Now_Or_Never/" title="Halsey - Now Or Never - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't wanna fight right now <br>Know you always right now <br>Know I need you 'round with me <br>But nobody waitin' 'round with me <br>Been through the ups <br>Yeah the ups and the downs with me <br>Got a whole lot of love <br>But you don't wanna spread it <br>'round with me yeah <br>Never pick up never call me <br>You know we're runnin' out of time <br>Never pick up when you want me <br>Now I gotta draw a line <br>Baby I done done enough talking <br>Need to know that you're mine <br>Baby we done done enough talking <br>Gotta be right now right now <br>Baby gon' love me now now <br>now now now now <br>Now or never hey hey hey <br>I want you to hold me down <br>down down down down down <br>Down forever hey hey hey <br>Said you know <br>I wanna keep you around <br>'Round forever hey hey hey <br>I want you to love me now now <br>now now now now <br>Now or never <br>I'm turnin' off <br>the light right now <br>I'm callin' it a night now <br>Wishin' you were 'round with me <br>But you're in a different town <br>than me <br>We've been through it all <br>But you could never spit it <br>out for me <br>Tryna talk to a wall <br>But you could never tear <br>it down for me yeah <br>Never pick up never call me <br>You know we're runnin' out of time <br>Never pick up when you want me <br>Now I gotta draw a line <br>Baby I done done enough talking <br>Need to know that you're mine <br>Baby we done done enough talking <br>Gotta be right now right now <br>Baby gon' love me now now <br>now now now now <br>Now or never hey hey hey <br>I want you to hold me down <br>down down down down down <br>Down forever hey hey hey <br>Said you know <br>I wanna keep you around <br>'Round forever hey hey hey <br>I want you to love me now now <br>now now now now <br>Now or never <br>Yeah draw the line up <br>Don't take no more time up yeah <br>Make your mind up <br>I need you to make <br>your mind up yeah <br>Draw the line up <br>Don't take no more time up yeah <br>Baby you gotta decide something <br>Let me know <br>Baby gon' love me now now <br>now now now now <br>Now or never hey hey hey <br>I want you to hold me down <br>down down down down down <br>Down forever hey hey hey <br>Said you know <br>I wanna keep you around <br>'Round forever hey hey hey <br>I want you to love me now now <br>now now now now <br>Now or never <br>]]></content><category term="Halsey" label="Halsey"/><category term="Now Or Never" label="Now Or Never"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JJK/Alley_cat/</id><title>JJK - Alley cat - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:31:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:31:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JJK/Alley_cat/" title="JJK - Alley cat - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[골목의 아침은 악취를 풍기며 <br>내게 다가와 <br>참 적응 안 되는 분위기야 <br>Bad News만 공유되는 News Feed <br>정치는 뭐가 이리 어려운지 <br>Smart phone <br>Dumb people <br>둘 다 bettery는 low <br>오늘도 피곤을 딛고 <br>일 하러 가자 일 <br>최저임금 캐는 광부 <br>더 어둡고 더운 건 <br>착각 이길 바랄 뿐 Ay <br>동등한 돈은 안 바래 <br>동등한 존중을 줘 <br>도움은 원하지도 않아 <br>기회를 얻을 권리를 줘 <br>연기를 뿜고 알콜을 부어 <br>이젠 못 배우고 멍청한 <br>취급 받는 것도 지겨워 <br>먹고 살 생각만 하다 보면 <br>치킨 될 병아리 된 기분이 들어 <br>삶의 도면 위에 <br>엎질러진 아이스 아메리카노 <br>뭐라도 해야겠다 싶어 한 게 <br>기껏해야 좋아요 꾹 <br>Beautiful Struggle <br>Beautiful Struggle <br>근데 왜 억울해 구겨진 얼굴 <br>난 니 집안 일하는 기계도 아니고 <br>니 지갑에서 돈 빼간 놈도 아닌데 <br>뭐야 그 시선은 <br>정당한 거야 눈깔서 힘 빼 <br>정당한 거야 눈깔서 힘 빼 <br>지들도 똑같으면서 <br>뭘 그리 지껄여 <br>니가 나와 같다면 <br>적어도 난 니 편이야 <br>무력감에 허우적대네 <br>눈 뜨고 직시해도 <br>어두컴한 내일 <br>다 이렇게 산다는 믿음만이 <br>내가 사는 골목의 유일한 희망 <br>워킹맘은 아이를 못 봐 <br>워킹대디는 명퇴권유로 got fired <br>둘 다 아직 30대고 <br>학교 간 아이는 <br>휴거라며 왕따 당하지 <br>아 다 왜 이 모양이야 <br>속 풀 곳 없어서 속 버렸더니 <br>속도 없는 놈 취급 <br>억울해 pour more liquor <br>부정적인 게 죄라서 <br>죄다 불구속입건 <br>긍정적인 놈들은 <br>다 이유가 있더군 <br>난 니 아빠나 너만큼 <br>잘 살 자신이 없어 <br>심지어 우리 아빠만큼 <br>살 자신도 없어 <br>겁이나 내가 이대로 <br>진짜 무력해질까 봐 <br>그때쯤 걸그룹 치마 <br>들춰준 바람 WOW <br>Beautiful Struggle <br>Beautiful Struggle <br>근데 왜 억울해 구겨진 얼굴 <br>난 니 집안 일하는 기계도 아니고 <br>니 지갑에서 돈 빼간 놈도 아닌데 <br>뭐야 그 시선은 <br>정당한 거야 눈깔서 힘 빼 <br>정당한 거야 눈깔서 힘 빼 <br>지들도 똑같으면서 <br>뭘 그리 지껄여 <br>니가 나와 같다면 <br>적어도 난 니 편이야 <br>겁이나 내가 이대로 <br>진짜로 무력해질까 봐 봐 봐 <br>게다가 넌 이런 내 무력감이 <br>이어지길 원하잖 아 아 아 <br>겁이나 내가 이대로 <br>진짜로 무력해질까 봐 봐 봐 <br>게다가 넌 이런 내 무력감이 <br>이어지길 원하잖 아 아 아 <br>겁이나 내가 이대로 <br>진짜로 무력해질까 봐 봐 봐 <br>게다가 넌 이런 내 무력감이 <br>이어지길 원하잖 아 아 아 <br>겁이나 내가 이대로 <br>진짜로 무력해질까 봐 봐 봐 <br>게다가 넌 이런 내 무력감이 <br>이어지길 원하잖 아 아 아 <br>]]></content><category term="JJK" label="JJK"/><category term="Alley cat" label="Alley cat"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JJK/GVOMA_Feat_수다쟁이/</id><title>JJK - G.V.O.M.A. (Feat. 수다쟁이) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:31:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:31:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JJK/GVOMA_Feat_%EC%88%98%EB%8B%A4%EC%9F%81%EC%9D%B4/" title="JJK - G.V.O.M.A. (Feat. 수다쟁이) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[골목은 웃고 떠드는 분위기로 <br>입가의 지워지지 않는 미소 <br>Good Vibes Only <br>장단 맞추지 뭐 <br>옥탑의 Grill 위의 <br>고등어 미세먼지로 <br>제일 싼 게 음악이래 <br>DJ drop the needle <br>춤 추네 <br>이자 갚기 바쁜 빚쟁이들 <br>세금 맥이고 토해내도 눈 감고 <br>I don't care at all <br>부정적인 Vibe는 <br>내가 이룰 성공에게 독 <br>안 오를 거야 <br>전세도 대출금리도 <br>물가는 물론이고 <br>가스나 전기도 <br>여기 다 정규직 못 될 <br>비정규직이고 <br>노조는 나라가 망한다니 <br>그냥 연예인 불륜 얘기로 <br>워킹맘은 돈 버느라 죄인이고 <br>어린이집 선생이 또 <br>애기를 때리고 <br>윽시로 큰 기업은 <br>애기들을 죽이고 <br>그래도 사과는 했으니까 <br>그럼 됐지 뭐 <br>Good Vibes Only My Ass yo <br>Good Vibes Only My Ass <br>춤은 니네들이나 땡겨 <br>긍정적이긴 개뿔 난 됐어 <br>Good Vibes Only My Ass yo <br>Good Vibes Only My Ass <br>춤은 니네들이나 땡겨 <br>긍정적이긴 개뿔 난 됐어 <br>분위기 완전 환율 안 떨어지지 <br>한잔 더 마셔 법이 가벼워지지 <br>낮엔 답 없는 놈들 밤이 되니 질문 <br>이 뭐였는지 다 까먹고 getting busy <br>여긴 모두 자본 없는 자본주의지 <br>전세냐 매매냐 니 월세는 밀리지 <br>여긴 학벌 위주 사회를 <br>신분제 사회로 <br>타파 하는 중이지 <br>모든 게 핫한 분위기 <br>Bad Vibe Lonely <br>분위기 깨지 말고 함께 외쳐 <br>Good Vibes Only <br>옮기 전에 걷어내 부정적인 공기 <br>좋은 게 좋은 거야 <br>You Only Live Once homie <br>Party on party on <br>잘 될 거야 밤이고 낮이고 <br>안 싸워도 나아질 건 나아지고 <br>기억해둬 Good Vibes Only yo <br>Good Vibes Only My Ass yo <br>Good Vibes Only My Ass <br>춤은 니네들이나 땡겨 <br>긍정적이긴 개뿔 난 됐어 <br>Good Vibes Only My Ass yo <br>Good Vibes Only My Ass <br>춤은 니네들이나 땡겨 <br>긍정적이긴 개뿔 난 됐어 <br>여기는 춤판 저기는 술판 <br>다 난장판 <br>그 가운데 유행어 자살각 <br>방 한 칸에 세 식구가 <br>밥상머리에 앉아 <br>방바닥 긁고 있는 그 이유나 알까 <br>그 건물주 님이 No 하셨기 때문 <br>골목이목 좋아졌기 때문 <br>이 집 저 집 목 놓아 울며 <br>애원 해 봤자 소용 없지 <br>주인은 좋아 부러 <br>주인 아들은 TV에 나와 <br>바라는 대로 갔더니 <br>현실이 됐다나 <br>그런 말 같지 않은 말만 <br>한 다스 채우고 나면 <br>일가족 자살 화면이 나오는 채널 <br>직원은 해고 돼도 사장은 배불러 <br>줄기 세포 주사 덕에 <br>사모님은 예뻐 <br>가득 쌓아놨지 뒤주의 치즈 <br>덕분에 줄 서 있네 쥐 새끼들 <br>머리부터 꼬리 <br>뼈째로 씹어 삼켜야 <br>속 시원할거야 밝히고 말 거야 <br>날 피곤한 새끼로만 여기건 말건 <br>여긴 내 골목 지킬 거야 <br>이게 내겐 좋은 느낌을 <br>쫓는 일이야 <br>이 맛 못 본 걔들은 모르지 <br>그러니깐 내 분위기 <br>망치지 말고 임마 <br>그만 좀 쌓아 불신 <br>]]></content><category term="JJK" label="JJK"/><category term="G.V.O.M.A. (Feat. 수다쟁이)" label="G.V.O.M.A. (Feat. 수다쟁이)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JJK/Dusty_bass_Feat_Don_Malik/</id><title>JJK - Dusty bass (Feat. Don Malik) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:31:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:31:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JJK/Dusty_bass_Feat_Don_Malik/" title="JJK - Dusty bass (Feat. Don Malik) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루종일 이 생각만해 <br>어떻게 더 벌까 <br>모두가 똑같은 마음이야 <br>뭘 더 해야 더 벌어 <br>남부러울 일 없게 좀 더 모을까 <br>모두가 똑같은 마음이야 <br>뭘 어째야 더 벌어 더 모아 <br>빚 없이 살아볼까 <br>모두가 똑같은 마음이야 <br>다 하루종일 이 생각만해 <br>어떻게 더 벌까 <br>너무 어려워 <br>서울 특별시에서 살기 <br>먹고 살기 빼곤 낭비 <br>매년 물가는 올라가지 <br>적금통장 금리는 낮지 <br>정부의 정책은 바뀔 기미는 없고 <br>광화문 앞은 막히지 <br>난 부모님 보다 못 살 수도 있는 <br>최초의 자식 <br>돈 모은 놈들은 모두 다 <br>부모님이랑 한 집 살고 <br>같이 올라온 놈들은 고시원 <br>옥탑 반지하 살어 <br>재계약 땐 얼마나 <br>더 올릴까 싶어 살펴보는 <br>월세 언제 전세 사나 <br>방세 내면 안남어 핰 <br>한 타임 더 알바 뛰어 <br>학자금대출 갚어 <br>신불자 되긴 싫어 <br>스펙 쌓을 시간마저 아껴 <br>자소서는 자소설 기업이여 <br>굽이 살피소서 <br>비정규직이 정규직 <br>될 리 없으니 눈 낮춰선 <br>안돼 2년 마다 뺑뺑이 <br>30대 한창 때 인생 종이 땡땡 <br>사실 20대 때 사실은 10대 때 <br>사실은 태어날 때 문 내 <br>숟갈 성분 때문에 <br>그 때문에 난 또 다시 <br>하루종일 이 생각만해 <br>어떻게 더 벌까 <br>모두가 똑같은 마음이야 <br>뭘 더 해야 더 벌어 <br>남부러울 일 없게 좀 더 모을까 <br>모두가 똑같은 마음이야 <br>뭘 어째야 더 벌어 더 모아 <br>빚 없이 살아볼까 <br>모두가 똑같은 마음이야 <br>다 하루종일 이 생각만해 <br>어떻게 더 벌까 <br>이런 말들이 오가는 술자리에 <br>남는 건 숙취 뿐이고 <br>고약한 악취나는 입으로 맞는 <br>아침에 냉수를 붓지 <br>대기 번호 뽑고 기다린 패배 <br>쓴 맛은 곧 <br>술 맛과 비슷하고 약은 쓰다들하며 <br>웃다 불만은 죽지 <br>엷은 노력 엔 떫은 열맨 당연해 <br>근데 떫은 노력에 조차도 <br>떫은 열매도 당연하고 <br>졸업 하자마자 빚더미에 <br>앉는것도 당연해 <br>당연하지 못한 건 나와 <br>내 친구새끼들의 다이어트 된 <br>통장 잔고 월급 세금 떼어 가고 <br>적금 들면 생활고 <br>넘쳐나 코 베어갈 놈 <br>엄마아빠가 쇠빠져 <br>일해서 투자한 데라곤 <br>나 뿐인데 지금 나보고 <br>나쁜 놈 되라고 <br>이쁜 말 하는 잘생긴 베스트셀러에 <br>침 뱉고 전화 받어 <br>Brrr Brrr 어디야 달리자 <br>어서 나와 좀 <br>주중에 삼킨 걱정 <br>또 술 먹고서 토해내 <br>내일 숙취는 좀 덜 했음 <br>한 뒤부턴 기억이 꼬이네 <br>하루종일 이 생각만해 <br>어떻게 더 벌까 <br>모두가 똑같은 마음이야 <br>뭘 더 해야 더 벌어 <br>남부러울 일 없게 좀 더 모을까 <br>모두가 똑같은 마음이야 <br>뭘 어째야 더 벌어 더 모아 <br>빚 없이 살아볼까 <br>모두가 똑같은 마음이야 <br>다 하루종일 이 생각만해 <br>어떻게 더 벌까 <br>]]></content><category term="JJK" label="JJK"/><category term="Dusty bass (Feat. Don Malik)" label="Dusty bass (Feat. Don Malik)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JJK/0_Feat_Horim/</id><title>JJK - 0 (Feat. Horim) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:32:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:32:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JJK/0_Feat_Horim/" title="JJK - 0 (Feat. Horim) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 돈이면 다 돼 라고 말하네 <br>돈 값을 하네 숫자는 정직하대 <br>Numbers don't lie <br>거짓말을 안한대 <br>숫자만 보고 쫓는 넌 몇 달러 <br>파운드 위안 엔 <br>모든걸 수치화 해 <br>내 미소와 애도도 <br>점수를 매겨도 넌 몰라 <br>나의 행복도 <br>관계도 주식하듯이 <br>주가 따라 맺고 너의 <br>숫자는 편리한데 <br>행복과는 멀고도 멀어 <br>뭐 나도 알어 우린 돈이 필요하지 <br>내 모든 단위가 <br>높아지길 기도하지 아니 <br>사실 충분 아닌 과분은 바라지 않지 <br>'cause cash ruined everything <br>around me <br>비단 돈만이 아니지 <br>모두 팔리길 바라는 <br>상품 처럼 살아 <br>아닌걸 알면서도 말야 <br>넌 공식 없는 존재 <br>수학적 풀이 불가 <br>너 자신까지 값 매기지마 <br>우린 모두 다 영 <br>Numbers do not say everything <br>'cause we got soul Y'na mean <br>Please be on your way <br>You got your own day <br>네 영의 반응을 따라가 <br>Alright <br>연봉이 사랑의 단위인 시대야 지금 <br>아파트 평 수에 따라 배경에 믿음을 <br>기름 처럼 섞일 일 없길 <br>아래 순위들과는 <br>'na mean 등록금 내 잘 배운 짓들 <br>난 그런 니들과는 어울리지 않아 <br>애초에 다른 category <br>넣지마 니들만의 <br>Chart 안에 그래서 <br>난 몇 위 몇 점 <br>내게 비비는걸 보니 안봐도 느껴져 <br>행복이 비교적이라면 그건 그저 <br>환상일뿐 비교는 늘 불행을 부추겨 <br>넌 니 몸에 달린 <br>가격표가 거슬리겠지 <br>실망하기 싫어 낮추는 <br>널 향한 기대치 <br>You see that shit <br>수를 다루는 천재도 <br>수에게 다뤄지면 역으로 멍청해져 <br>뭐가 더 중요한건지 <br>수 써 봤자 알 길 없지 <br>요율 따져봤자 <br>너의 진정한 값어치는 영 <br>Numbers do not say everything <br>'cause we got soul Y'na mean <br>Make you fly <br>Please be on your way <br>You got your own day <br>네 영의 반응을 따라가 <br>Alright <br>인간은 수를 세고 <br>악마는 수를 부려 <br>천사는 기록하고 있지 <br>니가 숫자에 얽메이고 <br>늘 헛된 수를 부려도 <br>신은 널 기억하고 있지 Love <br>더 자유로워도 돼 <br>더 자유로워도 돼 <br>더 자유로워도 돼 <br>우리 모두가 알고 있지 영 <br>Please you make you fly <br>Please you make you high <br>Please you make you fly <br>Please you make you high <br>]]></content><category term="JJK" label="JJK"/><category term="0 (Feat. Horim)" label="0 (Feat. Horim)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JJK/Im_here_Feat_초영/</id><title>JJK - I`m here (Feat. 초영) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:32:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:32:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JJK/Im_here_Feat_%EC%B4%88%EC%98%81/" title="JJK - I`m here (Feat. 초영) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[진실이 뭔지 모를 News Channel <br>이쁘장한 배우들의 <br>타이밍 좋은 Scandal <br>Rapper 들의 돈 실력과시 성공담 <br>선거철의 허언증 수준의 공약 Battle <br>Chef들의 요리 연예인의 육아 <br>수목 마다 걱정되는 재벌 가의 Drama <br>사연 많은 어린 음악가들의 Audition <br>주말 마다 Star들에게 부여되는 <br>별 의미 없는 Mission <br>닿을 수 없는 곳에 모두가 웃고 있었지 <br>밤이면 이불로 허무함을 덮었지 <br>왜냐면 내일도 출근은 해야 했고 <br>누군가는 대출금을 갚아야만 했어 <br>잘 살진 못해도 잘 사는 정도 쯤은 <br>당연한 거라 여겼지만 <br>그 당연함 앞에서 주늑 들어 <br>차마 주위를 볼 수 없네 <br>나는 이 세상 속 <br>그 어디에도 없었기에 <br>But I'm here <br>Just be my self Be my self <br>모두 거짓 뿐이지만 <br>But I'm here <br>Just be my self Be my self <br>천천히 걸어가 <br>Bikini의 그녀는 휴양지에 <br>그는 내 월세값하는 신발 신고 Party에 <br>뜨겁게 젊음을 태우는 선남선녀들 <br>그 화려함이 나의 비루한 손바닥 위에 <br>내 명의의 부동산 자영업의 꿈 <br>경험 할 여유 <br>언제든지 더 할 수 있는 공부 <br>스펙 쌓기 자기 개발 <br>빚이 아닌 등록금 <br>떠날려면 얼마든 떠나는 <br>가진 자들의 조언들 <br>모두 무슨 돈으로 여유를 부리는지 <br>낼 거 내며는 안 남는 건 나 뿐인 건지 <br>어느 틈에 모아 굴리는지 <br>사라진 저녁 새벽 술이 늘지 <br>누군가의 을의 눈치를 <br>보며 상상해 먹고 사는 것만이 <br>전부가 아닌 삶을 사는 나를 <br>지금 나의 불안감은 <br>오늘 내가 포기 한 것들을 <br>베고 잠들겠지 <br>재운 뒤엔 적막이 가득했지 <br>But I'm here <br>Just be my self be my self <br>모두 거짓 뿐이지만 <br>But I'm here <br>Just be my self be my self <br>천천히 걸어가 <br>매일 같이 굴러가는 쳇바퀴 <br>숨 조차 무거운 나날들 <br>그 속에서라도 진짜로 살고 싶어 <br>Oh be my self be my self <br>I'm here <br>But I'm here <br>Just be my self be my self <br>모두 거짓 뿐이지만 <br>But I'm here <br>Just be my self be my self <br>천천히 걸어가 <br>]]></content><category term="JJK" label="JJK"/><category term="I`m here (Feat. 초영)" label="I`m here (Feat. 초영)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JJK/Welcome_to_the_alley/</id><title>JJK - Welcome to the alley - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:32:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:32:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JJK/Welcome_to_the_alley/" title="JJK - Welcome to the alley - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 골목에 온 것을 <br>환영해 숙녀 여러분 <br>물론 신사 분도 환영해 <br>먼 길 오셨구만 <br>이름 같은 건 없어 <br>저 뒤에 내 친구들도 <br>마찬가지 하지만 사연은 <br>많지 뭐 예로 들면 <br>가게 키워 놨더니 <br>쫓겨났다거나 <br>임금 오르나 싶더니 <br>휴식 시간 뺐다거나 하는 <br>니네 동네엔 없는 얘기 <br>니가 TV나 인터넷에서 <br>본 거기가 여기야 <br>Welcome to alley <br>희망에게 버려지고 <br>저울은 기울여지고 <br>법대로 하며는 지고 <br>Welcome to alley <br>정의는 이가 빠지고 <br>권리는 상황 가리고 <br>평등은 자본주의고 <br>Welcome to alley <br>희망에게 버려지고 <br>저울은 기울여지고 <br>법대로 하며는 지고 <br>Welcome to alley <br>정의는 이가 빠지고 <br>권리는 상황 가리고 <br>평등은 자본주의고 <br>Welcome to alley <br>자 자 애들 인상이 <br>구려도 오해 말아 <br>고되게 살아서 그래 <br>그쪽한테 화난 거 아냐 <br>알고 보면 불쌍한 놈들이야 <br>당한 게 많아 <br>그럼에도 착해서 화내지도 <br>않고 서로를 나눠 <br>매일 나누고 나눠 <br>지들끼리 혐오하며 <br>갑과 을 기성 세대 <br>젊은 세대 심지어 남녀 <br>재벌과 서민 서민과 <br>좀 더 못 사는 서민 <br>뭉쳐도 모자랄 판에 <br>하악질 하며 털 세우니 <br>오늘은 어제와 같을 수 밖에 <br>내일도 없는 희망 <br>그렇다고 물 맞긴 싫어 <br>젖는 건 질색이니까 <br>처음 부터 이랬던 건 아냐 <br>골목도 따뜻했지 <br>햇빛 쬐며 고로롱 대는 <br>여유가 있었더랬지 <br>당신들도 참 하필 <br>지금 올게 뭐람 <br>다들 뜰라고 발악 <br>할 때 오면 나도 곤란해 <br>뭐 친하게 지내자구 <br>악수나 한번 때리지 <br>골목에 온걸 환영해 <br>Welcome to Alley <br>희망에게 버려지고 <br>저울은 기울여지고 <br>법대로 하며는 지고 <br>Welcome to alley <br>정의는 이가 빠지고 <br>권리는 상황 가리고 <br>평등은 자본주의고 <br>Welcome to alley <br>희망에게 버려지고 <br>저울은 기울여지고 <br>법대로 하며는 지고 <br>Welcome to alley <br>정의는 이가 빠지고 <br>권리는 상황 가리고 <br>평등은 자본주의고 <br>Welcome to alley <br>]]></content><category term="JJK" label="JJK"/><category term="Welcome to the alley" label="Welcome to the alley"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김연자/꽃_달_술/</id><title>김연자 - 꽃, 달, 술 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:32:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:32:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%97%B0%EC%9E%90/%EA%BD%83_%EB%8B%AC_%EC%88%A0/" title="김연자 - 꽃, 달, 술 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[술잔은 채워야 제 맛이지 <br>한 잔만 더 따라줘요 <br>아니야 오늘은 반 잔만 할래 <br>내 님 어디 계신가요 <br>당신이 떠난 이 자리에서 <br>나 홀로 또 술 한잔해 <br>내 꿈속에 오늘밤도 찾아와서 <br>못다했던 얘기를 해 <br>그대는 꽃이야 내 꽃이야 <br>내 가슴속에 피는 <br>그대는 달이야 내 달이야 <br>내 맘에 차오르는 <br>그대는 술이야 내 술이야 <br>취해버릴 것만 같아 <br>나에게 사랑한다 말해놓고 <br>지켜준다 말해놓고 어딜 갔나요 <br>슬프게 비가 오는 날에는 <br>그대와 나 자주 갔던 <br>그 술집에 잔을 두잔 놓고서 또 <br>그 사람을 기다리네 <br>그대는 꽃이야 내 꽃이야 <br>내 가슴속에 피는 <br>그대는 달이야 내 달이야 <br>내 맘에 차오르는 <br>그대는 술이야 내 술이야 <br>취해버릴 것만 같아 <br>나에게 사랑한다 말해놓고 <br>지켜준다 말해놓고 어딜 갔나요 <br>사랑이라 믿었고 <br>평생토록 우리 함께 할 줄 알았어 <br>슬프도록 아프게 <br>왜 자꾸만 나를 울려 <br>밤마다 피어나는 꽃잎 <br>그건 그대야 <br>나의 가슴에 차오르는 <br>달은 그대야 <br>그대는 술이야 내 술이야 <br>취해버릴 것 만 같아 <br>나에게 사랑한다 말해놓고 <br>지켜준다 말해놓고 어딜 갔나요 <br>]]></content><category term="김연자" label="김연자"/><category term="꽃, 달, 술" label="꽃, 달, 술"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/와이피지_YPZ/혼자있는_밤은_외로워/</id><title>와이피지 (YPZ) - 혼자있는 밤은 외로워 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:32:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:32:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%80%EC%9D%B4%ED%94%BC%EC%A7%80_YPZ/%ED%98%BC%EC%9E%90%EC%9E%88%EB%8A%94_%EB%B0%A4%EC%9D%80_%EC%99%B8%EB%A1%9C%EC%9B%8C/" title="와이피지 (YPZ) - 혼자있는 밤은 외로워 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 할 일은 내일로 <br>조금만 시간 좀 내줘 <br>혼자 있는 밤은 외로워 <br>I wanna do some today <br>오늘 할 일은 내일로 <br>조금만 시간 좀 내줘 <br>혼자 있는 밤은 외로워 <br>I wanna do some today <br>넌 어디서 뭐해 <br>난 외로워 이 밤이 <br>다시 전화해줘 빨리 <br>다른 약속 잡기 <br>전에 난 너와 <br>있는게 좋아 <br>친구들은 바쁘고 <br>club은 별로야 <br>후회할 일은 없으니 <br>말해봐 원하는건 뭐든지 <br>내 얼굴에 이상형을 대입해도되고 <br>방법은 여러가지야 거절은 <br>거절하니까 <br>곰곰이 다시 생각해봐 일단 <br>씻으면서 천천히 <br>아침까지 더 더 줄게 원 없이 <br>오늘 할 일은 내일로 <br>조금만 시간 좀 내줘 <br>혼자 있는 밤은 외로워 <br>I wanna do some today <br>오늘 할 일은 내일로 <br>조금만 시간 좀 내줘 <br>혼자 있는 밤은 외로워 <br>I wanna do some today <br>Slow down Jam out <br>One step Dance time <br>너와 오늘밤 we gon rock <br>이건 딱 봐도 찰떡 궁합 oh yeah <br>넌 왜 나를 오해해 <br>다른 남자들과 달라 <br>ain't a no brain man <br>나는 앞만보고가 황소같이 <br>ain't a no vacay <br>너 땜에 밤새도록 또 랩해 uh <br>Stay with me till the morning <br>회사 일 a thang ain't important <br>낮과 밤이 거꾸로 돌아가 팽이머리 <br>술은 그만해 now it's time for bed <br>We gon bust up our moves <br>아침에도 나랑 아침해 <br>Cuz i wanna love you too good <br>오늘 할 일은 내일로 <br>조금만 시간 좀 내줘 <br>혼자 있는 밤은 외로워 <br>I wanna do some today <br>오늘 할 일은 내일로 <br>조금만 시간 좀 내줘 <br>혼자 있는 밤은 외로워 <br>I wanna do some today <br>외로운 밤 that's no no <br>인생 뭐 있어 어차피 삶은 yolo <br>걍 내게 빨리 와 얼른 여기로 <br>고민할 거 없어 girl let's turn up <br>클럽은 너무 시끄러워 <br>조용하게 방 잡고 놀자 <br>so 지금 내게 전화해 <br>취하면 취하는대로 걍 그대로 눕자 <br>밖은 너무 추워 따뜻하게 이불 <br>안에 같이 숨자고 <br>예쁜 너의 바디라인 <br>못 참겠어 빨리 와 <br>기다리고 있을테니 <br>할꺼 다 하고 넘어와 <br>리드는 내가 할테니 넌 걍 따라와 <br>I be going so crazy <br>Yeh girl I be going <br>so crazy over you <br>오늘도 여전히 넌 너무 예뻐 <br>하루뿐이여도 생각하지 너는 내꺼 <br>오늘 할 일은 내일로 <br>조금만 시간 좀 내줘 <br>혼자 있는 밤은 외로워 <br>I wanna do some today <br>오늘 할 일은 내일로 <br>조금만 시간 좀 내줘 <br>혼자 있는 밤은 외로워 <br>I wanna do some today <br>]]></content><category term="와이피지 (YPZ)" label="와이피지 (YPZ)"/><category term="혼자있는 밤은 외로워" label="혼자있는 밤은 외로워"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DAY6_데이식스/Say_Wow/</id><title>DAY6 (데이식스) - Say Wow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:32:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:32:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DAY6_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EC%8B%9D%EC%8A%A4/Say_Wow/" title="DAY6 (데이식스) - Say Wow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You make me <br>You make me <br>You make me <br>You make me <br>You make me say wow <br>입이 다물어지지 않아 <br>그저 놀라워 <br>어떻게 넌 한번의 눈빛만으로 <br>날 붙잡아 <br>어딜 못 가겠어 <br>까만 배경에 너는 <br>은은하게 빛나 <br>흔들리고 있어 나 <br>어쩔 줄을 모르겠어 BABE <br>오늘 밤 내 앞의 넌 <br>그 어느 때보다 <br>사랑스러워 보여 <br>You make me say wow <br>하나부터 열까지 <br>하나도 빠짐없이 <br>감탄스러워 넌 <br>어쩜 그렇게 <br>나를 이렇게 <br>정신 못 차리게 <br>만들었대 <br>Girl you make me wanna say wow <br>1 2 3 4 <br>손을 갖다 대기 두려워 <br>아직 조금 더 <br>바라보고 싶어 <br>이 순간을 기억하고 싶어 <br>간직하고 싶어 <br>까만 배경에 너는 <br>은은하게 빛나 <br>안달 나고 있어 나 <br>이 다음은 모르겠어 BABE <br>오늘 밤 내 앞의 넌 <br>그 어느 때보다 <br>사랑스러워 보여 <br>You make me say wow <br>하나부터 열까지 <br>하나도 빠짐없이 <br>감탄스러워 넌 <br>어쩜 그렇게 <br>나를 이렇게 <br>정신 못 차리게 <br>만들었대 <br>Oh 다가갈까 하다 말고 <br>너를 안으려다 말고 <br>이렇게 하다 보면 <br>밤이 다 갈 것 같아 <br>Oh 다가갈까 하다 말고 <br>너를 안으려다 말고 밤새도록 <br>이 고민은 계속 돼 <br>오늘 밤 내 앞의 넌 <br>그 어느 때보다 <br>사랑스러워 보여 <br>You make me say wow <br>하나부터 열까지 <br>하나도 빠짐없이 <br>감탄스러워 넌 <br>어쩜 그렇게 <br>나를 이렇게 <br>정신 못 차리게 <br>만들었대 <br>Girl you make me wanna say wow <br>]]></content><category term="DAY6 (데이식스)" label="DAY6 (데이식스)"/><category term="Say Wow" label="Say Wow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DAY6_데이식스/장난_아닌데/</id><title>DAY6 (데이식스) - 장난 아닌데 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:32:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:32:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DAY6_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EC%8B%9D%EC%8A%A4/%EC%9E%A5%EB%82%9C_%EC%95%84%EB%8B%8C%EB%8D%B0/" title="DAY6 (데이식스) - 장난 아닌데 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[도대체 난 why why why 매일 밤 <br>천장만 바라보다가 <br>아이 아이야 너 땜에 <br>애만 태우는지 <br>그렇게 알아달라고 <br>눈치를 줘봐도 <br>전혀 알지 못하는데 <br>넌 왜 그걸 몰라 oh no <br>난 정말 너뿐인데 <br>장난 아닌데 <br>지금 내 눈에 <br>좋아한다 써져 있는데 <br>Why don't you feel it <br>이미 얼굴에 <br>티 날대로 나고 있는데 <br>너 계속 애매하게 애매하게 <br>웃으며 넘길 거야 <br>그렇게 또 그렇게 <br>너 맨날 이럴 거야 <br>커져만 가는 내 맘 <br>제발 어떻게 좀 해줘요 <br>I can’t stop loving you <br>이런 내 맘 포기해버릴까 <br>며칠 밤을 뜬 눈으로 고민해봐도 <br>안돼 안돼 너 때문에 <br>시선이 딴 데 못 가 <br>니 맘을 알아보려고 <br>말을 꺼내봐도 <br>농담처럼 넘기는데 <br>넌 왜 그걸 몰라 you know <br>난 너만 보고 있는 걸 <br>장난 아닌데 <br>지금 내 눈에 <br>좋아한다 써져 있는데 <br>Why don't you feel it <br>이미 얼굴에 <br>티 날대로 나고 있는데 <br>너 계속 애매하게 애매하게 <br>웃으며 넘길 거야 <br>그렇게 또 그렇게 <br>너 맨날 이럴 거야 <br>커져만 가는 내 맘 <br>제발 어떻게 좀 해줘요 <br>I can’t stop loving you <br>결국 쓸데없는 얘기만 듣다가 <br>얘기만 듣다가 <br>웃으며 널 보낸 나 왜 이러는데 oh <br>장난 아닌데 <br>지금 내 눈에 <br>좋아한다 써져 있는데 <br>Why don't you feel it <br>이미 얼굴에 <br>티 날대로 나고 있는데 <br>너 계속 애매하게 애매하게 <br>웃으며 넘길 거야 <br>그렇게 또 그렇게 <br>너 맨날 이럴 거야 <br>커져만 가는 내 맘 <br>제발 어떻게 좀 해줘요 <br>I can’t stop loving you <br>I can’t stop loving you <br>I can’t stop loving you <br>]]></content><category term="DAY6 (데이식스)" label="DAY6 (데이식스)"/><category term="장난 아닌데" label="장난 아닌데"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동교동바리스타_DongBar/벚꽃_보러가자/</id><title>동교동바리스타 (DongBar) - 벚꽃 보러가자 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:32:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:32:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EA%B5%90%EB%8F%99%EB%B0%94%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80_DongBar/%EB%B2%9A%EA%BD%83_%EB%B3%B4%EB%9F%AC%EA%B0%80%EC%9E%90/" title="동교동바리스타 (DongBar) - 벚꽃 보러가자 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이번 겨울은 괜히 더 춥더라 <br>차가웠던 만큼 아름다운 <br>꽃이 핀다고 하던데 <br>다가올 계절에 떨리는 맘으로 <br>너에게 고백할거야 <br>날씨 좋은 날 멀끔히 차려 입고 <br>너의 집 앞으로 데리러 갈 테니 <br>무작정 싫다고 말고 <br>제발 튕기지 좀 말고 <br>못이기는 척 <br>나와 함께 봄을 거닐어줘 <br>손을 잡으면 넌 내빼지 말고 <br>째려봐도 좋으니 <br>한숨 푹푹 쉬며 <br>질질 끌려 다니기만 해 <br>세상이 아름다울 거야 <br>한번 속는 셈 치고 <br>나랑 벚꽃 보러 가자 <br>요즘 독감이 유행이라더라 <br>아직 밤낮으로 꽃샘추위 <br>칼 바람 조심하라던데 <br>감기 들지 않게 따스히 안고서 <br>너에게 고백할거야 <br>날씨 좋은 날 멀끔히 차려 입고 <br>너의 집 앞으로 데리러 갈 테니 <br>무작정 싫다고 말고 <br>제발 튕기지 좀 말고 <br>못이기는 척 <br>나와 함께 봄을 거닐어줘 <br>손을 잡으면 넌 내빼지 말고 <br>째려봐도 좋으니 <br>한숨 푹푹 쉬며 <br>질질 끌려 다니기만 해 <br>세상이 아름다울 거야 <br>한번 속는 셈 치고 <br>나랑 벚꽃 보러 가자 <br>열심히 준비한 내 맘을 드디어 <br>너에게 전하는 순간 <br>니 얼굴 보자마자 <br>새하얘진 내 머릿속 <br>무심코 튀어나온 말 <br>오늘따라 참 날씨가 좋은데 <br>혼자 있을 니가 가엾기도 하고 <br>마침 나도 한가해서 <br>어쩌다가 근처라서 <br>쭈뼛거리다 어렵게 <br>꺼낸 말이었는데 <br>어쩜 그리도 허접할 수 있을까 <br>내가 준비한 건 고작 <br>이런 말이 아니었는데 <br>한심하고 부족하지만 <br>한번 속는 셈 치고 <br>나랑 벚꽃 보러 가자 <br>]]></content><category term="동교동바리스타 (DongBar)" label="동교동바리스타 (DongBar)"/><category term="벚꽃 보러가자" label="벚꽃 보러가자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Autograf/You_Might_Be_Feat_Lils/</id><title>Autograf - You Might Be (Feat. Lils) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:34:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:34:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Autograf/You_Might_Be_Feat_Lils/" title="Autograf - You Might Be (Feat. Lils) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's something in the air <br>There's something on the wire <br>There's something in the way I'm seeing <br>That keeps me satisfied <br>You've got it in my head <br>Stars up, you've got it in my eye <br>Somehow in the dark <br>You've found me and brought me to the light <br><br>And it feels like love <br>It feels like love <br>And it won't be enough <br>But it feels like <br>Like you might be the death of me <br><br>It's not like me to fall <br>It's really not my style <br>It's not like me to be so foolish <br>I haven't in a while <br>Cause it's something that you did <br>Is it something in my mind <br>I don't know what it is <br>That's got me, so beautifully blind <br><br>And it feels like love <br>It feels like love <br>And it won't be enough <br>But it feels like <br>Like you might be the death of me <br>You might be the death of me <br>Give me something to believe <br>You might be the death of me <br><br>And it feels like love <br>It feels like love <br>And it won't be enough <br>But it feels like <br>Like you might be the death of me <br>You might be the death of me <br>Give me something to believe <br>You might be the death of me]]></content><category term="Autograf" label="Autograf"/><category term="You Might Be (Feat. Lils)" label="You Might Be (Feat. Lils)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hailey_Knox/Geeks/</id><title>Hailey Knox - Geeks - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:34:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:34:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hailey_Knox/Geeks/" title="Hailey Knox - Geeks - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Just take a look at us, <br>Aren't we ridiculous? <br>It's safe to say we've got no common sense <br>Yeah, just take a peek at us <br>The free song, the mini-bus <br>The geeks you like to throw into the fense <br>You know it really hurts someone loving <br>You know it really hurts, but we'll rise above it <br>You know it's gonna hurt <br>Ooh ooh ooh oh, we know what we're worth <br>And you-uuu'll get what you deserve <br>When aaaaaa-all the Geeks inherit the Earth, yeah <br>Hey, aren't we absurd? We're just a bunch a nerds <br><br><br>Is safe to say you're much cooler than them <br>So, take your punch at us <br>Go ahead and steal the lunch from us <br>We'll take the blow and play our part in the end <br>You know it really hurts someone loving <br>You know it really hurts, but you can't stop it <br>Right where it really hurts <br>Ooh ooh ooh oh, we know what we're worth <br>And you-uuu'll get what you deserve <br>When aaaaaa-all the Geeks inherit the Earth, yeah <br>You toss your sticks and stones, and we'll just lick our wounds <br>Beware the underdog, payback is coming soon <br>Don't blame the Universe when the commas reverse <br>Just look at yourself <br>And you-uuu'll look at us and then you'll know it's up <br>'Cause ooh ooh oh, we know what we're worth <br>And you-uuu'll get what you deserve <br>When aaaaaa-all the Geeks inherit the Earth, yeah <br>Oooh ooh oh, we know what we're worth <br>We'll aaaa-all go from worst to first <br>When aaaaaa-all the Geeks inherit the Earth, yeah]]></content><category term="Hailey Knox" label="Hailey Knox"/><category term="Geeks" label="Geeks"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laidback_Luke/Paradise_Feat_Bright_Lights/</id><title>Laidback Luke - Paradise (Feat. Bright Lights) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:37:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:37:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laidback_Luke/Paradise_Feat_Bright_Lights/" title="Laidback Luke - Paradise (Feat. Bright Lights) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Can I take you there <br>Somewhere far where nobody cares <br>Who we are, what we doing here <br>I just wanna ride, no ceiling <br>I want that Sunday feeling <br>With the wind in your hair <br>And the sun on my lips <br>In the middle of nowhere <br>I could be your best rave <br>Everything you need I got <br>I know just what you like <br><br>I can be your paradise <br>I'll show you nothing but the bluest skies <br>I could be your paradise <br>Nobody but you and I <br><br>I can be your paradise <br>I can be your <br><br>I could be your dream babe <br>Fly you high to another place <br>Just leave your mind, let's go hideaway <br>I just wanna be your weekend <br>Your holiday, your season <br>With the wind in your hair <br>And the sun on my lips <br>In the middle of nowhere <br>I could be your best rave <br>Everything you need I got <br>I know just what you like <br><br>I can be your paradise <br>I'll show you nothing but the bluest skies <br>I could be your paradise <br>Nobody but you and I <br>I could be your <br><br>I can be your paradise <br>I can be your paradise <br>I can be your <br>I'll show you nothing but the bluest skies <br>I could be your paradise <br>Nobody but you and I <br>I could be your]]></content><category term="Laidback Luke" label="Laidback Luke"/><category term="Paradise (Feat. Bright Lights)" label="Paradise (Feat. Bright Lights)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공솔/내일을_거닐다/</id><title>공솔 - 내일을 거닐다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:38:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:38:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%EC%86%94/%EB%82%B4%EC%9D%BC%EC%9D%84_%EA%B1%B0%EB%8B%90%EB%8B%A4/" title="공솔 - 내일을 거닐다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아득한 세상 앞에 <br>한없이 작아져 가는 나의 꿈이 <br>점점 힘이 떨어져 가는데 <br>결국 난 푹 주저앉았어 <br>더 이상 내려갈 곳도 없는 <br>이 기분이 <br>견디기 힘들다 <br>나 버틸 수 있을까 <br>구부러진 이 길 위를 <br>나 걸을 수 있을까 <br>조금씩 아주 천천히 <br>발을 내딛어 <br>앞으로 걸어가면 <br>어제와 다른 내일이 <br>날 기다리진 않을까 <br>더는 자신이 없어 <br>앞이 보이지가 않아 <br>점점 희미해져만 가는데 <br>기댈 곳조차 없는걸 <br>더 이상 내려갈 곳도 없는 <br>이 기분이 <br>견디기 힘들다 <br>잘 해낼 수 있을까 <br>떨려오는 내 마음을 <br>붙잡을 순 없을까 <br>조금씩 아주 천천히 <br>손을 내밀어 앞으로 걸어가면 <br>어제와 다른 내일이 <br>날 기다리진 않을까 <br>이제야 나 알 것 같아 <br>내가 걸어온 이 길이 선명해져 <br>가는걸 봐 <br>어제와 다른 내일도 <br>날 웃음짓게 할거야 <br>조금씩 아주 천천히 <br>어제와 다른 내일이 <br>]]></content><category term="공솔" label="공솔"/><category term="내일을 거닐다" label="내일을 거닐다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/Zombie/</id><title>Jay Brannan - Zombie - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:38:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:38:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/Zombie/" title="Jay Brannan - Zombie - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Another head hangs lowly <br>Child is slowly taken <br>And the violence caused such silence <br>Who are we mistaken <br><br>But you see, it's not me, it's not my family <br>In your head, in your head they are fighting <br>With their tanks, and their bombs <br>And their bombs, and their guns <br>In your head, in your head, they are crying <br><br>What's in your head, in your head <br>Zombie, zombie, zombie <br>Hey, hey, hey What's in your head <br>In your head <br>Zombie, zombie, zombie <br>Hey, hey, hey, hey, oh, oh, oh <br>Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh <br><br>Another mother's breakin' <br>Heart is taken over <br>When the violence causes silence <br>We must be mistaken <br><br>It's the same old theme since 1916 <br>In your head, in your head they're still fighting <br>With their tanks, and their bombs <br>And their bombs, and their guns <br>In your head, in your head, they are dying <br><br>In your head, in your head <br>Zombie, zombie, zombie <br>Hey, hey, hey What's in your head <br>In your head <br>Zombie, zombie, zombie <br>Hey, hey, hey, hey, oh, oh, oh <br>Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh]]></content><category term="Jay Brannan" label="Jay Brannan"/><category term="Zombie" label="Zombie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/Good_Mother/</id><title>Jay Brannan - Good Mother - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:38:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:38:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/Good_Mother/" title="Jay Brannan - Good Mother - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've got money in my pocket <br>I like the color of my hair <br>I've got a friend who loves me <br>Got a house, I've got a car <br>I've got a good mother <br>And her voice is what keeps me here <br><br>Feet on ground <br>Heart in hand <br>Facing forward <br>Just be yourself <br>I've never wanted anything <br>No I've, no I've, I've never wanted anything so bad <br><br>Cardboard masks of all the people <br>I've been <br>Thrown out with all the rusted, tangled <br>Dented God Damned miseries <br>You could say I'm hard to hold <br>But if you knew me you'd know <br>I've got a good father <br>And his strength is what makes me cry <br><br>Feet on ground <br>Heart in hand <br>Facing forward <br>Just be yourself <br>I've never wanted anything <br>No I've, no I've, I've never wanted anything so bad <br><br>Feet on ground <br>Heart in hand <br>Feet on ground <br>Heart in hand]]></content><category term="Jay Brannan" label="Jay Brannan"/><category term="Good Mother" label="Good Mother"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/Both_Hands/</id><title>Jay Brannan - Both Hands - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:38:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:38:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/Both_Hands/" title="Jay Brannan - Both Hands - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I am walking <br>out in the rain <br>and I am listening to the low moan <br>of the dial tone again <br>and I am getting <br>nowhere with you <br>and I can't let it go <br>and I can't get through <br><br>And the old woman behind the pink curtains <br>and the closed door <br>on the first floor <br>she's listening through the air shaft <br>to see how long our swan song can last <br><br>And both hands <br>please use both hands <br>no don't close your eyes <br>I am writing <br>graffiti on your body <br>I am drawing the story of <br>how hard we tried]]></content><category term="Jay Brannan" label="Jay Brannan"/><category term="Both Hands" label="Both Hands"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/The_Freshmen/</id><title>Jay Brannan - The Freshmen - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:38:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:38:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/The_Freshmen/" title="Jay Brannan - The Freshmen - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I was young I knew everything <br>She a punk who rarely ever took advice <br>Now I'm guilt stricken, sobbing with my head on the floor <br>Stop a baby's breath and a shoe full of rice,no <br><br>I can't be held responsible <br>'Cause she was touching her face <br>I won't be held responsible <br>She fell in love in the first place <br><br>For the life of me I cannot remember <br>What made us think that we were wise and we'd never compromise <br>For the life of me I cannot believe we'd ever die for these sins <br>We were merely freshmen <br><br>My best friend took a week's vacation to forget her <br>His girl took a week's worth of valium and slept <br>Now he's guilt stricken sobbing with his head on the floor <br>Thinks about her now and how he never really wept he says <br><br>I can't be held responsible <br>'Cause she was touching her face <br>I won't be held responsible <br>She fell in love in the first place <br><br>For the life of me I cannot remember <br>What made us think that we were wise and we'd never compromise <br>For the life of me I cannot believe we'd ever die for these sins <br>We were merely freshmen <br><br>We've tried to wash our hands of all of this <br>We never talk of our lacking relationships <br>And how we're guilt stricken sobbing with our heads on the floor <br>We fell through the ice when we tried not to slip, we'd say <br><br>I can't be held responsible <br>'Cause she was touching her face <br>I won't be held responsible <br>She fell in love in the first place <br><br>For the life of me I cannot remember <br>What made us think that we were wise and we'd never compromise <br>For the life of me I cannot believe we'd ever die for these sins <br>We were merely freshmen <br><br>For the life of me I cannot remember <br>What made us think that we were wise and we'd never compromise <br>For the life of me I cannot believe we'd ever die for these sins <br>We were merely freshmen <br>We were merely freshmen <br>We were only freshmen]]></content><category term="Jay Brannan" label="Jay Brannan"/><category term="The Freshmen" label="The Freshmen"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/Drowning/</id><title>Jay Brannan - Drowning - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:38:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:38:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/Drowning/" title="Jay Brannan - Drowning - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's four AM again <br>Father, forgive me this sin <br>Uncomfortable in this life, yeah <br>I can't put down this knife, yeah <br><br>I'm carving words in my arms, baby <br>Hey, scars are part of my charm, maybe <br>I need the touch of a hand <br>This isn't what I had planned <br><br>I need relief from this life <br>I wanna slip away into the night <br>Don't wanna see the sun again <br>But can't get swallowed up by this tragic whirlwind <br>I wish the ocean was warm <br>I feel like drowning <br><br>I'm losing my faith in me <br>I can't remember the last time I felt free <br>From voices inside my head <br>When I taste liberation, they just feed me fear instead <br><br>You say I'm out of control <br>At least I still have a soul <br>No, I don't need your advice <br>Some compassion would be nice <br><br>I need relief from this life <br>I wanna slip away into the night <br>Don't wanna see the sun again <br>But can't get swallowed up by this tragic whirlwind <br>I wish the ocean was warm <br>I feel like drowning <br><br>I can't take any more of your pills <br>They hold my head up <br>But still it feels so wrong <br>I can't believe the price that I've paid <br>For this chemically induced, perceivably ideal, take it with a glass of water day <br><br>I need relief from this life <br>I wanna slip away into the night <br>Don't wanna see the sun again <br>But can't get swallowed up by this tragic whirlwind <br>I wish the ocean was warm <br>I feel like drowning]]></content><category term="Jay Brannan" label="Jay Brannan"/><category term="Drowning" label="Drowning"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/Blowin__In_The_Wind/</id><title>Jay Brannan - Blowin? In The Wind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:38:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:38:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/Blowin__In_The_Wind/" title="Jay Brannan - Blowin? In The Wind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How many roads must a man walk down <br>Before you call him a man <br>And how many seas must the white dove sail <br>Before she sleeps in the sand <br>And how many years must the cannonballs fly <br>Before they're forever banned <br><br>The answer, my friend, is blowin' in the wind <br>The answer is blowin' in the wind <br><br>And how many times can a man look up <br>Before he can see the sky <br>And how many ears must one man have <br>Before he can hear people cry <br>And how many deaths will it take 'til he knows that <br>Too many people have died <br><br>The answer, my friend, is blowin' in the wind <br>The answer is blowin' in the wind <br><br>And how many years can a mountain exist <br>Before it falls to the sea <br>And how many years must some people exist <br>Before they're allowed to be free <br>And how many times can a man turn his head <br>Pretending he just doesn't see <br><br>The answer, my friend, is blowin' in the wind <br>The answer is blowin' in the wind]]></content><category term="Jay Brannan" label="Jay Brannan"/><category term="Blowin? In The Wind" label="Blowin? In The Wind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/All_I_Want/</id><title>Jay Brannan - All I Want - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:38:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:38:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/All_I_Want/" title="Jay Brannan - All I Want - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I am on a lonely road and I am traveling <br>Looking for something, what can it be <br>Oh I hate you some, I hate you some, I love you some <br>Oh I love you when I forget about me <br><br>I want to be strong I want to laugh along <br>I want to belong to the living <br>Alive, alive, I want to get up and jive <br>I want to wreck my stockings in some juke box dive <br>Do you want do you want do you want to dance with me baby <br>Do you want to take a chance <br>On maybe finding some sweet romance with me baby <br>Well, come on <br><br>All I really really want our love to do <br>Is to bring out the best in me and in you too <br>All I really really want our love to do to do <br>Is to bring out the best in me and in you <br>I want to talk to you, I want to shampoo you <br>I want to renew you again and again <br>Applause, applause Life is our cause <br>When I think of your kisses my mind see saws <br>Do you see do you see do you see how you hurt me baby <br>And so I hurt you too <br>Then we both feel so blue <br><br>I am on a lonely road and I am traveling <br>Looking for the key to set me free <br>Oh the jealousy, the greed is the unraveling <br>And it undoes all the joy that could be <br>I want to have fun, I want to shine like the sun <br>Oh I want to be the one that you want to see <br>I want to knit you a sweater <br>I want to write you a love letter <br>I want to make you feel better <br>I want to make you feel free <br>I want to make you feel free <br>Oh I want to make you feel free <br>Oh I want to make you feel free]]></content><category term="Jay Brannan" label="Jay Brannan"/><category term="All I Want" label="All I Want"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/Say_Its_Possible/</id><title>Jay Brannan - Say It`s Possible - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:38:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:38:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/Say_Its_Possible/" title="Jay Brannan - Say It`s Possible - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I see the lights are turning <br>And I look outside the stars are burning <br>Through this changing time <br>It could have been anything we want <br>It's fine salvation was just a passing thought <br>It was just a passing thought <br><br>Don't wait act now <br>This amazing offer won't last long <br>It's only a chance to pave the path we're on <br>I know there are more exciting things to talk about <br>And in time we'll sort it out <br>And in time we'll sort it out <br><br>And though they say it's possible to me <br>I don't see how it's probable <br>I see the course we're on <br>Spinning farther from what I know <br>I'll hold on <br>Tell me that you won't let go <br>Tell me that you won't let go <br><br>And truth is such a funny thing <br>With all these people <br>Keep on telling me <br>They know what's best <br>And what to be frightened of <br>And all the rest are wrong <br>They know nothing about us <br>They know nothing about us <br><br>And though they say it's possible to me <br>I don't see how it's probable <br>I see the course we're on <br>Spinning farther from what I know <br>I'll hold on <br>Tell me that you won't let go <br>Tell me that you won't let go <br><br>I'm not alright <br>I'm not alright <br>I'm not alright <br>I'm not alright <br><br>This could be something beautiful <br>Combine our love into something wonderful <br>But times are tough I know and the pull <br>Of what we can't give up takes hold]]></content><category term="Jay Brannan" label="Jay Brannan"/><category term="Say It`s Possible" label="Say It`s Possible"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/Beautifully/</id><title>Jay Brannan - Beautifully - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:38:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:38:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jay_Brannan/Beautifully/" title="Jay Brannan - Beautifully - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Every time he goes, she dies <br>Every time she comes, she cries <br><br>He was her long, bright future <br>In the middle of a wrong, dark road <br>He loved her, but he wasn't too sure <br>If he could return the love she showed <br>When she said, my love extends <br>Beyond the realm of being friends <br>He kissed her head <br>And quietly he said <br><br>It's not that you're not beautiful, you're just not beautiful to me <br>She said, how beautiful do I have to be <br>When I look in the mirror, you're the only thing I see <br>And I have loved you beautifully <br><br>Well, ten thousand tears passed by <br>But she never let him see her cry <br>And he called up down one night <br>He said, let's get in the car and just drive <br><br>He talked a lot about loneliness <br>But why, she didn't know <br>And some song about Memphis <br>Was playin' on the radio <br>She said, let's stop the car and slow dance <br>Won't you just give me a chance <br>He took her hand <br>And hoped she'd understand <br><br>It's not that you're not beautiful, you're just not beautiful to me <br>She said, how beautiful do I have to be <br>When I look in the mirror, you're the only thing I see <br>And I have loved you beautifully <br><br>Well, she'll burn that bridge <br>And build a house <br>And swallow the smoke in her mouth <br>And she'll feel the burn <br>And then make the choice <br>To put the fire in her voice <br><br>It's not that you're not beautiful, you're just not beautiful to me <br>She said, how beautiful do I have to be <br>When I look in the mirror, you're the only thing I see <br>And I have loved you beautifully]]></content><category term="Jay Brannan" label="Jay Brannan"/><category term="Beautifully" label="Beautifully"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/Weighted_Down_With_Sorrow/</id><title>Insomnium - Weighted Down With Sorrow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:43:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:43:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/Weighted_Down_With_Sorrow/" title="Insomnium - Weighted Down With Sorrow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing can offer content <br>Nothing can ease the pain <br>Nothing can wear off the sorrow <br>One is born to bear within <br><br>While your world is worth of trying <br>My world is mere cold <br>No chance in disillusion <br>Only the end of the road <br><br>Man weighed down with sorrow <br>Anguished from the sole being <br>Destined to live with uneasiness <br>Always the hard way <br><br>Cold is the world <br>For the ones excluded <br>Dark is the path <br>In the absence of light <br>Compelled to cherish beauty in longing <br>Cling on love amidst of the suffering <br><br>No chance in disillusion <br>No, not in this world <br>Not for a man <br>Weighed down with sorrow <br>Only the end of the road]]></content><category term="Insomnium" label="Insomnium"/><category term="Weighted Down With Sorrow" label="Weighted Down With Sorrow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/Into_The_Woods/</id><title>Insomnium - Into The Woods - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:43:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:43:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/Into_The_Woods/" title="Insomnium - Into The Woods - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Now close your eyes <br>And open your weary heart <br>Let me soothe away the woes <br>Of fiendish world <br><br>As will the sun bathe the land <br>In its warming light <br>So shall the moon ascend <br>To guide the day to wane <br>In turn the rain to hush <br>The tumult of this world <br>And the wind to rise <br>Sigh a lullaby in trees <br><br>Not in these troubled times <br>I'm not the one you pined for <br>No, not into calmer waters <br>I'm not the one you long for <br><br>But a scarecrow, an anathema to the world <br>Looking in from the outside <br>It's time to turn my back <br>Walk off the beaten path <br>Seek heartening in solitude <br><br>The arch of sky is roof where I call it home <br>Drizzle of rain, the only music from now on <br>My bed is made from juniper's boughs <br>Of mire and moss my pillow <br><br>Lone footprints diverge from tree line <br>Autumn veils the sloughs with rime <br>Shell of quagmire <br>Yet too fragile to bear a man]]></content><category term="Insomnium" label="Insomnium"/><category term="Into The Woods" label="Into The Woods"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/The_Lay_Of_Autumn/</id><title>Insomnium - The Lay Of Autumn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:43:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:43:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/The_Lay_Of_Autumn/" title="Insomnium - The Lay Of Autumn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I I sing with a shattered voice <br>I I sing with a heavy heart <br><br>There in the deepest well of dreams <br>Echoed a distant song <br>I hearkened to the hallowed voice <br>Stirred from ageless sleep <br><br>Through this barren soil you came <br>Sweet scent of spring <br>Came and cast the earth in bloom <br>Lent your light to me <br><br>But now the summer's dreams are bent <br>Like grain against the scythe <br>And memories of blissful days <br>They fall like leaves <br><br>For autumn's songs are made of loss <br>Of yearning and regret <br>In bitter tone they are recited <br>Uttered with a heavy heart <br><br>I sing with shattered voice <br>A tale of marred souls <br>I cry for consumed hearts <br>And springs forever gone <br><br>The lights of sun and stars will fade <br>And moon covers its face <br>All the tunes will quiet down <br>And the songs shall die <br><br>As this wretched heart unfolds <br>Like mouth of furnace grins <br>Inside there's but a blackened cell <br>Full of filth and flames <br><br>There once was time when I resounded by your side <br>There once was time when I trembled under your eyes <br><br>What do I hear when you're gone <br>The wind's harrowing cry <br>What do I hear when you're gone <br>The sighing of the languid grief <br>Cold creeps in, silver crowns the land <br>Long are the evening now, grave the guilt's weight <br>Stars shriek their emptiness in the darkling sky <br>All the world is but a barrow shrouded in white]]></content><category term="Insomnium" label="Insomnium"/><category term="The Lay Of Autumn" label="The Lay Of Autumn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/Against_The_Stream/</id><title>Insomnium - Against The Stream - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:43:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:43:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/Against_The_Stream/" title="Insomnium - Against The Stream - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And down we go again <br>Into the ocean of sorrow <br>Towards to sea of despair <br>In the deep groves of the earth <br>Lifeline running in roaring stream <br><br>Like sand slipping through my fingers <br>Nothing ever lasts, ever will <br><br>To impart elegance all living <br>Experience the grandeur in giving <br>Felicity found in commitment <br>Tranquillity in mere being <br><br>And down we go again <br>Under the relentless waves <br>Into the arms of calm breakers <br>Into bayou of forgotten dreams <br><br>Like sand slipping through my fingers <br>Nothing ever lasts, ever will <br><br>To impart elegance all living <br>Experience the grandeur in giving <br>From existence into oblivion <br>Not in cycles but in lines <br><br>Getting nowhere fast <br>By contending with time <br>Accept the alteration <br>Come to terms with your days <br><br>Down we go just the same <br>Into the ocean of sorrow <br>Towards to sea of despair <br><br>This river runs relentlessly <br>And this river runs deep <br>Not in cycles but in lines]]></content><category term="Insomnium" label="Insomnium"/><category term="Against The Stream" label="Against The Stream"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/The_Harrowing_Years/</id><title>Insomnium - The Harrowing Years - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:43:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:43:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/The_Harrowing_Years/" title="Insomnium - The Harrowing Years - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This I have learnt <br>World forces all of us down <br>The fleeing years bend our backs <br>Love but smears our hearts <br><br>Here I now lie still like a broken bow <br>Soul sullen and rigid with the will to die <br>Sighing after the days long since gone <br>Cursing every step on this ill fated trail <br><br>In vain I try to forget In vain I try to forgive <br>Black bird from evening sky raven from heaths of night <br>Come and take my cares carry away the grief <br>Bereave me of my woes rend off these earthly throes <br>Fly them to deepest lakes to the starlit shores <br><br>This I have learnt <br>Even the sweetest wine turns to sour <br>We work our fingers to the bone <br>All our efforts of no avail <br><br>Here we all are but troubled guests <br>On darkling earth <br>Lost echoes that pine away <br>Into the dusk <br>Nothing more than the wind to rely on <br>Nothing more than the death <br>to comfort us in the end <br><br>This I have heard <br>All ends in serene sleep <br>All these sorrows are washed away <br>As we lapse into the night <br><br>But I know it's a lie]]></content><category term="Insomnium" label="Insomnium"/><category term="The Harrowing Years" label="The Harrowing Years"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/Where_The_Last_Wave_Broke/</id><title>Insomnium - Where The Last Wave Broke - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:43:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:43:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/Where_The_Last_Wave_Broke/" title="Insomnium - Where The Last Wave Broke - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How does it feel <br>To welcome the new day <br>Not worth saving <br>To fall down on own imprudent acts <br>The wind answers quietly <br>Clears the black smoke far thick to see <br>Unfolds the true nature of man <br><br>And this fire it burns <br>Consuming us all <br>Withered garden for posterity <br>Inheritance in flames <br><br>When the mankind moves <br>Rest of the life shakes <br>All once green turned into stone <br>Flesh into dust and soil <br>Where the last wave broke <br>The shores blazed red <br>And place once called home <br>Turned into hall of dead <br><br>How does it feel <br>Bite the hand that feeds you <br>Poison the well that waters you <br>Prospects made from castles of sand <br>Legacy in barren land <br><br>Breed, greed, bleed <br>Legacy in barren land <br>The last wave broke <br>Prospects made from castles of sand]]></content><category term="Insomnium" label="Insomnium"/><category term="Where The Last Wave Broke" label="Where The Last Wave Broke"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/Down_With_The_Sun/</id><title>Insomnium - Down With The Sun - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:43:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:43:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/Down_With_The_Sun/" title="Insomnium - Down With The Sun - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[O darkness, if in thy arms I could rest <br>For a while and with these earthly eyes <br>See thy dim smile <br><br>Maid of twilight, lass of duskfall <br>Hang the moon on the sky's arch <br>Soothe the weight of a darkling day <br><br>Rock here in the birch's lap <br>Swing in the manor of wind <br>Lay down your weary head <br>Let the blue stars darken <br><br>O silence, if in thy cradle I could sway <br>Like a child, heart the amending song <br>The sighing of the shades <br><br>Maid of twilight, lass of duskfall <br>Serve thy goblet to me <br>Let me drink to the last drop <br>The sweet opiate of the dreams <br><br>Ours is the silence <br>The echo old ageless night <br>A gleam in the blackest of streams <br>One fleeing moment <br><br>For vain is all the toil and trouble <br>Vain is all the heartbreak <br>In the end I'll find my solace <br>In an earthen cradle <br><br>So good night]]></content><category term="Insomnium" label="Insomnium"/><category term="Down With The Sun" label="Down With The Sun"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/Equivalence/</id><title>Insomnium - Equivalence - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:43:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:43:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Insomnium/Equivalence/" title="Insomnium - Equivalence - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Feed off the melancholy <br>Get drunk from despair <br>Rejoice in the name of failure <br>Deliverance found in pain <br><br>Live, learn and love <br>Treasure all the colours <br>Even in the thick of night <br>Daylight holds sway]]></content><category term="Insomnium" label="Insomnium"/><category term="Equivalence" label="Equivalence"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강소리/단둘이야_Inst/</id><title>강소리 - 단둘이야 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:44:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:44:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC/%EB%8B%A8%EB%91%98%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC_Inst/" title="강소리 - 단둘이야 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[단둘이야 내 눈 가리고 <br>빨간 장미꽃 내게 안겨줘 <br>단둘이야 입술을 열어 <br>달콤 달콤히 고백해줘요 <br>말해야 알까 모를까 <br>애타는 내 맘 <br>기다리다 지쳐만 갔네 <br>얄미워 미워 미워 미운 사람 <br>한 마리 벌이 되어 <br>콕 콕 나를 쏴주세요 <br>우리 둘이 나누는 유휴 유휴 <br>우리 둘이 나누는 유휴 유휴 <br>내숭은 그만 무뚝뚝 그만 <br>우리 둘이 둘이 단둘이 <br>단둘이야 내 눈 가리고 <br>빨간 장미꽃 내게 안겨줘 <br>단둘이야 입술을 열어 <br>달콤 달콤히 고백해줘요 <br>말해야 알까 모를까 <br>애타는 내 맘 <br>기다리다 지쳐만 갔네 <br>얄미워 미워 미워 미운 사람 <br>한 마리 벌이 되어 <br>콕 콕 나를 쏴주세요 <br>우리 둘이 나누는 유휴 유휴 <br>우리 둘이 나누는 유휴 유휴 <br>내숭은 그만 무뚝뚝 그만 <br>우리 둘이 둘이 단둘이 <br>우리 둘이 나누는 유휴 유휴 <br>우리 둘이 나누는 유휴 유휴 <br>내숭은 그만 무뚝뚝 그만 <br>우리 둘이 둘이 단둘이 <br>우리 둘이 둘이 단둘이]]></content><category term="강소리" label="강소리"/><category term="단둘이야 (Inst.)" label="단둘이야 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강소리/단둘이야/</id><title>강소리 - 단둘이야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:44:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:44:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC/%EB%8B%A8%EB%91%98%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC/" title="강소리 - 단둘이야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[단둘이야 내 눈 가리고 <br>빨간 장미꽃 내게 안겨줘 <br>단둘이야 입술을 열어 <br>달콤 달콤히 고백해줘요 <br>말해야 알까 모를까 <br>애타는 내 맘 <br>기다리다 지쳐만 갔네 <br>얄미워 미워 미워 미운 사람 <br>한 마리 벌이 되어 <br>콕 콕 나를 쏴주세요 <br>우리 둘이 나누는 유휴 유휴 <br>우리 둘이 나누는 유휴 유휴 <br>내숭은 그만 무뚝뚝 그만 <br>우리 둘이 둘이 단둘이 <br>단둘이야 내 눈 가리고 <br>빨간 장미꽃 내게 안겨줘 <br>단둘이야 입술을 열어 <br>달콤 달콤히 고백해줘요 <br>말해야 알까 모를까 <br>애타는 내 맘 <br>기다리다 지쳐만 갔네 <br>얄미워 미워 미워 미운 사람 <br>한 마리 벌이 되어 <br>콕 콕 나를 쏴주세요 <br>우리 둘이 나누는 유휴 유휴 <br>우리 둘이 나누는 유휴 유휴 <br>내숭은 그만 무뚝뚝 그만 <br>우리 둘이 둘이 단둘이 <br>우리 둘이 나누는 유휴 유휴 <br>우리 둘이 나누는 유휴 유휴 <br>내숭은 그만 무뚝뚝 그만 <br>우리 둘이 둘이 단둘이 <br>우리 둘이 둘이 단둘이 <br>]]></content><category term="강소리" label="강소리"/><category term="단둘이야" label="단둘이야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LP/No_Witness/</id><title>LP - No Witness - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:45:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:45:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LP/No_Witness/" title="LP - No Witness - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How do I get you out of my head <br>How do I get you back to my bed <br>Oh lord, oh lord <br>Tell me you're crazy, tell me you're scared <br>Tell me you still love what you had <br>Oh lord, oh lord <br><br>When there's no more sins to care about <br>And the hard rain dark times pour on down <br>When it's all been said and done <br>No one can save me <br><br>Oh, bear me no witness <br>Hear me now <br>Oh, oh oh, bear me no witness <br>Tell me how many highs can get us so down <br>Cause it don't matter how many times we go 'round <br>Oh, oh oh, bear me no witness <br><br>No one can save me, love me or hate me <br>I'll keep on waiting, nothing I won't do <br>Take you, my love like a street cut drug <br>Never know what you're really made of <br>Oh lord, oh lord <br><br>When there's no more sins to care about <br>And the hard rain dark times pour on down <br>When it's all been said and done <br>No one can save me <br><br>Oh, bear me no witness <br>Hear me now <br>Oh, oh oh, bear me no witness <br>Tell me how many highs can get us so down <br>Cause it don't matter how many times we go 'round <br>Oh, oh oh, bear me no witness <br><br>No one can save me, love me or hate me <br>No one can save me, love me or hate me <br>No one can save me, love me or hate me <br>No one can save me, love me or hate me <br><br>When there's no more sins to care about <br>And the hard rain dark times pour on down <br>When it's all been said and done <br>No one can save me <br><br>Oh, bear me no witness <br>Hear me now <br>Oh, oh oh, bear me no witness <br><br>Oh, bear me no witness <br>Hear me now <br>Oh, oh oh, bear me no witness <br>Hear me now <br>Oh, bear me no witness <br>Hear me now <br>Oh, oh oh, bear me no witness]]></content><category term="LP" label="LP"/><category term="No Witness" label="No Witness"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Evidence/Throw_It_All_Away/</id><title>Evidence - Throw It All Away - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:48:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:48:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Evidence/Throw_It_All_Away/" title="Evidence - Throw It All Away - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Chorus] <br>I got some money, I'mma blow it all today <br>They say 'Michael, don't throw it all away' <br>And my reply was 'There's more on the way' <br>When I said it, I was walking in the rain <br><br>[Verse 1] <br>I did a show in Chicago on the first <br>Now I'm back in LA like Chicago and First <br>No sun but I fathered this verse <br>That's all I'm probably worth <br>And I'm from sunny CA to reign on all of this earth <br>Rainy terrain, receive the God sent messages <br>We know the answer, but dance around what the question is <br>(What is it?) It's back to who's on first <br>It's my dog <br>It's his tail <br>It's the chase <br>It's the search <br>It's the ignorance that causes all the bliss in my surroundings <br>Cause dealing with reality's like drawing out your boundaries <br>And I refuse to be referred as less than a creative <br>So catch me when I'm live in town as I've been demonstrating <br>That I could find my greatness in the waking of my absence <br>And absolutely kill it when they're dealing out these bad hands <br>A player plays what a player's dealt <br>And carries baggage like conveyor belts <br>And never fucking saves his wealth <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I got some money, I'mma blow it all today <br>They say 'Michael, don't throw it all away' <br>And my reply was 'There's more on the way' <br>When I said it, I was walking in the rain <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>I write to Alchemist 'cause others don't inspire me <br>I got my people and they got my back entirely <br>I kill with Iriscience on the side of me <br>By myself, I lay 'em out and iron out the irony (Flat) <br>What a long winding road it's been <br>With no sign of slowing up around its turns and bends <br>How many have friends that ain't foes within? <br>Dirty laundry in the wash, but them clothes don't spin <br>I mean, really, I kill two birds with one bullet <br>The target's when I line it up, the trigger's when I pull it <br>Out the gate, a bit late, but the champ is back <br>I need a third hand to wear my rings and hold plaques <br>I hit the track like the run is new <br>Hands high like a stick-up, Killer Michael running jewels <br>It's true, the eyes slanted, my fam rock the planet <br>Don't take fans for granted like the money is due <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Got some money, I'mma blow it all today <br>They say 'Michael, don't throw it all away' <br>And my reply was 'There's more on the way' <br>When I said it, I was walking in the rain <br>(What is it?) <br>Got some money, I'mma blow it all today <br>They say 'Michael, don't throw it all away' <br>And my reply was 'There's more on the way' <br>When I said it, I was walking in the rain]]></content><category term="Evidence" label="Evidence"/><category term="Throw It All Away" label="Throw It All Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/We_The_Kings/The_Story_Of_Your_Life/</id><title>We The Kings - The Story Of Your Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:49:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:49:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/We_The_Kings/The_Story_Of_Your_Life/" title="We The Kings - The Story Of Your Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The story of your life is so twisted <br>‘cause someone out there is missing <br>Everything you do <br>You’re wasted <br>Nothing ever rearlly makes sense <br>If you keep searching, you’ll find me <br>Hidden inside you <br>Leave behind your troubled eyes <br>See brand new what I can do <br>Just say yes, if you really want me to <br>We can stay like this or go, go, go <br>We can take it too fast or take it slow <br>We can spend our lives oceanside <br>or count the stars in the desert on a magic night <br>You can lie awake in bed or come and sleep with me instead <br>You can give me one chance to take your hand <br>I’ll fill the empty pages as you write <br>the story of your life <br><br>the story of life is unwritten <br>So put me down as your ticket <br>Don’t even fight it <br>you’re shaking <br>you’re not sure of the ending <br>but let me be the beginning just put it in writing <br>so leave behind troubled eyes <br>See bran new what I can do <br>Just say yes, if you really want me to <br>We can stay like this or go, go, go <br>We can take it too fast or take it slow <br>We can spend our lives oceanside <br>or count the stars in the desert on a magic night <br>You can lie awake in bed or came and sleep with me instead <br>if give me one chance to take your hand <br>I’ll fill the empty pages as you write <br>the story of your life <br>This is now, I don’t mean maybe <br>just wanna scream and call you baby now <br>take a chance and call me crazy <br>smile kid, there’s only one way out <br>We can stay like this or go, go, go <br>We can take it too fast or take it slow <br>We can spend our lives oceanside <br>or count the stars in the desert on a magic night <br>You can lie awake in bed or come and sleep with me instead <br>if give me one chance to take your hand <br>I’ll fill the empty pages as you write <br>the story of your life <br>fill the empty pages <br>fill the empty pages]]></content><category term="We The Kings" label="We The Kings"/><category term="The Story Of Your Life" label="The Story Of Your Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/We_The_Kings/Heaven_Can_Wait/</id><title>We The Kings - Heaven Can Wait - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:49:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:49:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/We_The_Kings/Heaven_Can_Wait/" title="We The Kings - Heaven Can Wait - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a song for the nights I think too much and <br>Here’s a song when I imagine us together <br>here’s a song for when we talk too much and I forget my words <br>Heaven can wait up high in the sky <br>It’s you and I <br>Heaven can wait deep down in your eyes <br>I’m yours tonight <br>lay your heart next to mine I feel so alive <br>tell me you want me to stay forever cause heaven can wait <br><br>Here’s a song for the one who stole my heart and <br>ran so far that cupid couldn’t catch her <br>Here’s a song for the kid who aim so high, he shot her down <br>heaven can wait up high in the sky <br>It’s you and I <br>Heaven can wait deep down in your eyes <br>I’m yours tonight <br>lay your heart next to mine I feel so alive <br>tell me you want me to stay forever cause heaven can wait <br><br>Here’s a song for the nights I drink too much and spell my words <br>heaven can wait up high in the sky <br>It’s you and I <br>Heaven can wait deep down in your eyes <br>I’m yours tonight <br>lay your heart next to mine I feel so alive <br>tell me you want me to stay forever cause heaven can wait <br><br>cause heaven can wait <br>cause heaven can wait]]></content><category term="We The Kings" label="We The Kings"/><category term="Heaven Can Wait" label="Heaven Can Wait"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Buried_By_Time__Dust/</id><title>1349 - Buried By Time &amp; Dust - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:49:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:49:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Buried_By_Time__Dust/" title="1349 - Buried By Time &amp; Dust - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Visions of that no mornings <br>light ever will come <br>I'm to old now <br>The dark is so near <br>will I ever reach <br>the land beyond <br>This is where we go when we have to <br>die <br><br>I've been old since the birth of time <br>Time buried me in earth <br>centuries ago, I tasted blood <br>Buried by time and dust <br>Many years has pasted since the funeral <br>Missing the blood of human throats <br>so many years, ages ago <br>I must await, feel my bodies <br>stench <br><br>Wanderings out of space <br>Wandering out of time <br>A world out of light, death at the end <br>Only silence can be heard, silence of peoples tears <br>No one knows my grave <br>Buried by time and dust]]></content><category term="1349" label="1349"/><category term="Buried By Time &amp; Dust" label="Buried By Time &amp; Dust"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Liberation/</id><title>1349 - Liberation - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:50:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:50:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Liberation/" title="1349 - Liberation - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[As time floats by I'm stuck <br>on this point of no return <br>The world, a stage upon which <br>a neular play unfolds <br>flickering by in shades of grey <br>permeated by absurdity <br>like a glossy polished reality <br>slowly fading into oblivion <br><br>unconscious but aware <br>Awake, yet dreaming <br>Alive, still limbonic <br>Awaiting the liberation <br><br>The fallen angel of Doom appears <br>I behold his fury in fear <br>Disguised he enters the play <br>fulfilling the obscurity <br>I see the stage crumble <br>I see the curtains fall <br>the final act begins <br>as death reveals it's disguise <br><br>Escaping mankind, escaping doom <br>outrun the fear, outrun Death <br>Heading for the promised land <br>to gain immortality <br>Let the play of liberation begin anew <br><br>The circle is ended <br>a new play begins <br>no need to witness <br>know the end <br>Let all fears go by <br>drift into oblivion]]></content><category term="1349" label="1349"/><category term="Liberation" label="Liberation"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Evil_Oath/</id><title>1349 - Evil Oath - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:50:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:50:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Evil_Oath/" title="1349 - Evil Oath - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Riding the wings of the unholy wind <br>to be carried to an eclipsed place of <br>chaos <br>To be taken far away from holy ground <br>Away from the falling Christ and his <br>father <br><br>As nights and days passes, till we turned <br>to dust <br><br>Series of simple gestures make me <br>perish <br>as I said farewell to light an god of <br>disillusions <br>To follow thee into darkness which i long <br>for <br>The source of fire, always burning in my <br>heart <br><br>I hereby give you ME <br>to declare WAR <br>I bare no regrets for these actions <br>I fulfill them with pride, I worship all that <br>is ours <br>Joining the mach of the even fall <br>To be at your disposal, the blade when <br>you release damnation <br>I fulfill these actions with pride, I worship <br>all that is ours <br><br>Open the gates, greet me welcome <br>Independence carried me away from lies <br>and hypocrisy <br>The god of sickness and his sickening <br>angels <br>To reach a new aeon, which I seek <br><br>As nights and days passes until I've <br>turned to dust <br>My soul is thine to cleanse, to form <br>To shape like thy signs of yours]]></content><category term="1349" label="1349"/><category term="Evil Oath" label="Evil Oath"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Legion/</id><title>1349 - Legion - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:50:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:50:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Legion/" title="1349 - Legion - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Like a ghost I wander <br>Withdrawn from reality <br>becoming a misanthrope <br>summoning spirits to me <br>fighting humanity <br>no need to watch my back <br>for they are fighting with me <br><br>We match into war slaughtering mankind <br>If you try to stop us we will give you hell <br>from which we came <br>join us if you dare <br>fight us if you can <br>Choose sides <br>or escape to survive <br><br>Blood red is the sky <br>Blood red is the earth <br>Blood red are the rivers and mountains <br>that we pass <br>Black smoke fills the air <br>from the corpse pyres around <br>burning mankind <br>and have it buried underground <br><br>Their funeral pyres, lighting the earth <br>Smoke blots out the sun, creating eternal night <br>gone is humanity, trampled to the ground <br>suffocated by the ashes, utopia of thy design <br><br>Lend us your sword <br>and ours will be yours <br>Give us your strength <br>and receive it thousand told <br>The demon army <br>marching over forth <br>fulfilling the vision <br>an untained world <br><br>Don't oppose us resistance is futile <br>we annihilate all enemy forces <br>Nobody can stop us now <br>defeat of mankind, a victory of <br>misanthropy]]></content><category term="1349" label="1349"/><category term="Legion" label="Legion"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Satanic_Propaganda/</id><title>1349 - Satanic Propaganda - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:50:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:50:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Satanic_Propaganda/" title="1349 - Satanic Propaganda - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Guided by the voice of silence <br>I seek the chosen ones <br>To fulfill the wishes <br>of the master beneath <br>Their souls are mine to keep <br>sold for hopes and dreams <br>Signing with their own blood <br>I rule their destiny <br><br>I offer immortality <br><br>I offer power and <br>Influence on whatever their simple <br>and primitive minds is able to come <br>up with of <br>stupid wishes and pathetic human <br>materialistic requests <br><br>As Satan's army increases <br>endless lines of lost souls <br>is waiting to march out of hell <br><br>As the mighty demon hordes <br>spread their wings <br>and rise to the sky <br>The seven gates of hell opens wide <br><br>Sell your soul <br> to an evil cause]]></content><category term="1349" label="1349"/><category term="Satanic Propaganda" label="Satanic Propaganda"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Pitch_Black/</id><title>1349 - Pitch Black - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:50:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:50:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Pitch_Black/" title="1349 - Pitch Black - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dive into the primitive side <br>Seek the beast within <br>Forget all emotions and forget all rules <br>Let the animal come to life <br><br>I welcome you to a world beyond limits <br>Where nothing is as you know it today <br>A desert of death and destruction <br>Pray that only the suns make day <br><br>To reach this land you must travel far <br>Into space, beyond time <br>Leave civilisation behind and prepare for <br>Survival of the fittest a world of 3 suns <br><br>Behold the desert through nocturnal eyes <br>The endless day the night pitch black <br><br>Eclipsing the suns from the world <br>Leaving darkness and fear behind <br>Creatures rule this world <br>Hunt you down in the dark <br>Cling to the light and trust the strong to survive <br>This place is no place for humans <br>Only creatures get by <br><br>I welcome you to a world pitch black]]></content><category term="1349" label="1349"/><category term="Pitch Black" label="Pitch Black"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Riders_Of_The_Apocalypse/</id><title>1349 - Riders Of The Apocalypse - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:50:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:50:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Riders_Of_The_Apocalypse/" title="1349 - Riders Of The Apocalypse - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I ride on burning wings <br>With a blazing demon <br>We paint the night sky red <br>With the blood of god's angels <br>We piss on the tormented souls <br>Of religious believers <br>We rape the Virgin Mary <br>To create an Anti Christ <br><br>This is the war of angels <br>This is the war of demons <br>This is the war of heaven <br>This is the war of hell <br><br>Burning angels falling <br>Their corpses littering the ground <br>We crush the pearly gates <br>Burn all heaven down <br>We quench the sun <br>And burn the moon <br>Remove Jehovah <br>And welcome Emptiness <br><br>This is the war of angels <br>This is the war of demons <br>This is the war of heaven <br>This is the war of hell <br><br>Walk through the valley of death <br>Smell the stench of decay <br>As the war is ending <br>They will curse this day <br><br>On this day Death walks the earth <br>Reaping all mankind <br><br>As the sky burns we march forward <br>Crushing, tormenting and raping the <br>world <br>Hunt down all survivors, living in fear <br>We ride with death so no one is <br>spared <br>What once were will never be again <br>Because the horseman of death <br>brings the world to an end]]></content><category term="1349" label="1349"/><category term="Riders Of The Apocalypse" label="Riders Of The Apocalypse"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/I_Breathe_Spears/</id><title>1349 - I Breathe Spears - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:50:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:50:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/I_Breathe_Spears/" title="1349 - I Breathe Spears - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Falling into a nocturnal vacuum, I call for Satan, the <br>key holder <br>for his world I shall enter <br>My call is answered <br>By force am I taken to realms, darker than death <br>to witness the evil glory I have travelled to see <br><br>Many are the appearing shapes of Satan <br>Unfolding in utter grotesque horror <br>The air is frozen <br>I can hear the hateful rumbling and pounding in the <br>deep <br>I can see flickering spectres, silhouettes blistering with <br>electric coldness <br><br>I breathe spears <br>unleashing a pulsating storm of steel <br>Sulphur floats in my veins <br>My eyes burn with fury <br>Carbonised into my heart <br><br>Far away, a wast bastard cross manifests in <br>the air <br>How dare it shine so clear <br>here in these hellish realms <br>Oh, did I not know of the impurity <br><br>As the blasphemy becomes unbearable <br>I behold thousands of claws gripping the <br>golden cross from behind <br>Soon demons crawl like furious ants all over <br>the profaned shape <br>Screaming in unearthly rage and insanity <br>The symbol of Nazarene us thirb asunder <br>dripping with slime and rot <br><br>I shiver in cruel ecstasy <br>and laugh the madman's laughter <br><br>returning now <br>with diabolical strength <br>and a vicious grin in the face]]></content><category term="1349" label="1349"/><category term="I Breathe Spears" label="I Breathe Spears"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Manifest/</id><title>1349 - Manifest - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:50:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:50:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Manifest/" title="1349 - Manifest - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[For I have seen beyond the stars <br>I have felt the strength of chaos <br>I have reached the point of sanity <br>And was married by the Chaos star <br>I welcomed the darkness that filled my soul <br>I was blessed by the madness of the Chaos star <br><br>This is my destiny <br>The choices I have made <br>No hope, no fear <br>This is Manifest <br><br>If you could see through my eyes <br>You would see the things of which I speak <br>The point of sanity <br>And the mark of the Chaos star <br>I can show you the darkness that fills my soul <br>I can brand your empty soul with the mark of the Chaos star <br><br>This is my destiny <br>The choices I have made <br>No hope, no fear <br>This is Manifest <br><br>Do you dare to open your eyes <br>And see what is out there <br>Do you dare to close them again <br>And see it reflected in your mind <br><br>Do you know what to look for <br>Or do you see what you want to see <br>Is your mind open and free <br>Or polluted by Christianity <br><br>Do you speak your own mind <br>Or the mind of the masses <br>Do you practise what you preach <br>Or are you full of shit <br>Do you walk your own path <br>Or do you follow a leader <br> This is our manifest of war]]></content><category term="1349" label="1349"/><category term="Manifest" label="Manifest"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Ink/F_With_U_Feat_Ty_Dolla_ign/</id><title>Kid Ink - F With U (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:54:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:54:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Ink/F_With_U_Feat_Ty_Dolla_ign/" title="Kid Ink - F With U (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let's go woo <br>I've been tryna get over you <br>Hitmaker <br>Baby uh huh <br>$ign $ign <br>Baby you already know <br>what I'm tryna do <br>yeah yeah <br>Oh yeah <br>Mustard on the beat ho <br>Hot box drop top the 'rari <br>Hop out night life I’m sorry Skrrt <br>Red Bull mix that Bacardi <br>You know we likes to party <br>Na na na na wheels up on the jet <br>La la la la roll up after sex <br>I'm just here to find you <br>round the way <br>I'm just here to find oh yeah <br>I really like what you <br>done to me <br>I can't really explain it <br>I still fuck with you <br>I really like what you <br>done to me <br>I can't really explain it <br>I still fuck with you <br>Oh yeah down to the core yeah <br>Couldn't tell you <br>better than I show ya <br>Been tryin' so hard to ignore the <br>Way you make that clap Nola Nola <br>See you curve in a stack <br>in your frame girl <br>Dip swerve then I'm back <br>in your lane girl <br>Keep that ass up all night restless <br>I just finger roll and finesse it <br>Straight up no time for the extras <br>Know you been through it <br>but fuck all your exes aw yeah <br>The way you been lookin' so sexy <br>I might just let you take some <br>pics in my necklace aw yeah <br>I really like what you <br>done to me <br>I can't really explain it <br>I still fuck with you <br>I really like what you <br>done to me <br>I can't really explain it <br>I still fuck with you <br>Yeah yeah You Ooh <br>Yeah yeah You Ooh <br>Yeah yeah You Ooh <br>I still fuck with you with you <br>Please believe me believe me <br>I ain't talkin' Vegas <br>When I say <br>I'll take you to the Venetian <br>Gettin' high red eye on the PJ <br>Touch down top floor in the PH <br>I know you hear us loud on the PA <br>What I'm on <br>give her game like EA <br>Ease up baby give me a little leeway <br>But make sure you keep it in motion <br>Wake up and know we get <br>straight to memosas aw yeah <br>Be on the first thing smokin' <br>Or you if you down drop the roof <br>see me coastin' aw yeah <br>I really like what you <br>done to me <br>I can't really explain it <br>I still fuck with you <br>I really like what you <br>done to me <br>I can't really explain it <br>I still fuck with you <br>Yeah yeah You Ooh <br>Yeah yeah You Ooh <br>Yeah yeah You Ooh <br>I still fuck with you with you <br>]]></content><category term="Kid Ink" label="Kid Ink"/><category term="F With U (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign)" label="F With U (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김보경/기억을_걷다/</id><title>김보경 - 기억을 걷다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:54:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:54:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%B3%B4%EA%B2%BD/%EA%B8%B0%EC%96%B5%EC%9D%84_%EA%B1%B7%EB%8B%A4/" title="김보경 - 기억을 걷다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그땐 왜 그랬을까 너무 어렸었나 봐 <br>한마디 말이 모자라 <br>보내고 말았나 봐 <br>지나고 나니 이제야 알게 됐어 <br>내게 소중한 사람이란 걸 <br>시간을 되돌려 네게로 가면 <br>못 다했던 그 말 다 전할 수 있을까 <br>다가가면 너는 멀어져 버려 <br>닿을 듯한 네 모습이 다 모두 사라져 <br>어디로 가나 네가 없는 이 길에 <br>하루만큼 멀어지는 <br>너와의 기억을 걷고 있어 <br>잘 지내고 있을까 <br>자꾸만 걱정되나 봐 <br>그러지 말자 다짐해도 <br>난 어쩔 수 없나 봐 <br>뒤돌아보니 여전히 그대로 있어 <br>나의 사랑이 눈물이 되어 <br>시간이 흘러가 아득해지면 <br>아파했던 그 날 다 잊을 수 있을까 <br>다가가면 너는 멀어져 버려 <br>닿을듯한 네 모습이 다 모두 사라져 <br>어디로 가나 네가 없는 이 길에 <br>널 다 잊다가 어느 샌가 <br>다시 너는 떠오르고 <br>무심코 바라본 거울에 <br>거리마다 울리는 노래 속에도 <br>어딜 가나 앞에 있는 <br>너의 모습들이 잡힐 듯 멀어져 <br>어떡하나 자꾸 흩어져버려 <br>닿을듯한 네 모습이 다 모두 사라져 <br>어디로 가나 네가 없는 이 길에 <br>널 다 잊다가 어느 샌가 다가오는 <br>눈물에 나타나 결국 흩어져버려 <br>닿을듯한 네 모습이 다 모두 사라져 <br>어디로 가나 네가 없는 이 길에 <br>하루만큼 멀어지는 <br>너와의 기억을 걷고 있어 <br>]]></content><category term="김보경" label="김보경"/><category term="기억을 걷다" label="기억을 걷다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김페리/두_개의_밤/</id><title>김페리 - 두 개의 밤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:54:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:54:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%8E%98%EB%A6%AC/%EB%91%90_%EA%B0%9C%EC%9D%98_%EB%B0%A4/" title="김페리 - 두 개의 밤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밤이 지나가는데 또 말이 없나 <br>왜 우리는 <br>맘이 떠나가는데 또 바라보나 <br>왜 그대는 <br>말을 걸어보는데 <br>말이 없었는데 어제는 <br>맘이 떠나가는데 또 바라보네 <br>난 하지만 <br>너를 위한 밤에 너를 잃을까 싶어 <br>너를 잃은 맘이 나의 밤이 더 깊어 <br>너를 위한 밤에 너를 잃을까 싶어 <br>너를 잃은 맘이 나의 밤이 더 깊어 <br>you and I <br>달이 떠 두개 더 <br>밤이 지나가는데 또 말이 없나 <br>왜 우리는 <br>맘이 떠나가는데 또 바라보네 <br>왜 다시 또 <br>밤이 지나가는데 또 말이 없나 <br>왜 우리는 <br>너를 위한 밤에 너를 잃을까 싶어 <br>너를 잃은 맘이 나의 밤이 더 깊어 <br>너를 위한 밤에 너를 잃을까 싶어 <br>너를 잃은 맘이 나의 밤이 더 깊어 <br>너를 위한 밤에 너를 잃을까 싶어 <br>너를 잃은 맘이 나의 밤이 더 깊어 <br>너를 위한 밤에 너를 잃을까 싶어 <br>너를 잃은 맘이 나의 밤이 더 깊어 <br>you and I together <br>밤이 지나가는데 <br>또 잠을 자야해 이제는 <br>]]></content><category term="김페리" label="김페리"/><category term="두 개의 밤" label="두 개의 밤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/카키마젬/경주에서/</id><title>카키마젬 - 경주에서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:54:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:54:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B9%B4%ED%82%A4%EB%A7%88%EC%A0%AC/%EA%B2%BD%EC%A3%BC%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C/" title="카키마젬 - 경주에서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니가 고른 빨간 오토바이가 <br>등 뒤에선 oh 너의 향기가 <br>바람에 흩어진 내 고백은 <br>한참을 웃던 네 모습이 <br>벚꽃눈이 흩날리던 경주에서 <br>꼭 잡은 두 손에 온도가 <br>달달했던 우리 입맞춤이 <br>타오르는 저 붉은 노을과 <br>안압지에 품은 달빛이 <br>유채꽃이 살랑이던 경주에서 <br>음 꽃내음과 <br>안겨있는 너의 향기에 <br>이 봄에 취하고 너에게 취해서 <br>오늘 못 돌아갈지 몰라 <br>음 내일부터 자꾸만 <br>생각이 날 것 같은 <br>흔들린 유채꽃과 <br>흩날린 벚꽃잎과 <br>내 맘 흔들어 논 너와 이곳에 <br>흩날리는 벚꽃길을 지나가요 <br>살랑이는 유채꽃밭을 거닐어요 <br>음 꽃내음과 <br>안겨있는 너의 향기에 <br>이 봄에 취하고 너에게 취해서 <br>오늘 못 돌아갈지 몰라 <br>음 내일부터 자꾸만 <br>생각이 날 것 같은 <br>흔들린 유채꽃과 <br>흩날린 벚꽃잎과 <br>내 맘 흔들어 논 너와 이곳에 <br>경주에서 경주에서 <br>경주에서 경주에서 <br>]]></content><category term="카키마젬" label="카키마젬"/><category term="경주에서" label="경주에서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김재일/Chopin___In_Mir_Klingt_Ein_Lied_쇼팽___이별의_노래/</id><title>김재일 - Chopin : In Mir Klingt Ein Lied (쇼팽 : 이별의 노래) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:54:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:54:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9E%AC%EC%9D%BC/Chopin___In_Mir_Klingt_Ein_Lied_%EC%87%BC%ED%8C%BD___%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84%EC%9D%98_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="김재일 - Chopin : In Mir Klingt Ein Lied (쇼팽 : 이별의 노래) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In mir klingt ein Lied <br>ein kleines Lied <br>in dem ein Traum <br>von stiller Liebe bluht <br>fur dich allein <br>Eine heibe <br>ungestillte Sehnsucht <br>schreib die Melodie <br>In mir klingt ein Lied <br>ein kleines Lied <br>in dem ein Wunsch <br>von tausend Stunden gluht <br>bei dir zu sein <br>Sollst mit mir im Himmel leben <br>traumend uber Sterne schweben <br>ewig scheint die Sonne fur uns zwei <br>sehn dich herbei und mit dir <br>mein Gluck <br>Horst du die Musik <br>zartliche Musik <br>In mir klingt ein Lied <br>ein kleines Lied <br>in dem ein Wunsch <br>von tausend Stunden gluht <br>bei dir zu sein <br>Sollst mit mir im Himmel leben <br>traumend uber Sterne schweben <br>ewig scheint die Sonne fur uns zwei <br>sehn dich herbei und mit dir <br>mein Gluck <br>Horst du die Musik <br>zartliche Musik <br>]]></content><category term="김재일" label="김재일"/><category term="Chopin : In Mir Klingt Ein Lied (쇼팽 : 이별의 노래)" label="Chopin : In Mir Klingt Ein Lied (쇼팽 : 이별의 노래)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김재일/Schumann___Die_Lotosblume_Op25-7_슈만___연꽃_작품번호_25-7/</id><title>김재일 - Schumann : Die Lotosblume Op.25-7 (슈만 : 연꽃 작품번호 25-7) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:54:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:54:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9E%AC%EC%9D%BC/Schumann___Die_Lotosblume_Op25-7_%EC%8A%88%EB%A7%8C___%EC%97%B0%EA%BD%83_%EC%9E%91%ED%92%88%EB%B2%88%ED%98%B8_25-7/" title="김재일 - Schumann : Die Lotosblume Op.25-7 (슈만 : 연꽃 작품번호 25-7) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Die Lotosblume angstigt <br>Sich vor der Sonne Pracht <br>Und mit gesenktem Haupte <br>Erwartet sie traumend die Nacht <br>Der Mond der ist ihr Buhle <br>Er weckt sie mit seinem Licht <br>Und ihm entschleiert <br>sie freundlich <br>Ihr frommes Blumengesicht <br>Sie bluht und gluht und leuchtet <br>Und starret stumm in die Hoh <br>Sie duftet und weinet und zittert <br>Vor Liebe und Liebesweh <br>Vor Liebe und Liebesweh <br>]]></content><category term="김재일" label="김재일"/><category term="Schumann : Die Lotosblume Op.25-7 (슈만 : 연꽃 작품번호 25-7)" label="Schumann : Die Lotosblume Op.25-7 (슈만 : 연꽃 작품번호 25-7)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김재일/홀로사는_즐거움/</id><title>김재일 - 홀로사는 즐거움 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:54:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:54:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9E%AC%EC%9D%BC/%ED%99%80%EB%A1%9C%EC%82%AC%EB%8A%94_%EC%A6%90%EA%B1%B0%EC%9B%80/" title="김재일 - 홀로사는 즐거움 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[달빛이 산방에 들어와 <br>소리 없는 노래를 하고 <br>바람 불고 꽃 피고 지고 <br>구름 일고 안개 오르네 <br>강물이 풀리는 소리도 <br>조용히 귀 기울이면 <br>노을이 합장하듯 <br>내 마음 가득 번지는 노래 <br>홀로 핀 꽃처럼 <br>침묵은 아름답다 <br>자비로운 날들의 <br>홀로 사는 즐거움 <br>달빛이 꽃 위에 내려와 <br>소리 없는 기쁨을 주고 <br>해가 뜨면 사라진 다해도 <br>생명을 일깨워주네 <br>내 입 안에 말이 적고 <br>마음에 일이 적고 <br>한 그릇의 공양으로 <br>내 몸도 가벼워 지리니 <br>홀로 핀 꽃처럼 <br>침묵은 아름답다 <br>기도하는 날들의 <br>홀로 사는 즐거움 <br>기도하는 날들의 <br>홀로 사는 즐거움 <br>]]></content><category term="김재일" label="김재일"/><category term="홀로사는 즐거움" label="홀로사는 즐거움"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김재일/아버지/</id><title>김재일 - 아버지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:54:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:54:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9E%AC%EC%9D%BC/%EC%95%84%EB%B2%84%EC%A7%80/" title="김재일 - 아버지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[당신이 머물다간 그 자리에 <br>나도 모르게 서있습니다 <br>당신이 온몸으로 버텨냈던 <br>그 바람을 마주 합니다 <br>차가운 새벽녘 길을 걷다 <br>문뜩 떠올 립니다 <br>나를 부르던 당신의 <br>따뜻한 목소리를 <br>아버지 그리운 이름 <br>눈을 감고 불러봅니다 <br>또 부르지 못 할 <br>이름이 되었지만 <br>나 그립습니다 <br>당신이 걸어가던 그 골목을 <br>아들도 오늘 걸어갑니다 <br>당신의 손을 잡고 걷던 그 길 <br>힘겹게 걸어갑니다 <br>이제 내가 그 자리에 서서 <br>당신을 떠 올립니다 <br>나를 위해서 흘리던 눈물 <br>기억합니다 <br>아버지 나는 당신의 <br>전부임을 몰랐습니다 <br>나도 누군가의 아비가 되어 보니 <br>눈물납니다 <br>아버지 그리운 이름 <br>눈을 감고 불러봅니다 <br>또 부르지 못 할 <br>이름이 되었지만 <br>나 불러봅니다 <br>]]></content><category term="김재일" label="김재일"/><category term="아버지" label="아버지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김재일/그대_있음에/</id><title>김재일 - 그대 있음에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:54:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:54:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9E%AC%EC%9D%BC/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80_%EC%9E%88%EC%9D%8C%EC%97%90/" title="김재일 - 그대 있음에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대가 있어서 행복해 <br>오늘도 그것에 감사해 <br>작은 것 하나도 나에겐 <br>그대가 있어 감동이요 <br>그대 하나로 난 충분해 <br>내 곁에 있음을 감사해 <br>그대와 늘 함께 하기를 <br>하늘에 기도해 <br>모진 비바람 불어도 <br>그대만 내 곁에 있다면 <br>세상 어떤 고통과 슬픔 <br>모두 이겨내리 <br>그대와 만든 세상 안에 <br>나 영원히 살고 싶소 <br>그대와 함께하는 순간 <br>그것이 기쁨이요 <br>세상 두려울 것이 없오 <br>그대가 내 곁에 있기에 <br>갈 길을 몰라 해매일 때 <br>그댄 나에게 빛이 되고 <br>실패하고 쓰러질 때도 <br>그대가 내손 잡아줬오 <br>그대의 따뜻한 손길이 <br>날 일으켜 줬오 <br>모진 비바람 불어도 <br>그대만 내 곁에 있다면 <br>세상 어떤 고통과 슬픔 <br>모두 이겨내리 <br>그대와 만든 세상 안에 <br>나 영원히 살고 싶소 <br>그대와 함께하는 순간 <br>나에겐 기쁨이요 <br>그대여서 난 행복하오 <br>그대라서 감사하오 <br>나 다시 태어난다 해도 <br>그대를 사랑하리 <br>난 너무나 행복한 사람 <br>그대가 있음에 <br>]]></content><category term="김재일" label="김재일"/><category term="그대 있음에" label="그대 있음에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rejjie_Snow/Flexin_Feat_Ebenezer/</id><title>Rejjie Snow - Flexin` (Feat. Ebenezer) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:54:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:54:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rejjie_Snow/Flexin_Feat_Ebenezer/" title="Rejjie Snow - Flexin` (Feat. Ebenezer) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This is how we do it yeah <br>You niggas don't want it man <br>My money don't fold <br>Keep it in a rubber band <br>Young niggas just flexin' <br>Since '96 I had gold <br>all on my necklace <br>Young niggas just flexin' <br>Now I ride around <br>with a Lexus in my Lexus <br>Nigga I'm just flexing <br>Cracker cracker uh huh <br>Knick-knack-paddy-whack <br>Crashing up that Audi <br>I'm a schizo when I spit on track <br>This that shit that God was playing <br>In his fucking dreams <br>Beg the boy to river-dance I'm <br>Irish what you fucking mean <br>Come girl shake your laffy taffy <br>Breakdance on my mama's Camry <br>Fade away my knuckles knocking <br>Purple fluid zombie walking <br>Sick of all you rappers claiming <br>Plug plug that's kinda awkward <br>Sick of all you <br>thotties' plastic booties <br>All my homies slaughtered <br>Still my boys shoot at police <br>Tippy-toeing through the streets <br>Crooked cops and fucking opps <br>Record deals for major props <br>Cruising time recline the whip <br>Playing all my newest shit <br>Playing all my greatest hits <br>Greatest rapper suck my dick <br>This is how we do it yeah <br>You niggas don't want it man <br>My money don't fold <br>Keep it in a rubber band <br>Young niggas just flexin' <br>Since '96 I had gold <br>all on my necklace <br>Young niggas just flexin' <br>Now I ride around <br>with a Lexus in my Lexus <br>Nigga I'm just flexing <br>Flexing flexing flexing flexing <br>Gold all in my diamond necklace <br>Pockets swole you got me reckless <br>Chickenpox since '97 <br>Shotgun sitting playing Marvin <br>Cruising ramen noodle sponsored <br>Rap you like that Christmas concert <br>Belly's aching fuck tomorrow <br>Dreams of head inside the Lexus <br>Call me back I'm sick of texting <br>Little boy those skinny legs was <br>Fucking youts on intermission <br>Sloppy toppy Mrs Simpson <br>She was bad and we were Christian <br>Beg your pardon Fuck the witness <br>Gold chain no case love the system <br>I've got something on my mind <br>That I'm pimping <br>these flows dolomite <br>I've got some Henny in my cup <br>That I'm chugging <br>all night till the sun <br>This is how we do it yeah <br>You niggas don't want it man <br>My money don't fold <br>Keep it in a rubber band <br>Young niggas just flexin' <br>Since '96 I had gold <br>all on my necklace <br>Young niggas just flexin' <br>Now I ride around <br>with a Lexus in my Lexus <br>Nigga I'm just flexing <br>I see you niggas watching <br>This is how we flex <br>Keep it 100 no fronting <br>This is how we flex <br>This is how we do it yeah <br>You niggas don't want it man <br>My money don't fold <br>Keep it in a rubber band <br>Young niggas just flexin' <br>Since '96 I had gold <br>all on my necklace <br>Young niggas just flexin' <br>Now I ride around <br>with a Lexus in my Lexus <br>Nigga I'm just flexing <br>Flashing off of that light switch <br>My fists know them slave ships <br>My boo white she hood rich <br>This album one and my first skit <br>]]></content><category term="Rejjie Snow" label="Rejjie Snow"/><category term="Flexin` (Feat. Ebenezer)" label="Flexin` (Feat. Ebenezer)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Feder/Blame_Me/</id><title>Feder - Blame Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:54:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:54:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Feder/Blame_Me/" title="Feder - Blame Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Something got me paranormal <br>Losing my steps <br>Walking down this endless tunnel <br>I'm just trying to forget <br>Talk about another shot of redemption <br>I let you down <br>No making no exceptions <br>Backhanded back around <br><br>All I taste is fear <br>On the tip of my tongue <br>Lost inside here <br>I'm running nowhere <br>Hiding from it <br>Patience over <br>Breaking out <br><br>Now I can see why you blame me <br>Now I can feel what you feel <br>Now I know what you're faced with <br>And now I know this ain't real <br>Now I can see why you blame me, blame me, blame me <br>Now I can see why you blame me, blame me, blame me <br><br>Blurry kind of focus <br>Bad influence <br>Now my mind has started floating away <br>I'm not making sense <br>My pistol's fully loaded <br>What a turn of events <br>Now I'm acting like my head's exploded, fizzy soda <br>Falling off the fence <br><br>All I taste is fear <br>On the tip of my tongue <br>On the tip of my tongue <br>Lost inside here <br>I'm running nowhere <br>Hiding from it <br>Patience over <br>Breaking out <br><br>Now I can see why you blame me <br>Now I can feel what you feel <br>Now I know what you're faced with <br>And now I know this ain't real <br>Now I can see why you blame me, blame me, blame me <br>Now I can see why you blame me, blame me, blame me]]></content><category term="Feder" label="Feder"/><category term="Blame Me" label="Blame Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kodak_Black/Reminiscing_Feat_A_Boogie_Wit_Da_Hoodie/</id><title>Kodak Black - Reminiscing (Feat. A Boogie Wit Da Hoodie) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:55:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:55:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kodak_Black/Reminiscing_Feat_A_Boogie_Wit_Da_Hoodie/" title="Kodak Black - Reminiscing (Feat. A Boogie Wit Da Hoodie) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro: Kodak Black] <br>Off the head, shit, you know what I'm saying <br>Glee, brr, off the dome, man, I'm in, ayy <br><br>[Verse 1: Kodak Black] <br>22 hours locked down, ain't shit to do but think <br>I remember like it was yesterday, was drinkin' out the sink <br>I'm sittin' back plottin', I'm just sittin' back vibin' <br>A nigga can't complain, I had to use my time wisely <br>I'm sleepin' in a dorm, but they ain't send me off to college <br>I still got money buried from that lick I hit in Raleigh <br>I'm book-smart but the streets gave me all my knowledge <br>So there ain't nun' for you when you comin' out the projects <br>So there ain't nun' for you when you comin' out the slum <br>A mouth full of gold teeth, they think a nigga dumb <br>I got a head full of dreads, think a nigga illiterate <br>But I know when I go to talk, a nigga'll reconsider it <br>I know you niggas just tryna benefit <br>I ain't fuckin' with you a little bit <br>I ain't fuckin' with you at all <br>I ain't fuckin' with you at all <br>I was sellin' weed in middle school, just meet me in the halls <br>Right now I'm goin' in, but I was just behind the wall <br>This jail got me thinkin', I feel like everybody flawed <br>I got too much to lose, but I'll still go at a nigga jaw <br>I'm down for the count, I'm never down for the cause <br>I made a million dollars off of shows and goin' hard <br><br><br>[Chorus: A Boogie Wit Da Hoodie] <br>I love money, I can't go back to the bottom 'cause I <br>Hate it at the bottom, try to stop thinking about it <br>But, I'm reminiscing, yeah <br>I'm reminiscing, yeah <br>Fuck your problems, it's too late to tell me sorry <br>I pulled up in a 'rari, it don't come with no apologies <br>I'm reminiscing, yeah <br>I'm reminiscing, yeah <br><br>[Verse 2: Kodak Black] <br>I remember everythin', I done been through everythin' <br>I remember who shitted on me, or who been in the paint <br>Like Ray J, got a bitch from the Bronx givin' me brain <br>Like Ray J, I done walked through the motherfuckin' rain <br>Right now I done got too far to give a motherfucker a feature <br>I'm the freshest man in high school, but I'm a motherfuckin' senior <br>Lil' shawty want to kick it, I told her I don't play FIFA <br>I jumped up out the Beamer, now I'm slidin' in the regal <br>That pussy so tight but I be tryna go deeper <br>If she can make goulash, she a motherfuckin' keeper <br>Reminiscin' about my niggas, reminiscin' about my homies <br>I'm thinkin' 'bout my niggas, I'm thinkin' 'bout my whoadies <br>I don't fuck with Fooly no more but I still fuck with Cody <br>Got a booger in my nose, A Boogie on the chorus <br>A young nigga, I jumped off the porch, run Forrest <br>I'll lose it about that money, I'll go dumb for it <br>I'm workin' like a Mexican, fuck around and get deported <br>I bought my mama a crib, thirty clip in my forty <br>She said that my baby, I told that bih let's go to Maury <br>Lame niggas get extorted, if it ain't foreign then it's borin' <br><br><br>[Chorus: A Boogie Wit Da Hoodie] <br>I love money, I can't go back to the bottom 'cause I <br>Hate it at the bottom, try to stop thinking about it <br>But, I'm reminiscing, yeah <br>I'm reminiscing, yeah <br>Fuck your problem, it's too late to tell me sorry <br>I pulled up in a 'Rari, it don't come with no apologies <br>I'm reminiscing, yeah <br>I'm reminiscing, yeah <br>Reminiscing, yeah <br>I'm reminiscing, yeah]]></content><category term="Kodak Black" label="Kodak Black"/><category term="Reminiscing (Feat. A Boogie Wit Da Hoodie)" label="Reminiscing (Feat. A Boogie Wit Da Hoodie)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kodak_Black/Tunnel_Vision/</id><title>Kodak Black - Tunnel Vision - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:55:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:55:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kodak_Black/Tunnel_Vision/" title="Kodak Black - Tunnel Vision - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Gleeee <br>Southside <br>And Lil Metro on that beat <br>Lil Kodak they don't like <br>to see you winnin' <br>They wanna see you <br>in the penitentiary <br>I need me a lil' baby <br>who gon' listen <br>Girl I don't wanna <br>be the one you iggin' <br>My mama told me <br>Boy make a decision <br>Right now I gotta keep <br>a tunnel vision <br>I need me a lil' baby <br>who gon' listen <br>Girl I don't wanna <br>be the one you iggin' <br>Lil Kodak they don't like <br>to see you winnin' <br>They wanna see you <br>in the penitentiary <br>I need me a lil' baby <br>who gon' listen <br>Girl I don't wanna <br>be the one you iggin' <br>My mama told me <br>Boy make a decision <br>Right now I gotta keep <br>a tunnel vision <br>They sendin' all my homies <br>on a mission <br>And I ain't tryna miss out <br>on these millions <br>I jumped out of that Wraith <br>Kodak bought a Wraith <br>I get any girl I want <br>any girl I want <br>She want me to save the day <br>but I ain't got a cape <br>She wanna see me everyday <br>she wanna be my bae <br>That money make me cum it <br>made me fornicate <br>Uh I'm the shit <br>I need some toilet paper <br>Follow my player rules <br>then we gon' be okay <br>On the real I need a bih' <br>who gon' cooperate <br>Lil Kodak they don't like <br>to see you winnin' <br>They wanna see you <br>in the penitentiary <br>I need me a lil' baby <br>who gon' listen <br>Girl I don't wanna <br>be the one you iggin' <br>My mama told me <br>Boy make a decision <br>Right now I gotta keep <br>a tunnel vision <br>I need me a lil' baby <br>who gon' listen <br>Girl I don't wanna <br>be the one you iggin' <br>Lil Kodak they don't like <br>to see you winnin' <br>They wanna see you <br>in the penitentiary <br>I need me a lil' baby <br>who gon' listen <br>Girl I don't wanna <br>be the one you iggin' <br>My mama told me <br>Boy make a decision <br>Right now I gotta keep <br>a tunnel vision <br>They sendin' all my homies <br>on a mission <br>And I ain't tryna miss out <br>on these millions <br>I told you niggas <br>I'm gon' be that fuckin' nigga <br>Everything be good <br>until you doin' better than 'em <br>They wanna see a nigga shot <br>or see me in the system <br>All you niggas out here poison <br>like snake venom <br>Codeine in my liver <br>rockin' Balenciaga denim <br>I'm booted even when I'm sober <br>I don't need a jigga <br>They sendin' all my niggas <br>on a fuckin' journey <br>I told that baby to come over <br>'cause I'm fucking horny <br>My mama told me kill <br>these niggas son keep it goin' <br>I'm thug to the bone <br>but I'm still her baby boy <br>Lil Kodak boy they hate <br>to see you in a foreign <br>They miss when you was in <br>that 'Yota kickin' door <br>Lil Kodak they don't like <br>to see you winnin' <br>They wanna see you <br>in the penitentiary <br>I need me a lil' baby <br>who gon' listen <br>Girl I don't wanna <br>be the one you iggin' <br>My mama told me <br>Boy make a decision <br>Right now I gotta keep <br>a tunnel vision <br>I need me a lil' baby <br>who gon' listen <br>Girl I don't wanna <br>be the one you iggin' <br>Lil Kodak they don't like <br>to see you winnin' <br>They wanna see you <br>in the penitentiary <br>I need me a lil' baby <br>who gon' listen <br>Girl I don't wanna <br>be the one you iggin' <br>My mama told me <br>Boy make a decision <br>Right now I gotta keep <br>a tunnel vision <br>They sendin' all my homies <br>on a mission <br>And I ain't tryna miss out <br>on these millions <br>]]></content><category term="Kodak Black" label="Kodak Black"/><category term="Tunnel Vision" label="Tunnel Vision"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kodak_Black/Patty_Cake/</id><title>Kodak Black - Patty Cake - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:55:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:55:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kodak_Black/Patty_Cake/" title="Kodak Black - Patty Cake - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro] <br>Sniper Gang <br>Yeah, I like this lil' beat right here <br>Yeah, this a nice little beat <br>I'm sippin' on Belaire <br>Yeah, I'm finna paint a picture <br>Finna paint me a lil' picture <br>What this called? Oh this the new Belaire too <br>This the white wine, I like the white wine <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I'm sippin' on Belaire, my chick from Bel-Air <br>My whip from Germany, I'm cooler than LL <br>I'm sippin' on Belaire, my chick from Bel-Air <br>My whip from Germany, I'm cooler than LL <br>I clap a nigga like patty cake <br>I clap a nigga like patty cake <br>I'm swaggin', I got flavor, I got sauce, call me Ragu <br>I love my baby girl pussy bald, call her Caillou <br>I clap a nigga like patty cake <br><br>[Verse 1] <br>Yeah, dat way <br>I'm 'bout to grab the Wraith, I'm 'bout to grab the key <br>I'm 'bout to snatch your baby girl and skeet all on her face <br>I got a feelin' that today gon' be a fantastic day <br>I'm gettin' tired of the Rollie, I think I want Patek Philippe <br>It's either I win or you lose, 'cause I won't accept defeat <br>And everybody wanna have the sauce, well I got the recipe <br>I'm sippin' on Belaire 'cause it make me feel like I'm on ecstasy <br>I love my baby, when I come home, I be rubbin' on her feet <br>And she be always in my chair, she hate when I be in the streets <br>My rims taller than my son, I'm 'bout to drop another one <br>You think a nigga in a band the way I hit him with that drum, ayy <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I'm sippin' on Belaire, my chick from Bel-Air <br>My whip from Germany, I'm cooler than LL <br>I'm sippin' on Belaire, my chick from Bel-Air <br>My whip from Germany, I'm cooler than LL <br>I clap a nigga like patty cake <br>I clap a nigga like patty cake <br>I'm swaggin', I got flavor, I got sauce, call me Ragu <br>I love my baby girl pussy bald, call her Caillou <br>I clap a nigga like patty cake <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>My chain VVS <br>I'm booted up, I got more pills than a CVS <br>I'm the shit, baby girl, so I got stains in my drawers <br>All this money like a nigga hit the fuckin' Power Ball <br>Sippin' on champagne, my whip on Dana Dane's <br>No time for you lames, I'm flyer than a plane <br>I'm ridin' like a train, she love to give me brain <br>You shootin' with your eyes closed, you ain't Sniper Gang <br>She held me down when I was gone, I bought her Audemars Piguet <br>I love her like I love my brother, so I let her be my connect <br>I put her thick ass in the vet, ten bracelets on her neck <br>You know lil' Kodak love to flex, I got my momma out the 'jects <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I'm sippin' on Belaire, my chick from Bel-Air <br>My whip from Germany, I'm cooler than LL <br>I'm sippin' on Belaire, my chick from Bel-Air <br>My whip from Germany, I'm cooler than LL <br>I clap a nigga like patty cake <br>I clap a nigga like patty cake <br>I'm swaggin', I got flavor, I got sauce, call me Ragu <br>I love my baby girl pussy bald, call her Caillou <br>I clap a nigga like patty cake]]></content><category term="Kodak Black" label="Kodak Black"/><category term="Patty Cake" label="Patty Cake"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Superfly/愛をこめて花束を___Aiwo_Komete_Hanatabawo_사랑을_담아서_꽃다발을/</id><title>Superfly - 愛をこめて花束を / Aiwo Komete Hanatabawo (사랑을 담아서 꽃다발을) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:58:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:58:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Superfly/%E6%84%9B%E3%82%92%E3%81%93%E3%82%81%E3%81%A6%E8%8A%B1%E6%9D%9F%E3%82%92___Aiwo_Komete_Hanatabawo_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%84_%EB%8B%B4%EC%95%84%EC%84%9C_%EA%BD%83%EB%8B%A4%EB%B0%9C%EC%9D%84/" title="Superfly - 愛をこめて花束を / Aiwo Komete Hanatabawo (사랑을 담아서 꽃다발을) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[二人で？？を撮ろう ？かしいこの景色と <br>후타리데샤신오토로우 나쯔카시이코노케시키토 <br>둘이서 사진을 찍자 그리운 이 풍경과 <br><br>あの日と同じポ？ズで おどけてみせて欲しい <br>아노히토오나지포오즈데 오도케테미세테호시이 <br>그 날과 같은 포즈로 익살을 떨어 주길 바래 <br><br>見上げる空の？さを ？まぐれに雲は流れ <br>미아게루호시노아오사오 키마구레니쿠모와나가레 <br>올려다본 하늘의 푸름을 변덕스럽게 구름은 흐르고 <br><br>キレイなものは 遠くにあるからキレイなの <br>키레이나모노와 토오쿠니아루카라키레이나노 <br>아름다운 것은 멀리 있으니까 아름다운거야 <br><br>約束したとおりあなたと <br>야쿠소쿠시타토오리아나타토 <br>약속한 대로 그대와 <br><br>ここに？られて本？に良かったわ <br>코코니코라레테혼토우니요캇타와 <br>여기로 올 수 있어서 정말로 다행이야 <br><br>この？み上がる？持ちが 愛じゃないなら <br>코노코미아가루키모치가 아이쟈나이나라 <br>이 솟아오르는 감정이 사랑이 아니라면 <br><br>何が愛かわからないほど <br>나니가아이카와카라나이호도 <br>무엇이 사랑인지 모를 정도로 <br><br>愛をこめて花束を 大袈裟だけど受け取って <br>아이오코메테하나타바오 오오게사다케도우케톳테 <br>사랑을 담아서 꽃다발을 과장이지만 받아줘 <br><br>理由なんて訊かないでよね <br>리유우난테키카나이데요네 <br>이유 같은 건 묻지 말아 <br><br>今だけすべて忘れて 笑わないで受けとめて <br>이마다케스베테와스레테 와라와나이데우케토메테 <br>지금만은 모두 잊어버리고 웃지말고 받아들여줘 <br><br>照れていないで <br>테레테이나이데 <br>부끄러워하지말아 <br><br>昨日とよく似た今日は 何？ない分かれ道を <br>키노우토요쿠니타쿄우와 나니게나이와카레미치오 <br>어제와 비슷한 오늘은 아무렇지도 않게 갈림길을 <br><br>分かって選びそびれた 臆病のせいでしょう <br>와캇테에라비소비레타 오쿠뵤우노세이데쇼우 <br>깨닫고 고를 기회를 놓쳤어 겁쟁이이기 때문이겠지요 <br><br>私は泣くのが得意で <br>와타시와나쿠노가토쿠이데 <br>나는 우는 게 특기라서 <br><br>最初から慰めを？てにしてたわ <br>사이쇼카라나구사메오아테니시테타와 <br>처음부터 위로받는 걸 기대해왔어 <br><br>何度も間違った道 選び？けて <br>난도모마치갓타미치 에라비쯔즈케테 <br>몇 번이고 틀린 길 계속 선택하고 <br><br>正しく ここに？って？たの <br>타다시쿠 코코니모돗테키타노 <br>올바르게 이곳으로 돌아왔어 <br><br>巡り巡る時を超え いつもあなたの所へと <br>메구리메구루토키오코에 이쯔모아나타노토코로에토 <br>돌고 도는 시간을 넘어 언제나 그대의 곁으로 <br><br>この心 舞い？ってゆく <br>코노코코로 마이모돗테유쿠 <br>이 마음 되돌아 가 <br><br>無理に描く理想より 笑い合える今日の方が <br>무리니에가쿠리소우요리 와라이아에루쿄우노호우가 <br>무리하게 그리는 이상보다 서로 웃을 수 있는 오늘 편이 <br><br>ずっと幸せね <br>즛토시아와세네 <br>훨씬 행복하네 <br><br>violet, indigo, black and blue <br>flame, yellow, purple, sky blue, <br>pink, yellow green, ash, brown <br><br>あなたに贈る色は? <br>아나타니오쿠루이로와? <br>그대에게 보내는 색은? <br><br>巡り巡る時を超え いつもあなたの所へと <br>메구리메구루토키오코에 이쯔모아나타노토코로에토 <br>돌고 도는 시간을 넘어 언제나 그대의 곁으로 <br><br>この心 舞い？ってゆく <br>코노코코로 마이모돗테유쿠 <br>이 마음 되돌아 가 <br><br>ありがとうも言い出せずに 甘えていた <br>아리가토우모이이다세즈니 아마에테이타 <br>고맙다는 말도 꺼내지 못한 채 어리광부리고 있었어 <br><br>今日ここへ？るまでは <br>쿄우코코에쿠루마데와 <br>오늘 여기에 올 때까지는 <br><br>愛をこめて花束を 大袈裟だけど受け取って <br>아이오코메테하나타바오 오오게사다케도우케톳테 <br>사랑을 담아서 꽃다발을 과장이지만 받아줘 <br><br>理由なんて訊かないでよね <br>리유우난테키카나이데요네 <br>이유 같은 건 묻지 말아 <br><br>今だけすべて忘れて 笑わないで受けとめて <br>이마다케스베테와스레테 와라와나이데우케토메테 <br>지금만은 모두 잊어버리고 웃지말고 받아들여줘 <br><br>本？のわたしを <br>혼토우노와타시오 <br>진실한 나를 <br><br>いつまでもそばにいて <br>이쯔마데모소바니이테 <br>언제까지나 곁에 있어줘]]></content><category term="Superfly" label="Superfly"/><category term="愛をこめて花束を / Aiwo Komete Hanatabawo (사랑을 담아서 꽃다발을)" label="愛をこめて花束を / Aiwo Komete Hanatabawo (사랑을 담아서 꽃다발을)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Ink/Lamborghini_Dreaming_Feat_Verse_Simmonds/</id><title>Kid Ink - Lamborghini Dreaming (Feat. Verse Simmonds) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:59:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:59:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Ink/Lamborghini_Dreaming_Feat_Verse_Simmonds/" title="Kid Ink - Lamborghini Dreaming (Feat. Verse Simmonds) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So I don't even ask <br>what you want or what you thinkin' <br>I know what's your favorite <br>I know what's your favorite <br>So I just order all rose <br>from the waitress <br>Cause I know that's your favorite <br>I know that's your favorite <br>I just fucked around <br>and fell in love with your crazy <br>And you love the way <br>I hit your body like a taser <br>Lamborghini dreamin' <br>how she ride how she taste it <br>Lamborghini dreamin' <br>take off in my space ship <br>1-0-0 on the dash feel the matrix <br>We gone the vibe <br>so strong got you high <br>We stoned <br>gettin' hotter than the stove <br>when you ride me <br>Lamborghini dreamin' <br>I'm in love with your body <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>stay the night girl <br>Cause in the morning <br>I wanna wake up to you <br>Lamborghini dreamin' <br>I'm in love with your body <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>stay the night girl <br>I just wanna be the one that gets <br>closest to you yeah you <br>I wanna get closer closer <br>closer closer <br>I wanna get closer closer <br>closer closer <br>I wanna get closer closer <br>closer closer <br>I wanna get closer closer <br>closer closer closer <br>Closer exactly <br>where you supposed to be <br>Wake up <br>roll over and roll some <br>Eat you up for breakfast <br>good morning mimosas <br>We back at it again <br>I put that ass back to sleep <br>Even when she sleepin' <br>she sweet dreaming 'bout the D <br>And prolly goin' shoppin' <br>I cop shit that she don't need <br>Cause bossin' with my bitch <br>the bossest shit I know capiche <br>Sausin' in that salsa <br>slip 'n slide through the street <br>Driftin' down rodeo <br>why they take pictures <br>Young Bonnie and Clyde <br>yeah you know it's just <br>Me and my foreign shawty <br>lookin' so exotic <br>Lamborghini dreamin' <br>I'm in love with your body <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>stay the night girl <br>Cause in the morning <br>I wanna wake up to you <br>Lamborghini dreamin' <br>I'm in love with your body <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>stay the night girl <br>I just wanna be the one that gets <br>closest to you <br>I wanna be the one that gets <br>closer to you <br>Closer closer closer <br>Closer to you closer <br>closer closer <br>Closer to you closer closer closer <br>I wanna get closer to you closer <br>closer closer <br>Closer to you <br>Lamborghini dreamin' <br>I'm in love with your body <br>Lamborghini dreamin' <br>I'm in love with your body <br>Lamborghini dreamin' <br>I'm in love with your body <br>Lamborghini dreamin' <br>I'm in love with your body <br>I wanna get closer closer <br>closer closer <br>I wanna get closer closer <br>closer closer <br>I wanna get closer closer <br>closer closer <br>I wanna get closer closer <br>closer closer closer <br>]]></content><category term="Kid Ink" label="Kid Ink"/><category term="Lamborghini Dreaming (Feat. Verse Simmonds)" label="Lamborghini Dreaming (Feat. Verse Simmonds)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Invitation_Feat_Yade_Lauren/</id><title>Yellow Claw - Invitation (Feat. Yade Lauren) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:59:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:59:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Invitation_Feat_Yade_Lauren/" title="Yellow Claw - Invitation (Feat. Yade Lauren) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Say you wanna spend some time, want someone to do it right <br>Well, baby, I'm free tonight <br>Everybody needs that one good fire in their life <br>And if you wanna burn, I got the light <br>Let my body be your guide <br>Watch your breathing sync with mine <br>Keep your hands inside the ride <br>Oh oh, oh oh, oh yeah <br>Oh oh, oh oh, oh yeah <br>Thought an everlasting love would end up lost <br>So we got into it before the moon is gone <br><br>No looking back, eyes on mine, need to live and let go <br>Since we met, on my mind, you been on it the most <br>You can take it how you want it <br>You know the invitation's open <br><br>I give my every, I give my everything, for what <br>Love and devotion, you don't know what that means, at all <br>You give your every, you give your everything, for what <br>Love and devotion, that's all I really need and want <br><br>No looking back, eyes on mine, need to live and let go <br>Since we met, on my mind, you been on it the most <br>You can take it how you want it <br>You know the invitation's open]]></content><category term="Yellow Claw" label="Yellow Claw"/><category term="Invitation (Feat. Yade Lauren)" label="Invitation (Feat. Yade Lauren)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Rose_Horizon_Feat_STORi/</id><title>Yellow Claw - Rose Horizon (Feat. STORi) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:59:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:59:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Rose_Horizon_Feat_STORi/" title="Yellow Claw - Rose Horizon (Feat. STORi) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You said we can go anywhere <br>Anywhere your heart desires <br>So I guess we 'bout to take it there <br>Take it there, I love it when we go there, uh huh <br>When you do that thing, you make me so, uh huh <br>Trembling, ayo <br>When you kiss me like, you get me so charged up <br>Adrenaline, uh huh <br><br>Asking can we disappear <br>We say not yet, not yet, not yet, not yet <br>And we're riding through the endless sunset <br>Sunset, oh <br>On a rose horizon <br>On a rose horizon <br><br>Ye Ye Ye Yellow motherfucking Claw <br><br>Let's get down for a minute, let's get real for a minute <br>Have a private moment with the windows tinted yeah <br>Don't even need to speak and I'm with it <br>You know you're just the perfect thing, oh <br><br>Asking can we disappear <br>We say not yet, not yet, not yet, not yet <br>And we're riding through the endless sunset <br>Sunset, oh <br>On a rose horizon <br>On a rose horizon <br><br>Ye Ye Ye Yellow motherfucking Claw <br><br>On a rose horizon <br>On a rose horizon]]></content><category term="Yellow Claw" label="Yellow Claw"/><category term="Rose Horizon (Feat. STORi)" label="Rose Horizon (Feat. STORi)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Hold_On_To_Me_Feat_GTA/</id><title>Yellow Claw - Hold On To Me (Feat. GTA) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:59:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:59:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Hold_On_To_Me_Feat_GTA/" title="Yellow Claw - Hold On To Me (Feat. GTA) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If you feel this too, hold on to me <br>So I can give you all the love of me <br>It's like you and I are meant to be <br>So hold on tight and don't let go of me <br>If you feel this too, hold on to me <br>So I can give you all the love of me <br>It's like you and I are meant to be <br>So hold on tight and don't let go of me <br><br>Hold on to me, me <br>Hold on to me, me <br>Hold on to me, me <br>Hold on to me, me <br>Hold on to me, me <br>Hold on to me, me <br>Hold on to me, me <br>Hold on to me, me <br>If you feel this too hold on to me <br>So I can give you all the love of love of love of <br><br>Hold on to me <br>Hold on to <br>So I can give you all the love of me <br>Hold hold hold <br>Hold on to me, me <br>Hold on to me, me <br>If you feel this too, hold on to me <br>So I can <br><br>If you <br>If you feel this too, hold on to me <br>So I can give you all the love of me <br>It's like you and I are meant to be <br>So hold on tight and don't let go of me <br>Hold on to me <br>Me, me, me, me <br>Me, me, me, me <br>Me, me, me, me <br>Me, me, me, me <br><br>GTA and Yellow motherfuckin' Claw <br><br>Hold on to <br>Hold on to me, me <br>Hold on to me, me <br>If you feel this too, hold on to me <br><br>So I can <br>If you <br>So I can <br>If you <br>So I can]]></content><category term="Yellow Claw" label="Yellow Claw"/><category term="Hold On To Me (Feat. GTA)" label="Hold On To Me (Feat. GTA)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Light_Years_Feat_Rochelle/</id><title>Yellow Claw - Light Years (Feat. Rochelle) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:59:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:59:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Light_Years_Feat_Rochelle/" title="Yellow Claw - Light Years (Feat. Rochelle) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Electric nights, like fireflies <br>Time is frozen <br>Velvet skies, like lightning vibes <br>We be floating <br><br>'Cause when you touch me, I swear I can't speak <br>Out of body, there ain't no coming back <br>And when you touch me, it's what my heart needs <br>And we can run free, I know that <br><br>We can be light years away <br>I know I can find you <br>We can be light years away <br>I know we can shine through <br>Anywhere, anywhere, anywhere <br>I know I can find you <br>Anywhere, anywhere, anywhere <br>I know we can shine through <br><br>Yellow motherfucking Claw <br><br>Worlds apart, we're shooting stars <br>Skies are open <br>A ray of sparks, our beating hearts <br>Throw us in motion <br><br>'Cause when you touch me, I swear I can't speak <br>Out of body, there ain't no coming back <br>And when you touch me, it's what my heart needs <br>And we can run free, I know that <br><br>We can be light years away <br>I know I can find you <br>We can be light years away <br>I know we can shine through <br>Anywhere, anywhere, anywhere <br>I know I can find you <br>Anywhere, anywhere, anywhere <br>I know we can shine through <br><br>Yellow motherfucking Claw <br><br>Be be, be be, be be, be be <br>Be be, be be, be be, be be <br>Be be, be be, be be, be be <br>Be be, be be, be be, be be]]></content><category term="Yellow Claw" label="Yellow Claw"/><category term="Light Years (Feat. Rochelle)" label="Light Years (Feat. Rochelle)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Last_Paradise_Feat_Sody/</id><title>Yellow Claw - Last Paradise (Feat. Sody) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:59:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:59:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Last_Paradise_Feat_Sody/" title="Yellow Claw - Last Paradise (Feat. Sody) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We started as friends and now we're two lovers, since then, it still feels new <br>How can it be that you always know how to find the best in me <br>Memories of walking by your door, never saw you like this before <br>So take your hands off your heart and hold me tight <br><br>I never told you seventy times <br>I take you back in 'cause you think that I lie <br>But I keep falling when I look in your eyes <br>When I look in your eyes <br>Yeah, I think I love you a little bit more <br>The way that you kiss me and I'm all yours <br>I take you back in when you open your eyes <br>When you open your eyes <br>You're my last paradise <br><br>Are we mad It's still a mystery <br>Thinking 'bout who, our history <br>No, no days go by without you here <br>Nowhere else I'd rather be <br><br>I never told you seventy times <br>I take you back in 'cause you think that I lie <br>But I keep falling when I look in your eyes <br>When I look in your eyes <br>Yeah, I think I love you a little bit more <br>The way that you kiss me and I'm all yours <br>I take you back in when you open your eyes <br>When you open your eyes <br>You're my last paradise]]></content><category term="Yellow Claw" label="Yellow Claw"/><category term="Last Paradise (Feat. Sody)" label="Last Paradise (Feat. Sody)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Stacks_Feat_Quavo_Tinie_Tempah__Cesqeaux/</id><title>Yellow Claw - Stacks (Feat. Quavo, Tinie Tempah &amp; Cesqeaux) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:59:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:59:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Stacks_Feat_Quavo_Tinie_Tempah__Cesqeaux/" title="Yellow Claw - Stacks (Feat. Quavo, Tinie Tempah &amp; Cesqeaux) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Big fat titties on 'em <br>On 'em, on 'em, on 'em, on 'em <br>1, 2, 3, let's go <br><br>Big stack, throw it on 'em big fat titties <br>And I'm lookin' for some bitches I can take back with me <br>Bi bi big stack, throw it on 'em big fat titties <br>And I'm lookin' for some bitches I can take back with me <br>Bi bi big stack, throw it on 'em big fat titties <br>And I'm lookin' for some bitches I can take back with me <br>Bi bi big stack, throw it on 'em big fat titties <br>And I'm lookin' for some bitches I can take back with me <br><br>Bi bi big stack, throw it on 'em <br>Big stack, throw it on 'em <br>Big stack, throw it on 'em <br>Big stack, throw it on 'em <br>Big stack, big stack <br>Big stack, big stack <br>Big stack, throw it on 'em big fat titties <br><br>Big fat, big fat <br>Big fat titties <br>Big fat, big fat <br>It's 6 o'clock, rush hour <br>I'ma party right and I take a shower <br><br>Big stacks, throw it on 'em big fat titties <br>And I'm lookin' for some bitches I can take back with me <br>Big ol' titties, big ol' titties <br>Quavo with it, Quavo with it <br>I'ma get to it, she gon' pursue it <br>She gon' get down on it, Fatman Scoop it <br>I like thick hoes <br>Throw that money on the pole <br>Big wheels gon' turn <br>My backwood gon' burn <br><br>Big stack, throw it on 'em <br>Big stack, throw it on 'em <br>Big stack, throw it on 'em <br>Big stack, throw it on 'em <br>Big stack, big stack <br>Big stack, big stack <br>Big stack, throw it on 'em big fat titties <br><br>Big fat, big fat <br>Big fat titties <br>Big fat, big fat <br>Big fat titties <br>Big fat titties <br>She might even get me naughty <br>If she kiss that willy <br><br>Bi bi big stacks, throw it on her big fat titties <br>Got her freak on like Missy, when I'm drunk, I ain't dickie <br>Why you over there Come and give your boy a hickie <br>Definitely turn up, definitely litty <br>She gettin' down, down, I've got the pounds, pounds <br>Smokin' cheese in my studio, call it the SoundCloud <br>T, Yellow, Migos, Quavo <br>Whole, club, fucked, k hole <br><br>Big stack, throw it on 'em <br>Big stack, throw it on 'em <br>Big stack, throw it on 'em <br>Big stack, throw it on 'em <br>Big stack, big stack <br>Big stack, big stack <br>Big stack, throw it on 'em big fat titties <br><br>Big fat <br>Big stack, throw it on 'em <br>Big fat, big fat titties <br>Big fat <br>Big stack, throw it on 'em <br>Big fat, big stack titties]]></content><category term="Yellow Claw" label="Yellow Claw"/><category term="Stacks (Feat. Quavo, Tinie Tempah &amp; Cesqeaux)" label="Stacks (Feat. Quavo, Tinie Tempah &amp; Cesqeaux)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Friends_In_The_Dark_Feat_Otis_Parker/</id><title>Yellow Claw - Friends In The Dark (Feat. Otis Parker) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:59:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:59:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Friends_In_The_Dark_Feat_Otis_Parker/" title="Yellow Claw - Friends In The Dark (Feat. Otis Parker) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The faster we rise, the deeper we fall <br>You'll never know but you have it all <br>Friends in the dark is all that we are <br>Then when the lights go on, we break up <br><br>I wanna feel you, I can't leave without you tonight, ooh <br>I don't want nothing if I can't be with you tonight, ooh <br>I can't feel your love in the morning when I wake up feeling cold inside <br>And I can't stop myself from falling when we do the same things every night <br><br>Look what you started, look what you done <br>There's nowhere to turn, nowhere to run <br>Just friends in the dark is all we are <br>But when the lights go on, we fake love <br><br>I wanna feel you, I can't leave without you tonight, ooh <br>I don't want nothing if I can't be with you tonight, ooh <br>I can't feel your love in the morning when I wake up feeling cold inside <br>And I can't stop myself from falling when we do the same things every night]]></content><category term="Yellow Claw" label="Yellow Claw"/><category term="Friends In The Dark (Feat. Otis Parker)" label="Friends In The Dark (Feat. Otis Parker)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/City_on_Lockdown_Feat_Juicy_J__Lil_Debbie/</id><title>Yellow Claw - City on Lockdown (Feat. Juicy J &amp; Lil Debbie) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:59:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:59:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/City_on_Lockdown_Feat_Juicy_J__Lil_Debbie/" title="Yellow Claw - City on Lockdown (Feat. Juicy J &amp; Lil Debbie) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yellow motherfucking Claw <br><br>Roof is blazin' for me, let that motherfucker burn now <br>Tell these bitches watch it, it's my motherfuckin' turn now <br>We blazin', blazin', why you hatin' <br>Bitch, we blazin', blazin', so amazin' <br>Everythin' is heat bitch, hot chick, hot whip <br>Burn it like a furnace, bitch, 'cause all I know is hot shit <br>We blazin', blazin', so why you waitin' <br>Bitch, we blazin', blazin', so amazin' <br><br>Bitch, I'm on fire oh yeah <br>Bitch, I'm on fire oh yeah <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>We got your city on a lockdown lockdown <br>Bitch, I'm on fire oh yeah <br>Bitch, I'm on fire oh yeah <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>We 'bout to burn the fucking club down <br><br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bit bit bit bit bit bit <br>Bit bit bit bit bit bit <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>We 'bout to burn the fuckin' club down <br><br>You know it <br>I'm so fuckin' hot hot, I'm so fuckin' deep deep <br>I'm so fuckin' throat throat, I'm singin' in threes threes <br>I can't feel my face face, can't stand on my feet feet <br>Damn, right I'm trippy, ain't no better way to be be <br>Let's do it again 'gain, this time let's do mo' mo' <br>Let's blaze out 'til we pass out and wake up on the flo' <br>I woke up with your hoe hoe, my dick's still in her mouth mouth <br>That game so good that I could not take her out mmhmm <br><br>Bitch, I'm on fire oh yeah <br>Bitch, I'm on fire oh yeah <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>We got your city on a lockdown lockdown <br>Bitch, I'm on fire oh yeah <br>Bitch, I'm on fire oh yeah <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>We 'bout to burn the fucking club down <br><br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>Bit bit bit bit bit bit <br>Bit bit bit bit bit bit <br>Bitch, I'm on fire <br>We 'bout to burn the fuckin' club down <br><br>Yellow motherfucking Claw]]></content><category term="Yellow Claw" label="Yellow Claw"/><category term="City on Lockdown (Feat. Juicy J &amp; Lil Debbie)" label="City on Lockdown (Feat. Juicy J &amp; Lil Debbie)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Open_Feat_Moksi__Jonna_Fraser/</id><title>Yellow Claw - Open (Feat. Moksi &amp; Jonna Fraser) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:59:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:59:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Open_Feat_Moksi__Jonna_Fraser/" title="Yellow Claw - Open (Feat. Moksi &amp; Jonna Fraser) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let's take a moment and see how far we can explore <br>Body to body, a distant we open your door <br><br>Bottle rockets are blowing, hands are exploring <br>Position myself, I like <br>Whisky makes me controlling, I care for nothing <br>Let go and live for a night <br><br>Tell me nothing, tell me nothing <br>Show me love right in the open <br>Tell me nothing, tell me nothing <br>Show me love right in the open <br>Tell me nothing, tell me nothing <br>Show me love right in the open <br>Tell me nothing, tell me nothing <br>Show me love right in the open <br>Tell me <br><br>I'll bring the motion, just let it take over your life <br>Shoulder to shoulder, we both feel like losing control <br><br>Bottle rockets are blowing, hands are exploring <br>Position myself, I like <br>Whisky makes me controlling, I care for nothing <br>Let go and live for a night <br><br>Tell me nothing, tell me nothing <br>Show me love right in the open <br>Tell me nothing, tell me nothing <br>Show me love right in the open <br>Tell me nothing, tell me nothing <br>Show me love right in the open <br>Tell me nothing, tell me nothing <br>Show me love right in the open <br>Tell me]]></content><category term="Yellow Claw" label="Yellow Claw"/><category term="Open (Feat. Moksi &amp; Jonna Fraser)" label="Open (Feat. Moksi &amp; Jonna Fraser)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Good_Day_Feat_DJ_Snake__Elliphant/</id><title>Yellow Claw - Good Day (Feat. DJ Snake &amp; Elliphant) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:59:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:59:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Good_Day_Feat_DJ_Snake__Elliphant/" title="Yellow Claw - Good Day (Feat. DJ Snake &amp; Elliphant) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You make me feel like all those kids that <br>Were supposed to stay the night but <br>Changed their mind and called their mommy <br>You are not me, I am dirty <br>You make me feel like all those kids that <br>Were supposed to stay the night but <br>Changed their mind and called their mommy <br>You are not me <br><br>Remember that day, we met for coffee and you were late <br>Yeah, we chatted about you and you mostly but a bit about me <br>And then we went back to yours and I never been there before <br>On the blue line subway <br>Yeah, I think it was raining, yeah, you made me a painting <br>Sing a song about dolphins, young love, was calling <br><br>It was a good day <br>Oh, what a good day <br>But it is long gone now <br>When all the stars fell down <br>It was a good day <br>Oh, what a good day <br>That day you broke my heart <br>I loved you way too hard <br>Now I'm free <br><br>Remember so well, that time when I found a dog <br>I thought you'd be cool, not cool at all when you opened the door come on <br>You said I was your soulmate and I was there on my way <br>On the blue line subway <br>And I think it was snowing 'cause the city was glowing <br>Yeah, I started to notice, young love, was broken <br><br>It was a good day <br>Oh, what a good day <br>But it is long gone now <br>When all the stars fell down <br>It was a good day <br>Oh, what a good day <br>That day you broke my heart <br>I loved you way too hard <br>Now I'm free <br><br>Free, free, free falling]]></content><category term="Yellow Claw" label="Yellow Claw"/><category term="Good Day (Feat. DJ Snake &amp; Elliphant)" label="Good Day (Feat. DJ Snake &amp; Elliphant)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Love__War_Feat_Yade_Lauren/</id><title>Yellow Claw - Love &amp; War (Feat. Yade Lauren) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:59:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:59:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Love__War_Feat_Yade_Lauren/" title="Yellow Claw - Love &amp; War (Feat. Yade Lauren) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cut me through my skin <br>Through the heart, yeah, you went right in <br>I fell for every word you said <br><br>I can't leave but I can't stay <br>I don't know, I don't know, I don't know <br>Why some things have to be this way <br><br>We build it up to break it down <br>And then we're lost until we're found <br>And when we're high further from the ground <br>If all is fair in love and war <br>I can't do this anymore <br>If all is fair in love and war <br>I can't do this anymore <br><br>So unfair, so unfair, so unfair to me <br>So unfair, so unfair, so unfair to me <br><br>You told me from the start <br>Nothing could tear us apart <br>Now when I look I see a stranger <br><br>I can't leave but I can't stay <br>I don't know, I don't know, I don't know <br>Why some things have to end this way <br><br>We build it up to break it down <br>And then we're lost until we're found <br>And when we're high further from the ground <br>If all is fair in love and war <br>I can't do this anymore <br>If all is fair in love and war <br>I can't do this anymore <br><br>So unfair, so unfair, so unfair to me <br>So unfair, so unfair, so unfair to me]]></content><category term="Yellow Claw" label="Yellow Claw"/><category term="Love &amp; War (Feat. Yade Lauren)" label="Love &amp; War (Feat. Yade Lauren)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Without_You_Feat_The_Galaxy__Gia_Koka/</id><title>Yellow Claw - Without You (Feat. The Galaxy &amp; Gia Koka) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:59:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:59:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Without_You_Feat_The_Galaxy__Gia_Koka/" title="Yellow Claw - Without You (Feat. The Galaxy &amp; Gia Koka) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You got me not falling at all <br>I guess I knew was never yours <br>But I never heard about them all, no <br>You could've told me way before <br>One in a million, I was more <br>I wouldn't never let go <br>So you are quickly moving on 'cause <br>If you could've told me way before <br><br>But I'm good without you <br>I keep looking but I'll never go back, no <br>I was better but without your love <br>I'm good without you <br>And I'm not saying goodbye, baby, no <br>I was better but without your love <br><br>Good <br>But I'm good <br>But I'm <br>I was better but without your love <br><br>Tell me you know where do I go <br>When they said all that calls me home <br>Sometimes I wonder if we knew at all <br>The way we knew it right before <br>I see in your eyes, you hold back <br>You don't even tell it's the same <br>Sometimes I wonder if we all done <br>Would you be drowning in my love <br><br>But I'm good, ooh ooh ooh, without you, ooh ooh ooh <br>I can't, I can't ever go back, no <br>I was better but without your love, I'm <br><br>Good <br>But I'm good <br>I'm <br>I was better but without your love <br><br>I'm good, without you <br>But I'm good, without you <br>But I'm good, without you <br>But I'm good, without you]]></content><category term="Yellow Claw" label="Yellow Claw"/><category term="Without You (Feat. The Galaxy &amp; Gia Koka)" label="Without You (Feat. The Galaxy &amp; Gia Koka)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Home_Feat_Sophie_Simmons/</id><title>Yellow Claw - Home (Feat. Sophie Simmons) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T22:59:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T22:59:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yellow_Claw/Home_Feat_Sophie_Simmons/" title="Yellow Claw - Home (Feat. Sophie Simmons) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Take me home <br>While we're young and lives are living <br>Take me home <br>Choose before the night is through <br>I don't care <br>When you wanna keep the feelings <br>As long as I get to stay while you do <br>Take me home, with you <br>Take me home, with you <br>Take me home, with you <br>Take me home, with you <br><br>Tell me a story, make up the pieces <br>Tell me what you want me to do <br>Moving closer, I'm sick of the distance <br>Tell me what you want me to do <br><br>'Cause I'm here for you <br>'Cause I'm here for you <br>'Cause I'm here for you <br>'Cause I'm here for you <br><br>Love me like you never really wanna know my name <br>Everybody always thinks that they don't play these games <br>'Cause you wanna take me home and you wanna feel my soul <br>'Cause we wanna, 'cause we wanna get to know <br>Feel my soul <br>And you feel my soul <br>And you feel my soul <br>And you feel my soul <br>And you <br><br>Tell me a story, make up the pieces <br>Tell me what you want me to do <br>Moving closer, I'm sick of the distance <br>Tell me what you want me to do <br><br>'Cause I'm here for you <br>'Cause I'm here for you <br>'Cause I'm here for you <br>'Cause I'm here for you]]></content><category term="Yellow Claw" label="Yellow Claw"/><category term="Home (Feat. Sophie Simmons)" label="Home (Feat. Sophie Simmons)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/To_Die_For/Beautiful_Liam_Summers_Remix/</id><title>To Die For - Beautiful (Liam Summers Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:00:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:00:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/To_Die_For/Beautiful_Liam_Summers_Remix/" title="To Die For - Beautiful (Liam Summers Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Listen I know you've been hurt <br>without a reason <br>Can see it in the way <br>you're walking <br>Slowly hiding every tear <br>that's dropping <br>Don't hide it anymore <br>And if you're lost <br>The way to finding you <br>I will help you through <br>Just remember <br>that you're beautiful <br>Remember that you're beautiful <br>Remember that you're beautiful <br>Listen I know you've been hurt <br>without a reason <br>Can see it in the way <br>you're walking <br>Slowly hiding every tear <br>that's dropping <br>Don't hide it anymore <br>And if you're lost <br>The way to finding you <br>I will help you through <br>Just remember <br>that you're beautiful <br>Remember that you're beautiful <br>Remember that you're beautiful <br>beautiful <br>beautiful <br>Just remember <br>that you're beautiful <br>I see it in you <br>It's in everything you do <br>Remember that you're beautiful <br>Remember that you're beautiful <br>Remember that you're beautiful <br>Remember that you're beautiful <br>]]></content><category term="To Die For" label="To Die For"/><category term="Beautiful (Liam Summers Remix)" label="Beautiful (Liam Summers Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Traila_ong/Young_Luvin_Feat_DION_MICRODOT/</id><title>Traila $ong - Young Luvin` (Feat. DION, MICRODOT) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:00:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:00:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Traila_ong/Young_Luvin_Feat_DION_MICRODOT/" title="Traila $ong - Young Luvin` (Feat. DION, MICRODOT) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was dragged for <br>clubbing by my friends <br>but same type of guys and music <br>are not special to me anymore <br>But then I feel the graze from you <br>I like the way you move <br>I like the way you groove <br>I imagined that you coming to me <br>you can pull me out <br>from this boring club <br>I’m waiting for you <br>to fly away with the stars <br>all the stars are shinning for us <br>everything seems fine tonight <br>there is nothing to be scared <br>it’s just you and me <br>the night is forever <br>Young Young Luvin’ <br>nights forever <br>Young Young Luvin’ <br>nights forever <br>Young Young Luvin’ <br>Oh girl I like the way you move <br>I like the way you groove <br>the way you work your body <br>the way I like it clap clap <br>Club에서 만났지만 <br>여서 벗어날래 <br>여기에 탁한 공기가 <br>너랑은 잘 맞지 않네 <br>별말은 여기까지 <br>손을 잡고 따라오게 <br>입 술부터 따라 <br>시원하게 한잔할래 <br>오늘 밤은 별들과 <br>함께 보낼 거니까 <br>걱정하지 말아 <br>오늘 만은 우리 둘뿐이야 <br>the nights forever <br>Young Young Luvin’ <br>we gonna fly away with the stars <br>우주선을 건너서 갈 거니까 <br>돌아올 생각은 내려놔 <br>It’s time to say bye saiyonara <br>nights forever <br>Young Young Luvin’ <br>nights forever <br>Young Young Luvin’ <br>but same type of guys and music <br>Young Luvin’ <br>But then I feel the graze from you <br>Young Luvin’ <br>I like the way you move <br>I like the way you groove <br>I imagined that you coming to me <br>you can pull me out <br>from this boring club <br>I’m waiting for you <br>to fly away with the stars <br>all the stars are shinning for us <br>everything seems fine tonight <br>there is nothing to be scared <br>it’s just you and me <br>the night is forever <br>Young Young Luvin’ <br>]]></content><category term="Traila $ong" label="Traila $ong"/><category term="Young Luvin` (Feat. DION, MICRODOT)" label="Young Luvin` (Feat. DION, MICRODOT)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노시현/벚꽃_로맨스_Feat_지뉴/</id><title>노시현 - 벚꽃 로맨스 (Feat. 지뉴) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:00:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:00:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EC%8B%9C%ED%98%84/%EB%B2%9A%EA%BD%83_%EB%A1%9C%EB%A7%A8%EC%8A%A4_Feat_%EC%A7%80%EB%89%B4/" title="노시현 - 벚꽃 로맨스 (Feat. 지뉴) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[변했으면 해 우리 사이 온도 <br>내 신경은 너에게로 온통 <br>친구 사이에서 너를 원해 애인으로 <br>그건 내게 same as 로또 <br>요즘 따라 바쁘다는 핑계야 <br>무심한 니 말투 표정 하나까지 <br>니가 정말 좋긴 좋은데 <br>그러다가도 밉긴 미운데 <br>이쁘던 밉던 한 가지만 해 <br>살랑살랑 봄바람에 끌리는 <br>내 맘을 왜 자꾸 몰라주는 건데 <br>오 나와 입을 맞춰 <br>또 그대 나와 눈을 맞춰 <br>내 맘속엔 봄 향기가 나 <br>넌 나의 벚꽃 로맨스 <br>너는 나의 초코 쉐이커 <br>너무 사르르르 녹아 든 우리지만 <br>난 니가 살짝 미운걸 <br>너의 맘이 살짝 불안해 <br>이제 두근두근 긴장 좀 해봐 <br>3분 뒤에 답장할게 <br>뚜루뚜루 뚜뚜 뚜뚜 <br>oh 뚜루 뚜 뚜 뚜 <br>뚜루뚜루 뚜뚜 뚜뚜 <br>삐걱 삐걱 자꾸 늦는 답장에 <br>서운한 내 맘 왜 몰라주는 건데 <br>oh 내게 집중해줘 <br>너 좀 더 나를 꽉 안아줘 <br>내 마음 흔들리기 전에 <br>넌 나의 벚꽃 로맨스 <br>너는 나의 초코 쉐이커 <br>너무 사르르르 녹아 든 우리지만 <br>난 니가 살짝 미운걸 <br>너의 맘이 살짝 불안해 <br>이제 두근두근 긴장 좀 해봐 <br>3분 뒤에 답장할게 <br>뚜루뚜루 뚜뚜 뚜뚜 <br>oh 뚜루 뚜 뚜 뚜 <br>뚜루뚜루 뚜뚜 뚜뚜 <br>No more time <br>hurry up <br>can be lost uh <br>더 많은 hashtag 너만을 위한 <br>럽스타 를 만들어 <br>자랑하고 싶은데 <br>시간이 아까워 더 가까이 <br>너에게 다가갈래 <br>새까맣던 맘이 너를 생각하니 <br>하얗게 다 녹아내려 <br>벚꽃 눈 위로 날아가 <br>흩날리는 벚꽃 앞에 맹세해 <br>연애도 프로다운 자세로 <br>오늘은 꼭 프로포즈 <br>넌 나의 벚꽃 로맨스 <br>너는 나의 초코 쉐이커 <br>너무 사르르르 녹아 든 우리지만 <br>난 니가 살짝 미운걸 <br>너의 맘이 살짝 불안해 <br>이제 두근두근 긴장 좀 해봐 <br>3분 뒤에 답장할게 <br>뚜루뚜루 뚜뚜 뚜뚜 <br>oh 뚜루 뚜 뚜 뚜 <br>뚜루뚜루 뚜뚜 뚜뚜 <br>]]></content><category term="노시현" label="노시현"/><category term="벚꽃 로맨스 (Feat. 지뉴)" label="벚꽃 로맨스 (Feat. 지뉴)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/권미나/언제까지/</id><title>권미나 - 언제까지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:00:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:00:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B6%8C%EB%AF%B8%EB%82%98/%EC%96%B8%EC%A0%9C%EA%B9%8C%EC%A7%80/" title="권미나 - 언제까지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[품 속에 맺힌 너 <br>나는 아직도 잊지 못한 채 <br>어제도 바보처럼 난 <br>또다시 울었지만 <br>지금은 없는 너의 품 <br>누가 대신할 수 없다는 걸 알면서 <br>잊으려 애써보지만 결국 난 또 <br>왜 나만 여기 있는지 <br>언제까지 맘 아플지 <br>그만하자고 그만하자고 <br>언제까지 아플 거냐고 <br>물어도 보지만 나는 <br>멈춰 서 서있어보는 나는 <br>참 바보처럼 아무것도 <br>하지 않는 나는 언제까지 <br>너에게 있는 나를 이젠 꺼내줬음 해 <br>나만 아픈 이런 이별 <br>이젠 그만했음 해 <br>이렇게 아파해야 하는 <br>사인 아니었잖아 <br>언제까지 언제까지 <br>널 이렇게 그리워해야 해 <br>내가 만약 떠오르면 <br>눈 감아도 보인다면 <br>내게 와줄래 꼭 안아줄래 미안해도 <br>내 걱정 말고 우리의 <br>아픔들 모두 <br>다 지워내면 되잖아 다시 <br>따스했던 그때로만 <br>돌아가면 되는 우리인데 <br>]]></content><category term="권미나" label="권미나"/><category term="언제까지" label="언제까지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아거_AGER/뒷소문_Gossip/</id><title>아거 (AGER) - 뒷소문 (Gossip) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:00:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:00:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EA%B1%B0_AGER/%EB%92%B7%EC%86%8C%EB%AC%B8_Gossip/" title="아거 (AGER) - 뒷소문 (Gossip) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 너의 모든걸 이해해 <br>그것이 사실이었대도 <br>다 감싸줄게 그 누가 뭐래도 <br>속상하게 울지마 <br>아무렇지 않게 비꼬는 말투에 <br>그저 재미 삼아 내뱉는 널 이해 <br>할 순 없지만 그냥 생각할게 <br>사랑 받지 못한 니가 더 불쌍해 <br>It's over <br>말로 하는 모든 게 <br>I never <br>거짓도 진짜가 되니까 <br>It's over <br>두 눈을 마주치면 <br>I never <br>난 그런 적 없다고 <br>신경 쓰지마 넌 다르니까 <br>모두 너가 되고 싶어해 <br>모든 게 부러우니까 <br>너의 까만 피부 향기까지 모두 다 <br>질투해 너의 아름다운 <br>마음까지 모두 다 <br>금방 잊어 이젠 넌 모든걸 <br>어서 나와 잊어 난 너의 모든 것 <br>금방 잊어 이젠 넌 모든걸 <br>어서 나와 잊어 난 너의 모든 것 <br>나에게 다 말할 필요는 없어 <br>누구나 존재해 어두운 건 <br>난 그저 너가 원하는걸 <br>똑같이 바래줄게 <br>너의 STYLE <br>맞추려는 건 아냐 절대 <br>넌 지금 이대로 괜찮아 <br>만약 내가 없대도 넌 충분해 <br>SHOW SHOW ME <br>내겐 보여줘도 돼 <br>조금 망가져도 돼 <br>도망가지 않아 절대 <br>SHOW SHOW ME <br>내겐 약해져도 돼 <br>뭐가 맞고 틀린 지 <br>중요하지 않아 절대 <br>신경 쓰지마 넌 다르니까 <br>모두 너가 되고 싶어해 <br>모든 게 부러우니까 <br>너의 까만 피부 향기까지 모두 다 <br>질투해 너의 아름다운 <br>마음까지 모두 다 <br>금방 잊어 이젠 넌 모든걸 <br>어서 나와 잊어 난 너의 모든 것 <br>금방 잊어 이젠 넌 모든걸 <br>어서 나와 잊어 난 너의 모든 것 <br>MA WORLD <br>WHEN YOU'RE LOST <br>WHEN YOU CRY <br>WHEN YOU SMILE <br>WHEN YOU LOVE <br>WHEN YOU SAID MY NAME <br>ALWAYS ALWAYS GONNA BE THERE <br>]]></content><category term="아거 (AGER)" label="아거 (AGER)"/><category term="뒷소문 (Gossip)" label="뒷소문 (Gossip)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소심한_오빠들/퍽이나/</id><title>소심한 오빠들 - 퍽이나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:00:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:00:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EC%8B%AC%ED%95%9C_%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%A0%EB%93%A4/%ED%8D%BD%EC%9D%B4%EB%82%98/" title="소심한 오빠들 - 퍽이나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[돌아가려 해도 <br>돌아가려 해도 잊어버린 <br>너로 가득했던 시간들 <br>영원할 거라고 <br>영원할 거라고 믿어버린 <br>손에 남은 너의 체온 <br>Lay you lay you girl <br>뺨에 니 머릿결 <br>Leave me girl leave me girl <br>향기만 환상 속에 남아서 <br>퍽이나 널 잊겠다 <br>이건 이별도 아닌걸 <br>떠나간 이유라도 알려줘 <br>퍽이나 너 없이도 <br>그럭저럭 살 수 있겠다 <br>차라리 미워하게 해줘요 <br>언제 헤어져도 <br>언제 헤어져도 괜찮다고 <br>사랑은 믿을 수 없다고 <br>너 떠나가고 <br>찾을 수가 없던 이유들 <br>버리고 간 추억들만 <br>주워 담고 있는 나 <br>Blow you blow you girl <br>둘만의 비밀로 가득했던 <br>Leave me girl leave me girl <br>텅 비어버린 밤 홀로 남아서 <br>퍽이나 널 잊겠다 <br>이건 이별도 아닌걸 <br>떠나간 이유라도 알려줘 <br>퍽이나 너 없이도 <br>그럭저럭 살 수 있겠다 <br>차라리 미워하게 해줘요 <br>나 혼자 사랑하고 이별하는 방식 <br>이젠 정말 그만할 수 없나 <br>그대 그땐 왜 슬픈 눈빛은 <br>무슨 의미였나 <br>다시 너를 보고 싶어 미칠 것 같아 <br>퍽이나 널 잊겠다 <br>이건 이별도 아닌걸 <br>떠나간 이유라도 알려줘 <br>퍽이나 너 없이도 <br>그럭저럭 살 수 있겠다 <br>차라리 미워하게 해줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="소심한 오빠들" label="소심한 오빠들"/><category term="퍽이나" label="퍽이나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소심한_오빠들/그대만으로/</id><title>소심한 오빠들 - 그대만으로 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:00:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:00:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EC%8B%AC%ED%95%9C_%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%A0%EB%93%A4/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%A7%8C%EC%9C%BC%EB%A1%9C/" title="소심한 오빠들 - 그대만으로 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밤늦은 길을 걸었죠 <br>마치 처음인 것 같아서 <br>사실은 내 맘 텅 비어있었지 <br>상처만을 남겨둔 채 <br>내겐 소중했던 사소한 기억도 <br>이젠 내겐 너 하나만으로 <br>다르게 흐르던 우리의 날들이 <br>내겐 그대만으로 <br>내겐 그대 하나만으로 <br>수많은 실망과 기대 <br>다툼 또 이별 가운데 <br>한참을 울었어 원망했어 <br>내게 와준 그대만을 떠올려 난 <br>그댄 내게 운명이죠 <br>세상 그 무엇도 대신할 수 없어 <br>내겐 내겐 너 하나만으로 <br>다르게 흐르던 우리의 날들이 <br>나는 그대만으로 <br>내겐 그대 하나만으로 <br>세상의 고난도 모진 비바람도 <br>내가 곁에 있음으로 너 이대로만 <br>쓰러져 갈 일도 더 살아갈 힘도 <br>나는 그대만으로 <br>내겐 그대 하나만으로 <br>]]></content><category term="소심한 오빠들" label="소심한 오빠들"/><category term="그대만으로" label="그대만으로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소심한_오빠들/내_마음에_봄이오면/</id><title>소심한 오빠들 - 내 마음에 봄이오면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:00:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:00:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EC%8B%AC%ED%95%9C_%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%A0%EB%93%A4/%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C%EC%97%90_%EB%B4%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%98%A4%EB%A9%B4/" title="소심한 오빠들 - 내 마음에 봄이오면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[감기에 지독히 걸린 것 같아 <br>콧물이 멈추질 않네요 <br>땅은 녹아가고 볕은 따사로운 하루를 <br>혼자 차갑게 걷는다 <br>유난히도 춥던 지난 겨울은 <br>마음 속에 시린 바람 불어 <br>봄을 맞이하는 거리의 설레는 풍경에 <br>훌쩍 콧물을 닦는다 <br>내 맘에도 봄이 오기를 기다려 <br>내 맘에도 봄이 오면 <br>새 신을 신고 너와 함께 걸을래 <br>봄이 오면은 난 너의 손을 꼭 잡고 <br>흩날리는 꽃잎을 따라서 맘껏 뛰놀다 <br>미처 몰랐던 그 힘들었던 얘기들 <br>밤새워 앉아 토닥여줄게 <br>내 마음에 봄이 오면 <br>봄이 오면은 난 너의 손을 꼭 잡고 <br>흩날리는 꽃잎을 따라서 맘껏 뛰놀다 <br>미처 몰랐던 그 힘들었던 얘기들 <br>밤새워 앉아 토닥여줄게 <br>내 마음에 봄이 오면 <br>감기에 지독히 걸린 것 같아 <br>콧물이 멈추질 않네요 <br>땅은 녹아가고 볕은 따사로운 봄날을 <br>혼자 차갑게 걷는다 <br>차갑게 걷는다 <br>]]></content><category term="소심한 오빠들" label="소심한 오빠들"/><category term="내 마음에 봄이오면" label="내 마음에 봄이오면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소심한_오빠들/내게_기대/</id><title>소심한 오빠들 - 내게 기대 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:01:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:01:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EC%8B%AC%ED%95%9C_%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%A0%EB%93%A4/%EB%82%B4%EA%B2%8C_%EA%B8%B0%EB%8C%80/" title="소심한 오빠들 - 내게 기대 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[상처받은 마음에 <br>걱정말란 말을 해 <br>반복되는 위로에 <br>또 맘이 무뎌져 <br>그대와의 사랑이 <br>더 커진 것만 같아서 <br>말문이 막혀 와요 <br>그대 걱정만으로 가득해 <br>툭 한 방울이 떨어지던 <br>나 몰래 흘린 눈물 <br>더 이상 내버려 둘 순 없어 <br>그대 내게 기대 <br>한 번만 더 내게 기대줄래 <br>아무 말 없이 꼭 안겨줄래 <br>너 힘이 든다면 <br>그냥 이대로 기대 <br>내 손을 잡아봐요 <br>메마른 하루 끝에 <br>흠뻑 기대 <br>촉촉히 안겨봐요 <br>그댈 생각하다가 <br>달빛과 마주치면 <br>숨겨왔던 내 마음을 밤새워 말을 해 <br>툭 한 방울이 떨어지면 <br>나 몰래 흘린 눈물 <br>말없이 네 편이 되어줄게 <br>그대 내게 기대 <br>한 번만 더 내게 기대줄래 <br>아무 말 없이 꼭 안겨줄래 <br>너 힘이 든다면 <br>그저 내 어깨 기대 <br>내 팔이 저려와도 <br>괜찮아 너만 기대 <br>흠뻑 기대 <br>촉촉히 안겨봐요 <br>그대와 둘이서 마주잡은 두손 <br>]]></content><category term="소심한 오빠들" label="소심한 오빠들"/><category term="내게 기대" label="내게 기대"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소심한_오빠들/Apple/</id><title>소심한 오빠들 - Apple - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:01:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:01:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EC%8B%AC%ED%95%9C_%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%A0%EB%93%A4/Apple/" title="소심한 오빠들 - Apple - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh baby <br>내 겨울은 이미 끝났어 <br>창밖은 아직 추운데 <br>황홀함 니 웃음은 나에게 그래 <br>네게 중독 되도 될까 <br>Nobody knows <br>nobody knows <br>nobody knows <br>You're the apple of my eyes <br>너의 목소리는 <br>You're the apple of my eyes <br>다 노래 같아 <br>yeh yeh yeh 미칠 것 같아 <br>yeh yeh yeh 라랄라라 <br>yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh <br>오 빨리 봄이 왔으면 좋겠어 <br>내 맘 이미 개나리 밭 <br>왜 이제 나타난 걸까 <br>지금까지 만난 여자 모두 다 <br>어설픈 장난이 됬어 <br>Nobody knows <br>nobody knows <br>nobody knows <br>You're the apple of my eyes <br>너의 목소리는 <br>You're the apple of my eyes <br>다 노래 같아 <br>yeh yeh yeh 미칠 것 같아 <br>yeh yeh yeh 라랄라라 <br>yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh <br>너의 목소리는 <br>Oh Oh yeh yeh yeh yeh <br>yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh <br>미칠 것 같아 <br>yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh <br>You're the apple of my eyes <br>yeh yeh yeh 미칠 것 같아 <br>yeh yeh yeh 라랄라라 <br>]]></content><category term="소심한 오빠들" label="소심한 오빠들"/><category term="Apple" label="Apple"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소심한_오빠들/Fit_You/</id><title>소심한 오빠들 - Fit You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:01:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:01:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EC%8B%AC%ED%95%9C_%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%A0%EB%93%A4/Fit_You/" title="소심한 오빠들 - Fit You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이른 아침 눈을 뜰 때 <br>절대 생각나지 않는 여자 <br>삼십분만 같이 놀아도 <br>기가빨려 피곤한 여자 <br>어쩌다 재밌는 짤을 볼때 <br>얘기하고 싶지 않은 여자 <br>하나부터 열까지 통하지 않아 <br>모든 게 땅에 뚝뚝 <br>떨어지는 여자 <br>Fit you girl <br>내 여자 없나 <br>Fit you girl <br>혹시 내가 문제인걸까 <br>한 두 마디만 얘기해 봐도 <br>뭔가 나와 결이 같은 여자 <br>랄라라랄라라 팔짱 낄 땐 <br>기가 막히게 자로 잰 듯 <br>내게 딱 들어맞는 여자 <br>You're my beautiful <br>Fit you girl <br>내 여자 없나 <br>Fit you girl <br>혹시 내가 문제인걸까 <br>Fit you 나에게 넌 <br>혹시 니가 <br>Fit you girl <br>혹시 니가 <br>Fit you girl <br>내 여자 없나 <br>Fit you girl <br>혹시 내가 문제인걸까 <br>Fit you girl <br>처음인 것 같아 <br>Fit you girl <br>혹시 니가 운명인걸까 <br>]]></content><category term="소심한 오빠들" label="소심한 오빠들"/><category term="Fit You" label="Fit You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소심한_오빠들/밤과_음악사이/</id><title>소심한 오빠들 - 밤과 음악사이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:01:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:01:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EC%8B%AC%ED%95%9C_%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%A0%EB%93%A4/%EB%B0%A4%EA%B3%BC_%EC%9D%8C%EC%95%85%EC%82%AC%EC%9D%B4/" title="소심한 오빠들 - 밤과 음악사이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[불타는 금요일 저녁 <br>한잔 걸친 취기에 <br>거울 속에 내 모습 멋져 보여 <br>민증을 검사한 후에 <br>무도회장 오늘도 남탕이네요 <br>두루루루루루 뚜루루루루루루 <br>뚜루루루루루루루루 <br>어차피 또 볼 것도 아닌데 <br>지들도 뭐 나랑 똑같은 맘 <br>말 걸지도 않았어 <br>자꾸 됐다 그러네 <br>아이 아아아 아이 <br>친구 녀석 화를 내네 <br>여자들이 너무 튕긴대 <br>이럴 거면 오질 말지 왜 와서 <br>도도한척하고 그래 <br>친구야 입장 바꿔 생각해봐 <br>지금 망할 네 비주얼을 봐 <br>입에선 곱창 냄새 FACE <br>개 기름 조명에 번들거려 <br>수많은 남자들 속에 <br>둘러싸인 그녀는 <br>귀찮은 듯 짜증을 내고 있어요 <br>좋아하는 것 같기도 해 <br>보이지만 <br>하지만 그녀도 <br>밖에 나가면 쓸쓸해 <br>무도회장이라서 가능해 <br>나이는 자꾸 먹어가고 <br>주위에 다 나와 똑같은 맘 <br>외로움은 도무지 <br>익숙해지질 않네 <br>아이 아아아아이 <br>사람 사는 게 다 그렇지 머 <br>주위에 아무도 없는 밤 <br>반짝이는 이 밤은 <br>내게 비추질 않네 <br>아이 아아아아이 <br>]]></content><category term="소심한 오빠들" label="소심한 오빠들"/><category term="밤과 음악사이" label="밤과 음악사이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/22Bullets/Drop_In_The_Ocean_Feat_Hero_Baldwin/</id><title>22Bullets - Drop In The Ocean (Feat. Hero Baldwin) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:01:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:01:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/22Bullets/Drop_In_The_Ocean_Feat_Hero_Baldwin/" title="22Bullets - Drop In The Ocean (Feat. Hero Baldwin) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The silhouettes of what's before <br>The mess of minds we left at shore <br>They wash away in a ripe tide <br>And if in doubt the living proof <br>A gift of words I give to you <br>Won't be caught in a half lie <br><br>So don't go running through the dark without me <br>Secrets at night but I'm still loving <br>So don't go running through the dark without me <br>Secrets at night but I'm still loving <br><br>You are not a drop in the ocean <br>You are not a drop in the ocean <br>You are not a drop in the ocean <br>We're the ocean in a drop <br>You are not a drop in the ocean <br>You are not a drop in the ocean <br>You are not a drop in the ocean <br>We're the ocean in a drop <br><br>It isn't less until it's more <br>You can't be rich 'till you've been poor <br>And I've been living in both lives <br>And it's been rough <br>I didn't choose that broken bridge that leads to you <br>Life don't come with the guidelines <br>So don't go running through the dark without me <br>Secrets at night but I'm still loving <br>So don't go running through the dark without me <br>Secrets at night but I'm still loving <br><br>You are not a drop in the ocean <br>You are not a drop in the ocean <br>You are not a drop in the ocean <br>We're the ocean in a drop <br>You are not a drop in the ocean <br>You are not a drop in the ocean <br>You are not a drop in the ocean <br>We're the ocean in a drop <br><br>So don't go running through the dark without me secrets at night but I'm still loving <br>Don't go running through the dark without me secrets at night but I'm still loving <br>I'm still loving <br><br>You are not a drop in the ocean <br>You are not a drop in the ocean <br>You are not a drop in the ocean <br>We're the ocean in a drop]]></content><category term="22Bullets" label="22Bullets"/><category term="Drop In The Ocean (Feat. Hero Baldwin)" label="Drop In The Ocean (Feat. Hero Baldwin)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sophia_Somajo/Sapphire/</id><title>Sophia Somajo - Sapphire - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:03:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:03:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sophia_Somajo/Sapphire/" title="Sophia Somajo - Sapphire - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This will be the last time <br>We say goodbye, goodbye <br>And I'm not gonna cry <br>I'm just gonna let it die <br>Sapphire <br><br>This will be my masterpiece <br>A beautiful catastrophy <br>You're my perfect tragedy <br>You're the love that cannot be <br>So I'm gonna set you free <br><br>Cause you <br>Like a rare jewel <br>With your heart so blue <br>You'll never be mine <br>Sapphire <br>You <br>Like greedy fool <br>I've been clinging to <br>A love that can't be mine <br>Sapphire, sapphire <br>Sapphire <br><br>I'm gonna let you go <br>Cause I know, I know, I know <br>And I'm not gonna cry <br>I'm just gonna let it die <br>Sapphire <br><br>This will be my masterpiece <br>A beautiful catastrophy <br>You're my perfect tragedy <br>You're the love that cannot be <br>So I'm gonna set you free <br><br>Cause you <br>Like a rare jewel <br>With your heart so blue <br>You'll never be mine <br>Sapphire <br>You <br>Like greedy fool <br>I've been clinging to <br>A love that can't be mine <br>Sapphire, sapphire <br>Sapphire <br><br>I'm letting you go <br>I'm letting you go <br>I'm letting you go <br>Sapphire, sapphire <br><br>Cause you <br>Like a rare jewel <br>With your heart so blue <br>You'll never be mine <br>Sapphire <br>You <br>Like greedy fool <br>I've been clinging to <br>A love that can't be mine <br>Sapphire, sapphire <br>Sapphire <br>Sapphire, sapphire <br>Sapphire <br><br>Goodbye sapphire <br>Goodbye sapphire <br>Goodbye sapphire <br>I'm letting you go]]></content><category term="Sophia Somajo" label="Sophia Somajo"/><category term="Sapphire" label="Sapphire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sophia_Somajo/Mouth_To_Mouth/</id><title>Sophia Somajo - Mouth To Mouth - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:03:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:03:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sophia_Somajo/Mouth_To_Mouth/" title="Sophia Somajo - Mouth To Mouth - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The night is alive <br>It's thick and it's dark and it's pounding like a heart <br>It hits me hard <br>I walk through the fire <br>Them lonely bodies, moving like they're lost <br>Like crying stars <br><br>And I've been around this block <br>Too many times <br><br>Somebody help me out <br>I'm feeling lonely <br>Like I'm about to die <br>Somebody save my life <br>Mouth to mouth <br>Mouth to mouth <br>Mouth to mouth <br><br>And one is a crowd <br>Them whispering voices, ringing in my ears <br>It's hard to hear <br>I turn the music up loud <br>But the words of the song are spelling out my fears <br>I can taste the tears <br><br>And i've been around this block <br>Too many times <br><br>Somebody help me out <br>I'm feeling lonely <br>Like I'm about to die <br>Somebody save my life <br>Mouth to mouth <br>Mouth to mouth <br>Mouth to mouth <br><br>Somebody take me hard <br>I wanna feel that I'm alive <br>Somebody <br>Breathe <br>Life <br>Into me <br>Mouth to mouth <br>Mouth to mouth <br><br>Somebody help me out <br>I'm feeling lonely <br>Like I'm about to die <br>Somebody save my life <br>Mouth to mouth <br>Mouth to mouth <br>Mouth to mouth]]></content><category term="Sophia Somajo" label="Sophia Somajo"/><category term="Mouth To Mouth" label="Mouth To Mouth"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sophia_Somajo/Klein_Blue/</id><title>Sophia Somajo - Klein Blue - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:03:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:03:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sophia_Somajo/Klein_Blue/" title="Sophia Somajo - Klein Blue - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let me tell how I is like an ocean <br>A bottomless abyss of emotion <br>Where there isn't light, the colors lack <br>Darker than the night, but I'm not all black <br><br>Ay ay ay ay ay, I'm so deep <br>Ay ay ay ay ay, my sea <br>Oh, but I got color, color, color, color <br><br>Cause when I hit the light <br>You see that I'm a Klein blue <br>An electric hue if you get a better view of me, of me <br>When I hit the light <br>You see that I'm a Klein blue <br>And I shine through don't I shine through to you, to you <br>If I hit the light <br>Ain't I pretty <br><br>Let me tell you how I is <br>Like a waterfall <br>Violent, blue, and crisp <br>I am beautiful <br><br>Ay ay ay ay ay, it's so deep <br>Ay ay ay ay ay, my sea <br>Hey, but I got color, color, color, color <br><br>Cause when I hit the light <br>You see that I'm a Klein blue <br>An electric hue if you get a better view of me, of me <br>When I hit the light <br>You see that I'm a Klein blue <br>And I shine through don't I shine through to you, to you <br>If I hit the light <br>Ain't I pretty <br><br>Look at me now <br>Out of the dark and into the light <br>Look at me now <br>So bright <br><br>Cause when I hit the light <br>You see that I'm a Klein blue <br>An electric hue if you get a better view of me, of me <br>When I hit the light <br>You see that I'm a Klein blue <br>And I shine through don't I shine through to you, to you <br>If I hit the light <br>Don't I shine <br>Don't I shine <br>Don't I shine <br>So don't I shine <br>Ain't I pretty]]></content><category term="Sophia Somajo" label="Sophia Somajo"/><category term="Klein Blue" label="Klein Blue"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Darin/Ja_Ma_Du_Leva/</id><title>Darin - Ja Ma Du Leva - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:04:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:04:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Darin/Ja_Ma_Du_Leva/" title="Darin - Ja Ma Du Leva - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Varje dag, varje dag ar en ny dag <br>Andas in, o lamna spegeln for en stund <br>Skaka av dig dina tradar, lat mig torka alla dina tarar <br>Finns mer att fira an att sorja <br>Kan du tanka om, ja om fran borjan <br><br>For nar du blundar ar allting klart <br>Sag mig vad du ser nar du ser dig sjalv <br>Kan du sakna sant du redan har <br>Ett andetag, den tid du har kvar <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br><br>Varje dag, varje dag ar en nystart <br>Titta upp for himlen speglar all var mark <br>Vart du an i varlden hamnar <br>Vart du an i livet tanker stanna, oh <br>Nar det kanns som allting rasar <br>Finns det alltid nagon vag tillbaka <br><br>For nar du blundar ar allting klart <br>Sag mig vad du ser nar du ser dig sjalv <br>Kan du sakna sant du redan har <br>Ett andetag, den tid du har kvar <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br><br>Varje dag, varje dag ar en ny dag <br>Sa hoj ditt glas, for nu ar allting som det ska <br>Hey <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br>Ja ma du leva idag <br><br>For nar du blundar ar allting klart <br>Sag mig vad du ser nar du ser dig sjalv <br>Kan du sakna sant du redan har <br>Ett andetag, den tid du har kvar <br>Ja ma du leva idag]]></content><category term="Darin" label="Darin"/><category term="Ja Ma Du Leva" label="Ja Ma Du Leva"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ROO_루/사랑이겠죠/</id><title>ROO (루) - 사랑이겠죠 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:04:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:04:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ROO_%EB%A3%A8/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4%EA%B2%A0%EC%A3%A0/" title="ROO (루) - 사랑이겠죠 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언제부턴가 바라만 봐도 <br>난 알아요 everyday <br>새로운 계절이 찾아오듯 <br>맘이 갔죠 <br>입가에 미소 가득 담고서 <br>shiny day <br>기대할 것 없었던 <br>내 하루에 그대가 왔어요 <br>참 고단했는데 <br>피곤해 지친 날도 <br>다독여 줄 수 있는 <br>그대가 있어 든든하죠 <br>Whoo 사랑이겠죠 <br>매일 매일 느끼죠 <br>내 맘 속에 스며들어 <br>mashmellow처럼 <br>달달해져요 자꾸 <br>Whoo 내 편이겠죠 <br>just wanna be my love <br>기나긴 날 기다린 시간 <br>늘 내 곁에 늘 내 곁에 <br>그대만 있어줘요 <br>서로 다른 우리가 <br>기적처럼 만날 수 있던 건 <br>단순한 인연은 아니라 믿고 싶어 <br>혹 운명이 아닐까 <br>새로운 삶이 시작됐죠 <br>Whoo 사랑이겠죠 <br>매일 매일 느끼죠 <br>내 맘 속에 스며들어 <br>mashmellow처럼 <br>달달해져요 자꾸 <br>Whoo 내 편이겠죠 <br>just wanna be my love <br>기나긴 날 기다린 시간 <br>늘 내 곁에 늘 내 곁에 <br>그대만 있어줘요 <br>가끔씩 맘과 다른 말이 나와 <br>아이처럼 투정부리기도 해 <br>엇갈리는 Timing Timing <br>돌아서면 후회하는 <br>My heart My heart <br>내가 밉겠죠 <br>I let you down <br>다 알아요 <br>when I think of you <br>하지만 사랑인 걸 my love <br>Whoo 사랑이겠죠 <br>매일 매일 느끼죠 <br>내 맘 속에 스며들어 <br>mashmellow처럼 <br>달달해져요 자꾸 <br>Whoo 내 편이겠죠 <br>just wanna be my love <br>기나긴 날 기다린 시간 <br>늘 내 곁에 늘 내 곁에 <br>그대만 있어줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="ROO (루)" label="ROO (루)"/><category term="사랑이겠죠" label="사랑이겠죠"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/일레븐/NP/</id><title>일레븐 - NP - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:04:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:04:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%BC%EB%A0%88%EB%B8%90/NP/" title="일레븐 - NP - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nothings are hear and every where <br>even though heaven <br>Nothings have no problem <br>in no where <br>Nothings have no problem <br>in no where <br>Nothings are hear and every where <br>even though heaven <br>Nothings are hear and every where <br>even though heaven <br>Nothings have no problem <br>in no where <br>Nothings have no problem <br>in no where <br>Nothings are hear and every where <br>even though heaven <br>]]></content><category term="일레븐" label="일레븐"/><category term="NP" label="NP"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nitro_Fun/Come_With_Me_Feat_Anna_Yvtte/</id><title>Nitro Fun - Come With Me (Feat. Anna Yvtte) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:04:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:04:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nitro_Fun/Come_With_Me_Feat_Anna_Yvtte/" title="Nitro Fun - Come With Me (Feat. Anna Yvtte) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Anticipation <br>The twilight fuels <br>the intoxication <br>No hesitation <br>I'm giving <br>in to this sweet sensation <br>I've been good <br>I've been bad <br>But this moment is <br>all we really have <br>So when the night is calling <br>I pick up the phone <br>A voice is singing sweetly <br>You don't have to be alone <br>Come with me <br>Come with me <br>Come with me <br>Come with me <br>Come with me <br>Come with me <br>Come with me <br>Please don't go please don't go <br>Please don't go please don't go <br>I've been good <br>I've been bad <br>But this moment is <br>all we really have <br>So when the night is calling <br>I pick up the phone <br>A voice is singing sweetly <br>You don't have to be alone <br>Come with me <br>Come with me <br>Come with me <br>Come with me <br>Come with me <br>1 2 3 Go <br>Come with me <br>]]></content><category term="Nitro Fun" label="Nitro Fun"/><category term="Come With Me (Feat. Anna Yvtte)" label="Come With Me (Feat. Anna Yvtte)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/언더_루프_Under_Loop/얼마나_더_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>언더 루프 (Under Loop) - 얼마나 더.. (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:04:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:04:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%B8%EB%8D%94_%EB%A3%A8%ED%94%84_Under_Loop/%EC%96%BC%EB%A7%88%EB%82%98_%EB%8D%94_Acoustic_Ver/" title="언더 루프 (Under Loop) - 얼마나 더.. (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[햇살이 눈부신 날 <br>손을 잡고 함께 걷던 <br>그날 그 거리에 지금 나와있죠 <br>저만치 앞선 곳에서 <br>나를 보며 미소 짓던 <br>그 모습이 내 안에 살아있어요 <br>얼마나 더 아파해야 하는지 <br>이렇게 죽어가고 있는데 <br>내게 소중했던 내겐 전부였던 <br>그대는 어디에 <br>누군가 사랑은 <br>날 행복하게 할 거라고 <br>사랑 사람답게 사는 하나라고 <br>하지만 지금 내게 <br>날 비참하게 만드는 건 <br>바로 사랑 바로 사랑이에요 <br>얼마나 더 아파해야 하는지 <br>이렇게 죽어가고 있는데 <br>내게 소중했던 내겐 전부였던 <br>그대는 어디쯤에 있나요 <br>얼마나 더 아파해야 하는지 <br>이렇게 죽어가고 있는데 <br>내게서 멀어져 다신 볼 수 없는데 <br>얼마나 더 아파해야 하는지 <br>이렇게 죽어가고 있는데 <br>내게 소중했던 내겐 전부였던 <br>그대는 어디쯤에 있나요 <br>얼마나 더 <br>죽어가고 있는데 <br>그대는 어디에 <br>]]></content><category term="언더 루프 (Under Loop)" label="언더 루프 (Under Loop)"/><category term="얼마나 더.. (Acoustic Ver.)" label="얼마나 더.. (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/언더_루프_Under_Loop/얼마나_더/</id><title>언더 루프 (Under Loop) - 얼마나 더.. - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:04:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:04:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%B8%EB%8D%94_%EB%A3%A8%ED%94%84_Under_Loop/%EC%96%BC%EB%A7%88%EB%82%98_%EB%8D%94/" title="언더 루프 (Under Loop) - 얼마나 더.. - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[햇살이 눈부신 날 <br>손 꼭 잡고 함께 걷던 그대 <br>이젠 슬픈 가사 쓸 때 <br>영감을 주는 존재가 됐네 <br>아직도 책상 서랍 중의 <br>첫 번째 칸은 <br>추억들로 가득 찬 <br>보물창고 언제나 <br>네가 보고 싶을 때 <br>그 보물들 덕분에 <br>함께인 듯한 기분 <br>느낄 수 있어 사진 속에 <br>온 세상이 내 것인듯한 표정 <br>우린 손을 꼭 잡고 있고 <br>우릴 비추는 태양은 <br>절대 안 저물 것이라 <br>믿었어 사랑스러운 <br>넌 내 전부이자 자랑거리 <br>지금은 없어져버린 <br>내 전부 내 자랑거리 <br>너 떠나가고 홀로 보내는 <br>네 번째 겨울이 <br>왜 이리 추운지 <br>소용없어 장갑과 목도리 <br>내 삶은 이렇게 망가져가나 봐 <br>다시 잡을 수 없는 걸 <br>잡으려 하고 있잖아 <br>오늘 밤도 서랍 속 보물들을 <br>보면서 잠깐 <br>웃다가 한참을 울다가 <br>잠에 들겠지 <br>얼마나 더 아파해야 하는지 <br>이렇게 죽어가고 있는데 <br>내게 소중했던 내겐 전부였던 <br>그대는 어디에 <br>누군간 사랑 때문에 <br>살아있음을 느끼고 사람답게 <br>살 수 있다 말하며 웃지만 <br>난 그 사랑 때문에 <br>비참하게 가라앉는 중 <br>눈물과 함께 <br>바보가 되어가고 있는 중 <br>그 누구도 날 <br>치료해 줄 수 없어 <br>오로지 너만 할 수 있어 <br>네가 곁에 있어야 난 갈 수 있고 <br>또 날 수 있어 <br>내게 힘을 주었던 <br>그대 맑은 눈동자 <br>보고 싶어 마지막으로 딱 한 번만 <br>얼마나 더 아파해야 하는지 <br>이렇게 죽어가고 있는데 <br>내게 소중했던 내겐 전부였던 <br>그대는 어디쯤에 있나요 <br>이건 마지막 순간 <br>전에 못다 전한 <br>내 맘 속의 말들이야 <br>그때는 미처 다정하게 <br>말하지 못했던 <br>그대에겐 나쁘게 기억될 <br>놈의 진심이야 <br>내 말 한 번만 들어줘 <br>이건 마지막 순간 <br>전에 못 다 전한 <br>내 맘속의 말들이야 <br>그때는 미처 다정하게 <br>말하지 못했던 <br>그대에겐 나쁘게 기억될 <br>놈의 진심이야 <br>내 말 한 번만 들어줘 <br>]]></content><category term="언더 루프 (Under Loop)" label="언더 루프 (Under Loop)"/><category term="얼마나 더.." label="얼마나 더.."/></entry></feed>