<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:04:53+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kj김민수/친구보다_형제/</id><title>Kj김민수 - 친구보다 형제 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:04:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:04:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kj%EA%B9%80%EB%AF%BC%EC%88%98/%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC%EB%B3%B4%EB%8B%A4_%ED%98%95%EC%A0%9C/" title="Kj김민수 - 친구보다 형제 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 참 오래됐었지 <br>꿈 많던 시절에 <br>서로 얘길 나누고 <br>그렇게 또 밤을 세고 <br>세월이란 높은 산 <br>우릴 갈라 놔도 <br>느낄 수 있어요 <br>함께라면 모든 걸 이기죠 <br>함께 있지 않아도 <br>우리의 우정은 <br>소나무처럼 항상 널 기다려 <br>세월의 산을 넘고 <br>각자의 길을 떠날 때 <br>우리의 우정은 항상 <br>마음에 살지 <br>오늘은 헤어져도 <br>언젠가 서로 차 한잔 하며 <br>서로 어깰 두드리며 <br>잘 살았노라고 <br>말해요 <br>그땐 참 힘들었었지 <br>방황한 시절에 <br>마음도 많이 시렸고 <br>그렇게 또 아파하고 <br>세월이란 넓은 강 <br>우릴 갈라 놔도 <br>느낄 수 있어요 <br>함께라면 모든 걸 견디죠 <br>함께 하잔 그 말도 <br>그 어떤 약속도 <br>뜨거운 가슴 속에 <br>널 담아둬 <br>세월의 강을 건너 <br>각자의 길을 떠날 때 <br>우리의 우정은 항상 <br>마음에 살지 <br>오늘은 헤어져도 <br>언젠가 서로 차 한잔 하며 <br>서로 어깰 두드리며 <br>잘 살았노라고 <br>세월의 산을 넘고 <br>각자의 길을 떠날 때 <br>우리의 우정은 항상 <br>마음에 살지 <br>오늘은 헤어져도 <br>언제가 서로 차 한잔 하며 <br>서로 어깰 두드리며 <br>잘 살았노라고 <br>말해요 <br>내 인생 최고는 너야 <br>내 인생 최고의 행운 <br>비록 볼 순 없어도 <br>끝이 다가 온대도 그래요 <br>우리 또 다른 세상을 <br>꿈꿔요 <br>]]></content><category term="Kj김민수" label="Kj김민수"/><category term="친구보다 형제" label="친구보다 형제"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KIDZ_키즈/BETRAY_Feat_ody/</id><title>KIDZ (키즈) - BETRAY (Feat. $ody) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:04:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:04:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KIDZ_%ED%82%A4%EC%A6%88/BETRAY_Feat_ody/" title="KIDZ (키즈) - BETRAY (Feat. $ody) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[i knew he would betray me <br>uh amd i feel like <br>ok ok ok <br>get of my way <br>how i can not see <br>어떻게 내 앞이 보이지 <br>않아서 눈 감고 달려가지 <br>uh 시계는 돌아가지 <br>뒤로 돌아가진 않아 <br>빨간 불엔 멈추니까 <br>사고 날 이유 없지 wah <br>모두 날 속단하고 보내 <br>난 아직 <br>보여준 게 없었는데 <br>가난 하진 <br>않지만 난 부와 명예 <br>필요하지 <br>공부와는 어릴 때부터 <br>거리 멀지 <br>세월의 가면을 쓰니까 <br>바뀌어만 가는 내 성격이 <br>시간이 가면은 hoh <br>점점 더 나은 미래가 <br>기다리고 있다는 것을 <br>나는 hoh <br>아직은 모르겠네 why <br>알았으면 벌써 <br>성공을 하고도 남았지 <br>부모님 속 안 썩이고 나왔지 <br>난 달라 until i die <br>죽기 전까지는 난 <br>딴 따라가 될 거야 <br>아직은 안 들어가 <br>관광도 아직 난 못했어 hoh <br>기죽지 않고 난 날아가겠어 <br>현실이란 벽 다 부셔 <br>money time mind <br>다음 verse 에서 <br>i knew he would betray me <br>BETRAY <br>일단은 앞만 보고 가자고 <br>little while little while <br>자신 있게 말해 이게 맞다고 <br>BETRAY <br>못 버티겠다면 그냥 가라고 <br>little while little while <br>우린 멋대로 멋 부리고 산다고 <br>a yo 난 아무도 믿은 적 <br>없는데 배신을 당해 <br>내 착각 안에 계시는 분 <br>의자에만 앉아 계시네 <br>신에 계시에 의해서 <br>여태 이리 지내 <br>with a betray <br>hum hum <br>내가 달리 해석하고 <br>내가 달리 살아왔네 <br>태양의 반대편 그래 <br>새벽 몇 시 at the arena <br>고도를 기다렸어 <br>고도도 기다렸고 <br>동공은 좁혀져 <br>make some noise <br>이젠 범생이는 no no <br>i want you to know <br>you know <br>완전 100 프로 의 나 <br>i don't give a <br>아직 멀었어 <br>람보르기니 요놈 <br>humm get it now <br>get it now get it now right <br>it it boooom baby like <br>baby like baby like swervin' <br>$ody 사람들은 진짜가 <br>뭔지 이제 실감할 거야 <br>i feel like <br>노력은 진가를 발휘해 <br>배신하지 않아 <br>애초에 사람들을 <br>믿지 않았지만 <br>그들이 날 믿도록 <br>노력하지 날마다 <br>i knew he would betray me <br>BETRAY <br>일단은 앞만 보고 가자고 <br>little while little while <br>자신 있게 말해 이게 맞다고 <br>BETRAY <br>못 버티겠다면 그냥 가라고 <br>little while little while <br>우린 멋대로 멋 부리고 산다고 <br>너네가 경험하지 못한 플로우 <br>골방에 나를 가둬두고 연구한 <br>모든 것이 이제 <br>세상 밖으로 나와 <br>like big bang <br>아마 이걸 묻히고 살기엔 <br>혼날 거 같거든 신께 <br>몇 없는 달란트 <br>내 운명인데 어찌해 <br>그래 맞아 난 부자에 재격 <br>겸손을 알아가게 해주셨네 <br>thanks god <br>im own it 나만에 스타일 <br>얘들아 곧 내가 만들게 <br>랩 애국가 <br>BETRAY <br>일단은 앞만 보고 가자고 <br>little while little while <br>자신 있게 말해 이게 맞다고 <br>BETRAY <br>못 버티겠다면 그냥 가라고 <br>little while little while <br>우린 멋대로 멋 부리고 산다고 <br>BETRAY <br>일단은 앞만 보고 가자고 <br>little while little while <br>자신 있게 말해 이게 맞다고 <br>BETRAY <br>못 버티겠다면 그냥 가라고 <br>little while little while <br>우린 멋대로 멋 부리고 산다고 <br>]]></content><category term="KIDZ (키즈)" label="KIDZ (키즈)"/><category term="BETRAY (Feat. $ody)" label="BETRAY (Feat. $ody)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/범민/Bluescreen_Inst/</id><title>범민 - Bluescreen (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:04:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:04:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B2%94%EB%AF%BC/Bluescreen_Inst/" title="범민 - Bluescreen (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[도통 알 수 없어 <br>너의 마음이 <br>시도 때도 없이 <br>나타나서 왜 그래 <br>나를 흔들어놨어 <br>흔들어놨어 <br>흔들어놨어 <br>너의 마음이 <br>그 위에서 <br>하얗게 그려졌어 <br>알 수가 없잖아 <br>알고 싶어도 <br>난 알고 싶어도 <br>난 알 수가 없잖아 <br>블루 스크린 <br>그래 마치 내게 너 <br>블루 스크린 <br>나 고장나버렸어 <br>사라져 사라져 <br>내 모든 게 멈춰버린 <br>지금 블루스크린 <br>블루 스크린 <br>니 감정 그 위에서 <br>블루 스크린 <br>자꾸만 보여지고 <br>또 내게서 널 가뒀어 <br>블루스크린 <br>블루스크린 <br>난 언제나 네 눈밖에 <br>펴지지 않는 우산 같애 <br>너의 곁에 있지만 <br>쓸모 없게 네 손길이 <br>닿지 않지 <br>거짓말로 뒤덮인 Skin <br>그 속에 난 계속 Deep in <br>넌 나를 보며 대체 <br>어떤 생각을 하고 있니 Uh <br>잊어보려고 나를 속였어 <br>오늘까지만 널 <br>그리워하겠다고 <br>애써 맘을 비우려 했어 <br>그럴수록 니가 더 보였어 <br>돌아서가는 널 보면서 <br>바라보기만 했어 <br>나 바보 같았어 <br>아무 말도 못하고 <br>모든걸 버렸어 <br>널 잃어버렸어 <br>블루 스크린 <br>그래 마치 내게 넌 <br>블루 스크린 <br>나 고장나버렸어 <br>사라져 사라져 <br>내 모든 게 멈춰버린 <br>지금 블루스크린 <br>블루 스크린 <br>니 감정 그 위에서 <br>블루 스크린 <br>자꾸만 보여지고 <br>또 내게서 널 가뒀어 <br>블루스크린 <br>너 이젠 내게 오지마 <br>여기서 그만 가줘 <br>그대로 그렇게 떠나가버려 <br>Ay 그간 마지못해 <br>날 사랑한척한거야 No <br>아님 날 갖지못해 <br>날 포기하고만거야 No <br>거짓은 영원할 수 <br>없듯이 끝나버린 우리 <br>같잖은 말로 날 괴롭히던 <br>너도 끝났어 영원히 <br>너에겐 없지 나란 존재 <br>말할 필요없어 <br>다만 나에게도 <br>너란 존재는 이젠 <br>아무것도 아냐 <br>이 정도에서 끝내는게 <br>맞아 너는 Faker <br>기억속에서 마저 <br>지워버리고 싶어 <br>이 마지막이 너에게도 <br>상처로 남았으면 싶어 <br>블루 스크린 <br>그래 마치 내게 넌 <br>블루 스크린 <br>나 고장나버렸어 <br>사라져 사라져 <br>내 모든 게 멈춰버린 <br>지금 블루스크린 <br>블루 스크린 <br>니 감정 그 위에서 <br>블루 스크린 <br>자꾸만 보여지고 <br>또 내게서 널 가뒀어 <br>블루스크린 <br>]]></content><category term="범민" label="범민"/><category term="Bluescreen (Inst.)" label="Bluescreen (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/범민/Bluescreen_Feat_이도훈/</id><title>범민 - Bluescreen (Feat. 이도훈) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:05:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:05:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B2%94%EB%AF%BC/Bluescreen_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%84%ED%9B%88/" title="범민 - Bluescreen (Feat. 이도훈) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[도통 알 수 없어 <br>너의 마음이 <br>시도 때도 없이 <br>나타나서 왜 그래 <br>나를 흔들어놨어 <br>흔들어놨어 <br>흔들어놨어 <br>너의 마음이 <br>그 위에서 <br>하얗게 그려졌어 <br>알 수가 없잖아 <br>알고 싶어도 <br>난 알고 싶어도 <br>난 알 수가 없잖아 <br>블루 스크린 <br>그래 마치 내게 너 <br>블루 스크린 <br>나 고장나버렸어 <br>사라져 사라져 <br>내 모든 게 멈춰버린 <br>지금 블루스크린 <br>블루 스크린 <br>니 감정 그 위에서 <br>블루 스크린 <br>자꾸만 보여지고 <br>또 내게서 널 가뒀어 <br>블루스크린 <br>블루스크린 <br>난 언제나 네 눈밖에 <br>펴지지 않는 우산 같애 <br>너의 곁에 있지만 <br>쓸모 없게 네 손길이 <br>닿지 않지 <br>거짓말로 뒤덮인 Skin <br>그 속에 난 계속 Deep in <br>넌 나를 보며 대체 <br>어떤 생각을 하고 있니 Uh <br>잊어보려고 나를 속였어 <br>오늘까지만 널 <br>그리워하겠다고 <br>애써 맘을 비우려 했어 <br>그럴수록 니가 더 보였어 <br>돌아서가는 널 보면서 <br>바라보기만 했어 <br>나 바보 같았어 <br>아무 말도 못하고 <br>모든걸 버렸어 <br>널 잃어버렸어 <br>블루 스크린 <br>그래 마치 내게 넌 <br>블루 스크린 <br>나 고장나버렸어 <br>사라져 사라져 <br>내 모든 게 멈춰버린 <br>지금 블루스크린 <br>블루 스크린 <br>니 감정 그 위에서 <br>블루 스크린 <br>자꾸만 보여지고 <br>또 내게서 널 가뒀어 <br>블루스크린 <br>너 이젠 내게 오지마 <br>여기서 그만 가줘 <br>그대로 그렇게 떠나가버려 <br>Ay 그간 마지못해 <br>날 사랑한척한거야 No <br>아님 날 갖지못해 <br>날 포기하고만거야 No <br>거짓은 영원할 수 <br>없듯이 끝나버린 우리 <br>같잖은 말로 날 괴롭히던 <br>너도 끝났어 영원히 <br>너에겐 없지 나란 존재 <br>말할 필요없어 <br>다만 나에게도 <br>너란 존재는 이젠 <br>아무것도 아냐 <br>이 정도에서 끝내는게 <br>맞아 너는 Faker <br>기억속에서 마저 <br>지워버리고 싶어 <br>이 마지막이 너에게도 <br>상처로 남았으면 싶어 <br>블루 스크린 <br>그래 마치 내게 넌 <br>블루 스크린 <br>나 고장나버렸어 <br>사라져 사라져 <br>내 모든 게 멈춰버린 <br>지금 블루스크린 <br>블루 스크린 <br>니 감정 그 위에서 <br>블루 스크린 <br>자꾸만 보여지고 <br>또 내게서 널 가뒀어 <br>블루스크린 <br>]]></content><category term="범민" label="범민"/><category term="Bluescreen (Feat. 이도훈)" label="Bluescreen (Feat. 이도훈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강헌구/열우물길_Inst/</id><title>강헌구 - 열우물길 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:05:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:05:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%ED%97%8C%EA%B5%AC/%EC%97%B4%EC%9A%B0%EB%AC%BC%EA%B8%B8_Inst/" title="강헌구 - 열우물길 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어릴 적부터 살던 <br>우물 많은 우리 동네 <br>다들 가난했지만 <br>정은 많았었지 <br>어디로 갔을까 <br>그 많던 사람들 <br>이제 몇 집 안 남아 <br>그 자릴 지키고 있는데 <br>모두 떠난 자리에 <br>우리 집도 낡았고 <br>무너진 저 집처럼 <br>점점 더 가라앉고 <br>있는데 <br>언제가 될지 몰라 <br>여길 나가야 하는 것도 <br>정들었던 우리 동네 <br>모두 다 떠나야겠지 <br>언젠가는 <br>언제부터였을까 <br>빈집들이 늘어가고 <br>동네는 점점 낡아져 <br>영화촬영지로 <br>어디로 가야 하나 <br>집을 나서도 갈데 없는데 <br>동네 한 바퀴를 돌아 <br>전망 좋은 소방도로 위 <br>어두 캄캄한 밤에 <br>불 꺼진 창문 보며 <br>내 마음도 같이 꺼져가 <br>언제가 될지 몰라 <br>여길 나가야 하는 것도 <br>정들었던 우리 동네 <br>모두 다 떠나야겠지 <br>언제가 될지 몰라 <br>여길 나가야 하는 것도 <br>정들었던 우리 동네 <br>모두 다 떠나야겠지 <br>]]></content><category term="강헌구" label="강헌구"/><category term="열우물길 (Inst.)" label="열우물길 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강헌구/열우물길/</id><title>강헌구 - 열우물길 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:05:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:05:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%ED%97%8C%EA%B5%AC/%EC%97%B4%EC%9A%B0%EB%AC%BC%EA%B8%B8/" title="강헌구 - 열우물길 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어릴 적부터 살던 <br>우물 많은 우리 동네 <br>다들 가난했지만 <br>정은 많았었지 <br>어디로 갔을까 <br>그 많던 사람들 <br>이제 몇 집 안 남아 <br>그 자릴 지키고 있는데 <br>모두 떠난 자리에 <br>우리 집도 낡았고 <br>무너진 저 집처럼 <br>점점 더 가라앉고 <br>있는데 <br>언제가 될지 몰라 <br>여길 나가야 하는 것도 <br>정들었던 우리 동네 <br>모두 다 떠나야겠지 <br>언젠가는 <br>언제부터였을까 <br>빈집들이 늘어가고 <br>동네는 점점 낡아져 <br>영화촬영지로 <br>어디로 가야 하나 <br>집을 나서도 갈데 없는데 <br>동네 한 바퀴를 돌아 <br>전망 좋은 소방도로 위 <br>어두 캄캄한 밤에 <br>불 꺼진 창문 보며 <br>내 마음도 같이 꺼져가 <br>언제가 될지 몰라 <br>여길 나가야 하는 것도 <br>정들었던 우리 동네 <br>모두 다 떠나야겠지 <br>언제가 될지 몰라 <br>여길 나가야 하는 것도 <br>정들었던 우리 동네 <br>모두 다 떠나야겠지 <br>]]></content><category term="강헌구" label="강헌구"/><category term="열우물길" label="열우물길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ATRAIN/If_You_Feat_Young_Lion/</id><title>A.TRAIN - If You (Feat. Young Lion) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:05:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:05:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ATRAIN/If_You_Feat_Young_Lion/" title="A.TRAIN - If You (Feat. Young Lion) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 웃게만 해주고 싶지만 <br>지금의 내가 할 수 있을까 <br>기다려 달라고 말했지만 <br>그럴 자격 없는 건 나도 알어 <br>사랑하지만 <br>널 지켜줄 준비가 <br>아직 난 안 돼서 미안 <br>이런 모습 못난 거 아는데 <br>If you wanna be free <br>솔직히 말해주길 <br>I‘ll make you free <br>If you wanna be free <br>I’ll never stand in your way <br>I’ll let you free <br>너무 많은 꿈을 쫓았는데 <br>널 품에 안은 순간 깨달았네 <br>이제 내 꿈은 아무것도 없어 <br>오직 너와 함께 있는 건데 <br>남은 꿈마저 지킬 수 없네 <br>이토록 못난 나를 탓해 <br>널 아끼지만 <br>너를 가질 용기가 <br>아직 난 없어서 미안 <br>내가 이정도 밖에 안 되는 게 <br>If you wanna be free <br>솔직히 말해주길 <br>I‘ll make you free <br>If you wanna be free <br>I’ll never stand in your way <br>I’ll let you free <br>What’s love got to do with it <br>It’s not about love <br>내 맘은 무의미 <br>One bullet two birds choose one <br>And that's life <br>win some and lose some <br>So I shoot one bang bang <br>음표가 그려진 놈을 겨냥해 <br>다른 한 마리는 내 심장의 <br>반쪽을 가지고서 날 떠나네 <br>솔직히 말해줘 <br>너는 훨씬 더 나은 대접 <br>받을 자격 있는 걸 <br>널 위해 해줄 수 있는 건 <br>make you fly away <br>I will let you fly away <br>If you wanna be free <br>솔직히 말해주길 <br>I‘ll make you free <br>If you wanna be free <br>I’ll never stand in your way <br>I’ll let you free <br>]]></content><category term="A.TRAIN" label="A.TRAIN"/><category term="If You (Feat. Young Lion)" label="If You (Feat. Young Lion)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silly_Boot_씰리붓/Where_Your_Love_From__/</id><title>Silly Boot (씰리붓) - Where Your Love From ? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:05:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:05:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silly_Boot_%EC%94%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%B6%93/Where_Your_Love_From__/" title="Silly Boot (씰리붓) - Where Your Love From ? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Where your love from <br>What's wrong with you <br>What's wrong with me <br>How can we right this wrong <br>Where your love from <br>Who met before <br>Who loved before <br>Who taught this love <br>I lost my love <br>Love is complicated <br>It's like your thoughts <br>You're to complicated <br>I fuck her three times in one night <br>I know it's a kind of love <br>But I don't wanna talk <br>We no need to talk <br>Ooh we don't need to talk <br>uh I just wanna fuck <br>We just have fun <br>I can say I like the way <br>you move ur ass on ma D <br>I can tell ma bae ur ass <br>makes me insane oh god damn <br>pop n pour n pop n pour <br>n poppin' pu oh god damn <br>drank n fxxx n drank n fxxx n drank n <br>Oh what's problem <br>Where your love from <br>What's wrong with you <br>What's wrong with me <br>How can we right this wrong <br>Where your love from <br>Who met before <br>Who loved before <br>Who taught this love <br>I don't love you no more <br>I don't love you no more <br>If this is Love <br>I wouldn't love you no more <br>Oh This isn't Love <br>Love <br>Love <br>Love <br>Love <br>Hard to explain my emotion <br>All I can do is sippin' potion <br>I'm just hangin' out <br>and never thinkin' bout u <br>I'm not Frank Ocean <br>I rocked this clothes not for you <br>I rocked the club lookin' for girls <br>The party can't be over <br>She knows I'll never be sober <br>And I tell her <br>I can say I like the way <br>you move ur ass on ma D <br>I can tell ma bae ur ass <br>makes me insane oh god damn <br>pop n pour n pop n pour <br>n poppin' pu oh god damn <br>drank n fxxx n drank n fxxx n drank n <br>Oh what's problem <br>Where your love from <br>What's wrong with you <br>What's wrong with me <br>How can we right this wrong <br>Where your love from <br>Who met before <br>Who loved before <br>Who taught this love <br>I don't love you no more <br>I don't love you no more <br>If this is Love <br>I wouldn't love you no more <br>Oh This isn't Love <br>You got me fuckin' crazy <br>I don't get it baby <br>Where your love from <br>What's wrong with you <br>What's wrong with me <br>How can we right this wrong <br>Where your love from <br>Who met before <br>Who loved before <br>Who taught this love <br>I don't love you no more <br>I don't love you no more <br>If this is Love <br>I wouldn't love you no more <br>Oh This isn't Love <br>]]></content><category term="Silly Boot (씰리붓)" label="Silly Boot (씰리붓)"/><category term="Where Your Love From ?" label="Where Your Love From ?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silly_Boot_씰리붓/Paradise_Feat_Hash_Swan/</id><title>Silly Boot (씰리붓) - Paradise (Feat. Hash Swan) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:05:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:05:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silly_Boot_%EC%94%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%B6%93/Paradise_Feat_Hash_Swan/" title="Silly Boot (씰리붓) - Paradise (Feat. Hash Swan) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니가 사진첩의 우리를 지워도 <br>나는 다시 찍으면 된다고 믿어 <br>너의 마음을 돌릴 수 있다면 <br>난 십억을 <br>번 것처럼 완전 기뻐 <br>I don't give up <br>When you're mine <br>you fill my heart <br>I might be in a paradise <br>It's the paradise yeah <br>너를 다신 잃고 싶지 않아 <br>너와 함께면 어디든 <br>Paradise <br>난 너의 무조건적인 사랑을 원해 <br>내가 뜬금 없는 말을 해도 <br>일단 들어줘 <br>난 니가 집착 해주기를 바래 <br>나 아니면 다른 건 <br>필요 없다고 말해줘 <br>난 가진 게 없지만 너는 날 아네 <br>난 뭘 해서든 먹여 살릴 놈이기에 <br>니가 날 알게 된 게 팔자지 뭐 <br>너를 처음 본 날 <br>너무 예뻤던 게 탓이죠 <br>연애는 행복 하라고 하는 건데 <br>왜 우리는 싸우는 걸까 거의 전쟁 <br>왜 우리는 헤어졌을까 더 힘든데 <br>왜 우리는 다시 만날까 <br>또 싸울 건데 <br>난 더 깊게 생각을 해봤어 <br>삶은 선택에 따라 모든 게 바뀌지 <br>넌 이제 내 앞에서 방귀를 막 뀌지 <br>역시 나의 선택은 <br>넘나 멋지지 Yeah <br>니가 사진첩의 우리를 지워도 <br>나는 다시 찍으면 된다고 믿어 <br>너의 마음을 돌릴 수 있다면 <br>난 십억을 <br>번 것처럼 완전 기뻐 <br>I don't give up <br>When you're mine <br>you fill my heart <br>I might be in a paradise <br>It's the paradise yeah <br>너를 다신 잃고 싶지 않아 <br>너와 함께면 어디든 <br>Paradise <br>니가 사진첩의 우리를 지워도 <br>나는 다시 찍으면 된다고 믿어 <br>요즘 세상은 좋아 <br>난 아이맥 넌 아이폰 <br>You know what I'm sayin' <br>그대로 일거야 <br>내 집 비밀번호는 <br>내 집 비밀번호는 <br>아니 우리 집 비밀 번호는 <br>넌 그냥 다시 와서 캠핑 갈 준비해 <br>가서 다 풀고자 <br>이미 넌 챙겼잖아 버너를 <br>우리가 혹시 싸워도 <br>사진은 봐줄 테니 <br>내 번호는 놔둬줘 <br>니가 내가 크고 <br>성장 하는걸 봐줬으면 해 <br>키는 다 컸으니까 알잖아 다른 쪽 <br>우린 다투지 말자 계속 <br>지노 형이 다투는 건 <br>시간 낭비랬어 <br>난 니가 삐진 것 조차도 불안한데 <br>우리가 어떻게 <br>화를 내며 싸울 사이겠어 <br>니가 사진첩의 우리를 지워도 <br>나는 다시 찍으면 된다고 믿어 <br>너의 마음을 돌릴 수 있다면 <br>난 십억을 <br>번 것처럼 완전 기뻐 <br>I don't give up <br>When you're mine <br>you fill my heart <br>I might be in a paradise <br>It's the paradise yeah <br>너를 다신 잃고 싶지 않아 <br>너와 함께면 어디든 <br>Paradise <br>Everybody's gotta learn sometimes <br>I need ur lovin' like the sunshine <br>When you devastated <br>you yellin' like uh <br>We break up but we make up again <br>니가 사진첩의 우리를 지워도 <br>나는 다시 찍으면 된다고 믿어 <br>너의 마음을 돌릴 수 있다면 <br>난 십억을 <br>번 것처럼 완전 기뻐 <br>I don't give up <br>When you're mine <br>you fill my heart <br>I might be in a paradise <br>It's the paradise yeah <br>너를 다신 잃고 싶지 않아 <br>너와 함께면 어디든 <br>Paradise <br>it seems like <br>우리 둘은 산 넘고 바다를 건너 <br>미지의 세계를 찾아 헤매면서 <br>미국 대륙을 발견한 우연처럼 <br>운명의 장난에 내 맘은 이른 봄 <br>과거가 준 상처의 의미란 <br>우릴 더욱 강하게 할 뿐 <br>난 역전의 용사 <br>이름은 배수용 <br>너의 행동 말투 모두 <br>so beautiful <br>]]></content><category term="Silly Boot (씰리붓)" label="Silly Boot (씰리붓)"/><category term="Paradise (Feat. Hash Swan)" label="Paradise (Feat. Hash Swan)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silly_Boot_씰리붓/Find_Yourself/</id><title>Silly Boot (씰리붓) - Find Yourself - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:05:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:05:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silly_Boot_%EC%94%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%B6%93/Find_Yourself/" title="Silly Boot (씰리붓) - Find Yourself - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>천재 씔리붓 <br>Yeah I'm back again <br>내가 벌 돈은 <br>엔화로 백억엔 <br>난 날 힘들게 하는 것에 <br>소홀해 <br>반면 넌 힘드느라 <br>일을 미뤄 내일 모레로 <br>난 그러지 않아 왜냐면 <br>여긴 편하지 않아 <br>편하려고 하면 <br>상황은 변하지 않아 <br>난 선명하게 그렸네 <br>나의 미랠 <br>난 천억을 벌 놈이네 <br>I'll be that <br>난 밑에 누굴 두지 <br>않을거니까 날 빨지마 <br>그러고 싶은 여자들의 <br>마음은 잘 알지만 <br>내 꿈을 위해 늘 <br>스튜디오에 가있지 난 <br>브루스 리가 떠오르는 <br>눈빛의 살기 악 <br>이 친구는 말해 <br>XX 힘들어 살기가 <br>그럼 난 말해 <br>그럼 그딴 식으로 살지마 <br>Oh shit <br>그딴 식으로 말하지마 <br>니가 뭘 알어 <br>내 인생에 대해 XXXX야 <br>Damn <br>Man <br>Damn <br>난 정말로 <br>날고 싶어 하늘을 <br>난 호랑이처럼 <br>남기고 싶어 가죽을 <br>올해 중순까지 <br>알바했었어 파스쿠치에서 <br>근데 이제 하나 남은 <br>알바로 사는 중 <br>이 정도면 음악이 <br>취미라고 해도 돼 <br>직업란에 뮤지션이라고는 <br>못 적기에 <br>Don't call me hustler <br>Sometimes I wish I lived like <br>너네들처럼 어슬렁 거릴래 <br>홍대 Green Light <br>한신포차 썰파 <br>우리 같이 놀까 <br>2대 2가 좋을까 <br>아님 3대 3이 좋을까 <br>아님 4대 4가 좋을까 <br>아님 5대 5가 좋을까 <br>아님 우리 둘이 놀까 <br>몰카 없는 야놀자를 볼까 <br>Oh shit <br>그건 완전 내 스타일이 아냐 <br>난 이러려고 여기까지 <br>온게 아냐 <br>홈즈크루 돞밷 나는 멋진놈 <br>누가 뭐래도 나는 <br>떳떳하게 멋진놈 <br>Yeah <br>Oh man <br>Yeah <br>니 삶을 찾아 얼른 <br>니 삶을 찾아 얼른 <br>니 삶을 찾아 얼른 <br>니 삶을 찾아 얼른 <br>니 삶을 찾아 얼른 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>M.Z.N. Silly Boot 멋진놈 <br>Find yourself <br>Find yourself <br>Find yourself <br>Find yourself <br>Find yourself <br>Find yourself <br>Find yourself <br>Find yourself <br>]]></content><category term="Silly Boot (씰리붓)" label="Silly Boot (씰리붓)"/><category term="Find Yourself" label="Find Yourself"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silly_Boot_씰리붓/Wi-Fi/</id><title>Silly Boot (씰리붓) - Wi-Fi - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:05:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:05:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silly_Boot_%EC%94%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%B6%93/Wi-Fi/" title="Silly Boot (씰리붓) - Wi-Fi - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I got you baby <br>I got so crazy <br>We drank some <br>agwa bombs <br>Friday to Saturday <br>It was 7000 won <br>14000 won <br>I'll buy for you <br>I'll buy all for you <br>Yeah I like you <br>It's my payday <br>so I got you <br>Your sexy body moves <br>I need a one dance <br>I'm with you <br>I wanna take off my shirt <br>like you wanna <br>take off you skirt <br>I might hold you back <br>You love it <br>don't you babe <br>Burn let's let's make wild fire <br>connection like Wi-Fia <br>Burn let's make wild fire <br>connection <br>let's make wild fire <br>Burn burn burn burn <br>Let's let's make Wi-Fia <br>Burn burn burn burn <br>Let's let's make Wi-Fia <br>Burn burn burn burn <br>Let's let's make Wi-Fia <br>Burn burn burn burn <br>Let's let's make Wi-Fia <br>Apparently It's not a reality <br>Funny thing is everything <br>We don't see no sad thing <br>no bad thing <br>Oh hell yeah <br>She's gonna leave to Australia <br>I'm gonna leave to California <br>But we don't care about <br>the barrier <br>Worries in carrier <br>Oh yeah <br>let's make connection <br>We used make wild <br>fire seduction <br>I'm so bad cuz bed so wet <br>You call my name <br>you know my name is Bae <br>I wanna take off my shirt <br>like you wanna <br>take off your skirt <br>I might sex you back <br>You love it <br>don't you babe <br>Burn let's let's make wild fire <br>connection like Wi-Fia <br>Burn let's make wild fire <br>connection <br>let's make wild fire <br>Burn burn burn burn <br>Let's let's make Wi-Fia <br>Burn burn burn burn <br>Let's let's make Wi-Fia <br>Burn burn burn burn <br>Let's let's make Wi-Fia <br>Burn burn burn burn <br>Let's let's make Wi-Fia <br>우리도 만나면 <br>불꽃이 타올랐다가 <br>서로 멀어지면 <br>허무하게 꺼질까 <br>우리 사이가 <br>와이파이 같은 거라면 <br>난 오늘이라도 <br>너를 세게 안고싶어 <br>We can be F.W.B or B.F <br>even P.S.P <br>when you need that <br>어디에서든 난 <br>준비 돼 있으니 <br>Connect me anytime <br>Let's make wild fire <br>Burn burn burn burn <br>Let's let's make Wi-Fia <br>Burn burn burn burn <br>Let's let's make Wi-Fia <br>Burn burn burn burn <br>Let's let's make Wi-Fia <br>Burn burn burn burn <br>Let's let's make Wi-Fia <br>]]></content><category term="Silly Boot (씰리붓)" label="Silly Boot (씰리붓)"/><category term="Wi-Fi" label="Wi-Fi"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silly_Boot_씰리붓/Rich_N_Reach_U/</id><title>Silly Boot (씰리붓) - Rich N Reach U - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:05:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:05:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silly_Boot_%EC%94%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%B6%93/Rich_N_Reach_U/" title="Silly Boot (씰리붓) - Rich N Reach U - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I got a lot of money to earn <br>I got no time to burn <br>I got a lot of money to earn <br>I got no time to burn <br>You got the man <br>he's young <br>You got the man <br>he's brave <br>You got the man <br>he's sexy <br>You got the man <br>he's MZ <br>His goal is important but <br>now he can't stay <br>focused on nah <br>넌 날 너무나 <br>복잡하게 만들어 <br>oh God <br>I'll be rich and reach you <br>Be rich and reach you <br>I need to kiss you <br>I can make it true <br>나는 널 보러갈 <br>시간이 없어 <br>돈을 벌고 싶은 것 <br>밖에 없어 <br>그래 이런 나쁜게 <br>나의 적성에 맞아 <br>난 하나도 <br>아쉬울 것 없어 <br>맞아 난 감정이 <br>항상 앞서 <br>맞아 난 이기적이지 항상 <br>막상 날 알면 <br>내가 제일 나빠 <br>막상 날 까면 <br>나는 너무 어려 <br>너무 많은 일들이 <br>널 잡고 널 괴롭혀 <br>너는 현실을 훨씬 <br>더 잘 알거야 <br>너의 현실은 <br>나 없이도 잘 살거야 <br>근데 난 상황을 바꿀거야 <br>난 내 에너지를 <br>현실로 만들거야 <br>난 거의 맥그리거가 될거야 <br>거의 코너 <br>맥그리거처럼 될거야 <br>I got a lot of money to earn <br>I got no time to burn <br>I got a lot of money to earn <br>I got no time to burn <br>You got the man <br>he's young <br>You got the man <br>he's brave <br>You got the man <br>he's sexy <br>You got the man <br>he's MZ <br>His goal is important but <br>now he can't stay <br>focused on nah <br>넌 날 너무나 <br>복잡하게 만들어 <br>oh God <br>I'll be rich and reach you <br>Be rich and reach you <br>I need to kiss you <br>I can make it true <br>예뻐 보이던 건 <br>더 예뼈졌고 <br>안 예뻐 보이던 것도 <br>예뻐져 don't like it <br>몇 달간 안보던 책을 폈고 <br>몇 페이지를 넘기다 <br>다시 덮어 don't like it <br>내가 꼭 먹어야 <br>하는 아침을 먹고 <br>얄밉게 좋은 날씨에 <br>I feel fucked up <br>안 필려고 노력하던 <br>담배를 다시 꺼내 <br>이제야 실감이나 실감이나 <br>내가 한 행동들이 <br>다시 돌아와 날 괴롭혀 <br>이제야 다시 돌아가고 싶어 <br>너무 이기적인 <br>나의 방식인 걸 <br>넌 날 이제 믿지 못할거야 <br>다신 내게 기대고 <br>싶지가 않을거야 <br>근데 난 맥그리거가 될거야 <br>코너 맥그리거 처럼 <br>다 이뤄낼거야 <br>넌 그걸 알거야 <br>넌 그걸 알거야 <br>넌 그걸 알거야 <br>아무일에도 집중 <br>할 수 없어 <br>아무리 생각 해도 <br>나는 너 밖에 없어 <br>이제 겨울이야 <br>밖은 너무 춥고 <br>나는 너를 안고 싶은 <br>생각 말곤 뭐 없어 <br>내가 할 수 있는거는 <br>오직 하나뿐 <br>너를 보러 가야겠어 <br>니가 더 화가나든 <br>All these hoes keep <br>comin' back <br>but a silly boy <br>don't give a fuck and <br>go to meet you <br>있다가 우리봐요 <br>니 말대로 아직 <br>사랑을 모르는 나야 <br>니 말대로 다음 <br>여자한텐 그러면 안돼 <br>근데 난 다음 여잘 <br>만날 맘이 없단 말야 <br>남녀 사이엔 원래 <br>싸울 일이 많잖아 <br>너도 알아 우린 <br>너무 잘 어울리잖아 <br>Even though <br>I be a motherfuckin' star <br>나는 다른 놈들 처럼 <br>한 눈 팔지 않아 <br>I got a lot of money to earn <br>I got no time to burn <br>I got a lot of money to earn <br>I got no time to burn <br>You got the man <br>he's young <br>You got the man <br>he's brave <br>You got the man <br>he's sexy <br>You got the man <br>he's MZ <br>His goal is important but <br>now he can't stay <br>focused on nah <br>넌 날 너무나 <br>복잡하게 만들어 <br>oh God <br>I'll be rich and reach you <br>Be rich and reach you <br>I need to kiss you <br>I can make it true <br>]]></content><category term="Silly Boot (씰리붓)" label="Silly Boot (씰리붓)"/><category term="Rich N Reach U" label="Rich N Reach U"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silly_Boot_씰리붓/Theme/</id><title>Silly Boot (씰리붓) - Theme - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:05:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:05:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silly_Boot_%EC%94%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%B6%93/Theme/" title="Silly Boot (씰리붓) - Theme - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like I be Seouler <br>My brain needs a cooler <br>I drove my time to back <br>Why should I be so bad <br>She was beautiful <br>like my mom <br>It was a miracle <br>just like my birth <br>I wished I could have been <br>like my father <br>But it wasn't easy <br>to give everything <br>I'm so urban <br>난 이제부터 <br>들려 줄거야 <br>나에 대해 너에 대해 <br>우리에 대해 <br>난 이제부터 <br>물려 줄거야 <br>후세에게 <br>나의 메세지 <br>]]></content><category term="Silly Boot (씰리붓)" label="Silly Boot (씰리붓)"/><category term="Theme" label="Theme"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤븐_임팩트_미니스트리/주님이_오셨다_Inst/</id><title>헤븐 임팩트 미니스트리 - 주님이 오셨다 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:06:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:06:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EB%B8%90_%EC%9E%84%ED%8C%A9%ED%8A%B8_%EB%AF%B8%EB%8B%88%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AC/%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%B4_%EC%98%A4%EC%85%A8%EB%8B%A4_Inst/" title="헤븐 임팩트 미니스트리 - 주님이 오셨다 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[죄에 얽매인 <br>오랜 시간의 삶 <br>자기 뜻대로 <br>살아가는 자녀들 <br>그런 우리를 <br>너무 사랑하사 <br>친히 자신을 <br>내어주셨네 <br>찬송하여라 <br>거룩하신 주 예수를 <br>크게 외쳐라 <br>구원의 기쁜 소식을 <br>주님이 오셨다 <br>이 땅에 오셨다 <br>높으신 하나님 <br>독생자 그리스도 <br>우리 모든 죄 짊어지신 <br>하나님의 사랑 <br>온 세상에 선포하라 <br>홀로 남겨진 <br>길 잃은 양처럼 <br>그저 울면서 <br>방황하는 자녀들 <br>그런 우리를 <br>너무 아파하사 <br>친히 자신을 <br>나타내셨네 <br>찬송하여라 <br>거룩하신 주 예수를 <br>크게 외쳐라 <br>구원의 기쁜 소식을 <br>주님이 오셨다 <br>이 땅에 오셨다 <br>높으신 하나님 <br>독생자 그리스도 <br>우리 모든 죄 짊어지신 <br>하나님의 사랑 <br>온 세상에 선포하라 <br>주님이 오셨다 <br>이 땅에 오셨다 <br>높으신 하나님 <br>독생자 그리스도 <br>우리 모든 죄 짊어지신 <br>하나님의 사랑 <br>온 세상에 선포하라 <br>구세주 만왕의 왕 <br>그리스도 오셨도다 <br>]]></content><category term="헤븐 임팩트 미니스트리" label="헤븐 임팩트 미니스트리"/><category term="주님이 오셨다 (Inst.)" label="주님이 오셨다 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤븐_임팩트_미니스트리/주님이_오셨다/</id><title>헤븐 임팩트 미니스트리 - 주님이 오셨다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:06:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:06:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EB%B8%90_%EC%9E%84%ED%8C%A9%ED%8A%B8_%EB%AF%B8%EB%8B%88%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AC/%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%B4_%EC%98%A4%EC%85%A8%EB%8B%A4/" title="헤븐 임팩트 미니스트리 - 주님이 오셨다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[죄에 얽매인 <br>오랜 시간의 삶 <br>자기 뜻대로 <br>살아가는 자녀들 <br>그런 우리를 <br>너무 사랑하사 <br>친히 자신을 <br>내어주셨네 <br>찬송하여라 <br>거룩하신 주 예수를 <br>크게 외쳐라 <br>구원의 기쁜 소식을 <br>주님이 오셨다 <br>이 땅에 오셨다 <br>높으신 하나님 <br>독생자 그리스도 <br>우리 모든 죄 짊어지신 <br>하나님의 사랑 <br>온 세상에 선포하라 <br>홀로 남겨진 <br>길 잃은 양처럼 <br>그저 울면서 <br>방황하는 자녀들 <br>그런 우리를 <br>너무 아파하사 <br>친히 자신을 <br>나타내셨네 <br>찬송하여라 <br>거룩하신 주 예수를 <br>크게 외쳐라 <br>구원의 기쁜 소식을 <br>주님이 오셨다 <br>이 땅에 오셨다 <br>높으신 하나님 <br>독생자 그리스도 <br>우리 모든 죄 짊어지신 <br>하나님의 사랑 <br>온 세상에 선포하라 <br>주님이 오셨다 <br>이 땅에 오셨다 <br>높으신 하나님 <br>독생자 그리스도 <br>우리 모든 죄 짊어지신 <br>하나님의 사랑 <br>온 세상에 선포하라 <br>구세주 만왕의 왕 <br>그리스도 오셨도다 <br>]]></content><category term="헤븐 임팩트 미니스트리" label="헤븐 임팩트 미니스트리"/><category term="주님이 오셨다" label="주님이 오셨다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trio_Mindpoly_트리오_마인폴리/How_Come/</id><title>Trio Mindpoly (트리오 마인폴리) - How Come - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:06:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:06:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trio_Mindpoly_%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%98%A4_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B8%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC/How_Come/" title="Trio Mindpoly (트리오 마인폴리) - How Come - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How come <br>we're here to say goodbye <br>Lots of things we've been through <br>What made us come so far <br>No matter how we try <br>nothing would change but us <br>After all this how come <br>we have to say goodbye <br>This bud of love <br>by summer's ripening breath <br>may prove a beauteous flower <br>when next we meet <br>we can wave goodbye <br>without tears oh my dear <br>How come <br>I still recall the days <br>All the dreams that we share <br>that puts a smile on my face <br>No matter what they say <br>I guess we can call our own <br>Not that I care for us <br>we'd walk onto different dreams <br>This bud of love <br>by summer's ripening breath <br>may prove a beauteous flower <br>when next we meet <br>we can wave goodbye <br>without tears oh my dear <br>How come <br>we're here to say goodbye <br>Lots of things we've been through <br>What made us come so far <br>No matter how we try <br>nothing would change but us <br>After all this how come <br>we have to say goodbye <br>]]></content><category term="Trio Mindpoly (트리오 마인폴리)" label="Trio Mindpoly (트리오 마인폴리)"/><category term="How Come" label="How Come"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지혜리/사랑하기에/</id><title>지혜리 - 사랑하기에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:06:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:06:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%ED%98%9C%EB%A6%AC/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%98%EA%B8%B0%EC%97%90/" title="지혜리 - 사랑하기에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대가 주었던 사랑은 <br>어떤 말로도 담을 수 없을 만큼 <br>나를 살게 했던 가장 행복한 <br>사람이게 했던 <br>다시 안 올 행운이었어 <br>얼마나 더 울어야 이 후회가 <br>내게도 이별이 될까 <br>셀 수 없는 추억들이 과거가 될까 <br>그대에게 받은 사랑을 <br>돌려준대도 <br>다신 기회가 없죠 <br>온전한 맘으로 <br>모든걸 줬던 그대를 놓아버린 건 <br>사랑하기에 사랑했기에 <br>사랑하기에 안녕 <br>얼마나 더 흘러야 이 이별이 <br>지나간 인연이 될까 <br>셀 수 없는 얘기들이 침묵이 될까 <br>그대와 나눴던 사랑이 <br>끝나버려도 <br>절대 잊을 수 없죠 <br>온전한 맘으로 <br>모든 걸 줬던 그대를 놓아버린 건 <br>사랑하기에 사랑했기에 <br>사랑하기에 안녕 <br>]]></content><category term="지혜리" label="지혜리"/><category term="사랑하기에" label="사랑하기에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/원주민밴드/I_Love_You/</id><title>원주민밴드 - I Love You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:06:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:06:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9B%90%EC%A3%BC%EB%AF%BC%EB%B0%B4%EB%93%9C/I_Love_You/" title="원주민밴드 - I Love You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I Love You I Love You I Love You <br>I Love You I Love You I Love You <br>너의 마음속에 내 마음이 <br>들어갈 수만 있다면 <br>함께 있는 거야 날 느껴봐 <br>너를 위해 내가 있어 <br>다시 태어난 거야 너를 만난 건 <br>모든 것이 새롭게 느껴져 <br>서로 바라만 봐도 느낄 수 있어 <br>우리만의 사랑을 <br>큰소리 외쳐 날 불러 <br>널 위해 나 여깄을게 <br>네 맘속에 항상 숨쉬는 <br>너만의 나를 느껴봐 <br>I Love You I Love You I Love You <br>I Love You I Love You I Love You <br>너의 행복 속에 내 행복이 <br>함께할 수만 있다면 <br>더도 바라지 않아 <br>내 곁에만 있어줘 <br>내 모든걸 잃는다 해도 <br>너의 미소 속에 나의 하루는 <br>콧노래로 시작 돼 <br>귀를 기울여봐 너도 느껴봐 <br>우리만의 노래를 <br>큰소리 외쳐 날 불러 <br>널 위해 나 여깄을게 <br>네 맘속에 항상 숨쉬는 <br>너만의 나를 느껴봐 <br>I Love You I Love You I Love You <br>너만을 사랑해 <br>I Love You I Love You I Love You <br>너의 곁에 있을게 <br>I Love You I Love You I Love You <br>너만을 사랑해 <br>I Love You I Love You I Love You <br>너의 곁에 있을게 <br>]]></content><category term="원주민밴드" label="원주민밴드"/><category term="I Love You" label="I Love You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/권슬기/Whatever_You_Are/</id><title>권슬기 - Whatever You Are - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:06:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:06:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B6%8C%EC%8A%AC%EA%B8%B0/Whatever_You_Are/" title="권슬기 - Whatever You Are - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[앞이 어딘지 더딜지 모르지만 <br>어차피 갈 꺼 우물쭈물 고민 말고 <br>세상의 눈친지 뭔지 <br>멀리 버려두고 <br>해도 될까 궁상맞게 <br>생각지도 말고 <br>재밌게 살아보자 <br>두렵기도 무섭기도 하겠지만 <br>처음이 어렵지 <br>해보면 별 거 아니었단 생각에 <br>후회하지 말고 <br>Whatever you are <br>Whatever you are <br>그냥 해보는 거야 <br>남들처럼 똑같다면 재미없어 <br>너의 생각 너의 색을 그려봐 <br>Whatever you are <br>나는 나고 너는 너야 <br>재밌게 살아보자 <br>밝은 날이 올 거야 <br>두렵기도 무섭기도 하겠지만 <br>처음이 어렵지 <br>해보면 별 거 아니었단 생각에 <br>후회하지 말고 <br>Whatever you are <br>Whatever you are <br>그냥 해보는 거야 <br>남들처럼 똑같다면 재미없어 <br>너의 생각 너의 색을 그려봐 <br>Whatever you are <br>나는 나고 너는 너야 <br>재밌게 살아보자 <br>밝은 날이 올 거야 <br>근사했고 감사했던 날들아 <br>이젠 추억이 돼버린 <br>따듯한 조각들이 <br>새롭게 펼쳐질 더 넓을 세상에 <br>또 다른 퍼즐이 널 기다릴 테니 <br>Whatever you are <br>Whatever you are <br>그냥 해보는 거야 <br>남들처럼 똑같다면 재미없어 <br>너의 생각 너의 색을 그려봐 <br>Whatever you are <br>나는 나고 너는 너야 <br>재밌게 살아보자 <br>즐겁게 웃으면서 <br>]]></content><category term="권슬기" label="권슬기"/><category term="Whatever You Are" label="Whatever You Are"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이상순/All_Right_Rock_Ver_Vocal_유하나/</id><title>이상순 - All Right (Rock Ver.) (Vocal 유하나) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:06:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:06:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%81%EC%88%9C/All_Right_Rock_Ver_Vocal_%EC%9C%A0%ED%95%98%EB%82%98/" title="이상순 - All Right (Rock Ver.) (Vocal 유하나) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[길이 없어도 걷고 있다면 <br>All Right All Right <br>쉴 수 없어도 숨 쉴 수 있다면 <br>All Right All Right <br>느낄 수 없어도 알 수 있다면 <br>All Right All Right <br>혼자 있어도 널 생각하면 <br>All Right All Right All Right <br>항상 지친 내 어깨 위로 <br>보이던 세상의 꿈 <br>돌아보면 거짓말처럼 <br>사라져 하지만 <br>너는 내 안에 있어 <br>느낄 수 없어도 알 수 있다면 <br>All Right All Right <br>혼자 있어도 널 생각하면 <br>All Right All Right All Right <br>항상 지친 내 어깨 위로 <br>보이던 세상의 꿈 <br>돌아보면 거짓말처럼 <br>사라져 하지만 항상 <br>돌아보면 거짓말처럼 <br>사라져 하지만 <br>너는 내 안에 있어 <br>모든 게 다 괜찮아 <br>]]></content><category term="이상순" label="이상순"/><category term="All Right (Rock Ver.) (Vocal 유하나)" label="All Right (Rock Ver.) (Vocal 유하나)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이상순/횡단보도_Vocal_지은미/</id><title>이상순 - 횡단보도 (Vocal 지은미) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:06:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:06:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%81%EC%88%9C/%ED%9A%A1%EB%8B%A8%EB%B3%B4%EB%8F%84_Vocal_%EC%A7%80%EC%9D%80%EB%AF%B8/" title="이상순 - 횡단보도 (Vocal 지은미) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[신호등 불빛을 보며 <br>흩날리는 저 꽃잎을 보며 <br>그렇게 생각도 없이 <br>횡단보도에 서지 <br>길 건너 맞은 편에서 <br>흰 치마에 흰 모자의 그녀 <br>그 아름다운 모습이 <br>꼭 천사 같았어 <br>그 횡단보도 위에서 <br>난 온갖 상상을 하지 <br>엇갈리는 운명 아닌 <br>나란히 그 길을 건너는 꿈 <br>결코 건널 수 없던 그 횡단보도 <br>이제는 네가 있어 <br>결코 건널 수 없던 그 빨간 신호 <br>너는 나의 파란 불 <br>결코 건널 수 없던 내 운명의 길 <br>우리 함께 한다면 <br>결코 건널 수 없던 <br>그 횡단보도 이제는 걷는 거야 <br>그 횡단보도 위에서 <br>난 온갖 상상을 하지 <br>엇갈리는 운명 아닌 <br>나란히 그 길을 건너는 꿈 <br>결코 건널 수 없던 그 횡단보도 <br>이제는 네가 있어 <br>결코 건널 수 없던 그 빨간 신호 <br>너는 나의 파란 불 <br>결코 건널 수 없던 내 운명의 길 <br>우리 함께 한다면 <br>결코 건널 수 없던 <br>그 횡단보도 이제는 걷는 거야 <br>결코 건널 수 없던 그 횡단보도 <br>이제는 네가 있어 <br>결코 건널 수 없던 그 빨간 신호 <br>너는 나의 파란 불 <br>결코 건널 수 없던 내 운명의 길 <br>우리 함께 한다면 <br>결코 건널 수 없던 <br>그 횡단보도 이제는 걷는 거야 <br>이제는 걷는 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="이상순" label="이상순"/><category term="횡단보도 (Vocal 지은미)" label="횡단보도 (Vocal 지은미)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이상순/그대에게_젖어_Vocal_유하나/</id><title>이상순 - 그대에게 젖어 (Vocal 유하나) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:07:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:07:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%81%EC%88%9C/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_%EC%A0%96%EC%96%B4_Vocal_%EC%9C%A0%ED%95%98%EB%82%98/" title="이상순 - 그대에게 젖어 (Vocal 유하나) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비가 오네요 <br>그대가 내리네요 <br>내 맘에 곳곳에 <br>고여 있네요 <br>가끔은 폭풍우처럼 <br>가끔은 이슬비처럼 <br>그대가 날 가득 <br>적셔주네요 <br>우산도 소용없어요 <br>처마 밑 피해도 봤죠 <br>하지만 그대를 <br>막을 수 없어요 <br>우비도 소용없네요 <br>귀를 막아도 빗소린 <br>그치지 않죠 <br>정작 하늘은 맑은데 <br>침대에 누워 <br>잠 드려 해봐도 <br>밤새도록 그대 생각에 <br>잠 못 들어요 <br>우리는 친구일 뿐이죠 <br>난 그댈 사랑하지 않죠 <br>오늘도 속이고 <br>또 속여 보네요 <br>우산도 소용없어요 <br>처마 밑 피해도 봤죠 <br>하지만 그대를 <br>막을 수 없어요 <br>우비도 소용없네요 <br>귀를 막아도 빗소린 <br>그치지 않죠 <br>정작 하늘은 맑은데 <br>약을 먹어도 <br>떨림은 멈추질 않아요 <br>사실 난 알아요 <br>아주 오래 전부터 <br>그대에게 젖어 있죠 <br>우산도 소용없어요 <br>처마 밑 피해도 봤죠 <br>하지만 그대를 <br>막을 수 없어요 <br>우비도 소용없네요 <br>귀를 막아도 빗소린 <br>그치지 않죠 <br>정작 하늘은 맑은데 <br>정작 그대는 모르죠 <br>]]></content><category term="이상순" label="이상순"/><category term="그대에게 젖어 (Vocal 유하나)" label="그대에게 젖어 (Vocal 유하나)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이상순/그림자의_노래_Vocal_유하나/</id><title>이상순 - 그림자의 노래 (Vocal 유하나) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:07:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:07:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%81%EC%88%9C/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%BC%EC%9E%90%EC%9D%98_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98_Vocal_%EC%9C%A0%ED%95%98%EB%82%98/" title="이상순 - 그림자의 노래 (Vocal 유하나) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지난 겨울의 해진 저녁의 그 때 <br>어둠 속에서 울기만 했던 우리 <br>점점 내 모습이 <br>더욱 더 사라져만 가요 <br>그댈 생각했던 <br>내 맘은 이런 게 아닌데 <br>아침이 오면 다시 태어나 <br>너란 존재의 그림자 되어 <br>너의 모습을 너의 의미를 <br>모두 다 지켜 줄게요 <br>내가 내가 내가 지켜 줄게요 <br>점점 내 모습이 <br>더욱 더 사라져만 가요 <br>그댈 생각했던 <br>내 맘은 이런 게 아닌데 <br>아침이 오면 다시 태어나 <br>너란 존재의 그림자 되어 <br>너의 모습을 너의 의미를 <br>모두 다 지켜 줄게요 <br>아침이 오면 다시 태어나 <br>너란 존재의 그림자 되어 <br>너의 모습을 너의 의미를 <br>모두 다 지켜 줄게요 <br>내가 내가 내가 지켜 줄게요 <br>내가 내가 내가 지켜 줄게요 <br>]]></content><category term="이상순" label="이상순"/><category term="그림자의 노래 (Vocal 유하나)" label="그림자의 노래 (Vocal 유하나)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이상순/별_Vocal_지은미/</id><title>이상순 - 별 (Vocal 지은미) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:07:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:07:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%81%EC%88%9C/%EB%B3%84_Vocal_%EC%A7%80%EC%9D%80%EB%AF%B8/" title="이상순 - 별 (Vocal 지은미) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[만질 수 없어 닿을 수 없어 <br>세상에 눈 돌려 <br>저 빌딩을 향해 갔었지 뛰었지 <br>깜깜해져서 어둠 속에서 <br>어디로 가는지 <br>아무 불빛도 없는 두려움 속에서 <br>우연히 밤하늘을 올려봤지 <br>빛나는 별들을 따라 은하수 따라 <br>수많은 약속의 꿈을 따라 <br>내 속에 두근거리는 <br>그 목소리 따라 갈 거야 <br>손으로 만질 수 없어 닿을 수 없어 <br>너를 통해 이루어질 꿈들 <br>내 속에 두근거리는 <br>그 약속을 따라 갈 거야 <br>함께 가겠니 <br>만질 수 없어 닿을 수 없어 <br>세상에 눈 돌려 <br>저 빌딩을 향해 갔었지 뛰었지 <br>깜깜해져서 어둠 속에서 <br>어디로 가는지 <br>아무 불빛도 없는 두려움 속에서 <br>우연히 밤하늘을 올려봤지 <br>빛나는 별들을 따라 은하수 따라 <br>수많은 약속의 꿈을 따라 <br>내 속에 두근거리는 <br>그 목소리 따라 갈 거야 <br>손으로 만질 수 없어 닿을 수 없어 <br>너를 통해 이루어질 꿈들 <br>내 속에 두근거리는 <br>그 약속을 따라 갈 거야 <br>함께 가겠니 <br>함께 가겠니 <br>함께 하겠니 <br>함께 하겠니 <br>우연히 밤하늘을 올려봤지 <br>빛나는 별들을 따라 은하수 따라 <br>수많은 약속의 꿈을 따라 <br>내 속에 두근거리는 <br>그 목소리 따라 갈 거야 <br>손으로 만질 수 없어 닿을 수 없어 <br>너를 통해 이루어질 꿈들 <br>내 속에 두근거리는 <br>그 약속을 따라 갈 거야 <br>함께 가겠니 <br>함께 가겠니 <br>]]></content><category term="이상순" label="이상순"/><category term="별 (Vocal 지은미)" label="별 (Vocal 지은미)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이상순/All_Right_Vocal_유하나/</id><title>이상순 - All Right (Vocal 유하나) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:07:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:07:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%81%EC%88%9C/All_Right_Vocal_%EC%9C%A0%ED%95%98%EB%82%98/" title="이상순 - All Right (Vocal 유하나) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[길이 없어도 걷고 있다면 <br>All Right All Right <br>쉴 수 없어도 숨 쉴 수 있다면 <br>All Right All Right <br>느낄 수 없어도 알 수 있다면 <br>All Right All Right <br>혼자 있어도 널 생각하면 <br>All Right All Right All Right <br>항상 지친 내 어깨 위로 <br>보이던 세상의 꿈 <br>돌아보면 거짓말처럼 <br>사라져 하지만 <br>너는 내 안에 있어 <br>모든 게 다 괜찮아 <br>느낄 수 없어도 알 수 있다면 <br>All Right All Right <br>혼자 있어도 널 생각하면 <br>All Right All Right All Right <br>항상 지친 내 어깨 위로 <br>보이던 세상의 꿈 <br>돌아보면 거짓말처럼 <br>사라져 하지만 항상 <br>돌아보면 거짓말처럼 <br>사라져 하지만 <br>너는 내 안에 있어 <br>모든 게 다 괜찮아 <br>]]></content><category term="이상순" label="이상순"/><category term="All Right (Vocal 유하나)" label="All Right (Vocal 유하나)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이상순/천사커피_1호점_Vocal_유하나/</id><title>이상순 - 천사커피 1호점 (Vocal 유하나) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:07:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:07:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%81%EC%88%9C/%EC%B2%9C%EC%82%AC%EC%BB%A4%ED%94%BC_1%ED%98%B8%EC%A0%90_Vocal_%EC%9C%A0%ED%95%98%EB%82%98/" title="이상순 - 천사커피 1호점 (Vocal 유하나) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You are my love angel <br>You are so good my love <br>우연히 길을 걷다가 <br>마주친 그댄 <br>너무 아름다웠어 <br>너는 너무나 눈부셔 <br>옷에서 빛이 <br>나는걸 신기해 <br>그대가 자주 간 카페 <br>어느덧 나도 <br>그 카페 단골 됐네 <br>이제는 말해야겠어 <br>이제는 말하지 <br>않으면 죽겠어 <br>You are my love angel <br>이제는 내가 <br>그대의 천사될게 <br>You are so good my love <br>이제는 내가 <br>그대의 카페인 <br>그 카페는 문을 닫고 <br>그렇게 우리는 <br>만날 수 없었죠 <br>세 번의 겨울 지나고 <br>커피도 자주 <br>찾게 되지 않았죠 <br>그러던 그 해 봄날에 <br>갑자기 느껴진 <br>그 때 그 커피향 <br>그대 내 앞에 있었죠 <br>나도 모르게 <br>그대 손을 잡아요 <br>You are my love angel <br>이제는 내가 <br>그대의 천사될게 <br>You are so good my love <br>이제는 내가 <br>그대의 카페인 <br>You are my love angel <br>나 오직 너만의 <br>바리스타 될게 <br>You are so good my love <br>이제는 내가 <br>그대의 카페인 <br>You are my love angel <br>라라라라라라라라라라라라 <br>You are so good my love <br>라라라라라라라라라 <br>이제는 내가 <br>그대의 천사될게 <br>이제는 내가 <br>그대의 카페인 <br>나 오직 너만의 <br>바리스타 될게 <br>이제는 내가 <br>그대의 카페인 <br>]]></content><category term="이상순" label="이상순"/><category term="천사커피 1호점 (Vocal 유하나)" label="천사커피 1호점 (Vocal 유하나)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이상순/나를_움직이는_사랑_Vocal_지은미/</id><title>이상순 - 나를 움직이는 사랑 (Vocal 지은미) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:07:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:07:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%81%EC%88%9C/%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9B%80%EC%A7%81%EC%9D%B4%EB%8A%94_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_Vocal_%EC%A7%80%EC%9D%80%EB%AF%B8/" title="이상순 - 나를 움직이는 사랑 (Vocal 지은미) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[무얼 해야 하나요 <br>무엇을 더 이뤄야하죠 <br>아직 남았나요 <br>그대 마음에 들기까지 <br>무얼 해야 하나요 <br>무엇을 더 드려야하죠 <br>이젠 지쳤어요 <br>그대 멀리 있네요 <br>미처 몰랐죠 그대 <br>이미 날 사랑한 사실을 <br>누구보다도 나를 더욱 <br>사랑할 수가 없을 만큼 <br>이젠 알아요 그대 <br>이미 날 사랑한 사실을 <br>무엇보다도 나를 <br>움직이는 사랑 <br>무얼 해야 하나요 <br>무엇을 더 이뤄야하죠 <br>아직 남았나요 <br>그대 마음에 들기까지 <br>무얼 해야 하나요 <br>무엇을 더 드려야하죠 <br>이젠 지쳤어요 <br>그대 멀리 있네요 <br>미처 몰랐죠 그대 <br>이미 날 사랑한 사실을 <br>누구보다도 나를 더욱 <br>사랑할 수가 없을 만큼 <br>이젠 알아요 그대 <br>이미 날 사랑한 사실을 <br>무엇보다도 나를 <br>움직이는 사랑 <br>미처 몰랐죠 그대 <br>이미 날 사랑한 사실을 <br>누구보다도 나를 더욱 <br>사랑할 수가 없을 만큼 <br>이젠 알아요 그대 <br>이미 날 사랑한 사실을 <br>무엇보다도 나를 <br>움직이는 사랑 <br>미처 몰랐죠 그대 <br>이미 날 사랑한 사실을 <br>누구보다도 나를 더욱 <br>사랑할 수가 없을 만큼 <br>이젠 알아요 그대 <br>이미 날 사랑한 사실을 <br>무엇보다도 나를 <br>움직이는 사랑 <br>무엇보다도 나를 <br>움직이는 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="이상순" label="이상순"/><category term="나를 움직이는 사랑 (Vocal 지은미)" label="나를 움직이는 사랑 (Vocal 지은미)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이상순/행복_Vocal_황인성_지은미/</id><title>이상순 - 행복 (Vocal 황인성, 지은미) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:07:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:07:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%81%EC%88%9C/%ED%96%89%EB%B3%B5_Vocal_%ED%99%A9%EC%9D%B8%EC%84%B1_%EC%A7%80%EC%9D%80%EB%AF%B8/" title="이상순 - 행복 (Vocal 황인성, 지은미) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오랫동안 미뤄왔던 <br>많은 숙제들과 <br>쌓인 먼지 속에 <br>우리의 약속 <br>지나버린 시간 <br>난 달려갔죠 <br>문을 열고 약속된 <br>그 시간의 그 장소 <br>그리고 그대를 <br>보고 나서야 <br>난 미안했죠 <br>그댄 웃어요 <br>You smile again <br>잠시만 눈을 감고 <br>내 마음에 <br>솔직해지기로 해요 <br>나 그댈 사랑해요 <br>잠시 잊어버렸죠 <br>나란 사람이 미워요 <br>하지만 내 모습에 <br>상관 없이 <br>웃음 짓는 그대의 <br>놀라운 사랑 앞에 <br>난 작아졌죠 <br>그게 행복이죠 <br>Because I love you <br>다가와서 지친 <br>내 맘을 어루만지는 <br>그대의 작은 손 <br>그대의 사랑 <br>멈춰버린 시간 <br>가슴은 뛰죠 <br>행복이란 그런 거죠 <br>부끄럽기 만한 <br>그런 내 모습이 <br>그댈 인하여 <br>다시 용기 내요 <br>그 손 잡아요 <br>You smile again <br>잠시만 눈을 감고 <br>내 마음에 <br>솔직해지기로 해요 <br>나 그댈 사랑해요 <br>잠시 잊어버렸죠 <br>나란 사람이 미워요 <br>하지만 내 모습에 <br>상관 없이 <br>웃음 짓는 그대의 <br>놀라운 사랑 앞에 <br>난 작아졌죠 <br>그게 행복이죠 <br>Because I love you <br>잠시만 눈을 감고 <br>내 마음에 <br>솔직해지기로 해요 <br>나 그댈 사랑해요 <br>잠시 잊어버렸죠 <br>나란 사람이 미워요 <br>하지만 내 모습에 <br>상관 없이 <br>웃음 짓는 그대의 <br>놀라운 사랑 앞에 <br>난 작아졌죠 <br>놀라운 사랑 앞에 <br>난 작아졌죠 <br>놀라운 사랑 앞에 <br>난 작아졌죠 <br>그게 행복이죠 <br>Because I love you <br>]]></content><category term="이상순" label="이상순"/><category term="행복 (Vocal 황인성, 지은미)" label="행복 (Vocal 황인성, 지은미)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이상순/너신소_너의_신발을_만들던_그_소년과_그_소녀_Vocal_지은미/</id><title>이상순 - 너신소 (너의 신발을 만들던 그 소년과 그 소녀) (Vocal 지은미) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:07:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:07:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%81%EC%88%9C/%EB%84%88%EC%8B%A0%EC%86%8C_%EB%84%88%EC%9D%98_%EC%8B%A0%EB%B0%9C%EC%9D%84_%EB%A7%8C%EB%93%A4%EB%8D%98_%EA%B7%B8_%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84%EA%B3%BC_%EA%B7%B8_%EC%86%8C%EB%85%80_Vocal_%EC%A7%80%EC%9D%80%EB%AF%B8/" title="이상순 - 너신소 (너의 신발을 만들던 그 소년과 그 소녀) (Vocal 지은미) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니가 신고 있는 <br>그 신발이 <br>어느 이름모를 나라 <br>어린 아이의 손에 <br>만들어진 건 넌 아는지 <br>지금쯤이면 <br>그 아인 뭘 할까 <br>계속 신발을 <br>만들고 있을까 <br>신발 공장은 더 싼 <br>아이들을 찾아서 떠났지 <br>떠났지 <br>떠났지 <br>니가 신고 있는 <br>그 신발이 <br>너의 신발을 <br>만들던 그 소년은 <br>굶어 죽거나 <br>알콜중독자가 됐겠지 <br>너의 신발을 <br>만들던 그 소녀는 <br>구걸하거나 에이즈에 <br>걸려버렸지 <br>니가 신고 있는 <br>그 신발이 <br>어느 이름모를 나라 <br>어린 아이의 손에 <br>만들어진 건 넌 아는지 <br>지금쯤이면 <br>그 아인 뭘 할까 <br>계속 신발을 <br>만들고 있을까 <br>신발 공장은 <br>더 싼 아이들을 <br>찾아서 떠났지 <br>떠났지 <br>너의 신발을 <br>만들던 그 소년은 <br>굶어 죽거나 <br>알콜중독자가 됐겠지 <br>너의 신발을 <br>만들던 그 소녀는 <br>구걸하거나 에이즈에 <br>걸려버렸지 <br>너의 신발을 만들던 <br>그 소년과 그 소녀 <br>너의 신발을 만들던 <br>그 소녀는 <br>자신을 닮은 어린 <br>아이 곁을 떠났지 <br>니가 신고 있는 <br>그 신발이 <br>]]></content><category term="이상순" label="이상순"/><category term="너신소 (너의 신발을 만들던 그 소년과 그 소녀) (Vocal 지은미)" label="너신소 (너의 신발을 만들던 그 소년과 그 소녀) (Vocal 지은미)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태완_Taewan/Put_Me_Down/</id><title>태완 (Taewan) - Put Me Down - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:07:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:07:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%99%84_Taewan/Put_Me_Down/" title="태완 (Taewan) - Put Me Down - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Words like bullets <br>Pull the trigger <br>We can't let this go <br>on forever <br>Sayin' that our love's through <br>Don't tell me that it don't matter <br>'Cuz everyday and every single <br>night I think only how I can do better <br>You know we can't give up <br>Baby just please come home <br>It's been too many nights <br>I have slept alone <br>Baby pick up the phone <br>Let's just talk this out <br>I think I now know what <br>This is all about <br>Oooo <br>I think you know we can do it better <br>You ain't gotta leave it baby <br>Oooo <br>I think you know we can do it better <br>Is that possible possible <br>Pull me down like this <br>You pull me down like this baby <br>Pull me down like this <br>You pull me down like this baby <br>Pull me down like this <br>You pull me down like this baby <br>Pull me down like this <br>You pull me down <br>Pull pull me down <br>Nobody know me like you do <br>We ride until we die <br>But I can't look into your eyes <br>When all they do is cry <br>We were shot callers baby <br>King and Queen my lady <br>We lost the way <br>Tell me what changed <br>Oooo <br>I think you know we can do it better <br>You ain't gotta leave it baby <br>Oooo <br>I think you know we can do it better <br>Is that possible possible <br>Pull me down like this <br>You pull me down like this baby <br>Pull me down like this <br>You pull me down like this baby <br>Pull me down like this <br>You pull me down like this baby <br>Pull me down like this <br>Pull me down pull me down <br>Hold up <br>Slow it down <br>We can reignite the flame <br>Hold up <br>Slow it down <br>We can turn this back around <br>Oh you <br>Got me <br>Up all night baby <br>Time to come home <br>Time to come home <br>My baby <br>Oh you <br>Got me <br>Up all night baby <br>Up all night <br>Up all night <br>Oooo <br>I think you know we can do it better <br>I said it and I mean it baby <br>Oooo <br>I think you know we can do it better <br>Is that possible possible <br>Pull me down like this <br>You pull me down like this baby <br>Pull me down like this <br>You pull me down like this baby <br>Pull me down like this <br>You pull me down like this baby <br>Pull me down like this <br>You pull me down <br>Pull pull me down <br>]]></content><category term="태완 (Taewan)" label="태완 (Taewan)"/><category term="Put Me Down" label="Put Me Down"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태완_Taewan/필요해/</id><title>태완 (Taewan) - 필요해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:08:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:08:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%99%84_Taewan/%ED%95%84%EC%9A%94%ED%95%B4/" title="태완 (Taewan) - 필요해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Man in the mirror <br>상처로 채워진 <br>내가 더 미워 <br>그 기억은 내 목을 조여 <br>Ooh <br>아무리 씻으려 애를 써도 <br>얼룩은 짙어 <br>그때와 똑같은 표정으로 <br>비웃고 있어 <br>너무 많이 입에 댄 <br>수많은 달콤한 것 <br>돌이킬 수 없는 걸 <br>날 안아줘 <br>깨진 조각처럼 <br>무너진 날 다시 <br>일으켜줘 <br>날 잡아줘 <br>검게 타락해져 <br>버린 날 여기서 <br>구원해줘 <br>니가 필요해 <br>니가 필요해 <br>니가 필요해 <br>여기엔 없어 <br>따뜻한 사랑 따윈 <br>반복해서 말해보고 있어 <br>굳은 내 입술에 붙는 니 이름 <br>다시 너를 만지고 <br>또 너를 볼 수 있다면 <br>날 안아줘 <br>깨진 조각처럼 <br>무너진 날 다시 <br>일으켜줘 <br>날 잡아줘 <br>검게 타락해져 <br>버린 날 여기서 <br>구원해줘 <br>니가 필요해 <br>니가 필요해 <br>니가 필요해 <br>니가 필요해 <br>니가 필요해 <br>정말 니가 필요해 <br>날 여기 혼자 두지 말아줘 <br>난 부서져 <br>부서지고 있는 걸 <br>나를 안아줘 <br>깨진 조각처럼 <br>무너진 날 다시 <br>일으켜줘 <br>다시 잡아줘 <br>검게 타락해져 <br>버린 날 여기서 <br>구원해줘 <br>니가 필요해 <br>니가 필요해 <br>니가 필요해 <br>니가 필요해 <br>니가 필요해 <br>니가 필요해 <br>]]></content><category term="태완 (Taewan)" label="태완 (Taewan)"/><category term="필요해" label="필요해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Earthists/Resonating_Light/</id><title>Earthists. - Resonating Light - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:08:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:08:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Earthists/Resonating_Light/" title="Earthists. - Resonating Light - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not unconscious <br>But I can't take the first step <br>Every time I look ahead <br>I feel like I'm paralyzed <br>I would be saved If could say them loud <br>These words I can't seem to utter <br><br>If I wouldn't get out of this room <br>Would I and my surroundings forever stay the same <br>I thought it was extrication from this world <br><br>I close my eyes and hold my breath <br>I feel our heartbeats <br>I breathe out and slowly open my eyes <br>I wanna be with you <br>Let's slowly move forward while seeking the meaning of life <br>Let's not forget the panorama we saw together <br><br>I close my eyes and hold my breath <br>I feel our heartbeats <br>I breathe out and slowly open my eyes <br>Let's not forget the panorama we saw together]]></content><category term="Earthists." label="Earthists."/><category term="Resonating Light" label="Resonating Light"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이유나/바보처럼/</id><title>이유나 - 바보처럼 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:09:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:09:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%9C%A0%EB%82%98/%EB%B0%94%EB%B3%B4%EC%B2%98%EB%9F%BC/" title="이유나 - 바보처럼 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 곁에만 그대 <br>머물러줘요 <br>내가 멀어진대도 <br>날 사랑해주던 <br>날 보고웃어주던 <br>그때처럼 날 안아줘요 <br>바보처럼 정말 <br>사랑했는데 <br>그댄 나를보면 <br>피하기만 하네요 <br>한번만 더 그댈 <br>보고싶어서 <br>하루종일 그댈 <br>기다리는 나 <br>정말 한심하죠 <br>조금만 더 내게 <br>시간을 줘요 <br>아직 나의 맘속엔 <br>날 사랑해주던 <br>날 보고 웃어주던 <br>미소가 아른거려요 <br>바보처럼 정말 <br>사랑했는데 <br>그댄 나를보면 <br>피하기만 하네요 <br>한번만 더 그댈 <br>보고싶어서 <br>하루종일 그댈 <br>기다리는 나 <br>정말 한심하죠 <br>1년이면 그댈 <br>잊을 수 있나요 <br>10년이 지나도 <br>여전할 것 같아 <br>멀리 떠나가면 <br>잊을 수 있나요 <br>그래도 아무 소용 없겠죠 <br>바보처럼 정말 <br>사랑했는데 <br>그댄 나를보면 <br>피하기만 하네요 <br>한번만 더 그댈 <br>보고싶어서 <br>하루종일 그댈 <br>기다리는 나 <br>정말 한심하죠 <br>]]></content><category term="이유나" label="이유나"/><category term="바보처럼" label="바보처럼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Delvs/Come_My_Way/</id><title>Delv!s - Come My Way - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:09:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:09:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Delvs/Come_My_Way/" title="Delv!s - Come My Way - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know I want it <br>Nothing real will come my way <br>Oooh baby <br><br>I know it's coming <br>But nothing real will come today <br>I don't need it <br>And it feels like its eternal <br>Nothing's gonna come my way <br>Yeah I know it will <br>And it feels like I am burning <br>Slowly I will fade away <br>Yes I know I will <br><br>I'm on it <br>I want it <br>Feels like I'm the only one who wants it <br>I need it bad right now <br>I'm on it <br>I want it <br>Feels like I'm the only one who wants it <br>I need it bad right now <br><br>I know I've got it <br>Nothing really seems to stay <br>Oooh baby <br>I know I love it <br>I'm dancing 'til the end of days <br>I really need it <br><br>I'm on it <br>I want it <br>Feels like I'm the only one who wants it <br>I need it bad right now <br>I'm on it <br>I want it <br>Feels like I'm the only one who wants it <br>I need it bad right now <br><br>So tonight I'm gonna try to break the chain <br>Baby another story to fill up my pain <br>Baby another hit to blow until the fire burns it down <br>So tonight I will try not to hit the ground <br>It's all coming back to me <br><br>I know I'm on it <br>Nothing going on today <br>Oooh baby <br>I keep on talking <br>Nothing real is left to say <br>I'm not needed <br>And it feels like it's eternal <br>Nothing's gonna come my way <br>Yeah I know it will <br>And it feels like I am burning <br>Slowly I will fade away <br>Yes I know I will <br><br>I'm on it <br>I want it <br>Feels like I'm the only one who wants it <br>I need it bad right now <br>I'm on it <br>I want it <br>Feels like I'm the only one who wants it <br>I need it bad right now <br><br>So tonight I'm gonna try to break the chain <br>Baby another story to fill up my pain <br>Baby another hit to blow until the fire burns it down <br>So tonight I will try not to hit the ground <br>It's all coming back to me]]></content><category term="Delv!s" label="Delv!s"/><category term="Come My Way" label="Come My Way"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이즐/사랑해_안녕_Inst/</id><title>헤이즐 - 사랑해 안녕 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:09:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:09:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EC%A6%90/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4_%EC%95%88%EB%85%95_Inst/" title="헤이즐 - 사랑해 안녕 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[처음부터 너를 <br>없던 것처럼 <br>내 가슴 도려내도 <br>니 목소리 들려와 <br>애써 눈물 지며 <br>모른척해도 <br>여전히 사랑인걸 <br>스쳐가도 알기에 <br>이 아픔 내가 <br>견딜게 언제나 <br>누구보다 사랑했단 걸 <br>지우지도 못해 <br>괜찮아 사랑보다 <br>더 널 아낄께 <br>멀리서 널 보는게 <br>다 겠지만 <br>닿을 거리라 해도 <br>흔한 인사조차도 <br>못하나봐 <br>너를 사랑해 안녕 <br>Time To Say Good bye <br>그날처럼 돌아 선 <br>너의 모습 <br>멍하니 바라보며 <br>믿고 싶지 않았어 <br>무슨 말이라도 <br>내게 했다면 <br>아픔도 추억하며 <br>눈물로 널 잊겠지 <br>이 아픔 내가 <br>견딜게 언제나 <br>누구보다 사랑했단 걸 <br>지우지도 못해 <br>괜찮아 사랑보다 <br>더 널 아낄께 <br>멀리서 널 보는게 <br>다 겠지만 <br>닿을 거리라 해도 <br>흔한 인사조차도 못하나봐 <br>너를 사랑해 안녕 <br>이젠 지우려 해도 <br>한없이 너만 보여 <br>목놓아 울어보아도 사랑해 <br>아려와 너무 아파도 <br>난 버틸께 <br>우연히 널 보아도 <br>나 잊을께 <br>하루하루 그리워 <br>살아갈 수 있을까 <br>바보처럼 <br>마지막인걸 안녕 <br>Time To Say Good bye <br>Time To Say Good bye <br>]]></content><category term="헤이즐" label="헤이즐"/><category term="사랑해 안녕 (Inst.)" label="사랑해 안녕 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이즐/사랑해_안녕/</id><title>헤이즐 - 사랑해 안녕 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:09:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:09:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EC%A6%90/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4_%EC%95%88%EB%85%95/" title="헤이즐 - 사랑해 안녕 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[처음부터 너를 <br>없던 것처럼 <br>내 가슴 도려내도 <br>니 목소리 들려와 <br>애써 눈물 지며 <br>모른척해도 <br>여전히 사랑인걸 <br>스쳐가도 알기에 <br>이 아픔 내가 <br>견딜게 언제나 <br>누구보다 사랑했단 걸 <br>지우지도 못해 <br>괜찮아 사랑보다 <br>더 널 아낄께 <br>멀리서 널 보는게 <br>다 겠지만 <br>닿을 거리라 해도 <br>흔한 인사조차도 <br>못하나봐 <br>너를 사랑해 안녕 <br>Time To Say Good bye <br>그날처럼 돌아 선 <br>너의 모습 <br>멍하니 바라보며 <br>믿고 싶지 않았어 <br>무슨 말이라도 <br>내게 했다면 <br>아픔도 추억하며 <br>눈물로 널 잊겠지 <br>이 아픔 내가 <br>견딜게 언제나 <br>누구보다 사랑했단 걸 <br>지우지도 못해 <br>괜찮아 사랑보다 <br>더 널 아낄께 <br>멀리서 널 보는게 <br>다 겠지만 <br>닿을 거리라 해도 <br>흔한 인사조차도 못하나봐 <br>너를 사랑해 안녕 <br>이젠 지우려 해도 <br>한없이 너만 보여 <br>목놓아 울어보아도 사랑해 <br>아려와 너무 아파도 <br>난 버틸께 <br>우연히 널 보아도 <br>나 잊을께 <br>하루하루 그리워 <br>살아갈 수 있을까 <br>바보처럼 <br>마지막인걸 안녕 <br>Time To Say Good bye <br>Time To Say Good bye <br>]]></content><category term="헤이즐" label="헤이즐"/><category term="사랑해 안녕" label="사랑해 안녕"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Adolphson__Falk/Just_A_Machine/</id><title>Adolphson &amp; Falk - Just A Machine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:10:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:10:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Adolphson__Falk/Just_A_Machine/" title="Adolphson &amp; Falk - Just A Machine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was built by Mr Jones <br>And he's an awfully clever man <br>He's regarded as the foremost in his field <br>His command of all God's science <br>Is renowned throughout the land <br>My existence is his craftmanship revealed <br>He has etched my nerves of silicon <br>And stitched my nylon skin <br>Designed my megabrain <br>And all the thoughts within <br>With unsurpassed precision <br>I've been put through every test <br>And charged with the mortal gift of life <br>I was made with such perfection <br>I am complete in every way <br>I'm guaranteed to never ever fail <br>I simply can not falter <br>As humans often do <br>Like the men who start me up and turn me off <br>I find it very frightening <br>The disorder of their plans <br>And I wonder at the use that's made <br>With the info they demand <br>But I have no right to question <br>The decisions which they make <br>My fate is not to reason why <br>I'm just a machine <br>I'm just a machine <br>They speak with all respect of Mr Jones <br>Despite all my perfection <br>I can never intervene <br>I'm just a machine <br>I'm just a machine]]></content><category term="Adolphson &amp; Falk" label="Adolphson &amp; Falk"/><category term="Just A Machine" label="Just A Machine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Adolphson__Falk/They_Put_My_Baby_On_The_Air/</id><title>Adolphson &amp; Falk - They Put My Baby On The Air - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:10:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:10:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Adolphson__Falk/They_Put_My_Baby_On_The_Air/" title="Adolphson &amp; Falk - They Put My Baby On The Air - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I hear your voice from the place next door <br>They tune you in more and more <br>Wherever I go I can't get away <br>When they broadcast every word you say <br>Oh no, not that station <br>Hey man, please turn it off <br>How can they do this to me <br>They got my baby on the air <br>They say your show is a lot of fun <br>They say that girl is a number one <br>But they don't know what you did to me <br>And they can't see my misery <br>Oh no, not that station <br>Hey man, please turn it off <br>How can they do this to me <br>They got my baby on the air <br>You broke my heart <br>Now you're rubbin' it in <br>Telling our secrets <br>To any dumb fool who calls in <br>You wrecked our lives <br>And you knocked me right down <br>Now you're making it public <br>And spreading it all over town <br>You're talking hip like you know where it's at <br>You tell them love is as easy as that <br>They're calling in to get your advice <br>They like to hear you 'cause they think you're so wise <br>Oh no, not that station <br>Hey man, please turn it off <br>How can they do this to me <br>They got my baby on the air <br>They put my baby on the air]]></content><category term="Adolphson &amp; Falk" label="Adolphson &amp; Falk"/><category term="They Put My Baby On The Air" label="They Put My Baby On The Air"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Woods/Dangerous/</id><title>Roy Woods - Dangerous - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:11:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:11:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Woods/Dangerous/" title="Roy Woods - Dangerous - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Whoa, whoa, whoa <br>Whoa <br><br>Can I hang with you I'm just tryna hang with you <br>When I get low you turn me up <br>Together we're dangerous, well uh <br>Can I hang with you I'm just tryna hang with you <br>When I get low you turn me up <br>Together we're dangerous <br><br>You light the pole to get me stuck, tell me who's more dangerous <br>Like Busta Rhymes so dangerous <br>Bad lil mama come hang with us <br>I know, what you came in for, it's not to be on your own out here <br>And there's friends with you, I got friends but don't <br><br>I'm addicted to you listening to me <br>In the clubs that you trick to me <br>Better keep up the pace with me, la, da, de, da, da <br>We get that breath of ecstasy <br>I'm so icy, water drip off me <br>You're my type of person, indeed <br>Can you sip Hennessy when you're with me <br><br>First off, I want no lies, open up <br>I'm addicted, I'm addicted <br>We both said we won't fall in love <br>We're both addicted, we're both addicted <br><br>Can I hang with you I'm just tryna hang with you <br>When I get low you turn me up <br>Together we're dangerous, well uh <br>Can I hang with you I'm just tryna hang with you <br>When I get low you turn me up <br>Together we're dangerous <br><br>Ooh, push down on the pedal to start my love, yeah, yeah <br>I get higher on you without the drugs, yeah, yeah <br>No time's wasted if I spend time with you, yeah, yeah <br>I'm pulling up now, baby <br>Don't you have what I want Got weed, ain't love <br>Bring my body to the floor, turn me up a lil more <br>Oh, girl, we got it going on, got it moving on <br>Make me leave your body strong <br>Hide you went on my life, I lost friends on the highway <br>Can I stay 'til the light <br>Nocturnal every night, can you spend nights by my side <br>Let's get lost on the light, I want to splash your water <br>Pull out my arms, I got you, I follow my arms <br><br>First off, I want no lies, open up <br>I'm addicted, I'm addicted <br>We both said we won't fall in love <br>We're both addicted, we're both addicted <br><br>Can I hang with you I'm just tryna hang with you <br>When I get low you turn me up <br>Together we're dangerous, well uh <br>Can I hang with you I'm just tryna hang with you <br>When I get low you turn me up <br>Together we're dangerous <br>Together we're dangerous <br>Yeah, turn me up, yeah <br>Together we're dangerous <br>Yeah, turn me up, yeah <br>Together we're dangerous]]></content><category term="Roy Woods" label="Roy Woods"/><category term="Dangerous" label="Dangerous"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Woods/Love_You/</id><title>Roy Woods - Love You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:11:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:11:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Woods/Love_You/" title="Roy Woods - Love You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love you <br>Love you <br>Love you <br>Love you <br>Love you <br><br>I was only tryin' to love you <br>I was only tryin' to love you <br>I was only tryin' to love you <br>Love you <br>I was only tryin' to love you <br>I was only tryin' to love you <br><br>Miss days of her laughter <br>But I've turned another chapter <br>In the 6 with my Raptors <br>Went ghost, now you calling me Caspar <br>Could it be, that it's not serious to me <br>I stay with these <br>Cause it hurt me way more to leave <br>Cutting ties after hot sex in the bathroom <br>Now that we're over I won't look at you <br>Feelings in my stomach like it's high school <br>I know there are other niggas looking at you <br>But you can't diss me on my set <br>You cuss me by my text <br>Said it received, but not read <br>20 minutes later a paragraph or two <br><br>I was only tryin' to love you <br>I was only tryin' to love you <br>I was only tryin' to love you <br>Love you <br>I was only tryin' to love you <br>I was only tryin' to love you <br><br>Naked <br>Does he make love while you're naked <br>Do you never let him taste it <br>Does he fuck you like he loves you <br>Treat you good like a man should <br>Does he bathe in the shower for you <br>Does he do the things that I do <br>Does he tell you that I want you <br>I know how much I really love you <br>I can't s put no one above you <br>I'm a lover man for you <br>You the down girl for me <br>Rolling blunts on your roof <br>Let my ex know about you <br>She can't do things you do <br>Inside and on the room <br>You're the only one that knew that <br><br>I was only tryin' to love you <br>I was only tryin' to love you <br>I was only tryin' to love you <br>Love you <br>I was only tryin' to love you <br>I was only tryin' to love you <br>I was only tryin' to love you <br>Love you <br>I was only tryin' to love you <br>And you knew that I wanna love you <br>Love you <br>Love you <br>Love you <br>Love you]]></content><category term="Roy Woods" label="Roy Woods"/><category term="Love You" label="Love You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Woods/Instinct_Feat_MadeinTYO/</id><title>Roy Woods - Instinct (Feat. MadeinTYO) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:11:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:11:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Woods/Instinct_Feat_MadeinTYO/" title="Roy Woods - Instinct (Feat. MadeinTYO) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Brown skin's all fine <br>Puerto Rican offline, Cuban shorty all fine <br>Get your badass with me no left goin' sixteen <br>Same bag in the trunk <br>Bitches switch ways now her nigga got it in the trunk <br>I was for her when you were ready to give her up <br>I was on it, makin' missions just to pick her up <br>Floppin', never showing up, she she did religiously <br>I can't trust a nigga or I treat the friends my enemy <br>You ain't got sauce like I got sauce No <br>Bitch I got juice, quench your thirst with Ciroc <br>All the baddies on top don't know what I got <br>No boy, no man could handle my spot <br>Think you know right, but I'm changin' a lot <br>Can't be no Ma, who you knew from the block <br>Wait until you got it then your loss <br><br>With my instinct <br>Just following my instinct <br>Just know that I stay in sync <br>Never wrong, anyting or anyting in the South <br><br>I'm just following my instinct <br>Just following my instinct <br>Just know that I stay in sync <br>Never wrong, anyting or anyting in the Southside <br>Following my <br><br>Hit me up when you get this <br>Talk to you girl cause you listen Hey <br>I still love you when you're bitchin' <br>She bite her lips when Tokyo switch positions <br>You ain't gotta call the Uber when you're with me Skrt <br>She say she miss her Mother, yeah she from Philly <br>Rocks in your ear, you know I'm wavy Skrt, skrt <br>Yeah, I'm just following my instincts Ooh <br>Yellow stones like I'm simpsons <br>I'm just following my instincts Hey <br>Yea I'm ballin' like a Piston Ooh <br>Tell me what you wanna do <br>Yeah, I'm just following my instincts Hey <br>Tell me what you wanna do <br>Yea I'm in the Six, baby coming' through <br><br>With my instinct <br>Just following my instinct <br>Just know that I stay in sync <br>Never wrong, anyting or anyting in the South <br><br>I'm just following my instinct <br>Just following my instinct <br>Just know that I stay in sync <br>Never wrong, anyting or anyting in the Southside <br>Following my]]></content><category term="Roy Woods" label="Roy Woods"/><category term="Instinct (Feat. MadeinTYO)" label="Instinct (Feat. MadeinTYO)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Woods/Involved/</id><title>Roy Woods - Involved - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:11:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:11:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Woods/Involved/" title="Roy Woods - Involved - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ah ah ah ah ah <br>Ah ah aah ah yeah <br><br>I walked into the club <br>Popped a few bottles with my bruhs <br>It ain't ever less, no fuck niggas rolling with me <br>Can't trust some niggas in the beez <br>Acting all nice in ya face, but it's what you don't see <br>The snake, that's never in me <br>Backwoods rolled right before I touch road <br>And already shawty got money like in the telly <br>And <br><br>I just bought a nice lil' thing for my momma not a hoe <br>Pull up in a Range all black she love my coat <br>Cold as ice cream when you come into the North <br>She screams for me cause the buddy is tearing up her walls <br><br>And when she wants the booty call <br>She gon' send an Uber to my place <br>I got kush smoke a lot girl <br>Do you wanna get involved with me <br>And when she wants the booty call <br>She gon' send an Uber to my place <br>I got kush smoke a lot girl <br>Do you wanna get involved with me <br>Do you wanna get involved with me <br>Do you wanna get involved with me <br><br>I got a lot of big things to do <br>My lil' shorty on to me <br>I need to make sure of the reasons she hot wants for me <br>If you gettin' do with me shorty show some loyalty <br>I don't really need these problems anymore nah, nah <br>Been going through this too long now and ma a <br>Too long for her now <br>Who else gon' treat you like a queen You don't know <br>Presto <br>She stop at the <br>When you want a re fill, you know where the cup <br>Hit her with a right stroke, hit her with a left stroke <br>And make your pum pum cum cum all over me <br><br>And when she wants the booty call <br>She gon' send an Uber to my place <br>I got kush smoke a lot girl <br>Do you wanna get involved with me <br>And when she wants the booty call <br>She gon' send an Uber to my place <br>I got kush smoke a lot girl <br>Do you wanna get involved with me <br>Do you wanna get involved with me <br>Do you wanna get involved with me <br><br>I just bought a nice lil' thing for my momma not a hoe <br>Pull up in a Range all black she love my coat <br>Cold as ice cream when you come into the North <br>She screams for me cause the buddy is tearing up her walls <br>Bought a nice lil' thing for my momma not a hoe <br>Pull up in a Range all black she love my coat <br>Cold as ice cream when you come into the North <br>She screams for me cause the buddy is tearing up her walls <br>Tearing up her walls <br>Tearing up her walls <br>I just bought a nice lil' thing for my momma not a hoe <br>Come into the North]]></content><category term="Roy Woods" label="Roy Woods"/><category term="Involved" label="Involved"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Woods/Chilli_Peppers_Feat_Majid_Jordan/</id><title>Roy Woods - Chilli Peppers (Feat. Majid Jordan) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:11:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:11:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Woods/Chilli_Peppers_Feat_Majid_Jordan/" title="Roy Woods - Chilli Peppers (Feat. Majid Jordan) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oooh <br>Mister Woods Mali Maj <br>Woah she knows I'm bad <br>I like her though <br>I like her though <br>She's kinda cute <br>not kinda though <br>not kinda though <br>Move it a little bit <br>body is too fit <br>oh me oh my <br>Shawty been too fine <br>I can tell she makes 'em whine <br>you don't want that's all you know <br>Go deeper in you <br>I want what your heart <br>knows is there <br>Get me throwed <br>since I'm down <br>I'll get you good <br>Can't feel for sure <br>thought this life could let me know <br>She's down for the low <br>she'll keep it lowkey <br>she'll keep it lowkey <br>She's down for the low <br>she'll keep it lowkey <br>she'll keep it lowkey <br>She's down for the low <br>she'll keep it lowkey <br>she'll keep it lowkey <br>She's down for the low <br>she'll keep it lowkey <br>She's hot as red hot chili peppers <br>hot hot hot <br>Going on a Californiacation <br>She's hot as red hot chili peppers <br>hot hot hot <br>Going on a Californiacation <br>She's hot as red hot chili peppers <br>hot hot hot <br>Going on a Californiacation <br>She's hot as red hot chili peppers <br>hot hot hot <br>Going on a Californiacation <br>Oh oh oh <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Up 'til four yesterday <br>yes-yesterday <br>You don't know where I been <br>where I been <br>Take it slow <br>this is just another <br>late night episode <br>This is just another <br>late night episode <br>Maybe I should go <br>a little more slow <br>I'm impatient at best that's all <br>I know-ow <br>Baby it sounds like <br>you are on a Californiacation <br>She's hot as red hot chili peppers <br>hot <br>Going on a Californiacation <br>She's hot as red hot chili peppers <br>hot <br>Going on a Californiacation <br>She's hot as red hot chili peppers <br>hot <br>Going on a Californiacation <br>Oh oh oh <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>]]></content><category term="Roy Woods" label="Roy Woods"/><category term="Chilli Peppers (Feat. Majid Jordan)" label="Chilli Peppers (Feat. Majid Jordan)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Woods/Four_Seasons/</id><title>Roy Woods - Four Seasons - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:11:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:11:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Woods/Four_Seasons/" title="Roy Woods - Four Seasons - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I made it out the city quick <br>Mom finally proud of me <br>Mom finally proud of me <br>My friends are not my friends no more <br>My friends are not my friends no more <br>I'm twenty and that's how I gotta go <br>I'm twenty and that's how I gotta go <br>Barry Sanders with the pick and I sing when I feel it <br>Went to Toronto and began to fuck with the realest <br>Went to Toronto and began to fuck with the realest <br>Oh so you listen to me if you hear music <br>Eeny, meeny, miny, moe, I'm choosin' all these foreigns <br>Get my mom in a foreign, skrrt, skrrt <br>Get my dad a new car, get my sister some money <br>'Cause they always there for me, can not forget it <br>I would not have known it, more than dollars when I show it <br>Don't you ever try my lady, i pull up faster than police <br>You'll get a and know this <br>Our side was the focus for the scene but don't look like it <br>I done came up on the Southside Southside <br>Do it for my moms and my family, I was more than football signed <br>Singing 'fore 'bout four, three years, what was it for Only now I know why <br><br>Don't you be fake with me <br>You can be honest with me <br>Who could relate to me <br>Don't go near me like it's Vegas <br>Man this life ain't no vacation <br>Don't you be fake with me <br>You can be honest with me <br>Who could relate to me <br>Don't go near me like it's Vegas <br>Man this life ain't no vacation <br><br>Back then I was on my own, little home studio <br>Ain't no shawty called, don't know why I had this phone <br>Couldn't, still can't keep a girl, light the blunt I roll <br>What It ease my mind, way more than you <br>I'm, I'm, I'm on my own, partying next door <br>Brought a couple girls, she told her friends to roll <br>Trees up, with you it was, backwoods to the dome <br>You just have to answer, so I'm not alone <br>You the realest one that I met since <br>Hope you don't get tired, I'm here like a marathon <br>When we fuckin', best enjoy yourself before they lose it all <br>When it buckin', choose your weapon, be like left Ontario <br><br>Don't you be fake with me <br>Don't you be fake with me <br>You can be honest with me <br>You could be on this brigade <br>Who could relate to me <br>Don't go near me like it's Vegas <br>Man this life ain't no vacation <br>Don't you be fake with me <br>Don't you be fake with me <br>You can be honest with me <br>You could be on this brigade <br>Who could relate to me <br>Don't go near me like it's Vegas <br>Man this life ain't no vacation]]></content><category term="Roy Woods" label="Roy Woods"/><category term="Four Seasons" label="Four Seasons"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Woods/Magic/</id><title>Roy Woods - Magic - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:11:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:11:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Woods/Magic/" title="Roy Woods - Magic - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[OVO, UTU <br>OVO, UTU <br>OVO, UTU <br><br>Oh, wake up, I'ma get up later when I want, touch snooze <br>Pack heat then I turn up blunt in the room <br>Shawty calls but I'm not answerin' calls <br>I don't throw money, those panties still fall droppin', droppin' <br>Gettin' down with a lil' thing from the North Northside <br>Southside got 'em all down where they want sure nigga <br>Sippin' white Gin for the night and the cars yeah, yeah <br>We can fuck though I got pain in my heart <br><br>Knock knock boy, is you ready Is you ready <br>From the top dropped down with your lady skrr, skrr, hey <br>Hit the club, skrr'ting off from the lames skrrt'ing off <br>I need a who will throw it from the B's <br>I'm gettin' down with a shawty like me <br>And it's benign to a yella like me <br>I been movin' alright <br>Why ask You ain't transform me <br><br>You can get mad that I made it <br>You ain't know the work I put in <br>Check my profile and they hit me <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>You can get mad that I made it <br>You ain't know the work I put in <br>Check my profile and they hit me <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>I be makin' magic on the daily <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>I be makin' magic on the daily <br>I been doing me on the <br><br>You think you know me From what nigga <br>I know how to start up from nothin' start up from the bottom <br>Basement days now we up mama we up mama <br>I ain't just sippin' on nothin' <br>Niggas out there like to front, uh <br>I do what I say when I'm ready <br>You check my steez, do me at ease <br><br>Knock knock boy, is you ready Is you ready <br>From the top dropped down with your lady skrr, skrr, hey <br>Hit the club, skrr'ting off from the lames skrrt'ing off <br>I need a who will throw it from the B's <br>I'm gettin' down with a shawty like me <br>And it's benign to a yella like me <br>I been movin' alright <br>Why ask You ain't transform me <br><br>You can get mad that I made it <br>You ain't know the work I put in <br>Check my profile and they hit me <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>You can get mad that I made it <br>You ain't know the work I put in <br>Check my profile and they hit me <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>I be makin' magic on the daily <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>I been doing me on the daily <br>I be makin' magic on the daily <br>I been doing me on the <br><br>Yeah, yeah <br>I been doing me <br>Do you shawty <br>'Cause I been doing me <br>Yeah, aw yeah, aw yeah <br>Ye ah ha ha ha <br>Ye ah ha ha ha <br>Ye ah ha ha ha <br>Oh oh yeah ha <br>Ye ah ha ha ha]]></content><category term="Roy Woods" label="Roy Woods"/><category term="Magic" label="Magic"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이상번/청춘인생/</id><title>이상번 - 청춘인생 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:12:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:12:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%81%EB%B2%88/%EC%B2%AD%EC%B6%98%EC%9D%B8%EC%83%9D/" title="이상번 - 청춘인생 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1절 <br>사랑도 주고 사랑도 받고 <br>그게 바로 인생길이라 <br>마음비우고 욕심버리고 <br>그것 또한 인생길이라 <br>사랑아 인생아 <br>한세상을 웃고 웃었지 <br>바람아 구름아 <br>저 세월을 원망도 했지 <br>친구만나면 술한잔 사고 <br>노래하고 춤도춰보게 <br>어제도 청춘 오늘도 청춘 <br>우린바로 청춘인생 <br>2절 <br>사랑도 있고 <br>이별도 있고 <br>그것또한 인생길이라 <br>피고 또 피고 <br>지고 또 피고 <br>그것 또한 인생길이라 <br>사랑아 인생아 <br>내 가는길 막지를 마라 <br>미자야 옥자야 <br>이 오빠가 행차 마신다 <br>울지를 마라 <br>우지를 마라 <br>울어본들 소용있겠니 <br>예쁜 옷 입고 여행도 가고 <br>우린바로 청춘인생 <br>우린 바로 청춘이라네 <br>청춘인생]]></content><category term="이상번" label="이상번"/><category term="청춘인생" label="청춘인생"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엄소영/보고_싶어요/</id><title>엄소영 - 보고 싶어요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:12:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:12:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%84%EC%86%8C%EC%98%81/%EB%B3%B4%EA%B3%A0_%EC%8B%B6%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="엄소영 - 보고 싶어요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[시간이 지나면 <br>잊혀진다고 <br>그렇게 믿었죠 <br>그렇게 생각했죠 <br>몇번 울고나면 <br>괜찮아진다고 <br>바보 같이 항상 <br>아픈 맘을 숨겨왔죠 <br>그댈 지우고 또 지우려 <br>종일 울어봐도 <br>우리 함께 웃던 사진만 <br>또 되돌아봐요 <br>오늘도 그대가 <br>너무 보고싶어요 <br>나 혼자 <br>그대 없는 기억에 <br>머물러있어요 <br>아직도 그대가 <br>조금 남았나봐요 <br>이렇게 아파하고 있는데 <br>돌아와줄 순 없나요 <br>다른 사람 만나 <br>행복하라고 <br>그렇게 말했죠 <br>그렇게 떠나갔죠 <br>혼자 남겨져도 <br>괜찮을거라고 <br>웃을 수 있다고 <br>아픈 맘을 속여왔죠 <br>그댈 지우고 또 지우려 <br>종일 걸어봐도 <br>우리 함께 걷던 거리만 <br>또 되돌아와요 <br>오늘도 그대가 <br>너무 보고싶어요 <br>나 혼자 그대 없는 기억에 <br>머물러있어요 <br>아직도 그대가 <br>조금 남았나봐요 <br>이렇게 아파하고 있는데 <br>돌아와줄 순 없나요 <br>그대 가끔 내가 <br>보고싶나요 <br>그대도 그리움에 <br>혼자 운적있나요 <br>우리 혹시 마주친다면 <br>다시 볼 수 있다면 <br>나를 떠나지 못하게 <br>붙잡을텐데 <br>오늘도 그대가 <br>너무 보고싶어요 <br>나 혼자 그대 없는 기억에 <br>머물러있어요 <br>아직도 그대가 <br>조금 남았나봐요 <br>이렇게 아파하고 있는데 <br>돌아와줄 순 없나요 <br>]]></content><category term="엄소영" label="엄소영"/><category term="보고 싶어요" label="보고 싶어요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/빈챈현스_다이아/너는_달_지구/</id><title>빈챈현스 (다이아) - 너는 달 지구 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:12:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:12:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%88%EC%B1%88%ED%98%84%EC%8A%A4_%EB%8B%A4%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%84/%EB%84%88%EB%8A%94_%EB%8B%AC_%EC%A7%80%EA%B5%AC/" title="빈챈현스 (다이아) - 너는 달 지구 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[돌아서면 그래 <br>내가 생각하는 건 <br>너와 나의 거릴 <br>또 체크하는 거 <br>오늘은 얼마나 <br>또 멀어지나 봐 <br>너와 걷던 거리 추억은 <br>부서져만 가 <br>Lost without you <br>If I never know that <br>This love without you <br>너 없이 괜찮다는 생각은 <br>얼마 못 가 무너지는 착각 <br>그 안에 갇혀버린 건 나 혼자 <br>넌 달 난 지구 <br>마치 평행선 <br>마주보고 걸어봐도 <br>나의 건너편 <br>바라보긴 해도 <br>네 손 잡지 못해 <br>너에게 닿지 못해 <br>그저 바라보며 걷네 <br>보고 싶어 이 한마디를 <br>너에게 말하지 못해 난 <br>아프게 웃고 있을 너니까 <br>돌아와줘 이 한마디를 <br>너에게 말할 수 없어 난 <br>이별을 말한 건 나니까 <br>나 혼자 쓸쓸히 <br>걷긴 해도 지금 <br>날 따라 걷는 너는 <br>달이고 지구 <br>뒤돌아 걷는 너도 <br>나와 같을까 <br>나와 같길 바란다면 <br>그건 욕심인 걸까 <br>뒤돌아봐 따라 <br>걷는 날 좀 봐 <br>손 잡진 못해도 <br>그저 바라보잖아 <br>네 손을 밀어냈던 건 나야 <br>그래 바보같이 후회하는 나야 <br>외면할 수 없던 기억들 <br>오늘은 어떤 하루였는지 <br>이런 내 맘이 네게 닿아도 <br>모른 척 해 <br>넌 달 난 지구 <br>마치 평행선 <br>마주보고 걸어봐도 <br>나의 건너편 <br>바라보긴 해도 <br>네 손 잡지 못해 <br>너에게 닿지 못해 <br>그저 바라보며 걷네 <br>보고 싶어 이 한마디를 <br>너에게 말 하지 못해 난 <br>아프게 웃고 있을 너니까 <br>돌아와줘 이 한마디를 <br>너에게 말할 수 없어 난 <br>이별을 말한 건 나니까 <br>그냥 나 바보 같아 <br>말 해 줄래 <br>아직도 난 네가 <br>내 옆 일거라 <br>생각해 <br>저기 저 아래 혼자 <br>있는 벤치마저 <br>누굴 기다리는 걸까 <br>안쓰러운 지금 <br>너는 지금 뭐해 <br>흩날리는 질문 <br>이제 와서 뭐해 <br>부질없는 짓을 <br>넌 항상 너다웠고 여전해 <br>널 바라보는 나만 <br>예전과 달라 <br>봐 줄만 해 <br>익숙한 이 거리에 <br>맴도는 건 향수 <br>에 취해 홀로 <br>거릴 걷는 내 모습 <br>어떤 이유로 또 네가 <br>떠올랐는지 <br>내 생각보다 네 존재는 <br>컸었나 봐 <br>괜찮다고 믿었는데 <br>너무 보고 싶어 <br>하지만 너에게 <br>말하지 않을게 <br>]]></content><category term="빈챈현스 (다이아)" label="빈챈현스 (다이아)"/><category term="너는 달 지구" label="너는 달 지구"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Shake_It_For_Me_Feat_2_Chainz/</id><title>Austin Mahone - Shake It For Me (Feat. 2 Chainz) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:13:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:13:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Shake_It_For_Me_Feat_2_Chainz/" title="Austin Mahone - Shake It For Me (Feat. 2 Chainz) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In the night when the sun goes down <br>And your wild side comes out <br>Baby, that's when you shake it for me <br>Soon as that door's shuts <br>Turn the bed to a club <br>Baby, that's when you shake it for me <br><br>Fingers on your clothes, girl <br>I been thinking that you always worked out <br>Living in LA now <br>But I swear you move like you come from the south <br>When we getting private <br>You show me tricks you don't show no one else <br>I wonder where you learned that <br>Want you to show me <br><br>Oh I can tell that you're a pro girl 'cause you do it right <br>Then you become an other person when I hit the lights <br>I could've sworn you were a dancer in another life <br>I gotta know, I gotta know <br><br>'Cause in the night when the sun goes down <br>And your wild side comes out <br>Baby, that's when you shake it for me <br>Soon as that door's shuts <br>Turn the bed to a club <br>Baby, that's when you shake it for me <br>And you go up and you come down <br>You turn around and then you poke it out for me <br>When you get my love and your body erupt <br>Baby, that's when you shake it for me <br><br>Shake it like a tambourine, girl <br>You see only you do that things you do <br>In and outta jeans, girl <br>Makes no difference to me to see you outta tune <br>It's gotta be magic <br>Some type of illusion, baby <br>I wonder where you learned that <br>Want you to show me <br><br>Oh I can tell that you're a pro girl 'cause you do it right <br>Then you become an other person when I hit the lights <br>I could've sworn you were a dancer in another life <br>I gotta know, I gotta know <br><br>'Cause in the night when the sun goes down <br>And your wild side comes out <br>Baby, that's when you shake it for me <br>Soon as that door's shuts <br>Turn the bed to a club <br>Baby, that's when you shake it for me <br>And you go up and you come down <br>You turn around and then you poke it out for me <br>When you get my love and your body erupt <br>Baby, that's when you shake it for me <br><br>Yeah, 2 Chainz <br>Turn the bedroom to a nightclub <br>I got idea, yes a light bulb <br>Then I lay back, let you get on top <br>See if you can join the bike club <br>First you told me you don't like clubs <br>Unless you see it's the right one <br>Outta all the girls that left <br>I'm starting to think you're the right one <br>We make a movie and sequel <br>We don't need siskle and eber <br>I'm like an eagle that's eager <br>I turn to a beast when I need you <br>Wait 'til the dark when I see you <br><br>'Cause in the night when the sun goes down <br>And your wild side comes out <br>Baby, that's when you shake it for me <br>Soon as that door's shuts <br>Turn the bed to a club <br>Baby, that's when you shake it for me <br>And you go up and you come down <br>You turn it around and you girl]]></content><category term="Austin Mahone" label="Austin Mahone"/><category term="Shake It For Me (Feat. 2 Chainz)" label="Shake It For Me (Feat. 2 Chainz)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Except_For_Us/</id><title>Austin Mahone - Except For Us - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:13:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:13:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Except_For_Us/" title="Austin Mahone - Except For Us - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Up close and personal <br>Study your body <br>I wanna stay right here <br>With your arms around me <br>Hold you like I do <br>Show me all of you oh <br>I'll show you me too <br>Give it to you like it <br>never been kissed <br>Like it never been loved <br>Give it to you like it never done this <br>Like you've never been touched <br>Like nobody else exists <br>except for us <br>Give it to you like it <br>never been loved <br>Give it to you like it never been <br>Give it to you like it never been oh <br>Give it to you like it never been oh <br>Like nobody else exists <br>except for us <br>Give it to you like it <br>never been loved <br>Give it to you like it never been <br>Give it to me like it never been <br>Deeper than physical <br>I got you open <br>Know how to take you there <br>Put you in motion <br>Hold you like I do <br>Show me all of you oh <br>I'll show you me too <br>Give it to you like it <br>never been kissed <br>Like it never been loved <br>Give it to you like it <br>never done this <br>Like you've never been touched <br>Like nobody else exists <br>except for us <br>Give it to you like it <br>never been loved <br>Give it to you like it never been <br>Give it to me like it never been <br>There's nobody like you <br>There's nobody like you <br>There's nobody like you <br>There's nobody like you <br>Give it to you like it <br>never been kissed <br>Like it never been loved <br>Give it to you like it never done this <br>Like you've never been touched <br>Like nobody else exists <br>except for us <br>Give it to you like it <br>never been loved <br>Give it to you like it never been <br>Give it to you like it <br>never been kissed <br>Like it never been loved <br>Give it to you like it never done this <br>Like you've never been touched <br>Like nobody else exists <br>except for us <br>Give it to you like it <br>never been loved <br>Give it to you like it never been <br>Give it to you like it never been <br>]]></content><category term="Austin Mahone" label="Austin Mahone"/><category term="Except For Us" label="Except For Us"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Wait_Around/</id><title>Austin Mahone - Wait Around - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:13:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:13:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Wait_Around/" title="Austin Mahone - Wait Around - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's too damn late to be thinking 'bout <br>These old mistakes, it's crazy how we're <br>Up and down, up and down <br>I need to know if you're in or out, in or out <br><br>Can we both agree, ain't the same <br>Time will tell, things have changed <br>I need you to tell me, baby <br>Tell me, baby, tell me, babe <br>Tell me how to see, I gotta know <br>Either way <br><br>'Cause I can't wait around for you, you, you <br>'Cause I got too many things to prove, ooh <br>I think it's time that you choose <br>What this really means to you <br>I wish I could read your mind <br>Just to predict your next move <br>Yeah 'cause I can't wait around for you, you, you <br><br>'Cause the good ones will go <br>If you wait too long <br>I learned that from my <br>Favourite song <br>We're up and down, up and down <br>I need to know if you're in or out, in or out <br><br>Can we both agree, ain't the same <br>Time will tell, things have changed <br>I need you to tell me, baby <br>Tell me, baby, tell me, babe <br>Tell me how to see, I gotta know <br>Either way <br><br>'Cause I can't wait around for you, you, you <br>'Cause I got too many things to prove, ooh <br>I think it's time that you choose <br>What this really means to you <br>I wish I could read your mind <br>Just to predict your next move <br>Yeah 'cause I can't wait around for you, you, you <br><br>Baby, I'm still home holding on for all of my patience <br>Baby, I'm still holding on, holding on to you <br><br>'Cause I can't wait around for you, you, you <br>'Cause I got too many things to prove, ooh <br>I think it's time that you choose <br>What this really means to you <br>I wish I could read your mind <br>Just to predict your next move <br>Yeah 'cause I can't wait around for you, you, you]]></content><category term="Austin Mahone" label="Austin Mahone"/><category term="Wait Around" label="Wait Around"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Double_Up/</id><title>Austin Mahone - Double Up - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:13:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:13:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Double_Up/" title="Austin Mahone - Double Up - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Landed I landed a new girl <br>I claimed it <br>You're mine <br>and I'm not sharing you <br>We've been up <br>we've been down <br>but we come back around <br>I'm not leaving until you say so <br>I knew way from the jump <br>You and me were meant to be <br>Finally find the love <br>that came to me so easily <br>Now now I see girl <br>Let's go don't ask me <br>no questions <br>I got you you got me <br>and it's just like ooh <br>You felt frustrated <br>don't worry we'll make it <br>'Cause lately I'm feeling like <br>We should double up <br>Girl it's kinda tough <br>Live the life without you <br>It just ain't enough <br>Yeah ooh trust me it's worth it <br>You know I put work in <br>And lately I'm feeling like oh <br>Lately I'm feeling like oh <br>Lately I'm feeling like <br>There ain't no doubt <br>what I'm feeling <br>You got my head in the clouds <br>No coming down <br>I don't wanna come down <br>High off you <br>so I can't touch the ground <br>Now it's love that I see <br>And always so real to me <br>So let's go go where we <br>Want to go babe don't you worry <br>I knew way from the jump <br>You and me were meant to be <br>Finally find the love <br>that came to me so easily <br>Now now I see girl <br>Let's go don't ask me <br>no questions <br>I got you you got me <br>and it's just like ooh <br>You felt frustrated <br>don't worry we'll make it <br>'Cause lately I'm feeling like <br>We should double up <br>Girl it's kinda tough <br>Live the life without you <br>It just ain't enough <br>Yeah ooh trust me it's worth it <br>You know I put work in <br>And lately I'm feeling like oh <br>Lately I'm feeling like oh <br>Lately I'm feeling like <br>We should double up <br>Girl it's kinda tough <br>Live the life without you <br>It just ain't enough <br>Yeah ooh trust me it's worth it <br>You know I put work in <br>And lately I'm feeling like oh <br>Lately I'm feeling like <br>Lately I'm feeling like <br>]]></content><category term="Austin Mahone" label="Austin Mahone"/><category term="Double Up" label="Double Up"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Better_With_You/</id><title>Austin Mahone - Better With You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:13:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:13:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Better_With_You/" title="Austin Mahone - Better With You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's Saturday <br>I finally got you to myself <br>oh yeah all day oh yeah <br>I know a place <br>Where we can shed the whole <br>world out and hide away away <br>See the cold drinks <br>have a sweeter taste <br>Whenever you're around <br>whenever you're around <br>And the bedsheets feel <br>a different way <br>And it feels good <br>somethin' in your touch <br>Whenever you're around me <br>Whenever you're around <br>And it should be <br>come as no surprise <br>I like it better with you <br>There's nothing that compares <br>to your company <br>I like it better with you <br>You come around and change <br>how I'm seeing things oh yeah <br>So baby don't you run away <br>run away run away <br>'Cause I just wanna stay at dawn <br>I like it better with you <br>There's nothing that could best <br>'till you copy in <br>A city night <br>Is so enticing <br>but I'd rather stay inside <br>with you <br>So lay beside <br>Me and you do all the things <br>we wanna try oh yeah <br>See the cold drinks <br>have a sweeter taste <br>Whenever you're around <br>whenever you're around <br>And the bedsheets feel <br>a different way <br>And it feels good <br>somethin' in your touch <br>Whenever you're around me <br>Whenever you're around <br>And it should be <br>come as no surprise <br>I like it better with you <br>There's nothing that could best <br>'till you copy in <br>I like it better with you <br>You come around and change <br>how I'm seeing things oh yeah <br>So baby don't you run away <br>run away run away <br>'Cause I just wanna stay at dawn <br>I like it better with you <br>There's nothing that could best <br>'till you copy in <br>Traffic ain't bad <br>when you're here with me <br>I even love the rain <br>when you're here with me <br>I don't really care what we do <br>long as I'm there with you baby <br>Traffic ain't bad <br>when you're here with me <br>I even love the rain <br>when you're here with me <br>I don't really care what we do <br>I like it better with you <br>There's nothing that compares <br>to your company <br>I like it better with you <br>You come around and change <br>how I'm seeing things oh yeah <br>So baby don't you run away <br>run away run away <br>'Cause I just wanna stay at dawn <br>I like it better with you <br>There's nothing that compares <br>to your company <br>]]></content><category term="Austin Mahone" label="Austin Mahone"/><category term="Better With You" label="Better With You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Lady_Feat_Pitbull/</id><title>Austin Mahone - Lady (Feat. Pitbull) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:13:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:13:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Lady_Feat_Pitbull/" title="Austin Mahone - Lady (Feat. Pitbull) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This is for the beautiful girls <br>around the world <br>Mr Worldwide <br>This is for the beautiful girls <br>around the world <br>Austin M talk to 'em <br>Lady hear me tonight <br>'Cause my feeling is just so right <br>As we dance by the moonlight <br>Can't you see you're my delight <br>Lady I just feel like <br>I won't get you out of my mind <br>I feel love for the first time <br>And I know that it's true <br>I can tell by the look in your eyes <br>I don't know your game <br>but it's magic <br>I like how it feels <br>when we're dancing <br>Just let go <br>don't make it a challenge baby <br>yeah baby <br>So give me yours and girl <br>I'll give you mine <br>Show me something <br>for I spend some time <br>'Cause I got love <br>I wanna make all night <br>With you baby <br>with you baby <br>Lady hear me tonight <br>'Cause my feeling is just so right <br>As we dance by the moonlight <br>Can't you see you're my delight <br>Lady I just feel like <br>I won't get you out of my mind <br>I feel love for the first time <br>And I know that it's true <br>I can tell by the look in your eyes <br>Now I'm back in the love alert <br>Laidback open up <br>now it's my turn <br>Let me make sure that you feel right <br>feel good <br>Feel wet feel freaky <br>feel nasty feel wood <br>It's all good <br>we can keep it on the low <br>hush hush <br>I made it skate skate skate <br>no rush <br>We can make straight love <br>or straight fuck <br>As long as EPT say no plus <br>Lady <br>Lately I've been thinkin' <br>'bout you my baby <br>I've been thinkin' bout <br>sexin' you crazy <br>I've been thinkin' 'bout <br>doin' the things you shouldn't do <br>Like in a bathroom star with a car <br>On the dancefloor <br>over the bar <br>Or next time in LA <br>pull over get off <br>and you feel me right <br>next to my Hollywood star <br>Play with it <br>Lady hear me tonight <br>'Cause my feeling is just so right <br>As we dance by the moonlight <br>Can't you see you're my delight <br>Lady I just feel like <br>I won't get you out of my mind <br>I feel love for the first time <br>And I know that it's true <br>I can tell by the look in your eyes <br>Lady Lady <br>Lady hear me tonight <br>'Cause my feeling is just so right <br>As we dance by the moonlight <br>Can't you see you're my delight <br>Lady I just feel like <br>I won't get you out of my mind <br>I feel love for the first time <br>And I know that it's true <br>I can tell by the look in your eyes <br>]]></content><category term="Austin Mahone" label="Austin Mahone"/><category term="Lady (Feat. Pitbull)" label="Lady (Feat. Pitbull)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Pretty_And_Young/</id><title>Austin Mahone - Pretty And Young - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:13:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:13:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Pretty_And_Young/" title="Austin Mahone - Pretty And Young - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let your hair down <br>with your hands up <br>Feeling our way right <br>beneath your waist <br>Pretty and young <br>growing the sun <br>Putting your heart over everything <br>I need you here <br>don't disappear <br>when the moon's up <br>I need you here <br>don't disappear <br>When you're pretty and young <br>you're pretty and young <br>Don't give your times to anyone <br>When you're pretty and young <br>pretty and young <br>Just live your life and have some fun <br>'Cause you're pretty and young <br>Your light supernova <br>Just let me come over <br>And give you just what you need <br>Don't long to this moment <br>There's no disappointment <br>As long as we're living free <br>I need you here <br>don't disappear <br>when the moon's up <br>I need you here <br>don't disappear <br>When you're pretty and young <br>you're pretty and young <br>Don't give your times to anyone <br>When you're pretty and young <br>pretty and young <br>Just live your life and have some fun <br>'Cause you're pretty and young <br>Any man will try to use <br>What you built to tear you down <br>you down <br>All you got is time to lose <br>But tell me you won't play around <br>around <br>'Cause you're pretty and young <br>pretty and young <br>When you're pretty and young <br>you're pretty and young <br>Don't give your times to anyone <br>When you're pretty and young <br>pretty and young <br>Just live your life and have some fun <br>'Cause you're pretty and young <br>Pretty and you ung you ung you ung <br>Pretty and you ung you ung you ung <br>Pretty and young <br>]]></content><category term="Austin Mahone" label="Austin Mahone"/><category term="Pretty And Young" label="Pretty And Young"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Love_At_Night_Feat_Juicy_J/</id><title>Austin Mahone - Love At Night (Feat. Juicy J) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:13:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:13:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Austin_Mahone/Love_At_Night_Feat_Juicy_J/" title="Austin Mahone - Love At Night (Feat. Juicy J) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When we make love at night <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love <br>Girl you had me from the start <br>Had me on Mars <br>Bad me seeing stars <br>That's why I gave you all my heart <br>Spending all my night <br>seen the day's up <br>I hope we never ever break up <br>Have so much fun around you <br>I can get used to the straight up <br>Girl you blow my mind <br>Even when you wasn't mine <br>That's why I gave you all my time <br>Something about you feels right <br>You told me to be patient <br>You got my heartbeat racing <br>Telling all my boys <br>I ain't going nowhere <br>'Cause I've been waiting <br>to make love to you <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love <br>Girl you know I love you so <br>When we make love at night <br>I will never let you go <br>When we make love at night <br>Cross my heart and hope to die <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love at night <br>Everything about her is just so chill <br>It's just so real all <br>and I love the way her body feels <br>So come a little closer <br>Never want this love to be over <br>So much fun when I'm around you <br>I just wanna kiss and hold you <br>Girl you blow my mind <br>Anything you want is fine <br>I just want you around <br>I just wanna love your body down <br>Every time we get together <br>It's like California weather <br>The best thing you've ever felt <br>In the whole well <br>there ain't nothing <br>better then our love <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love <br>Girl you know I love you so <br>When we make love at night <br>I will never let you go <br>When we make love at night <br>Cross my heart and hope to die <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love at night <br>Girl you know I love you so <br>I will never let you go <br>Cross my heart and hope to die <br>When we make love at night <br>Girl you know I love you so <br>When we make love at night <br>I will never let you go <br>When we make love at night <br>Cross my heart and hope to die <br>When we make love at night <br>When we make love at night <br>Girl you know I love you so <br>I will never let you go <br>Cross my heart and hope to die <br>When we make love at night <br>]]></content><category term="Austin Mahone" label="Austin Mahone"/><category term="Love At Night (Feat. Juicy J)" label="Love At Night (Feat. Juicy J)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kharisma/Where_Ive_Been_Bonus/</id><title>Kharisma - Where I`ve Been (Bonus) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:13:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:13:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kharisma/Where_Ive_Been_Bonus/" title="Kharisma - Where I`ve Been (Bonus) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I remember standing in the doorway of two thousand and fifteen <br>Just an average joe, with some big dreams <br>Hoping that I would go on to do big things <br>Ready for the year ahead and everything it could bring <br><br>I made promise to myself, that I would build <br>a better man before you, while I walk out on the field <br>where I stumbled and tripped, into the jungle of it <br>Went back to uni and thought it was just a horrible fit <br><br>I was back in the classroom, studying my masters <br>to be teacher, to inspire but after, I started <br>I was feeling so half hearted <br>because I knew exactly where my heart was <br><br>Rewind to last year <br>December to be exact <br>To an email that would tell me to go and pack <br>My bags in February, it felt extraordinary <br>To think, that I would be in Japan was kinda scary <br><br>Because, I'd be jumping up on stage <br>Spitting all these writtens that were living on a page <br>Make a living getting paid <br>By the people that would say <br>I would lift them up when they were being pushed into their graves <br><br>It was incredible and I could never forget it <br>To get a taste of a life that I had never expected <br>I never knew from the day that I had begun <br>That my music would fly me to the land of the rising sun, holy smokes <br><br>I still can't believe it happened <br>To think that every moment I invested in my passion <br>would open up the gates, with the music that I had made <br>In my bedroom on the nights I would stay up late <br><br>I don't know <br>I just Had to leave <br>University because I had believed <br>That it was time for me, to actually <br>make moves to a life that I have to lead <br><br>and so a gradually, worked steady on my craft <br>just to get to where I'm at, slowly writing out these raps <br>I got sad and I got mad, frustrated at the fact <br>that the next song I wrote could well and truly be my last <br><br>I need a break need a break <br>You can see it written all over my face <br>Thought that I should slow down, so I went and got a job <br>Bill's kept coming round, and I needed to get paid <br><br>So, I signed the dotted line to the mailroom <br>in the hopes that my situation go and change soon <br>I was getting money, I was staying on my grind <br>But monotony had got me thinking I had lost my mind <br><br>Till I found her, she came at the right time <br>Till I found her, I was feeling slowly left behind <br>Till I found her, the mountain felt impossible to climb <br>But she extended out her hand, saying it will all be fine <br><br>and so, in October 2015 <br>My first album came out and it felt like a dream <br>to see, my work up on that CD shelf <br>to claim that I had an LP under my belt <br><br>was crazy Shout out to Goontrax and Link 6 <br>MonoCreation, RoS we've got this <br>I've got friends that are talented people <br>Talented individuals that consider me equal <br><br>Had bouts with self doubt, but I've figured it out <br>I'm facing the situation and I'm turning it round <br>I was knocked down, and had my face pushed in the ground <br>And now I'm back up, and I'm ready with my eyes on the crown <br><br>because I'm a king in my own mind, own mind <br>said I'll make it in own time, own time <br>In a race against myself, and I'm in it to win <br>not stopping till conquer every battle within lets go]]></content><category term="Kharisma" label="Kharisma"/><category term="Where I`ve Been (Bonus)" label="Where I`ve Been (Bonus)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kharisma/Coming_Home/</id><title>Kharisma - Coming Home - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:14:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:14:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kharisma/Coming_Home/" title="Kharisma - Coming Home - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know you miss me <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>Since the last time <br>I saw ya <br>But don't you worry <br>it wont be long <br>until I come home <br>it wont be long <br>until I come home <br>I love her <br>and I hate to leave her lonely <br>ring ring went the iPhone <br>it was my lovely <br>lady back home <br>I know that she is missing me <br>Paris Tokyo in my headphones <br>listening <br>To Lupe <br>trying to get inspired <br>The journey's been long <br>and I'm really feeling tired <br>but I know that when I step <br>through that front door <br>that the woman I adore <br>will be waiting with kisses <br>and hugs and everything more <br>that I could want and <br>that is why I'm feeling <br>so excited <br>I might just <br>walk up with a poem <br>and recite it <br>Just to tell her <br>that every night <br>I had spent alone <br>I was wishing for that instant <br>I would chill with her at home <br>Damn <br>whoever thought that <br>someone like me <br>Would find a love like this <br>it was unlikely <br>A future spent with you <br>is just what I see <br>Were we born to be together <br>I think we just might be <br>I know you miss me <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>Since the last time <br>I saw ya <br>But don't you worry <br>it wont be long <br>until I come home <br>it wont be long <br>until I come home <br>Day and night <br>Our ships go by <br>it never gets easier <br>wanna be right by your side <br>I just wanna be close to you <br>hold you until we <br>reach our future <br>we can finally meet again <br>feel my heart <br>feel the rhythm <br>Of the better days <br>when i finally get to you <br>Because the days <br>have been long and <br>the nights have been cold <br>As we're speaking <br>on the phone <br>in a different time zone <br>I hate leaving you alone <br>but I know I gotta go <br>So I'm trying hard to pass <br>the time until I'm coming home <br>Because I know that you miss me <br>I can hear it in the way you speak <br>wishing I could reach <br>Far enough across the ocean <br>just to kiss you on the cheek <br>you know that by your side's <br>the only place I wanna be <br>I know you miss me <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>Since the last time <br>I saw ya <br>But don't you worry <br>it wont be long <br>until I come home <br>it wont be long <br>until I come home <br>I know you miss me <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>Since the last time <br>I saw ya <br>But don't you worry <br>it wont be long <br>until I come home <br>it wont be long <br>until I come home <br>I know you miss me <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>Since the last time <br>I saw ya <br>But don't you worry <br>it wont be long <br>until I come home <br>it wont be long <br>until I come home <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>I know you miss me <br>I know you miss me <br>I know you miss me <br>it feels like <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>feels like a lifetime <br>feels like a <br>feels like a <br>feels like a lifetime <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>it feels like <br>it feels like a lifetime <br>]]></content><category term="Kharisma" label="Kharisma"/><category term="Coming Home" label="Coming Home"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kharisma/Getaway/</id><title>Kharisma - Getaway - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:14:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:14:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kharisma/Getaway/" title="Kharisma - Getaway - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[faraway faraway <br>faraway faraway <br>faraway faraway <br>I just wanna escape <br>faraway faraway <br>faraway faraway <br>faraway faraway <br>to place that nobody knows <br>Grab a back pack <br>and the car keys <br>Time to make tracks <br>to where the stars be <br>I know you're sick <br>and tired of that routine <br>Walking into work <br>feeling down <br>because you can't see <br>Any hope of things <br>getting better <br>And it feels like forever <br>you've been keeping it together <br>For the sake of a dollar <br>and the number on a pay check <br>Courting all the money <br>you ain't made yet <br>I wanna <br>getaway to where the sun stays <br>Feel the warmth of the summer <br>as we're cruising down the highway <br>Listening to Weezer through <br>the speakers with the windows down <br>Can't deny the feeling of <br>this freedom that we finally found <br>I look to the left and see <br>my girl smile <br>And suddenly a thought <br>has come across my mind <br>Even though I know that <br>it has been a while <br>I'm finally at peace and I can leave <br>all my troubles behind <br>Getaway getaway <br>getaway getaway now <br>I just wanna escape <br>To a faraway place <br>because they say that <br>time don't wait <br>for no one at all <br>So lets go <br>to place that nobody knows <br>to a place only we can go <br>I got my hands on <br>the steering wheel <br>feeling in control <br>Of the path that I wanna take <br>choosing where to go <br>Tires to the asphalt <br>hit the open road <br>With no destination as <br>we look for the unknown <br>We can go <br>anywhere that you want to <br>Just as long <br>as I know I am beside you <br>We don't even need a map <br>it don't matter where we are <br>We can go and set up camp <br>underneath all of the stars <br>By the seashore or <br>the mountain side <br>we can ride <br>till the sun sets <br>on the skyline <br>we can fly <br>overseas <br>up into the clouds <br>till we can't see <br>people on the ground <br>living life <br>feeling care free <br>I don't really care <br>where we end up <br>I just want to feel alive <br>until our times up <br>From the cradle to the grave <br>in the moments in between <br>there's so many things to see <br>as we're living out our dreams <br>getaway to where the sun stays <br>Feel the warmth of the summer <br>as we're cruising down <br>the highway <br>We don't need a map <br>it don't matter where we are <br>We can go and set up camp <br>underneath all of the stars <br>Getaway getaway <br>getaway getaway now <br>I just wanna escape <br>To a faraway place <br>because they say that <br>time don't wait <br>for no one at all <br>So lets go <br>to place that nobody knows <br>to a place only we can go <br>Getaway getaway <br>getaway getaway now <br>I just wanna escape <br>To a faraway place <br>because they say that <br>time don't wait <br>for no one at all <br>So lets go <br>to place that nobody knows <br>to a place only we can go <br>faraway faraway <br>faraway faraway <br>faraway faraway <br>to place that nobody knows <br>faraway faraway <br>faraway faraway <br>faraway faraway <br>to a place only we can go <br>]]></content><category term="Kharisma" label="Kharisma"/><category term="Getaway" label="Getaway"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kharisma/Meant_For_More/</id><title>Kharisma - Meant For More - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:14:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:14:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kharisma/Meant_For_More/" title="Kharisma - Meant For More - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[As I sit between these four walls <br>I know that I was truly meant for more <br>So where do I go now <br>I’m tired of running in place <br>with no hope of joy or escape <br>Baby tell me is there no other way <br>From the second <br>that I clock in I feel locked in <br>and I gotta find a way out <br>Sit down take a seat <br>start a count down <br>as I watch the hands of the clock <br>make their way around <br>my neck as I sit at my desk <br>I look at my time <br>and what little is left <br>I wish I had the strength <br>to get up and be brave <br>before I lose my drive <br>and my spirit decays <br>Sitting in the mailroom <br>hoping I’ll prevail soon <br>before I feel frail face <br>paled from the same rou- <br>-tine while I daydream <br>hoping that there may be <br>a way to escape this <br>cycle of monotony <br>What has it gotten me <br>A bit of currency <br>to keep my floating <br>while I dream of where I want to be <br>I keep trying to outrun my flaws <br>because I know deep down <br>I was meant for more <br>As I sit between these four walls <br>I know that I was truly meant for more <br>so where do I go now <br>I’m tired of running in place <br>with no hope of joy or escape <br>Baby tell me is there no other way <br>because I’m really trying to find it <br>Searching for escape <br>but I’m feeling so blinded <br>reminded that everything <br>I need to be aligned with <br>is outside these walls <br>that I feel so confined in <br>I'm tired of running <br>I'm getting frustrated <br>I'm working for nothing <br>I'm losing my patience <br>I try to be calm but every morning <br>I’m waking up feeling lost <br>trying to find motivation <br>To go on and <br>just fight through the sadness <br>of knowing that I’m living <br>so far from my passion <br>Because I am dressed <br>in these business threads <br>I’m so stressed with these thoughts <br>running through my head <br>My heart aches with the feeling <br>I will never be <br>who I was meant to be <br>in a life that wasn’t meant for me <br>Feeling defeated when I hear it call <br>Because I know for sure <br>that I was meant for more <br>As I sit between these four walls <br>I know that I was truly meant for more <br>so where do I go now <br>I’m tired of running in place <br>with no hope of joy or escape <br>Baby tell me is there no other way <br>Cos I know who I am <br>I just don’t understand why I’m here <br>or what led me here <br>'cause I’m down and out of my mind <br>and I’m scared that I’m out of time <br>I try so hard but that’s not enough <br>As I sit between these four walls <br>I know that I was truly meant for more <br>so where do I go now <br>I’m tired of running in place <br>with no hope of joy or escape <br>Baby tell me is there no other way <br>I’m so sick of feeling unfamiliar <br>Looking at a stranger <br>when I look into the mirror <br>I see all the changes <br>and the problems I’m at war with <br>Afraid of my reflection <br>and the way it’s been distorted <br>I used to have high hopes <br>I said I used to have high hopes <br>But now everything is changed <br>and I’m feeling so damn ashamed <br>I’m fighting the wrong fights <br>while I’m trying to switch lanes <br>Trapped in a nine to five <br>that I thought would be the force <br>that would drive my music <br>further than it ever has before <br>But look at me know beaten down <br>fallen to the floor <br>and beaten into the ground <br>but I still hear the call <br>of my inner voice telling me <br>I am meant for more <br>]]></content><category term="Kharisma" label="Kharisma"/><category term="Meant For More" label="Meant For More"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kharisma/Gotta_Go/</id><title>Kharisma - Gotta Go - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:14:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:14:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kharisma/Gotta_Go/" title="Kharisma - Gotta Go - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I’m looking out <br>the window of a train <br>analysing my reflection <br>and the way <br>that it has changed <br>and it’s clear <br>I’m not the same <br>as the person <br>that I once was <br>looking back to the place <br>that I had come from <br>I say thanks for the lessons <br>that had brought me here <br>even though the future is not <br>clear <br>I often wonder <br>what the universe <br>is keeping in store <br>Does it acknowledge my plans <br>or does it keep them ignored <br>I’m not waiting for the day <br>that I’ll be number one <br>Truth be told <br>I know that day will <br>probably never come <br>so while the sun is up <br>I’m walking <br>in a different lane <br>that aspires to achieve <br>what truly cannot <br>be explained <br>because I know <br>that there’s a lot <br>that I still have to do <br>and it’s truly up to me <br>to see it through <br>If you’re searching <br>for direction I am <br>in the same position <br>come and listen <br>while I tell you how it is <br>go and sing it like <br>I don’t want to wait <br>another moment for the day <br>that I will say <br>it’s just too late <br>So I’ve gotta go <br>I’ve gotta go <br>I don’t want to wait <br>another moment for the day <br>that I will say <br>it’s just too late <br>It’s been a long time <br>since I felt like this <br>Contemplating my future <br>and the life that I live <br>Thinking one day <br>I can confidently say <br>that I’ve come a long way <br>from the days I would create <br>these songs in my bedroom <br>songs in my bedroom <br>Thinking I should <br>go to bed soon <br>I should go to bed soon <br>because I gotta <br>wake up early <br>so I do not miss my train <br>I wish I didn’t need to <br>but I need to get paid <br>Because my wallet gets lighter <br>as my bills stack up <br>but I know that I’m a fighter <br>though my skills still suck <br>I’ve spent <br>a long time feeling down <br>on my luck <br>but that’s all about to change <br>everything is looking up <br>Got a fresh new perspective <br>on the world I see <br>Feeling positive <br>knowing it was made for me <br>Both hands on the wheel <br>in control of my fate <br>so I gotta go <br>because I know <br>my destiny awaits <br>]]></content><category term="Kharisma" label="Kharisma"/><category term="Gotta Go" label="Gotta Go"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kharisma/Switch_Lanes/</id><title>Kharisma - Switch Lanes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:14:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:14:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kharisma/Switch_Lanes/" title="Kharisma - Switch Lanes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey I see you over there <br>Living without a care <br>I wish that I could be like you <br>Do you feel ever the same <br>Wishing you could just <br>switch lanes <br>switch lanes <br>I wanna break this flow <br>i’ll take it real slow <br>I’m gonna take control <br>you will see <br>there’s a place in the unknown <br>where my mind runs free <br>somewhere that we can go <br>beyond everything we see <br>Wake up to the sound <br>of an alarm clock <br>Try to hit the snooze button <br>but it won't stop <br>Ears keep ringing <br>as I listen to the sound <br>Of my phone telling me <br>that the time is now <br>I I I I gotta go get a move on <br>Get dressed put my shoes on <br>Stressed but I gotta be strong <br>Eyelids heavy <br>struggling to leave bed <br>Thoughts running <br>through my head like <br>Is today gonna be the day <br>that things change <br>or will it all stay the same <br>So tired of this never <br>ending cycle <br>Daydreaming of the things <br>that I would like to <br>do with my time <br>but I’m lost <br>in the cost of a dime <br>At a desk stressed hoping <br>that I’ll be next in line <br>and I wonder <br>will I be here forever <br>And I wonder <br>will it ever get better <br>Hey I see you over there <br>Living without a care <br>I wish that I could be like you <br>Do you ever feel the same <br>Wishing you could <br>just switch lanes <br>I’ve got a lot on my mind <br>I’m so scared of the feeling <br>that I’ll run out of time <br>because I’m trying to be <br>free enough to take flight <br>and grab a hold of my dreams <br>I downright refuse <br>to be forced to choose <br>to keep living a life <br>when I’ve got <br>so much to lose <br>I was meant for more <br>I wasn’t built for this <br>I was meant for more <br>I can’t call it quits <br>I've worked too hard <br>to let this go <br>And now I know <br>that sometimes <br>you gotta be brave <br>To save everything <br>you worked <br>so hard to grow <br>You have to show <br>you're strong <br>enough to lead the way <br>Don't follow your dreams <br>just make them <br>Put your pride to the side <br>and just take them <br>Trying to switch <br>lanes not knowing <br>where it takes me <br>Desperate for change <br>so I'm hitting the escape key <br>When it feels <br>like everyone is trying <br>to slow you down <br>When you feeling sick <br>and tired and <br>you're feeling uninspired <br>all you gotta do is <br>When in need of help <br>just believe <br>and yourself and just <br>Put the pedal to the metal <br>and get on another level <br>you just gotta go <br>and switch lanes <br>Hey I see you over there <br>Living without a care <br>I wish that I could be like you <br>Do you ever feel the same <br>Wishing you could <br>just switch lanes <br>]]></content><category term="Kharisma" label="Kharisma"/><category term="Switch Lanes" label="Switch Lanes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/권나무/튀김우동/</id><title>권나무 - 튀김우동 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:14:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:14:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B6%8C%EB%82%98%EB%AC%B4/%ED%8A%80%EA%B9%80%EC%9A%B0%EB%8F%99/" title="권나무 - 튀김우동 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어두운 밤이 다 <br>지나갈 때까지만 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>아니 따뜻한 봄이 <br>다시 올 때까지만 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>마당이 있는 집을 <br>지을 때까지만 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>아니 내가 늙어서 <br>다 마를 때까지만 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>이런 나와 늘 <br>함께해주는 <br>네게 난 항상 <br>기대지 못할 <br>좁은 마음만 <br>보이고 뜨겁게 <br>널 사랑한다 말하지만 <br>정작 따뜻하진 못하고 <br>어두운 밤이 다 <br>지나갈 때까지만 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>아니 따뜻한 봄이 <br>다시 올 때까지만 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>아 물이 끓는다 <br>튀김우동이 다 <br>익을 때까지만 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>튀김우동이 다 <br>익을 때까지만 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>튀김우동이 다 <br>익을 때까지만 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>튀김우동이 다 <br>익을 때까지만이라도 <br>곁에 있어줘 <br>]]></content><category term="권나무" label="권나무"/><category term="튀김우동" label="튀김우동"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동요세상/푸른_하늘_은하수/</id><title>동요세상 - 푸른 하늘 은하수 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:14:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:14:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81/%ED%91%B8%EB%A5%B8_%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98_%EC%9D%80%ED%95%98%EC%88%98/" title="동요세상 - 푸른 하늘 은하수 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[푸른 하늘 은하수 한 번 찾아보자 <br>별들이 다 모여 있는 신비로운 세계 <br><br>별이 모여서 은하를 만들고 있어요 <br>저 우주에 별이 몇 개일까 <br>한 번 세어볼까 <br><br>푸른 하늘 은하수 정말 아름다워 <br>언젠가는 별들을 <br>다 세는 날 올거야 <br>다 세는 날 올거야 <br>다 세는 날 올거야 <br><br>푸른 하늘 은하수 한 번 찾아보자 <br>별들이 다 모여 있는 신비로운 세계 <br><br>별이 모여서 은하를 만들고 있어요 <br>저 우주에 별이 몇 개일까 <br>한 번 세어볼까 <br><br>푸른 하늘 은하수 정말 아름다워 <br>언젠가는 별들을 <br>다 세는 날 올거야 <br>다 세는 날 올거야 <br>다 세는 날 올거야]]></content><category term="동요세상" label="동요세상"/><category term="푸른 하늘 은하수" label="푸른 하늘 은하수"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Better_Together_English_Ver/</id><title>Nicholas Edwards - Better Together (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Better_Together_English_Ver/" title="Nicholas Edwards - Better Together (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone has seen the rain <br>Everyone has felt the pain <br>Of a world broken apart <br>Of an empty broken heart <br>Let's make it better <br><br>Doesn't matter if it's wrong or right <br>Doesn't matter if it's day or night <br>The world will trun around <br>Even faster than the speed of sound <br>Put your hand in mine and we'll make a pact <br>Never gonna let the darkness take us <br>Never gonna let the hate replace us together now <br><br>Everyone has seen the rain <br>Everyone has felt the pain <br>Of a world broken apart <br>Of an empty broken heart <br>Let's make it better <br><br>When the moon won't shine there's no light <br>When we feel we're gonna lose the fight <br>Find more lyrics at ※ Mojimcom <br><br>The world will trun around <br>Even faster than the speed of sound <br>Put your hand in mine and we'll make a pact <br>Never gonna let the darkness take us <br>Never gonna let the hate replace us together now <br><br>Everyone has seen the rain <br>Everyone has felt the pain <br>Of a world broken apart <br>Of an empty broken heart <br>Let's make it better <br><br>Everyone has seen the rain <br>Everyone has felt the pain <br>Of a world broken apart <br>Of an empty broken heart <br><br>Everyone has seen the rain <br>Everyone has felt the pain <br>Of a world broken apart <br>Of an empty broken heart <br>Better together]]></content><category term="Nicholas Edwards" label="Nicholas Edwards"/><category term="Better Together (English Ver.)" label="Better Together (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Loving_My_Lover_English_Ver/</id><title>Nicholas Edwards - Loving My Lover (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Loving_My_Lover_English_Ver/" title="Nicholas Edwards - Loving My Lover (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They told me no but you are not afraid <br>The're watching us but I am not afraid <br>And I know I should know better than to <br>Follow you into the night but you <br>Seem to have a hold on me and I go hungry again <br><br>Loving My Lover <br>Loving My Lover <br>Get me sweating in your starlight <br>Don't be scared to do what feels right <br>I am loving my lover <br>Loving my lover <br><br>Just a taste, my worries melt away <br>Thrill me babe, my inhibitions fade <br>And I been spending too much time trying to <br>Do what people think is right so I'll <br>Find more lyrics at ※ Mojimcom <br>Give myself away to you I'm letting go of the shame <br><br>And at the risk of sounding vulgar <br>I'm asking if you'll take me further <br>We let our bodies do the talking <br>Cause empty words will be forgotten <br><br>Loving My Lover <br>Loving My Lover <br>Get me sweating in your starlight <br>Don't be scared to do what feels right <br>I am loving my lover <br>Loving my lover <br><br>Loving My Lover <br>Loving My Lover <br>Loving My Lover <br>Loving My Lover]]></content><category term="Nicholas Edwards" label="Nicholas Edwards"/><category term="Loving My Lover (English Ver.)" label="Loving My Lover (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Someday_Somewhere_English_Ver/</id><title>Nicholas Edwards - Someday Somewhere (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Someday_Somewhere_English_Ver/" title="Nicholas Edwards - Someday Somewhere (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Some people say maybe someday <br>Everything we gave away will find it's way back if we pray <br>I promise if I find it I'll bring it you night away <br><br>Some people say maybe someday <br>Somewhere beyond the clouds that there may be another, better way <br>I wonder if we'll find it, know it tonight under the moonlight <br><br>The stars are always kind <br>They've given me what's mine <br>So let the morning come <br>And let's be overrun <br>We've found it, love has found it <br><br>Find more lyrics at ※ Mojimcom <br>Summer is like blueberry wine <br>Sweet on our lips like something I had never known <br>Something so kind <br>You whisper softly asking if I wouldn't stay through the night <br>one more night <br><br>Some people say maybe someday <br>Everything we gave away will find it's way back if we pray <br>I promise if I find it I'll bring it you right away, right away <br><br>Some people say maybe someday <br>Somewhere beyond the clouds that there may be another, better way <br>I wonder if we'll find it, know it tonight under the moonlight <br>I wonder if we'll find it, know it tonight in the moonlight <br>]]></content><category term="Nicholas Edwards" label="Nicholas Edwards"/><category term="Someday Somewhere (English Ver.)" label="Someday Somewhere (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Feel_It_English_Ver/</id><title>Nicholas Edwards - Feel It (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Feel_It_English_Ver/" title="Nicholas Edwards - Feel It (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let your body feel it <br>Feel it baby feel it <br>Let your body feel it <br>Feel it baby feel it <br><br>Throwing it away always seemed like best course of action <br>They told me it was a free world I tried to agree <br>But in the lime light I realized that I couldn't accept it <br>Illusions that the world was right are just fantasy <br><br>And so we break free, break free from the shackles that bind us <br>And we break free, break free from wishing <br>that nothing was ever the same ever again, again <br>Now I ask you what makes you happier than you've ever been <br><br>Let your body feel it <br>Feel it baby feel it <br>Let your body feel it <br>Feel it baby feel it <br><br>So finally we know that even when life seems out of control <br>We own the way we feel inside, it's up to me <br>And every day we grow searching for a better tomorrow <br>Cause I will never let it die, that sweet fantsy <br>Find more lyrics at ※ Mojimcom <br><br>And so we break free, break free from the shackles that bind us <br>And we break free, break free from wishing <br>that nothing was ever the same ever again, again <br>Now I ask you what makes you happier than you've ever been <br><br>Even as the stormy clouds arrive above us <br>Even as the ground beneath our feet's betraying us we <br>Never let them see us cry cause together know we are strong <br><br>And so we break free, break free from the shackles that bind us <br>And we break free, break free from wishing <br>that nothing was ever the same ever again, again <br>Now I ask you what makes you happier than you've ever been <br><br>Let your body feel it <br>Feel it baby feel it <br>Let your body feel it <br>Feel it baby feel it <br><br>Even as the stormy clouds above us <br>Even as the ground beneath our feet is <br>Even as the stormy clouds above us <br>Even as the ground beneath our feet is]]></content><category term="Nicholas Edwards" label="Nicholas Edwards"/><category term="Feel It (English Ver.)" label="Feel It (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Mona_Lisa_English_Ver/</id><title>Nicholas Edwards - Mona Lisa (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Mona_Lisa_English_Ver/" title="Nicholas Edwards - Mona Lisa (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The world is spinning at the speed of sound <br>Maybe faster, I don't get around much <br>Never went to university <br>Never lived in a big city but <br>Does that make me dumb <br>Just a country bumpkin <br>Did I write this rhyme <br>Knowing that it didn't make any sense Did I <br><br>I guess you think you know what I should do <br>But baby I done killed the kid you thought you knew <br>The truth is that some truth to say <br>Didn't hop on a jet to come and play <br>Get your story straight <br>Cause I don't fuck with second rate <br>So get the whiskey out <br>And I'll write a couple lines for the kids to talk about <br><br>But I will make amends <br>I'll rush it, I'll floor it, I'm in this till the end <br><br>Mona Lisa　I got a ways to go <br>Mona Lisa　And I don't know no, no <br>Mona Lisa　You heard it here first <br>Mona Lisa　Working on my Mona Lisa <br><br>I'm sitting in a room in Tokyo <br>I'm writing songs like I got yen to blow yet <br>The truth is that I got a skill to sell <br>But no ones ringing the bell, what <br>I got bills to pay <br>I ain't gettin' laid, ugh <br>Find more lyrics at ※ Mojimcom <br>No this shit ain't free <br>Probably got another couple of pits ahead of me <br><br>My mama told to be a good boy <br>My daddy told me not to be nobody's toy <br>It's gonna be my name on that CD <br>You can bet I'm gonna look pretty <br>Sorry 'bout it now <br>But I ain't sorry at all <br>So get the vodka out <br>And I'll write a couple lines for the kids to talk about <br><br>But I will make amends <br>I'll rush it, I'll floor it, I'm in this till the end <br><br>Mona Lisa　I got a ways to go <br>Mona Lisa　And I don't know no, no <br>Mona Lisa　You heard it here first <br>Mona Lisa　Working on my Mona Lisa <br><br>By now you know I talk a lot of shit <br>I guess I'm petty maybe just a little bit <br>I bet you been the same a time or two <br>Maybe threw a punch for trying you <br><br>But I will make amends <br>I'll rush it, I'll floor it, I'm in this til the end <br><br>Mona Lisa　I got a ways to go <br>Mona Lisa　And I don't know no, no <br>Mona Lisa　You heard it here first <br>Mona Lisa　Working on my Mona Lisa <br>]]></content><category term="Nicholas Edwards" label="Nicholas Edwards"/><category term="Mona Lisa (English Ver.)" label="Mona Lisa (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/W_W_W_English_Ver/</id><title>Nicholas Edwards - W/W/W (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/W_W_W_English_Ver/" title="Nicholas Edwards - W/W/W (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pick it up and put it on down <br>but there ain't nothing wrong with me <br>You know I'll come back every time <br>Giving it all to make you mine <br><br>Thick and thin I'm holding you down <br>and I ain't never gonna leave <br>Baby woah <br><br>I been spending all my time trying to get <br>a bit of time babe I just wanna your man <br>I ain't perfect yeah I know but <br>I'll never let you go let me show you that we can <br>You met a guy and he make you feel good <br>but he can't do what I do <br>So lemme lay it on down tonight <br>You'll be mine tonight <br><br>You're like a picture in my soul <br>Your love has got me wanting more <br>The brightest picture in my soul <br>You make me wanna get up <br><br>Whatever whenever wherever <br>Baby gotta let me know <br>I just can't keep lose control <br>Ain't nobody else can do it better <br><br>Whatever whenever wherever <br>Baby gotta let me know <br>I just can't keep control <br>Ain't nobody ain't nobody else but you <br><br>Never thought I'd find myself here <br>barely breathing, into you <br>Baby it's messing with my mind <br>Maybe I'm running out time <br><br>But thick and thin, I'm holding you down <br>Find more lyrics at ※ Mojimcom <br>and I ain't never gonna leave <br>Baby woah <br><br>Got my baby on my mind and I hope you <br>wouldn't mind but I just wanna be your man <br>It ain't never tell you no, girl I'm never <br>letting go let me show you that we can <br>You met a guy and he make you feel good <br>but he can't do what I do <br>So lemme lay it on down tonight <br>You'll be mine tonight <br><br>You're like a picture in my soul <br>Your love has got me wanting more <br>The brightest picture in my soul <br>You make me wanna get up <br><br>Whatever whenever wherever <br>Baby gotta let me know <br>I just can't keep lose control <br>Ain't nobody else can do it better <br><br>Your body's got me reeling <br>I gotta fight this feeling <br>I take a step and then it's gone <br><br>You're so convicing baby <br>I'm satisfied with maybe <br>I take a step and then it's gone <br>But then you're mine <br><br>You're like a picture in my soul <br>Your love has got me wanting more <br>The brightest picture in my soul <br>You make me wanna get up <br><br>Whatever whenever wherever <br>Baby gotta let me know <br>I just can't keep lose control <br>Ain't nobody else can do it better]]></content><category term="Nicholas Edwards" label="Nicholas Edwards"/><category term="W/W/W (English Ver.)" label="W/W/W (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Homebound_English_Ver/</id><title>Nicholas Edwards - Homebound (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Homebound_English_Ver/" title="Nicholas Edwards - Homebound (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Seventeen, I thought I had it all figured out <br>I and me was everything I cared about <br>Have you ever felt that life had left you behind <br>I thought I knew myself once upon a time <br><br>Now my heart is beating faster <br>And all I see is empty pastures <br>Wondering where I left yesterday <br><br>Everything I thought fulfilled me <br>Made me question if I will be <br>Learning what I really have to say <br><br>Homebound, there is no road too long <br>Homebound, I've written you a song <br>Homebound, in every tear I cried <br>Homebound, is all my love my might <br>Find more lyrics at ※ Mojimcom <br><br>Little boy grew to a man and he figured out <br>Everyone is trying to survive the doubt <br>Children will one day grow older and change their minds <br>The world ain't made up of single file lines <br><br>And I ain't getting any younger <br>I'm clinging to my sense of wonder <br>Swear to God I'll never let it die <br><br>If lose that youhful dreamer <br>I would lose my will to be there <br>The kid in me deserves to see the light <br><br>Homebound, there is no road too long <br>Homebound, I've written you a song <br>Homebound, in every tear I cried <br>Homebound, is all my love my might]]></content><category term="Nicholas Edwards" label="Nicholas Edwards"/><category term="Homebound (English Ver.)" label="Homebound (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Little_Town_English_Ver/</id><title>Nicholas Edwards - Little Town (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Little_Town_English_Ver/" title="Nicholas Edwards - Little Town (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Kitchen lights, sleepless nights <br>Your heart beats here with me <br>Silly fights, but we're alright <br>In your arms is where I'll be <br>Remembering when we met at that cafe <br>A year ago in the later half of May <br>You pulled me close and I never asked you why <br>I knew it then that this love was worth a try <br><br>Tear me down, little town <br>I promise you we'll make it through tonight <br><br>I'm coming home <br>Find more lyrics at ※ Mojimcom <br>I'm coming home to you <br><br>Remember when on the road we lost our way <br>A year ago in the later half of May <br>I pulled you close when I saw you start cry <br>You looked at me and you told me you were mine <br><br>Tear me down, little town <br>I promise you we'll make it through tonight <br><br>Tear me down, little town <br>I promise you we'll make it through tonight <br><br>I promise you we'll make it through tonight]]></content><category term="Nicholas Edwards" label="Nicholas Edwards"/><category term="Little Town (English Ver.)" label="Little Town (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/DR1VE_English_Ver/</id><title>Nicholas Edwards - DR1VE (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/DR1VE_English_Ver/" title="Nicholas Edwards - DR1VE (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[See your body glistening while we're drifing under neon lights <br>Tonight Tonight <br>Like we're Hollywood'ing but we shouldn't drift like satellites <br>Tonight Tonight <br><br>I got the keys to move you　So let my kiss control you <br>Now all you gotta do is sayalright <br><br>You got the look now don't you　I see them all adore you <br>And all I gotta say ishey, she's mine <br><br>So come on and drive I can feel you coming to life <br>There's a party downtown, so get naughty cause were messing around <br><br>Feel your body riffing as we're dripping through the summer nights <br>Tonight Tonight <br>And we ain't behaving but we gotta exercise our rights <br>Tonight Tonight <br><br>I got the keys to move you　So let my kiss control you <br>Find more lyrics at ※ Mojimcom <br>Now all you gotta do is sayalright <br><br>You got the look now don't you　I see them all adore you <br>And all I gotta say ishey, she's mine <br><br>So come on and drive I can feel you coming to life <br>There's a party downtown, so get naughty cause were messing around <br><br>Ain't nobody else gonna do you better <br>Ain't nobody else gonna even measure <br>Alright Alright, Alright Alright <br>Ain't nobody else gonna do it better <br>Give me all you got, it's now or never <br>Alright Alright, Alright Alright <br><br>So come on and drive I can feel you coming to life <br>There's a party downtown, so get naughty cause were messing around <br><br>So come on and drive I can feel you coming to life <br>There's a party downtown, so get naughty cause were messing around]]></content><category term="Nicholas Edwards" label="Nicholas Edwards"/><category term="DR1VE (English Ver.)" label="DR1VE (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/We_Get_By_English_Ver/</id><title>Nicholas Edwards - We Get By (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/We_Get_By_English_Ver/" title="Nicholas Edwards - We Get By (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tires on the road, tired of being alone <br>Windows down, trying to let go <br>Never thought I'd pray to a god I don't believe in <br>Never thought I'd find myself running out of hope <br>Looking for different life on the horizon <br>Pedal to the ground, I'm replace what I broke <br><br>Better days are right beyond the headlights <br>Even through the tears we're going to be alright <br>We get by, we get by <br>Better days are coming past the red light <br>Ever through the fears we're going to be alright <br>We get by, we get by <br><br>Everywhere but here everything is so clear <br>Windows down, trying to get near <br>Never thought I'd pray to a god I don't believe in <br>Never thought I'd find myself running out of hope <br>Looking for a different life on the horizon <br>Find more lyrics at ※ Mojimcom <br>Prdal to the ground, I'm replacing what I broke <br><br>Better days are right beyond the headlights <br>Even through the tears we're going to be alright <br>We get by, we get by <br>Better days are coming past the red light <br>Ever through the fears we're going to be alright <br>We get by, we get by <br><br>Every tear I'm crying <br>Everywhere we're riding <br>Baby we'll be alright <br>Promise we'll be alright <br><br>Better days are right beyond the headlights <br>Even through the tears we're going to be alright <br>We get by, we get by <br>Better days are coming past the red light <br>Ever through the fears we're going to be alright <br>We get by, we get by]]></content><category term="Nicholas Edwards" label="Nicholas Edwards"/><category term="We Get By (English Ver.)" label="We Get By (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Sticks__Stones_English_Ver/</id><title>Nicholas Edwards - Sticks &amp; Stones (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Sticks__Stones_English_Ver/" title="Nicholas Edwards - Sticks &amp; Stones (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She's locked and loaded <br>she's got a taste for the explosive and she's <br>She's fucking with my mind <br>she's trying to get me down but I see the signs <br>I never play games, just taking names <br>you're duly noted til we're back to where we were <br>addicted to our words drunk on blowing out <br><br>And I see the look that you have in your eyes <br>But I'm never gonna give it away for you <br>I'mma make you work for what you want tonight <br>Sticks and stones <br><br>Baby I can feel my body breaking <br>and I can see your heart is racing <br>Another touch and I can take you higher <br>Maybe we can make it happen baby <br>and we can make it faster baby <br>Another touch and you can take me higher <br><br>Don't need no more words <br>Don't need no hurt <br>All we need to tonight is those sticks and stones <br><br>I know I'm over thinking I watch her hips go lower and she <br>She thinks she's ready to be mine so <br>I'mma tell her to get in line <br>She love to play games I'm taking names <br>you're duly noted til we back to where we were <br>addicted to our words drunk on blowing out <br><br>And I see the look that you have in your eyes <br>But I'm never gonna give it away for you <br>Find more lyrics at ※ Mojimcom <br>I'mma make you work for what you want tonight <br>Sticks and stones <br><br>Baby I can feel my body breaking <br>and I can see your heart is racing <br>Another touch and I can take you higher <br>Maybe we can make it happen baby <br>and we can make it faster baby <br>Another touch and you can take me higher <br><br>Don't need no more words <br>Don't need no hurt <br>All we need to tonight is those sticks and stones <br><br>I know it's wrong I'm in love with the danger <br>Every time I think I've made it out <br>I'm back in your arms, in your heart <br>Nobody but your sticks and sotnes <br><br>Baby I can feel my body breaking <br>and I can see your heart is racing <br>Another touch and I can take you higher <br><br>Baby I can feel my body breaking <br>and I can see your heart is racing <br>Another touch and I can take you higher <br>Maybe we can make it happen baby <br>and we can make it faster baby <br>Another touch and you can take me higher <br><br>Don't need no more words <br>Don't need no hurt <br>All we need to tonight is those sticks and stones]]></content><category term="Nicholas Edwards" label="Nicholas Edwards"/><category term="Sticks &amp; Stones (English Ver.)" label="Sticks &amp; Stones (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Freeze_English_Ver/</id><title>Nicholas Edwards - Freeze (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nicholas_Edwards/Freeze_English_Ver/" title="Nicholas Edwards - Freeze (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Calling calling all cars <br>What we've got is an emergency <br>She is on the run <br>Girl is armed and crazy <br>Hesitation is your enemy <br>And it's all for fun <br>Criminal in everything you do <br>Turn around and then she's gone <br>Serial offender on the loose <br>Don't let her steal your heart <br>And now the search in on tonight <br>Tonight tonight <br>You got the look it's in your eyes <br>Your eyes your eyes <br>Freeze don't move <br>You're guilty that's what you do <br>Say Give it one more night <br>say it one more time now <br>Freeze don't move <br>Your body's telling the truth <br>Say Give it one more night <br>say it one more time <br>Why you gotta break the rules <br>I gotta bring the law to you <br>Baby got me searching and <br>searching and searching <br>Show me what you got to prove <br>Baby what you got to lose <br>Baby got me searching and <br>searching and searching <br>For you <br>The crime you played me like a fool <br>Should've known you'd do me wrong <br>do me wrong <br>do me wrong <br>do me wrong <br>Evidence is fire over you <br>And your lips the smoking gun <br>And now the search is on tonight <br>Tonight tonight <br>You got the look it's in your eyes <br>Your eyes your eyes <br>Freeze don't move <br>You're guilty that's what you do <br>Say Give it one more night <br>say it one more time now <br>Freeze don't move <br>Your body's telling the truth <br>Say Give it one more night <br>say it one more time <br>Why you gotta break the rules <br>I gotta bring the law to you <br>Baby got me searching and <br>searching and searching <br>Show me what you got to prove <br>Baby what you got to lose <br>Baby got me searching and <br>searching and searching <br>For you <br>Why can't you listen to what I say <br>Why can't you kiss it be my baby <br>Why can't you listen do what I say <br>Why can't you why can't you <br>Freeze don't move <br>You're guilty that's what you do <br>Say Give it one more night <br>say it one more time now <br>Freeze don't move <br>Your body's telling the truth <br>Say Give it one more night <br>say it one more time <br>Why you gotta break the rules <br>I gotta bring the law to you <br>Baby got me searching and <br>searching and searching <br>Show me what you got to prove <br>Baby what you got to lose <br>Baby got me searching and <br>searching and searching <br>For you <br>]]></content><category term="Nicholas Edwards" label="Nicholas Edwards"/><category term="Freeze (English Ver.)" label="Freeze (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/turpee_터피/puzzle/</id><title>turpee (터피) - puzzle - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/turpee_%ED%84%B0%ED%94%BC/puzzle/" title="turpee (터피) - puzzle - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[부드러운 duvet <br>늦은 새벽에 침대 위 <br>노란 빛의 조명이 <br>은은하게 방을 밝히지 <br>포근하게 느껴지는 <br>soft blanket <br>향의 공기 <br>I’m not worried <br>가득히 넘치는 joy <br>나를 단단하게 하는 <br>hardship <br>이건 마치 저마다 맞춘 <br>harden steel <br>내게 주어지는 모든 것 gift <br>점점 가까워지는 verity <br>life is puzzle <br>life is puzzle game <br>life is puzzle <br>처음부터 완벽한 그림 <br>life is puzzle <br>life is puzzle game <br>life is puzzle <br>흩어진 그림의 조각들 <br>나를 다른 사람과 <br>비교하면서 <br>가지지 못한 걸 <br>가져야 한다고 생각했어 <br>It was lonely and empty <br>nothing is for granted <br>나를 단단하게 하는 <br>hardship <br>이건 마치 저마다 맞춘 <br>harden steel <br>내게 주어지는 모든 것 gift <br>점점 가까워지는 verity <br>life is puzzle <br>life is puzzle game <br>life is puzzle <br>처음부터 완벽한 그림 <br>life is puzzle <br>life is puzzle game <br>life is puzzle <br>흩어진 그림의 조각들 <br>there's nothing wrong <br>모두의 퍼즐이 맞춰지고 있어 <br>누군가 부정적이라면 <br>just process is all <br>I did before <br>life is puzzle <br>life is puzzle game <br>life is puzzle <br>처음부터 완벽한 그림 <br>life is puzzle <br>life is puzzle game <br>life is puzzle <br>흩어진 그림의 조각들 <br>life is puzzle <br>life is puzzle game <br>life is puzzle <br>처음부터 완벽한 그림 <br>life is puzzle <br>life is puzzle game <br>life is puzzle <br>흩어진 그림의 조각들 <br>]]></content><category term="turpee (터피)" label="turpee (터피)"/><category term="puzzle" label="puzzle"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Le_Mans/Catastrofe_No17/</id><title>Le Mans - Catastrofe No.17 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Le_Mans/Catastrofe_No17/" title="Le Mans - Catastrofe No.17 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Suelo pensar a veces <br>Que bien estoy en casa <br>Cuando no estas <br><br>Si nuestra buena suerte <br>Vino a quedarse en nada <br>Por que no te vas]]></content><category term="Le Mans" label="Le Mans"/><category term="Catastrofe No.17" label="Catastrofe No.17"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Le_Mans/La_Balada_De_La_Primavera/</id><title>Le Mans - La Balada De La Primavera - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Le_Mans/La_Balada_De_La_Primavera/" title="Le Mans - La Balada De La Primavera - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Siempre estas a mi lado <br>Bien guardado en mi corazon <br>Ya no se echarte de menos <br>Te llevo dentro alla donde estes <br><br>Junto a ti, de tu mano <br>Eternamente, donde vayas me tendras <br><br>Brilla el sol y a nuestra sombra <br>Pasa el mundo en su soledad <br>Quien me ve solo encuentra <br>En mis ojos <br>El reflejo <br>De tus ojos <br>Alla donde estes <br><br>Descansar en tus brazos <br>Eternamente, en tus palabras, en tu voz <br>En tu mirada, mi amor]]></content><category term="Le Mans" label="Le Mans"/><category term="La Balada De La Primavera" label="La Balada De La Primavera"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Le_Mans/Revelacion/</id><title>Le Mans - Revelacion - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:15:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:15:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Le_Mans/Revelacion/" title="Le Mans - Revelacion - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Quiero que escuches esta cancion <br>Que tanto me gusta oir <br><br>Quiero que aprendas como soy yo <br>Para poderme querer <br><br>Quiero pasar un rato sin ti <br>Pensando en volverte a ver <br><br>Quiero que escuches esta cancion]]></content><category term="Le Mans" label="Le Mans"/><category term="Revelacion" label="Revelacion"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Le_Mans/Mi_Novela_Autobiografica/</id><title>Le Mans - Mi Novela Autobiografica - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:16:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:16:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Le_Mans/Mi_Novela_Autobiografica/" title="Le Mans - Mi Novela Autobiografica - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Suelo despertar con una impresion de infelicidad <br>Me pregunto si en la realidad solo hay ilusion pero nada mas, no hay nada <br>No me hace ilusion la vida formal, la revolucion ni el materialismo <br>Filosofar sobre esta vida y la de alla Que pesadez <br><br>Suelo despertar con una impresion de infelicidad <br>Si pudiera desaparecer esta desazon, si no fuera mas que un mal momento <br>No me hace ilusion ir a trabajar a un gran almacen, ser ingeniera <br>Tampoco veo mi vocacion en la maternidad Que pesadez <br><br>Como puede ser tanta adversidad estorbada por pasatiempos <br>Pocas cosas hay nuevas bajo el sol <br>Y la novedad, tampoco es novedad <br><br>No me hace ilusion esto de escribir, ni de publicar, ser reconocida <br>Tampoco ser la guitarrista de un grupo rock Que pesadez]]></content><category term="Le Mans" label="Le Mans"/><category term="Mi Novela Autobiografica" label="Mi Novela Autobiografica"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/진보라/Bride/</id><title>진보라 - Bride - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:16:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:16:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%84%EB%B3%B4%EB%9D%BC/Bride/" title="진보라 - Bride - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[당신의 신부가 된다는 건 <br>흰 드레스를 입고 <br>꽃관을 쓴 신부일거란 <br>생각은 없죠 <br>그 험한 산도 넘고 <br>골짜길 건너 <br>주 계신 곳 따라가 <br>살아도 주와 함께 있고 <br>죽어도 주와 함께 <br>살아도 주와 함께 있고 <br>죽어도 주와 함께 <br>오 놀라운 영원토록 <br>함께하는 사랑 <br>오 변치 않는 영원함 <br>그 영원함 <br>내 맘을 움직이네 <br>오 변치 않는 그 사랑 <br>그 사랑이 주와 걷게 해 <br>오 변치 않는 영원함 <br>그 영원함 <br>내 맘을 움직이네 <br>오 변치 않는 그 사랑 <br>그 사랑이 주와 걷게 해 <br>당신의 신부가 된다는 건 <br>흰 드레스를 입고 <br>꽃관을 쓴 신부일거란 <br>생각은 없죠 <br>그 험한 산도 넘고 <br>골짜길 건너 <br>주 계신 곳 따라가 <br>]]></content><category term="진보라" label="진보라"/><category term="Bride" label="Bride"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MINUE_노민우/Believe/</id><title>MINUE (노민우) - Believe - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:17:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:17:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MINUE_%EB%85%B8%EB%AF%BC%EC%9A%B0/Believe/" title="MINUE (노민우) - Believe - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This is the only way <br>that I can feel my heart <br>When I see true words <br>through your heart <br>This is the only way <br>that I know where to go <br>When I hear your voice <br>through my dreams <br>Oh If you did not believe me <br>I would have been broken <br>Oh If you did not believe me <br>I would not be here <br>I believe now <br>I believe now <br>I know when I was lost <br>You were the only one <br>oh who believed in me <br>I believe you <br>I believe you <br>Yes your love was my all <br>I would not be here <br>without your love tonight <br>When I think I'm all alone <br>There's no one who sees me <br>You look at me and Say <br>I'm here with you <br>Oh If you did not believe me <br>I would have been broken <br>Oh If you did not believe me <br>I would not be here <br>I believe now <br>I believe now <br>I know when I was lost <br>You were the only one <br>oh who believed in me <br>I believe you <br>I believe you <br>Yes your love was my all <br>I would not be here <br>without your love tonight <br>I believe you <br>I believe you <br>Yes your love was my all <br>I would not be here <br>without your love tonight <br>I believe your voice <br>I believe your voice <br>Yes you are my desire <br>You're why I'm standing here <br>reminds me when you cry <br>This is the only way <br>that I can feel my heart <br>When I feel your love <br>through your heart <br>I miss you <br>Miss you <br>Tonight <br>]]></content><category term="MINUE (노민우)" label="MINUE (노민우)"/><category term="Believe" label="Believe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MINUE_노민우/We_Rock/</id><title>MINUE (노민우) - We Rock - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:17:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:17:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MINUE_%EB%85%B8%EB%AF%BC%EC%9A%B0/We_Rock/" title="MINUE (노민우) - We Rock - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In the air 行くよ (유쿠요) <br>雲の上まで (쿠모노우에마데) <br>In the air 音と (오또또) <br>翼廣げて (츠바사히로게떼) <br><br>WE ROCK! <br>WE ROCK! <br><br>Shoelace ほどけた靴 もつれる足 <br>(호도케따구쯔 모쯔레르아시) <br>全てに 疲れてる その 涕を <br>(스베떼니 츠카레데루 소노 나미다오) <br>拭いて ？明しよう 僕はス-パ-スタ- <br>(후이떼 쇼메이시요우 보쿠와수퍼스타) <br>君を 抱きしめ 空高く飛ぶよ <br>(키미오 다키시메 소라타카쿠 토부요) <br><br>EO EO EO <br>Everybody say <br>EO EO EO <br><br>In the air 行くよ <br>雲の上まで <br>In the air 音と <br>翼廣げて <br><br>Everybody ROCK! <br>Put your hands up in the air dance <br><br>Everybody ROCK! <br>Put your hands up in the air dance <br><br>Everybody ROCK! <br>Put your hands up in the air dance <br><br>Dance <br>Dance <br>Dance <br><br>WE ROCK! <br>WE ROCK! <br><br>Shoelace 結び直す もう泣かない <br>(무스비나오스 모우나카나이) <br>いつでも 君には この歌がついてる <br>(이츠데모 키미니와 코노우타가쯔이떼루) <br><br>EO EO EO <br>Everybody say <br>EO EO EO <br><br>In the air 行くよ <br>雲の上まで <br>In the air 音の <br>翼廣げて <br><br>Everybody ROCK! <br>Put your hands up in the air dance <br><br>Everybody ROCK! <br>Put your hands up in the air dance <br><br>Everybody ROCK! <br>Put your hands up in the air dance <br><br>Dance <br>Dance <br>Dance <br><br>WE ROCK! <br>WE ROCK! <br>WE ROCK! <br>WE ROCK! <br><br>EO EO EO <br>Everybody say <br>EO EO <br>Put your hands up in the air dance <br><br>EO EO EO <br>Everybody say <br>EO EO EO <br><br>In the air 行くよ <br>雲の上まで <br>In the air 音の <br>翼廣げて <br><br>Everybody ROCK! <br>Put your hands up in the air dance <br><br>Everybody ROCK! <br>Put your hands up in the air dance <br><br>Everybody ROCK! <br>Put your hands up in the air dance <br><br>Dance <br>Dance <br>Dance <br><br>WE ROCK! <br>WE ROCK! <br>WE ROCK!]]></content><category term="MINUE (노민우)" label="MINUE (노민우)"/><category term="We Rock" label="We Rock"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MINUE_노민우/Gravity/</id><title>MINUE (노민우) - Gravity - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:17:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:17:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MINUE_%EB%85%B8%EB%AF%BC%EC%9A%B0/Gravity/" title="MINUE (노민우) - Gravity - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm like a falling star tonight <br>We can't be here anymore <br>I'll leave my past full of mistakes <br>but I know that you'll still be there <br><br>See the stars and I will shine <br>but I know waiting love is there <br>We'll never fall in love again <br><br>OH OH OH OH <br>OH OH OH OH <br><br>Free love has gone away <br><br>You said we're the stars <br>and when the sun's down <br>You want us to be <br>Your love is GRAVITY <br><br>抑えられない (오사에라레나이) <br>離れられない (하나레라레나이) <br>君が好き (키미가스키) <br>Your love is GRAVITY <br><br>So why do the shooting stars exist <br>You always lose to gravity <br>And so I will leave this to you <br>In the end I'll still be there <br><br>引き寄せられて (히키요세라레떼) <br>誰も逃げられない (다레모니게라레나이) <br>We'll never fall in love again <br><br>OH OH OH OH <br>OH OH OH OH <br><br>Free love has gone away <br><br>甘い戀 落ちてゆく (아마이코이 오찌떼유쿠) <br>引き寄せる 君の聲に (히키요세루 키미노코에니) <br>抑えられない (오사에라레나이) <br>離れられない (하나레라레나이) <br>君が好き (키미가스키) <br>Youe love is GRAVITY <br><br>Never let me go <br>Never let me go <br>Never let me go <br><br>We'll never fall in love again <br><br>甘い戀 落ちてゆく (아마이코이 오찌떼유쿠) <br>引き寄せる 君の聲に (히키요세루 키미노코에니) <br>抑えられない (오사에라레나이) <br>離れられない (하나레라레나이) <br>君が好き (키미가스키) <br>Youe love is GRAVITY <br><br>OH OH OH OH <br>Your love is GRAVITY <br><br>Your love is GRAVITY <br>OH OH OH OH <br>OH OH OH OH <br>Your love is GRAVITY <br>OH OH OH OH <br>OH OH OH OH]]></content><category term="MINUE (노민우)" label="MINUE (노민우)"/><category term="Gravity" label="Gravity"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slyme_Young/이길_일만_남았지/</id><title>Slyme Young - 이길 일만 남았지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:17:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:17:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slyme_Young/%EC%9D%B4%EA%B8%B8_%EC%9D%BC%EB%A7%8C_%EB%82%A8%EC%95%98%EC%A7%80/" title="Slyme Young - 이길 일만 남았지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm tryna win <br>이제껏 준비해 왔지 <br>상대가 누구던 간에 <br>I'm tryna be yeah <br>who I wanna be <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>uh 이길 일만 남았지 <br>got nuthin' to lose uh <br>yeah I'm with my clique <br>NTL 이제 우리가 다 해먹어 <br>나이를 먹어 <br>포기하는 놈들 사이에 <br>우린 아주 당당히 서있지 <br>꿈을 꾸는 진짜 남자지 <br>내 이름은 <br>Slyme to the Young <br>muhfucker <br>a.k.a Sideburn Chan <br>muhfucker <br>If you don't know <br>now you know uh <br>이제 서서히 알려질 <br>우리의 이름 <br>외워두려 <br>하지 않아도 알게 될걸 <br>다운 받지 않아도 <br>듣게 될걸 넌 묻게 될걸 <br>이 진짜 같은 친구들 <br>누구냐고 <br>우리 노래에 <br>웃고 울게 될걸 <br>이제 여유롭게 박자를 타는 <br>professional <br>작업량도 엄청나지 <br>내년엔 정규를 낼 거고 <br>내년 고딩 들의 플레이리스트엔 <br>NTL이 가득하겠지 ya <br>우린 준비가 됐어 <br>내가 말했지 진짜 <br>이길 일만 남아있지 <br>I'm tryna win <br>이제껏 준비해 왔지 <br>상대가 누구던 간에 <br>I'm tryna be yeah <br>who I wanna be <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>Got nuthin' to lose muhfucker <br>NTL came here to win <br>Got nuthin' to lose muhfucker <br>NTL came here to win <br>Got nuthin' to lose muhfucker <br>NTL came here to win <br>Got nuthin' to lose muhfucker <br>NTL came here to win <br>man Can I get a 인정 <br>Can I get a 박수 uh <br>노력하는 예술가 <br>life of Jean Michel uh <br>영감 많이 받은 MC <br>난 위대하지 Gatsby <br>왁스는 바르지 않고 <br>모자 푹 눌러써 that's me <br>Max B 처럼 I bring the WAVE <br>난 내가 <br>하고 싶은 대로 할거야 <br>누가 뭐라던 지 난 <br>Slyme Young <br>이제야 자유로운 나 <br>이제 당당해 난 <br>independent artist <br>I got money &amp; the power <br>많은 돈 없지만 <br>나만의 힘이 있다고 <br>말 많아 보이지만 <br>그건 내가 할말이 <br>많다는 거지 <br>보드를 타듯이 멋지게 <br>박자를 타지 <br>이미 높은 경지에 <br>왔다는 거지 <br>한참 전에 왔지 다음 <br>단계로 갈 거지 <br>지금 나의 현주소 <br>나도 잘 몰라 넌 <br>나에 대해 말하지마 함부로 <br>매끄러운 내 flow <br>flow sicker than a flu <br>fuck this is how I do <br>얘네 sweeter <br>than a macaron <br>패배자라고 얼굴에 <br>새겨줄게 마카로 uh <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>Got nuthin' to lose muhfucker <br>NTL came here to win <br>Got nuthin' to lose muhfucker <br>NTL came here to win <br>Got nuthin' to lose muhfucker <br>NTL came here to win <br>Got nuthin' to lose muhfucker <br>NTL came here to win <br>I'm tryna win <br>이제껏 준비해왔지 <br>I'm tryna be yeah <br>who I wanna be <br>이길 일만 남았지 <br>]]></content><category term="Slyme Young" label="Slyme Young"/><category term="이길 일만 남았지" label="이길 일만 남았지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slyme_Young/이불_밖은_위험하니까_Feat_몬스타비_원봄/</id><title>Slyme Young - 이불 밖은 위험하니까 (Feat. 몬스타비, 원봄) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:17:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:17:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slyme_Young/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B6%88_%EB%B0%96%EC%9D%80_%EC%9C%84%ED%97%98%ED%95%98%EB%8B%88%EA%B9%8C_Feat_%EB%AA%AC%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80%EB%B9%84_%EC%9B%90%EB%B4%84/" title="Slyme Young - 이불 밖은 위험하니까 (Feat. 몬스타비, 원봄) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이불 밖은 위험하니까 <br>이불 안에서 <br>LET'S MAKE LOVE <br>이불 밖은 위험하니까 <br>이불 안에서 <br>YEAH <br>이불 밖은 위험하니까 <br>이불 안에서 <br>LET'S MAKE LOVE <br>이불 밖은 위험하니까 <br>이불 안에서 <br>YEAH <br>이불 밖은 위험해 <br>현실은 우릴 자꾸만 시험해 <br>YEAH YEAH <br>니 옆에 내가 언제나 있어 <br>DONT BE AFRAID GIRL <br>내 옆에 딱 달라붙어 <br>그래 TWIX처럼 <br>우린 닮았어 TWIN처럼 <br>우린 잘 어울려 <br>BEYONCE와 JAY Z처럼 AH <br>오늘은 그냥 집에 있자 <br>너가 좋아하는 <br>예능도 받아놨어 <br>뭐 먹을래 피자 <br>맛있으면 살 안 쪄 <br>진짜야 괜찮어 <br>맥주 두 병에 <br>우린 알딸딸 해져 <br>널 너무나 사랑해서 난 <br>이불 밖은 위험하니까 <br>이불 안에서 <br>LET'S MAKE LOVE <br>이불 밖은 위험하니까 <br>이불 안에서 <br>YEAH <br>이불 밖은 위험하니까 <br>이불 안에서 <br>LET'S MAKE LOVE <br>이불 밖은 위험하니까 <br>이불 안에서 <br>YEAH <br>아침에 일어나 <br>너의 얼굴을 바라봐 <br>너무 완벽하지 <br>이대로 시간이 멈췄으면 해 <br>하루를 시작하기 <br>싫어 난 더 니 옆에 있고 싶어 <br>너의 향기를 맡고 느끼고 싶어 <br>함께 꿈을 꾸고 싶어 <br>이불 밖에 나가기 싫어 <br>BUT WE KNOW <br>WE GOTTA GO OUT <br>INTO THE WORLD <br>너 없이 보내는 하루는 싫지만 <br>돈은 벌어야 돼 <br>GOTTA GET THAT DOUGH <br>힘든 하루를 마치고 <br>널 보는 것만으로 <br>피곤함이 풀리네 <br>오늘 하루는 어땠어 <br>이제 편하게 숨 쉬어도 돼 <br>딱 붙어 내 옆에 <br>이불 밖은 위험하니까 <br>거기서 도망쳐 여기로 숨어 <br>이불 밖은 위험하니까 <br>어서 빨리 내 옆에 와서 <br>숨쉬어 UH <br>GIRL GIRL GIRL GIRL <br>GIRL GIRL GIRL <br>RIGHT NOW <br>GIRL GIRL GIRL GIRL <br>GIRL GIRL GIRL <br>RIGHT NOW <br>OH YEAH <br>위험해 위험해 위험해 <br>OH YEAH <br>위험해 위험해 <br>UH YEAH <br>SO STAY WITH ME <br>STAY WITH ME GIRL <br>SO STAY WITH ME <br>STAY WITH ME GIRL <br>위험해 위험해 위험해 <br>OH YEAH <br>위험해 위험해 <br>UH YEAH <br>이불 밖은 위험해 <br>이불 밖은 위험해 <br>이불 밖은 위험해 <br>OH YEAH <br>]]></content><category term="Slyme Young" label="Slyme Young"/><category term="이불 밖은 위험하니까 (Feat. 몬스타비, 원봄)" label="이불 밖은 위험하니까 (Feat. 몬스타비, 원봄)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유솜/여름감기_Inst/</id><title>유솜 - 여름감기 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:18:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:18:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EC%86%9C/%EC%97%AC%EB%A6%84%EA%B0%90%EA%B8%B0_Inst/" title="유솜 - 여름감기 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대와 함께 보낸 <br>한 여름날의 기억을 <br>잊지 못한대도 <br>난 괜찮아요 <br>난 괜찮아요 <br>한 여름 열병처럼 <br>지나가버린 그대 <br>침대에 누워 천장에 <br>그려보는 그대 모습 <br>그대와 마주보는 이 순간 <br>이젠 너무 멀게 <br>느껴지는 그대 모습에 <br>마음이 한껏 아려오네 <br>그댄 내게 <br>아픈 손가락 <br>열손가락 중 <br>제일 아픈 손가락 <br>잠시 지나가는 <br>소나기인데 왜 이리 <br>순간 순간이 <br>아픈 걸까요 <br>깨물어서 <br>아픈 손가락 <br>영원히 아플 것만 <br>같은 손가락 <br>잠시 지나가는 <br>사랑이라 해도 <br>이렇게 아플 수도 <br>있는 걸까요 <br>눈만 감으면 선명했던 <br>그대의 뒤척임이 <br>이젠 남아있지 <br>않는대도 괜찮아요 <br>좋게 기억하려 <br>애쓰는 마음에 <br>병이 되버린 거죠 <br>섣불렀던 나의 사랑이 <br>오히려 그대에겐 <br>독이 된 거죠 <br>밤새워 기다린 <br>수많은 날들을 <br>아마 그대는 <br>절대 모를 거예요 <br>오 그댄 나를 <br>잊어도 돼요 <br>이젠 그댈 <br>기다리지 않을래요 <br>한 번 지나가버린 <br>사랑은 또 다시 <br>간절히 바래도 <br>안 되는 거겠죠 <br>오 그댄 내게 <br>아픈 손가락 <br>열손가락 중 <br>제일 아픈 손가락 <br>한여름 뜨겁던 <br>감기일 뿐이죠 <br>음 랄랄라라 <br>]]></content><category term="유솜" label="유솜"/><category term="여름감기 (Inst.)" label="여름감기 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유솜/여름감기/</id><title>유솜 - 여름감기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:18:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:18:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EC%86%9C/%EC%97%AC%EB%A6%84%EA%B0%90%EA%B8%B0/" title="유솜 - 여름감기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대와 함께 보낸 <br>한 여름날의 기억을 <br>잊지 못한대도 <br>난 괜찮아요 <br>난 괜찮아요 <br>한 여름 열병처럼 <br>지나가버린 그대 <br>침대에 누워 천장에 <br>그려보는 그대 모습 <br>그대와 마주보는 이 순간 <br>이젠 너무 멀게 <br>느껴지는 그대 모습에 <br>마음이 한껏 아려오네 <br>그댄 내게 <br>아픈 손가락 <br>열손가락 중 <br>제일 아픈 손가락 <br>잠시 지나가는 <br>소나기인데 왜 이리 <br>순간 순간이 <br>아픈 걸까요 <br>깨물어서 <br>아픈 손가락 <br>영원히 아플 것만 <br>같은 손가락 <br>잠시 지나가는 <br>사랑이라 해도 <br>이렇게 아플 수도 <br>있는 걸까요 <br>눈만 감으면 선명했던 <br>그대의 뒤척임이 <br>이젠 남아있지 <br>않는대도 괜찮아요 <br>좋게 기억하려 <br>애쓰는 마음에 <br>병이 되버린 거죠 <br>섣불렀던 나의 사랑이 <br>오히려 그대에겐 <br>독이 된 거죠 <br>밤새워 기다린 <br>수많은 날들을 <br>아마 그대는 <br>절대 모를 거예요 <br>오 그댄 나를 <br>잊어도 돼요 <br>이젠 그댈 <br>기다리지 않을래요 <br>한 번 지나가버린 <br>사랑은 또 다시 <br>간절히 바래도 <br>안 되는 거겠죠 <br>오 그댄 내게 <br>아픈 손가락 <br>열손가락 중 <br>제일 아픈 손가락 <br>한여름 뜨겁던 <br>감기일 뿐이죠 <br>음 랄랄라라 <br>]]></content><category term="유솜" label="유솜"/><category term="여름감기" label="여름감기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소리보따리/반짝이는_별/</id><title>소리보따리 - 반짝이는 별 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:19:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:19:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC%EB%B3%B4%EB%94%B0%EB%A6%AC/%EB%B0%98%EC%A7%9D%EC%9D%B4%EB%8A%94_%EB%B3%84/" title="소리보따리 - 반짝이는 별 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[캄캄한 밤하늘 빛나는 별들 <br>반짝 반짝 아름답구나 <br>반짝이는 별 반짝이는 별 <br>라라라라 라라라라 <br>라라라 아름답구나 <br>라라라라 라라라라 <br>정말 아름답구나 <br>라라라라 라라라라 <br>정말 아름답구나]]></content><category term="소리보따리" label="소리보따리"/><category term="반짝이는 별" label="반짝이는 별"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소리보따리/하늘에서_눈송이가/</id><title>소리보따리 - 하늘에서 눈송이가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:19:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:19:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC%EB%B3%B4%EB%94%B0%EB%A6%AC/%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C_%EB%88%88%EC%86%A1%EC%9D%B4%EA%B0%80/" title="소리보따리 - 하늘에서 눈송이가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[랄라라 랄랄라 - 눈이 내려요 <br>송이 송이 눈송이가 <br>랄라라 랄랄라 - 눈이 내려요 <br>송이 송이 눈송이가]]></content><category term="소리보따리" label="소리보따리"/><category term="하늘에서 눈송이가" label="하늘에서 눈송이가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소리보따리/흰_눈이_내리는_겨울/</id><title>소리보따리 - 흰 눈이 내리는 겨울 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:19:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:19:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC%EB%B3%B4%EB%94%B0%EB%A6%AC/%ED%9D%B0_%EB%88%88%EC%9D%B4_%EB%82%B4%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8/" title="소리보따리 - 흰 눈이 내리는 겨울 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흰 눈이 내리는 <br>겨울창 밖엔 새하얀 세상 <br>소복소복 소복소복 <br>동글동글 동글동글 <br>떼굴떼굴 떼굴떼굴 <br>눈사람 되었죠]]></content><category term="소리보따리" label="소리보따리"/><category term="흰 눈이 내리는 겨울" label="흰 눈이 내리는 겨울"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/뉴올/Climax_Feat_Justhis/</id><title>뉴올 - Climax (Feat. Justhis) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:19:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:19:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%89%B4%EC%98%AC/Climax_Feat_Justhis/" title="뉴올 - Climax (Feat. Justhis) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No Sunshine No Dreaming <br>No Champagne Oh No <br>No Sunshine No Dreaming <br>No Champagne Oh No <br>Nuol I need a beat yep <br>넌 날 질투하지만 <br>난 필요없어 니 질투가 <br>이건 큰 차이 <br>내 비비안 웨스트우드가 <br>고딩 때 입던 츄리닝과 <br>다르냐면 하나 안 달라 <br>니가 느끼는 <br>나만 바뀐 거지 <br>I'm different 2 Chainz <br>걸었던 적이 없어 <br>I'm still the same person <br>너를 이해하는 <br>나 알아버린 거지 <br>니가 아무리 짜쳐도 <br>내가 옛날에 알던 <br>너는 존재해 나의 평생에 <br>난 그 때를 너무 <br>너무 사랑해서 <br>벗어날 수 없는거야 <br>이 attitude <br>근데 그게 통해 맨 첨에 <br>니가 날 질투한 이유 <br>노스페이스 없이도 <br>쏘다닌 이유 <br>손과 발이 너무 시리는데도 <br>노랠 틀어놓으면 <br>탔지 타임머신을 <br>No Sunshine It's all good <br>No Dreaming It's all good <br>No Champagne what what <br>Oh No One more time yo <br>No Sunshine It's all good <br>No Dreaming It's all good <br>No Champagne what what <br>Oh No <br>But it's all good Why <br>내 친군 아직 내 친구지 <br>Yo it's all good Why <br>내 위에는 상사 없지 <br>내가 boss all good Why <br>I know the pain ain't cheap <br>Yo it's all good <br>Stop askin' why mo' fuckers <br>I'm real real good <br>I'm real real good <br>사람은 다 <br>서로를 이해못해 <br>근데 이해를 구걸하는 <br>너를 이해해 어떻게 <br>현실은 선과 <br>악보다 복잡해 <br>욕하고 난 다음 밤에 <br>천장에 오늘 뱉은 <br>말들이 떠다녀 <br>이걸 참았다 말해주는 <br>사람들 고마워 <br>Check myself all day <br>하지 명상 <br>나는 착한 <br>사람이였나 물어봐 <br>착한 사람 <br>나쁜 사람 어딨어 <br>모두 그냥 사람인거지 <br>위 아래 어딨어 <br>근데 누가 누구를 <br>돈으로 부리는 한 <br>시간의 귀중함은 없는 거지 <br>get it 놓쳤지 <br>모두 기회를 <br>그래서 모두가 <br>노리는 가봐 기회를 <br>그걸 잡아도 문제 <br>누군 지가 누군지도 모르네 <br>But I'm too straight <br>Woo th the music gotta move <br>Woo gotta move <br>Woo th the music gotta move <br>Woo gotta move <br>No Sunshine It's all good <br>No Dreaming It's all good <br>No Champagne what what <br>Oh No One more time yo <br>No Sunshine It's all good <br>No Dreaming It's all good <br>No Champagne what what <br>Oh No <br>But it's all good Why <br>내 친군 아직 내 친구지 <br>Yo it's all good Why <br>내 위에는 상사 없지 <br>내가 boss all good Why <br>I know the pain ain't cheap <br>Yo it's all good <br>Stop askin' why mo' fuckers <br>I'm real real good <br>I'm real real good <br>Stop askin' why mo' fuckers <br>I'm real real good <br>I'm real real good <br>Stop askin' why mo' fuckers <br>I'm real real good <br>I'm real real good <br>]]></content><category term="뉴올" label="뉴올"/><category term="Climax (Feat. Justhis)" label="Climax (Feat. Justhis)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SUZANDO/피아노수리순서/</id><title>SUZANDO - 피아노수리순서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:19:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:19:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SUZANDO/%ED%94%BC%EC%95%84%EB%85%B8%EC%88%98%EB%A6%AC%EC%88%9C%EC%84%9C/" title="SUZANDO - 피아노수리순서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지금부터 내가 알려줄게 <br>피아노수리순서 <br>왜 니가 이걸 알려주냐구 <br>내가 했던 일이거든 <br>들어봐 <br>댐퍼 떨어졌을 시 <br>목공으로 붙이고 <br>본드로 위에 마감 해 <br>그렇게 하면 돼 <br>해머 해머 대는 아랫부분을 <br>롱노우즈로 물어서 <br>부드럽게 만들고 <br>목공용 본드로만 끼워 넣을 것 <br>줄 교체 1 번 <br>줄 길이 만들고 앞에 약간 <br>세 바퀴 반 돌려서 한 옥타브 <br>윗 음 맞추기 <br>풀리는 것 생각해서 <br>그러는 거야 <br>그러니까 잘 돌려서 <br>맞춰놓길 바랄께 <br>다시 한번 내가 알려줄게 <br>피아노 수리 순서 <br>왜 또 알려주냐구 <br>내가 이해 못했거든 <br>들어봐 <br>댐퍼 떨어졌을 시 <br>목공으로 붙이고 <br>본드로 위에 마감해 <br>그렇게 하면 돼 <br>해머 해머 대는 <br>아랫부분을 롱노우즈로 <br>물어서 부드럽게 만들고 <br>목공용 본드로만 끼워 넣을 것 <br>줄 교체 1 번 <br>줄 길이 만들고 <br>앞에 약간 세 바퀴 반 <br>돌려서 한 옥타브 <br>윗 음 맞추기 <br>풀리는 것 생각해서 <br>그러는 거야 <br>그러니까 잘 돌려서 <br>맞춰놓길 바랄께 <br>고음부터 9 13 <br>여기가 끝이야 <br>더 이상 가사 안 나와 <br>어쩔 수 없거든 <br>내가 일을 그만뒀어 <br>음악 한다고 사춘기 <br>아이처럼 뛰쳐나와 <br>지금 보다시피 <br>노래 부르고 있어 <br>댐퍼 떨어졌을 시 <br>댐퍼 떨어졌을 시 <br>해머 해머 대는 <br>해머 해머 대는 <br>댐퍼 댐퍼 <br>댐퍼 댐퍼 <br>해머 해머 <br>해머 해머 <br>줄교체 1 번 <br>줄 길이 만들고 <br>앞에 약간 세 바퀴 반 <br>돌려서 한 옥타브 <br>윗 음 맞추기 <br>풀리는 것 생각해서 <br>그러는 거야 <br>그러니까 잘 돌려서 <br>맞춰놓길 바랄께 <br>댐퍼 댐퍼 빠 빠 빰 <br>해머 해머 빠 빠 빰 <br>댐퍼 댐퍼 빠 빠 빰 <br>해머 해머 빠 빠 빰 <br>]]></content><category term="SUZANDO" label="SUZANDO"/><category term="피아노수리순서" label="피아노수리순서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SUZANDO/오래된_생각/</id><title>SUZANDO - 오래된 생각 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:19:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:19:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SUZANDO/%EC%98%A4%EB%9E%98%EB%90%9C_%EC%83%9D%EA%B0%81/" title="SUZANDO - 오래된 생각 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언제부터인지 모르겠지만 <br>너와의 시간이 의미가 없어졌어 <br>너와 걷던 그 길도 <br>너와 자주 가던 까페도 <br>너와 소풍 갔던 공원도 <br>너와 맞았던 소나기도 <br>너와 걸었던 길 틈엔 꽃이 피었고 <br>까페 소파 아래엔 무서운 고양이 <br>공원에는 비둘기들이 여전하고 <br>추웠던 소나기 다음엔 따뜻한 밤 <br>우 <br>너와 걸었던 길 틈엔 꽃이 피었고 <br>까페 소파 아래엔 무서운 고양이 <br>공원에는 비둘기들이 여전하고 <br>추웠던 소나기 다음엔 따뜻한 밤 <br>언제부터인지 모르겠지만 <br>너와의 시간이 의미가 없어졌어 <br>너와 걷던 그 길도 <br>너와 자주 가던 까페도 <br>너와 소풍 갔던 공원도 <br>너와 맞았던 소나기도 <br>언제부터인지 모르겠지만 <br>미안해 <br>이렇게는 나에게 <br>미안한 일이야 <br>걱정하지마 죽진 않을게 <br>니가 아니어도 난 <br>아 <br>너와 걷던 그 길도 <br>너와 자주 가던 까페도 <br>너와 소풍 갔던 공원도 <br>너와 맞았던 소나기도 <br>]]></content><category term="SUZANDO" label="SUZANDO"/><category term="오래된 생각" label="오래된 생각"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SUZANDO/Am/</id><title>SUZANDO - Am - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:19:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:19:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SUZANDO/Am/" title="SUZANDO - Am - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[에라이 미친놈 <br>에라이 미친놈 <br>에라이 미친놈 <br>에라이 미친놈 <br>에라이 미친놈 <br>에라이 미친놈 <br>에라이 미친놈아 <br>어떤남자와 여자는 <br>길가에서 마주치면 <br>살짝 웃으며 <br>인사를 하지 <br>어떤남자와 여자는 <br>길가에서 마주치면 <br>살짝 안으며 <br>인사를 하지 <br>우우 우우 없어 <br>나는 그런거 <br>어떤 여자와 남자중에 <br>나란 없어 그런거 <br>우우 우우 없어 <br>나는 그런거 <br>어떤 사람을 만나도 <br>나는 그러지 못해 <br>우우 우우 없어 <br>나는 그런거 <br>어떤 여자와 남자중에 <br>나란 없어 그런거 <br>우우 우우 없어 <br>나는 그런거 <br>어떤 사람을 만나도 <br>나는 그러지 못해 <br>에라이 미친놈 <br>에라이 미친놈 <br>에라이 미친놈 <br>에라이 미친놈 <br>에라이 미친놈 <br>에라이 미친놈 <br>에라이 미친놈아 <br>어떤남자와 여자는 <br>길가에서 마주치면 <br>살짝 웃으며 <br>인사를 하지 <br>어떤남자와 여자는 <br>길가에서 마주치면 <br>살짝 안으며 <br>인사를 하지 <br>우우 우우 없어 <br>나는 그런거 <br>어떤 여자와 남자중에 <br>나란 없어 그런거 <br>우우 우우 없어 <br>나는 그런거 <br>어떤 사람을 만나도 <br>나는 그러지 못해 <br>우우 우우 없어 <br>나는 그런거 <br>어떤 여자와 남자중에 <br>나란 없어 그런거 <br>우우 우우 없어 <br>나는 그런거 <br>어떤 사람을 만나도 <br>나는 그러지 못해 <br>에에 에에 에라이 미친놈 <br>나도 사랑을 하고 싶어 <br>에에 에에 에라이 미친놈 <br>하지만 그러지 못해 <br>에에 에에 에라이 미친놈 <br>가슴 아프지만 나는 아직도 <br>에에 에에 에라이 미친놈 <br>내 님을 만나지 못해 <br>오오오오오오 <br>가슴 아파도 <br>오오오오오오 <br>어쩔 수가 없는걸 <br>오오오오오오 <br>가슴 아파도 <br>오오오오오오 <br>어쩔 수가 없는걸 <br>]]></content><category term="SUZANDO" label="SUZANDO"/><category term="Am" label="Am"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/옆집_남자/인사/</id><title>옆집 남자 - 인사 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:19:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:19:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%86%EC%A7%91_%EB%82%A8%EC%9E%90/%EC%9D%B8%EC%82%AC/" title="옆집 남자 - 인사 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[매일 지나치는 너의 집 <br>퇴근길 버스 안에서 우연히 <br>고개를 내밀고 빼꼼히 <br>창 밖을 바라보는 <br>너를 봤지 <br>그게 너무도 아파서인지 <br>한동안 난 그 길을 피했지만 <br>그래도 아쉬움이 미련이 남아서 <br>다시 그 버스 안으로 올랐네 <br>가끔은 이렇게 널 볼 수 있을까 <br>계절이 바뀌고 <br>네 창이 활짝 열릴 때 즈음 <br>매일 난 이렇게 <br>네게 인사를 하지만 <br>보이는 건 불 꺼진 <br>너의 창문 앞 뜰에 그 길가에 <br>앙상하게 남아 있는 <br>우리의 추억들만이 <br>네가 손 흔들던 정류장 <br>반가움과 아쉬움 가득했던 <br>너와 나의 인사는 추억이 되어서 <br>결국 두 개의 창 사이를 맴도네 <br>가끔은 이렇게 널 볼 수 있을까 <br>계절이 바뀌고 <br>네 창이 활짝 열릴 때 즈음 <br>매일 난 이렇게 <br>네게 인사를 하지만 <br>보이는 건 불 꺼진 <br>너의 창문 앞 뜰에 그 길가에 <br>앙상하게 남아 있는 <br>우리의 추억들만이 <br>가끔은 이렇게 널 볼 수 있을까 <br>계절이 바뀌고 <br>네 창이 활짝 열릴 때 즈음 <br>가끔은 이렇게 널 볼 수 있다면 <br>계절이 바뀌고 <br>네 창이 활짝 열리기를 <br>매일 난 꿈꾸며 <br>네게 인사를 하지만 <br>보이는 건 불 꺼진 <br>너의 창문 앞 뜰에 그 길가에 <br>앙상하게 남아 있는 <br>우리의 추억들만이 <br>추억들만이 <br>]]></content><category term="옆집 남자" label="옆집 남자"/><category term="인사" label="인사"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DammitimDrunk/Eyes_On_Me_Inst/</id><title>Dammiti`mDrunk - Eyes On Me (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:19:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:19:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DammitimDrunk/Eyes_On_Me_Inst/" title="Dammiti`mDrunk - Eyes On Me (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>따라쟁이 rappers <br>따라 막 랩을 뱉어 <br>주관 없는 애들 <br>keep your eyes <br>on my zone <br>지키는 건 태도 아닌 <br>유명인들 asshole <br>로또 바라는 새끼 <br>keep your eyes <br>on my zone <br>keep your eyes <br>on my zone <br>어찌 하는지 보라고 <br>Kick Snare도 몰랐던 <br>내가 여기까지 왔다고 <br>노력했다고 생각한적 <br>없지 언제나 즐겨왔으니 <br>괜히 누워서 날길 바라는 <br>새끼들이나 악쓰지 <br>지금은 무릎 꿇고 있지 <br>추진력을 얻기 위해 <br>사냥감 앞에 발톱을 <br>감추는 포식자의 지혜 <br>이제는 때가 된듯해 <br>내가 가진 패를 보여줄게 <br>속임수 없이도 확신에 <br>차있지 난 나를 믿네 <br>실력 없는 놈들이나 <br>두려워하지 실패 <br>만약 이 곡이 안되더라도 <br>난 바로 다음 준비해 <br>이게 너와 나의 차이 <br>check ma sign <br>check ma sign <br>I’m always on ma grind <br>on ma grind <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>이제 verse 2의 차례 <br>지금 나의 모습과 같네 <br>지금까진 그저 준비 단계 <br>이제 돈을 벌기 위해 밖에 <br>자신감이 넘치는 상태 <br>어떻게 해야 할지 알기에 <br>그냥 나답게 어차피 <br>쓰러질 애들 신경 쓰지 않네 <br>여긴 내 적이 없어 <br>그냥 다 나의 zone <br>내 꼴리는 대로 하면 <br>되는 거지 뭐 <br>사랑 노래 하는 <br>Welcome Newdayz 도 <br>하고 싶은 거 잘 하고 있지 <br>언제나 멋있어 <br>뒤를 돌아보기엔 <br>너무 멀리까지 왔지 <br>뭐 애초에 후진할 <br>생각조차 없었지 딱히 <br>난 아직 여기 있는데 <br>도망친 놈이 뭐라 해 감히 <br>패배자들의 충고 따윈 <br>필요하지 않지 <br>ELEV 우리 영역을 <br>구축하는 중 <br>그냥 노는 거야 <br>너와 태도가 좀 다를 뿐 <br>우린 놀기 위해 살고 <br>음악은 내 놀이터 <br>그래서 난 오늘도 <br>goin' hard <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>]]></content><category term="Dammiti`mDrunk" label="Dammiti`mDrunk"/><category term="Eyes On Me (Inst.)" label="Eyes On Me (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DammitimDrunk/Eyes_On_Me/</id><title>Dammiti`mDrunk - Eyes On Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:19:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:19:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DammitimDrunk/Eyes_On_Me/" title="Dammiti`mDrunk - Eyes On Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>따라쟁이 rappers <br>따라 막 랩을 뱉어 <br>주관 없는 애들 <br>keep your eyes <br>on my zone <br>지키는 건 태도 아닌 <br>유명인들 asshole <br>로또 바라는 새끼 <br>keep your eyes <br>on my zone <br>keep your eyes <br>on my zone <br>어찌 하는지 보라고 <br>Kick Snare도 몰랐던 <br>내가 여기까지 왔다고 <br>노력했다고 생각한적 <br>없지 언제나 즐겨왔으니 <br>괜히 누워서 날길 바라는 <br>새끼들이나 악쓰지 <br>지금은 무릎 꿇고 있지 <br>추진력을 얻기 위해 <br>사냥감 앞에 발톱을 <br>감추는 포식자의 지혜 <br>이제는 때가 된듯해 <br>내가 가진 패를 보여줄게 <br>속임수 없이도 확신에 <br>차있지 난 나를 믿네 <br>실력 없는 놈들이나 <br>두려워하지 실패 <br>만약 이 곡이 안되더라도 <br>난 바로 다음 준비해 <br>이게 너와 나의 차이 <br>check ma sign <br>check ma sign <br>I’m always on ma grind <br>on ma grind <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>이제 verse 2의 차례 <br>지금 나의 모습과 같네 <br>지금까진 그저 준비 단계 <br>이제 돈을 벌기 위해 밖에 <br>자신감이 넘치는 상태 <br>어떻게 해야 할지 알기에 <br>그냥 나답게 어차피 <br>쓰러질 애들 신경 쓰지 않네 <br>여긴 내 적이 없어 <br>그냥 다 나의 zone <br>내 꼴리는 대로 하면 <br>되는 거지 뭐 <br>사랑 노래 하는 <br>Welcome Newdayz 도 <br>하고 싶은 거 잘 하고 있지 <br>언제나 멋있어 <br>뒤를 돌아보기엔 <br>너무 멀리까지 왔지 <br>뭐 애초에 후진할 <br>생각조차 없었지 딱히 <br>난 아직 여기 있는데 <br>도망친 놈이 뭐라 해 감히 <br>패배자들의 충고 따윈 <br>필요하지 않지 <br>ELEV 우리 영역을 <br>구축하는 중 <br>그냥 노는 거야 <br>너와 태도가 좀 다를 뿐 <br>우린 놀기 위해 살고 <br>음악은 내 놀이터 <br>그래서 난 오늘도 <br>goin' hard <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>A Keep Your eyes on my zone <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>Eyes On Me Eye-Eyes On Me <br>]]></content><category term="Dammiti`mDrunk" label="Dammiti`mDrunk"/><category term="Eyes On Me" label="Eyes On Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한경일/내_맘을_어떡해_Inst/</id><title>한경일 - 내 맘을 어떡해 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T16:20:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T16:20:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EA%B2%BD%EC%9D%BC/%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%98%EC%9D%84_%EC%96%B4%EB%96%A1%ED%95%B4_Inst/" title="한경일 - 내 맘을 어떡해 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어떻게 그래요 <br>내 맘을 어떡해 <br>아픈 난 어떡해 <br>그렇게 떠나면 <br>눈물뿐인걸 정말 <br>가까이 설 수도 없다는게 <br>곁에서 볼 수가 없다는게 <br>서글퍼 눈물이 <br>멈추질 않아요 <br>하루도 둘이 아닌적 없어 <br>잠시도 아쉬워 했었는데 <br>혼자만 남겨져 <br>그대를 그리워 하죠 <br>어떻게 그래요 <br>내 맘을 어떡해 <br>아픈 난 어떡해 <br>그렇게 떠나면 <br>눈물뿐인걸 정말 <br>낯설게만 느껴지는 하루 <br>이렇게 길줄은 몰랐었어 <br>모든게 그대로 <br>그대만 없을뿐인데 <br>어떻게 그래요 <br>내 맘을 어떡해 <br>아픈 난 어떡해 <br>그렇게 떠나면 <br>눈물뿐인걸 정말 <br>그대없이는 <br>살 수가 없어요 <br>자신이 없어요 <br>이대로 혼자라는 현실이 <br>어떻게 그래요 <br>내 맘을 어떡해 <br>아픈 난 어떡해 <br>그렇게 떠나면 <br>눈물뿐인걸 정말 <br>사랑을 했다면 <br>이렇게 가지마 <br>제발 돌아와줘 <br>바라만 보아도 <br>좋았었잖아 우리 <br>]]></content><category term="한경일" label="한경일"/><category term="내 맘을 어떡해 (Inst.)" label="내 맘을 어떡해 (Inst.)"/></entry></feed>