<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:07:19+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_The_Child/Go_애플_아이패드_프로_iPad_Pro_광고_삽입곡/</id><title>Louis The Child - Go (애플 아이패드 프로 (iPad Pro) 광고 삽입곡) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:07:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:07:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_The_Child/Go_%EC%95%A0%ED%94%8C_%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%ED%8C%A8%EB%93%9C_%ED%94%84%EB%A1%9C_iPad_Pro_%EA%B4%91%EA%B3%A0_%EC%82%BD%EC%9E%85%EA%B3%A1/" title="Louis The Child - Go (애플 아이패드 프로 (iPad Pro) 광고 삽입곡) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Water-thin can't get in <br>What you runnin' for? <br>Where is it you wanna go? <br>Where is it you wanna go <br>Overtime I'm overtime <br>I've heard it all <br>What is it you wanna know? <br>The fuck is it you wanna know <br><br>Filling your head up <br>it won't be better 'till your <br>Filling your head up <br>Filling your head up <br>it won't be better 'till your <br>Filling your head up <br>Where is it you wanna go? <br>Where is it you wanna go? <br>Where is it you wanna go? <br>Where is it you wanna go <br>Where is it you wanna go? <br>Where is it you wanna go <br><br>Walls are thin fallin' in <br>Knockin' down the door <br>Where is it you wanna go? <br>Where is it you wanna go <br>After all the time all the lives <br>I found the fall <br>What is it your waitin' for? <br>The fuck is it you're waitin' for <br><br>Filling your head up <br>it won't be better 'till your <br>Filling your head up <br>Filling your head up <br>it won't be better 'till your <br>Filling your head up <br>Where is it you wanna go? <br>Where is it you wanna go? <br>Where is it you wanna go? <br>Where is it you wanna go <br>Where is it you wanna go? <br>Where is it you wanna go <br><br>Where is it you wanna go? <br>Where is it you wanna go <br>Where is it you wanna go? <br>Where is it you wanna go]]></content><category term="Louis The Child" label="Louis The Child"/><category term="Go (애플 아이패드 프로 (iPad Pro) 광고 삽입곡)" label="Go (애플 아이패드 프로 (iPad Pro) 광고 삽입곡)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LunchMoney_Lewis/HOE_Heaven_On_Earth_Feat_Ty_Dolla_ign/</id><title>LunchMoney Lewis - H.O.E. (Heaven On Earth) (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:07:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:07:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LunchMoney_Lewis/HOE_Heaven_On_Earth_Feat_Ty_Dolla_ign/" title="LunchMoney Lewis - H.O.E. (Heaven On Earth) (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Told my mama that I met a girl <br>That I wanna make my wife <br>She sleepy but she come and see me <br>When I hit her up on a late night <br>I wanna take a bite Klondike <br>You the only one I want in my life <br>She sweet and sexy <br>thick and independent <br>Lookin' at your jeans like <br>How you get up in it baby <br>I can't live a day without you <br>And I swear <br>you're like a dream come true <br>And after all <br>all of the things <br>we've been through <br>Just to put in words <br>a little heaven on <br>heaven on earth <br>Told my daddy <br>That I think I found the girl <br>I wanna have my son with <br>She freaky every time she see me <br>We gon' probably end up making love <br>I gotta have that lil baby love <br>I told lil baby <br>she can trust Dolla yeah <br>I'm just being honest when I tell ya <br>I can't live a day without you <br>And I swear <br>you're like a dream come true <br>And after all <br>all of the things <br>we've been through <br>Just to put in words <br>a little heaven on <br>heaven on earth <br>Heaven heaven <br>heaven on earth heaven <br>You my slice of apple pie <br>My fireworks for 4th of July <br>Your onion booty make me wanna cry <br>Lately have I told you that I love you <br>love you love you <br>I can't live a day without you <br>And I swear <br>you're like a dream come true <br>And after all <br>all of the things <br>we've been through <br>Just to put in words <br>a little heaven on <br>heaven on earth <br>Heaven heaven <br>heaven on earth heaven <br>Just to put in words <br>a little heaven on <br>heaven on earth <br>Heaven <br>Heaven <br>Heaven <br>Heaven on earth <br>]]></content><category term="LunchMoney Lewis" label="LunchMoney Lewis"/><category term="H.O.E. (Heaven On Earth) (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign)" label="H.O.E. (Heaven On Earth) (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤오/단_한사람_Inst/</id><title>윤오 - 단 한사람 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:08:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:08:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%98%A4/%EB%8B%A8_%ED%95%9C%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C_Inst/" title="윤오 - 단 한사람 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 함께 걷던 그 길 <br>자꾸 떠올라서 <br>어느새 난 니 생각에 <br>혼자 걸어봤어 <br>온통 너로 물든 거리 <br>그 하늘 아래서 <br>오늘도 난 바보처럼 <br>또 웃고 있었지 <br>멀리 반짝이는 <br>햇살 닮은 <br>눈부신 니 모습 <br>아이처럼 너만을 <br>원하는 한 사람 <br>그대여 그대여 <br>그댈 만난 이후로 <br>나의 모든 세상이 <br>다시 태어난 거죠 <br>사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>내 소중한 사람 <br>그대만 늘 지켜줄게요 <br>매일 아침 니 생각에 <br>설레이는 하루 <br>내일도 난 오늘처럼 <br>또 웃고 있겠지 <br>멀리 한걸음씩 <br>다가오는 <br>눈부신 니 모습 <br>오랜 시간 꿈꿔온 <br>단 하나의 사랑 <br>그대여 그대여 <br>그댈 만난 이후로 <br>나의 모든 세상이 <br>다시 태어난 거죠 <br>사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>내 소중한 사람 <br>그대만 늘 지켜줄게요 <br>시간이 흘러도 <br>그대 사랑 하나로 <br>나의 모든 세상이 <br>더 아름다운 거죠 <br>오늘도 또 내일도 <br>나 사랑할게요 <br>그댄 나의 소중한 사람 <br>그대만이 소중한 사람 <br>그댈 사랑하는 한 사람 <br>]]></content><category term="윤오" label="윤오"/><category term="단 한사람 (Inst.)" label="단 한사람 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤오/단_한사람/</id><title>윤오 - 단 한사람 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:08:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:08:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%98%A4/%EB%8B%A8_%ED%95%9C%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C/" title="윤오 - 단 한사람 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 함께 걷던 그 길 <br>자꾸 떠올라서 <br>어느새 난 니 생각에 <br>혼자 걸어봤어 <br>온통 너로 물든 거리 <br>그 하늘 아래서 <br>오늘도 난 바보처럼 <br>또 웃고 있었지 <br>멀리 반짝이는 <br>햇살 닮은 <br>눈부신 니 모습 <br>아이처럼 너만을 <br>원하는 한 사람 <br>그대여 그대여 <br>그댈 만난 이후로 <br>나의 모든 세상이 <br>다시 태어난 거죠 <br>사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>내 소중한 사람 <br>그대만 늘 지켜줄게요 <br>매일 아침 니 생각에 <br>설레이는 하루 <br>내일도 난 오늘처럼 <br>또 웃고 있겠지 <br>멀리 한걸음씩 <br>다가오는 <br>눈부신 니 모습 <br>오랜 시간 꿈꿔온 <br>단 하나의 사랑 <br>그대여 그대여 <br>그댈 만난 이후로 <br>나의 모든 세상이 <br>다시 태어난 거죠 <br>사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>내 소중한 사람 <br>그대만 늘 지켜줄게요 <br>시간이 흘러도 <br>그대 사랑 하나로 <br>나의 모든 세상이 <br>더 아름다운 거죠 <br>오늘도 또 내일도 <br>나 사랑할게요 <br>그댄 나의 소중한 사람 <br>그대만이 소중한 사람 <br>그댈 사랑하는 한 사람 <br>]]></content><category term="윤오" label="윤오"/><category term="단 한사람" label="단 한사람"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/새하얀_거짓말/작은_고백/</id><title>새하얀 거짓말 - 작은 고백 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:18:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:18:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%83%88%ED%95%98%EC%96%80_%EA%B1%B0%EC%A7%93%EB%A7%90/%EC%9E%91%EC%9D%80_%EA%B3%A0%EB%B0%B1/" title="새하얀 거짓말 - 작은 고백 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[스쳐가는 별들에게 물었어 <br>왜 난 혼자여야 해 <br>너의 눈은 그를 향해 있었고 <br>나의 맘은 무너져 <br>내게도 기회를 줘 <br>오늘만큼은 네게 말을 할거야 <br>너를 사랑한다고 <br>헝클어진 머릴 단정히 하고 <br>너에게로 걸어가 <br>이게 아닌데 얼어버린 내 입은 <br>말을 하지 못 해 <br>숨겨왔던 나의 작은 고백은 <br>별이 되어 사라져가 <br>흘러가는 별들에게 말했어 <br>내 마음을 전해줘 <br>너의 눈 속에 담긴 그 사람이 <br>사실 나였으면 해 <br>내게도 기회를 줘 <br>오늘만큼은 네게 말을 할거야 <br>너를 사랑한다고 <br>헝클어진 머릴 단정히 하고 <br>너에게로 걸어가 <br>이게 아닌데 얼어버린 내 입은 <br>말을 하지 못 해 <br>숨겨왔던 나의 작은 고백은 <br>별이 되어 사라져가 <br>오늘만큼은 네게 말을 할거야 <br>너를 사랑한다고 <br>헝클어진 머릴 단정히 하고 <br>너에게로 걸어가 <br>이게 아닌데 얼어버린 내 입은 <br>말을 하지 못 해 <br>숨겨왔던 나의 작은 사랑은 <br>별이 되어 사라져가 <br>]]></content><category term="새하얀 거짓말" label="새하얀 거짓말"/><category term="작은 고백" label="작은 고백"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Art_Of_Anarchy/The_Madness/</id><title>Art Of Anarchy - The Madness - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:19:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:19:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Art_Of_Anarchy/The_Madness/" title="Art Of Anarchy - The Madness - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm frozen within the ice and bitter wind <br>I'm far from blameless <br>Left alone to the beginning of the end <br>As seconds bleed down everyone <br>I can't stop counting <br>I'm lost in a free fall <br>But I'm not free at all <br><br>The otherside of fear is freedom <br>The otherside of pain is healing <br>The madness keeps me from the otherside <br>The truth, the lie, the shame, the glory <br>The love, the hate, an endless story <br>The madness or the otherside <br><br>I'm running into the sun <br>And it's burning me <br>Feeling touched by heaven and all I see <br>Are just illusions that are real to me <br>There's an angel leading me along <br>An endless highway <br>I left all I love behind <br>Killing me inside <br><br>The otherside of fear is freedom <br>The otherside of pain is healing <br>The madness keeps me from the otherside <br>The truth, the lie, the shame, the glory <br>The love, the hate, an endless story <br>The madness or the otherside <br><br>The madness <br>The otherside <br><br>The otherside of fear is freedom <br>The otherside of pain is healing <br>The madness keeps me from the otherside <br>The truth, the lie, the shame, the glory <br>The love, the hate, an endless story <br>The madness or the otherside]]></content><category term="Art Of Anarchy" label="Art Of Anarchy"/><category term="The Madness" label="The Madness"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Art_Of_Anarchy/No_Surrender/</id><title>Art Of Anarchy - No Surrender - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:19:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:19:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Art_Of_Anarchy/No_Surrender/" title="Art Of Anarchy - No Surrender - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I no longer burn inside <br>Washed away that night when I realized <br>The supernatural crossed the great divide <br>Take a breath <br>Breathe in life <br>There's no time to lose your mind <br>Time has stopped <br>Time to choose <br>This could be the end of you <br>This could be the end of you <br><br>No way out <br>Hit the flatline <br>We get up no surrender <br>It's your time <br>Grab the lifeline <br>We get up up no surrender <br>No surrender <br><br>Slowly I kneel before you <br>A final farewell say my last goodbye <br>The heavens open up with blinding light <br>Hold on tight <br>Cling to life <br>Stills are flashing before your eyes <br>Time has stopped <br>Time to choose <br>This could be the end of you <br>This could be the end of you <br><br>No way out <br>Hit the flatline <br>We get up no surrender <br>It's your time <br>Grab the lifeline <br>We get up no surrender <br>No surrender <br><br>Time has stopped <br>Time to choose <br>This could be the end of you <br>Time has stopped <br>Time to choose <br>This could be the end of you <br><br>No way out <br>Hit the flatline <br>We get up no surrender <br>It's your time <br>Grab the lifeline <br>We get up no surrender <br>No way out <br>Hit the flatline <br>We get up no surrender <br>We get up no surrender <br>We get up no surrender <br>No surrender]]></content><category term="Art Of Anarchy" label="Art Of Anarchy"/><category term="No Surrender" label="No Surrender"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Art_Of_Anarchy/Echo_Of_A_Scream/</id><title>Art Of Anarchy - Echo Of A Scream - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:19:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:19:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Art_Of_Anarchy/Echo_Of_A_Scream/" title="Art Of Anarchy - Echo Of A Scream - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Blurred out vision <br>A losing premonition <br>Of the day I knew would come <br>Souls gone missing <br>Gave up on the wishing <br>When I killed the seventh son <br>Heart <br>Racing <br>Just don't know what I'm chasing <br>Lights are fading <br>And I'm just imitating <br>The man they want me to be <br>Landed in the fire <br>Of the sinners and the liars <br>And a burned out history <br>I can't hear you <br>I don't fear you <br>I can't hear you <br>I don't fear you <br>Lost I can't make out a sound <br>No rhythm in a dying dream <br>Lost and I'll never be found <br>I'm just an echo of a scream <br>Tomorrows bleeding <br>And yesterday is leaving <br>Like the ghost in the new machine <br>Days got stolen <br>Nights got woven <br>Into waves that you've never seen <br>One voice in my head <br>Says this is the end <br>Not listening <br>I'm not listening <br>I can't hear you <br>I don't fear you <br>I can't hear you <br>I don't fear you <br>Lost I can't make out a sound <br>No rhythm in a dying dream <br>Lost and I'll never be found <br>I'm just an echo of a scream <br>I'm just an echo of a scream <br>Lost I can't make out a sound <br>No rhythm in a dying dream <br>Lost and I'll never be found <br>I'm just an echo of a scream <br>Lost I can't make out a sound <br>No rhythm in a dying dream <br>Lost and I'll never be found <br>I'm just an echo of a scream <br>I'm just an echo of a scream <br>OF A SCREAMMMMMM]]></content><category term="Art Of Anarchy" label="Art Of Anarchy"/><category term="Echo Of A Scream" label="Echo Of A Scream"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/AJR/Im_Not_Famous/</id><title>AJR - I`m Not Famous - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:19:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:19:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/AJR/Im_Not_Famous/" title="AJR - I`m Not Famous - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Where my haters? <br>Where my haters? <br>I don't got 'em <br>I'm not famous, no <br>It don't matter what my name is <br>I don't got one, I'm not famous, no <br>And I don't hate it, no <br>You never heard of me <br>Or the weird shit I do and say <br>That's my favorite thing <br>That I'm not famous, no <br>And I'm never on T.V. <br>Throwing up on an L.A. street <br>Nobody judges me <br>'Cause I'm not famous, no <br>Paparazzi is at an all-time low <br>Paparazzi they don't care where I go <br>Where my haters <br>Where my haters? <br>I don't got 'em <br>I'm not famous, no <br>It don't matter what my name is <br>I don't got one, I'm not famous, no <br>And I don't hate it, no <br>I'm not famous, no <br>I'm not famous, no <br>I'm not famous, no <br>And I don't hate it, no <br>You never overheard <br>That I blew twenty grand on shirts <br>Nobody knows my quirks <br>'Cause I'm not famous, no <br>Everyone got their habits <br>But you'll never hear what mine is <br>Best thing bout my life is <br>I'm not famous, no <br>Paparazzi is at an all-time low <br>Paparazzi, they don't care where I go <br>Where my haters? <br>Where my haters? <br>I don't got 'em <br>I'm not famous, no <br>It don't matter what my name is <br>I don't got one, I'm not famous, no <br>And I don't hate it, no <br>I'm not famous, no <br>I'm not famous, no (Go!) <br>I'm not famous, no <br>And I don't hate it, no <br>Hate it, hate, hate it, no <br>Hate it, hate, hate it <br>Where my haters? <br>Where my haters? <br>I don't got 'em <br>I'm not famous, no <br>It don't matter what my name is <br>I don't got one, I'm not famous, no <br>(I'm not, I'm not) <br>And I don't hate it, no <br>I'm not famous, no <br>I'm not famous, no <br>I'm not famous, no <br>And I don't hate it, no <br>And I don't hate it, no <br>I'm not famous, no]]></content><category term="AJR" label="AJR"/><category term="I`m Not Famous" label="I`m Not Famous"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/AJR/Weak/</id><title>AJR - Weak - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:20:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:20:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/AJR/Weak/" title="AJR - Weak - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["No thank you" is what I should've said, I should be in bed <br>But temptations of trouble on my tongue, troubles yet to come <br>One sip, bad for me <br>One hit, bad for me <br>One kiss, bad for me <br>But I give in so easily <br>And no thank you is how it should've gone <br>I should stay strong <br>But I'm weak, and what's wrong with that? <br>Boy, oh boy I love it when I fall for that <br>I'm weak, and what's wrong with that? <br>Boy, oh boy I love ya when I fall for that <br>I'm weak <br>But I'm weak, and what's wrong with that? <br>Boy, oh boy I love ya when I fall for that <br>(Boy, oh boy I love ya when I fall for that) <br>No thank you <br>They call me after dark, I don't want no part <br>My habits, they hold me like a grudge <br>I promise I won't budge <br>One sip, bad for me <br>One hit, bad for me <br>One kiss, bad for me <br>But I give in so easily <br>And no thank you is how it should've gone <br>I should stay strong <br>But I'm weak, and what's wrong with that? <br>Boy, oh boy I love ya when I fall for that <br>I'm weak, and what's wrong with that? <br>Boy, oh boy I love ya when I fall for that <br>I'm weak <br>But I'm weak, and what's wrong with that? <br>Boy, oh boy I love ya when I fall for that <br>We, we fall for that <br>Wake up, we fall again <br>We, we fall for that <br>Can't wait to fall again <br>One sip, bad for me <br>One hit, bad for me <br>One kiss, bad for me <br>But I give in so easily <br>And no thank you is how it should've gone <br>I should stay strong <br>But I'm weak, and what's wrong with that? <br>Boy, oh boy I love ys when I fall for that <br>I'm weak, and what's wrong with that? <br>Boy, oh boy I love ya when I fall for that <br>I'm weak <br>Go! <br>But I'm weak, and what's wrong with that? <br>Boy, oh boy I love ya when I fall for that]]></content><category term="AJR" label="AJR"/><category term="Weak" label="Weak"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/쿠마파크/STARLIGHT_Remastering_Feat_G2_JUSTHIS/</id><title>쿠마파크 - STARLIGHT (Remastering) (Feat. G2, JUSTHIS) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:20:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:20:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BF%A0%EB%A7%88%ED%8C%8C%ED%81%AC/STARLIGHT_Remastering_Feat_G2_JUSTHIS/" title="쿠마파크 - STARLIGHT (Remastering) (Feat. G2, JUSTHIS) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[별들보다 익숙해진 <br>도시 속에 불빛 <br>요즘 따라 하늘보다 <br>보는 주변 눈치 <br>나이 하나씩 먹을수록 <br>달라지는 눈빛 <br>나도 날 몰라 <br>얼굴이란 가면 속에 숨지 <br>tryn not to lose myself <br>in this concrete jungle <br>called seoul <br>and sometimes I feel like <br>it's not even worth it no more <br>But I know <br>This is just somethin <br>I gotta conquer <br>더 큰 그림 위해 <br>도시에 바치는 내 청춘 <br>뭔가 내 귓속에 속삭여 <br>지금 좆같아도 괜찮다며 <br>믿어 달래 곧 나져 <br>나만 모르게 지금 손안에 <br>지어 쥘 거라고 more power <br>무언가 내게 또 말해 더 싸워 <br>빌어먹을 세상 it's ours <br>뭔 확신인지 모르겠지만 <br>믿고 손을 모아 <br>시컴한 하늘 위를 난 바라봐 <br>눈감고 나니 <br>똑같은 목소리가 또 들려 <br>깨달았지 그토록 찾았던 <br>별이 나란걸 <br>별들보다 익숙해진 <br>도시의 불빛 <br>우린 우리가 뭘 <br>놓쳤는지 까먹었지 <br>소원 빌어 지나가는 <br>자동차 불빛에 <br>It was all a dream <br>but turn into reality <br>별들보다 익숙해진 <br>도시의 불빛 <br>우린 우리가 뭘 <br>놓쳤는지 까먹었지 <br>소원 빌어 지나가는 <br>자동차 불빛에 <br>It was all a dream <br>but turn into reality <br>하기 싫은 거라도 <br>해야만 하는 것 즈음에 <br>산다는 나의 친구들은 <br>나를 하고 싶은 걸 하며 즈음에 <br>분류해놓고 만나 불편해 <br>근데 내가 볼 때 우린 말야 <br>인생이 어쩌다 이렇게 즈음에 <br>살고 있다고 느껴지는데 말야 <br>그래 넌 너고 난 나지 <br>peace out 삼켰어 <br>하고 싶던 말들 <br>너무 많이 삼켜서 <br>하고 싶던 말들이 <br>먹기 싫은 약처럼 <br>목구멍 중간쯤 <br>껴있는 기분 <br>필요해 relax <br>그래서 또 약을 먹지 <br>What a life of pi <br>Time don't stand <br>still so we gotta move on <br>On and on <br>마치 잠들었다 눈 떴을 때 <br>노트북처럼 항상 켜있는 내 인생 <br>They say <br>His workflow is insane <br>But I ain't proud at all <br>이 꿈이 내 꿈 <br>아님 깰래 잠에서 <br>It was all a dream <br>But turn into reality <br>우린 우리가 놓친 걸 알지만 <br>정확히 뭘 놓쳤는진 까먹었지 <br>마치 새벽 두 세시쯤에 <br>옥상에 누워 <br>별보고 빌었던 <br>소원 썰을 내가 풀면 <br>우리가 언제 <br>그랬었냐는 너희를 보며 <br>나도 꺼내버린 <br>주머니 속 스마트폰처럼 <br>두 손은 모았지만 소원 못 빌어 <br>옥상에 올랐지만 하늘은 시커메 <br>지나가는 자동차 <br>불빛에 소원 빌어 <br>별들보다 익숙해진 <br>도시의 불빛 <br>우린 우리가 뭘 <br>놓쳤는지 까먹었지 <br>소원 빌어 지나가는 <br>자동차 불빛에 <br>It was all a dream <br>but turn into reality <br>별들보다 익숙해진 <br>도시의 불빛 <br>우린 우리가 뭘 <br>놓쳤는지 까먹었지 <br>we look into the city <br>only darkness in the sky <br>That’s why we pray <br>into them city lights <br>카메라가 쫓아다니는 아이들 <br>그건 cctv 혹은 아이폰 <br>각자 철학들이 <br>자기만의 바이블 <br>사회 속엔 룰이 없어 <br>It’s a survival <br>학교에서 배운걸 <br>쓴 적이 없어 아직두 <br>I'm not trippin <br>눈 크게 뜨고 봐 이걸 <br>어릴 적 상상만 했던 <br>곳에 내가 와있어 <br>That’s why we pray <br>to them city lights <br>Move thru the city lights <br>Our truth be the city lights <br>니넨 몰라 나의 진실함 <br>허나 그걸 신경 안 쓰는 게 <br>내가 있는 레벨이지 aight <br>we look into the city <br>only darkness in the sky <br>That’s why we pray <br>into them city lights <br>별들보다 익숙해진 <br>도시의 불빛 <br>우린 우리가 뭘 <br>놓쳤는지 까먹었지 <br>소원 빌어 지나가는 <br>자동차 불빛에 <br>It was all a dream <br>but turn into reality <br>별들보다 익숙해진 <br>도시의 불빛 <br>우린 우리가 뭘 <br>놓쳤는지 까먹었지 <br>소원 빌어 지나가는 <br>자동차 불빛에 <br>It was all a dream <br>but turn into reality <br>]]></content><category term="쿠마파크" label="쿠마파크"/><category term="STARLIGHT (Remastering) (Feat. G2, JUSTHIS)" label="STARLIGHT (Remastering) (Feat. G2, JUSTHIS)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/쿠마파크/WALKIN_Feat_NUCK_넋업샨_수다쟁이/</id><title>쿠마파크 - WALKIN` (Feat. NUCK (넋업샨), 수다쟁이) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:20:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:20:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BF%A0%EB%A7%88%ED%8C%8C%ED%81%AC/WALKIN_Feat_NUCK_%EB%84%8B%EC%97%85%EC%83%A8_%EC%88%98%EB%8B%A4%EC%9F%81%EC%9D%B4/" title="쿠마파크 - WALKIN` (Feat. NUCK (넋업샨), 수다쟁이) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 이 바닥에서 몇 년째 몇 세대 <br>혹은 뭘 이뤄 냈고 뭘 잃었는지 <br>누가 요즘 대세 <br>전혀 관심 없고 그딴 거 일없어 <br>필요한 지도는 <br>이미 다 거의 대충 귀로 읽었어 <br>MC 길고 길었던 삶 속에 <br>나 한숨 따위 쉴 곳이 없어 <br>이 미련했던 어법 <br>형체는 사라지고 내 목소리만 <br>남아서 숨쉬고 죽어 <br>이게 내 운명이라 나발을 불어 <br>나만 흔들어 대는 거 같다지만 <br>누구에게나 다 거들먹거리지 <br>치명적인 이쁜 유혹들 깃든 눈웃음 <br>그 새끼는 조심하라고 했지 <br>끄덕거리는 고개짓 <br>이제 뭘 하라고 니가 뭘 알았건 <br>그건 내 입에서 나온 건지는 <br>나도 모른다고 <br>사뿐히 리듬에 산책하듯 쓴 게 <br>입 밖으로 뱉어보니까 <br>또 진하게 더 쓰네 <br>Boy Alright <br>좋아 느려도 너와나 <br>그냥 가볍게 Oh baby <br>Let's walkin' around <br>Boy Alright <br>좋아 느려도 너와나 <br>그냥 가볍게 Oh baby <br>Let's walkin' around <br>]]></content><category term="쿠마파크" label="쿠마파크"/><category term="WALKIN` (Feat. NUCK (넋업샨), 수다쟁이)" label="WALKIN` (Feat. NUCK (넋업샨), 수다쟁이)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/쿠마파크/WHAT__Feat_Qim_Isle/</id><title>쿠마파크 - WHAT? (Feat. Qim Isle) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:20:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:20:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BF%A0%EB%A7%88%ED%8C%8C%ED%81%AC/WHAT__Feat_Qim_Isle/" title="쿠마파크 - WHAT? (Feat. Qim Isle) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마치 처음으로 파도를 타듯 <br>전혀 갈피를 잡지 못하는 <br>불안 심리의 새벽 2시 <br>난 여전히 부동의 자세로 <br>Just waiting for the right rhymes <br>어쩜 게으른 나에겐 <br>지나치게 두꺼운 <br>이 공책에 빠른 속도로 <br>진하게 스며드는 <br>잉크와 같이 빼곡히 채워지듯 <br>검어지는 my lung <br>형광등 아래에 시끄러운 곡선을 <br>그리는 연기에 인상을 <br>찌푸리며 I think <br>is it the smoke or <br>is it my thoughts dirty <br>진짜 빛이 비추려 한 건 뭔지 <br>I've been thinkin' all morning <br>피곤이 막 몰려오네 <br>어지럼증을 느끼며 어릴 적엔 <br>아마도 반쯤 <br>이해했을 랩을 난 뱉어 <br>Still lost in their translations <br>그들에 환각에서 <br>이때 난 두 눈이 다 마주쳐 <br>방 한 켠 사악한 미소를 띄운 <br>To be continued <br>I dived in to swim good <br>But we're drowning drowning <br>I dived in to swim good <br>But we're drowning drowning <br>Christ will hold you down <br>그가 점 찍은 스타가 <br>너라면 계단 없이 <br>구름에 닿아 두둥실 낮춰 <br>아니라면 네 지적 수준 <br>깊게 갈 필요 없어 <br>걍 맞춰 다 매스컴에 <br>리틀 포르노 그래피 예 폭력 예 <br>Drug money car be alcoholic 예 <br>우스운 모자와 또 걸음걸이 예 <br>Abuse women <br>go call 'em all hoes and bit <br>이때 난 마이크를 뺐고 <br>흥분을 뱉어 <br>Rappers could better themselves up <br>이곳에 시간이 몇 신줄 안다면 <br>2017 and it's not about the image <br>It's all about the being &amp; freeing <br>우리 정신을 온갖 차별 <br>폭력과 편견에서 <br>너는 자유를 외치고는 <br>슬쩍 칼을 꺼냈어 <br>With all that much of violence <br>What the fuck you trying to say <br>Seoul City's snowing dust <br>Made of human skins <br>I dived in to swim good <br>But we're drowning drowning <br>I dived in to swim good <br>But we're drowning drowning <br>]]></content><category term="쿠마파크" label="쿠마파크"/><category term="WHAT? (Feat. Qim Isle)" label="WHAT? (Feat. Qim Isle)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/쿠마파크/SUNSHINE_Feat_Paloalto/</id><title>쿠마파크 - SUNSHINE (Feat. Paloalto) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:20:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:20:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BF%A0%EB%A7%88%ED%8C%8C%ED%81%AC/SUNSHINE_Feat_Paloalto/" title="쿠마파크 - SUNSHINE (Feat. Paloalto) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈을 감아줘 <br>나를 원한다면 <br>나를 잡아줘 <br>네가 원한다면 <br>손을 잡아줘 <br>나를 원한다면 <br>가져도 좋아 <br>네가 원한다면 <br>네가 원한다면 <br>네가 원한다면 <br>네가 원한다면 <br>i've got the sunshine <br>you've got the moonlight <br>we've got the right <br>i could be the sunshine <br>you could be the moonlight <br>we can make it right <br>i've got the sunshine <br>you've got the moonlight <br>we've got the right <br>i could be the sunshine <br>you could be the moonlight <br>we can make it right <br>너는 해 나는 달 서로 <br>참 달랐던 하늘 <br>근데 우리 만난 순간 <br>기적이 이뤄진거야 <br>한참을 헤매던 밤 결국엔 하나된 밤 <br>너도 원했고 나 역시 원했지 <br>이게 사랑인가봐 <br>smile happiness 그림을 그려 <br>우린 누려 기쁨과 만족에 흠뻑젖어 <br>낮과 밤 사이를 누벼 <br>오직 두명 이 공간에 둘 뿐이야 <br>모두 공유해 마치 투명 <br>벗어던졌지 부끄러움 <br>삼켰지 빛을 eclipse <br>뒤섞인 이 느낌 mystic <br>불확실함과 속임수로부터 <br>자유로운 듯이 <br>eclipse 뒤섞인 이 느낌 mystic <br>달이 태양을 감추듯한 몸짓 일식 <br>eclipse 뒤섞인 이 느낌 mystic <br>불확실함과 속임수로부터 <br>자유로운 듯이 <br>eclipse 뒤섞인 이 느낌 mysitc <br>눈 감으면 비로소 보게돼 <br>현실 아닌 신비 <br>i've got the sunshine <br>you've got the moonlight <br>we've got the right <br>i could be the sunshine <br>you could be the moonlight <br>we can make it right <br>]]></content><category term="쿠마파크" label="쿠마파크"/><category term="SUNSHINE (Feat. Paloalto)" label="SUNSHINE (Feat. Paloalto)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/쿠마파크/WE_GOT_THE_LUV_Remastering_Feat_damiankim_Young_Vinyls/</id><title>쿠마파크 - WE GOT THE LUV (Remastering) (Feat. damiankim, Young Vinyls) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:20:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:20:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BF%A0%EB%A7%88%ED%8C%8C%ED%81%AC/WE_GOT_THE_LUV_Remastering_Feat_damiankim_Young_Vinyls/" title="쿠마파크 - WE GOT THE LUV (Remastering) (Feat. damiankim, Young Vinyls) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Why you wanna be <br>the hip hop rapper <br>microphone checker <br>그에 대한 답인 이 가사를 내뱉어 <br>내가 존경하는 Nas and the Premo <br>나 감히 <br>고민 답 없이 다 덤빈다 뭐 <br>믿고 가는 벗 <br>뭣도 모른 날 이끌어준 빽 <br>yeah luv jones <br>get lucky 어깨에 걸친 내 간판은 <br>밝게 빛나지 always YV <br>YV 흔들리는 길을 걸어 <br>천천히 가도 확실한 이 걸음마 <br>하지만 언젠가 다 지날 <br>유행이라는 우려엔 조그맣게 <br>미소를 짓고 딛고 올라설 그때를 봐 <br>어차피 나조차 몰랐던 때도 <br>날 섰던 태도 <br>여전히 같이 한 채로 <br>Luv Jones 이름을 새롭게 붙여 <br>Hold up Y to V is on the beat <br>And we are with our new team <br>bringing the heat <br>LJ the king is back home <br>Vets and young bloods <br>we all in that zone <br>향수에 젖은 멜로디로 <br>우린 승부를 봐 <br>20년전의 전성기로 분위길 돌려놔 <br>우린 제일 잘 알아 <br>that feeling <br>and what its all about <br>새 시대의 roc boys come on <br>we in the house <br>I was in da house what <br>now I'm rolling in the PARK side <br>이건 삶 꿈이 아냐 잠 다 잤어 <br>나를 봐 난 하지말라던게 좋았기에 <br>so 여기까지 왔어 <br>now I'm rockin with dj noah <br>난 문을 두드리다 깨 이제 <br>내 지난 날의 페이백 <br>that's not in maybach <br>내 목소린 체급을 올려 <br>now i'm heavtweight <br>LJ three oh you know <br>how we deal wit that <br>Now put some drums on it <br>Now put some bass on it <br>Now put some jazz on it <br>Now put some uh on it <br>Now put some drums on it <br>Now put some bass on it <br>Now put some jazz on it <br>Now let the Dj put scratch on it <br>]]></content><category term="쿠마파크" label="쿠마파크"/><category term="WE GOT THE LUV (Remastering) (Feat. damiankim, Young Vinyls)" label="WE GOT THE LUV (Remastering) (Feat. damiankim, Young Vinyls)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/AKUA_아쿠아/PLEASE_NEXT/</id><title>AKUA (아쿠아) - PLEASE NEXT - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:20:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:20:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/AKUA_%EC%95%84%EC%BF%A0%EC%95%84/PLEASE_NEXT/" title="AKUA (아쿠아) - PLEASE NEXT - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[when we keep in love <br>so greatly i'll shine <br>when i swim in you <br>so brightly like ruby <br>when we keep in love <br>so greatly I'll shine <br>when i swim in you <br>so brightly like ruby <br>still in love with you <br>will be alright be alright <br>lay your hands on me <br>will be alright be alright <br>when we keep in love <br>so greatly I'll shine <br>when i swim in you <br>so brightly like ruby <br>when we keep in love <br>so greatly I'll shine <br>when i swim in you <br>so brightly like ruby <br>when we keep in love <br>so greatly I'll shine <br>when i swim in you <br>so brightly like ruby <br>when we keep in love <br>so greatly I'll shine <br>when i swim in you <br>so brightly like ruby <br>when we keep in love <br>so greatly I'll shine <br>when i swim in you <br>so brightly like ruby <br>]]></content><category term="AKUA (아쿠아)" label="AKUA (아쿠아)"/><category term="PLEASE NEXT" label="PLEASE NEXT"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이원우/내게_와주길/</id><title>이원우 - 내게 와주길 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:20:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:20:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%9B%90%EC%9A%B0/%EB%82%B4%EA%B2%8C_%EC%99%80%EC%A3%BC%EA%B8%B8/" title="이원우 - 내게 와주길 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[앞으로만 천천히 또 걸어와 줄래 <br>걷다가 걷다 보니 <br>멀어지는 우리의 사이만 <br>좀처럼 잡지 못하는 <br>내 맘속에 널 묻어둘래 <br>아무런 감정 없이 널 바라 봐줄게 <br>말없이 미소 짓고 <br>커져가는 우리의 마음만 <br>좀처럼 잡지 못하는 <br>내 맘속에 널 묻어둘게 <br>밤 새워 혼자 소리 없이 <br>흐느껴 울던 어제가 <br>좀처럼 잊혀지질 않아 <br>한 순간도 널 보내기엔 <br>내게는 가혹한 일인데 <br>예전처럼 바라보긴 힘들지만 <br>언젠간 다시 그날 온다면 <br>그때는 내 마음 전해 받아주길 <br>꼭 그런 날이 내게 와주길 <br>아무렇지 않게 그냥 넘어가줄래 <br>모른 척 미소 짓고 <br>커져가는 우리의 마음만 <br>좀처럼 잡지 못하는 <br>내 맘속에 널 묻어둘게 <br>밤새워 혼자 소리 없이 <br>흐느껴 울던 어제가 <br>좀처럼 잊혀지질 않아 <br>한 순간도 널 보내기엔 <br>내게는 가혹한 일인데 <br>예전처럼 바라보긴 힘들지만 <br>언젠간 다시 그날 온다면 <br>그때는 내 마음 전해 받아주길 <br>꼭 그런 날이 내게 와주길 <br>어쩌면 알고 있을지 몰라 <br>모른척해도 알아 <br>알고 있을지 몰라 <br>망설임 없이 내게 온다면 <br>밤새워 혼자 소리 없이 <br>흐느껴 울던 어제가 <br>좀처럼 잊혀지질 않아 <br>한 순간도 널 보내기엔 <br>내게는 가혹한 일인데 <br>지금처럼 바라보긴 힘들지만 <br>언젠간 다시 돌아 온다면 <br>그때는 내 마음 전해 받아주길 <br>꼭 그런 날이 내게 와주길 <br>All day I need you <br>can't stop thinking all about you <br>Oh I want you <br>to call me like I'm doing all day <br>I don't know where you are <br>but If you listen what I'm singing <br>Please don't hesitate <br>come back to me again baby <br>All day I need you <br>can't stop thinking all about you <br>Oh I want you <br>to call me like I'm doing all day <br>I don't know where you are <br>but If you listen what I'm singing <br>Don't hesitate come back to me <br>]]></content><category term="이원우" label="이원우"/><category term="내게 와주길" label="내게 와주길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Die_Musik_Sind_Wir_Live/</id><title>Beatrice Egli - Die Musik Sind Wir (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:22:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:22:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Die_Musik_Sind_Wir_Live/" title="Beatrice Egli - Die Musik Sind Wir (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Kannst du es spur'n <br>Kannst du es atmen <br>Wie ein Augenblick <br>Der Ewigkeit <br><br>Komm lass dich fall'n <br>Komm lass dich treiben <br>Und dann vergiss <br>Raum und Zeit <br><br>Und jetzt tauchen wir <br>Hinein ins Freudenspiel <br>Nur aus Rhythmus <br>Und unendlichem Gefuhl <br><br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Tief in dir und mir <br>Sind millionen Lieder <br>Die uns beruhr'n <br><br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Heute jetzt und hier <br>Und dann immer wieder <br>Das Feuerwerk spur'n <br><br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Oh oh <br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Oh oh <br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Oh oh <br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Oh oh <br>Die Musik sind wir <br><br>Alles wird eins <br>Zehntausend Stimmen <br>Jeder geht mit <br>Bei diesem Sound <br><br>Endloser Tanz <br>Klingendes Fieber <br>Seele und Herz <br>Perfekt gelaunt <br><br>Und jetzt packt uns dieser Beat <br>Mit voller Kraft <br>Eine Explosion aus purer Leidenschaft <br><br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Tief in dir und mir <br>Sind millionen Lieder <br>Die uns beruhr'n <br><br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Heute jetzt und hier <br>Und dann immer wieder <br>Das Feuerwerk spur'n <br><br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Oh oh <br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Oh oh <br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Oh oh <br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Oh oh <br>Die Musik sind wir <br><br>Alles wird eins <br>Kannst du es spur'n <br>Zehntausend Stimmen <br><br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Tief in dir und mir <br>Sind millionen Lieder <br>Die uns beruhr'n <br><br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Heute jetzt und hier <br>Und dann immer wieder <br>Das Feuerwerk spur'n <br><br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Oh oh <br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Oh oh <br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Oh oh <br>Die Musik sind wir <br>Oh oh <br>Die Musik sind wir]]></content><category term="Beatrice Egli" label="Beatrice Egli"/><category term="Die Musik Sind Wir (Live)" label="Die Musik Sind Wir (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Jetzt_Erst_Recht_Live/</id><title>Beatrice Egli - Jetzt Erst Recht (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:22:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:22:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Jetzt_Erst_Recht_Live/" title="Beatrice Egli - Jetzt Erst Recht (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wir konnen leuchten in der Nacht <br>Denn der Sturm hat unser Feuer stark gemacht <br>Und wir geben alles nur nicht auf <br>Aus dem Stein im Weg hab'n wir uns ein Schloss gebaut <br><br>Und wir mussten oft den Kopf riskier'n <br>Um unser Herz nicht zu verlier'n <br>Doch wir sind noch immer hier <br><br>Jetzt erst recht <br>Auch wenn der langste Weg noch vor uns liegt <br>Sich der Zweifel vor die Sonne schiebt <br>Halten wir einander fest <br><br>Jetzt erst recht <br>Wir sind hell wenn wir zusammen steh'n <br>Die Welt kann uns're Flamme seh'n <br>Und der Traum der uns verbindet <br>Der ist echt <br>Jetzt erst recht <br><br>Wir konnen Abenteuer sein <br>Denn wir fragen nicht wie hoch <br>Und nicht wie weit <br>Wir konnen segeln ohne Wind <br>Weil die Sehnsucht uns doch immer weiter bringt <br><br>Und wir mussten oft den Kopf riskier'n <br>Um unser Herz nicht zu verlier'n <br>Und es wird uns immer fuhr'n <br><br>Jetzt erst recht <br>Auch wenn der langste Weg noch vor uns liegt <br>Sich der Zweifel vor die Sonne schiebt <br>Halten wir einander fest <br><br>Jetzt erst recht <br>Wir sind hell wenn wir zusammen steh'n <br>Die Welt kann uns're Flamme seh'n <br>Und der Traum der uns verbindet <br>Der ist echt <br><br>Wir fragen nicht wieso <br>Oh oh oh <br>Wir fragen nicht wie hoch <br>Oh oh oh <br>Wir fragen nicht wieso <br>Oh oh oh <br>Wir starten einfach los <br><br>Jetzt erst recht <br>Auch wenn der langste Weg noch vor uns liegt <br>Sich der Zweifel vor die Sonne schiebt <br>Halten wir einander festwir einander fest <br><br>Jetzt erst recht <br>Wir sind hell wenn wir zusammen steh'n <br>Die Welt kann uns're Flamme seh'n <br>Und der Traum der uns verbindet <br>Der ist echt <br>Jetzt erst recht]]></content><category term="Beatrice Egli" label="Beatrice Egli"/><category term="Jetzt Erst Recht (Live)" label="Jetzt Erst Recht (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Weck_Mich_Auf_Live/</id><title>Beatrice Egli - Weck Mich Auf (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Weck_Mich_Auf_Live/" title="Beatrice Egli - Weck Mich Auf (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wie du liebst <br>Wie du kusst <br>Das sagt mir <br>Wer du bist <br><br>Ungeschminkte Zeit <br>Im Kerzenschein <br>Wieg mich sanft <br>Dann schlaf ich ein <br><br>Bitte weck mich auf <br>Erst in 100 Jahr'n <br>Lass mich noch weiter trau'm <br>In deinem Arm <br><br>Weck mich auf <br>Erst in 100 Jahr'n <br>Hier konn't ich ewig sein <br>Ein Leben lang <br>Ein Leben lang <br><br>Bin Zuhaus <br>Nur bei dir <br>Lass die Welt <br>Vor der Tur <br><br>Du kennst mich so gut <br>Mein Seelenkleid <br>Uns're kleine Ewigkeit <br><br>Bitte weck mich auf <br>Erst in 100 Jahr'n <br>Lass mich noch weiter trau'm <br>In deinem Arm <br><br>Weck mich auf <br>Erst in 100 Jahr'n <br>Vermisste Zartlichkeit <br>Hat so gut getan <br><br>Bitte weck mich auf <br>Erst in 100 Jahr'n <br>Lass mich noch weiter trau'm <br>In deinem Arm <br><br>Weck mich auf <br>Erst in 100 Jahr'n <br>Vermisste Zartlichkeit <br>Hat so gut getan <br><br>Lass mich weiter trau'm <br>Ein Leben lang]]></content><category term="Beatrice Egli" label="Beatrice Egli"/><category term="Weck Mich Auf (Live)" label="Weck Mich Auf (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Karussell_Live/</id><title>Beatrice Egli - Karussell (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Karussell_Live/" title="Beatrice Egli - Karussell (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Alles dreht sich na na na na <br>Alles dreht sich nur noch um dich <br>Alles dreht sich na na na na <br>Alles dreht sich nur noch um dich <br><br>Du hast mich einfach angetanzt <br>Kamst mir gleich gefahrlich nah <br>Kein Gefuhl im Ruckwartsgang <br>Das war mir ganz ehrlich klar <br>Rettungslos verlor'n total <br>Einfach so im uberschall <br>Ich flieg viel zu hoch, viel zu schnell <br><br>Hab'n Karussell in meinem Kopf <br>ich werd' verruckt <br>Immer wennn mein Herz Stakkato klopft <br>flieg ich ins Gluck <br>Ich war noch nie schwindelfrei bei dir <br>wenn du mich kusst <br>Denn es dreht sich <br>schneller noch als schnell <br>Hab dich vermisst <br>Alles dreht sich na na na na <br>Alles dreht sich nur noch um dich <br>Alles dreht sich na na na na <br>Alles dreht sich nur noch um dich <br><br>Ich hatte Dich schon immer gern <br>Hab mich nur noch nie getraut <br>doch jetzt vergeht mir seh'n und hor'n <br>denn du hast das Eis getaut <br>Hunderttausend Volt und mehr <br>Immer wieder nur mit Dir <br>flieg ich ich viel zu hoch, viel zu schnell <br><br>Hab'n Karussell in meinem Kopf <br>ich werd' verruckt <br>Immer wennn mein Herz Stakkato klopft <br>flieg ich ins Gluck <br>Ich war noch nie schwindelfrei bei dir <br>wenn du mich kusst <br>Denn es dreht sich <br>schneller noch als schnell <br>Hab dich vermisst <br>Alles dreht sich na na na na <br>Alles dreht sich nur noch um dich <br>Alles dreht sich na na na na <br>Alles dreht sich nur noch um dich <br><br>Hundertausend Volt und mehr <br>Immer wieder nur mit dir <br>flieg ich ich viel zu hoch, viel zu schnell <br><br>Hab'n Karussell in meinem Kopf <br>ich werd' verruckt <br>Immer wennn mein Herz Stakkato klopft <br>flieg ich ins Gluck <br>Ich war noch nie schwindelfrei bei dir <br>wenn du mich kusst <br>Denn es dreht sich <br>schneller noch als schnell <br>Hab dich vermisst <br>Alles dreht sich na na na na <br>Alles dreht sich nur noch um dich <br>Alles dreht sich na na na na <br>Alles dreht sich nur noch um dich <br>Alles dreht sich]]></content><category term="Beatrice Egli" label="Beatrice Egli"/><category term="Karussell (Live)" label="Karussell (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Jetzt_Und_Hier_Fur_Immer_Live/</id><title>Beatrice Egli - Jetzt Und Hier Fur Immer (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Jetzt_Und_Hier_Fur_Immer_Live/" title="Beatrice Egli - Jetzt Und Hier Fur Immer (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Drei uhr fruh, zwei tranen geh'n auf reisen <br>Wo, wo bist du, zwei tranen die beweisen <br>Ohne dich ohne dich, ist alles kalt und leer <br>Du fehlst mir so, du fehlst mir hier so sehr <br><br>Ich will dich jetzt und hier fur immer <br>Ich will den wahnsinn jeden tag <br>Will deinen duft in meinem zimmer <br>Weil ich die sehnsucht nicht ertrag <br>Ich will dich jetzt und hier fur immer <br>Ich will den himmel jede nacht <br>Und tag fur tag wirds immer schlimmer <br>Du hast mich willenlos gemacht <br><br>Vier uhr fruh, gedanken in mir kreisen <br>Du und ich, wie konnt' es so entgleisen <br>Unser traum unser traum, vom lebenslangem gluck <br>Ich halt ihn fest, und wunsche dich zuruck <br><br>Ich will dich jetzt und hier fur immer <br>Ich will den wahnsinn jeden tag <br>Will deinen duft in meinem zimmer <br>Weil ich die sehnsucht nicht ertrag <br>Ich will dich jetzt und hier fur immer <br>Ich will den himmel jede nacht <br>Und tag fur tag wirds immer schlimmer <br>Du hast mich willenlos gemacht <br><br>Ich will dich jetzt und hier fur immer <br>Ich will den wahnsinn jeden tag <br>Will deinen duft in meinem zimmer <br>Weil ich die sehnsucht nicht ertrag <br><br>Ich will dich jetzt und hier fur immer <br>Ich will den wahnsinn jeden tag <br>Will deinen duft in meinem zimmer <br>Weil ich die sehnsucht nicht ertrag <br>Ich will dich jetzt und hier fur immer <br>Ich will den himmel jede nacht <br>Und tag fur tag wirds immer schlimmer <br>Du hast mich willenlos gemacht <br><br>Ich will dich jetzt und hier fur immer <br>Ich will den wahnsinn jeden tag <br>Will deinen duft in meinem zimmer <br>Weil ich die sehnsucht nicht ertrag <br>lied klingt langsam aus]]></content><category term="Beatrice Egli" label="Beatrice Egli"/><category term="Jetzt Und Hier Fur Immer (Live)" label="Jetzt Und Hier Fur Immer (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Ich_Bin_Da_Live/</id><title>Beatrice Egli - Ich Bin Da (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Ich_Bin_Da_Live/" title="Beatrice Egli - Ich Bin Da (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ich kann es kaum erwarten <br>Es kribbelt so im Bauch <br>Der Puls geht steil nach oben <br><br>Fuhlt ihr das denn auch <br><br>Ein Knistern und ein Beben <br>Ich halt es kaum noch aus <br>Mich kann nicht's mehr halten <br>Will nur noch zu euch raus <br><br>Ich bin da <br>Das Leben lacht <br>Das ist alleine uns're Nacht <br><br>Jetzt geht's los <br>Heu't feiern wir <br>Und dass Beste das seid ihr <br><br>Ich bin da <br>Das Feuer brennt <br>Soviele Freunde die man kennt <br><br>Wir sind eins <br>Ich freu mich so <br>Wir sind gut drauf <br>Verruckt und froh <br><br>Euch alle hier zu sehen <br>Ich glaub ich flipp gleich aus <br>Vor Freude und vom glucklich sein <br>Wir rocken heu't das Haus <br><br>Hemmungslos und losgelost <br>Ich spur die heisse Glut <br>Durch Musik verbunden <br>Ihr wisst wie gut das tut <br><br>Ich bin da <br>Das Leben lacht <br>Das ist alleine uns're Nacht <br><br>Jetzt geht's los <br>Heu't feiern wir <br>Und dass Beste das seid ihr <br><br>Ich bin da <br>Das Feuer brennt <br>Soviele Freunde die man kennt <br>Wir sind eins <br>Ich freu mich so <br>Wir sind gut drauf <br>Verruckt und froh <br><br>Einmalig Einzigartig <br>Euch ganz nah zu spur'n <br>Schenken uns was fur immer bleibt <br>Unvergessliche Zeit <br><br>Ich bin da <br>Das Leben lacht <br>Das ist alleine uns're Nacht <br><br>Jetzt geht's los <br>Heu't feiern wir <br>Und dass Beste das seid ihr <br><br>Ich bin da <br>Das Feuer brennt <br>Soviele Freunde die man kennt <br><br>Wir sind eins <br>Ich freu mich so <br>Wir sind gut drauf <br>Verruckt und froh <br><br>Ich bin da]]></content><category term="Beatrice Egli" label="Beatrice Egli"/><category term="Ich Bin Da (Live)" label="Ich Bin Da (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Kick_Im_Augenblick_Live/</id><title>Beatrice Egli - Kick Im Augenblick (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Kick_Im_Augenblick_Live/" title="Beatrice Egli - Kick Im Augenblick (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Die Zeit ging voruber <br>Manchmal drehte sich die Welt zu schnell <br>Wir haben oft uns vergessen <br><br>Und uns alles anders vorgestellt <br>Es hat uns zerrissen <br>Doch wir wissen Tranen trocknen schnell <br>Denn wir erkannten <br>Was in unsrem Leben wirklich fehlt <br><br>Wir leben den Kick im Augenblick <br>Momente wie diese <br>Kommen nie wieder <br>Nie wieder zuruck <br>Wir leben den Kick im Augenblick <br>Das Ziel ist erreichbar <br>Der Weg war nie leichter <br>Nie leichter ins Gluck <br>Mit dem Kick im Augenblick <br><br>Wir stehen dazu <br>Keiner hat gesagt, es ware leicht <br>Und all die schweren Zeiten <br>Waren auch fur etwas gut vielleicht <br>Wir machten das Beste <br>Kriegt man, wenn man nach den Sternen greift <br>Doch ein kleines Stuck <br>Hatte uns doch allemal gereicht <br><br>Wir leben den Kick im Augenblick <br>Momente wie diese <br>Kommen nie wieder <br>Nie wieder zuruck <br>Wir leben den Kick im Augenblick <br>Das Ziel ist erreichbar <br>Der Weg war nie leichter <br>Nie leichter ins Gluck <br><br>Wir haben eben <br>Zu selten dran gedacht <br>Hey, unser Leben <br>Ist, was man daraus macht <br><br>Wir leben den Kick im Augenblick <br>Momente wie diese <br>Kommen nie wieder <br>Nie wieder zuruck <br>Wir leben den Kick im Augenblick <br>Das Ziel ist erreichbar <br>Der Weg war nie leichter <br>Nie leichter ins Gluck <br><br>Wir leben den Kick <br>Wir leben den Kick <br>Wir leben den Kick]]></content><category term="Beatrice Egli" label="Beatrice Egli"/><category term="Kick Im Augenblick (Live)" label="Kick Im Augenblick (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Fliegen_Live/</id><title>Beatrice Egli - Fliegen (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beatrice_Egli/Fliegen_Live/" title="Beatrice Egli - Fliegen (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Der letzte Sonnenstrahl des Tages <br>streichelt meine Haut <br>Ein warmes Wohlgefuhl <br><br>ganz tief in mir <br>Die Farben meiner Seele <br>zeichnen dein Gesicht so vertraut <br>Ich kann es fuhlen <br>Gleich bin ich bei dir <br><br>Ein Funke der mein Lied entfacht <br>Ich sing' es nur fur dich <br>Feuerflugel Ruckenwind <br>Wir heben ab <br>Mit dir um die ganze Welt <br>hoch hinauf zum Himmelszelt <br>Lass uns alle Wunderdinge seh'n <br>und fliegen <br>Mit dir um die ganze Welt <br>Hab das Gluck fur uns bestellt <br>Gib mir dein Hand halt dich ganz fest <br>und flieg' mit mir fort <br><br>Ein Sonnenbad, ein Sternenregen <br>Ein Hauch Gluckseligkeit <br>Kein Berg ist uns zu hoch <br>Kein Weg zu weit <br>Durch Raum und Zeit, gedankenlos <br>sind wir fur immer eins <br>Ich zeig' dir meine Welt <br>Komm sei bereit <br><br>Ein Funke der mein Lied entfacht <br>Ich sing' es nur fur dich <br>Feuerflugel Ruckenwind <br>Wir heben ab <br>Mit dir um die ganze Welt <br>hoch hinauf zum Himmelszelt <br>Lass uns alle Wunderdinge seh'n <br>und fliegen <br>Mit dir um die ganze Welt <br>Hab das Gluck fur uns bestellt <br>Gib mir dein Hand halt dich ganz fest <br>und flieg' mit mir fort <br><br>Oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>Lass uns alle Wunderdinge seh'n <br>und fliegen <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>Gib mir deine Hand halt dich ganz fest <br>und flieg' mit mir fort <br>Mit dir um die ganze Welt]]></content><category term="Beatrice Egli" label="Beatrice Egli"/><category term="Fliegen (Live)" label="Fliegen (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/As_I_Feel_I_Die_Demo_Ver/</id><title>Caravan - As I Feel I Die (Demo Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/As_I_Feel_I_Die_Demo_Ver/" title="Caravan - As I Feel I Die (Demo Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[With a song on my mind I'm thinking of you <br>Through the dreams of a million eyes I'll stand still with you <br>And wait till I find the world that you're searching for <br>A cloud coloured blind has entered my eyes <br>And everything's going a slight shade of purple <br>But me, I don't mind <br>Today is my day <br>I'm living the life that I choose <br>I've found a way <br><br>I can see a noser <br>Sit there all alone <br>And dream I'm sitting here <br><br>While magic fires the moon <br>I turn around my mind <br>And bid farewell to fear <br><br>Swimming through a wish <br>That I know I'm in a dream <br>I'm changing the music by ear <br><br>I'll have to leave behind <br>To re ensure them in <br>And wanting oh so clear <br><br>Deep inside of time <br>I catch my breath to find <br>I've got so far to go <br><br>Howlin' through the trees <br>A cry which is my ears <br>I turn around and go <br><br>Following the dream <br>Is not the easiest thing <br>Out of the shadows I see <br><br>And blackened till the moon <br>A magic creature moves <br>And says belongs to me]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="As I Feel I Die (Demo Ver.)" label="As I Feel I Die (Demo Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Hello_Hello_Demo_Ver/</id><title>Caravan - Hello Hello (Demo Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Hello_Hello_Demo_Ver/" title="Caravan - Hello Hello (Demo Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Up on a hilltop far from the city <br>Overlooking a stream <br>I heard a sound, it made me look round <br>I looked back where I had just been <br>There just behind a ledge <br>There was a man, he leapt to and fro <br>Clipping away at a hedge <br><br>Suddenly I heard a ringing singing <br>But he was nowhere to be seen <br><br>Pulling my trousers up to my knees <br>I waded across the stream <br>Back to the place where I could hear sounds <br>And where the old man once had been <br>There just behind a ledge <br>I looked about, I couldn't make out <br>Where he had been clipping the hedge <br><br>I could not hear what he was singing <br>But I found my ears ringing with the sound]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="Hello Hello (Demo Ver.)" label="Hello Hello (Demo Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/And_I_Wish_I_Were_Stoned_Demo_Ver/</id><title>Caravan - And I Wish I Were Stoned (Demo Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/And_I_Wish_I_Were_Stoned_Demo_Ver/" title="Caravan - And I Wish I Were Stoned (Demo Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Once I had a dream, nothing else to do <br>Sat and played my mind in time with all of you <br>Got down in the road, crossed my heart and cried <br>When you told me how you'd love to live and not to die <br><br>Why why why <br>I wish I were stoned on my mind <br>Why why why, oh why <br><br>Dreamed I saw a man walked upon the sea <br>Dreamed it once again and saw that he was me <br>Looking close at me I looked a lot like you <br>Knowing where to go but not quite what to do <br><br>Why why why <br>I wish I were stoned on my mind <br>Why why why, oh why <br><br>Give me all your love in a smile <br>And I'll tell you what I'm thinking <br>Let me see the world through your eyes <br>And I'll show you where I'm sitting <br><br>Once I had a dream, nothing else to do <br>Sat and played my mind in time with all of you <br>Got down in the road, crossed my heart and cried <br>When you told me how you'd love to kill and not to die <br><br>Why why why <br>I wish I were stoned on my mind <br>Why why why, oh why <br><br>Give me all your love in a smile <br>And I'll tell you what I'm thinking <br>Let me see the world through your eyes <br>And I'll show you where I'm sitting <br><br>Don't worry about me <br>I've got all that I need <br>And I'm singing my song to the sky <br><br>You know how it feels <br>With the breeze of the sun in your eyes <br>Not minding that time's passing by <br><br>I've got all and more <br>My smile, just as before <br>Is all that I carry with me <br><br>I talk to myself <br>I need nobody else <br>I'm lost and I'm mine, yes I'm free]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="And I Wish I Were Stoned (Demo Ver.)" label="And I Wish I Were Stoned (Demo Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/A_Day_In_The_Life_Of_Maurice_Haylett/</id><title>Caravan - A Day In The Life Of Maurice Haylett - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/A_Day_In_The_Life_Of_Maurice_Haylett/" title="Caravan - A Day In The Life Of Maurice Haylett - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The little man who rang <br>And danced while he sang <br>Sits in the back of my head <br><br>He wears Navy Blue <br>And he knows what to do <br>When he meets with his lady friend <br><br>He came home yesterday <br>From a trip far away <br>Tells me I've got a new face <br><br>And it wasn't my fault <br>The day he got caught <br>Speeding on mind's highway]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="A Day In The Life Of Maurice Haylett" label="A Day In The Life Of Maurice Haylett"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Limits/</id><title>Caravan - Limits - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Limits/" title="Caravan - Limits - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If your world is big enough for you <br>Don't go spoiling it for someone else]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="Limits" label="Limits"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Cant_Be_Long_Now/</id><title>Caravan - Can`t Be Long Now - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Cant_Be_Long_Now/" title="Caravan - Can`t Be Long Now - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes I'm thinking <br>Whatever did I do <br>Nights are always chilly <br>In these days of you <br><br>Streets outside are empty <br>No one can be seen <br>Wisdom points a finger <br>To the judgement that's been]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="Can`t Be Long Now" label="Can`t Be Long Now"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Asforteri/</id><title>Caravan - Asforteri - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Asforteri/" title="Caravan - Asforteri - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wish that I could be you <br>Don't you wish to wish that, too <br>Wish that I could be you]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="Asforteri" label="Asforteri"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Hello_Hello/</id><title>Caravan - Hello Hello - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Hello_Hello/" title="Caravan - Hello Hello - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Up on a hilltop far from the city <br>Overlooking a stream <br>I heard a sound, it made me look round <br>I looked back where I had just been <br>There just behind a ledge <br>There was a man, he leapt to and fro <br>Clipping away at a hedge <br><br>Suddenly I heard a ringing singing <br>But he was nowhere to be seen <br><br>Pulling my trousers up to my knees <br>I waded across the stream <br>Back to the place where I could hear sounds <br>And where the old man once had been <br>There just behind a ledge <br>I looked about, I couldn't make out <br>Where he had been clipping the hedge <br><br>I could not hear what he was singing <br>But I found my ears ringing with the sound]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="Hello Hello" label="Hello Hello"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/With_An_Ear_To_The_Ground_You_Can_Make_It/</id><title>Caravan - With An Ear To The Ground You Can Make It - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/With_An_Ear_To_The_Ground_You_Can_Make_It/" title="Caravan - With An Ear To The Ground You Can Make It - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Would you like to ride with me <br>While you're waiting for the band to come <br>Can tell me all you'd like to see <br>While you're waiting for the band to come <br>Would you make me take me slightly for you <br>If we talked about your pride and swollen gladness too <br><br>You and I our only need <br>Waiting for the band to come <br>Searching for someone to see <br>And hoping that the band will come <br>Chemistries attention taste in your mind <br>And the thought that puzzled me you may be left behind <br><br>Would you like to ride with me <br>While you're waiting for the band to come <br>Searching for someone to see <br>And hoping that the band will come <br>Would you make me take me slightly for you <br>If we talked about your pride and swollen gladness too <br><br>Would you believe it possible <br>To leave yourself behind <br>Turning upside down inside out <br>Now someone else my mind <br>Help me, someone <br>Someone please help me <br><br>So, where but for you would I <br>Dreaming, make your face my eyes <br>Turning so slow, taking care <br>Just a smile I do for you <br><br>So wipe away all those fears <br>I'm longing to feel the years go slipping by <br>While you stand, mind in hand with me, with me <br><br>Would you like to ride with me <br>Would you like to ride with me <br>While you're waiting for the band to come <br>We're waiting for the band <br>Can tell me all you'd like to see <br>You can tell me what to see <br>While you're waiting for the band to come <br>Would you make me take me slightly for you <br>If we talked about your pride and swollen gladness too]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="With An Ear To The Ground You Can Make It" label="With An Ear To The Ground You Can Make It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/As_I_Feel_I_Die/</id><title>Caravan - As I Feel I Die - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/As_I_Feel_I_Die/" title="Caravan - As I Feel I Die - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[With a song on my mind I'm thinking of you <br>Through the dreams of a million eyes I'll stand still with you <br>And wait till I find the world that you're searching for <br>A cloud coloured blind has entered my eyes <br>And everything's going a slight shade of purple <br>But me, I don't mind <br>Today is my day <br>I'm living the life that I choose <br>I've found a way <br><br>I can see a noser <br>Sit there all alone <br>And dream I'm sitting here <br><br>While magic fires the moon <br>I turn around my mind <br>And bid farewell to fear <br><br>Swimming through a wish <br>That I know I'm in a dream <br>I'm changing the music by ear <br><br>I'll have to leave behind <br>To re ensure them in <br>And wanting oh so clear <br><br>Deep inside of time <br>I catch my breath to find <br>I've got so far to go <br><br>Howlin' through the trees <br>A cry which is my ears <br>I turn around and go <br><br>Following the dream <br>Is not the easiest thing <br>Out of the shadows I see <br><br>And blackened till the moon <br>A magic creature moves <br>And says belongs to me]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="As I Feel I Die" label="As I Feel I Die"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/And_I_Wish_I_Were_Stoned___Dont_Worry/</id><title>Caravan - And I Wish I Were Stoned / Don`t Worry - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/And_I_Wish_I_Were_Stoned___Dont_Worry/" title="Caravan - And I Wish I Were Stoned / Don`t Worry - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Once I had a dream, nothing else to do <br>Sat and played my mind in time with all of you <br>Got down in the road, crossed my heart and cried <br>When you told me how you'd love to live and not to die <br><br>Why why why <br>I wish I were stoned on my mind <br>Why why why, oh why <br><br>Dreamed I saw a man walked upon the sea <br>Dreamed it once again and saw that he was me <br>Looking close at me I looked a lot like you <br>Knowing where to go but not quite what to do <br><br>Why why why <br>I wish I were stoned on my mind <br>Why why why, oh why <br><br>Give me all your love in a smile <br>And I'll tell you what I'm thinking <br>Let me see the world through your eyes <br>And I'll show you where I'm sitting <br><br>Once I had a dream, nothing else to do <br>Sat and played my mind in time with all of you <br>Got down in the road, crossed my heart and cried <br>When you told me how you'd love to kill and not to die <br><br>Why why why <br>I wish I were stoned on my mind <br>Why why why, oh why <br><br>Give me all your love in a smile <br>And I'll tell you what I'm thinking <br>Let me see the world through your eyes <br>And I'll show you where I'm sitting <br><br>Don't worry about me <br>I've got all that I need <br>And I'm singing my song to the sky <br><br>You know how it feels <br>With the breeze of the sun in your eyes <br>Not minding that time's passing by <br><br>I've got all and more <br>My smile, just as before <br>Is all that I carry with me <br><br>I talk to myself <br>I need nobody else <br>I'm lost and I'm mine, yes I'm free]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="And I Wish I Were Stoned / Don`t Worry" label="And I Wish I Were Stoned / Don`t Worry"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/If_I_Could_Do_It_All_Over_Again_Id_Do_It_All_Over_You/</id><title>Caravan - If I Could Do It All Over Again, I`d Do It All Over You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/If_I_Could_Do_It_All_Over_Again_Id_Do_It_All_Over_You/" title="Caravan - If I Could Do It All Over Again, I`d Do It All Over You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Who do you think you are <br>Do you think you <br>Who do you think you are <br>Do you think you <br><br>I really don't know <br>I really don't know <br><br>Gimme that stuff enough, enough to slow me down <br>I'll give you anything that I've got if you take me away <br>Lovin' is the stuff the thing, the thing that slows me down <br>More than anything that I know, gimme some <br><br>Who do you think you are <br>Do you think you <br>Who do you think you are <br>Do you think you <br><br>Who do you think you are <br>Do you think you <br>Who do you think you are <br>Do you think you <br><br>Who do you think you are <br>Do you think you <br>Who do you think you are <br>Do you think you <br><br>Gimme that stuff enough, enough to slow me down <br>I'll give you anything that I've got if you take me away <br>Lovin' is the stuff, the thing, the thing that slows me down <br>More than anything that I know, gimme some <br><br>Who do you think you are <br>Do you think you <br>Who do you think you are <br>Do you think you <br><br>Who do you think you are]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="If I Could Do It All Over Again, I`d Do It All Over You" label="If I Could Do It All Over Again, I`d Do It All Over You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Group_Girl/</id><title>Caravan - Group Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Group_Girl/" title="Caravan - Group Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a place where I can go, where I listen to the <br>Wind singing <br>Songs of happiness I know, and it brings it all back <br>Again <br>Somewhere deep inside of me, there's a song that I can <br>Sing <br>Jigsaw puzzles on a tree, and it brings it all back again <br>Will the day be warm and bright, or will it snow <br>There are people waiting here who really want to know <br><br>And sometimes I think of wine, songs and laughter flowing <br>Free <br>People talking all the time, and it brings it all back to <br>Me <br><br>Will the day be warm and bright, or will it snow <br>There are people waiting now who really have to know <br><br>Can't you feel it in the air I wonder what it's meant to <br>Be <br>It's the thought that can't be spared, and it brings it <br>All back to me <br>Yes it brings it all back to me]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="Group Girl" label="Group Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Winter_Wine/</id><title>Caravan - Winter Wine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Winter_Wine/" title="Caravan - Winter Wine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Winter Wine <br>How you're always flowing, blowing in my mind <br>Like a stream, these magic waters move me to a dream <br>Of travelling with you, drifting carefree, dropping downward through fresh grasses <br>Bubbles merrily as it passes, never knowing where you're going <br>Carry me with you, carry me with you <br><br>Be conjured up in a midnight dream, ancient castles dark <br>As wandering minstrels play tunes of yesterday <br>When dragons roamed the land, knights in armour gold <br>Charged on horseback bold <br>The maids were saved, the dragons slayed <br><br>Sail scene, sea green, sailing forward to a new land <br>Treasure waits, paradise gates, for the taking, can't start waiting <br>All you need, but take heed, remember it pays to pay the sandman well <br>Make no fuss, for you must, in stardust, he puts all the colours in your dreams <br><br>Bells chime three times, naked dancers enter slowly <br>Smoky room, scented gloom, audience eating, fat men drinking <br>Candles burn, a dull red light illuminates the breasts of four young girls <br>Dancing, prancing, provoking, dreams are always ending far too soon <br><br>Life's too short to be sad, wishing things you'll never have <br>You're better off not dreaming of the things to come <br>Dreams are always ending far too soon <br>Sounds of a distant melody, once played, lost from memory <br>Funny how it's clearer now, you're close to me <br>We'll be together all the time]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="Winter Wine" label="Winter Wine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Aristocracy/</id><title>Caravan - Aristocracy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Aristocracy/" title="Caravan - Aristocracy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You talk of all the many things that you have <br>And you smile from day to day <br>But no one has ever seen any of these <br>And those smiles just fade away <br>Someone keeps shouting out 'I want to know' <br>Well I can't help singing this song <br>When they tell me that the devil is a gentleman too <br>I know I can't go wrong <br><br>I have to slip away today <br>I've been invited down to stay <br>Yes I feel my going down <br><br>They say that eight fishes call men in the sea <br>And use man made for the bait <br>And shoots all the people that fly in the sky <br>That chance on his estate <br>That feeds on salmon, that just has to be seen <br>And none but he can do <br>They tell me this and they tell me that <br>And tell me this is always, always something new <br><br>You'd better believe it's so <br>I made up my mind to go <br>A whole world waits for you <br><br>I'll sit with my head thrust down on your knees <br>And smile for you again <br>And you won't have to worry about anything now <br>I'll be halfway there by ten <br>It only takes a moment to decide on the move <br>It all seems so absurd <br>Still I know that the devil is a gentleman too <br>Who never keeps his word <br><br>I made up my mind to go <br>You'd better believe it's so <br>A whole world waits for me]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="Aristocracy" label="Aristocracy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/I_Dont_Know_Its_Name_Alias_The_Word/</id><title>Caravan - I Don`t Know It`s Name (Alias The Word) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/I_Dont_Know_Its_Name_Alias_The_Word/" title="Caravan - I Don`t Know It`s Name (Alias The Word) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Flower in a garden <br>A garden with no gate <br>Flower imprisoned by ice crystals <br>The summer came too late <br>To melt the snow on white hedgerows <br>Don't let the winter hide you <br>Or freeze your love for me <br>Like frozen flowers forgotten <br>They're flying in the cold <br>Completely lost in winter's frost <br>I remember still <br>The colour of your hair <br>As I stare <br>Through sunshine <br>Spend these lonely hours <br>Dreaming of your touch <br>I came to love so much <br>It's spring free frozen flowers <br>That warm your love for me <br>For winter can't last long <br>I tell you that I love you <br>But still you do not hear <br>Yet in my dreams I find you <br>But like mist you disappear <br>In the gloom of my room <br>Forgotten frozen flowers <br>Left flying in the cold <br>In winter's frost <br>I tell you that I love you <br>But still you do not hear <br>And in my dreams I find you <br>But like mist you disappear <br>In the gloom of my room]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="I Don`t Know It`s Name (Alias The Word)" label="I Don`t Know It`s Name (Alias The Word)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Nine_Feet_Underground/</id><title>Caravan - Nine Feet Underground - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Nine_Feet_Underground/" title="Caravan - Nine Feet Underground - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look at the day that is dawning <br>What do you see with your eyes <br>Think of me now while you're yawning <br>Sunshine the tears from my cries <br><br>What I see I know is real <br>What I touch I know I feel <br>If I don't care for what you say <br>It won't mean much to me today <br><br>For I see your world that is living <br>My mind is yours, yours is mine <br>Don't talk to me 'bout forgiving <br>So much to do, no more time <br><br>All my love goes straight to you <br>With just a thought for something new <br>All I have is what you feel <br>With hands in mouth, you gently kneel <br><br>What I see I know is real <br>What I touch I know I feel <br>All my love goes straight to you <br>All my love is you <br><br>There's a place where I can go <br>Where I listen to the wind singing <br>Songs of happiness I know <br>And it brings it all back again <br><br>Somewhere deep inside of me <br>There's a song that I can sing <br>Jigsaw puzzles on a tree <br>And it brings it all back again <br><br>Will the day be warm and bright, or will it snow <br>There are people waiting here who really want to know <br><br>And sometimes I think of wine <br>Songs and laughter flowing free <br>People talking all the time <br>And it brings it all back to me <br><br>Will the day be warm and bright, or will it snow <br>There are people waiting now who really have to know <br><br>Can't you feel it in the air <br>I wonder what it's meant to be <br>It's the thought that can despair <br>And it brings it all back to me <br>Yes it brings it all back to me]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="Nine Feet Underground" label="Nine Feet Underground"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/In_The_Land_Of_Grey__Pink/</id><title>Caravan - In The Land Of Grey &amp; Pink - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/In_The_Land_Of_Grey__Pink/" title="Caravan - In The Land Of Grey &amp; Pink - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In the land of grey and pink where only boy scouts stop to think <br>They'll be coming back again, those nasty grumbly grimblies <br>And they're climbing down your chimney, yes they're trying to get in <br>Come to take your money isn't it a sin, they're so thin <br>They've black buckets in the sky, don't leave your dad in the rain <br>Cigarettes burn bright tonight, they'll all get washed down the drain <br><br>So we'll sail away for just one day to the land where the punk weed grows <br>You won't need any money, just fingers and your toes <br>And when it's dark our boat will park on a land of warm and green <br>Pick our fill of punk weed and smoke it till we bleed, that's all we'll need <br>While sailing back in morning light, we'll wash our teeth in the sea <br>And when the day gets really bright, we'll go to sea drinking tea <br><br>So we'll sail away for just one day to the land where the punk weed grows <br>You won't need any money, just fingers and your toes <br>And when it's dark our boat will park on a land of warm and green <br>Pick our fill of punk weed and smoke it till we bleed, that's all we'll need <br>They've black buckets in the sky, don't leave your dad in the rain <br>Cigarettes burn bright tonight, they'll all get washed down the drain]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="In The Land Of Grey &amp; Pink" label="In The Land Of Grey &amp; Pink"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Love_To_Love_You_And_Tonight_Pigs_Will_Fly/</id><title>Caravan - Love To Love You (And Tonight Pigs Will Fly) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:23:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:23:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Love_To_Love_You_And_Tonight_Pigs_Will_Fly/" title="Caravan - Love To Love You (And Tonight Pigs Will Fly) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I dreamed of all the magic things that be <br>When we'd ride to a dock on bended knee <br>But you'd just smile and gently shake your head <br>And put a hole through me so I was dead <br>Oh, I'd fall down and I was left alone <br>With a feeling of you still that was my own <br><br>Oh, I would love to, love to love you <br>Yes, indeed, I do love you, love you <br>My my, pigs might fly, that can't be bad <br>How you have the cheek to smile and tell me I'm mad <br><br>A man came through the wall and stood by me <br>Complete with bag of nuts and fancy free <br>He said without a tonal fleeting glance <br>I'd like to get deep down inside your pants <br>How you opened up his head and smiled <br>And rubbish from your mouth you tipped inside <br><br>Oh, I would love to, love to love you <br>Yes, indeed, I do love you, love you <br>My my, pigs might fly, that can't be bad <br>How you have the cheek to smile and tell me I'm mad <br><br>Oh, I would love to, love to love you <br>Yes, indeed, I do love you, love you <br>My my, pigs might fly, that can't be bad <br>How you have the cheek to smile and tell me I'm mad <br><br>Oh, I would love to, love to love you <br>Yes, indeed, I do love you, love you <br>My my, pigs might fly, that can't be bad <br>How you have the cheek to smile and tell me I'm mad]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="Love To Love You (And Tonight Pigs Will Fly)" label="Love To Love You (And Tonight Pigs Will Fly)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Winter_Wine/</id><title>Caravan - Winter Wine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:24:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:24:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Winter_Wine/" title="Caravan - Winter Wine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Winter wine <br>How you're always flowing, blowing in my mind <br>Like a stream, these magic waters move me to a dream <br>Of travelling with you, drifting carefree <br>Dropping downward through fresh grasses <br>Bubbles merrily as it passes <br>Never knowing where you're going <br>Carry me with you carry me with you <br>Carry me with you carry me with you <br><br>Be conjured up in a midnight dream <br>Ancient castles dark <br>As wandering minstrels play tunes of yesterday <br>When dragons roamed the land <br>Knights in armour cold charged on horseback bold <br>The maids were saved, the dragons slain <br><br>Sail scene, sea green <br>Sailing forward to a new land <br>Treasure waits, paradise gates <br>For the taking, don't start waking <br>All you need, but take heed <br>Remember it pays to pay the sandman well <br>Make no fuss, for you must in stardust <br>He puts all the colours in your dreams <br><br>Bells chime three times <br>Naked dancers enter slowly <br>Smoky room, scented gloom <br>Audience eating, fat men drinking <br>Candles burn, a dull red light <br>Illuminates the breasts of four young girls <br>Dancing, prancing, provoking <br>See, dreams are always ending far too soon <br><br>Life's too short to be sad <br>Wishing things you'll never have <br>You're better off not dreaming of the things to come <br>Dreams are always ending far too soon <br><br>Sounds of a distant melody <br>Once played, lost from memory <br>Funny how it's clearer now you're close to me <br>We'll be together all the time <br><br>Sounds of a distant melody <br>Once played, lost from memory <br>Funny how it's clearer now you're close to me <br>We'll be together all the time <br>Time time <br><br>Sail scene, sea green <br>Sailing forward to a new land <br>Treasure waits, paradise gates <br>For the taking, don't start waking <br>All you need, but take heed <br>Remember it pays to pay the sandman well <br>Make no fuss, for you must in stardust <br>He puts all the colour in your dreams]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="Winter Wine" label="Winter Wine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Golf_Girl/</id><title>Caravan - Golf Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:24:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:24:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caravan/Golf_Girl/" title="Caravan - Golf Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Standing on a golf course dressed in PVC <br>I chanced upon a golf girl selling cups of tea <br>She asked me did I want one, asked me with a grin <br>For three pence you can buy one full right to the brim <br><br>So of course I had to have one in fact I ordered three <br>So I could watch the golf girl, could see she fancied me <br>And later on the golf course after drinking tea <br>It started raining golf balls and she protected me <br><br>Her name was Pat <br>And we sat under a tree <br>She kissed me <br>We go for walks in fine weather <br>All together <br>On the golf course <br>We talk in morse <br><br>Standing on a golf course dressed in PVC <br>I chanced upon a golf girl selling cups of tea <br>She asked me did I want one, asked me with a grin <br>For three pence you can buy one full right to the brim <br><br>So of course I had to have one in fact I ordered three <br>So I could watch the golf girl, could see she fancied me <br>And later on the golf course after drinking tea <br>It started raining golf balls and she protected me <br><br>Her name was Pat <br>And we sat under a tree <br>She kissed me]]></content><category term="Caravan" label="Caravan"/><category term="Golf Girl" label="Golf Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rkomi/Rossetto/</id><title>Rkomi - Rossetto - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:24:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:24:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rkomi/Rossetto/" title="Rkomi - Rossetto - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Non la tocchi la mia mmh <br>Non la tocchi la mia mmh <br>Saluto Kemel, mangio falafel <br>Da piazzale Cuoco torno in Calvairate <br>Vado prima che mi inghiottisca <br>Questa fogna e la mia fortuna <br>Siete poltiglia <br><br>Dormivo in cantina, fai la gattina <br>Ma e gia partita la mia partita <br>Avvisa chi devi ma che piccina <br>Con quegli occhietti starei qui Shh <br>Pure in silenzio, col mio filmaccio <br>Le tue paranoie, il nostro linguaggio <br>Figli di troia con la coda di paglia <br>Mi fa gola la villa, non la vita che fai, bang bang <br>In strada come i zingari i miei Bang bang <br>Al commissario non ci parlano i miei Bang bang <br>Quella merda non la toccano i miei <br>Tu sei niente di nuovo e niente di che <br>Il cielo mi parla vuole dirmi qualcosa <br>Gioco a un gioco a cui non voglio giocare <br>No, voglio giocare, non dargliela vinta, non la voglio la luna <br>Giuda aggiustati il rossetto <br>Giuda aggiustati il rossetto <br>Per 'sti soldi come se schiavi <br>Fanno i conti con se stessi quando tornano a casa <br>Giuda aggiustati il rossetto Sisi <br>Giuda aggiustati il rossetto Sisi <br>Nebbia, Rkomi, ah <br><br>Non ho fretta, non voglio correre <br>Non ho fretta, non voglio correre <br>Non ho fretta, non voglio correre <br>Non ho fretta, non voglio correre <br>Non ho fretta, non voglio correre <br>Non ho fretta, non voglio correre <br>Non ho fretta, non voglio correre <br><br>Non voglio correre, non voglio correre <br>Sono tornato, sono tornato, sono tornato, si <br>Come un tornado, come un tornado, come un tornado, bang <br>Sono tornato, sono tornato, sono tornato, eh <br>Come un tornado, come un tornado <br>Come un tornado, bang bang <br><br>Io che ho fatto un po' tutto Io che ho fatto un po' tutto <br>Mi sono fatto un po' tutto Mi sono fatto un po' tutto <br>Io che ho fatto un po' tutto Io che ho fatto un po' tutto <br>Mi sono fatto un po' tutto Proprio io si <br>Tu che hai fatto un po' tutto Tu che hai fatto un po' tutto <br>E ti sei fatto un po' tutto E ti sei fatto un po' tutto <br>Abbiamo fatto un po' tutto Abbiamo fatto un po' tutto <br>Ci siamo fatti un po' tutto Ci siamo fatti un po' tutto <br><br>Non la tocchi la mia mmh <br>Non la tocchi la mia mmh <br>Saluto Kemel, mangio falafel <br>Da piazzale Cuoco torno in Calvairate <br>Vado prima che mi inghiottisca <br>Questa fogna e la mia fortuna <br>Siete poltiglia, Nebbia fai il tuo <br>In zona e Cortina, un piano cottura <br><br>Ok, stiamo lavorando al disco <br>Siamo incazzati neri, sono con Nebbia <br>E abbiamo piu fame di quella <br>Che avevamo ai tempi di Sissignore <br><br>Non la tocchi la mia mmh <br>Non la tocchi la mia mmh <br>Saluto Kemel, mangio falafel <br>Da piazzale Cuoco torno in Calvairate <br>Vado prima che mi inghiottisca <br>Questa fogna e la mia fortuna <br>Siete poltiglia, Nebbia fai il tuo <br>In zona e Cortina, un piano cottura <br><br>Sono tornato, sono tornato, sono tornato si <br>Come un tornado, come un tornado, come un tornado <br>Sono tornato, sono tornato, sono tornato, eh <br>Come un tornado, come un tornado, come un tornado <br>Bang bang, bang bang <br><br>Oh Mirko, stai arrivando <br>Dai che io ho gia ordinato una cifra di pesce <br>Senti un attimo, il pandino mettilo dentro quando arrivi eh <br>Intanto ho riascoltato i pezzi, ma che bombe sono]]></content><category term="Rkomi" label="Rkomi"/><category term="Rossetto" label="Rossetto"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Angie/Spun/</id><title>Angie - Spun - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:24:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:24:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Angie/Spun/" title="Angie - Spun - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Avoid eye contact, you want it, I know it's a fact <br>Yeah, you want that snatch but I am moving too fast <br>Every morning violet sky breaks up the ice <br>Living on em' lies, my perfect paradise <br><br>I smoke it, I snort it, I roll it, love it <br>I buy it, I pop it, I want it, I love it <br><br>I'm spun, hit me up, light me up, then we can go for the crime <br>I'm spun, candy eyes in the night, babe, you might like my vibe <br>I'm spun, put a line on the time tracks, you stay on my grind <br>So spun, so spun, so spun <br><br>I got company, borderline disorder, that's me <br>Manic energy, can't you see I'm living the dream <br>Every morning violet sky breaks up the ice <br>Living on em' lies, my perfect paradise <br><br>I'm spun, hit me up, light me up, then we can go for the crime <br>I'm spun, candy eyes in the night, babe, you might like my vibe <br>I'm spun, put a line on the time tracks, you stay on my grind <br>So spun, so spun, so spun <br>I'm spun <br>I'm spun <br>So spun, so spun, so spun <br><br>I smoke it, I snort it, I roll it, I love it <br>I buy it, I pop it, I want it, I love it <br>I smoke it, I snort it, I roll it, I love it <br>I buy it, I pop it, I want it, I love it <br><br>I'm spun, hit me up, light me up, then we can go for the crime <br>I'm spun, candy eyes in the night, babe, you might like my vibe <br>I'm spun, put a line on the time tracks, you stay on my grind <br>So spun, so spun, so spun <br>I'm spun <br>I'm spun <br>So spun, so spun, so spun]]></content><category term="Angie" label="Angie"/><category term="Spun" label="Spun"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clean_Bandit/Rockabye_Feat_Sean_Paul__Anne-Marie_Ryan_Riback_Remix/</id><title>Clean Bandit - Rockabye (Feat. Sean Paul &amp; Anne-Marie) (Ryan Riback Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:24:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:24:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clean_Bandit/Rockabye_Feat_Sean_Paul__Anne-Marie_Ryan_Riback_Remix/" title="Clean Bandit - Rockabye (Feat. Sean Paul &amp; Anne-Marie) (Ryan Riback Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[call it love and devotion <br>call it a mom's adoration <br>foundation <br>a special bond of creation, hah <br>for all the single moms out there <br>going through frustration <br>clean bandit, sean-da-paul, anne-marie <br>sing, make them hear <br>she works the nights, by the water <br>she's gone astray, so far away <br>from her father's daughter <br>she just wants a life for her baby <br>all on her own, no one will come <br>she's got to save him(daily struggle) <br>she tells him, "Oh, love, no one's ever gonna hurt you, love <br>i'm gonna give you all of my love <br>nobody matters like you" <br>(stay out there, stay out there) <br>she tells him, "Your life ain't gonna be nothing like my life <br>You're gonna grow and have a good life <br>i'm gonna do what I've got to do" <br>(stay out there, stay out there) <br>so, rockabye baby, rockabye <br>i'm gonna rock you <br>rockabye baby, don't you cry <br>somebody's got you <br>rockabye baby, rockabye <br>i'm gonna rock you <br>rockabye baby, don't you cry <br>rockabye, no <br>rockabye-rocka-rocka-rocka-bye <br>(rockbye, yeah oh oh) <br>rockabye-rocka-rocka-rocka-bye <br>single mama you doing out there <br>facing the hard life, without no fear (yeah) <br>just so you know that you really care <br>cause any obstracle come you're well prepared(oh no) <br>and no mama, you never shed tear <br>cause you have to shed things year after year <br>and you give the youth love beyond compare(yeah) <br>you find his school fee and the bus fare(yeah) <br>Mmm, Marie, the papas'disappear <br>in the round back can't find him nowhere <br>steadily you work flow, everything you know <br>so you nah stop no time-no time for your jear <br>now she got a six-year-old <br>trying to keep him warm <br>trying to keep out the cold <br>when he looks in her eyes <br>he don't know he is safe <br>when she says "oh, love, no one's ever gonna hurt you, love <br>i'm gonna give you all of my love <br>nobody matters like you" <br>sorockabye baby, rockabye <br>i'm gonna rock you <br>rockabye baby, don't you cry <br>somebody's got you <br>rockabye baby, rockabye <br>i'm gonna rock you <br>rockabye baby, don't you cry <br>(oh-badda-bang-bang-bang, alringt then) <br>rockabye, no <br>rockabye-rocka-rocka-rocka-bye <br>(rockabye, yeah oh oh) <br>rockabye-rocka-rocka-rocka-bye <br>rockabye, don't bother cry <br>lift up your head, lift it up to the sky <br>rockabye, don't bother cry <br>angels surround you, just dry your eye <br>now she got a six-year-old <br>trying to keep him warm <br>trying to keep out the cold <br>when he lookcs in her eyes <br>he don't know he is safe <br>she tells him, "oh, love, no one's ever gonna hurt you, love <br>i'm gonna give you all of my love <br>nobody matters like you" <br>(stay out there, stay out there) <br>she tells him, "your life ain't gonna be nothing like my life <br>you're gonna grow and have a good life <br>i'm gonna do what i've got to do <br>(stay out there, stay out there) <br>so, rockabye baby, rockabye <br>(rockabye-rocka-rocka-rocka-rocka-bye) <br>i'm gonna rock you <br>rockabye baby, don't you cry <br>(rockabye-rocka-rocka-rocka-bye) <br>somebody's got you <br>rockabye baby, rockabye <br>(rockabye-rocka-rocka-rocka-bye) <br>i'm gonna rock you <br>rockabye baby, don't you cry <br>(oh-badda-bang-bang-bang, alright then) <br>rockabye <br>rockabye, don't bother ry <br>lift up your head, lift it up to the sky(rockabye) <br>rockabye, don't bother cry(yeah) <br>angels surround you, just dry your eye(yeah) <br>rockabye, don't bother cry(no) <br>lift up you head, lift it up to the sky(oh) <br>rockabye, don't bother cry <br>angels surround you, just dry your eye]]></content><category term="Clean Bandit" label="Clean Bandit"/><category term="Rockabye (Feat. Sean Paul &amp; Anne-Marie) (Ryan Riback Remix)" label="Rockabye (Feat. Sean Paul &amp; Anne-Marie) (Ryan Riback Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/From_The_Blue/Good_Times/</id><title>From The Blue - Good Times - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:26:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:26:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/From_The_Blue/Good_Times/" title="From The Blue - Good Times - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The days are gone <br>With no satisfaction <br>We have paid our future <br>Only to get a pile of ashes <br>Now I can only see <br>A monster in the mirror <br>We are too far from home <br>From what we wanna be <br>Bring me back to the time <br>Back to the days I walked my way <br>Now I realize that <br>I'm just holding a broken dream <br>Bring me back to the time <br>Back to the days <br>I kicked those worries <br>Give me the strength <br>to save myself from this madness <br>A piece of memory in my life <br>always smiling at me <br>Could we laugh as <br>we had done once more <br>I hope I could be there again <br>Good times have passed away <br>I have chased what I'd already had <br>Everlasting dreams <br>vanished from my heart <br>I dream where I left behind <br>So much weight on my shoulders <br>makes me feel that I am nothing <br>Happiness will die away <br>If we find ourselves in good times <br>Bring me back to the time <br>Back to the days <br>I kicked those worries <br>Give me the strength <br>To save myself from this madness <br>Good times have passed away <br>I have chased what I'd already had <br>Everlasting dreams <br>vanished from my heart <br>I dream where I left behind <br>Bring me back to the time <br>Bring me back <br>Good times have passed away <br>I have chased what I'd already had <br>Everlasting dreams <br>vanished from my heart <br>I dream where I left behind <br>Good times have passed away <br>I have chased what I'd already had <br>Everlasting dreams <br>vanished from my heart <br>I dream where I left behind <br>]]></content><category term="From The Blue" label="From The Blue"/><category term="Good Times" label="Good Times"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/From_The_Blue/Of_The_Night/</id><title>From The Blue - Of The Night - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:26:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:26:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/From_The_Blue/Of_The_Night/" title="From The Blue - Of The Night - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This night is mine <br>Now this is the war <br>You’ll see the fiercest fight your own <br>Show me what you’ve desired <br>Take the crown or be a failure <br>Burn this place <br>Light the fire in your soul <br>Stand tall <br>Give a shot It never comes again <br>See what is happened <br>Come closer to the core of the night <br>You’ll take the triumph <br>This night will come <br>to you <br>See what is happened <br>Come closer to the core of the night <br>You’ll take the triumph <br>This night will come to you <br>The time has come <br>Don’t look back with a regret <br>The time has come <br>The throne is waiting for you <br>See what is happened <br>Come closer to the core of the night <br>You’ll take the triumph <br>This night will come <br>The sun is hiding far <br>beyond the horizon <br>Stars will shine on you <br>will shine on you <br>The time has come <br>the throne is waiting for you <br>This night this night is MINE <br>This night will be mine <br>Light the fire in your soul <br>Give a shot It never comes again <br>Light the fire in your soul <br>The throne is waiting for you <br>]]></content><category term="From The Blue" label="From The Blue"/><category term="Of The Night" label="Of The Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동요세상/알파벳송/</id><title>동요세상 - 알파벳송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:26:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:26:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81/%EC%95%8C%ED%8C%8C%EB%B2%B3%EC%86%A1/" title="동요세상 - 알파벳송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[에이비씨디 이에프쥐 <br>에이치아이제이케이엘엠엔 <br>오피큐알에스티유 <br>브이더블유엑스와이제트 <br><br>재미있는 알파벳 <br>공부하며 놀아요 <br>친구들과 다 같이 <br>알파벳을 외워요 <br><br>에이비씨디 이에프쥐 <br>에이치아이제이케이엘엠엔 <br>오피큐알에스티유 <br>브이더블유엑스와이제트 <br><br>에이비씨디 이에프쥐 <br>에이치아이제이케이엘엠엔 <br>오피큐알에스티유 <br>브이더블유엑스와이제트 <br><br>재미있는 알파벳 <br>공부하며 놀아요 <br>친구들과 다 같이 <br>알파벳을 외워요 <br><br>에이비씨디 이에프쥐 <br>에이치아이제이케이엘엠엔 <br>오피큐알에스티유 <br>브이더블유엑스와이제트]]></content><category term="동요세상" label="동요세상"/><category term="알파벳송" label="알파벳송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/魔法鏡___Magic_Mirror/</id><title>Radwimps - 魔法鏡 / Magic Mirror - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:27:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:27:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/%E9%AD%94%E6%B3%95%E9%8F%A1___Magic_Mirror/" title="Radwimps - 魔法鏡 / Magic Mirror - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[탓타히토츠다케아야메타토시테모 <br>탓타히토츠다케키즈츠케타토시테모 <br>사바카레나이이노치가코코니아루요 <br>코노테노이치방소바니 <br><br>키즈츠케아우코토와데키테모 <br>소노테와니기레와시나쿠테 <br>코에와챤토키코에테이루노니 <br>보쿠노코마쿠와유레나이노 <br><br>모우스코시다케코노마부타니놋테테 <br>이츠닷테소우미에루노와히토리다케 <br>모우스코시다케소노코에후루와세테테 <br>나키타이노니나케누나라와라에바이이 <br><br>탓타히토츠다케키라와레타토시테모 <br>탓타히토츠다케우라기라레타토시테모 <br>키미오하나사나이이노치가아룬다요 <br>소노테노이치방소바니 <br><br>소레오마못테이케루노카나 <br>나쿠사나이데이라레루카나 <br>나쿠시타쿠테모나쿠세야시나이요 <br>보쿠와보쿠오야메레나이노 <br><br>모우스코시다케코노마부타니놋테테 <br>테라시다시테모미에루노와히토리다케 <br>모우스코시다케소노코에후루와세테테 <br>나키타이테모야마누나라우타에바이이 <br><br>키미와키미오마모레루카나유우키노츠카이카타가와카루카나 <br>키미와킷토니가테다카라데키루코토와보쿠모테츠다우카라 <br>쿠치다케와탓샤나아이츠와킷토네하즈카시가리야다카라 <br>카가미니와우츠라나이케도무코우가와데키미오미테루카라 <br><br>모우스코시다케코노마부타니놋테테 <br>이츠닷테소우우츠루노와히토리다케 <br>모시카시테사아노토키노카가미노 <br>나키다시소우나카오시타아노보쿠와]]></content><category term="Radwimps" label="Radwimps"/><category term="魔法鏡 / Magic Mirror" label="魔法鏡 / Magic Mirror"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/オ-ダ-メイド___Ordermade/</id><title>Radwimps - オ-ダ-メイド / Ordermade - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:27:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:27:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/%E3%82%AA-%E3%83%80-%E3%83%A1%E3%82%A4%E3%83%89___Ordermade/" title="Radwimps - オ-ダ-メイド / Ordermade - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[킷토보쿠와아타스네라레탄다로 <br>우마레루마에도코카노다레카니 <br>미라이토가코도치라가히토츠오 <br>미레루요우니시테아게루카라사 <br>돗치가이이? 돗치가이이? <br><br>소시테보쿠와가코오에란단다로 <br>츠요이히토요리야사시이히토니 <br>나레루요우니나레마스요우니토 <br>오모이뎃테난다카와카루요우니 <br><br>츠즈케테다레카상와보쿠니이우 <br>우데모아시모구치모미미모메모 <br>심조모옵파이모하나노아나모 <br>후타츠즈츠츠케테아게루카라네 <br>이이데쇼? 이이데쇼? <br><br>다케도보쿠와오네가이시탄다요 <br>구치와히토츠다케데이이데스토 <br>보쿠가히토리데켄카시나이요우니 <br>히토리도다케키스가데키루요우니 <br><br>와스레타이데모와스레나이 <br>콘나오모이오난토요부노카이 <br><br>스코시후키겐나카오노소노히토와 <br>마타시카타나쿠하나시하지메타 <br>이치방다이지나심조오와사 <br>료오무네니츠케테아게루카라네 <br>이이데쇼? 이이데쇼? <br><br>마타마타보쿠와오네가이시탄다 <br>오소레이리마스가코노보쿠니와 <br>미기가와노심조오와이리마센 <br>와가마마바카리잇테스미마센 <br><br>보쿠니다이세츠나히토가데키테 <br>소노코다키시메루토키하지메테 <br>후타츠노코도오가챤토무네노 <br>료오와가데나루노가와카루요우니 <br><br>히다리와보쿠노데미기와키미노 <br>히다리와키미노데미기와보쿠노 <br>히토리쟈도코카카케테루요우니 <br>히토리데나도이키테카나이요우니 <br><br>와스레타이데모와스레나이 <br>콘나오모이오난토요부노카이 <br>무네가사와가시이데모나츠카시이 <br>콘나오모이오난토요부노카이 <br><br>소이에바사이고니모우히토츠다케 <br>나미다모옵숀데츠케요우카? <br>나쿠테모젠젠신쇼우와나이케도 <br>멘도다카랏테츠케나이히토모이루요 <br>도우스루? 도우스루? <br><br>소시테보쿠와오네가이시탄다요 <br>츠요이히토요리야사시이히토니 <br>나레루요우니나레마스요우니토 <br>다이세츠테난다카와카루요우니 <br><br>쟈아치나미니나미다노아지다케도모 <br>키미노스키나아지오에란데요 <br>스파쿠시타리시옷파쿠시타리 <br>카라시쿠시타리아오마쿠시타리 <br>도레데모스키나노오에란데요 <br>도레가이이? 도레가이이? <br><br>노조미도리스베테가 <br>카나에라레테이루데쇼우? <br>다카라나미다니쿠레루 <br>소노카오오챤토미세테요 <br>사아호코라시게니미세테요 <br><br>혼토니아리가토고자이마시타 <br>이로이로토오테스오카케마시타 <br>사이고니히토츠다케이이데스카? <br><br>돗카데오아이시타코토아리마스카?]]></content><category term="Radwimps" label="Radwimps"/><category term="オ-ダ-メイド / Ordermade" label="オ-ダ-メイド / Ordermade"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Remelody/사랑하긴_했었다면/</id><title>Remelody - 사랑하긴 했었다면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:27:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:27:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Remelody/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%98%EA%B8%B4_%ED%96%88%EC%97%88%EB%8B%A4%EB%A9%B4/" title="Remelody - 사랑하긴 했었다면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 넌 아무말도 못하니 <br>눈물만 흘릴거니 <br>무슨 말을 준비한거니 <br>설마 이별인거니 <br>왜 넌 나를 보지도 않니 <br>이제는 둘이 아닌가봐 <br>무슨 말이든 해야 하는데 <br>어떤 말보다 그냥 눈물이 흘러 <br>사랑하긴 했었다면 <br>조금은 날 생각한다면 <br>거짓말이라도 제발 해줘 <br>되돌릴 수 있다는 말 <br>그냥 해줘 <br>왜 넌 굳이 떠나려 하니 <br>이미 네 맘은 괜찮은가봐 <br>벌써 내일이 난 두려운데 <br>끝이라는 걸 혼자라는 걸 <br>정말 믿어야 하는거니 <br>사랑하긴 했었다면 <br>조금은 날 생각한다면 <br>거짓말이라도 제발 해줘 <br>되돌릴 수 있다는 말 <br>]]></content><category term="Remelody" label="Remelody"/><category term="사랑하긴 했었다면" label="사랑하긴 했었다면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/세비야/사랑_노래/</id><title>세비야 - 사랑 노래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:27:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:27:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%B8%EB%B9%84%EC%95%BC/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="세비야 - 사랑 노래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[말 안 해도 알아요 <br>얼굴에 써있네요 <br>얼마나 나를 사랑하는지 <br>어린아이 같은 <br>그대 눈빛이 말해주네요 <br>이런 사랑은 또 없다고 <br>오 난 정말이지 행복해요 <br>그대와 함께 있다면 정말 <br>Oh I see you <br>Singing I love you <br>그댈 위해 노래하네 <br>I can say all day always love you <br>Singing I love you <br>사랑 노랠 불러 <br>그댈 위한 사랑 노래 <br>오 난 정말이지 행복해요 <br>그대와 함께 있다면 <br>Oh I see you <br>Singing I love you <br>그댈 위해 노래하네 <br>I can say all day always love you <br>Singing I love you <br>사랑 노랠 불러 <br>그댈 위한 사랑 노래 <br>]]></content><category term="세비야" label="세비야"/><category term="사랑 노래" label="사랑 노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코드코즈_Chord_Coze/Night/</id><title>코드코즈 (Chord Coze) - Night - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:27:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:27:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%93%9C%EC%BD%94%EC%A6%88_Chord_Coze/Night/" title="코드코즈 (Chord Coze) - Night - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑하는 그대와 함께 눈을 감고 <br>한 곳을 바라보면 느껴지는 상상 <br>밤하늘에 별이 쏟아지는 듯한 <br>상상이 현실이 되는 기분 <br>Tonight tonight <br>그대 오늘 밤 <br>어떤 꿈을 꾸는지 궁금해 <br>웃고 있는 모습이 <br>꿈속에 취한 듯 <br>추운 밤도 잊은 듯 <br>별에 물들어 밤에 취한 얼굴 <br>깨우기 아깝죠 <br>캄캄한 하늘에 흐르는 <br>빛줄기를 타고 <br>함께 여행하는 기분 Tonight <br>Hold on take your time <br>Hold my hands <br>We're going across the starlight <br>We didn't say and <br>Didn't even hesitate the moment <br>Tonight <br>그대 꿈에 뭘 찾고 있나 <br>별빛이 흐르는 하늘 <br>보고 있나요 <br>꿈속에 취한듯한 밤의 얼굴 <br>Tonight tonight tonight <br>tonight tonight <br>Fast and slow that our memories <br>Hold on take your time <br>Hold my hands <br>We're going across the starlight <br>We didn't say and <br>Didn't even hesitate the moment <br>Hold on take your time <br>Hold my hands <br>We're going across the starlight <br>We didn't say and <br>Didn't even hesitate the moment <br>]]></content><category term="코드코즈 (Chord Coze)" label="코드코즈 (Chord Coze)"/><category term="Night" label="Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스페이스_보이_Space_Boy/That_Time_That_Space/</id><title>스페이스 보이 (Space Boy) - That Time That Space - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:31:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:31:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8E%98%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4_%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4_Space_Boy/That_Time_That_Space/" title="스페이스 보이 (Space Boy) - That Time That Space - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그 공간 그 설레임 가득한 <br>따뜻함에 넌 꿈처럼 <br>달콤하게 다가왔죠 그대 <br>그 공간 햇살 아래 <br>우연히 맑았던 날씨 <br>따뜻함에 나는 <br>녹아버리는걸 어떡하죠 <br>그대 마음 속에 그대 눈빛 속에 <br>나도 알 수 없는 이런 마음을 <br>나도 알 수 없는 이런 기분을 <br>그대 마음 속에 그대 눈빛 속에 <br>우리 함께 할 수 있는 시간을 <br>우리 함께 할 수 있는 사랑을 <br>그 시간 그 설레임 가득한 <br>포근함에 넌 꿈처럼 <br>달콤하게 다가왔죠 그 날 <br>그 시간 햇살 아래 <br>우연히 맑았던 날씨 <br>포근함에 나는 <br>녹아버리는걸 어떡하죠 <br>그대 마음 속에 그대 눈빛 속에 <br>나도 알 수 없는 이런 마음을 <br>나도 알 수 없는 이런 기분을 <br>그대 마음 속에 그대 눈빛 속에 <br>우리 함께 할 수 있는 시간을 <br>우리 함께 할 수 있는 사랑을 <br>]]></content><category term="스페이스 보이 (Space Boy)" label="스페이스 보이 (Space Boy)"/><category term="That Time That Space" label="That Time That Space"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조지훈/Emotion_이모션/</id><title>조지훈 - Emotion (이모션) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:31:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:31:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%A7%80%ED%9B%88/Emotion_%EC%9D%B4%EB%AA%A8%EC%85%98/" title="조지훈 - Emotion (이모션) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[햇살처럼 그대 머리위로 <br>My emotion <br>순간마다 문득 니 생각에 <br>My emotion <br>이젠 멈출 수 없어 난 다 <br>내 맘을 적시고 싶어 <br>그대 <br>지금 사랑은 내게 <br>내 맘은 그대 <br>온종일 내겐 <br>그대향기 <br>이젠 So much I love you <br>how to stay <br>Than I so much I love you <br>how to stay <br>넌 아침 하늘 푸르른 날의 꿈처럼 <br>So much I love you <br>오늘 하루 그대 생각으로 <br>My emotion <br>웃고 있는 그대 떠올라서 <br>My emotion <br>이젠 멈출 수 없어 난 다 <br>내 맘을 적시고 싶어 <br>그대 <br>지금 사랑은 내게 <br>내 맘은 그대 <br>온종일 내겐 <br>그대향기 <br>이젠 So much I love you <br>how to stay <br>Than I so much I love you <br>how to stay <br>넌 아침 하늘 푸르른 날의 꿈처럼 <br>So much I love you <br>햇살처럼 따뜻한 너 <br>간직해줘 나의 고마운 사람아 <br>햇살처럼 그대 머리위로 <br>my emotion <br>순간마다 문득 니 생각에 <br>my emotion <br>이젠 So much I love you <br>how to stay <br>Than I so much I love you <br>how to stay <br>넌 아침 하늘 푸르른 날의 꿈처럼 <br>So much I love you <br>]]></content><category term="조지훈" label="조지훈"/><category term="Emotion (이모션)" label="Emotion (이모션)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유형균/벚꽃이_피면/</id><title>유형균 - 벚꽃이 피면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:31:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:31:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%ED%98%95%EA%B7%A0/%EB%B2%9A%EA%BD%83%EC%9D%B4_%ED%94%BC%EB%A9%B4/" title="유형균 - 벚꽃이 피면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흐드러지게 핀 사월에 <br>그대는 서럽게 울었지 <br>길 위에 뿌려진 <br>복잡한 감정들 사이에 <br>지난날 잘못과 후회들 <br>아아아 부디 이해해줄래 <br>아아아 이게 마지막일 테니 <br>벚꽃이 피면 벚꽃이 지면 <br>그 간절했던 곧 추억이 된 <br>오 고맙던 그대 생각에 <br>또 눈물이 나 <br>널 위한 고백 널 위한 눈물 <br>널 노래했던 지난날 속에 <br>오 이제는 <br>흐드러지게 진 사월에 <br>그대는 서럽게 웃었지 <br>길 위에 뿌려진 <br>아련한 기억들 사이에 <br>지난날 원망과 미련들 <br>아아아 부디 이해해줄래 <br>아아아 정말 마지막일 테니 <br>벚꽃이 피면 벚꽃이 지면 <br>그 간절했던 곧 추억이 된 <br>오 고맙던 그대 생각에 <br>또 눈물이 나 <br>널 위한 고백 널 위한 눈물 <br>널 노래했던 지난날 속에 <br>오 이제는 <br>또 다시 <br>벚꽃이 피면 <br>]]></content><category term="유형균" label="유형균"/><category term="벚꽃이 피면" label="벚꽃이 피면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SUPERBEE/Look_At_It_Prod_By_N-Soul/</id><title>SUPERBEE - Look At It (Prod. By N-Soul) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:32:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:32:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SUPERBEE/Look_At_It_Prod_By_N-Soul/" title="SUPERBEE - Look At It (Prod. By N-Soul) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[whip whip whip it hard then I <br>nay nay <br>사고날 것 같이 드라이브해 <br>so reckless <br>선명하게 남긴 <br>스키드 마크 조심해 man <br>마치 운전대를 잡은듯이 난 랩해 <br>못 따라올꺼면 시도조차 <br>안 하는 걸 추천 <br>내 motormouth 마치 nascar <br>동네똥차인 너네 절대 못 쫓아와 <br>I go 0 to 100 gimchi <br>real quick real quick <br>errtime I backfire u go flinchin <br>gimchis be shittin on they jeans <br>Oh god oh god <br>These gimchis go hard as <br>mofuckers 좀 봐 <br>놀라워 놀라워 <br>어디까지 올라가나 끝을 몰라 <br>I'll let you take a look at it <br>내 지갑 내 가방 내 벨트 <br>Hermes Gucci LV <br>3000 dollars on rent <br>누군가는 묻겠지 <br>man fuck 니가 어떻게 대체 <br>Three words for ya look at it <br>Two words for ya <br>I'm good That's it <br>이거 봐봐 yay yay <br>지갑 안은 yay yay <br>항상 얇아 yay yay <br>카드 한장 yay yay <br>Look at it tho <br>Petal to the metal makin dough <br>Look at it tho <br>나때문에 너넨 불쌍해지고 <br>Lookin Lookin Lookin Lookin <br>Lookin Look at it <br>Lookin Lookin Lookin Look at it ya <br>Lookin Lookin Lookin Lookin Lookin <br>Lookin Lookin Lookin Look at it ya <br>allday errday 82 day <br>다음은 day date 손목가리개 <br>유럽인이 만든 옷 파리지앵 <br>nobody에서 somebody 돼 woo <br>저걸 내가 가지게 해 woo <br>you know i gotta get it woo <br>그걸 내가 가지게 해 woo <br>you know i gotta get it woo <br>누가 불장난을 했어 내 phone <br>말했잖아 수백번 퇴학생이 교수처럼 <br>대학교를 배회하고 <br>사촌 아닌 것들까지 배아퍼 <br>황금보다 비싼 감정소비를 <br>내게 낭비하곤 <br>ay 난 그것도 몰라 <br>cuz i don't give a fuck <br>예쁜 음악 메이킹 <br>빼고는 일이 없어 <br>생각해보니 이건 내게 취미였어 <br>근데 돈까지 줘 <br>i mean like what the fuck <br>ay look at it 누가 행복하게 살아 <br>얘 look at it <br>재미로 했던게 여전히 재미고 <br>난 이제 유명해 look at it <br>괌에 3년안에 집을 지을거야 봐 <br>look at it ya <br>내 야망이 어디까지 가는지를 봐 <br>look at it ha <br>이거 봐봐 yay yay <br>지갑 안은 yay yay <br>항상 얇아 yay yay <br>카드 한장 yay yay <br>Look at it tho <br>Petal to the metal makin dough <br>Look at it tho <br>나때문에 너넨 불쌍해지고 <br>Lookin Lookin Lookin Lookin <br>Lookin Look at it <br>Lookin Lookin Lookin Look at it ya <br>Lookin Lookin Lookin Lookin Lookin <br>Lookin Lookin Lookin Look at it ya <br>]]></content><category term="SUPERBEE" label="SUPERBEE"/><category term="Look At It (Prod. By N-Soul)" label="Look At It (Prod. By N-Soul)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로맨틱_펀치/Zzz/</id><title>로맨틱 펀치 - Zzz - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:32:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:32:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%A7%A8%ED%8B%B1_%ED%8E%80%EC%B9%98/Zzz/" title="로맨틱 펀치 - Zzz - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사실은 너의 마음 속에 뜨는 달이 <br>어떤 색인지는 1도 관심 없어요 <br>그래요 그런 얘긴 니 방 <br>침대에 누워 <br>널 좋아하는 고양이에게나 <br>사실은 아까부터 일어나고 <br>싶었는데 <br>헛소리가 은근히 재미났어요 <br>그래도 그런 얘긴 니 방 <br>책상에 앉아 <br>널 기다리는 일기장에나 <br>이거 참 지루해 지루해 <br>이제 일어날래요 <br>잘 있어요 나는 집에 갈 거예요 <br>배고프고 졸리기도 하고 <br>잘 있어요 나는 집에 갈 거예요 <br>개똥 같은 소리 듣고 싶진 않아 <br>마냥 자기 멋에 취해 뱉는 말들 <br>뭔 소릴 하는지 1도 모르겠어요 <br>오히려 내가 이해 못 하는 거 라니 <br>참나 어이가 없단 말이야 <br>너무 큰 목소리 꾸며낸 유토피아 <br>헛소리죠 당신이나 잘하세요 <br>차라리 나는 티비 앞의 <br>소파에 누워 <br>탱글탱글한 사과나 먹을래 <br>이거 참 지루해 지루해 <br>이제 일어날래요 <br>잘 있어요 나는 집에 갈 거예요 <br>배고프고 졸리기도 하고 <br>잘 있어요 나는 집에 갈 거예요 <br>개똥 같은 소리 듣고 싶진 않아 <br>너의 신경 쓴 몸짓들까지도 <br>날 보며 꾸며진 표정들마저도 <br>모두 만들어진 네 세상이 <br>난 난 난 피곤하단 말야 <br>잘 있어요 나는 집에 갈 거예요 <br>배고프고 졸리기도 하고 <br>잘 있어요 나는 집에 갈 거예요 <br>개똥 같은 소리 듣고 싶진 않아 <br>잘 있어요 나는 집에 갈 거예요 <br>배고프고 졸리기도 하고 <br>잘 있어요 나는 집에 갈 거예요 <br>진심 없는 얘긴 듣고 싶진 않아요 <br>]]></content><category term="로맨틱 펀치" label="로맨틱 펀치"/><category term="Zzz" label="Zzz"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vera_Lynn/Well_Meet_Again_2017_Ver/</id><title>Vera Lynn - We`ll Meet Again (2017 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:32:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:32:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vera_Lynn/Well_Meet_Again_2017_Ver/" title="Vera Lynn - We`ll Meet Again (2017 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We'll meet again <br>We'll meet again <br>Don't know where <br>Don't know when <br>But I know we'll meet again some sunny day <br>Keep smiling through <br>Just like you always do <br>Till the blue skies drive the dark clouds far away <br><br>So will you please say Hello <br>To the folks that I know <br>Tell them I won't be long <br>They'll be happy to know <br>That as you saw me go <br>I was singing this song <br><br>We'll meet again <br>Don't know where <br>Don't know when <br>But I know we'll meet again some sunny day <br><br> We'll meet again <br>Don't know where <br>Don't know when <br>But I know we'll meet again some sunny day <br>Keep smiling through <br>Just like you always do <br>'Til the blue skies <br>Drive the dark clouds far away <br>So will you please sayHello <br>To the folks that I know <br>Tell them I won't be long <br>They'll be happy to know <br>That as you saw me go <br>I was singin' this song <br><br>We'll meet again <br>Don't know where <br>Don't know when <br>But I know we'll meet again some sunny day]]></content><category term="Vera Lynn" label="Vera Lynn"/><category term="We`ll Meet Again (2017 Ver.)" label="We`ll Meet Again (2017 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Manuel_Figueroa/Tierno_Pecado/</id><title>Jose Manuel Figueroa - Tierno Pecado - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:32:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:32:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Manuel_Figueroa/Tierno_Pecado/" title="Jose Manuel Figueroa - Tierno Pecado - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pasan los meses, pasan los anos <br>Y yo ausente <br>Tierno pecado, no esta a mi lado <br><br>No, no esta presente <br>Yo no sabia que sufriria <br>Y hoy mecayo el veinte <br>Se que he cambiado y su confianza <br>Ya no esta vigente <br>Sol que ilumina noches y soledad <br>Volver a sentir tu cuerpo hasta volar <br>Una vez mas y a tu lado quiero despertar <br>Ay resusito si es que tu perdon me das <br>Pasan los meses, pasan los anos <br>Y yo ausente <br>Tierno pecado, no esta a mi lado <br>No, no esta presente <br>Sol que ilumina noches y soledad <br>Volver a sentir tu cuerpo hasta volar <br>Una vez mas y a tu lado quiero despertar <br>Ay resusito si es que tanto amor me das <br>ay, resusito si es que tu perdon me das]]></content><category term="Jose Manuel Figueroa" label="Jose Manuel Figueroa"/><category term="Tierno Pecado" label="Tierno Pecado"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Niska/BOC/</id><title>Niska - B.O.C - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:34:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:34:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Niska/BOC/" title="Niska - B.O.C - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Que du sale, que du sale, que du sale <br>De la B <br>Charo c'est charo <br>Tu cours ou tu cours <br>Mais revenez, mais revenez <br>Mais pourquoi vous courez <br>Hey <br><br>Mon gava des gavas, gavon des gavons <br>24 sur 24, ca cotoie des plavons <br>Ici c'est charo, mes negros sont bavons <br>Moi, dans le bando, j'ai l'diplome du brave <br>J'suis a la salle, j'fais mes bravas bravo <br>J'suis venu representer Brazzaville <br>Y'a des metisses comme au Bresil, choque <br>Ce soir j'vais pas finir bredouille ah non <br>Qui veut me chercher des palabres <br>Va finir avec des balafres voila <br>Toujours un flingue quand je me balade normal <br>Ma cherie trouve que j'suis malade <br>Oh, bando na bando <br>J'controle le game, un peu comme Nintendo <br>Violent c'est violent, charo c'est charo charo <br>Oh, Seigneur, j'suis barjo <br>Bitches <br><br>Batards ont couru <br>Chiens, chiens <br>Ces batards ont couru <br>Mais pourquoi <br>Batards ont couru <br>Bando na bando <br>Ces batards ont couru <br>Batards, batards <br>Batards ont couru <br>Chiens, chiens <br>Ces batards ont couru <br>Oui <br>Batards ont couru <br>Allez reviens <br>Batards ont couru <br><br>Ces batards ont couru pourtant j'ai prevenu <br>Ils font les tetus, c'est nous les patrons <br>Toujours rester pro', former la compo' <br>Moi et mon equipe, on s'en fout de ta tronche <br>Non T'as mis des ballerines degage <br>Tu vas jamais dormir chez moi dommage <br>Collateraux sont les dommages c'est naze <br>Tu fais la mala mais tu pointes au chomage <br>Ma femme est belle car elle fait des gommages <br>C'est moi, j'entretiens ma nana bien sur <br>Tada, Djiri, Dakou, Niama <br>J'suis congolais comme N'Goma longwa <br>Quand j'n'ai pas de biff, je me sens mal voila <br>242, c'est normal <br>J'suis congolais comme N'Goma bantou <br>243, c'est normal <br>Bitches <br><br>Batards ont couru <br>Chiens, chiens <br>Ces batards ont couru <br>Mais pourquoi <br>Batards ont couru <br>Bando na bando <br>Ces batards ont couru <br>Batards, batards <br>Batards ont couru <br>Chiens, chiens <br>Ces batards ont couru <br>Oui <br>Batards ont couru <br>Allez reviens <br>Batards ont couru <br><br>Batards ont couru <br>Zifu' des Zifu' <br>Ces batards ont couru <br>'koro des 'koro <br>Batards ont couru <br>J'ai colle la petite <br>Ces batards ont couru <br>Elle a lache son mogo <br>Batards ont couru <br>'koro des Zifu' <br>Ces batards ont couru <br>Donc c'est Zifu' des 'koro <br>Batards ont couru <br>Oh, Zifu' des 'koro <br>Batards ont couru <br><br>Oui <br>Batards ont couru <br>Chiens, chiens <br>Ces batards ont couru <br>Mais pourquoi <br>Batards ont couru <br>Bando na bando <br>Ces batards ont couru <br>Batards, batards <br>Batards ont couru <br>Chiens, chiens <br>Ces batards ont couru <br>Oui <br>Batards ont couru <br>Allez, reviens <br>Batards ont couru <br><br>Batards ont couru <br>Ces batards ont couru <br>Batards ont couru <br>Ces batards ont couru <br>Batards ont couru <br>Batards ont couru]]></content><category term="Niska" label="Niska"/><category term="B.O.C" label="B.O.C"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mike_Will_Made-It/Aries_YuGo_Feat_Pharrell/</id><title>Mike Will Made-It - Aries (YuGo) (Feat. Pharrell) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:37:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:37:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mike_Will_Made-It/Aries_YuGo_Feat_Pharrell/" title="Mike Will Made-It - Aries (YuGo) (Feat. Pharrell) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hold up to be clear <br>I believe in miracles <br>But I don't believe in waiting for 'em Nah <br>You gotta make that shit happen <br>In ways they cannot imagine <br>Make them think it's magic Yeah <br>It ain't your chain or your vehicles <br>When you that nigga with the bag Yeah <br><br>Just be that nigga with the bag <br>So when they say Who is that <br>Oh, that's the nigga with the bag <br>They be like Who that rolling past <br>Oh, that's that nigga with the bag <br>Yugo, Yugo, Yugo <br>That Yugo, Yugo, Yugo <br>That Yugo, Yugo, Yugo <br>That Yugo, Yugo, Yugo <br><br>Let this motivate ya <br>Turn you up <br>Make you ravenous <br>You know they gon' try and curve you <br>You know they hate you <br>Don't let the fuck niggas burn you up <br>Use this as fuel <br>You know that deep down by that light out in the streets Yeah <br>So the gatekeepers hold up <br>They just let you go, Yugo, Yugo <br>Let you go , Yugo, Yugo <br><br>Just be that nigga with the bag <br>So when they say who is that <br>Oh, that's the nigga with the bag <br>That close encounter riding past What's that spaceship riding past <br>That be the nigga with the bag <br>Yugo ,Yugo, Yugo <br>That Yugo, Yugo, Yugo <br>That Yugo, Yugo, Yugo <br>That Yugo, Yugo <br><br>Skurt, Station Wagon P <br>I'm just dangling my keys <br>Open up the door and take the Danger out the G <br>Take the G out the danger with the alien degree <br>Paparazzi yelling freeze while the cops are yelling freeze <br>From the ambulance, that nigga dying in the street <br>He do the Hammer Dance and his killler blowing weed <br>Like it's some hammer pants <br>He is numb, he don't feel it like a pack of xans <br>They riding different colored ghosts like it's Pac Man <br>But don't run up on the window, you get blast man <br>I hear three sucka in the backseat yelling ''Yes man'' <br>They ain't your friend if shit go down and they leave your ass <br>I told you drones was on your home, need to free your ass <br>And once you learn it's your turn nigga we don't ask <br>We get a bag so big it has a hole in it, illegal paths <br>You see the math Follow <br>'Cause we see the path like we're giraffes Follow, follow <br><br>Hold up to be clear <br>I believe in miracles <br>But I don't believe in waiting for 'em <br>You gotta make that shit happen <br>And is a killing I'd imagine <br>Make them think it's magic Yeah <br>It ain't your chain or your vehicles <br>When you that nigga with the bands Yeah <br>Just be that nigga with the bag <br>So, when they say who is that <br>Oh, that's the nigga with the bag <br>You see that watch, that's made of glass <br>It's on the wrist they grab the bag <br>Yugo, Yugo, Yugo <br>That Yugo, Yugo, Yugo <br>That Yugo, Yugo, Yugo <br>That Yugo, Yugo <br><br>Remembers insecurity sets in <br>You ride around like the Jetson's <br>Your the sun's reflection <br>You shining, come on, hello <br><br>You see that watch, that's made of glass <br>It's on the wrist, they grab the bag <br>What was that spaceship ridin' past <br>Oh, that's the nigga with the bag <br>He do one prayer and then brag <br>That Yugo, Yugo, Yugo <br>Oh, that's the nigga with the bag <br>That Yugo, Yugo, Yugo <br>He do one prayer and then brag <br>Oh, that's the nigga with the bag]]></content><category term="Mike Will Made-It" label="Mike Will Made-It"/><category term="Aries (YuGo) (Feat. Pharrell)" label="Aries (YuGo) (Feat. Pharrell)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Local_Natives/I_Saw_You_Close_Your_Eyes/</id><title>Local Natives - I Saw You Close Your Eyes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:37:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:37:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Local_Natives/I_Saw_You_Close_Your_Eyes/" title="Local Natives - I Saw You Close Your Eyes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey now, is it the dawn or the end <br>The hours we talked <br>You wished we'd stopped <br>Acting like it's nothing at all <br>In the first act, you'll gun 'em all <br>The kick back in New York <br>Shoulder was always hard to ignore <br>Hey <br><br>Even if I'm on your side <br>I saw the way you close your eyes <br>Even if I'm on your side <br>I saw the way you close your eyes <br><br>Hey now, the slip, the doubt, the itch <br>You bow so long to live beyond <br>Now you're walking, humming your song <br>Mirror in the bathroom, nails getting long <br>Aw please, tell me I'm wrong <br>In the third act, it's gotta go off <br>Hey <br><br>Even if I'm on your side <br>I saw the way you close your eyes <br>Even if I'm on your side <br>I saw the way you close your eyes <br><br>Even if I'm on your side <br>I saw the way you close your eyes <br>Even if I'm on your side <br>I saw the way you close your eyes]]></content><category term="Local Natives" label="Local Natives"/><category term="I Saw You Close Your Eyes" label="I Saw You Close Your Eyes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로이도/예전엔_Rewind/</id><title>로이도 - 예전엔 (Rewind) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:37:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:37:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%84/%EC%98%88%EC%A0%84%EC%97%94_Rewind/" title="로이도 - 예전엔 (Rewind) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꽤 늦었던 시간 <br>내 눈앞에 넌 <br>너무 아름다운 채 있어 <br>니 옆에 남자완 <br>꽤 오래된 것 같아 girl <br>나를 떠난 그 날이 참 <br>가깝게만 느껴져 <br>나만 혼자 이런 게 난 <br>꽤 억울해져 baby <br>넌 여전히 그대로인 걸 느꼈어 <br>변함없는 미소 때문에 느꼈어 <br>나 없이도 행복할 수 있단 게 <br>내 가슴을 아프게 해 girl baby <br>눈을 마주칠 수 없었어 <br>난 여기에서 <br>멀리서 지켜 보는걸 <br>예전에 우릴 그리며 <br>내가 바라던 시선이 <br>남아있어 넌 여전히 <br>아직 지워지지 않은 널 <br>바라만 보아도 <br>다시 굳어가 천천히 <br>너를 잊기엔 난 아직 <br>시간이 좀 필요한 거 같아 <br>꽤 지났어도 <br>우리 예전엔 <br>누구 보다 빛난 사이였고 <br>우리 예전엔 <br>그 누구 보다 아름다웠어 <br>우리 예전엔 <br>그래 누구보다 더 <br>좋았었어 <br>네게 하나만 묻고 싶어 <br>Did U Miss me right <br>난 그 대답을 듣고 싶어 Ma Girl <br>이미 굳어버린 이 관계를 난 alright <br>다시 녹인다면 니 옆에 있는 건 <br>그 놈이 아니야 girl know it <br>수많았던 기억들이 날 스쳐가 <br>너와 웃던 많은 날들만 떠올라 <br>왜 이리도 너란 사람에게서 <br>벗어날 수 없는지 난 왜 babe <br>눈을 마주칠 수 없었어 <br>난 여기에서 <br>멀리서 지켜 보는걸 <br>예전에 우릴 그리며 <br>내가 바라던 시선이 <br>남아있어 넌 여전히 <br>아직 지워지지 않은 널 <br>바라만 보아도 <br>다시 굳어가 천천히 <br>너를 잊기엔 난 아직 <br>시간이 좀 필요한 거 같아 <br>꽤 지났어도 <br>우리 예전엔 <br>누구 보다 빛난 사이였고 <br>우리 예전엔 <br>그 누구 보다 아름다웠어 <br>우리 예전엔 <br>그래 누구보다 더 <br>좋았었어 <br>]]></content><category term="로이도" label="로이도"/><category term="예전엔 (Rewind)" label="예전엔 (Rewind)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박명수/Saxophone_Magic_Feat_유재환_초희/</id><title>박명수 - Saxophone Magic (Feat. 유재환, 초희) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:38:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:38:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EB%AA%85%EC%88%98/Saxophone_Magic_Feat_%EC%9C%A0%EC%9E%AC%ED%99%98_%EC%B4%88%ED%9D%AC/" title="박명수 - Saxophone Magic (Feat. 유재환, 초희) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[oh my god <br>눈이 막 돌아가 <br>여기저기 Hot한 Ladies <br>난 더 못 참아 <br>요즘 내 주가는 난리 <br>but i like to party G-PARK <br>풀어버려 나의 고삐 달려 오늘 밤 <br>다 섞어 섞어 목 적셔 적셔 <br>클럽 안에 우리들은 다 컸어 컸어 <br>벌써 벌써 뒤로 빼는 녀석 <br>신경 쓰지 말고 hold up <br>난 젊기 때문에 오늘은 좋기 때문에 <br>쭉 달려 달려 달려 OMG <br>oh my god <br>너와 나 너 바로 내 앞에 와 <br>oh my god <br>난 네게 너 바로 내 앞에 가 <br>이 밤이 지나고 <br>and never stop tonight <br>밤이 다 가기 전에 해가 뜨기 전에 <br>Saxophone Magic <br>Saxo Saxophone Magic <br>Saxo Saxophone Magic <br>Saxo Saxophone Magic <br>Saxo Saxophone Magic <br>Everybody 우리 모두 party <br>Everybody 난 내 맘대로 살래 <br>Everybody 우리 모두 party <br>Everybody 난 내 맘대로 살래 <br>다 섞어 섞어 목 적셔 적셔 <br>클럽 안에 우리들은 다 컸어 컸어 <br>벌써 벌써 뒤로 빼는 녀석 <br>신경 쓰지 말고 hold up <br>난 젊기 때문에 오늘은 좋기 때문에 <br>쭉 달려 달려 달려 OMG <br>oh my god <br>너와 나 너 바로 내 앞에 와 <br>oh my god <br>난 네게 너 바로 내 앞에 가 <br>이 밤이 지나고 <br>and never stop tonight <br>밤이 다 가기 전에 해가 뜨기 전에 <br>Saxophone Magic <br>Saxo Saxophone Magic <br>Saxo Saxophone Magic <br>Saxo Saxophone Magic <br>Saxo Saxophone Magic <br>oh Friday night <br>아무 생각하지 마 시작해 <br>after party <br>oh G.PARK 볼륨을 높여줘 <br>tonight OMG <br>oh my god <br>너와 나 너 바로 내 앞에 와 <br>oh my god <br>난 네게 너 바로 내 앞에 가 <br>이 밤이 지나고 <br>and never stop tonight <br>밤이 다 가기 전에 해가 뜨기 전에 <br>Saxophone Magic <br>Saxo Saxophone Magic <br>Saxo Saxophone Magic <br>Saxo Saxophone Magic <br>Saxo Saxophone Magic <br>]]></content><category term="박명수" label="박명수"/><category term="Saxophone Magic (Feat. 유재환, 초희)" label="Saxophone Magic (Feat. 유재환, 초희)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesus_Ojeda_Y_Sus_Parientes/No_Es_Un_Juego/</id><title>Jesus Ojeda Y Sus Parientes - No Es Un Juego - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:40:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:40:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesus_Ojeda_Y_Sus_Parientes/No_Es_Un_Juego/" title="Jesus Ojeda Y Sus Parientes - No Es Un Juego - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No es un juego que me gustes mas de lo indicado <br>No es un juego lo que ya siento por ti <br>Tu me gustas y me gusta mas que se me note <br>Y ojala te dieras cuenta que me haces muy feliz <br><br>No es un juego que te llame por las madrugadas <br>Solamente para escucharte hablar <br>No puedo dormir si no me das las buenas noches <br>Tengo muchas pesadillas, es mas que la verdad <br><br>Y no es un juego cuando digo que te quiero <br>Cuando digo que en tus ojos encontre lo que buscaba <br>Porque desde que llegaste, aunque tu no me lo creas <br>Ya no me hace falta nada <br><br>Y no es un juego el carino que te tengo <br>Porque en muy poquito tiempo aprendi a necesitarte <br>No es un juego lo que siento, soy completamente tuyo <br>Desde que tu me besaste <br><br>Y no es un juego cuando digo que te quiero <br>Cuando digo que en tus ojos encontre lo que buscaba <br>Porque desde que llegaste, aunque tu no me lo creas <br>Ya no me hace falta nada <br><br>Y no es un juego el carino que te tengo <br>Porque en muy poquito tiempo aprendi a necesitarte <br>No es un juego lo que siento, soy completamente tuyo <br>Desde que tu me besaste]]></content><category term="Jesus Ojeda Y Sus Parientes" label="Jesus Ojeda Y Sus Parientes"/><category term="No Es Un Juego" label="No Es Un Juego"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/47/WL/</id><title>47 - WL - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:40:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:40:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/47/WL/" title="47 - WL - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ay yeah 나는 잘 몰라 <br>그냥 너가 좋아 <br>딱히 없어 그런 거창한 이유는 <br>그거뿐이야 <br>너가 눈을 맞춘다면 <br>나는 웃을 거고 <br>입을 맞춰도 그냥 웃을 거야 <br>keep touching 너의 그 긴 머리 <br>밑 잘록한 허리 더 밑까지 <br>my God I can’t talk too much <br>너무 좋아 너의 눈이 <br>다 사라지는 미소가 <br>oh God 안돼 그만해 나 지옥 가 <br>늦은 밤 너의 푹 파인 탑에 <br>I said woo <br>뭐 어쩌겠어 <br>나는 20대 남자야 <br>what should I do <br>합을 맞춰 하나 둘 ay ay <br>에이 나는 너무 20대 남자야 <br>하얘져 내 머리 속은 <br>너를 볼 때마다 <br>다 예뻐서 그냥 난 웃음이 나와 <br>깊게 생각 안 할래 <br>그냥 난 이게 좋은데 <br>아 몰라 그냥 <br>우리 하던 거나 마저 하자 <br>one and two three four five <br>아주 오랜 시간 동안 <br>나는 참고 있었다고 <br>six seven eight nine ten <br>나는 이젠 나를 벗어 던질 거야 so I say <br>Baby you gotta kill me <br>Baby you gotta kill me <br>Baby you gotta kill me <br>Baby you gotta <br>나는 20대 남자 <br>너는 30대 여자 <br>너 나이가 너의 유일한 <br>아킬레스건이야 <br>아닌 듯 불현듯 난 생각했어 <br>아무리 무겁더라도 <br>나이는 내가 다 들기로 생각했어 <br>난 여전히 어린 놈이지 <br>만날 때마다 <br>나는 외모가 보이지 <br>솔직히 할게 <br>나는 엉덩이를 좋아해 <br>정말로 나는 엉덩이를 좋아해 <br>정죄하지마 나를 정죄하지마 <br>나도 내 죌 알고 <br>이래봬도 내가 설 델 아니까 <br>나는 너 앞에 서려고 <br>만들어진 듯해 <br>순결을 탐할 땐 칼 들어 찌를래 <br>부모를 떠나서 한 몸이 되자 <br>난 그 밤과 아침을 <br>바라고 있어 그냥 쉽게 가 <br>나는 20대 남자 <br>너는 30대 여자 <br>사랑이라면 우리가 가진 <br>아킬레스건 따위 nonsense baby <br>one and two three four five <br>아주 오랜 시간 동안 <br>나는 참고 있었다고 <br>six seven eight nine ten <br>나는 이젠 나를 벗어 던질 거야 so I say <br>Baby you gotta kill me <br>Baby you gotta kill me <br>Baby you gotta kill me <br>Baby you gotta <br>죽겠어 <br>Baby you gotta kill me <br>Baby you gotta kill me <br>Baby you gotta kill me <br>Baby you gotta <br>Baby you gotta kill me <br>Baby you gotta kill me <br>Baby you gotta kill me <br>Baby you gotta <br>죽겠어 <br>Baby you gotta kill me <br>Baby you gotta kill me <br>Baby you gotta kill me <br>Baby you gotta <br>]]></content><category term="47" label="47"/><category term="WL" label="WL"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/47/86/</id><title>47 - 86 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:40:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:40:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/47/86/" title="47 - 86 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 오혁 따라 한다고 <br>머리 밀었을 때 <br>그때 너는 나를 좋아했지 <br>정말로 못 봐 주겠는 <br>그때 내 사진을 보니까는 <br>너는 나의 속을 좋아했지 <br>너와 내가 어떤 모습이든지 간에 <br>모두 손을 가져서 <br>어떻다 해도 손가락질을 하겠지 <br>그래도 너는 나를 좋아해 <br>나도 너를 좋아해 <br>어이 허이 넌 내 이기심을 솎아내 <br>너가 어디 출신이든지 간에 <br>하루를 끝내는 시간에 <br>너와 난 서로의 피날래 <br>아직은 그림 같애 <br>꿈 같애 그런 집 같애 <br>너 없는 어제 밤엔 <br>궁금했어 언제가 될 지 <br>갈증이 절제가 안돼 <br>나는 매일 변태 같애 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>내가 너의 세상에 없는 <br>물리적인 시간 동안 <br>무슨 생각을 하며 살았어 <br>나는 여기저기 <br>기댈 곳을 찾아 헤맸고 <br>그들에게 기대도 했어 <br>내 목마름을 채워달라고 <br>근데 안되더라고 <br>you know money come and go <br>bitches come and go <br>love come and go <br>여기는 소망이 없어 <br>붙들어줘 나의 손 <br>그리고 끄집어 댕겨줘 <br>너의 진리 속으로 <br>내가 이상한 소리 해도 <br>다 받아주세요 <br>뒤에서 젖은 머리 <br>다 말려줄게요 <br>싱글이든 슈퍼싱글이든 더블이든 <br>우리는 이미 하나가 됐을 거야 <br>벽을 터뜨리는 밤 <br>You’ll be my king <br>You’ll be my queen <br>물질들은 별로 중요하지 않아 <br>밤새 떠들었지 죽고 나서도 <br>나랑 살 거냐고 <br>같이 거닐기는 하자고 <br>어디에 가더라도 <br>oh Jesus <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>Want you to be 내가 <br>]]></content><category term="47" label="47"/><category term="86" label="86"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/47/Vanillatte/</id><title>47 - Vanillatte - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:40:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:40:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/47/Vanillatte/" title="47 - Vanillatte - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 얼마나 따스한 놈이냐면 <br>나는 따듯한 바닐라라떼를 마셔 <br>내가 얼마나 따스한 놈이냐면 <br>겨울에도 널 위해 <br>반팔이 될 수 있다고 <br>숫가락이나 젓가락을 <br>놓아주는 건 <br>내 꺼 물 따를 때 <br>너 꺼도 따라주는 건 <br>가끔 잊어먹더라도 나는 따스해 <br>내가 너의 옷이 되어줄게 <br>물줄기가 흐르는 듯한 <br>피아노 소리를 아니 <br>조명은 누리끼리하게 <br>되도록이면 빨리 <br>캐치해야지 정방형으로 <br>혹은 16 대 9로 너를 영화배우로 <br>맘을 먹으면 여기 홍대점에 <br>모든 메뉴를 다 뚜까팰 수 있어 <br>그럼에도 너에게 할당해주는 <br> 너의 분량에 <br>곱하기 47을 하면 <br>감히 가늠할 수 있는 나의 따스함 <br>언제부턴가 너가 나에게 와서 <br>나의 날개 돼서 나를 날게 해줘 <br>네 아래 달려 있을게 아이 <br>내 위에 달려 있을래 아이 <br>언제부턴가 너가 나에게 와서 <br>나의 날개 돼서 나를 날게 해줘 <br>네 아래 달려 있을게 아이 <br>내 위에 달려 있을래 아이 <br>계산을 너가 하면 <br>나는 돈을 안 벌어 <br>덜 민망해지는 법만 배울 걸 <br>어 어 어 어 어 <br>나에게 절실함을 심어줘 <br>먹여 살리는 그런 마인드로 <br>성공을 해볼게요 <br>왜요 <br>나는 솔직함이 무기야 <br>그래서 부담감을 <br>같이 짊어지게 한다고 <br>나는 못났다고 <br>너를 내 로봇으로 만들고 <br>싶지 않으니까 <br>내가 니 로봇이 돼야겠다고 <br>생각이 듭디다 <br>이상적으로 내가 네가 되어보고 <br>다시 내가 되어본 후 <br>깨달은 걸 내려놓고 <br>그러면 헤어짐이 <br>부끄러운 것 아닌가 <br>그러면 헤어짐이 <br>부끄러운 것 아닌가 <br>자아를 포기하고 의탁하는 <br>법을 배우는 중 넌 가끔 빛 같다는 <br>니 사랑의 너머엔 빛이 있는 듯해 <br>너에게 맡기면 난 빛에 있는 듯해 <br>둘 셋 <br>언제부턴가 너가 나에게 와서 <br>나의 날개 돼서 나를 날게 해줘 <br>네 아래 달려 있을게 아이 <br>내 위에 달려 있을래 아이 <br>언제부턴가 너가 나에게 와서 <br>나의 날개 돼서 나를 날게 해줘 <br>네 아래 달려 있을게 아이 <br>내 위에 달려 있을래 아이 <br>언제나 옆에 있을게 <br>언제나 옆에 있을게 <br>언제나 옆에 있을게 <br>언제나 옆에 있을게 <br>언제나 옆에 있을게 <br>언제나 옆에 있을게 <br>언제나 옆에 있을게 <br>언제나 옆에 있을게 <br>언제나 옆에 있을게 <br>언제나 옆에 있을게 <br>언제나 옆에 있을게 <br>언제나 옆에 있을게 <br>언제나 옆에 있을게 <br>언제나 옆에 있을게 <br>언제나 옆에 있을게 <br>언제나 기도해줄게 정말로 <br>]]></content><category term="47" label="47"/><category term="Vanillatte" label="Vanillatte"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/47/12_47/</id><title>47 - 12:47 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:40:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:40:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/47/12_47/" title="47 - 12:47 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What you gonna say <br>If I crush on you <br>오늘 밤 안에는 끝을 볼거야 <br>너의 토끼눈 올라간 발뒤꿈치 <br>우주비행을 하는 듯한 기분 <br>대답을 기다릴 땐 마치 pause <br>아직은 찍지 말아 마침표 <br>밤하늘에 달이 마침 떴어 <br>So what you gonna say <br>What you gonna say <br>내가 너를 볼 때 나는 무지 급해 <br>그 모습을 다 담아야 하니까 <br>나의 눈에 <br>너가 자꾸 그렇게 이쁘겠다면은 <br>내가 정말 참다가 <br>죽을 수도 있을건데 <br>계속 그런 식으로 나오시겠다면 <br>너가 항상 환장하는 달고 짠 먹을 <br>것으로 홀려서 낭낭한 밤까지 너를 <br>묶어두고선 selfie 잘 나오는 <br>가로수로 갈거야 <br>그리고 너의 두 눈을 쭉 쳐다 보곤 <br>천천히 그리고 정성스래 <br>한부분 한부분 <br>딱 붙는 치마만 뺀 <br>너를 칭찬을 해주곤 <br>아주 재미있는 시간을 <br>보내고야 말거야 <br>그리고 달이 아주 이쁠 때쯤 <br>산책을 하다가 너의 손과 내 손 <br>자꾸만 스치게 하다가 그거를 냉큼 <br>잡고선 제의할거야 <br>why don't u come to 내 품 <br>What you gonna say <br>If I crush on you <br>오늘 밤 안에는 끝을 볼거야 <br>너의 토끼눈 올라간 발뒤꿈치 <br>우주비행을 하는 듯한 기분 <br>대답을 기다릴 땐 마치 pause <br>아직은 찍지 말아 마침표 <br>밤하늘에 달이 마침 떴어 <br>So what you gonna say <br>What you gonna say <br>너도 바보는 아니니까는 그치 <br>알꺼야 내가 너를 이렇게 굳이 <br>늦은 시간까지 잡아두는 <br>이유가 뭔지 <br>대충 감을 잡고 있어줘 그래야 흥이 <br>깨지지 않으니까 그래야 너의 맘 <br>내 맘과 함께 리듬 <br>탈 수 있을 테니까 <br>생각해 보겠단 그런 쓸데 없는 말 <br>집어 치우고 걍 내가 너의 옆에서 <br>같이 걷는 걸 상상해봐 aint it cool <br>해지는 것부터 <br>달 질 때까지 함께 있는 <br>인스타 업데이트 사진을 함께 <br>이쁘게 보정하는 순간들을 말야 <br>aint it cool <br>결국에는 뭐가 됐건 너의 맘이지 <br>근데 너의 앞에 있는 건 <br>개멋진 나 이기도 하고 <br>잠깐 what time is it <br>열두시 사십칠분 <br>연애 시작하기엔 딱이지 <br>그냥 같이 있고 싶어서 그래 <br>너무 많은거는 나는 안바라 <br>넌 내 옆에서 뭘 해도 되니까 <br>그저 내 곁에서 있어주면 좋겠어 <br>u can go everywhere with me <br>with me <br>u can do everything with me <br>with me <br>u can meet every time with me <br>with me <br>u can love me u can love me <br>u can go everywhere with me <br>with me <br>u can do everything with me <br>with me <br>u can meet every time with me <br>with me <br>u can love me u can love me <br>u can go everywhere with me <br>with me <br>u can do everything with me <br>with me <br>u can meet every time with me <br>with me <br>u can love me u can love me <br>u can go everywhere with me <br>with me <br>]]></content><category term="47" label="47"/><category term="12:47" label="12:47"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/47/Costco/</id><title>47 - Costco - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:40:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:40:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/47/Costco/" title="47 - Costco - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s go Costco with you <br>부부가 된 듯이 아주 편한 기분 <br>구두는 잠깐 두고 와 rockin sneaker <br>이뻐 넌 그래도 아주 이뻐 <br>나는 개 멋지게 카트를 rollin <br>2종 보통인데도 화끈하게 turnin <br>그 위에 너를 태우고선 달릴꺼야 <br>지하로 가는 에스컬레이터로 <br>hurry up 왜냐면 time for sale <br>니가 저번에 <br>노래를 부르던 <br>아주 이쁜 분홍색 고기 <br>들이 줄을 서고 있으니까 <br>빨리 와 폐점까지 남은 시간 <br>이제 십분이야 <br>나는 아주 행복해 <br>내 옆엔 아주 예쁜 애 <br>가 나를 따라다니면서 <br>계속해서 까부네 <br>what u sayin what u sayin <br>keep talkin to me <br>저거는 내가 담을게 <br>shoppin shoppin <br>we tryna get somethin <br>이만한 데가 없을거야 <br>사랑을 나누 긴 <br>just two of us <br>just two of us <br>shoppin shoppin <br>we tryna get somethin <br>이만한 데가 없을거야 <br>사랑을 나누 긴 <br>just two of us <br>just two of us <br>Let’s go to the second floor <br>to get some mo <br>배가 고프니까 <br>bite some pizza n bacon <br>입에 가득 물고 있는 너도 개 이뻐 <br>몇개 포장해 이런 너를 또 볼래 <br>빨리 가야해 여긴 이제 곧 닫어 <br>못 산 것이 있다해도 괜찮어 <br>우리에겐 내일도 <br>내일 모래도 있으니까 <br>it ain’t proulem 코스코만 있다면 <br>낼은 주말이니까 너는 요리 하지마 <br>이렇게 바리바리 사가니까 우리같 <br>이 새우 까먹으면서 티비나 보자 <br>아무도 끼지 말고 단 우리 둘이만 <br>나는 아주 행복해 <br>내 옆엔 아주 예쁜 애 <br>가 나를 따라다니면서 <br>계속해서 까부네 <br>what u sayin what u sayin <br>keep talkin to me <br>저거는 내가 담을게 <br>shoppin shoppin <br>we tryna get somethin <br>이만한 데가 없을거야 <br>사랑을 나누 긴 <br>just two of us <br>just two of us <br>shoppin shoppin <br>we tryna get somethin <br>이만한 데가 없을거야 <br>사랑을 나누 긴 <br>just two of us <br>just two of us <br>]]></content><category term="47" label="47"/><category term="Costco" label="Costco"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/산체스_Sanchez/변한_게_없는데/</id><title>산체스 (Sanchez) - 변한 게 없는데 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:40:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:40:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%82%B0%EC%B2%B4%EC%8A%A4_Sanchez/%EB%B3%80%ED%95%9C_%EA%B2%8C_%EC%97%86%EB%8A%94%EB%8D%B0/" title="산체스 (Sanchez) - 변한 게 없는데 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tell me why you cannot <br>love me anymore <br>서로의 잘못된 오해들로 인해 <br>이렇게 마음의 상처는 커져만 가고 <br>다시는 볼 수 없단 생각에 불안해져 <br>자존심이 뭐길래 <br>내게 집중해줘 <br>It's what you said <br>Baby girl 미안해요 나 약속할게 <br>너만을 위한 사랑을 <br>I just want you to know <br>I love you <br>We cannot end this way <br>내 사랑 변한 게 없는데 <br>다투고 많이 싸워도 <br>그 또한 사랑인 거니까 <br>Baby 용서해줘 <br>넌 내가 말로만 사랑한다 했어 <br>넌 내게 마음이 아닌 <br>눈으로 하는 사랑은 싫다고 <br>매일 투정 부리고 <br>짜증 내는 널 무시했던 나 <br>몰래 눈물 훔치고 <br>아파하는 널 이해 못한 나 <br>용서해 자존심은 버릴게 <br>내가 노력할게 <br>너에게 진실된 모습으로 다가갈래 <br>너만을 위한 사랑을 <br>I just want you to know <br>I love you <br>We cannot end this way <br>내사랑 변한 게 없는데 <br>다투고 많이 싸워도 <br>그 또한 사랑인거니까 <br>Baby 용서해줘 <br>Ain't nobody ever <br>got me feeling like <br>Ain't nobody ever <br>healed my pain like <br>Ain't nobody ever <br>got me crazy like you like you <br>Ain't nobody ever <br>talked to me like <br>Ain't nobody ever <br>held me down like <br>Ain't nobody ever <br>got me sprung like you like you <br>We cannot end this way <br>내 사랑 변한 게 없는데 <br>다투고 많이 싸워도 <br>그 또한 사랑인 거니까 <br>Baby 용서해줘 <br>]]></content><category term="산체스 (Sanchez)" label="산체스 (Sanchez)"/><category term="변한 게 없는데" label="변한 게 없는데"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/산체스_Sanchez/5분만_더_Feat_빈지노/</id><title>산체스 (Sanchez) - 5분만 더 (Feat. 빈지노) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:40:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:40:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%82%B0%EC%B2%B4%EC%8A%A4_Sanchez/5%EB%B6%84%EB%A7%8C_%EB%8D%94_Feat_%EB%B9%88%EC%A7%80%EB%85%B8/" title="산체스 (Sanchez) - 5분만 더 (Feat. 빈지노) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 조금만 더 같이 있을래요 <br>헤어지긴 너무 싫어요 나 어떡하죠 <br>조금만 더 곁에 있어줘 <br>5분만 더 우리 단둘이 <br>조금만 더 내 품에 있어줘 <br>5분만 더 우리 단둘이 <br>Let's make love <br>함께 있으면 참 따뜻해요 <br>그대의 온기가 좋아 <br>침대 속 밖은 너무 추워요 <br>Just stay with me <br>우리 입술이 맞닿을 때 <br>나의 두 손이 니 허리를 감쌀 때 <br>양쪽 두 볼이 빨개졌을 때 <br>Ooh baby <br>We fallin' in love again <br>우리 조금만 더 같이 있을래요 <br>헤어지긴 너무 싫어요 나 어떡하죠 <br>조금만 더 곁에 있어줘 <br>5분만 더 우리 단둘이 <br>조금만 더 내 품에 있어줘 <br>5분만 더 우리 단둘이 <br>Let's make love <br>Just 5 more minutes <br>조금만 더 있길 <br>Couldn’t get enough with <br>아까 내 목에 남긴 이끼 <br>이게 뭔 말인지 모르면 <br>말해줄게 쉽게 <br>오빤 다 알잖아 날 물어봐 <br>I’m wikipedia <br>피리야 음악이 나올 느낌 <br>가사만 나오면 돼 talk dirty to me <br>내 파트가 들어갈 <br>타이밍만 잘 알려주길 <br>때가 되면 나를 봐줘 뚫어져 버리게 <br>Let’s go <br>여기까지가 내 속 마음 <br>이렇게는 난 못 말해 <br>그랬다간 도망가네 <br>착한 기믹의 한국 오빤 <br>너를 지키고파 <br>착한 발라드로 도발하려고 하네 <br>딴 거 안 바라 <br>난 그냥 좋은 음악과 함께 <br>너의 몸 아이쿠 <br>너의 손잡고 blah blah <br>근데 넌 maxwell 을 좋아한대 <br>그중에서 특히 <br>till the cops come knocking <br>헤어지기 싫잖아 <br>5분만 더 있어요 <br>헤어지기 싫잖아 <br>5분만 더 있어줘 <br>그대 조금만 더 가까이 와줄래요 <br>멀어지긴 너무 싫어요 꽉 안아줘요 <br>5 minutes ain't enough <br>5 minutes ain't enough <br>5 minutes ain't enough <br>No I just want you to stay <br>5 minutes ain't enough <br>5 minutes ain't enough <br>5 minutes ain't enough <br>No I just want you to stay <br>]]></content><category term="산체스 (Sanchez)" label="산체스 (Sanchez)"/><category term="5분만 더 (Feat. 빈지노)" label="5분만 더 (Feat. 빈지노)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김지유/안단테/</id><title>김지유 - 안단테 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:40:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:40:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%80%EC%9C%A0/%EC%95%88%EB%8B%A8%ED%85%8C/" title="김지유 - 안단테 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[파란 하늘 위로 <br>하얀 구름 속을 날아 <br>지난 아픔 벗어버리고 <br>작은 창틈 사이 <br>비친 푸른 달빛 속에 <br>바람처럼 스쳐 가는 너 <br>서투른 고백에 멀어진 그 사람 <br>지나간 꿈처럼 한 걸음 뒤에서 <br>따라가도 이젠 괜찮아 <br>자꾸 보고 싶어져 오늘 같은 밤 <br>버려도 커져가는 그댈 향한 <br>나의 마음 <br>자꾸 보고 싶어져 찬비 내리면 <br>스치듯 바람처럼 몰래 지나쳐간 <br>내 사람 <br>서투른 고백에 멀어진 그 사람 <br>지나간 꿈처럼 한 걸음 뒤에서 <br>따라가도 이젠 괜찮아 <br>자꾸 보고 싶어져 오늘 같은 밤 <br>버려도 커져가는 그댈 향한 <br>나의 마음 <br>자꾸 보고 싶어져 찬비 내리면 <br>스치듯 바람처럼 몰래 지나쳐간 <br>내 사람 <br>]]></content><category term="김지유" label="김지유"/><category term="안단테" label="안단테"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Sound_For_Language_Demo/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Sound For Language (Demo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Sound_For_Language_Demo/" title="Hot Water Music - Sound For Language (Demo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All around my home there is living sound <br>In my head It's in my head, I know and I hear it It's in me <br>Rhythm in the air, in my home you can breathe in the air <br>In my head And live from it <br><br>You watch it, close your eyes and listen <br>Listen <br><br>Close your eyes, you can see around the world <br>See around the world <br>Close your eyes, you can see around the world <br>See around the world <br><br>All around my home there½s potential sound <br>In my head Got to let it happen It's in me <br>Take it all, in my home it will never end <br>In my head If we let it live It's in me <br><br>See around the world]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Sound For Language (Demo)" label="Sound For Language (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Loft_Demo/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Loft (Demo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Loft_Demo/" title="Hot Water Music - Loft (Demo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And the beauty wreaks my soul <br>and i'll see the light all night <br>and the power kills my will <br>and this feeling leaves me cold <br>and this power kills my will where could <br>we run why could we try and the structure wrecks <br>my soul and the power kills my will <br>and this meaning leaves me cold <br>and this power kills my will what would it <br>take to find a place without a name <br>i won't lie down my hands for this <br>it wrecks my it shows me it sees me where i need]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Loft (Demo)" label="Loft (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Us__Chuck_Demo/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Us &amp; Chuck (Demo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Us__Chuck_Demo/" title="Hot Water Music - Us &amp; Chuck (Demo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I should've walked <br>I should've turned my head around <br>What is real and what is plastic <br>Are not meant to be <br><br>I would talk unended <br>I would speak my mind <br>I would walk on endless <br>'till I find my way home <br><br>When I'm backed against the wall <br>I won't stop until I fall When I fall, if I fall <br>True to, want to kind of feeling <br>In the moment I'll be gone before my time <br><br>I won't lecture if you won't pretend <br>If you'll be the paper then I'll be the pen <br>Show me all your insides if you're ready to begin <br>'Cause this is why we're called out]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Us &amp; Chuck (Demo)" label="Us &amp; Chuck (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Powder_Demo/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Powder (Demo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Powder_Demo/" title="Hot Water Music - Powder (Demo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I never thought I'd know, I know what's in me and what grows <br>What's willing and obscene, what grows inside of <br>I never realized the glow, the glow that we all know <br>The glow inside of me <br><br>I know what's on my mind <br>Breath, see, feel what we find and it's all good <br><br>Take me now in vein 'cause I'm not the same <br>I'm not half as bad as everyone might say <br>Treat me all the same as you did yesterday <br>I'm not half as scared, I'm on my last leg <br><br>I'm true I am true]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Powder (Demo)" label="Powder (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/The_Passing_Demo/</id><title>Hot Water Music - The Passing (Demo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/The_Passing_Demo/" title="Hot Water Music - The Passing (Demo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It was a day of passing <br>Someone thought something was in the way <br>No one caught what I caught but I caught it full on <br>I didn't want to mixed up that way <br>Die Not today <br>Cause I know one thing, stuck in my head <br>Should I let it work, cause I'll see it once again <br>I laid down my hands for this <br>it might be the last time <br>And when I find the passing <br>I find myself caught in the exchange <br>If i could stop hurting, if I could get away <br>I'd like to look and find my place <br>You were right behind me]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="The Passing (Demo)" label="The Passing (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Bleeder/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Bleeder - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Bleeder/" title="Hot Water Music - Bleeder - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You came to me like a dream <br>The kind that always leaves <br>Just when the best part starts <br>It ends so abruptly <br>To leave you stunned and naked <br>In the bedroom all alone <br>It's kinda funny how something so soothing <br>Gets interrupted by the ring of a telephone <br><br>And you broke me like the cigarette <br>That i busted on the day i quit <br>But now that i've been drinking <br>I'm outta smokes <br>And i wish that i had it <br>Woke up to my daily headache <br>And the realization that you were gone <br>Oh my sweet darling happiness <br>You've been away from me all along <br><br>It's one thing that i've never said <br>I'm truly happy <br>In my heart and in my head <br>A lonely liver suspended in liquid <br><br>You came to me like a dream <br>The kind that always leaves <br>Just when the best part starts <br>It ends so abruptly <br>To leave you stunned and naked <br>In the bedroom all alone <br>It's kinda funny how something so soothing <br>Gets interrupted by the ring of a telephone <br><br>It's one thing i've never said <br>I'm truly happy in my heart and in my head <br>A lonely liver suspended in liquid <br>It's one thing i never did <br>Was smile <br>Missing a case <br>Lacking a lid <br>My heart bleeds for what you never did until now <br><br>Verdict <br><br>Oh did i just fuck up by talking right there oh]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Bleeder" label="Bleeder"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Radio/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Radio - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Radio/" title="Hot Water Music - Radio - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Shaking like a dog shittin' razorblades <br>Waking up next to nothing after dreaming of you and me <br>I'm waking up all alone, waking up so relieved <br>While you're taking your time with apologies <br><br>I'm making my plans for revenge <br>Red eyes on orange horizons <br>If Columbus was wrong, I'd drive straight off the edge <br>I'd drive straight off the edge <br><br>Taking your own life with boredom <br>I'm taking my own life with wine <br>It helps you to rule out the sorrow <br>It helps me to empty my mind <br><br>Making the most of a bad time <br>I'm smoking the brains from my head <br>Leaving the coal calling the kettle black and orange and red <br>This kettle is seeing red <br><br>I've got a big fat fuckin' bone to pick with you my darling <br>In case you haven't heard I'm sick and tired of trying <br>I wish you would take my radio to bathe with you <br>Plugged in and ready to fall <br><br>Shaking like a dog shittin' razorblades <br>Waking up next to nothing after dreaming of you and me <br>Waking up all alone, waking up so relieved <br>While you're taking your time with apologies <br><br>I'm planning out my revenge <br>Red eyes on orange horizons <br>If Columbus was wrong I'd drive straight off the edge <br>I'm seeing red <br><br>I've got a big fat fuckin' bone to pick with you my darling <br>In case you haven't heard, I'm sick and tired of trying <br>I wish you would take my radio to bathe with you <br>Plugged in and ready to fall <br><br>Plugged in and ready to fall <br>Plugged in and ready to fall <br>Plugged in and ready to fall]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Radio" label="Radio"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Springtime/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Springtime - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Springtime/" title="Hot Water Music - Springtime - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a little bit of springtime in the back of my mind <br>That remembers when there was a time <br>When we danced and laughed an spent some time drinking wine <br>And somewhere in there <br>There's a little child without a thought <br>Without a doubt that every cloud is silver lined <br>He is warm and everything is new <br>And everything is clean and everything is free <br>And there were still so many things to see <br>So many things still left to be <br>You're a very small drop in the middle of a big sea <br>Of high and mighty things <br>Your fascination for larger than life <br>Your brand new appetite, as though we'd invented it <br>We danced <br>There's a little bit of springtime in the back of my mind <br>That remembers things, perhaps as they should've been <br>Rather than lies, rather than the cruelty <br>That sometimes we were guilty of and as everyone knows <br>We were only young and really couldn't have known <br>We were very young and it's nice to know there's a place to go <br>And still so many things left to see <br>You're a drop in the middle of a big sea of high and mighty things <br>Your fascination for larger than life <br>Your brand new appetite <br>As though we'd invented it <br>We danced <br>It could be the longest time and I'll remember it <br>You don't know what's in store, when we laugh]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Springtime" label="Springtime"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/No_Surrender/</id><title>Hot Water Music - No Surrender - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/No_Surrender/" title="Hot Water Music - No Surrender - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, we bursted out of class <br>Had to get away from those fools <br>We learned more from a three minute record, baby <br>Than we ever learned in school <br>Tonight I hear the neighborhood drummer sound <br>I can feel my heart begin to pound <br>You say you're tired and you just want to close your eyes <br>And follow your dreams down <br><br>Well, we made a promise we swore we'd always remember <br>No retreat, baby, no surrender <br>Like soldiers in the winter's night <br>With a vow to defend <br>No retreat, baby, no surrender <br><br>Well, now young faces grow sad and old <br>And hearts of fire grow cold <br>We swore blood brothers against the wind <br>Now I'm ready to grow young again <br>And hear your sister's voice calling us home <br>Across the open yards <br>Well maybe we'll cut someplace of own <br>With these drums and these guitars <br><br>Because we made a promise we swore we'd always remember <br>No retreat, baby, no surrender <br>Blood brothers in the stormy night <br>With a vow to defend <br>No retreat, baby, no surrender <br><br>Now on the street tonight the lights grow dim <br>The walls of my room are closing in <br>There's a war outside still raging <br>You say it ain't ours anymore to win <br>I want to sleep beneath <br>Peaceful skies in my lover's bed <br>With a wide open country in my eyes <br>And these romantic dreams in my head <br><br>Once we made a promise we swore we'd always remember <br>No retreat, baby, no surrender <br>Blood brothers in a stormy night <br>With a vow to defend <br>No retreat, baby, no surrender <br><br>Oh, oh, oh <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>Oh, oh, oh]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="No Surrender" label="No Surrender"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/The_Clampdown/</id><title>Hot Water Music - The Clampdown - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/The_Clampdown/" title="Hot Water Music - The Clampdown - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One, two, three, four <br>What are we gonna do now <br><br>Taking off his turban, he said, Is this man a Jew <br>Working for the clampdown <br>They put up a poster saying we earn more than you <br>Working for the clampdown <br><br>We will teach our twisted speech <br>To the young believers <br>We will train our blue eyed men <br>To be young believers <br><br>The judge said five to ten, I say double that again <br>Working for the clampdown <br>No man born with a living soul and fate <br>Working for the clampdown <br><br>Kick over the wall 'cause government's to fall <br>How can you refuse it <br>Let fury have the hour, anger can be power <br>Did you know that you can use it <br><br>Voices in your head are calling <br>Stop wasting time, there's nothing coming <br>Only a fool would think someone could save you <br><br>The men at the factory are old and cunning <br>You don't owe nothing, so boy, get running <br>It's the best years of your life they want to steal <br><br>But you grow up and you calm down <br>Working for the clampdown <br>You start wearing blue and brown <br>Working for the clampdown <br><br>So you got someone to boss around <br>It makes you feel big now <br>You drift until you brutalize <br>You made your first kill now <br><br>In these days of evil presidents <br>Working for the clampdown <br>Lately one or two has fully paid their due <br>Working for the clampdown <br><br>Working for the clampdown <br>Working for the clampdown <br>Work, work, work]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="The Clampdown" label="The Clampdown"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Wild_In_The_Streets/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Wild In The Streets - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Wild_In_The_Streets/" title="Hot Water Music - Wild In The Streets - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wild, wild, wild, wild <br>Wild in the streets <br>Wild in the streets <br>Wild in the streets <br>Wild in the streets <br><br>In the heat of the summer <br>Better call out a plumber <br>Turn on the steam pipe <br>Cool me off <br>With your big crime fighters <br>And your newspaper writers <br>Still need a drugstore <br>To cure my buzz <br><br>Wild in the streets, running, running <br>Wild in the streets, running, running <br>Wild in the streets, running, running <br>Wild in the streets <br><br>'64 Valiant, hand full of Valiums <br>Couple of beers really do me right <br>You better believe us, better trust us <br>Teenage jive, walking wreck <br><br>Wild, wild, wild, running wild <br>Wild in the streets, running, running <br>Wild in the streets, running, running <br>Wild in the streets, running, running <br>Wild in the streets <br><br>Got a gang called the wolves <br>You have to choose <br>Play with the boys <br>You're bound to lose <br>A bottle in one hand <br>A can in the other <br>Don't fool around because they're real <br>Mean mothers <br><br>Wild, wild, wild, wild <br>Wild running, running <br>Wild <br>Mrs America, how's your favorite son <br>Do you care just what he's done No <br>Wild in the streets, running, running <br>Wild in the streets, running, running <br>Wild in the streets, running, running <br>Wild in the streets, running, running <br><br>Wild in the streets, we're running, running <br>Wild in the streets, we're running, running <br>Wild in the streets, we're running, running <br>Wild in the streets]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Wild In The Streets" label="Wild In The Streets"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Prince_Of_The_Rodeo/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Prince Of The Rodeo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Prince_Of_The_Rodeo/" title="Hot Water Music - Prince Of The Rodeo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br><br>Hi ridin' daddy o <br>Prince of the rodeo <br>Spur hump hey ho let's go <br>Prince of the rodeo <br>Fornicator of the lasso <br>Prince of the rodeo <br>Sperminator of the asshole <br>Prince of the rodeo <br><br>Shoot the chute <br>Pull the flute <br>I'm back in the saddle <br>The world's most promising cowboy <br><br>Lo ridin' daddy o <br>Prince of the rodeo <br>Sexy denim romeo <br>Prince of the rodeo <br>Rhinestone homo rock n roll <br>Prince of the rodeo <br>Buns of steel Geronimo <br>Prince of the rodeo <br><br>Jerk that calf <br>Half n half <br>I'm back in the saddle <br>The world's most progressive cowboy <br><br>And don't forget the clown <br><br>I'm ridin' high, I'm ridin' low <br>Prince of the rodeo]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Prince Of The Rodeo" label="Prince Of The Rodeo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Dreamworld/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Dreamworld - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Dreamworld/" title="Hot Water Music - Dreamworld - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The Breakfast Creek Hotel is up for sale <br>The last square mile of terra firma gaveled in a mail <br>So farewell to those Norfolk Island pines <br>No amount of make believe can help this heart of mine <br><br>End, your dreamworld is just about to end <br>Fall, your dreamworld is just about to fall <br>Your dreamworld will fall <br><br>Shut that buckle and turn that key again <br>Take me to a place they say the dreaming never ends <br>Open wide, drive that mystery road <br>Walk through Eden's garden and then wonder as you go <br><br>End, your dreamworld is just about to end <br>Fall, your dreamworld is just about to fall <br>Your dreamworld is just about to fall <br><br>Sign says 'Honeymoon For Rent' <br>Cloud land in dreamland turns <br>Sun comes up and we all learn <br>Those wheels must turn <br><br>End, your dreamworld is just about to end <br>Fall, your dreamworld is just about to fall <br><br>End, your dreamworld is just about to end <br>Fall, fall, fall, fall, fall, your dreamworld is just about to fall]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Dreamworld" label="Dreamworld"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Jaded_Eyes/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Jaded Eyes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Jaded_Eyes/" title="Hot Water Music - Jaded Eyes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've judged you wrong I thought <br>In your head, have no plot <br><br>Got the jaded eyes, so naive <br><br>Talk flies, hours roll <br>Some folks have no lip control <br><br>Got the jaded eyes, so naive <br><br>Another bottle touches lips <br>Ankh tattoo, on her hip <br><br>Got the jaded eyes, so naive]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Jaded Eyes" label="Jaded Eyes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Sound_For_Language/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Sound For Language - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Sound_For_Language/" title="Hot Water Music - Sound For Language - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All around my home there is living sound <br>In my head It's in my head, I know and I hear it It's in me <br>Rhythm in the air, in my home you can breathe in the air <br>In my head And live from it <br><br>You watch it, close your eyes and listen <br>Listen <br><br>Close your eyes, you can see around the world <br>See around the world <br>Close your eyes, you can see around the world <br>See around the world <br><br>All around my home there½s potential sound <br>In my head Got to let it happen It's in me <br>Take it all, in my home it will never end <br>In my head If we let it live It's in me <br><br>See around the world]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Sound For Language" label="Sound For Language"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Loft/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Loft - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Loft/" title="Hot Water Music - Loft - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And the beauty wreaks my soul <br>and i'll see the light all night <br>and the power kills my will <br>and this feeling leaves me cold <br>and this power kills my will where could <br>we run why could we try and the structure wrecks <br>my soul and the power kills my will <br>and this meaning leaves me cold <br>and this power kills my will what would it <br>take to find a place without a name <br>i won't lie down my hands for this <br>it wrecks my it shows me it sees me where i need]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Loft" label="Loft"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Us__Chuck/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Us &amp; Chuck - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Us__Chuck/" title="Hot Water Music - Us &amp; Chuck - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I should've walked <br>I should've turned my head around <br>What is real and what is plastic <br>Are not meant to be <br><br>I would talk unended <br>I would speak my mind <br>I would walk on endless <br>'till I find my way home <br><br>When I'm backed against the wall <br>I won't stop until I fall When I fall, if I fall <br>True to, want to kind of feeling <br>In the moment I'll be gone before my time <br><br>I won't lecture if you won't pretend <br>If you'll be the paper then I'll be the pen <br>Show me all your insides if you're ready to begin <br>'Cause this is why we're called out]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Us &amp; Chuck" label="Us &amp; Chuck"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Powder/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Powder - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Powder/" title="Hot Water Music - Powder - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[i never thought i'd know what's in me <br>and what grows what's willing <br>and obscene what grows inside of <br>i never realized the glow the glow that <br>we all know the glow inside of me <br>i know what's on my mind breath see feel <br>what we find and it's all good take me now in vein <br>cause i'm not the same <br>i'm on my last leg i'm true]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Powder" label="Powder"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Russian_Roulette/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Russian Roulette - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Russian_Roulette/" title="Hot Water Music - Russian Roulette - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She lives like russian roulette Barrel up to the head <br>Where every sweet young move is belonging to a sickness <br>Now enter special things to detour all the pain <br>like a brand new, solid mess <br>But nothing seems to last <br>It strikes when you've thought you won <br>It's self destruction <br>It strikes when you've thought you won <br>And the delicate balance won't survive the turbulence <br>Now, enter the escape from everything you've made <br>Cause something wrong inside won't let you live your life <br>It strikes when you've thought you won <br>It's self destruction <br>It strikes when you've thought you won <br>And down you will go <br>with a tail of flames stretched out behind you <br>The cold wind will blind you <br>And in all that you can't see <br>The simplicity is beautiful]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Russian Roulette" label="Russian Roulette"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/God_Deciding/</id><title>Hot Water Music - God Deciding - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/God_Deciding/" title="Hot Water Music - God Deciding - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Transgressions are made <br>While cowards convey <br>With a demon's ear, fixed and set to slay <br><br>While the statue awaits <br>To be whittled away <br>With a mock of a slogan hiding filth with fear <br><br>Never to learn <br>Only to burn and be burned <br>Branded straight through slate <br>Clear as common day <br><br>Go slowly cause at the moment <br>Things you'd never think you'd ever see <br>Are happening and you can't believe the hatred <br><br>What shall be the mark to be made <br>When we crush it all to burn it down <br>Without sight, without sound <br>Not anything but a casualty forgotten in the ground <br>A simple shell, that's solemn still without sight, without sound <br><br>Make a martyr <br>A pedestal with ribbons of slaughter <br>Feed the altar <br>Stoke the fire it will take over <br><br>Ignore the cut the skin with callus as well as interest <br>If all are reckless none is to profit <br>None is to win it <br><br>Go slowly cause at the moment <br>Things you'd never think you'd ever see <br>Are happening and you can't believe the hatred 2x <br><br>So who will pay for all the tears <br>All the lives, from either side <br>All the years, all the time of living blind <br>Playing God Deciding <br>And who will die next in line for the lie <br>Justified for the rise of sitting high playing God Deciding <br>And who will walk away <br>From the rage and revenge <br>Inhumane consequence comes in time <br>Playing God Deciding <br>And who will fall in line to arrive <br>Out of sight and out of mind <br>Out of mind <br>Out of mind <br>Out of]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="God Deciding" label="God Deciding"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/So_Many_Days/</id><title>Hot Water Music - So Many Days - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:41:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:41:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/So_Many_Days/" title="Hot Water Music - So Many Days - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Is there something wrong <br>Do ya hate this song <br>Cuz I'm singin about it again <br>Did ya know the words <br>Before you read them <br>Did ya notice <br>She had it and she wants it again <br>He had it and he lost it again <br>In the fallout or the aftermath of <br>So many days so many days I guess it's all been done <br>Maybe it's all been sung <br>Before By wiser people but its not stopping anyone <br>Falling apart from heartache <br>She had it and she wants it again <br>He had it and he lost it again In the fallout or the aftermath of <br>So many days so many days <br>Another second is another made <br>So many days]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="So Many Days" label="So Many Days"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Home/</id><title>Hot Water Music - Home - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T08:42:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T08:42:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Water_Music/Home/" title="Hot Water Music - Home - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can close my eyes and see your lips move close to mine <br>Hear your words so crystal clear with your breath in my ear <br><br>Still So far away from you, it cuts so quick and clean <br>Still so far away from you but I still want more <br><br>I can close my lips before I taste ours soaked in wine <br>Lay my head upon your breast and count your beats and smiles <br><br>This is where the time stops and this is where it starts <br>This is where we mend our broken hearts <br>I'm on my way, can't stay away <br>Since this love stings like it does over and again <br>Again <br><br>I'm on my way, I can't stay away <br>Since this love stings like it does over and again <br>I'm on my way, homeward bound <br>Since this love stings like it does over and again and again <br>I'm on my way, can't stay away <br>Since this love stings like it does over and again and again]]></content><category term="Hot Water Music" label="Hot Water Music"/><category term="Home" label="Home"/></entry></feed>