<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:25:57+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NOW__THEN_나우앤덴/위로/</id><title>NOW__THEN_나우앤덴 - 위로 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:53:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:53:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NOW__THEN_%EB%82%98%EC%9A%B0%EC%95%A4%EB%8D%B4/%EC%9C%84%EB%A1%9C/" title="NOW__THEN_나우앤덴 - 위로 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쓸모 없는 사람이 <br>어딨겠어요 <br>다들 필요에 의해 <br>필요에 의해 <br>괴롭지 않은 사람이 <br>어딨겠어요 <br>다들 티나지 않게 <br>그렇게 사는 것뿐 <br>시간은 무서워요 나를 <br>기다려주지 않으니까요 <br>왜냐고 묻지 마요 제발 <br>정답이란건 없는 세상에서 <br>쓸모 없는 사람이 <br>어딨겠어요 <br>다들 필요에 의해 <br>필요에 의해 <br>괴롭지않은 사람이 <br>어딨겠어요 <br>다들 티나지 않게 <br>그렇게 사는 것뿐 <br>내가 없이도 <br>시간은 구름처럼 <br>사라져가 <br>오늘이 지나면 <br>잊혀질 꿈이라 <br>생각해 난 <br>]]></content><category term="NOW &amp; THEN (나우앤덴)" label="NOW &amp; THEN (나우앤덴)"/><category term="위로" label="위로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Midland/Drinkin_Problem/</id><title>Midland - Drinkin` Problem - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:53:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:53:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Midland/Drinkin_Problem/" title="Midland - Drinkin` Problem - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One more night, one more down <br>One more, one more round <br>First one in, last one out <br>Giving this town lots to talk about <br>They don't know what they don't know <br><br>People say I got a drinkin' problem <br>That ain't no reason to stop <br>People saying that I've hit rock bottom <br>Just cause I'm living on the rocks <br>It's a broken hearted thinkin' problem <br>So pull another bottle off the wall <br>People say I got a drinkin' problem <br>But I got no problem drinkin' at all <br><br>They keep on talking <br>Drawing conclusions <br>They call it a problem, I call it a solution <br><br>Last call gets later and later <br>I come in here so I don't have to hate her <br>Same old folks, same old songs <br>The same old same old blue neon <br>The same old buzz, just because <br><br>People say I've got a drinkin' problem <br>That ain't no reason to stop <br>People saying that I've hit rock bottom <br>Just cause I'm living on the rocks <br>It's a broken hearted thinkin' problem <br>So pull another bottle off the wall <br>People say I got a drinkin' problem <br>But I got no problem drinkin' at all <br><br>They keep on talking <br>Drawing conclusions <br>They call it a problem, I call it a solution <br>Just sitting here in all my grand illusions <br>They call it a problem, I call it a solution <br><br>Just a solution <br><br>It's a broken hearted thinkin' problem <br>So pull another bottle off the wall <br>People say I got a drinkin' problem <br>But I got no problem drinkin' at all <br><br>They keep on talking <br>Drawing conclusions <br>They call it a problem, I call it a solution <br>Sitting here in all my grand illusions <br>They call it a problem, I call it a solution]]></content><category term="Midland" label="Midland"/><category term="Drinkin` Problem" label="Drinkin` Problem"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스윙바나나_Swingbanana/모두_떠난뒤/</id><title>스윙바나나_Swingbanana - 모두 떠난뒤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:54:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:54:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%EC%9C%99%EB%B0%94%EB%82%98%EB%82%98_Swingbanana/%EB%AA%A8%EB%91%90_%EB%96%A0%EB%82%9C%EB%92%A4/" title="스윙바나나_Swingbanana - 모두 떠난뒤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[집에 도착할 때 문 앞은 <br>하얀빛 다시 이문을 나올 때면 <br>조금은 어두워져 <br>거꾸로 사는 건 조금은 아쉽지만 <br>기다리면 올 나의 불빛 <br>조금만 기다려 <br>허무한 그렇다고도 놓지 못할 <br>익숙한 나는 하루를 또 시작해 <br>모두 끝난 뒤 텅 빈자리 <br>아침 해가 뜰 때까지 <br>귓가에 맴돌길 <br>기억해줘 나나나나 <br>흘러가는 멜로디 모두 떠난 뒤 <br>신나게 뛰놀았던 <br>조용히 듣고 있던 사람들까지도 <br>기억해줘 나나나나 <br>흘러가는 멜로디 모두 떠난 뒤 <br>벌써 잊어버린 지난밤 <br>하나둘 다시 기억에 남을 때면 <br>조금은 아쉬워져 <br>언젠가 한번쯤 그날을 떠올리며 <br>기다리면 올 나의 불빛 <br>조금만 기다려 <br>허무한 그렇다고도 놓지 못할 <br>익숙한 나는 하루를 또 시작해 <br>모두 끝난 뒤 텅 빈자리 <br>아침 해가 뜰 때까지 <br>귓가에 맴돌길 <br>기억해줘 나나나나 <br>흘러가는 멜로디 모두 떠난 뒤 <br>신나게 뛰놀았던 <br>조용히 듣고 있던 사람들까지도 <br>기억해줘 나나나나 <br>흘러가는 멜로디 모두 떠난 뒤 <br>]]></content><category term="스윙바나나 (Swingbanana)" label="스윙바나나 (Swingbanana)"/><category term="모두 떠난뒤" label="모두 떠난뒤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/거짓말쟁이_조조/말없이/</id><title>거짓말쟁이_조조 - 말없이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:54:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:54:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B1%B0%EC%A7%93%EB%A7%90%EC%9F%81%EC%9D%B4_%EC%A1%B0%EC%A1%B0/%EB%A7%90%EC%97%86%EC%9D%B4/" title="거짓말쟁이_조조 - 말없이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너는 살며시 고개를 숙인 채 <br>아무 말 없이 미소를 짓지 <br>나는 그 한참을 두근거렸어 <br>스웨이드 샌들에 발목이 보이던 <br>네 짙은 청바지 예쁘다 <br>나 혼자서 널 바라보는 건 쓸쓸해 <br>오 오랫동안 말없이 말없이 <br>오 오늘은 꼭 <br>하고 싶던 네게 전하고 싶던 <br>말이 너무 많잖아 그건 너무 지쳐 <br>난 네 손을 잡고 가만히 <br>이 표정으로는 <br>이 표정으로는 넌 모를까 <br>오 오랫동안 말없이 말없이 <br>오 오늘은 꼭 <br>하고 싶던 네게 전하고 싶던 <br>오 오랫동안 말없이 말없이 <br>오 오늘은 꼭 <br>하고 싶던 네게 전하고 싶던 <br>오 오랫동안 말없이 말없이 <br>오 오늘은 꼭 <br>하고 싶던 네게 전하고 싶던 <br>]]></content><category term="거짓말쟁이 조조" label="거짓말쟁이 조조"/><category term="말없이" label="말없이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서바울/Saturday_Radio_Edit_Feat_Dynamite_제이디/</id><title>서바울 - Saturday (Radio Edit) (Feat. Dynamite, 제이디) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:55:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:55:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EB%B0%94%EC%9A%B8/Saturday_Radio_Edit_Feat_Dynamite_%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%EB%94%94/" title="서바울 - Saturday (Radio Edit) (Feat. Dynamite, 제이디) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 딱온 느낌 <br>논현보단 이태원 <br>간만에 멤버들 불러서 <br>불토를 태워 <br>댄디부터 힙합 <br>다갖춘 Style <br>먼저 고르는게 <br>임자 따로없어 Avengers <br>가볍게 적시자 <br>우주포차가서 <br>소주보단 소맥 <br>이건 에피타이져 <br>학돌아 넌 벌써 <br>빨가니까 물로 조절 <br>오늘은 절대로 <br>용서못해 이른 방전 <br>뒷골목은 <br>어김없이 바글 <br>내숭떼고 다들 노려 <br>오늘밤 대박을 <br>나는 예외라 하는 <br>순간 빠져버린걸 <br>헤어 나오지못해 <br>갈색 긴머리에 굵은컬 <br>진한눈썹에 피부는 <br>애도 울고가 <br>너의 몸몸몸매 <br>터질듯한 볼륨감 <br>핸드폰 뒷로고 같이 <br>깨물뻔한 애플힙 <br>고민은 여기까지 <br>Let me hollla <br>어디든 완벽한 날이야 <br>술이 날 적시는 밤이야 <br>오늘밤은 이대로는 <br>너무 아쉬워 <br>저기 저 완벽한 라인 <br>잠깐만 서두르지마 <br>오늘밤은 이대로는 <br>너무 아쉬워 <br>D’squad baby ya <br>평소엔 얌전해도 <br>놀땐 노는 남자 <br>Saturday Night <br>불을 지펴라 <br>홍대 신사 어디라도 <br>곧 갈 테니까 <br>쉴 새 없이 <br>달리자 아우토반 <br>놀 줄 아는 이 하나 둘 <br>다 불러 모아 <br>간만에 뭉친 드림팀 <br>달아오른 분위기 <br>참아왔던 본능이 <br>한순간에 눈을떠 <br>많이 피곤하면 <br>잠깐 기대도 되 <br>오늘 난 네것이야 baby <br>모른척 살며시 <br>손을 줘 그리고 <br>속삭여 단 둘이 <br>나가자 어디든 <br>어디든 레드카펫 <br>주인공이 된듯한 <br>기분 너무 핫해 <br>Saturday night light live <br>Saturday night light live <br>어디든 완벽한 날이야 <br>술이 날 적시는 밤이야 <br>오늘밤은 이대로는 <br>너무 아쉬워 <br>저기 저 완벽한 라인 <br>잠깐만 서두르지마 <br>오늘밤은 이대로는 <br>너무 아쉬워 <br>널 안고 싶어 나 조금만 더 <br>궁금해 또 다른 네 모습도 <br>짧게 느껴져 Saturday night <br>이대로 즐기는건 어때 <br>I wanna be with you <br>Be with you tonight <br>어디든 완벽한 날이야 <br>술이 날 적시는 밤이야 <br>오늘밤은 이대로는 <br>너무 아쉬워 <br>저기 저 완벽한 라인 <br>잠깐만 서두르지마 <br>오늘밤은 이대로는 <br>너무 아쉬워 <br>]]></content><category term="서바울" label="서바울"/><category term="Saturday (Radio Edit) (Feat. Dynamite, 제이디)" label="Saturday (Radio Edit) (Feat. Dynamite, 제이디)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서바울/555_Dear엄마_Feat_BOK/</id><title>서바울 - 555 (Dear.엄마) (Feat. B.O.K) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:55:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:55:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EB%B0%94%EC%9A%B8/555_Dear%EC%97%84%EB%A7%88_Feat_BOK/" title="서바울 - 555 (Dear.엄마) (Feat. B.O.K) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[시간지나며 얻은 <br>어른이란 title <br>내 모든것에 책임이란게 <br>붙을 때쯤 <br>가버렸어 저 멀리 <br>와닿지 않는 거리 <br>있을땐 몰랐을까 <br>잘하지 못하고 대충 <br>하던 대답들만 <br>가슴에 남아서 <br>지워지지 않는 멍 <br>받지도못해 처방전 <br>필요했어 타임슬립 <br>누구보다 더 간절히 <br>원해 부끄럽기만 했던 <br>내 자기 소개서 <br>딱히 없었던 <br>사춘기 시절의 아집 <br>학교 때려치고 음악을 <br>다 커서 선택 클릭 <br>장마같이 쏟아진 <br>비난의 손가락질 <br>유일하게 우산이 <br>되줬어 그날 끝까지 <br>하나뿐인 내가 자꾸밟혀 <br>쉽게 눈을 감지못한 <br>그 모습이 맘에 박혀 <br>보낼수없었어 엄마 <br>Nobody but you <br>오전 그대로 멈춘 <br>다섯시 오십오분 <br>엄마 그댄 어디있나요 <br>엄마 나를 떠나 가진 말아요 <br>엄마 시간을 <br>되돌릴 순 없나요 <br>엄마 그대의 품에 있던 <br>다시 그때로 <br>내 맘대로 떠벌려논 말들 <br>모여서 만든 <br>약속만 한가득 <br>지키지 못하게 <br>된 거짓말이되서 <br>못난 아들로 남아 <br>버리는게 되는걸까 나는 <br>8살 뻥치고 첨가본 오락실 <br>걸려 내쫓겼어 같이 <br>태권도복과 책가방 <br>그땐 알지 못했던 <br>중요한 사실 <br>유독 내게 엄격했던건 <br>딴것 아닌 거짓말 <br>아무도 내 힘든것 <br>다 몰라 줄때 <br>언제나 전화와 내가 <br>꿈속에서 울고 있데 <br>그 목소리가 그리운 <br>요즘에 나 기대 <br>하고 전활 걸지만 <br>자동응답이 대답해 <br>제대로 된것 하나 <br>보여주지 못하고 <br>무조건 적인 사랑 <br>받기만한 못난놈 <br>난 보낼수 없었어 엄마 <br>Nobody but you <br>새벽 그대로 멈춘 <br>다섯시 오십 오분 <br>엄마 그댄 어디있나요 <br>엄마 나를 떠나 가진 말아요 <br>엄마 시간을 되돌릴 순 없나요 <br>엄마 그대의 품에 있던 <br>다시 그때로 <br>엄마 그댄 어디있나요 <br>엄마 나를 떠나 가진 말아요 <br>엄마 시간을 되돌릴 순 없나요 <br>엄마 그대의 품에 있던 <br>다시 그때로 <br>]]></content><category term="서바울" label="서바울"/><category term="555 (Dear.엄마) (Feat. B.O.K)" label="555 (Dear.엄마) (Feat. B.O.K)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서바울/Do_Yo_Thang/</id><title>서바울 - Do Yo Thang - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:55:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:55:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EB%B0%94%EC%9A%B8/Do_Yo_Thang/" title="서바울 - Do Yo Thang - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자신감을 갖고 <br>던져 인마 <br>난 충분해 무게로 치면 <br>이미 비만 <br>다이어트 할껀 <br>사실 너무나 많아 <br>가식같은 디톡스 <br>결국엔 요요현상 <br>아무렇지 않은척 <br>웃다 골병나 <br>새로운 길을 <br>개척 해봐 오바마 <br>딱 중간만 할 <br>생각보다 이왕 하는거 <br>빡세게 해 이건 <br>에이스 군필자의 말 <br>Keep it real <br>사라지고 득과실 <br>따지기 바빠지며 <br>실종된 positive <br>보이는게 중요 <br>짝퉁이 판쳐 요지경 <br>이제 내 말좀 들어 <br>벗어나야지 오징어 <br>외적인 것보다 <br>내면에 중심을 둬 <br>아직 넌 사춘기 <br>벗어나 질풍노도 <br>닫히지 않은 성장판 <br>limit 무한대로 <br>쭉쭉 올라가 끝은 <br>안보이지 절대로 <br>Do yo thang do yo thang Huh <br>Do yo thang do yo thang Huh <br>I I think of it day and night <br>모두가 확 가게 <br>일단 질러봐 huh <br>Do yo thang do yo thang Huh <br>Do yo thang do yo thang Huh <br>I I think of it day and night <br>모두가 확 가게 <br>일단 질러봐 huh <br>기본기 부터 <br>uh you think you fucking genius <br>과거는 닦어 <br>자 클린넥스 <br>아무도 건드리지 못하게 <br>날 믿어 Got yo back <br>시작하자 긴 race <br>버려 오지랖 <br>it's none of your business <br>뒷담 무서워하지마 <br>Be Ambitious <br>똑바로 가라고 말해도 <br>꺾어질 네 의지 <br>안할거라면 주먹내밀고 <br>let's do this <br>궁금 할 수록 더더 <br>더욱더 달려갈때 <br>탄탄한 길은 <br>니발로 밟고 만들어내 <br>항상 이길 순 없어 <br>가끔 남의 길이되서 <br>밟힘을 당해도 <br>언제나 do yo thang <br>확실한 기승전결 <br>원래 평범을 거부 <br>대신 담백하게 <br>빼내서 버려 모든 거품 <br>이제 real 전투 벗어 <br>도깨비 감투 <br>누차 말했잖아 <br>잘들어 내가 rap 장군 <br>Do yo thang do yo thang Huh <br>Do yo thang do yo thang Huh <br>I I think of it day and night <br>모두가 확 가게 <br>일단 질러봐 huh <br>Do yo thang do yo thang Huh <br>Do yo thang do yo thang Huh <br>I I think of it day and night <br>모두가 확 가게 <br>일단 질러봐 huh <br>쉽게 끓이고 <br>식히는 방법 <br>남보다 빠른 머리 <br>굴리는 과정 <br>조울증 아냐 내가 <br>좀 빨라 밤만 빼고 <br>허세 아냐 허 대신 <br>실을 확 집어 넣줘 <br>I Just wanna do what I want <br>나에게 랩이 <br>뭐냐 묻는다면 <br>유일하게 내가 <br>밀고 있는 아집 <br>아빠 미안 이것만 <br>부모 이기는 자식 <br>Do yo thang do yo thang Huh <br>Do yo thang do yo thang Huh <br>I I think of it day and night <br>모두가 확 가게 <br>일단 질러봐 huh <br>Do yo thang do yo thang Huh <br>Do yo thang do yo thang Huh <br>I I think of it day and night <br>모두가 확 가게 <br>일단 질러봐 huh <br>Do yo thang 니꺼해 <br>Do yo thang huh <br>Do yo thang 니꺼해 <br>Do yo thang huh <br>Do yo thang 니꺼해 <br>Do yo thang huh <br>Do yo thang Do yo thang <br>]]></content><category term="서바울" label="서바울"/><category term="Do Yo Thang" label="Do Yo Thang"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서바울/자꾸_Feat_RICH/</id><title>서바울 - 자꾸 (Feat. RICH) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:55:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:55:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EB%B0%94%EC%9A%B8/%EC%9E%90%EA%BE%B8_Feat_RICH/" title="서바울 - 자꾸 (Feat. RICH) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[일찍 잠자리에 누워도 자꾸 <br>잠이 오질 않아 보였어 니 얼굴 <br>이런적 첨 인것 같은데 왠지 나 <br>느낌이 나쁘지만은 <br>않은 것 같아 yeah <br>간만에 느낀 뜨거운 설렘에 <br>새벽을 지나 아침까지 밤을 새 <br>피곤해 붓기는 내겐 방해 <br>되지 않아 널 지금 만나러 가는데 <br>그래도 비비로 다크는 좀 가리고 <br>뿌려도 볼게 나 생일날 받은 향수 <br>미리다 알아본 코스는 아마도 <br>맘에 들걸 웃는 네가 보여 <br>눈을 감아도 <br>왠지 너 에게 자꾸 끌리는 것 같아 <br>이런 내가 나도 어색하지만 <br>왠지 너도 날 자꾸 당기는 것 같아 <br>이런 네가 나는 싫지가 않아 <br>만나면 꼭 물어봐야지 했던 말 <br>막상 보니 백지처럼 초기화 <br>대신 내 Adlib과 <br>터지는 네 웃음이 <br>가득 채워줬어 깜지로 <br>이건 Green light <br>난 제빈 아니지만 너란 집에 <br>자릴 잡을래 흥부도 기가 막히게 <br>오핸 하지마 하룻밤 마지막으로 <br>생각 하면 만들지도 않아 이 노래 <br>그냥 스칠 인연 같진 않아 <br>분명 내 주변 친구들 보기엔 <br>영화 찍는다 <br>비꼬아 그럼 주인공 하면 되지 <br>우리 두명 <br>이런 적 처음이야 날 믿어봐 <br>날 보는 나날이 절대 안 변해 <br>넌 가만히 <br>지금처럼 웃으면 <br>따라와줘 영원히 <br>왠지 너 에게 자꾸 끌리는 것 같아 <br>이런 내가 나도 어색하지만 <br>왠지 너도 날 자꾸 당기는 것 같아 <br>이런 네가 나는 싫지가 않아 <br>네게 자꾸 끌리는 것같아 <br>이런 나도 어색하지만 <br>날 자꾸 당기는 것같아 <br>그게 싫지가 않아 <br>자꾸 너만 보게 된단 말야 <br>이대로 너만 보고싶단 말야 <br>왠지 너 에게 자꾸 끌리는 것 같아 <br>이런 내가 나도 어색하지만 <br>왠지 너도 날 자꾸 당기는 것 같아 <br>이런 네가 나는 싫지가 않아 <br>왠지 너 에게 자꾸 끌리는 것 같아 <br>이런 내가 나도 어색하지만 <br>왠지 너도 날 자꾸 당기는 것 같아 <br>이런 네가 나는 싫지가 않아 <br>]]></content><category term="서바울" label="서바울"/><category term="자꾸 (Feat. RICH)" label="자꾸 (Feat. RICH)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서바울/Sweet_Love_Feat_RICH_학돌/</id><title>서바울 - Sweet Love (Feat. RICH, 학돌) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:55:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:55:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EB%B0%94%EC%9A%B8/Sweet_Love_Feat_RICH_%ED%95%99%EB%8F%8C/" title="서바울 - Sweet Love (Feat. RICH, 학돌) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[달콤한 어느 사탕같은 너 <br>상큼한 작은 딸기같은 너 <br>우리의 만남은 <br>이렇게 시작이 되고 <br>어느 순간 부터 난 <br>Ooh baby <br>너의 향기가 또 <br>나를 감싸고 있고 <br>나의 온기가 또 <br>너를 감싸고 있어 <br>힘이 들때도 넌 <br>밝게 웃어줘 항상 <br>내가 곁에 있을게 <br>나만의 아이스크림 <br>나의 곁에서 넌 천사가 되죠 <br>나만의 아이스크림 <br>너의 옆에서 난 웃고 있겠죠 <br>나만의 아이스크림 <br>이게 깨지 않는 <br>꿈이기를 바라죠 <br>우리 둘이 <br>Oh 우리 둘이 <br>영원히 <br>My Sweet love My Sweet love <br>My Sweet love My Sweet love <br>My Sweet love My Sweet love <br>My Sweet love My Sweet love <br>눈이 마주친 순간 그대로 얼음 <br>이렇게 예쁜 사람 처음봐 <br>내 나이 서른 <br>내가 좋다며 손을 잡고 깍지껴 <br>이런 경험 하는 것도 난생 처음 <br>바비돌 같은 외모 <br>허스키한 목소리 <br>털털한 말투 행동 <br>그때부터 Wanna be <br>너의 남자 걱정하지마 순간 반짝 <br>아냐 자리할게 니 안에 깊숙히 <br>나만의 아이스크림 <br>나의 곁에서 넌 천사가 되죠 <br>나만의 아이스크림 <br>너의 옆에서 난 웃고 있겠죠 <br>나만의 아이스크림 <br>이게 깨지 않는 <br>꿈이기를 바라죠 <br>우리 둘이 <br>Oh 우리 둘이 <br>영원히 <br>한참이나 더운 날씨에도 불구 <br>하고 내게 안겨 팔짱긴 <br>넌 beautiful <br>같이 있고 싶지만 <br>이제 집에 갈 시간 <br>택시 잡을 동안 좀 더 <br>날 꽉안아줘 <br>너의 긴 팔이 뒤에서 <br>나를 감싸 <br>안을때 내 배위 손 올려 <br>조금 민망 <br>귀엽다 웃어주던 <br>니가 벌써 생각나 <br>첨으로 고마웠던 뱃살 <br>Baby call you mine <br>My Sweet love My Sweet love <br>My Sweet love My Sweet love <br>My Sweet love My Sweet love <br>My Sweet love My Sweet love <br>]]></content><category term="서바울" label="서바울"/><category term="Sweet Love (Feat. RICH, 학돌)" label="Sweet Love (Feat. RICH, 학돌)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서바울/Saturday_Feat_Dynamite_제이디/</id><title>서바울 - Saturday (Feat. Dynamite, 제이디) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:55:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:55:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EB%B0%94%EC%9A%B8/Saturday_Feat_Dynamite_%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%EB%94%94/" title="서바울 - Saturday (Feat. Dynamite, 제이디) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 딱온 느낌 <br>논현보단 이태원 <br>간만에 멤버들 불러서 <br>불토를 태워 <br>댄디부터 힙합 <br>다갖춘 Style <br>먼저 고르는게 임자 <br>따로없어 Avengers <br>가볍게 적시자 <br>우주포차가서 <br>소주보단 소맥 이건 <br>에피타이져 <br>학돌아 넌 벌써 빨가니까 <br>물로 조절 <br>오늘은 절대로 용서못해 <br>이른 방전 <br>해밀턴 뒷골목은 <br>어김없이 바글 <br>내숭떼고 다들 노려 <br>오늘밤 대박을 <br>나는 예외라 하는 순간 <br>빠져버린걸 <br>헤어 나오지못해 <br>갈색 긴머리에 굵은컬 <br>진한눈썹에 피부는 <br>애도 울고가 <br>너의 몸몸몸매 <br>터질듯한 볼륨감 <br>핸드폰 뒷로고 같이 <br>깨물뻔한 애플힙 <br>고민은 여기까지 <br>Let me hollla <br>어디든 완벽한 날이야 <br>술이 날 적시는 밤이야 <br>오늘밤은 이대로는 <br>너무 아쉬워 <br>저기 저 완벽한 라인 <br>잠깐만 서두르지마 <br>오늘밤은 이대로는 <br>너무 아쉬워 <br>D'squad baby ya <br>평소엔 얌전해도 <br>놀땐 노는 남자 <br>Saturday Night <br>불을 지펴라 <br>홍대 신사 어디라도 <br>곧 갈 테니까 <br>쉴 새 없이 달리자 <br>아우토반 <br>놀 줄 아는 이 <br>하나 둘 다 불러 모아 <br>간만에 뭉친 드림팀 <br>달아오른 분위기 <br>참아왔던 본능이 <br>한순간에 눈을떠 <br>많이 피곤하면 <br>잠깐 기대도 되 <br>오늘도 난 네것이야 baby <br>모른척 살며시 <br>손을 줘 그리고 <br>속삭여 단 둘이 <br>나가자 어디든 <br>어디든 레드카펫 <br>주인공이 된듯한 <br>기분 너무 핫해 <br>Saturday night light live <br>Saturday night light live <br>어디든 완벽한 날이야 <br>술이 날 적시는 밤이야 <br>오늘밤은 이대로는 <br>너무 아쉬워 <br>저기 저 완벽한 라인 <br>잠깐만 서두르지마 <br>오늘밤은 이대로는 <br>너무 아쉬워 <br>널 안고 싶어 조금만더 <br>궁금해 또 다른 네 모습도 <br>짧게 느껴져 <br>Saturday night <br>이대로 즐기는건 어때 <br>I wanna be with you <br>Be with you tonight <br>어디든 완벽한 날이야 <br>술이 날 적시는 밤이야 <br>오늘밤은 이대로는 <br>너무 아쉬워 <br>저기 저 완벽한 라인 <br>잠깐만 서두르지마 <br>오늘밤은 이대로는 <br>너무 아쉬워 <br>]]></content><category term="서바울" label="서바울"/><category term="Saturday (Feat. Dynamite, 제이디)" label="Saturday (Feat. Dynamite, 제이디)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서바울/스토커_Feat_이나겸/</id><title>서바울 - 스토커 (Feat. 이나겸) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:55:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:55:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EB%B0%94%EC%9A%B8/%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%BB%A4_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%EB%82%98%EA%B2%B8/" title="서바울 - 스토커 (Feat. 이나겸) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우린 이미 끝난 사인걸 알아 <br>이젠 그만 할게 나를 좀 놓아줘 <br>니가 아무리 잡으려해도 <br>내맘은 변했어 <br>이젠 모두 다 끝났어 <br>잠깐 너 내말 좀 들어봐 멈춰서 <br>어제만 해도 안놓겠다며 니두손 <br>꽉 잡던게 마지막 <br>빠져나간 모래같아 <br>잘 한번 설명해봐 <br>잘해줘서 질렸단 말은 닥치고 <br>날 탐탁치 않게 바라보던 가족 <br>귀는 닫기로 했잖아 <br>미래를 봐서 나만 감옥 <br>살이하는거 같아 구해달라 <br>너를 찾아갔지만 <br>대답없는 노크만 <br>수백번 내 존심은 담보로 <br>삼겨졌어 심지어 블락돼 <br>버렸더군 너의 인스타 <br>수많은 니 팔로워 보다 <br>못해져 버린 나의 위치가 <br>즈려밟힌 진달래 꽃 <br>추억은 다 빛바랬고 <br>모든 약속은 반품도 안돼서 <br>버려야만 해 남은재고 <br>내 신부는 누가 될지 <br>모르지만 응답하라 묻는다면 <br>사실 너라고 생각했어 <br>나 내 끝사랑 <br>돌아온다면 받아줄 생각중 <br>아직 난 너만의 랩스타 <br>니 생각에 쓴 노래들 못 듣겠으니 <br>제발 들어 줄래 내 부탁 <br>나만의 스토커 스토커 스토커 <br>외로운 넌 스토커 스토커 스토커 <br>태양을 보아도 날 볼수없어 <br>그림자가 돼버린 날 <br>그댄 스토커 스토커 스토커 <br>외로운 넌 스토커 스토커 스토커 <br>다가오려 하면 다가올수록 <br>점점 멀어지는나 넌 나의 스토커 <br>궁금해 단지 알고 싶어 <br>너 달라진이유 <br>헤어지고도 다시 먼저 <br>전화로 보고싶다 울구 <br>돌아왔다 확신했던 <br>내게 실수 라며 선을 근후 <br>니가 날려준 카운터 <br>펀치 덕분에 더이상 회복불능 <br>참지 못하고 찾아간 <br>너희 집앞에서 전화버튼 <br>눌러보지만 역시나 <br>받지않고 창에 비친 노란 커튼 <br>사이로 웃는 니 얼굴 화가나 <br>내피가 거꾸로 솟기 시작해 <br>근데 미소를 띄고 <br>넌 누구랑 계속 통화중 <br>혼자선 힘들어 친구들과 <br>모여 걸친 술 한잔 <br>너와 남은 끈과 취하기 <br>싫은 정신은 간당간당 <br>결국 나도 몰래 찾아간 <br>니 집앞 문만 바라보다 <br>돌아와서 다짐해 모든사진에 <br>담긴 내맘은 깊은바다 <br>속에 던져 다신 떠오르지 <br>못하게 큰 돌을 묶어 <br>니가 벌인 살인에 확인사살 <br>두 세번 내맘을 죽여 <br>걱정마 너랑 달리말야 <br>정이남아 막지않아 앞길 <br>그래도 책임지고 가야지 <br>니가 밟고간 내 마지막 존심 <br>나만의 스토커 스토커 스토커 <br>외로운 넌 스토커 스토커 스토커 <br>태양을 보아도 날 볼수없어 <br>그림자가 돼버린 날 <br>그댄 스토커 스토커 스토커 <br>외로운 넌 스토커 스토커 스토커 <br>다가오려 하면 다가올수록 <br>점점 멀어지는나 넌 나의 스토커 <br>나는 니가 정말 좋아서 그래 <br>이상한 사람아냐 <br>왜 갑자기 하는거야 존대 <br>예전과 달라진 태도 <br>내손을 자꾸만 빼도 <br>난 어디 갈 수 없더라 <br>넌 이미 산소 이상의 존재 <br>이건 정말 괴롭히려는 게 아냐 <br>내맘이 겪고있어 <br>내 생 최고의 가난 <br>너한테 보내는 문자 <br>안봐도 좋아 그순간 <br>내게 다시 웃어 <br>줄 때까지 포기 못하니까 <br>나만의 스토커 스토커 스토커 <br>외로운 넌 스토커 스토커 스토커 <br>태양을 보아도 날 볼수없어 <br>그림자가 돼버린 날 <br>그댄 스토커 스토커 스토커 <br>외로운 넌 스토커 스토커 스토커 <br>다가오려 하면 다가올수록 <br>점점 멀어지는나 넌 나의 스토커 <br>넌 나의 스토커 <br>]]></content><category term="서바울" label="서바울"/><category term="스토커 (Feat. 이나겸)" label="스토커 (Feat. 이나겸)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서바울/연애_참_가볍다_Feat_신나라/</id><title>서바울 - 연애 참 가볍다 (Feat. 신나라) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:55:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:55:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EB%B0%94%EC%9A%B8/%EC%97%B0%EC%95%A0_%EC%B0%B8_%EA%B0%80%EB%B3%8D%EB%8B%A4_Feat_%EC%8B%A0%EB%82%98%EB%9D%BC/" title="서바울 - 연애 참 가볍다 (Feat. 신나라) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[애써 잘해 줘봐야 어차피 가 Love <br>기껏 보내 줘봐야 너혼자 Good love <br>다시 생각해봐도 주윈 다 말려 <br>I hate You You You <br>가벼워 연애 그 느낌 <br>알고 있어 니가 원하던건 돈 <br>이나 뭐 그런게 아니란 걸 <br>너에 대한 맘이 더 꽉찰수록 <br>차있지않고 비워지는 내 잔고 <br>넌 괜찮다지만 달라 남잔 <br>퍼주고픈 맘에 사실 난 부담 <br>하지마 오핸 그래서 널 보낸 <br>건 아냐 혹시나 해서 그냥 한말 <br>너만 봤어 내 두눈엔 <br>널 위해 만든 내 사랑 노래 <br>상상했어 쭉 너 만이 내 신부 <br>너 이별 고하기 5분 전에두 <br>쌓여가는 변명과 핑계 <br>쳐져가 너의 표정과 어깨 <br>못찾아 걸어도 목숨을 담보 <br>정리해 버린 니맘 되돌릴 방법 <br>애써 잘해 줘봐야 어차피 가 Love <br>기껏 보내 줘봐야 너혼자 Good love <br>다시 생각해봐도 주윈 다 말려 <br>I hate You You You <br>가벼워 연애 그 느낌 <br>아침 눈뜨자마자 <br>널 깨워줘야해 전화를 잡아 <br>화면 속 니가 보이지 않은 걸 보고 <br>바로 현실 자각 <br>모든 사진과 편지를 지워 <br>내진못해 눈을 피해 다 숨겨 <br>근데 느껴져 니흔적 내 습관들로 <br>마른 눈물을 불러 <br>내 손 처음 맞 잡을때 <br>말했던 너 확신은 도대체 <br>어디로 간거야 짜증도 나지만 <br>할수있는건 고작 그게 다지 나 <br>이별앞에선 초보 운전자 <br>매번 겪어도 익숙치 않아 <br>물까지 부어버린 꺼진 불씨 <br>끝난거 다알아 어차피 우리 <br>애써 잘해 줘봐야 어차피 가 Love <br>기껏 보내 줘봐야 너혼자 Good love <br>다시 생각해봐도 주윈 다 말려 <br>I hate You You You <br>가벼워 연애 그 느낌 <br>밤새 둘이서 함께 미래를 그리던 <br>그 추억들이 날 아프게 해 <br>기억 모두 다 가져가 <br>애써 잘해 줘봐야 어차피 가 Love <br>기껏 보내 줘봐야 너혼자 Good love <br>다시 생각해봐도 <br>다시 생각해봐도 I hate you <br>애써 잘해 줘봐야 어차피 가 Love <br>기껏 보내 줘봐야 너혼자 Good love <br>다시 생각해봐도 주윈 다 말려 <br>I hate You You You <br>가벼워 연애 그 느낌 <br>연락은 온데간데 끝난거 같애 <br>꿈꾸던 우리 미래 <br>나 혼자 출발한 여행 <br>버렸어 내 존심 변한거지 <br>하지않아 변심 <br>이기고 지는게 아냐 <br>단지 달랐던 무게감 <br>약지에 낀 반지 <br>]]></content><category term="서바울" label="서바울"/><category term="연애 참 가볍다 (Feat. 신나라)" label="연애 참 가볍다 (Feat. 신나라)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서바울/Keep/</id><title>서바울 - Keep - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:55:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:55:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EB%B0%94%EC%9A%B8/Keep/" title="서바울 - Keep - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[태어날 때부터 날 가둬왔던 죄 <br>한가운데 떠있던 중심 박은채 <br>하늘보고 외쳐 겉은론 센척 <br>해도 빌었던 용서 빽돈 없어 One way <br>억지로 골라야만 돼 <br>주어진 보기보다 <br>내가 만드는게 편했어 주관식 <br>말이 꽤나 많다보니 얻은닉넴 Estteee <br>그게난데 That's me 짊어질 책임 <br>곤조가 고집이 돼 <br>타협까지 내려온 <br>몽당 연필과 달리 <br>다듬어진 조약돌 <br>유연해 어디서든 <br>적응할게 아마존 <br>자신있지만 잡아 <br>먹지만은 말아줘 <br>시간이 흘러가도 <br>절대 조급해 하지마 <br>쌓여가고 있으니까 <br>실력과 커리어 <br>쓸데없는 걱정 저 개나 주고와 <br>제발 떨어지지 마오 <br>마지막 잎새여 <br>Follow my voice <br>야망을 가져 boys <br>그림은 완성 되기 <br>전까진 모르는 법 <br>Follow my voice <br>야망을 가져 boys <br>망설이지마 It s time to go <br>Follow my voice <br>야망을 가져 boys <br>퀵보단 상승곡선을 계속 keep <br>Follow my voice <br>내가 갖고 시작한 <br>수많은 옵션 중에서도 하필 <br>다 때려치고 이짓 선택 후 불가피 <br>잘하는건 없어도 <br>못하는 것도 딱히 <br>확실한건 하나 <br>믿어주세요 우리 아버지 <br>인정 Fucking haters don't know about me <br>내위친 신상도 아냐 택도 없지 <br>But I aint you 할줄 알아도 화투 <br>밑장 빼기 따윈 절대 안해 타짜 고니 <br>가까워서 커보이는상태 <br>난 멀리라서 보다 <br>작아보이는 존재 <br>Yo 반전을 원한다면 그건 숨을 쉴때 <br>까지만 이라고 제발 명심해 <br>후회는 절대 될수 없어 1등 <br>하고싶다면 움직여 Like yo role model <br>끝없는 가뭄 적셔줄거야 단비로 <br>올라갈 것만 생각해 From the bottom <br>Follow my voice <br>야망을 가져 boys <br>그림은 완성 되기 전까진 모르는 법 <br>Follow my voice <br>야망을 가져 boys <br>망설이지마 It's time to go <br>Follow my voice <br>야망을 가져 boys <br>]]></content><category term="서바울" label="서바울"/><category term="Keep" label="Keep"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김미경/눈을_감아/</id><title>김미경 - 눈을 감아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:55:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:55:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%AF%B8%EA%B2%BD/%EB%88%88%EC%9D%84_%EA%B0%90%EC%95%84/" title="김미경 - 눈을 감아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[때론 듣고 싶지 않은 말들이 있어 <br>너의 입에서 <br>쏟아져 나오는 호기심에 더 이상 <br>난 <br>눈을 감아 이제 어떡해야 하나 <br>귀를 막아 듣지 말아야 했던 그 말 <br>어떤 표정을 지어야 하나 <br>어떤 대답을 해야 하나 <br>알 수 없는 너의 말들로 <br>가득 찬 이곳엔 <br>알 수 없는 너와 내가 <br>서로를 묻는다 <br>희미해진 공간 속을 <br>지나쳐 이곳엔 <br>희미해진 너와 내가 <br>서로를 그린다 <br>눈을 감아 이제 어떡해야 하나 <br>귀를 막아 듣지 말아야 했던 그 말 <br>어떤 표정을 지어야 하나 <br>어떤 대답을 해야 하나 <br>알 수 없는 너의 말들로 <br>가득 찬 이곳엔 <br>알 수 없는 너와 내가 <br>서로를 묻는다 <br>희미해진 공간 속을 <br>지나쳐 이곳엔 <br>희미해진 너와 내가 <br>서로를 그린다 <br>알 수 없는 너의 말들로 <br>가득 찬 이곳엔 <br>알 수 없는 너와 내가 <br>서로를 묻는다 <br>희미해진 공간 속을 <br>지나쳐 이곳엔 <br>희미해진 너와 내가 <br>서로를 그린다 <br>때론 듣고 싶지 않은 말들이 있어 <br>너의 입에서 <br>쏟아져 나오는 호기심에 더 이상 <br>난 <br>]]></content><category term="김미경" label="김미경"/><category term="눈을 감아" label="눈을 감아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/장기섭/살려줘_수진아/</id><title>장기섭 - 살려줘 수진아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:55:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:55:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%EA%B8%B0%EC%84%AD/%EC%82%B4%EB%A0%A4%EC%A4%98_%EC%88%98%EC%A7%84%EC%95%84/" title="장기섭 - 살려줘 수진아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자유를 얻었어 두발 뻗고 잤어 <br>새로운 사랑을 또 꿈꿨어 <br>매일 싸웠잖아 둘 다 지쳤잖아 <br>그래 우린 인연이 아니야 <br>미쳤었나봐 시간이 지날 수록 <br>빈 자리가 더욱 커져가 <br>가슴아 내 가슴아 <br>멈춰버린 심장아 <br>크게 이름부른다 수진아 <br>가슴아 나의 심장아 돌아와줘 <br>너 없인 난 틀렸다 <br>사랑 하나 지키지 못해 애원한다 <br>제발 나를 살려줘 수진아 <br>매일 싸웠잖아 밉다고 했잖아 <br>이럴바엔 우리 그만 끝내 <br>변했어 많이 자유롭다 믿었어 <br>너를 보낸 며칠 동안은 <br>가슴아 내 가슴아 <br>멈춰버린 심장아 <br>크게 이름부른다 수진아 <br>가슴아 나의 심장아 돌아와줘 <br>너 없인 난 틀렸다 <br>사랑하나 지키지 못해 애원한다 <br>제발 나를 살려줘 <br>지금 너의 집 앞이야 <br>사실 매일 밤 찾아왔어 <br>어쩌니 크게 소리쳐 <br>너를 부르고 싶다 <br>내 가슴아 멈춰버린 심장아 <br>크게 이름부른다 수진아 <br>미안해 날 용서해줘 난 틀렸다 <br>너 없인 난 끝났다 <br>사랑 하나 지키지 못해 애원한다 <br>다시 돌아와주라 <br>제발 <br>]]></content><category term="장기섭" label="장기섭"/><category term="살려줘 수진아" label="살려줘 수진아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Puddy_퍼디/Kiss_Your_Body_2/</id><title>Puddy_퍼디 - Kiss Your Body 2 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:55:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:55:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Puddy_%ED%8D%BC%EB%94%94/Kiss_Your_Body_2/" title="Puddy_퍼디 - Kiss Your Body 2 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby I know you want me <br>I want you too and I'm so thirsty <br>깊은 골짜기 아래 웅덩이 <br>I wanna go there 오늘밤 <br>그 곳에 난 목이 말라 <br>넌 뭔가 달라 <br>니 흉부 니 엉덩이 <br>뭐 딱히 필요하진 않지 우리 <br>너와 내 사이엔 <br>까만 어둠과 술이 <br>맨정신에도 대낮에라도 <br>대낮에라도 우린 항상 <br>그 다음날의 해를 보지 <br>니가 없인 충분히 쪄죽기에 <br>문제없다고 생각했던 <br>한국의 여름은 너무 추워 <br>밤이건 낮이건 너의 <br>beutiful body baby <br>I can't wait <br>니가 너무 좋아서 일루와 <br>you you <br>I want your body baby <br>you you baby <br>I want your body baby <br>let me kiss again <br>let me kiss again <br>let me kiss again <br>one more one more <br>you you <br>I want your body baby <br>you you baby <br>I want your body baby <br>let me kiss again <br>let me kiss again <br>let me kiss again <br>one more one more <br>one more time when we feel <br>볼륨은 stereo <br>in the night in the day <br>우리는 alien <br>in the sky in the space <br>저 높은 우주위로 <br>I just wanna love you <br>넌 요즘 내 심장의 representer <br>난 이미 상상만도 수백번했어 <br>난 널 원해 원해 원해 원해 <br>너와 나 하루종일 <br>바로 지금 make it <br>make love make it rain <br>pour right 액체란 액체는 <br>전부 strike 몸서리치는 <br>건물 like us waterfalls <br>yeah I just wanna kiss <br>너의 모든 것에 다 <br>yeah I just wanna kiss <br>nobody but you baby 한번 더 <br>one more time when we feel <br>볼륨은 stereo <br>in the night in the day <br>우리는 alien <br>in the sky in the space <br>저 높은 우주위로 <br>you're so dangerous <br>you're so dangerous <br>you you <br>I want your body baby <br>you you baby <br>I want your body baby <br>let me kiss again <br>let me kiss again <br>let me kiss again <br>one more one more <br>you you <br>I want your body baby <br>you you baby <br>I want your body baby <br>let me kiss again <br>let me kiss again <br>let me kiss again <br>one more one more <br>뭐 딱히 필요하진 않지 우리 <br>너와 내 사이엔 <br>까만 어둠과 술이 <br>맨정신에도 대낮에라도 <br>대낮에라도 우린 항상 <br>그 다음날의 해를 보지 <br>one more time when we feel <br>볼륨은 stereo <br>in the night in the day <br>우리는 alien <br>in the sky in the space <br>저 높은 우주위로 <br>]]></content><category term="Puddy (퍼디)" label="Puddy (퍼디)"/><category term="Kiss Your Body 2" label="Kiss Your Body 2"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/원종찬/다_너_때문이야/</id><title>원종찬 - 다 너 때문이야... - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:57:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:57:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9B%90%EC%A2%85%EC%B0%AC/%EB%8B%A4_%EB%84%88_%EB%95%8C%EB%AC%B8%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC/" title="원종찬 - 다 너 때문이야... - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하얀 구름이 <br>마치 나를 <br>반겨주는 듯 <br>이 바람도 <br>아주 적당히 <br>또 불어온다 <br>조금 들떴나봐 <br>조금 신나보이지 <br>그래 이건 확실해 <br>다 너 때문이야 <br>또 지쳐있구나 <br>많이 피곤해보여 <br>소리없이 안아줄게 <br>더 해줄게없어 <br>난 이것 뿐이야 <br>많이 초라 하지만 <br>이런 나를 사랑하는 <br>내가 더 감사해 <br>한 두 번 보는 것 <br>조차 아닌데 <br>알면 알수록 <br>자꾸 미칠것 같아 <br>널 사랑한다 <br>이 말로는 <br>도저히 분이 <br>안풀린다 <br>I love you <br>I need you <br>I falling in love <br>당장 내일 조차 <br>재밌을것 같아 <br>이젠 난 영원히 <br>다 함께라서 너라서 <br>그냥 너라서 감사해 <br>한 두 번 보는 것 <br>조차 아닌데 <br>보면 볼수록 <br>자꾸 진정이 안돼 <br>널 사랑한다 <br>이 말로는 <br>도저히 분이 <br>안풀린다 <br>I love you <br>I need you <br>I falling in love <br>당장 내일 조차 <br>재밌을것 같아 <br>이젠 난 영원히 <br>다 함께라서 너라서 <br>그냥 너라서 감사해 <br>I love you <br>I need you <br>I falling in love <br>당장 내일 조차 <br>재밌을것 같아 <br>이젠 난 영원히 <br>다 함께라서 너라서 <br>그냥 너라서 감사해 <br>계속 웃고 있잖아 <br>정말 행복하나봐 <br>마냥 좋아 실없이 <br>또 웃고있어 <br>조금 바보같지 <br>그냥 어린애 같지 <br>그래 이건 확실해 <br>다 너 때문이야 <br>]]></content><category term="원종찬" label="원종찬"/><category term="다 너 때문이야..." label="다 너 때문이야..."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/The_Rains/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - The Rains - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:57:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:57:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/The_Rains/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - The Rains - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, it hadn't rained in as many Sundays as the preacher he had prayed <br>But it didn't matter 'cause nobody prayed it anyway <br>Some danced and some sang <br>Some threw silver rings <br>And the corn got yella and the wheat all died <br>And the sun dried up the springs <br>When the rains came <br>The whole town lost it's mind <br>Poured gasoline down Main Street <br>And we set it up on fire <br>When the rains came <br>How were we to know <br>We'd held on for so long <br>And just to let it go <br>When the rains came <br>And they called in the state troopers <br>And they called in the police <br>And they arrested everybody <br>My brothers and me <br>And when we got to court <br>And they put us on the stand <br>We just looked at each other <br>Started laughing once again <br>'Cause when the rains came <br>The whole town lost it's mind <br>Poured gasoline down Main Street <br>And we set it up on fire <br>When the rains came <br>How were we to know <br>We'd held on for so long <br>And just to let it go <br>When the rains came <br>Some say it's a tragedy <br>Some say it's a shame <br>Some say it's the water <br>We never got to drink <br>Some blame Jesus <br>Some blame the rock and roll <br>I think we were just trying to get <br>A little bit of control <br>So, when the rains came <br>The whole town lost it's mind <br>Poured gasoline down Main Street <br>And we set it up on fire <br>When the rains came <br>How were we to know <br>We'd held on for so long <br>And just to let it go <br>When the rains came <br>When the rains came <br>When the rains came <br>When the rains came <br>When the rains came]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="The Rains" label="The Rains"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Tired/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Tired - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:57:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:57:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Tired/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Tired - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Better take some extra blankets <br>Going out past sixty <br>They say the wind is cold <br>Comin' in off the shelf <br>Better take some extra flour <br>Take some extra biscuits <br>Take another bedroll <br>And a few more shotgun shells <br>Don't you ever get tired of herding up those cattle <br>From low to high and high to low <br>And always changing ground <br>Don't you ever get tired of setting in that saddle <br>Starin' at that Western sky watching the sun go down <br>They say the blacktop's tore up <br>Right up through Topeka <br>They're pulling people over <br>And the trucks are moving slow <br>I got a friend out back <br>He knows a couple side roads <br>The troopers stay out of there <br>And the weigh stations are closed <br>Don't you ever get tired of herding up those cattle <br>From low to high and high to low <br>And always changing ground <br>Don't you ever get tired of setting in that saddle <br>Starin' at that Western sky watching the sun go down <br>They found old Ray Mcguire last week up on Jimmy Ridge <br>He was wrapped up like a mummy <br>Frozen colder than a stone <br>They said they found his herd <br>He had them fenced and hitched <br>He had several different breeds <br>And the brands weren't all his own <br>Don't you ever get tired of herding up those cattle <br>From low to high and high to low <br>And always changing ground <br>Don't you ever get tired of setting in that saddle <br>Starin' at that Western sky watching the sun go down]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Tired" label="Tired"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Millies_Cafe/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Millie`s Cafe - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:58:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:58:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Millies_Cafe/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Millie`s Cafe - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They put up a sign for the very last time <br>At Milly's Cafe <br>They loaded their stuff into the car <br>And they drove away <br>Milly looked back for one last time <br>And when she turned around, she was crying <br>Billy just listened to the songs the radio played <br>They drove all the way from Fort Worth to Amarillo <br>When Milly woke up she had makeup all over her pillow <br>Billy had stopped at Easy Pawn <br>And bought them up a couple of guns <br>Tomorrow, he said, was gonna be a brand new day <br>Billy and Milly tore up the entire West <br>They started holding up liquor stores and then they turned to banks <br>And it wasn't very long, you know <br>Their picture was on the post office wall <br>And it seemed that the whole world was looking for them <br>And the roads just get rougher <br>Out in West Texas <br>The cowboys are tougher <br>And the young girls are restless <br>And the winds take the towns <br>And there ain't any signs <br>But there's always a hill to climb <br>On the West Texas skyline <br>Milly was raised by Christians in Aberdeen <br>Her father was a preacher in the biggest church you ever did see <br>When word came down about Milly and Billy <br>He made a call up to New York City <br>He said for some boys to come down and set things straight <br>He met Milly in El Paso <br>Underneath a tree in the parking lot of the motel <br>And the next day when Billy went in the bank <br>She started the car and she drove away <br>When Billy came out, he never had a chance <br>And the roads just get rougher <br>Out in West Texas <br>The cowboys are rougher <br>And the young girls are restless <br>And the winds take the towns <br>And there ain't any signs <br>But there's always a hill to climb <br>On the West Texas skyline <br>Put up the sign one more time <br>At Milly's cafe <br>They loaded the stuff out of the car and into the doorway <br>Milly looked back the one last time <br>And when she turned around she was crying <br>Her daddy just got in his car and he drove away <br>And the roads just get rougher <br>Out in West Texas <br>Cowboys are tougher <br>But the young girls are restless <br>And the winds takes the town <br>And there ain't any signs <br>There's always a hill to climb <br>On the West Texas skyline <br>There's always a hill to climb <br>On the West Texas skyline]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Millie`s Cafe" label="Millie`s Cafe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Rocky/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Rocky - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:58:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:58:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Rocky/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Rocky - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Rocky, I'm writing you this letter <br>I'm in the Sunset Home <br>My grandkids went and put me here <br>They got everything I own <br>I know you're out in Albuquerque <br>I saw Freddie just last week <br>He said your eyesight's failing you <br>And your mouth's too sore to speak <br>Rocky, I've been thinking lately <br>How we never got along <br>How mostly I was right <br>And sometimes I was wrong <br>Remember that horse we bought in Tulsa <br>It was afraid of the startin' gun <br>You'd fill his ears full of cotton <br>And all the money that we won <br>Rocky, you sure were a good cowboy <br>You did sure could rope and ride <br>I always told you not to chew that goddamned tobacco <br>You coulda listened just one time <br>They don't show many Westerns on TV here <br>They took away my gun <br>But I still got that Western saddle <br>The one we stole from Freddie's son <br>Rocky, I hear that they're feeding you <br>And it sure do make me sad <br>I never thought in all my days <br>You'd ever end up like that <br>Remember that trailer in Minnesota <br>That axle broke right in two <br>We wired it together with four by fours <br>And we drove the whole night through <br>Rocky, you sure were a good cowboy <br>You did sure could rope and ride <br>I always told you not to chew that goddamned tobacco <br>You coulda listened just one time <br>So, Rocky, I'll just sign off now <br>I've been up most of the night <br>I just wanted to tell you when I heard the news <br>It damned near made me cry <br>Remember that gun we bought in Reno <br>You shot Freddie right through the hand <br>You wrapped it up in your best Western shirt <br>Gave him all the money you had <br>Rocky, you sure were a good cowboy <br>You did sure could rope and ride <br>I always told you not to chew that goddamned tobacco <br>You coulda listened just one time <br>You coulda listened just one time]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Rocky" label="Rocky"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Summer_Is_Over/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Summer Is Over - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:58:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:58:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Summer_Is_Over/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Summer Is Over - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, summer is over <br>The turnstiles are seized <br>The Ferris wheel turns by itself in the breeze <br>And the big diesel engines <br>Idle out on the lawn <br>Summer is over <br>And my baby's gone <br>And the roller coaster <br>Pulls at it's pins <br>The bumper boats drift out <br>And they drift back in <br>And the September breezes <br>Are bringing winter along <br>Summer is over <br>And my baby's gone <br>And the ring that she won me <br>Is broken in pieces <br>And I sat on the hat <br>Now it's got extra creases <br>And she didn't answer <br>The last time I called <br>To tell her they were scrubbing <br>Our names off the wall <br>But she left a message <br>And I should have known <br>Summer is over <br>And my baby's gone <br>Yeah, summer is over <br>And my baby's gone]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Summer Is Over" label="Summer Is Over"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Kansas/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Kansas - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:58:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:58:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Kansas/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Kansas - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's always Kansas <br>That's where I always break down <br>That's where my world <br>Tumbles to the ground <br>It's always Kansas <br>That's where I fall apart <br>That's where my broken heart <br>Catches up with the news <br>It's always Kansas <br>It's always Kansas <br>Always Kansas <br>Makes me think of you <br>Those sad sad songs <br>On the radio <br>In the juke box in the truck stops <br>They don't bother me <br>You know <br>I can face the day <br>I can walk away <br>I can tell myself <br>I'm gonna be okay <br>It's always Kansas <br>That's where I always break down <br>That's where my world <br>Tumbles to the ground <br>It's always Kansas <br>That's where I fall apart <br>That's where my broken heart <br>Catches up with the news <br>It's always Kansas <br>It's always Kansas <br>Always Kansas <br>Makes me think of you <br>I don't know why you had to go <br>I've thought and thought it out <br>Leavenworth to Dodge <br>I've traveled every road <br>It's always Kansas <br>That's where I always break down <br>That's where my world <br>Tumbles to the ground <br>That's where I fall apart <br>It's where my broken heart <br>Catches up with the news <br>It's always Kansas <br>It's always Kansas <br>Always Kansas <br>Makes me think of you <br>It's always Kansas]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Kansas" label="Kansas"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Silhouettes/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Silhouettes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:58:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:58:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Silhouettes/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Silhouettes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hold me baby <br>Hold me like only you can do <br>Two silhouettes dancin <br>By the light of the moon <br>Hold me baby <br>Hold me like you used to do <br>Two silhouettes dancin <br>By the light of the moon <br>I always told you <br>I loved you <br>Till the end of time <br>Always told you <br>Now I wanna tell you <br>That never <br>Have I changed my mind <br>Hold me baby <br>Hold me <br>You know my love is true <br>Two silhouettes dancin <br>By the light of the moon <br><br>I always told you <br>Always told you I love you <br>There wouldn't be any doubt <br>Now I wanna tell you <br>You're someone <br>I don't wanna have to <br>Live without <br>So hold me baby <br>Hold me <br>You know my love is true <br>Two silhouettes dancin <br>Hold me <br>By the light of the moon <br>Two silhouettes dancin <br>Hold me <br>By the light of the moon]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Silhouettes" label="Silhouettes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Car/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Car - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:58:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:58:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Car/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Car - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1, 2 <br>1, 2, 3, 4 <br><br>I thought I saw you in a car <br>I thought I saw you on a morning train <br>Saw you walkin in a bar <br>I thought I saw you in a car <br><br>I thought I saw you in a magazine <br>I thought I saw you in a movie screen <br>I made a wish upon a star <br><br>I thought I saw you a traffic cop <br>I thought I saw you at a bus stop <br>I see you everywhere you are <br>I thought I saw you in a car <br><br>I thought I saw you in a country club <br>I thought I saw you you were cleaning up <br>I thought I saw you and your eyes were shut <br>I thought I saw you in a car <br>I thought I saw you on a fine trimmed lawn <br>It seemed like everybody else was gone <br>You were dancin in the dark <br>I thought I saw you in a car <br><br>I thought I saw you on a side road <br>I saw you broken down, you know <br>Never tore me right apart <br>I thought I saw you in a car <br><br>I thought I saw you on a morning train <br>You know it nearly drove me insane <br>I think you've taken it too far <br>I thought I saw you in a car <br><br>I thought I saw you in a car <br>I thought I saw you in a car <br>I thought I saw you in a car <br>I thought I saw you in a car]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Car" label="Car"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Dynamite_And_Whiskey/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Dynamite And Whiskey - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:58:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:58:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Dynamite_And_Whiskey/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Dynamite And Whiskey - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamite and whiskey <br>It's all the same <br>Tobacco in the sunshine <br>Sleeping in the rain <br>Jesus said for sure <br>He's coming back again <br>Dynamite and whiskey <br>It's all the same <br><br>Ain't no tomorrow <br>Hold me with no eyes <br>Stand back away <br>And you'll wait for a ride <br>Stand by the water <br>And you'll whisper something <br>Dynamite and whiskey <br>It's all the same <br><br>Rub it in your blood <br>Rub it on your mind <br>When she wipes just flapping out of time <br>I seen some things I won't see again <br>It's all the same <br>It's all the same <br><br>I think it's gonna rain <br><br>Dynamite and whiskey <br>It's all the same <br>Tobacco in the sunshine <br>Sleepin in the rain <br>Stand by the water <br>And you'll whisper something <br>Dynamite and whiskey <br>It's all the same <br>It's all the same <br><br>It's all the same <br>It's all the same <br><br>Dynamite and whiskey <br>It's all the same <br>It's all the same]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Dynamite And Whiskey" label="Dynamite And Whiskey"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Rebecca_Street/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Rebecca Street - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:58:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:58:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Rebecca_Street/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Rebecca Street - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well it's rainin out on Rebecca Street <br>And I aint doin that well <br>I was gonna do a whole lot better this time <br>That's what I told myself <br>And I'm waiting for the lights to change <br>These days they never do <br>And all the girls on Rebecca street <br>Look by you <br><br>I saw Katie Kinkade <br>She said to say hello <br>And she said she was sorry <br>When I told her the story <br>She said that she didn't know <br><br>Funny how she's wearing her hair these days <br>The same way you used to <br>And all the girls on Rebecca street <br>Look like you <br>And every magazine <br>And every mezzanine <br>Is starin right back at me <br>And everywhere I go <br>Everybody that I know <br>Every picture on TV <br><br>And the light used to turn from red to green <br>But these days they just turn blue <br>And all of the girls on Rebecca street <br>Look like you <br>And all of the girls on Rebecca street <br>Look like you]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Rebecca Street" label="Rebecca Street"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Gone_Too_Long/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Gone Too Long - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:58:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:58:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Gone_Too_Long/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Gone Too Long - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How many nights <br>How many days <br>How many nights <br>Since you went away <br>You been gone too long <br>Gone too long <br>You been gone too long <br>Gone too long <br>Did I do something wrong <br>You been gone too long <br>Gone too long <br>I went to your house <br>I knocked on your door <br>The neighbors said <br>They didn't think you lived there no more <br>You been gone too long <br>Gone too long <br>You been gone too long <br>Gone too long <br>Did I do something wrong <br>You been gone too long Gone too long <br><br>I went to a bar <br>I stood on a stool <br>The bartender said <br>You're just another fool <br>She's been gone too long <br>She been gone too long <br>Gone too long <br>Did I do something wrong <br>Gone too long <br><br>Packed up my things <br>I'm leavin this town <br>Ain't no use stayin <br>If you ain't around <br>You been gone too long <br>Gone too long <br>You been gone too long <br>Gone too long <br>Did I do something wrong]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Gone Too Long" label="Gone Too Long"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Shallow/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Shallow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:59:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:59:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Shallow/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Shallow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well look at how you're being <br>Now that you've gone off the deep end <br>Look at how you're being <br>To me and nearly all my friends <br>You told all the secrets <br>You promised everybody you would keep <br>I could be that shallow too <br>If only I wasn't in so deep <br><br>Along the dust of silence <br>Imaginary beggars call you knight <br>And your telephone doesn't ring <br>But you keep it off the hook just the same <br>And you lie awake at night <br>Pretending that you just can't get to sleep <br>I could be that shallow too <br>If only I wasn't in so deep <br><br>I seen your only house <br>Behind that brand new subdivision <br>I stood behind you in line <br>While you agonized over your decision <br>And your choice has turned out to be the same <br>As all the others, shitty <br>I could be that shallow too <br>If only I wasn't in so deep <br>I could be that shallow too <br>If only I wasn't in so deep <br>I could be that shallow too <br>If I really wanted to <br>I could do what you do <br>I could be that shallow too <br>I could be that shallow too <br>If I really wanted to <br>I could do what you do <br>I could be that shallow too <br>I could be that shallow too <br>If I really wanted to <br>I could do what you do <br>I could be that shallow too <br>I could be that shallow too <br>If I really wanted to <br>I could do what you do <br>I could be that shallow too <br>I could be that shallow too]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Shallow" label="Shallow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/I_Would/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - I Would - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:59:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:59:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/I_Would/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - I Would - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well if you're wondering <br>It would seem if you <br>When the world came near or you <br>I would I would <br>When it came crash into your roof <br>Who would be there for you <br>I would I Would <br>When nobody else would stay <br>I would I would <br>When nobody else would pray <br>I would I would <br>If you're wonderin who would be there <br>When nobody seemed to care <br>I would I would <br>I would I would <br>I would I would <br>If the bullets were a flyin <br>And you didn't feel like dyin <br>I would I would <br>If the ending was coming <br>And someone there running <br>I would I would <br>If we ever go over the wall <br>I would I would <br>If someone helps stay in front <br>I would I would <br>If someone had to take it <br>And you couldn't make it <br>I would I would <br>I would I would <br>I would I would <br><br>I would I would <br>I would I would <br>If you're sitting all alone <br>And you need someone to come over <br>I would I would <br>If you're tired of talkin <br>You just feel like walkin <br>I would I would <br>If you wanna sit on the steps <br>I would I would <br>If you wanna see the solar eclipse <br>I would I would <br>If you wanna fall in love <br>Give me the code <br>I would I would <br>I would I would <br>I would I would <br>I would I would <br>I would I would <br>I would I would <br>I would I would]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="I Would" label="I Would"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Sliver_Of_The_Moon/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Sliver Of The Moon - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:59:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:59:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Sliver_Of_The_Moon/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Sliver Of The Moon - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Just a sliver of the moon <br>Just a wisp of a girl <br>A hint of perfume <br>In a tiny little world <br>Just a drop of spring <br>Just a favorite song <br>One I have to sing <br>I've fallen in love <br><br>The treetops quietly sign <br>The dewdrops turn to mist <br>Teardrops in her eyes <br>A quickly stolen kiss <br>A secret on the wind <br>And stars blinking above <br>I've done it once again <br>I've fallen in love <br>A secret on the wind <br>Stars blinking above <br>I've done it once again <br>I've fallen in love]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Sliver Of The Moon" label="Sliver Of The Moon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Tricks/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Tricks - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:59:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:59:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Tricks/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Tricks - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stinking up the curb lane baby <br>In the middle of the afternoon <br>I thought I saw somebody <br>On the street looked like you do <br>I jammed the brakes <br>I dipped the block <br>I swung in a circle around <br>By the time I got to where I thought I saw you <br>You were nowhere to be found <br><br>You're playing tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>You're playing tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>Now I see you now I don't <br>First you love me, then you won't <br><br>You're playing tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>You're playing tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>You're playing tricks on me <br><br>Tricks <br>It is always messy baby <br>And your dress is just a little undone <br>I think you're trying to drive me crazy <br>And I'm not the only one <br>My friends say I'm all you talk about <br>Whenever I leave this town <br>When I come back and search you out <br>You're no where around <br><br>You're playing tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>Now I see you now I don't <br>First you love me, and then you won't <br>You're playing tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>You're playing tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>You're playing tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>You're playing tricks on me <br>Tricks <br><br>Tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>Tricks <br>You're playing tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>You're playing tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>Tricks <br><br>Tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>You're playing tricks on me <br>You're playing tricks on me <br>You're playing tricks on me <br>Tricks on me <br>You're playing tricks on me <br>You're playing tricks on me]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Tricks" label="Tricks"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Careless/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Careless - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:59:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:59:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Careless/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Careless - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I think you're careless with my love <br>You forget how my heart breaks <br>I don't know what you're thinking of <br>Don't you remember how you love me <br><br>I think you're careless with my love <br>I'm like your favorite pair of pants <br>You bring me home and hang me up <br>You only take me out to dance <br><br>I think you're hard on my emotions <br>You take the push and make it shove <br>Throw away the magic potion <br>I think you're careless with my love <br><br>I think you're careless with my love <br>I'm like your favorite pair of pants <br><br>You bring me home and hang me up <br>You only take me out to dance <br><br>I think you're careless with my love <br>You forget how my heart breaks <br>I don't know what you're thinking of <br>I don't know what it's gonna take <br><br>I think you're careless with my love <br>I'm not the only star above <br>You wish upon it when you're lonely <br>I think you're careless with my love <br><br>I think you're careless with my love 4 xs]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Careless" label="Careless"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Attention_24/여행비둘기/</id><title>Attention_24 - 여행비둘기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:59:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:59:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Attention_24/%EC%97%AC%ED%96%89%EB%B9%84%EB%91%98%EA%B8%B0/" title="Attention_24 - 여행비둘기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사라져 가버린 <br>너의 기억 속에서 <br>잊혀져 가버린 <br>나의 기분을 알까 <br>모든 게 사라진 <br>너의 수많은 기억 <br>모든 걸 지워간 <br>나의 마음을 알까 <br>If I had to say good bye <br>When should I say good bye <br>If I had to say good bye <br>When should I <br>모든 걸 지워간 <br>너의 수많은 기억 <br>이제는 너에게 <br>나는 없는 것 같아 <br>그렇듯 모든 건 <br>끝이 정해져 있고 <br>이제는 나에게 <br>너도 없는 것 같아 <br>If I had to say good bye <br>When should I <br>라라라라라 <br>라라라라라 <br>라라라라라라라 <br>라라라라라 <br>라라라라라 <br>라라라라라라라 <br>라라라라라 <br>라라라라라 <br>라라라라라라라 <br>라라라라라 <br>라라라라라 <br>라라라라라라라 <br>빠르게 지나가버린 <br>우리의 모든 기억들 <br>이제는 점점 사라져 <br>빠르게 지나가버린 <br>우리의 모든 기억들 <br>이제는 점점 사라져 <br>빠르게 지나가버린 <br>우리의 모든 기억들 <br>]]></content><category term="Attention 24" label="Attention 24"/><category term="여행비둘기" label="여행비둘기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Attention_24/Can_You_Go_On__EP_Ver/</id><title>Attention_24 - Can You Go On? (EP Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:59:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:59:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Attention_24/Can_You_Go_On__EP_Ver/" title="Attention_24 - Can You Go On? (EP Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무 길 없는 숲 <br>답답한 내 가슴속 <br>아무도 손을 내밀지 않아 <br>더 이상은 포기할지도 몰라 <br>아무도 난 믿지 않아 <br>시작도 없고 <br>더 이상의 끝도 없어 <br>어디로 가야 할지를 몰라 <br>꿈이란 건 내가 살아갈 이유 <br>더 이상 포기하진 않아 <br>이 세상에 수많은 사람들 <br>내게 한 번만 물어봐 줄래 <br>하고 싶은 일 <br>내가 되고 싶은 것 <br>포기하지 마 <br>조금만 더 힘을 내 <br>오에오오 오에오오 <br>Are you ok Can you go on <br>오에오오 오에오오 <br>You are ok Keep going on <br>끝이 없는 길 <br>지금 네 앞에 열린 <br>문으로 들어갈 수 있겠니 <br>답도 없고 앞이 보이지 않아 <br>어디로 가야 할지를 몰라 <br>똑같은 생각 <br>모두 똑같은 표정으로는 <br>살아갈 순 없어 <br>하고 싶은 데로 <br>내가 가고 싶은 데로 <br>그러다 너무 힘들어도 난 <br>웃으며 살고 싶은 걸 Hey <br>오에오오 오에오오 <br>Are you ok Can you go on <br>오에오오 오에오오 <br>You are ok Keep going on <br>잡힐 듯 잡히지 않는 어둠 속에 <br>투명한 그림자 내게 다가오네 <br>아직도 난 불안하기만 한데 <br>오에오오 오에오오 <br>오에오오 오에오오 <br>오에오오 오에오오 <br>Are you ok Can you go on <br>오에오오 오에오오 <br>You are ok Keep going on <br>Keep going on <br>]]></content><category term="Attention 24" label="Attention 24"/><category term="Can You Go On? (EP Ver.)" label="Can You Go On? (EP Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Attention_24/In_Stereotype/</id><title>Attention_24 - In Stereotype - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:59:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:59:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Attention_24/In_Stereotype/" title="Attention_24 - In Stereotype - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세상이 변한대도 사람들은 지금 <br>어떤 변화도 원하지 않고 있어 <br>어느 순간 모두 그저 그렇게 <br>똑같은 길을 따라가고 있어 <br>네가 직접 본 것도 아닌데 왜 넌 또 <br>생각 없이 말하고 있어 <br>아무 생각 없는 너 나중엔 모른 척 <br>머릿속엔 변명뿐이지 <br>완전히 잘못됐어 <br>모두가 알고 있어 <br>어떻게 해야 할지도 <br>결과를 걱정하는 <br>두려운 마음에 넌 <br>거짓말로 널 위로해 <br>세상이 변한대도 사람들은 지금 <br>어떤 변화도 원하지 않고 있어 <br>어느 순간 모두 그저 그렇게 <br>똑같은 길을 따라가고 있어 <br>세상이 변한대도 사람들은 지금 <br>어떤 변화도 원하지 않고 있어 <br>어느 순간 모두 그저 그렇게 <br>똑같은 길을 따라가고 있어 <br>원하지 않고 있어 <br>원하지 않고 있어 <br>]]></content><category term="Attention 24" label="Attention 24"/><category term="In Stereotype" label="In Stereotype"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Attention_24/누구세요/</id><title>Attention_24 - 누구세요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:59:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:59:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Attention_24/%EB%88%84%EA%B5%AC%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94/" title="Attention_24 - 누구세요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한낮에도 여유로워 보여요 <br>밤늦게까지 놀기도 하구요 <br>언제나 택시만 타네요 <br>아무 근심 걱정 없나 봐요 <br>일어나는 시간이 매일 달라요 <br>아무 일 없이 집에 있기도 하구요 <br>목이 마르면 카페에 가네요 <br>정말 부족한 게 없나 봐요 <br>언제나 늘 웃는 얼굴에 <br>언제나 두둑한 지갑에 <br>나랑은 너무 다른 당신이 <br>누군지 정말 궁금하네요 <br>얼마든지 넉넉한 시간에 <br>오늘은 어딜 갈까 고민을 <br>하고 있는 당신을 보고 난 <br>신은 공평한가 생각하게 되네요 <br>월 화 수 목 금 토 일 모두 <br>아무 걱정 없이 즐거운 하루 <br>오늘은 뭐 하지라고 <br>생각하고 있는 당신은 <br>누구세요 누구세요 누구세요 <br>누구시길래 이러고 있죠 <br>누구세요 누구세요 누구세요 <br>나랑 같은 사람 아닌가 봐요 <br>월 화 수 목 금 토 일 모두 <br>아무 걱정 없이 즐거운 하루 <br>오늘은 뭐 하지라고 <br>생각하고 있는 당신은 <br>누구세요 누구세요 누구세요 <br>누구시길래 이러고 있죠 <br>누구세요 누구세요 <br>누구세요 누구세요 <br>누구세요 누구세요 누구세요 <br>누구시길래 이러고 있죠 <br>누구세요 누구세요 누구세요 <br>나랑 같은 사람 아닌가 봐요 <br>]]></content><category term="Attention 24" label="Attention 24"/><category term="누구세요" label="누구세요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Attention_24/비나_와버려라/</id><title>Attention_24 - 비나 와버려라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:59:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:59:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Attention_24/%EB%B9%84%EB%82%98_%EC%99%80%EB%B2%84%EB%A0%A4%EB%9D%BC/" title="Attention_24 - 비나 와버려라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한참을 기다렸어 꿈같은 오늘 <br>압구정 4번 출구 널 만나기로 해 <br>시간이 다 됐는데 연락도 안 와 <br>신경 좀 썼는데 나 바람맞았나 봐 <br>너에게 전화 와 돌아가는 내게 <br>택시를 돌려서 다시 약속 장소로 <br>3시간 기다렸어 연락도 안 와 <br>이대로 돌아갈 순 없어 <br>날씨가 좋은 거야 왜에에 <br>햇살은 따사로와 왜에에 <br>구름도 한 점 없고 왜에에 <br>오늘만 이런 거야 왜에에 <br>비나 와버려라 비나 비나 비나 <br>비나 와버려라 비나 비나 비나 <br>비나 와버려라 비나 비나 비나 <br>비나 와버려라 비나 비나 비나 <br>창밖에 연인들은 <br>오늘이 마지막인 것처럼 <br>서로를 보며 웃는데 <br>날씨가 좋은 거야 왜에에 <br>햇살은 따사로와 왜에에 <br>구름도 한 점 없고 왜에에 <br>오늘만 이런 거야 왜에에 <br>비나 와버려라 비나 비나 비나 <br>비나 와버려라 비나 비나 비나 <br>비나 와버려라 비나 비나 비나 <br>비나 와버려라 비나 비나 비나 <br>비나 와버려라 <br>비나 비나 비나 <br>]]></content><category term="Attention 24" label="Attention 24"/><category term="비나 와버려라" label="비나 와버려라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/The_Light_Brigade/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - The Light Brigade - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:59:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:59:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/The_Light_Brigade/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - The Light Brigade - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The first on the field <br>And the last one off <br>With a whiff of tobacco <br>And a soldiers cough <br>We stood our ground <br>When the rest of them ran <br>When our rifles were too hot <br>To hold in our hands <br><br>The Light Brigade <br>The Light Brigade <br>Through the smoke and the mud <br>With our blood we paid <br>The Light Brigade <br>The Light Brigade <br>We poured our powder <br>We stayed and we stayed <br>The Light Brigade <br><br>We trampled over <br>The wheat and the maize <br>And they wrapped our wounds <br>In grease and rags <br>We carried on through <br>The sun and the rain <br>We carried on through <br>The Light Brigade <br><br>I was a hero <br>When I got back here <br>They bought me whiskey <br>And they bought me beer <br>They put me on their shoulders <br>And they thanked me and they thanked me <br>Brother would you like to buy a book of matches]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="The Light Brigade" label="The Light Brigade"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Fancy_God/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Fancy God - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:59:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:59:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Fancy_God/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Fancy God - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[That God you got is a fancy God <br>And he's not the one I know <br>He don't live in parking lots <br>Outside of monster homes <br>My God ain't in the government <br>He don't put on a big show <br>That God you got is a fancy God <br>And he's not the one I know <br><br>My God lives on gravel roads <br>And goes down into hollers <br>Goes down and saves the souls <br>Of your very sons and daughters <br>Your crystal meth <br>And your cocaine breath <br>And your tingling to your toes <br>That God you got is a fancy God <br>And he's not the one I know]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Fancy God" label="Fancy God"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Tinderbox/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Tinderbox - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:59:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:59:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Tinderbox/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Tinderbox - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The church is like a tinderbox <br>The preachers got a match <br>Salvation is a raining down <br>And falling down the cracks <br>The choir master revved em up <br>And washed em white as snow <br>Somebody's crying in the very back row <br><br>The cemetery's sizzling <br>Out behind the fence <br>They're buttoning down the devil <br>Like Jesus with a wrench <br>The sisters are a twisting <br>And the men are singing low <br>Somebody's crying in the very back row <br><br>The elders and the deacons <br>Are dancing like a bar <br>The children are a screaming like they're <br>Trapped inside a car <br>The world's about to end, and everybody knows <br><br>Now the shadows are a stealing <br>Across the empty pews <br>The piano players sleeping <br>And the choir missed it's cue <br>The pentecost is simmering <br>The preachers going home <br>Somebody's crying in the very back row <br>Somebody's crying in the very back row <br>Somebody's crying in the very back row <br>Somebody's crying in the very back row <br>Somebody's crying in the very back row]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Tinderbox" label="Tinderbox"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Quietly/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Quietly - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T14:59:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T14:59:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Quietly/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Quietly - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Quietly <br>Her fair falls across her pillow <br>Quietly <br>She stirs in the morning light <br>Quietly she stares up at the ceiling <br>The she sits up <br>And she looks into my eyes <br><br>Quietly <br>She stares out of the window <br>She glances down <br>Into an empty street <br>Then she turns <br>And looks back at me again <br>And quietly <br>Her eyes fill up with tears <br>Then she brushes her lips <br>Across my hand <br>And stands up <br>And she walks across the floor <br>Then she stops <br>And looks back at me again <br>She picks up her things <br>And quietly she walks out the door <br><br>Quietly <br>I stare into the mirror <br>There's a man in there <br>I used to know <br>He's so tired <br>Of all of her sadness <br>And all of her tears <br>So quietly now I'll just let her go <br>So quietly now I'll just let her go]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Quietly" label="Quietly"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Chain_Gang/</id><title>Fred_Eaglesmith - Chain Gang - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:00:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:00:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_Eaglesmith/Chain_Gang/" title="Fred_Eaglesmith - Chain Gang - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Give me water <br>I need some shade <br>I've been out here <br>For days and days <br>Show me mercy <br>Call my name <br>I'm on the chain gang <br>The chain gang again <br><br>I'm on the chain gang <br>The chain gang of love <br>Her eyes are my prison <br>The walls are her touch <br>I try to run Lord <br>But I always give up <br>I'm on the chain gang <br>The chain gang of love <br><br>I looked up <br>Into her smile <br>Somebody said <br>15 to life <br>I looked down <br>I never raised my head <br>Indefinite term <br>Was all she said]]></content><category term="Fred Eaglesmith" label="Fred Eaglesmith"/><category term="Chain Gang" label="Chain Gang"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Monday_Feeling/So_Long_The_City_On_My_Mind/</id><title>The_Monday_Feeling - So Long, The City On My Mind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:00:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:00:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Monday_Feeling/So_Long_The_City_On_My_Mind/" title="The_Monday_Feeling - So Long, The City On My Mind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jessy is dancing on the roof <br>She looks so pretty <br>but she is naked <br>and her boyfriend is drinking vodka <br>from the bottle on daddy's SUV <br>When the night comes <br>they'll go to jail <br>Maybe She will think they look like <br>Bonnie and clyde <br>maybe no one will remember <br>who they are <br>Oh So long my old good friends <br>Johnny is driving to his home <br>he doesn't have a license <br>and He looks so nervous <br>because he's drunk <br>But jessy is pushing him <br>to go fast <br>while Shouting Baby <br>Faster <br>When the night comes <br>they'll go to jail <br>Maybe He will think <br>they look like Bonnie and clyde <br>maybe no one will remember <br>who they are <br>Oh So long my old good friends <br>When the night comes <br>they'll go to jail <br>Maybe they will think <br>they look like Bonnie and clyde <br>but I know nobody will remember <br>who they are <br>Oh So long my old good friends <br>]]></content><category term="The Monday Feeling" label="The Monday Feeling"/><category term="So Long, The City On My Mind" label="So Long, The City On My Mind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Monday_Feeling/Midnight_Blues/</id><title>The_Monday_Feeling - Midnight Blues - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:00:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:00:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Monday_Feeling/Midnight_Blues/" title="The_Monday_Feeling - Midnight Blues - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Where are you going <br>Too late too go out <br>Now I don't know <br>what to say no more <br>You know I can't stop you <br>my girl <br>While lying on our bed <br>I'm just watching that <br>you're getting free <br>I'm covered in your shadow <br>Let me know how I get through <br>When the morning comes <br>I hope I can see you <br>as always <br>as always <br>as always <br>Where are you going <br>Too Late to go out <br>Now I don't know <br>what to do no more <br>I'm getting used to <br>my girl <br>While lying on his bed <br>Maybe You'll think that <br>you are getting free <br>I'm covered in your shadow <br>Let me know how I get through <br>When the morning comes <br>I hope I can see you <br>as always <br>as always <br>as always <br>I'm covered in your shadow <br>Let me know how I get through <br>When the morning comes <br>I hope I can see you <br>as always <br>as always <br>as always <br>Where are you going <br>Too Late to go out <br>But i'm just watching that <br>you're getting free <br>]]></content><category term="The Monday Feeling" label="The Monday Feeling"/><category term="Midnight Blues" label="Midnight Blues"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Monday_Feeling/Song_For_Us/</id><title>The_Monday_Feeling - Song For Us - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:01:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:01:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Monday_Feeling/Song_For_Us/" title="The_Monday_Feeling - Song For Us - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm chasing after your soul <br>I can see the trace <br>but it's blurred like my eyes <br>I'm trying to find my way <br>in the dark <br>Definetely <br>There's a shadow of you <br>From a distance <br>I'm just crawling-as you see <br>you got me down on <br>my knees and took my <br>everything I've got <br>I wanna wake up <br>from this nightmare <br>oh please don't tell me <br>that it's my destiny <br>oh please don't tell me <br>that it's my destiny <br>oh please don't tell me <br>that it's my destiny <br>oh please don't tell me <br>that it's my destiny <br>I can feel the breath of <br>you and me <br>So freezing but it makes me <br>feel i'm alive <br>All the thing we made is <br>crashing down <br>Do you hear that sound <br>Oh I think it's the end <br>From a distance <br>I'm just crawling-as you see <br>you got me down on <br>my knees and took my <br>everything I've got <br>I wanna wake up <br>from this nightmare <br>oh please don't tell me <br>that it's my destiny <br>oh please don't tell me <br>that it's my destiny <br>oh please don't tell me <br>that it's my destiny <br>oh please don't tell me <br>that it's my destiny <br>]]></content><category term="The Monday Feeling" label="The Monday Feeling"/><category term="Song For Us" label="Song For Us"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Monday_Feeling/The_Signs_Of_Dawn/</id><title>The_Monday_Feeling - The Signs Of Dawn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:01:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:01:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Monday_Feeling/The_Signs_Of_Dawn/" title="The_Monday_Feeling - The Signs Of Dawn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Shining lights <br>Footsteps of Somebody <br>Now He's walking <br>on the empty highway <br>He doesn't have a watch <br>He forgot when the sun has gone <br>He doesn't remember <br>how to go back <br>The man from the past <br>The man from the memory <br>oh those were his names <br>but now they're meaningless <br>Oh the signs of dawn <br>Now he senses <br>the signals of the morning <br>Oh the signs of dawn <br>And that makes him find his way <br>When he got out of his home <br>there were a number of choices <br>for the next day <br>But he thought don't matter <br>which way I choose <br>cuz this is not for the beginning <br>but the end <br>The man from the past <br>but now that's nothing to him <br>Oh the signs of dawn <br>Now he senses the signals <br>of the morning <br>Oh the signs of dawn <br>And that makes him find his way <br>Oh the signs of dawn <br>Now he senses the signals <br>of the morning <br>Oh the signs of dawn <br>And that makes him find his way <br>]]></content><category term="The Monday Feeling" label="The Monday Feeling"/><category term="The Signs Of Dawn" label="The Signs Of Dawn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Monday_Feeling/Open/</id><title>The_Monday_Feeling - Open - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:01:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:01:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Monday_Feeling/Open/" title="The_Monday_Feeling - Open - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lately You might not have seen <br>the blue shiny sky <br>The sun is eclipsed <br>because nobody wants <br>to feel the day <br>And every night <br>I see the falling of the stars <br>I think that's a <br>curtain call for all of us <br>Hey yeah Open your eyes <br>Open your mouth <br>Shout anything what you want <br>and feel you're alive <br>Hey yeah Open your eyes <br>Open your mind <br>and get ready for the final <br>moment of our generation <br>Your life is always bound to the rules <br>you made yourself <br>How dose it feel I know that drives <br>you almost insane <br>Standing on the Corner <br>We think too much day by day <br>There's enough time for Change <br>We cannot live forever <br>Hey yeah Open your eyes <br>Open your mouth <br>Shout anything what you want <br>and feel you're alive <br>Hey yeah Open your eyes <br>Open your mind <br>and get ready for the final <br>moment of our generation <br>We’ll see the real world <br>We’ll see the real world <br>We’ll see the real world <br>We’ll see the real world <br>let's get into the real world <br>let's get into the real world <br>let's get into the real world <br>let's get into the real world <br>Hey yeah Open your eyes <br>Open your mouth <br>Shout anything what you want <br>and feel you're alive <br>Hey yeah Open your eyes <br>Open your mind <br>and get ready for the final <br>moment of our generation <br>]]></content><category term="The Monday Feeling" label="The Monday Feeling"/><category term="Open" label="Open"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DinoT_다이노티/I_Own_It_Feat_스킬레토/</id><title>DinoT_다이노티 - I Own It (Feat. 스킬레토) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:01:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:01:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DinoT_%EB%8B%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8%ED%8B%B0/I_Own_It_Feat_%EC%8A%A4%ED%82%AC%EB%A0%88%ED%86%A0/" title="DinoT_다이노티 - I Own It (Feat. 스킬레토) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[i own it i own it <br>난 원해 박근혜의 지위 <br>또 곽한구의 외제차까지 <br>i own it i own it <br>난 원해 호킹의 휠체어와 <br>킬러조의 배짱까지도 <br>i own it all 원하는 <br>모든 걸 내 안에 품어 <br>원하는 모든 걸 <br>니 품안에서 뺏어 <br>i own it i own it <br>So don't fuck with my groove <br>우린 뻗어나가 우주 <br>난 다 가질거야 맹세해 <br>Pray to ma god <br>자신에게 신에게 <br>걸어왔지 가시밭길 <br>피나게 차까진 아니어도 <br>Im already FILA Gang <br>허나 아직 만족은 안해 <br>이게 완전 안 하다면 <br>난 반쪽은 안해 <br>난 꽉 잡아 너네 <br>숨 막혀 할 때 <br>선두자리 놓지않아 <br>imma 숨마쿰라우데 <br>일년 반 만에 <br>이쯤에 위치해 <br>불만족으로 이룸에도 <br>빛나지 내 이름이 <br>No matter what you said <br>I don't give a shit <br>난 내년이 기다려지지 <br>병신년은 내꺼야 <br>I'll be in this bitch <br>만들거야 make it rain <br>make it rain <br>비가 더 내리게 내리게 <br>텅빈 내 통장에 공짜로 <br>0짜가 생기게 생기게 <br>네개 다섯개 여섯개 <br>일곱개 여덟개 아홉개 <br>아빠는 포르셰몰고 <br>난 여의도 꼭대기로 이사해 <br>도끼네 옆집에 <br>천육백짜리 마이크로 벙개쏭 <br>영광의 순간은 바로 지금 강백호 <br>실패는 성공의 어머니 <br>애미없이 잘 나갈거야 <br>I'll fuckin’ own it bitch <br>i own it i own it <br>난 원해 박근혜의 지위 <br>또 곽한구의 외제차까지 <br>i own it i own it <br>난 원해 호킹의 휠체어와 <br>킬러조의 배짱까지도 <br>i own it all 원하는 <br>모든 걸 내 안에 품어 <br>원하는 모든 걸 <br>니 품안에서 뺏어 <br>i own it i own it <br>So don't fuck with my groove <br>우린 뻗어나가 우주 <br>i own it all hell mo’fucker <br>다이노티와 스킬레토는 <br>긁지않은 복권 <br>승률 100퍼센트 <br>승자가 정해진 포커 <br>미리미리 빨아 삐리뽕 <br>내 asshole choco <br>난 랩 깡패 비트위에다 <br>엙 칵 퉤 <br>튀기는 침들이 음악이 되어 <br>니 고막을 다 take it <br>진짜들은 진짜끼리 <br>다 알아서 알아보네 <br>난 악역을 추종해 알카포네 <br>대부호 저장해 너네폰에 <br>니 허세와 구라에 거품 낀 <br>인지도 좋아요 엄지도 <br>니들이 올린 질투섞인 중지도 <br>중지를 가리는 18k 반지도 <br>한가지도 남김없이 가지고 <br>난 지독히 뿜어내 간지로 <br>내 실력이 부러움 <br>자지를 말던가 <br>개쩌는 모습을 <br>보지를 말던가 <br>ill take your money <br>빨리 토껴 멀리 <br>도끼형 money까지 <br>머리 꼭대기부터 <br>발 끝까지 내가 원하는걸로 <br>싹 갖다 붙일라니까 <br>난 한다면 하는 불도져 <br>타고난 리듬이 온 몸에 도져 <br>도저히 못 말려 내 도전 <br>결과는 대성해서 <br>T o p 두개의 태양이 돼 <br>비정상적인 우리 <br>육감으로 승리까지 <br>own it Hello win day <br>이 곡은 우리 목표의 시발점 <br>씨 발아 시키는 거름 <br>걸음걸음 버는거를 지켜봐 <br>원하는건 all i own it <br>i own it i own it <br>난 원해 박근혜의 지위 <br>또 곽한구의 외제차까지 <br>i own it i own it <br>난 원해 호킹의 휠체어와 <br>킬러조의 배짱까지도 <br>i own it all 원하는 <br>모든 걸 내 안에 품어 <br>원하는 모든 걸 <br>니 품안에서 뺏어 <br>i own it i own it <br>So don't fuck with my groove <br>우린 뻗어나가 우주 <br>]]></content><category term="Dino.T (다이노티)" label="Dino.T (다이노티)"/><category term="I Own It (Feat. 스킬레토)" label="I Own It (Feat. 스킬레토)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DinoT_다이노티/Survibe/</id><title>DinoT_다이노티 - Survibe - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:01:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:01:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DinoT_%EB%8B%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8%ED%8B%B0/Survibe/" title="DinoT_다이노티 - Survibe - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[started from the bottom <br>빽도 없는 놈이 <br>그저 살기위해 <br>빽 발악을 해 <br>때 껴 버린 행복속에 <br>뺏긴 아비 원수를 <br>신이란놈께 돌려 <br>take it all ya fuckin’ fake <br>man Amen Jesus <br>Im done 할만큼 했어 <br>기도 가끔은 모친과 <br>조모의 손이 닳까봐 울기도 <br>그 기돌 깨끗이 <br>씹어버린 이들을 위해서 <br>내 가사가 돼는 냉소 <br>역한 비웃음소리 위에서 <br>자아 안에서의 불신과 <br>불건전한 심신 <br>내게 신신당부하는 <br>식솔들의 현실들에 실실대는 <br>hater와의 십시일반을 꿈꿔대며 <br>쉰 쉼으로 지은 시는 <br>신들은 당연 싫지 <br>Im Dino.T 내 무기는 <br>vocal producing and Rap <br>이 무기가 살아남으려 <br>용쓰는 날카론 이빨이 돼 <br>천국 믿지않아 <br>극락도 사치 씨발 웩 <br>Ill survive through me <br>날믿어 나는 fuck 할렐루야 <br>survive in ma vibe <br>i just survive in da fire <br>im so tough and a wild <br>and so on <br>살아남아 난 꼭 Ay <br>survive in ma vibe <br>i just survive in da fire <br>im so tough and a wild <br>and so on <br>차원이 다른 래퍼 <br>rough and tough <br>survive in ma vibe <br>survive in ma vibe <br>survive in ma vibe <br>and so on <br>바닥에 깔릴바에 <br>알아서 기어가 Hell Fire <br>represent Ilsan city <br>난 꽃의도시 <br>고양을 대표해서 <br>랩 실력마저 고양돼 <br>보장된 이 동네 보약 man <br>i gotta 거물 대물 title <br>대를 이을 내 재물의 제물인 <br>퇴물들을 홍대서 섭취 <br>꽤 기대돼는 내 거취 <br>Look at me 제 페이스를 <br>찾아 밟고 tasty 나를 맛봐 <br>페이스북 인스타에 <br>날 쳐봐 face도 존나 준수 <br>실력이 Y고 성장이 X면 <br>화살표는 2시방향을 찔러 <br>챔프형이 내게 가라사대 <br>발음 존나좋다고 <br>일부러 좀 씹으래 <br>첨 시작하는 내게 <br>중지를 냈던 애들은 <br>내 뒷구멍 찾아서 와 <br>무대밑에서 날 보면서 와 <br>존나 잘한다를 연발해 <br>홍콩 느와르 주윤발 <br>총알이 알아서 비껴가지 <br>니 중지도 마찬가지 엿빨어 <br>인상쓰는 애들 면상 <br>웃게해줬지 조커 <br>show &amp; prove 일단 봐 <br>중지가 엄지로 돼 무조건 <br>J Q K A 10 승자가 정해진 포커 <br>넌 내일을 살지 <br>난 오늘을 살아 <br>survive 이 아저씨가 말야 <br>survive in ma vibe <br>i just survive in da fire <br>im so tough and a wild <br>and so on <br>살아남아 난 꼭 Ay <br>survive in ma vibe <br>i just survive in da fire <br>im so tough and a wild <br>and so on <br>차원이 다른 래퍼 <br>rough and tough <br>survive in ma vibe <br>survive in ma vibe <br>survive in ma vibe <br>and so on <br>바닥에 깔릴바에 <br>알아서 기어가 Hell Fire <br>우글대는 좀비들을 봐 <br>계속 늘어가는 좀비들의 밭 <br>설 자리를 잃은 청중들의 발 <br>그들과 같아질바에 <br>내 입에 방아쇠를 당겨 <br>우글대는 좀비들을 봐 <br>계속 늘어가는 좀비들의 밭 <br>설 자리를 잃은 청중들의 발 <br>그들과 같아질바에 <br>내 입에 방아쇠를 당겨 <br>survive in ma vibe <br>i just survive in da fire <br>im so tough and a wild <br>and so on <br>살아남아 난 꼭 Ay <br>survive in ma vibe <br>i just survive in da fire <br>im so tough and a wild <br>and so on <br>차원이 다른 래퍼 <br>rough and tough <br>survive in ma vibe <br>survive in ma vibe <br>survive in ma vibe <br>and so on <br>바닥에 깔릴바에 <br>알아서 기어가 Hell Fire <br>]]></content><category term="Dino.T (다이노티)" label="Dino.T (다이노티)"/><category term="Survibe" label="Survibe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/그레이준/Wish_You/</id><title>그레이준 - Wish You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:02:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:02:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EC%A4%80/Wish_You/" title="그레이준 - Wish You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 바쁜 하루 속에 <br>어제와 다른 만남을 <br>꿈꾸며 지금 여기서 <br>너와의 그 희망을 이어가 <br>Wish You <br>바보처럼 아무 말 없이 <br>하염없이 하늘만 바라보다 <br>어제와 같은 시간을 <br>맴돌며 또 나 혼자 꿈꾸며 <br>I wish a I wish a <br>I wish a close to you <br>I wish a I wish a <br>I wish a you song for you <br>I wish a I wish a <br>I wish a telling you <br>I wish a I wish a <br>I wish you lean on me <br>Wish You <br>이제는 나와 함께 걸어가 <br>어떤 어려움을 마주쳐도 <br>항상 네 옆에 있으며 <br>너와 나 같은 꿈을 꾸며 <br>걱정하지마 슬퍼하지마 <br>뒤돌아보지마 후회하지마 <br>같은 길을 함께 걸어가며 <br>I wish a I wish a <br>I wish a close to you <br>I wish a I wish a <br>I wish a you song for you <br>I wish a I wish a <br>I wish a telling you <br>I wish a I wish a <br>I wish you always with me <br>Wish You <br>]]></content><category term="그레이준" label="그레이준"/><category term="Wish You" label="Wish You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ChocolatD_쇼콜라디/당분간은_밤이_길어지겠네/</id><title>ChocolatD_쇼콜라디 - 당분간은 밤이 길어지겠네 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:02:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:02:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ChocolatD_%EC%87%BC%EC%BD%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%94%94/%EB%8B%B9%EB%B6%84%EA%B0%84%EC%9D%80_%EB%B0%A4%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B8%B8%EC%96%B4%EC%A7%80%EA%B2%A0%EB%84%A4/" title="ChocolatD_쇼콜라디 - 당분간은 밤이 길어지겠네 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어제까지 길었던 낮이가고 <br>허우룩한 맘에 불을 밝혀도 <br>길어진 옷들이 <br>나를 감싸 안아도 <br>당분간 밤이 길어지겠네 <br>매일 걷던 익숙한 이 거리가 <br>한순간 다른곳 같다면 <br>마치 길을 잃은 아이처럼 <br>얼어붙어 가만히 멈춰서있네 <br>이 밤 허전히 <br>긴 밤 외로히 <br>내 맘 서운히 <br>지낼 수 밖에 없을까 <br>오늘 같은 따스한 날이 가면 <br>당분간 밤이 길어지겠네 <br>매일 보던 따스한 저 하늘이 <br>한순간 다른곳같다면 <br>마치 엄말 잃은 아이 처럼 <br>얼어붙어 멍하니 멈춰서있네 <br>이 밤 허전히 <br>긴 밤 외로히 <br>내 맘 서운히 <br>지낼 수 밖에 없을까 <br>오늘 같은 따스한 날이 가면 <br>당분간 밤이 길어지겠네 <br>당분간 밤이 길어지겠네 <br>당분간 밤이 길어지겠네 <br>]]></content><category term="Chocolat.D (쇼콜라디)" label="Chocolat.D (쇼콜라디)"/><category term="당분간은 밤이 길어지겠네" label="당분간은 밤이 길어지겠네"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최영우/새벽거리/</id><title>최영우 - 새벽거리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:03:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:03:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%98%81%EC%9A%B0/%EC%83%88%EB%B2%BD%EA%B1%B0%EB%A6%AC/" title="최영우 - 새벽거리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[무대가 끝난뒤 <br>거리에 나와보니 <br>화려한 불빛은 <br>하나둘 꺼져가네 <br>거리엔 여전히 <br>비틀거리는 사람들 <br>그들도 하나둘 <br>거리를 떠나가네 <br>가만히 이길을 걷다보니 <br>차가운 새벽바람만 멀리서 <br>스치듯 들려오는 차소리 <br>고요한 곳을 찾아 <br>한없이 헤매다 <br>그러다 문득 <br>마주친 사람들 <br>그들도 여전히 <br>이길을 걷고 있네 <br>가만히 이길을 걷다보니 <br>차가운 새벽바람만 멀리서 <br>스치듯 들려오는 차소리 <br>고요한 곳을 찾아 <br>한없이 헤매다 <br>그러다 문득 <br>마주친 사람들 <br>그들도 여전히 <br>이길을 걷고 있네 <br>그들도 외로이 <br>이길을 걷고 있네 <br>]]></content><category term="최영우" label="최영우"/><category term="새벽거리" label="새벽거리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/야운/석가모니불/</id><title>야운 - 석가모니불 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:03:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:03:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%84%9D%EA%B0%80%EB%AA%A8%EB%8B%88%EB%B6%88/" title="야운 - 석가모니불 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나무 영산불멸 <br>학수쌍존 시아본사 <br>석가모니불 석가모니불 <br>석가모니불 석가모니불 <br>석가모니불 석가모니불 <br>석가모니불 석가모니불 <br>석가모니불 석가모니불 <br>천상천하무여불 <br>시방세계역무비 <br>세간소유아진견 <br>일체무유여불자 <br>고아일심 귀명정례 <br>석가모니불 <br>]]></content><category term="야운" label="야운"/><category term="석가모니불" label="석가모니불"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/야운/오늘은_좋은날/</id><title>야운 - 오늘은 좋은날 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:03:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:03:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98%EC%9D%80_%EC%A2%8B%EC%9D%80%EB%82%A0/" title="야운 - 오늘은 좋은날 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Are you Ready for this HA <br>행복이 찾아오는날 <br>온갖 꽃들이 피어나는 날 <br>오늘은 기분 좋은 날 <br>바로 부처님 오신날 <br>소중한 날 <br>파란하늘을 자유롭게 <br>날아갈듯한 기분으로 <br>난 노래하며 살아가리 <br>Forever <br>오늘은 좋은 날 <br>부처님 오신 날 <br>온갖 꽃 피어나는 <br>만생명 축복의 날 <br>오늘은 기쁜 날 <br>님께서 오신 날 <br>별 담은 새벽 이슬 <br>연꽃이 피는 날 <br>한줄기 찬란한 <br>햇살이 눈부셔 <br>온세상 빛이 되어 <br>노래하리 <br>오늘은 좋은 날 <br>부처님 오신 날 <br>진리의 함성이 <br>온누리 퍼지네 <br>Let me breakdown Baby <br>쿵쾅거리는 내 심장이 <br>터질것 같이 기쁘다 <br>부처님 오신날이다 <br>연꽃이 피어나 <br>우리 마음을 <br>따뜻하게 비춰줘 <br>모두 하나가 되어 친구들 <br>노래하리 박자에 맞춰 <br>원 투 쓰리 포 <br>Let's GO <br>오늘은 기쁜 날 <br>님께서 오신 날 <br>별 담은 새벽 이슬 <br>연꽃이 피는 날 <br>한줄기 찬란한 <br>햇살이 눈부셔 <br>온세상 빛이 되어 <br>노래하리 <br>오늘은 좋은 날 <br>부처님 오신 날 <br>진리의 함성이 <br>온누리 퍼지네 <br>환희의 노래로 <br>온누리 퍼지네 <br>]]></content><category term="야운" label="야운"/><category term="오늘은 좋은날" label="오늘은 좋은날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/야운/다비식/</id><title>야운 - 다비식 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:03:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:03:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EB%8B%A4%EB%B9%84%EC%8B%9D/" title="야운 - 다비식 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잘가세요 잘가세요 <br>나무아미타불 <br>감사합니다 감사합니다 <br>나무아미타불 <br>하얀 연기가 되어 <br>이제 바람의 노래를 <br>떠나네 떠나네 <br>이제 간다네 <br>부처님께 간다네 <br>새도 울고 나도 울고 <br>흐르는 눈물 모두 <br>자꾸 떠오르는 얼굴 <br>이제 해탈의 노래를 <br>저 멀리 저 멀리 <br>더 먼곳으로 가요 <br>자유롭게 떠나요 <br>떠나요 떠나요 <br>극락세계로 <br>부처님 나라로 <br>하얀 연기가 되어 <br>이제 바람의 노래를 <br>떠나네 떠나네 <br>이제 간다네 <br>부처님께 간다네 <br>새도 울고 나도 울고 <br>흐르는 눈물 모두 <br>자꾸 떠오르는 얼굴 <br>이제 해탈의 노래를 <br>저 멀리 저 멀리 <br>더 먼곳으로 가요 <br>자유롭게 떠나요 <br>떠나요 떠나요 <br>극락세계로 <br>부처님 나라로 <br>잘가세요 잘가세요 <br>나무아미타불 <br>감사합니다 감사합니다 <br>나무아미타불 <br>잘가세요 잘가세요 <br>나무아미타불 <br>감사합니다 감사합니다 <br>나무아미타불 <br>잘가세요 잘가세요 <br>나무아미타불 <br>감사합니다 감사합니다 <br>다음 생에 만나요 <br>]]></content><category term="야운" label="야운"/><category term="다비식" label="다비식"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/야운/이곳이_극락이네/</id><title>야운 - 이곳이 극락이네 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:03:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:03:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%9D%B4%EA%B3%B3%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B7%B9%EB%9D%BD%EC%9D%B4%EB%84%A4/" title="야운 - 이곳이 극락이네 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이곳이 극락이네 <br>내가 서있는 길 <br>우리함께 미소짓는 <br>오늘이 극락이네 <br>하루 하루 힘들어도 <br>부처님 품안에서 <br>우리 모두 정진하면 <br>극락이라네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>내가 서있는 길 <br>우리함께 미소짓는 <br>오늘이 극락이네 <br>하루 하루 힘들어도 <br>부처님 품안에서 <br>우리 모두 정진하면 <br>극락이라네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>이곳이 극락이네 <br>]]></content><category term="야운" label="야운"/><category term="이곳이 극락이네" label="이곳이 극락이네"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/야운/지심귀명례/</id><title>야운 - 지심귀명례 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:03:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:03:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%A7%80%EC%8B%AC%EA%B7%80%EB%AA%85%EB%A1%80/" title="야운 - 지심귀명례 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지심귀명례 지심귀명례 <br>지심귀명례 지심귀명례 <br>한줄기향 사르오며 <br>귀의합니다 <br>지성다해 드리우는 <br>이 마음을 받으소서 <br>계향 정향 혜향 <br>해탈향 해탈지견향 <br>계향 정향 혜향 <br>해탈향 해탈지견향 <br>하염없는 자비한맘 <br>끊임없이 펼치시며 <br>걸림없는 눈빛으로 <br>온세상을 살피시니 <br>우리의 온갖 소원 이루리라 <br>사바하 사바하 사바하 <br>세상 티끌 씻어내니 깨끗해라 <br>사바하 사바하 사바하 <br>지심귀명례 지심귀명례 <br>지심귀명례 지심귀명례 <br>맑은향 사르오며 <br>귀의합니다 <br>지성다해 드리우는 <br>이 정성을 받으소서 <br>계향 정향 혜향 <br>해탈향 해탈지견향 <br>계향 정향 혜향 <br>해탈향 해탈지견향 <br>몸과 마음 향이되어 <br>재가 되고 사라져도 <br>해탈세계 향하는 <br>이 신심 변함없으니 <br>향 연기 두루퍼져 <br>길상이어라 <br>사바하 사바하 사바하 <br>한결같은 마음이여 <br>길상이어라 <br>사바하 사바하 사바하 <br>]]></content><category term="야운" label="야운"/><category term="지심귀명례" label="지심귀명례"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/야운/향불을_올리고/</id><title>야운 - 향불을 올리고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:03:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:03:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%BC%EC%9A%B4/%ED%96%A5%EB%B6%88%EC%9D%84_%EC%98%AC%EB%A6%AC%EA%B3%A0/" title="야운 - 향불을 올리고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[간절히 간절히 부처님께 <br>향불을 올리고 <br>소중한 소중한 마음담아 <br>기도를 올리네 <br>그동안그 동안 숨겨놓은 <br>내 안의 근심들 <br>쉽없이 쉽없이 한숨쉬던 <br>모든 업장 태우네 <br>향내가 나를 어루만지듯 <br>좌복에 앉아 합장을 하고 <br>부처님을 물끄러미 바라보니 <br>눈가에 고이는건 환희심인가 <br>간절히 간절히 부처님께 <br>향불을 올리고 <br>소중한 소중한 마음담아 <br>기도를 올리네 <br>그동안 그동안 숨겨놓은 <br>내 안의 근심들 <br>쉽없이 쉽없이 한숨쉬던 <br>모든 업장 태우네 <br>향내가 나를 어루만지듯 <br>좌복에 앉아 합장을 하고 <br>부처님을 물끄러미 바라보니 <br>눈가에 고이는건 환희심인가 <br>간절히 간절히 부처님께 <br>향불을 올리고 <br>소중한 소중한 마음담아 <br>기도를 올리네 <br>]]></content><category term="야운" label="야운"/><category term="향불을 올리고" label="향불을 올리고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/야운/반야심경/</id><title>야운 - 반야심경 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:03:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:03:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EB%B0%98%EC%95%BC%EC%8B%AC%EA%B2%BD/" title="야운 - 반야심경 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마하반야 바라밀다심경 <br>관자재보살 행심반야 바라밀다 <br>시 조견오온개공도 <br>일체고액 사리자 <br>색불이공 공불이색 <br>색즉시공 공즉시색 <br>수상행식 역부여시 사리자 시 <br>제법공상 불생불멸 불구부정 <br>부증불감 시고 공중무색 <br>무수상행식 무안이비설신의 <br>무색성향미촉법 <br>무안계 내지 무의식계 무무명 <br>역무무명진 내지 <br>무노사 역무노사진 <br>무고집멸도 무지역무득 <br>이무소득고 보리살타 <br>의반야바라밀다고 심무가애 <br>무가애고 무유공포 <br>원리전도몽상 <br>구경열반 삼세제불 <br>의반야바라밀다 <br>고득아뇩다라삼먁삼보리 <br>고지반야바라밀다 <br>시대신주 시대명주 <br>시무상주 시무등등주 <br>능제일체고 진실불허 <br>고설 반야 바라밀다주 즉설주왈 <br>아제 아제 바라아제 <br>바라승아제 모지 사바하 <br>아제 아제 바라아제 <br>바라승아제 모지 사바하 <br>아제 아제 바라아제 <br>바라승아제 모지 사바하 <br>오온이 공한것을 비추어보면 <br>일체 괴로움이 없어지니 <br>물질과 공이 다르지 않고 <br>공과 물질이 다르지 않아 <br>눈 귀 코 혀는 <br>의식도 없고 뜻도 없고 <br>빛 소리 향기는 감촉과 법도 없고 <br>더럽지도 않고 <br>깨끗하지도 않아 <br>늘지도 않고 줄지도않네 <br>나지도 않고 없어지지도 않아 <br>과거 현재 미래 모든 것중 <br>가장 신비한 주문이며 <br>가장 밝은 주문이며 <br>가장 높은 주문이다 <br>반야심경 <br>아제 아제 바라아제 <br>바라승아제 모지 사바하 <br>아제 아제 바라아제 <br>바라승아제 모지 사바하 <br>아제 아제 바라아제 <br>바라승아제 모지 사바하 <br>아제 아제 바라아제 <br>바라승아제 모지 사바하 <br>]]></content><category term="야운" label="야운"/><category term="반야심경" label="반야심경"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/야운/연꽃처럼/</id><title>야운 - 연꽃처럼 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:03:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:03:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%97%B0%EA%BD%83%EC%B2%98%EB%9F%BC/" title="야운 - 연꽃처럼 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[연꽃처럼 연꽃처럼 연꽃처럼 <br>우 연꽃처럼 <br>그대 힘든일이 있나요 <br>그대 아픈 마음이 보여요 <br>지금 이순간은 비우고 <br>모든 마음을 내려놔요 <br>하루하루 부처님에게 <br>모든 근심을 털어놓아요 <br>나의 마음의 무거움을 <br>바람처럼 날려 버려요 <br>연꽃처럼 연꽃처럼 연꽃처럼 <br>우 연꽃처럼 <br>연꽃처럼 연꽃처럼 연꽃처럼 <br>우 연꽃처럼 <br>하루하루 부처님에게 <br>모든 근심을 털어놓아요 <br>나의 마음의 무거움을 <br>바람처럼 날려 버려요 <br>번뇌 속의 그 연꽃처럼 <br>세파 속에 그 연꽃처럼 <br>당신을 닮은 연꽃처럼 <br>염화미소를 지어봐요 <br>연꽃처럼 연꽃처럼 연꽃처럼 <br>우 연꽃처럼 <br>]]></content><category term="야운" label="야운"/><category term="연꽃처럼" label="연꽃처럼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/야운/참회/</id><title>야운 - 참회 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:03:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:03:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%B0%B8%ED%9A%8C/" title="야운 - 참회 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[참회합니다 참회합니다 <br>내업이네 내업이네 <br>이모든것 내업이네 <br>고통 고통의 시간 <br>슬픔 슬픔의 기억 <br>내것이네 내것이네 <br>이모든것 내것이네 <br>옴살바 못자모지 사다야 사바하 <br>옴살바 못자모지 사다야 사바하 <br>고통 고통의 시간 <br>슬픔 슬픔의 기억 <br>내것이네 내것이네 <br>이모든것 내것이네 <br>옴살바 못자모지 사다야 사바하 <br>옴살바 못자모지 사다야 사바하 <br>]]></content><category term="야운" label="야운"/><category term="참회" label="참회"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/야운/태우고_태워도/</id><title>야운 - 태우고 태워도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:03:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:03:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%BC%EC%9A%B4/%ED%83%9C%EC%9A%B0%EA%B3%A0_%ED%83%9C%EC%9B%8C%EB%8F%84/" title="야운 - 태우고 태워도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[태우고 태우고 또 태워도 <br>내 번뇌는 가시질 않고 <br>참고 또 참아도 내 마음은 <br>한 여름 뜨거운 태양처럼 <br>얼마나 더 더워야하나 <br>얼마나 많이 울어야하나 <br>내가 무슨 욕심을 부렸던가 <br>나 이제 방법을 모르겠네 <br>얼마나 더 참아야 하나 <br>얼마나 더 견뎌야 하나 <br>불심은 대체 무엇일까 <br>나 이젠 대답이 필요하네 <br>얼마나 더 더워야하나 <br>얼마나 많이 울어야하나 <br>내가 무슨 욕심을 부렸던가 <br>나 이제 방법을 모르겠네 <br>태우고 태우고 또 태워도 <br>내 번뇌는 가시질 않고 <br>참고 또 참아도 내 마음은 <br>한 여름 뜨거운 태양처럼 <br>한 여름 뜨거운 태양처럼 <br>한 여름 뜨거운 태양처럼 <br>]]></content><category term="야운" label="야운"/><category term="태우고 태워도" label="태우고 태워도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Azure_Sea_아주르씨/나침반_Feat_심경화_Remastered_Ver/</id><title>Azure_Sea_아주르씨 - 나침반 (Feat. 심경화) (Remastered Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:04:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:04:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Azure_Sea_%EC%95%84%EC%A3%BC%EB%A5%B4%EC%94%A8/%EB%82%98%EC%B9%A8%EB%B0%98_Feat_%EC%8B%AC%EA%B2%BD%ED%99%94_Remastered_Ver/" title="Azure_Sea_아주르씨 - 나침반 (Feat. 심경화) (Remastered Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[무얼 따라 어디로 가는지 <br>무얼 찾아서 떠났나 <br>저기 저 구름들도 <br>그저 흘러가 <br>버리고 마는데 <br>스쳐가던 사람들 말하네 <br>나를 위해서 살라고 <br>다들 제 갈길 따라 <br>그저 바쁘게 <br>떠나가고 만다고 <br>난 그 동안 <br>누굴 위해 살았나 <br>어디로 가는지 <br>나도 알 수가 없는데 <br>고장 난 나침반처럼 <br>길을 잃어 버렸네 <br>흔들리는 바늘 따라 <br>나도 흔들리고 있네 <br>가리키는 데로만 <br>살아가고 있었네 <br>흔들리는 바늘 따라 <br>나도 흔들리고 있네 <br>가리키는 데로만 <br>살아가고 있었네 <br>흔들리고 있었네 <br>왜 그리도 살았나 <br>누굴 위해 살았나 <br>그대로만 이젠 그만 <br>스쳐가던 사람들 말하네 <br>나를 위해서 살아가라고 <br>나를 위해서 살아가라고 <br>]]></content><category term="Azure Sea (아주르씨)" label="Azure Sea (아주르씨)"/><category term="나침반 (Feat. 심경화) (Remastered Ver.)" label="나침반 (Feat. 심경화) (Remastered Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/심경화/기차_안에서_Remastered_Ver/</id><title>심경화 - 기차 안에서 (Remastered Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:04:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:04:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%AC%EA%B2%BD%ED%99%94/%EA%B8%B0%EC%B0%A8_%EC%95%88%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C_Remastered_Ver/" title="심경화 - 기차 안에서 (Remastered Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어느새 쌀쌀해진 바람 <br>창 밖으로 지나가는 <br>가을의 풍경들을 <br>차곡차곡 담아내 <br>마시멜로우 밭을 지나 <br>노랗고 붉은 나무들 <br>구름도 없이 파란 하늘 아래 <br>달리는 기차 한 대 <br>그 안의 나 <br>물결처럼 일렁이는 전깃줄 <br>잔잔했던 풍경 안에 <br>내가 두고 온 것들이 <br>자꾸만 눈에 밟혀도 <br>마시멜로우 밭을 지나 <br>노랗고 붉은 나무들 <br>구름도 없이 파란 하늘 아래 <br>달리는 기차 한 대 <br>그 안의 나 <br>푸르게 일렁이는 강을 건너 <br>도시의 숲 속 나무들 <br>구름도 없이 파란 하늘 아래 <br>멈춰서는 기차 한 대 <br>그 안의 나 <br>푸르게 일렁이는 강을 건너 <br>도시의 숲 속 나무들 <br>구름도 없이 파란 하늘 아래 <br>멈춰서는 기차 한 대 <br>그 안의 나 <br>]]></content><category term="심경화" label="심경화"/><category term="기차 안에서 (Remastered Ver.)" label="기차 안에서 (Remastered Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최경식/안개_Feat_심경화_Remastered_Ver/</id><title>최경식 - 안개 (Feat. 심경화) (Remastered Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:04:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:04:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EA%B2%BD%EC%8B%9D/%EC%95%88%EA%B0%9C_Feat_%EC%8B%AC%EA%B2%BD%ED%99%94_Remastered_Ver/" title="최경식 - 안개 (Feat. 심경화) (Remastered Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흐린 오후에 멍하니 걷다 <br>문득 떠오른 너의 모습이 <br>눈을 조금씩 가려 와 <br>보이지 않는 흰 바람처럼 <br>점점 더 내게 가까워지다 <br>바람에 맴도는 생각들이 <br>머물지 못하다 <br>서서히 멀어져 가 <br>조용히 <br>짙게 핀 안개 속 웃음소리가 <br>떨리듯 춤추며 흩어져간다 <br>바람에 맴도는 생각들이 <br>머물지 못하다 <br>서서히 멀어져 가 <br>조용히 <br>흐릿한 말들 속에 <br>흐릿한 말들 속에 <br>점점 더 빛을 잃어 <br>잡으려 아무리 애를 써도 <br>소리 내 불러도 <br>무의미한 말들뿐 <br>바람에 맴돌던 생각들도 <br>버티지 못하다 <br>다시 또 잦아들어 <br>조용히 <br>]]></content><category term="최경식" label="최경식"/><category term="안개 (Feat. 심경화) (Remastered Ver.)" label="안개 (Feat. 심경화) (Remastered Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송보람/우리빛_Remastered_Ver/</id><title>송보람 - 우리,빛 (Remastered Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:04:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:04:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EB%B3%B4%EB%9E%8C/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%B9%9B_Remastered_Ver/" title="송보람 - 우리,빛 (Remastered Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[부서진 햇살 그 안의 너는 <br>우리 기억을 모여들게 해 <br>익숙한 바람 그 안의 너는 <br>우리 노래를 새롭게 해 <br>흔들리는 풀잎들과 <br>춤추는 그대를 보면 <br>어둠 속 떠다닌 <br>내 상처를 다 잊게 해 <br>살아있는 바로 지금 <br>이 순간을 가득 채운 <br>그대를 닮은 빛들은 <br>떠오르는 우릴 비추네 <br>흔들리는 풀잎들과 <br>춤추는 그대를 보면 <br>어둠 속 떠다닌 <br>내 상처를 다 잊게 해 <br>살아있는 바로 지금 <br>이 순간을 가득 채운 <br>그대를 닮은 빛들은 <br>떠오르는 우릴 비추네 <br>]]></content><category term="송보람" label="송보람"/><category term="우리,빛 (Remastered Ver.)" label="우리,빛 (Remastered Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/8th_Floor/바라보다/</id><title>8th_Floor - 바라보다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:04:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:04:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/8th_Floor/%EB%B0%94%EB%9D%BC%EB%B3%B4%EB%8B%A4/" title="8th_Floor - 바라보다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흩날리는 가지 사이 <br>혼자 남은 풍선 하나 아 너일까 <br>언제나 내게 웃어주던 그 모습이 <br>자꾸만 생각나 이제 와서 <br>다가오던 네 모습 <br>받아줄 수 없었던 <br>너무나도 작았던 내 마음 <br>차갑던 너의 상처 <br>안아줄 수 없었던 <br>너무도 날카롭던 내 두 손 <br>햇살이 비치는 거리 <br>어느새 멀어지는 걸음 <br>아 현실일까 <br>조금 더 빠르게 뛰어봐도 <br>다시 또 내게서 <br>멀어지는 환상일까 <br>따스한 너의 온기 <br>애써 외면했었지 <br>내 마음을 외롭게 가둔 채로 <br>멍하니 주저앉아 <br>그저 바라보겠지 <br>누군가 다가와도 모른 채로 <br>바람이 불어와 <br>날려보낼 수 있다면 <br>잡아도 잡히지 않는 먼지처럼 <br>흐르는 강물에 <br>떠나 보낼 수 있다면 <br>손 틈새로 빠져나가는 <br>비처럼 너를 <br>다가오던 네 모습 <br>받아줄 수 없었던 <br>너무나도 작았던 내 마음 <br>차갑던 너의 상처 <br>안아줄 수 없었던 <br>너무도 날카롭던 내 두 손 <br>]]></content><category term="8th Floor" label="8th Floor"/><category term="바라보다" label="바라보다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/8th_Floor/새벽/</id><title>8th_Floor - 새벽 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:04:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:04:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/8th_Floor/%EC%83%88%EB%B2%BD/" title="8th_Floor - 새벽 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지친 생각을 가둘 곳 없어 <br>낯선 마음 한 구석에 몰아넣네 <br>허황된 위로에 귀는 무뎌지고 <br>달콤한 독설만이 나를 감아 <br>진실이 거짓인지 <br>거짓이 진실인지 <br>알 수 없는 궤도 속에서 <br>들키지 않으려 <br>더 깊이 감추려 애를 쓰다 <br>새벽이 밝아온다 <br>진실이 거짓인지 <br>거짓이 진실인지 <br>알 수 없는 궤도 속에서 <br>들키지 않으려 <br>더 깊이 감추려 애를 쓰다 <br>새벽이 밝아온다 <br>긴 밤의 꼬리에 오갈 데 없이 <br>춤추던 낯선 그림자들이 <br>저물어 가는 달빛에 <br>조금씩 부서진다 <br>긴 밤의 꼬리에 오갈 데 없이 <br>춤추던 낯선 그림자들 <br>]]></content><category term="8th Floor" label="8th Floor"/><category term="새벽" label="새벽"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/현진주/거울을_깨고/</id><title>현진주 - 거울을 깨고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:04:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:04:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%98%84%EC%A7%84%EC%A3%BC/%EA%B1%B0%EC%9A%B8%EC%9D%84_%EA%B9%A8%EA%B3%A0/" title="현진주 - 거울을 깨고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[손에 있는 고장 난 시계 <br>바라본 내 기억속의 <br>거울이 말해주네요 <br>You are You are You are <br>작은 거울 안에 갇혔던 소녀 <br>바래온 순간을 이제는 <br>더 높게 더 멀리 그렇게 <br>우아 우아 우아하게 <br>많은 사람 속에 한걸음 <br>이 시간 이렇게 이제 난 <br>Time to let you go <br>내 앞에 놓인 거울을 깨고 <br>꿈꿨던 내 세상을 <br>이 장면 속에 그대로 담아 <br>멈췄던 내 시간을 <br>심장소리에 맞춰 <br>Shine like a shooting star <br>절대 멈추지 마 <br>잠시만 눈을 감고 문을 향해서 <br>가면을 벗고 두드려 <br>찾아온 나를 나를 외면하지 마 <br>Turn Back <br>You are You are You are <br>작은 거울 안에 갇혔던 소녀 <br>바래온 순간을 이제는 <br>더 높게 더 멀리 그렇게 <br>우아 우아 우아하게 <br>많은 사람 속에 한걸음 <br>이 시간 이렇게 이제 난 <br>Time to let you go <br>내 앞에 놓인 거울을 깨고 <br>꿈꿨던 내 세상을 <br>이 장면속에 그대로 담아 <br>멈췄던 내 시간을 <br>심장소리에 맞춰 <br>Shine like a shooting star <br>절대 멈추지 마 <br>내 앞에 놓인 거울을 깨고 <br>꿈꿨던 내 세상을 <br>이 장면 속에 그대로 담아 <br>멈췄던 내 시간을 <br>심장소리에 맞춰 <br>Shine like a shooting star <br>절대 멈추지 마 <br>]]></content><category term="현진주" label="현진주"/><category term="거울을 깨고" label="거울을 깨고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Why/Feel_Me_Now/</id><title>Why - Feel Me Now - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:05:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:05:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Why/Feel_Me_Now/" title="Why - Feel Me Now - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너만보고 걸어가 <br>아무도 날 못막아 <br>눈이 마주친 순간에 <br>boom boom party time <br>까다로운 내눈에 꽃힌 <br>slender body 못참아 <br>그래 너야 모르는척 하지마 <br>너도 날 원하고 있잖아 oh <br>I want you baby <br>I need you baby ah <br>너만 보이잖아 <br>Oh Ah feel you baby <br>Ah feel me baby baby baby <br>Search that beauty <br>scan the body ooh <br>나 들어가 Feel me now <br>거울을 슥 훑어봐 <br>뭘 입어도 테가나 <br>이정도면 나 어디가도 <br>woo woo yeah <br>그래도 니앞에만 서면 <br>dowdy boy but uh <br>Doo doo doo doo doo doo <br>그래 너야 모르는척 하지마 <br>너도 날 원하고 있잖아 oh <br>I want you baby <br>I need you baby ah <br>너만 보이잖아 <br>Oh Ah feel you baby Ah <br>feel me baby baby baby <br>Search that beauty <br>scan the body ooh <br>나 들어가 Feel me now <br>이게뭐야 홀린것 같아 <br>자꾸만 더 흐려지는 focus <br>can't stop me now <br>널 안을수 있을것만 같아 <br>tonight <br>자꾸 날 미치게 만들어 oh <br>I want you baby <br>I need you baby ah <br>너만 보이잖아 <br>oh I feel you baby ah <br>feel me baby baby baby <br>Search that beauty <br>scan the body ooh <br>나 들어가 Feel me now oh <br>Search that beauty <br>scan the body <br>Feel me now oh <br>나 들어가 Feel me now <br>]]></content><category term="Why" label="Why"/><category term="Feel Me Now" label="Feel Me Now"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sik-K_식케이/RING_RING_Feat_개코/</id><title>Sik-K_식케이 - RING RING (Feat. 개코) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:05:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:05:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sik-K_%EC%8B%9D%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4/RING_RING_Feat_%EA%B0%9C%EC%BD%94/" title="Sik-K_식케이 - RING RING (Feat. 개코) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Woogie on and on <br>May I hit you up <br>in late night yeah yeah <br>만약에 네 생각이 난다면 <br>전화할꺼니깐 그냥 받어 <br>내가 많은 여자들이랑 <br>만나고 다니지는 않았지만 <br>다른 여자들은 <br>아마도 밥맛이야 <br>심장은 뛰어서 <br>너한테 더 가까이가 <br>now I'm at the studio <br>makin songs <br>about you and me <br>It's lit <br>keep callin' your phone <br>ring ring ring ring <br>ring ring ring <br>네가 만약 네가 나라면 <br>나는 나를 잡아뒀어 <br>딱 하나 하나 말하면 <br>널 만나면서 난 달라졌어 <br>May I hit you up <br>in late night yeah yeah <br>만약에 네 생각이 난다면 <br>전화할꺼니깐 그냥 받어 <br>ring ring ring ring <br>ring ring <br>Can I hit you up <br>ring ring ring ring <br>ring ring <br>Can I hit you up <br>네가 만약 내게 억지로 <br>맞춰주는게 아니라면 <br>우린 먼가 통하는게 <br>많이 있는 것 같아 <br>침대에 던져둔 전화에 <br>신경 곤두 세우느라 <br>매일 밤 선잠 <br>날 알고난 다음 <br>유도제 없으면 힘든거 알아 <br>네가 보고싶고 <br>너도 내게 오고싶고 <br>나 센척하지만 권력을 <br>네게 양도하고싶어 <br>너의 수저는 변덕이 심해 <br>소금간 미원간 <br>넌 금수저를 제일 <br>좋아라해 허나 <br>그저 디퓨져 같아 <br>그의 터보차 안에 <br>오늘 나랑 진짜 <br>소셜 네트워크 해 <br>빨리 카택 불러서와 <br>너를 원해 <br>지금 전화 연결중이야 쩜쩜쩜 <br>립글로스만 입술에 <br>쩜쩜쩜 바르고나와 <br>May I hit you up <br>in late night yeah yeah <br>만약에 네 생각이 난다면 <br>전화할꺼니깐 그냥 받어 <br>ring ring ring ring <br>ring ring <br>Can I hit you up <br>ring ring ring ring <br>ring ring <br>Can I hit you up <br>In day time <br>I need you in my place <br>In late night <br>I need you in my place <br>네가 필요해 지금 내 곁에 <br>나는 정말 네가 필요해 <br>지금 내 옆에 <br>지금 네 폰이 울고 있잖아 <br>why don't you pick it up right now <br>May I hit you up <br>in late night yeah yeah <br>만약에 네 생각이 난다면 <br>전화할꺼니깐 그냥 받어 <br>ring ring ring ring <br>ring ring <br>Can I hit you up <br>ring ring ring ring <br>ring ring <br>Can I hit you up <br>]]></content><category term="Sik-K (식케이)" label="Sik-K (식케이)"/><category term="RING RING (Feat. 개코)" label="RING RING (Feat. 개코)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제이핏_J_Fit/Trap_Card/</id><title>제이핏_J_Fit - Trap Card - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:09:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:09:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%ED%95%8F_J_Fit/Trap_Card/" title="제이핏_J_Fit - Trap Card - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 laid back shit <br>누가 못해 요즘 trap flow <br>다 ASAP이지 <br>성공하려한대 rap으로 <br>이쁜 박자를 choice해 <br>여긴 마치 Ten pro <br>100% 불보듯 뻔해 <br>이번에도 copy cat으로 <br>예왼없어 내 성공처럼 <br>확정됐지 니 박자놀이 <br>Rap star들을 보고 <br>키워냈던 너의 상상력이 <br>무너지는 순간 뭐 <br>여기까지도 잘한거지 <br>난 깨나 이기적이여서 <br>니가 상처받던 상관없지 <br>근데 또 사실 <br>형이 맘이 약해 <br>정말이야 이런 swag해도 <br>Peace and one love을 외쳐 <br>넌 더 여기에 서서 rap해줘 <br>은 는 fake다 이 병신아 <br>농담이고 봐 발 밑 <br>You just activated <br>my trap card Die bitch <br>yeah this is trap card <br>함정 카드 발동 했어 <br>인마 손들어 <br>uh this is trap card <br>함정 카드 발동 했어 <br>인마 손들어 <br>yeah this is trap card <br>함정 카드 발동 했어 <br>인마 손들어 <br>uh this is trap card <br>함정 카드 발동 했어 <br>인마 손들어 <br>roll the dice no <br>운 안 바라지 <br>보이는 모습보다도 냉정해 <br>꽤나 i'm cold as ice <br>올해도 여름은 오지만 <br>여기 놀음은 빙판 <br>이 노래가 <br>나의 trap card <br>방심하다 죄다 자빠졌지 uh <br>저기 문제 많은 rapper들 listen <br>여기엔 없지 정지버튼 <br>같은건 내 음악은 <br>계속해서 돌아가는 roof <br>형태를 그려 <br>널 빠져들게하지 <br>마치 이건 함정과도 <br>같은 너의 꿈 <br>난 늘 하던대로 하기 때문에 <br>뭐라 지껄이던간에 <br>내게 문제따윈 없어 <br>기다려왔지 내게 <br>총구를 겨누기를 <br>난 위아래를 다 엎어 <br>니 뒤를 치기 위한 <br>준비 충분히 되있으니 다 덤벼 <br>그럼 곧 일어날 사건에 <br>범인은 내가 되겠지 <br>피는 더 번져 <br>yeah this is trap card <br>함정 카드 발동 했어 <br>인마 손들어 <br>uh this is trap card <br>함정 카드 발동 했어 <br>인마 손들어 <br>yeah this is trap card <br>함정 카드 발동 했어 <br>인마 손들어 <br>uh this is trap card <br>함정 카드 발동 했어 <br>인마 손들어 <br>this is trap card <br>위협적이지 Jack knife <br>같이 숨겨뒀던 날을 세워 <br>쑤셔넣지 내 생각들을 <br>그러곤 rise to fame <br>몇몇들에겐 개의치 <br>않겠지만 너넨 <br>이미 걸려들었어 <br>여기 belzebute의 game에 <br>Taming했지 계집같은 <br>cutie rappers 전부 샘내 <br>내가 안된다고 했던 <br>놈들의 말 Curse of Pele <br>무시하고 더 밟아줘 <br>쌓인 mileage가 <br>이제 막터졌지 분수 <br>근데 감흥없지 <br>난 bitch같이 ha <br>인마 다 올려 tension <br>뒤엎을 준빈 됐어 <br>masterpiece만을 뱉어 낼게 <br>진짜 달라지는 level <br>So 다음 stage를 대령해 <br>너무 좁아 우리가 날뛰기엔 <br>이제 역사를 만들 시간 <br>Mark hunt와 Ray sefo <br>Mark hunt와 Ray sefo <br>우린 전 세계를 울릴 echo <br>Belzebuth 준비는 됐고 <br>이 앨범 곡들은 <br>이 다음편의 예고 <br>이 다음편의 예고 <br>이 다음편의 예고 <br>이 다음편의 예고 <br>Belzebuth we on <br>]]></content><category term="제이핏 (J Fit)" label="제이핏 (J Fit)"/><category term="Trap Card" label="Trap Card"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제이핏_J_Fit/Call_My_Name/</id><title>제이핏_J_Fit - Call My Name - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:09:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:09:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%ED%95%8F_J_Fit/Call_My_Name/" title="제이핏_J_Fit - Call My Name - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[call ma name 첫번째는 <br>J FIT가 나고 houzz형이 <br>내게 건낸 제의 <br>재미있어 보여 <br>노력했던 모습을 오려 <br>붙여 도형같이 <br>곧 튀어나올듯한 내 그림의 표현 <br>좀 더 잘 보렴 난 mrparagon <br>내 태도는 21년전 <br>뱃속 태동에서부터 계속 <br>발버둥 쳤지 빠져나가기 위해 <br>멋진 삶을 살고싶어 <br>내게 걸어 기댈 <br>이제 더 나를 알려 <br>이건 신호탄 또는 <br>제야의 종 내 새시대를 알려 <br>달려 왔다가 찾은 쉼터는 <br>내게 여유가됐고 <br>무대 위 내 모습에 <br>몇몇은 점점 정신 팔려 <br>곧 내 공연을 보고 다수가 날 hashtag해 <br>facebook 담벼락엔 <br>내 글들이 쏟아지겠네 <br>달콤한 그 꽃향기에 <br>더 날아 난 나비같애 <br>갈수록 힘이 넘쳐 <br>꿈이란 목표 그 박진감에 <br>hey 내게 돌을 던져 <br>댔던 어른들은 이제 <br>내 주위엔 없어 <br>현실이라던 설정에 <br>혁신을 적어냈어 이 메모장에 <br>이제 넌 내 이름을 외쳐 call my name <br>call my name call my name J Fit <br>call my name call my name J Fit <br>call my name call my name J Fit <br>call my name call my name <br>mother fucker <br>call my name call my name <br>mother fucker <br>call my name call my name <br>mother fucker <br>call my name call my name <br>call my name J Fit <br>몇년 전의 나는 절망했지 왜 <br>공부가 전부고 결과랬지 생각 <br>보다 더 엿같았던 사회 <br>과학자 꿈을 때려치고 <br>1년간의 사춘기 기간 <br>기대의 뒷통수를 치고 <br>뒤로 쳐져가는 느낌 <br>느끼게 될쯤에 <br>물에 잠수라도 하듯 <br>깊은 생각 속에 빠져들게 <br>되고 일찍이 철들어 버린 아이 <br>그 후 음악과의 만남 <br>아직까지 난 기억하지 <br>yeah 나 혼자 어두운 방에 섞여 <br>귀를 덮은 해드셋이 주는 <br>공간속에 몸을 던져 <br>멈춘듯한 시간 속에서 <br>날 알리기 위해 뱉어 이 공간안에 <br>이제 넌 내 이름을 외쳐 call my name <br>call my name call my name J Fit <br>call my name call my name J Fit <br>call my name call my name J Fit <br>call my name call my name <br>mother fucker <br>call my name call my name <br>mother fucker <br>call my name call my name <br>mother fucker <br>call my name call my name <br>call my name J Fit <br>call my name J Fit <br>call my name J Fit <br>call my name J Fit <br>call my name J Fit <br>]]></content><category term="제이핏 (J Fit)" label="제이핏 (J Fit)"/><category term="Call My Name" label="Call My Name"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제이핏_J_Fit/빨간줄_Red_Line/</id><title>제이핏_J_Fit - 빨간줄 (Red Line) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:09:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:09:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%ED%95%8F_J_Fit/%EB%B9%A8%EA%B0%84%EC%A4%84_Red_Line/" title="제이핏_J_Fit - 빨간줄 (Red Line) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[yeah a move 니 몸을 붕 뜨게 <br>사로잡어 니 마음 가슴 <br>기분 들뜨게 wake up crowd <br>wake up crowd yeah 그리고 bounce <br>move the crowd 니들 맘을 뺏는 범죄 <br>이건 그어 red line yeah <br>we are Belzebuth came <br>from the fuckin' hell <br>add red line in my fuckin' profile ay <br>add red line in my fuckin' profile ay <br>add red line in my fuckin' profile ay <br>red line 죄의 대가지 <br>but no dead line 내겐 행사지 <br>이 siren 소리에 상기된 <br>내 피부 톤이 검은 <br>몸을 집어 삼킬때 <br>무대 위에서 뺏어 너의 심장 마치 <br>이건 still heart 하지만 <br>그년 떠나지 않지 아직 <br>찰칵이는 소릴내는 <br>저들 손 위 셔터 <br>카메란 내게 윙클하지 장전 하듯 <br>계속 들리는 sound <br>저기 저 렌즈속에 찍힌내 사진 <br>내 잔상같은 존재가되고 <br>현상수배같이 <br>어딘가에 기재가 돼 <br>근데 난 전혀 후회 않지 <br>곧 나의 시대가 돼 <br>세상은 아직 미개하지 <br>그래 내 empire가 돼 <br>내 생각 이것들을 <br>낙서하듯 엉망진창으로 전부 <br>여기 나열해봐 기억 나는대로 <br>내 꿈에 불효라며 <br>그어졌던 새빨간선이 <br>이젠 붉은 실처럼 보여 <br>결국 내게 이건 <br>운명이였다는 거지 <br>yeah a move 니 몸을 붕 뜨게 <br>사로잡어 니 마음 가슴 <br>기분 들뜨게 wake up crowd <br>wake up crowd yeah 그리고 bounce <br>move the crowd 니들 맘을 뺏는 범죄 <br>이건 그어 red line yeah <br>we are Belzebuth came <br>from the fuckin' hell <br>add red line in my fuckin' profile ay <br>add red line in my fuckin' profile ay <br>add red line in my fuckin' profile ay <br>정신이 몽롱해 약을 빤 것 처럼 <br>they call me 미친새끼 <br>괜찮아 다 살려뒀어 <br>고맙거든 니들 덕에 내가 rap해 <br>발버둥쳐 계속해서 <br>일어나줘 잡초처럼 <br>Yeah I feel like I'm charles manson <br>Uh 조금씩 잘라야 더 아프겠군 <br>극도의 쾌감 강자만이 <br>먹이 사슬의 끝 <br>위에서 느낄 수 있지 <br>이 감정 너도 담 생에는 <br>이빨은 달고 태어나야지 좀 닿겠군 <br>어차피 상대는 안 돼 <br>난 아무거나 막 깨물어 <br>불구가 되겠지 <br>전의를 상실한 초점 huh <br>애써 아닌 척 해봐도 <br>내 눈에 다 보여 <br>이미 뽀려냈지 절도범 <br>니 팔짱을 성공적으로 풀어 <br>자물쇠 따듯 살인 rap을 보고서 uh <br>여기 목격자들 <br>수도 없이 붙겠지 이제 <br>내 montage가 여기저기 붙을테니 shit <br>yeah a move 니 몸을 붕 뜨게 <br>사로잡어 니 마음 가슴 <br>기분 들뜨게 wake up crowd <br>wake up crowd yeah 그리고 bounce <br>move the crowd 니들 맘을 뺏는 범죄 <br>이건 그어 red line yeah <br>we are Belzebuth came <br>from the fuckin' hell <br>add red line in my fuckin' profile ay <br>add red line in my fuckin' profile ay <br>add red line in my fuckin' profile ay <br>ay belzebuth <br>광견 &amp; J Fit <br>Houzz의 killn' beat <br>rap이 흉기라면 이미 너네 다 뒤졌지 <br>we out <br>]]></content><category term="제이핏 (J Fit)" label="제이핏 (J Fit)"/><category term="빨간줄 (Red Line)" label="빨간줄 (Red Line)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제이핏_J_Fit/Flashlight_발광/</id><title>제이핏_J_Fit - Flashlight (발광) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:09:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:09:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%ED%95%8F_J_Fit/Flashlight_%EB%B0%9C%EA%B4%91/" title="제이핏_J_Fit - Flashlight (발광) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[참 오래도 기다렸지 <br>애무는 이제 끝났어 <br>지금 이 땅의 흐름 <br>쳇바퀴의 중간 정도 <br>난 확신해 바뀌네 <br>반복적 무간도의 <br>내 혀를 집어 넣고 끊어 <br>절대 없어 문답형 <br>Flash light I got a <br>Flash light <br>Flash light I got a <br>Flash light <br>Flash light I got a <br>Flash light <br>Flash light I got a <br>Flash light <br>찰져 내 땜핑 <br>못 감당해 우주안에 <br>있는 어떤 소음도 <br>이 암캐들의 고음도 <br>난 성량 깡패지 <br>누구처럼 수줍게 안해 <br>알면서 뭘 쳐물어 <br>딥빡처럼 소금 쳐뿌려 <br>니 면전에다 대놓고 <br>침을 투 하고 뱉어 <br>니 새끼가 하는게 <br>Hip hop이라니 error <br>내 상스러운 표현법은 <br>살아있음을 느끼게 해 <br>난 붓 대신 혀를 털며 <br>색칠해 이 그림 위에 <br>잘 봐라 인마 <br>난 감각부터가 달라 <br>애초부터 성립 안돼 Battle <br>날 무시하던 <br>거지 새끼들은 어디 <br>Self로 다 주둥이를 채웠네 <br>네 네 안녕하십네까 <br>이런 rap해요 새로 <br>왔어요 이번에 <br>가수로 지원했는데 <br>박수로 환영해주세요 <br>형들 저 맘에 안들죠 <br>미안해 발광이 <br>주체가 안되네여 <br>알아서 피해가 <br>홍해를 가르듯이 이건 뭐 <br>열려라 참깨 네여 <br>지금 이 순간부터 <br>너의 자아는 너가 <br>좆밥임을 알게돼여 <br>반말 했다 안했다 <br>꼴리는대로 막 해 <br>봤지 난 미친개 <br>상태에여 Ah <br>Flash light I got a <br>Flash light <br>Flash light I got a <br>Flash light <br>Flash light I got a <br>Flash light <br>Flash light I got a <br>Flash light <br>한꺼번에 덤벼 다 <br>감질나 삼켜 한방에 <br>Houzz형 씨발 총 좀 여 <br>장전 발사 <br>뒤져 다 너와 내가 <br>무슨 발전을 도모해 <br>쓸 데 없이 왜 <br>체력을 소모해 <br>안 들려 반사 <br>탁상공론 같은 소리하네 <br>중2병 걸린 혁명가 <br>꼬마 새끼가 기껏 뱉은 말은 <br>instant보다 영양가가 없지 <br>유식한 척 하는 <br>사자성어 껍데기 <br>꼰대를 욕하지만 사실 <br>자기가 그 꼰대인지도 <br>모른체 신념을 주입 <br>시키지 어린 애들한테 <br>그걸 듣는 애기들의 <br>초점을 강탈해 <br>다 개구라인데 <br>지 고집을 팔뚝에 tatoo해 <br>사는 대로 적힌 대로 rap을 한대 <br>애들은 몰라 <br>내 인지도가 걔보다 <br>작아서 샘을 한대 <br>이런 개 같은 언플이 <br>한국 Hip hop의 <br>현 주소인게 너무 신이나 <br>이 정도 수준은 돼 줘야지 <br>가사의 소재들이 막 생기지 ha <br>내가 할말도 없이 <br>rap하는 너랑 똑같지 않아 <br>두 눈 뜨고 봐 인마 <br>이빨만 까는 걔를 <br>내가 부러워 해 <br>좆까지 마라 <br>]]></content><category term="제이핏 (J Fit)" label="제이핏 (J Fit)"/><category term="Flashlight (발광)" label="Flashlight (발광)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제이핏_J_Fit/Heavent：Belzebuth_Feat_Trigga/</id><title>제이핏_J_Fit - Heaven`t：Belzebuth (Feat. Trigga) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:09:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:09:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%ED%95%8F_J_Fit/Heavent%EF%BC%9ABelzebuth_Feat_Trigga/" title="제이핏_J_Fit - Heaven`t：Belzebuth (Feat. Trigga) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ay belzebuth J to the FIT <br>yeah that's my name <br>ay ay 예전의 기분으로 <br>내 꿈과 매일을 <br>받치며 즐겼던 때처럼 <br>음악이란건 역시 볼매야 <br>느껴져 중3때 느꼈던 feel이 <br>뭐에 그리 목 매달았었는지 <br>돈을 쫒아왔던게 아닌걸 알어 <br>그저 뱉어댔던 음절에 <br>빠져버려서 해왔었단 것 <br>무덤 속의 존재인듯이 <br>잠시 잊었었나봐 <br>불시에 내 퍼즐이 엇나갔던건 <br>끝이 안보여 지쳤었나봐 <br>무기가된 내 music <br>난 dream chaser <br>돈이야 번다면 좋지 <br>but 그에 취해서 <br>벌기위함만 따라간다면 때려쳐 <br>fuckin' money code <br>창작의 싸움 이건 <br>놈들을 뒤엎을 곡을 <br>챙겨 왔지 <br>물론 내껄 가지고서 <br>채워왔지 <br>내 technology <br>내 형들 사이에서 <br>배워왔지 덕에 <br>현재의 내 mind rhythm <br>flow와 rhyme 들이 전부 다 <br>생겨났지 감사함을 전해 <br>날 보여줄때 됐어 <br>목표는 세워놨지 <br>we got no money no fan <br>but 더 멀리 더 높게 가 <br>우린 정신없이 등엔 총매 <br>무게추 같은 현실 따위에도 <br>no panic <br>no panic 우린 다른 level ay <br>no panic 우린 다른 level ay <br>no panic 우린 다른 level ay <br>no panic 우린 다른 level ay <br>개 천박하고 개 느려 <br>간지터지게 <br>내 가사 하나 하나 <br>전부 귀에 꽂히게 <br>걔는 때려박지 못해 <br>절대 남자답지 못해 <br>달려있는 버섯떼고 <br>달아줄게 조개 bitch <br>상구형의 말처럼 비겁하구만 <br>사실 그럴것도 없지 <br>돈을 원하는게 아니니깐 <br>근데 이거 하나 알아줬음해 형 <br>어디가서 Hip hop한다 <br>씨부리지마 huh <br>난 음악가기 이전에 <br>microphone checker <br>이건 중요해 난 음악을 <br>팔지않아 니 mic를 뺏어 <br>공감을 구걸 할거라면 <br>난 애초에 안 했어 <br>웃겨 Kendrick을 respect 한단 <br>니 병신같은 swagger <br>뭔가 크게 잘 못 돌아가 <br>나 이대론 못 돌아가 <br>다 돌았나봐 빙글빙글 <br>어지러워 세상 돌아가는 <br>꼴이 아주 빙글빙글 <br>김연아 빙신같지 <br>정치판을 운운하는 <br>그 주둥이는 참 치밀하지 huh <br>we got no money no fan <br>but 더 멀리 더 높게 가 <br>우린 정신없이 등엔 총매 <br>무게추 같은 현실 따위에도 <br>no panic <br>no panic 우린 다른 level ay <br>no panic 우린 다른 level ay <br>no panic 우린 다른 level ay <br>no panic 우린 다른 level ay <br>bless on me <br>2pac in my soul <br>1 프로도 관심없어 <br>얻어걸린 인기와 돈 <br>그건 쟤네 league <br>이건 특수 강력 절도 flow uh <br>trill till i die <br>이게 날 알리는 법 <br>여긴 빈수레들만 넘쳐 <br>늘 하는것만 보이는 법 <br>소신 없이 늘 대세타면 <br>다 낼름 내밀지 혀를 <br>내게 등 돌린 성공을 <br>난 기회라고 불러 <br>걔도 마음에 드는 눈치지 <br>look i'm the fuckin' manual <br>yeah i'm make something new <br>항상 기록 갱신 <br>또 항상 i'm doin' great <br>넌 잠깐 시끄런 매미 <br>boy that's my time <br>yeah that's my time <br>매분 매시 매일 매주 항상 <br>난 꿈을 이뤄가지 ho <br>니넨 잃어가지만 <br>어떤 상황이 닥쳐도 <br>난 닥치고 있지 않아 <br>yeah i proove boy i'm back <br>pretty boy show me twerk <br>여기 받어 곰인형 <br>인마 다 어림없어 bro <br>we got no money no fan <br>but 더 멀리 더 높게 가 <br>우린 정신없이 등엔 총매 <br>무게추 같은 현실 따위에도 <br>no panic <br>no panic 우린 다른 level ay <br>no panic 우린 다른 level ay <br>no panic 우린 다른 level ay <br>no panic 우린 다른 level ay <br>]]></content><category term="제이핏 (J Fit)" label="제이핏 (J Fit)"/><category term="Heaven`t：Belzebuth (Feat. Trigga)" label="Heaven`t：Belzebuth (Feat. Trigga)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goat_고트/라라라/</id><title>Goat_고트 - 라라라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:09:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:09:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goat_%EA%B3%A0%ED%8A%B8/%EB%9D%BC%EB%9D%BC%EB%9D%BC/" title="Goat_고트 - 라라라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘은 널 만나지 않아 <br>지쳐간 걸까 나 더 이상 <br>더 이상 널 보고 싶지 않아 <br>너에게 난 어떤 의미일까 <br>스쳐가는 흔한 놈일까 그런 걸까 <br>난 시시했던 걸까 <br>라 라 라 라 라 라 라 라 라 라 라 <br>날 보며 짓던 너의 표정이 <br>오늘밤엔 떠나질 않아 <br>그럼 난 이젠 어째야 할까 나 <br>너의 작은 추억들 속에 <br>나의 많은 추억들이 왜 왜 없을까 <br>이젠 어째야 하나 나 <br>라 라 라 라 라 라 라 라 라 라 라 <br>아 난 왜 벼랑 끝에 서있는 걸까 <br>뛰어버리면 편해지는 걸까 <br>아 난 왜 너는 날 밀어내는 걸까 <br>뛰어버리면 편해지긴 할까 <br>어제와 같은 하루 속에 <br>너의 생각들로 가득한 <br>그런 난 어디에 있는 걸까 <br>멀어져 가는 너의 모습이 <br>흐려져 가는 너의 모습이 <br>그 모습이 이건 아닌거 같아 <br>라 라 라 라 라 라 라 라 라 라 라 <br>아 난 왜 벼랑 끝에 서있는 걸까 <br>뛰어버리면 편해지는 걸까 <br>아 난 왜 너는 날 밀어내는 걸까 <br>뛰어버리면 편해지긴 할까 <br>아무것도 난 아무 말도 난 <br>아무 일도 난 없었던 거야 <br>아무것도 난 아무 말도 난 <br>아무 일도 난 없었던 거야 <br>아 난 왜 벼랑 끝에 서있는 걸까 <br>뛰어버리면 편해지는 걸까 <br>아 난 왜 너는 날 밀어내는 걸까 <br>뛰어버리면 편해지긴 할까 <br>아 난 왜 벼랑 끝에 서있는 걸까 <br>뛰어버리면 편해지는 걸까 <br>아 난 왜 너는 날 밀어내는 걸까 <br>뛰어버리면 편해지긴 할까 아 아 <br>아 아 아 아 <br>]]></content><category term="Goat (고트)" label="Goat (고트)"/><category term="라라라" label="라라라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goat_고트/Plus/</id><title>Goat_고트 - Plus - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:09:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:09:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goat_%EA%B3%A0%ED%8A%B8/Plus/" title="Goat_고트 - Plus - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 엉켜진 내 맘을 <br>넌 하얗게 풀어내 <br>넌 이 밤에 불타고 <br>그런 너에게 취해 나는 또 <br>끝이 나는 이 거리가 <br>너와 함께 다가올까 <br>무슨 생각하니 왜 <br>그저 멍하니 서있니 <br>지금 네 몸을 부둥켜 <br>안아 너에게 말을 해 <br>아무렇지 않은 거니 <br>너는 나의 숨결인걸 <br>I just breathe You just fill me <br>I just breathe You just fill me <br>아직 못다한 말들과 <br>그저 멀어져 가는 널 <br>이 자리에서 태울게 <br>숨막힐듯한 연기와 <br>I just breathe You just fill me <br>I just breathe You just fill me <br>I just breathe You just fill me <br>I just breathe You just fill me <br>]]></content><category term="Goat (고트)" label="Goat (고트)"/><category term="Plus" label="Plus"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goat_고트/Fallen/</id><title>Goat_고트 - Fallen - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:09:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:09:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goat_%EA%B3%A0%ED%8A%B8/Fallen/" title="Goat_고트 - Fallen - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[고요한 밤에도 멀리서 보여요 <br>꺾여진 나무는 힘없이 서있죠 <br>떨어지는 메마른 낙엽은 <br>비틀어진 가지를 떠나요 <br>짙은 밤 안에서 멀리서 보여요 <br>앙상히 서있는 나무는 울었죠 <br>떨어지는 메마른 낙엽은 <br>미련 없이 가지를 떠나요 <br>떨어지는 메마른 낙엽은 <br>비틀어진 가지를 떠나요 <br>떨어져요 떨어져요 <br>떨어져요 떨어져요 <br>고요한 밤에도 멀리서 보여요 <br>꺾여진 나무는 여전히 서있죠 <br>]]></content><category term="Goat (고트)" label="Goat (고트)"/><category term="Fallen" label="Fallen"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bro/사랑입니다_Inst/</id><title>Bro - 사랑입니다 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:11:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:11:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bro/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9E%85%EB%8B%88%EB%8B%A4_Inst/" title="Bro - 사랑입니다 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세상이란게 누구나 <br>한번은 살다가 <br>눈물나도록 기쁜날 <br>슬픈날도 있죠 <br>사랑이란것 그 또한 다르지 않죠 <br>눈물나도록 우리 <br>좋은날 슬픈날도 있죠 <br>너무 너무 아픈 사랑 <br>그건 사랑이 아니래 <br>그댈 사랑하는건 <br>이렇게 아픈일인데 <br>그래도 내겐 사랑입니다 <br>가슴이 터져 숨을 <br>쉴 수 없다고 해도 <br>세월이 가고 기억도 무뎌진대도 <br>사무치게 그대 <br>보고싶은 날도 있죠 <br>너무 너무 아픈 사랑 <br>그건 사랑이 아니래 <br>그댈 사랑하는게 <br>이렇게 아픈일인데 <br>그래도 내겐 사랑입니다 <br>가슴이 터져 숨을 <br>쉴 수 없다고 해도 <br>여기서 이렇게 <br>우리가 헤어져야 하는지 <br>너무 너무 아픈 나는 <br>사랑이 될 수 없나요 <br>그댈 사랑하는게 <br>그렇게 잘못인가요 <br>그래도 내겐 사랑입니다 <br>가슴이 터져 숨을 <br>쉴 수 없다고 해도 사랑입니다 <br>]]></content><category term="Bro" label="Bro"/><category term="사랑입니다 (Inst.)" label="사랑입니다 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bro/사랑입니다/</id><title>Bro - 사랑입니다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:11:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:11:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bro/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9E%85%EB%8B%88%EB%8B%A4/" title="Bro - 사랑입니다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세상이란게 누구나 <br>한번은 살다가 <br>눈물나도록 기쁜날 <br>슬픈날도 있죠 <br>사랑이란것 그 또한 다르지 않죠 <br>눈물나도록 우리 <br>좋은날 슬픈날도 있죠 <br>너무 너무 아픈 사랑 <br>그건 사랑이 아니래 <br>그댈 사랑하는건 <br>이렇게 아픈일인데 <br>그래도 내겐 사랑입니다 <br>가슴이 터져 숨을 <br>쉴 수 없다고 해도 <br>세월이 가고 기억도 무뎌진대도 <br>사무치게 그대 <br>보고싶은 날도 있죠 <br>너무 너무 아픈 사랑 <br>그건 사랑이 아니래 <br>그댈 사랑하는게 <br>이렇게 아픈일인데 <br>그래도 내겐 사랑입니다 <br>가슴이 터져 숨을 <br>쉴 수 없다고 해도 <br>여기서 이렇게 <br>우리가 헤어져야 하는지 <br>너무 너무 아픈 나는 <br>사랑이 될 수 없나요 <br>그댈 사랑하는게 <br>그렇게 잘못인가요 <br>그래도 내겐 사랑입니다 <br>가슴이 터져 숨을 <br>쉴 수 없다고 해도 사랑입니다 <br>]]></content><category term="Bro" label="Bro"/><category term="사랑입니다" label="사랑입니다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/데이브니어_Dave_Near/그대_지금_어딨나요/</id><title>데이브니어_Dave_Near - 그대 지금 어딨나요. - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:12:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:12:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%B8%8C%EB%8B%88%EC%96%B4_Dave_Near/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80_%EC%A7%80%EA%B8%88_%EC%96%B4%EB%94%A8%EB%82%98%EC%9A%94/" title="데이브니어_Dave_Near - 그대 지금 어딨나요. - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[별아 나를 그 바닷가로 <br>데려가주렴 <br>그대 함께 거닐었던 <br>아름다운 밤으로 <br>손을 잡고 끝도 없이 얘기나누며 <br>그 눈빛에 담겨있는 <br>슬픔을 느꼈었지 <br>그대는 바다 저 멀리를 <br>물끄러미 바라보며 <br>운명처럼 다가온 우리 <br>사랑을 받아들이기로 했지만 <br>그대 지금 어딨나요 <br>잘 지내고 있나요 <br>나는 그대 그리워요 <br>그대는 바다 저 멀리를 <br>물끄러미 바라보며 <br>운명처럼 다가온 우리 <br>사랑을 받아들이기로 했지만 <br>그대 지금 어딨나요 <br>잘 지내고 있나요 <br>나는 그대 그리워요 <br>그대 지금 어딘가에 <br>누구로 살고 있나요 <br>그대도 나 그립나요 <br>]]></content><category term="데이브니어 (Dave Near)" label="데이브니어 (Dave Near)"/><category term="그대 지금 어딨나요." label="그대 지금 어딨나요."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lailas_Lounge/Bebastereo/</id><title>Lailas_Lounge - Bebastereo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:13:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:13:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lailas_Lounge/Bebastereo/" title="Lailas_Lounge - Bebastereo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Segala yang tersisih <br>adalah jiwamu <br>Persisnya mentari <br><br>di senja menghilang <br>Engkaulah yang kau rasa <br>Bebas suaramu <br>Setelah tertunda <br>diselamkan gelap malam <br><br>Engkaulah dirimu <br>Bicara apa yang kau rasa <br>Bebas jiwamu yang selalu <br>ditelan dihempas dunia <br><br>Segala yang tersisih <br>adalah jiwamu <br>Bangkit dan laungkan <br>di terbitnya fajar <br>Engkaulah yang kau rasa <br>Bebas terasmu <br>Setelah tertunda <br>di Temasya Gelap Malam <br><br>Engkaulah dirimu <br>Bicara apa yang kau rasa <br>Bebas jiwamu yang selalu <br>ditelan dihempas dunia]]></content><category term="Laila`s Lounge" label="Laila`s Lounge"/><category term="Bebastereo" label="Bebastereo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soundgarden/Searching_With_My_Good_Eye_Closed_Live_At_The_Paramount_Theatre_Seattle___1992/</id><title>Soundgarden - Searching With My Good Eye Closed (Live At The Paramount Theatre, Seattle / 1992) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:15:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:15:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soundgarden/Searching_With_My_Good_Eye_Closed_Live_At_The_Paramount_Theatre_Seattle___1992/" title="Soundgarden - Searching With My Good Eye Closed (Live At The Paramount Theatre, Seattle / 1992) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Painted blue across my eyes <br>And tie the linen on <br>And I'm on my way <br>Looking for the paradigm <br>So I can pass it off <br>Is it on my side <br>Is it to the sky <br>Looking to the sky and down <br>Searching for a ground <br>With my good eye closed <br>If I took you for a ride <br>Would you take it wrong <br>Or would you make it right <br>Looking for a pedestal <br>That I can put you on <br>And be on my way <br>Is it to the sky <br>Looking to the sky and down <br>Searching for a ground <br>With my good eye closed <br>Stop you're trying to bruise my mind <br>I can do it on my own <br>Stop you're trying to kill my time <br>It's been my death since I was born <br>I don't remember half the time <br>If I'm hiding or I'm lost <br>But I'm on my way]]></content><category term="Soundgarden" label="Soundgarden"/><category term="Searching With My Good Eye Closed (Live At The Paramount Theatre, Seattle / 1992)" label="Searching With My Good Eye Closed (Live At The Paramount Theatre, Seattle / 1992)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/뽕짝히어로/짝사랑/</id><title>뽕짝히어로 - 짝사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:16:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:16:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%BD%95%EC%A7%9D%ED%9E%88%EC%96%B4%EB%A1%9C/%EC%A7%9D%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="뽕짝히어로 - 짝사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너를 처음 본 그날 <br>말할 수 없이 좋았던 순간 <br>아쉽게 돌아서던 내게 <br>웃으며 흔들던 두 손 <br>잡고 싶었다 <br>끝도 없이 시작된 <br>나 혼자 만의 사랑은 <br>너의 곁에 남자로 <br>남고만 싶다 하지만 <br>사랑한다고 <br>지금 달려가 <br>말하려 해도 <br>사랑해 널 <br>네 앞에만 서면 <br>나는 나는 나는 <br>바보가 되나 봐 <br>사랑한다고 <br>너 하나만 <br>그 한마디 못 하지만 네 곁에 <br>이 순간 <br>웃고 있는 내 모습은 이렇게 <br>오늘도 <br>한없이 행복해 <br>하루하루 함께 한 시간은 <br>쌓아갈 수 없는 듯 <br>언제나 편한 친구라는 <br>웃으며 말하는 입술 <br>갖고 싶었다 <br>끝도 없이 시작된 <br>나 혼자만의 고백은 <br>사랑해 <br>내가 너의 남자라 <br>외치고 싶다 하지만 <br>사랑한다고 <br>지금 달려가 <br>말하려 해도 <br>사랑해 널 <br>네 앞에만 서면 <br>나는 나는 나는 <br>바보가 되나 봐 <br>사랑한다고 <br>너 하나만 <br>그 한마디 못 하지만 네 곁에 <br>이 순간 <br>웃고 있는 내 모습은 이렇게 <br>오늘도 <br>한없이 행복해 <br>보고 싶다 말 못하는 <br>사랑한다 말 못하는 <br>내가 있잖아 <br>너 하나만을 보면서 <br>내가 바로 여기 있잖아 <br>]]></content><category term="뽕짝히어로" label="뽕짝히어로"/><category term="짝사랑" label="짝사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/닥터오_프로젝트_DrOh_Project/이쁜_Girl/</id><title>닥터오_프로젝트_DrOh_Project - 이쁜 Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:19:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:19:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A5%ED%84%B0%EC%98%A4_%ED%94%84%EB%A1%9C%EC%A0%9D%ED%8A%B8_DrOh_Project/%EC%9D%B4%EC%81%9C_Girl/" title="닥터오_프로젝트_DrOh_Project - 이쁜 Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[솔솔 불어오는 가을 바람 <br>10월 금요일 <br>살랑이는 낙엽처럼 맘이 설레 <br>step by step one two three <br>앞으로 한걸음씩 걷고 <br>up today <br>하루가 즐거워 <br>show me the happy <br>샤랄랄라 물든 단풍 아래 <br>카페에 들어가 <br>메뉴보러 니 앞에 선 순간 난 <br>clap eyes on <br>설렜어 너만 바라보던 내눈 <br>slap me pop <br>심쿵해 너의 심장 어택에 난 <br>이쁜 girl 이쁜 girl <br>내겐 너무나 이쁜걸 <br>너의 눈 코 입 목소리 <br>빨간 볼터치까지 <br>귀여운 girl 섹시한 girl <br>니 매력에 빠졌는걸 <br>너의 향기 행동 말투가 <br>내겐 너무 이쁜걸 <br>무슨 생각하고 <br>계신가요란 그 질문에 <br>떠오르는 건 너밖에 없오 <br>oh my love <br>back to the <br>그때로 우리가 만났던 그때로 <br>try to ask <br>이름과 네 번호라도 물을껄 <br>이쁜 girl 이쁜 girl <br>내겐 너무나 이쁜걸 <br>너의 눈 코 입 목소리 <br>빨간 볼터치까지 <br>귀여운 girl 섹시한 girl <br>니 매력에 빠졌는걸 <br>너의 향기 행동 말투가 <br>내겐 너무 이쁜걸 <br>잊지를 못해 feeling <br>아쉽기만 해 ending <br>꿈에서라도 <br>널 다시 보면 나는 고백할래 <br>이쁜 girl 이쁜 girl <br>내겐 너무나 이쁜걸 <br>지워지지 않는 <br>그 시간 그 장소에 우리 <br>귀여운 girl 섹시한 girl <br>니 매력에 빠졌는걸 <br>귀에 멤돌던 <br>니가 내게 하던 그 말들이 <br>]]></content><category term="닥터오 프로젝트 (Dr.Oh Project)" label="닥터오 프로젝트 (Dr.Oh Project)"/><category term="이쁜 Girl" label="이쁜 Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kate_Kim_케이트_킴/I_Dont_Wanna_Go/</id><title>Kate_Kim_케이트_킴 - I Don`t Wanna Go - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:21:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:21:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kate_Kim_%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4%ED%8A%B8_%ED%82%B4/I_Dont_Wanna_Go/" title="Kate_Kim_케이트_킴 - I Don`t Wanna Go - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don’t wanna go <br>I don’t wanna go <br>나 날 붙잡아 줘요 <br>I don’t wanna go <br>I don’t wanna go <br>아직은 나 가기 싫어요 <br>I don’t wanna go <br>I don’t wanna go <br>나 날 보내지 마요 <br>I don’t wanna go <br>You don’t wanna go <br>Hey boy <br>꼼지락 거리는 손 <br>Shy girl <br>니 뒤 쫓는 수줍은 걸음 <br>내 입술은 <br>조금씩 마르고 oh <br>아쉬운 맘 <br>아직은 이른감 oh <br>날 순진하게 보진마 <br>이젠 나 알건 다 알아 <br>I know you know <br>이젠 날 <br>애타게 하지마 <br>말 없는 Body language <br>보고 눈치 좀 채줘 <br>I don’t wanna go <br>왜 몰라주니 내 마음을 <br>I don’t wanna go <br>I don’t wanna go <br>나 날 붙잡아 줘요 <br>I don’t wanna go <br>I don’t wanna go <br>아직은 나 가기 싫어요 <br>I don’t wanna go <br>I don’t wanna go <br>나 날 보내지 마요 <br>I don’t wanna go <br>You don’t wanna go <br>Why love <br>그대가 미워요 <br>Hey 꼭 내 입으로 <br>말해야겠니 <br>또 내 속은 그대로 <br>타들어 가 <br>이 바보는 <br>아직도 모르고 no <br>소중히 여겨주는 건 <br>너무 고맙긴 하지만 <br>I know you know <br>이젠 더 <br>대담해도 돼요 <br>어떤 말을 해도 난 <br>대충 속아줄게요 <br>All you gotta do <br>내게 말해줘 <br>니 마음을 <br>I don’t wanna go <br>I don’t wanna go <br>나 날 붙잡아 줘요 <br>I don’t wanna go <br>I don’t wanna go <br>아직은 나 가기 싫어요 <br>I don’t wanna go <br>I don’t wanna go <br>나 날 보내지 마요 <br>I don’t wanna go <br>You don’t wanna go <br>I don’t wanna go <br>멍하니 있지말고 <br>뭐라고 말좀해봐 <br>우물쭈물 하지말고 제발 <br>Don’t you want it <br>혹시 나 매력이 <br>없어 그런거니 <br>또 한번참고 <br>mind control <br>Listen baby <br>I don’t wanna go <br>I don’t wanna go <br>나 날 붙잡아 줘요 <br>I don’t wanna go <br>I don’t wanna go <br>아직은 나 가기 싫어요 <br>I don’t wanna go <br>I don’t wanna go <br>나 날 보내지 마요 <br>I don’t wanna go <br>You don’t wanna go <br>]]></content><category term="Kate Kim (케이트 킴)" label="Kate Kim (케이트 킴)"/><category term="I Don`t Wanna Go" label="I Don`t Wanna Go"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아이니/머뭇머뭇/</id><title>아이니 - 머뭇머뭇 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:22:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:22:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%88/%EB%A8%B8%EB%AD%87%EB%A8%B8%EB%AD%87/" title="아이니 - 머뭇머뭇 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[머뭇머뭇하는 모습 <br>그대를 한 번에 표현할 수 있죠 <br>일부러 더 빤히 보네요 <br>내게 무슨 하고픈 말 있지 않나요 <br>조심스럽게 눈이 마주치게 <br>안돼요 내 맘 알지 못하게요 <br>머뭇머뭇 거리던 <br>그대의 얼굴이 가끔 <br>아른아른 거려서 <br>웃음이 나곤 해요 <br>힐끔힐끔 거리던 <br>그대의 눈빛이 자꾸 <br>알짱알짱 대요 <br>내 머릿속을 아니 내 맘속을 <br>조심스럽게 두근거리게 <br>그런데 왜요 <br>내 맘 알지 못하네요 <br>머뭇머뭇 거리던 <br>그대의 얼굴이 가끔 <br>아른아른 거려서 <br>웃음이 나곤 해요 <br>힐끔힐끔 거리던 <br>그대의 눈빛이 자꾸 <br>알짱알짱 대요 <br>내 머릿속을 아니 내 맘속을 <br>머뭇머뭇하는 모습 <br>그대는 한 번에 나를 사로잡죠 <br>]]></content><category term="아이니" label="아이니"/><category term="머뭇머뭇" label="머뭇머뭇"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박광선/시간이_멈춘듯_Inst/</id><title>박광선 - 시간이 멈춘듯 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:22:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:22:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EA%B4%91%EC%84%A0/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B0%84%EC%9D%B4_%EB%A9%88%EC%B6%98%EB%93%AF_Inst/" title="박광선 - 시간이 멈춘듯 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[끝이 없을 것 같은 <br>잠들지 않는 숲에서 <br>해맑게 웃고 있는 넌 <br>왠지 나조차도 <br>두렵지 않나 봐 <br>깊고 깊은 어둠 속 <br>그 길을 밝혀주는 듯 <br>환하게 웃고 있는 넌 <br>왠지 따사로운 꽃 같아 <br>시간이 멈춘 듯 <br>늪에 빠진 것처럼 <br>움직일 수 없어 <br>다가갈 수도 없어 <br>바람이 멈춘 듯 <br>마법에 빠져 버린 듯 <br>향기로운 그 길 끝에서 <br>널 본 것만 같아 <br>Maybe you <br>It's you <br>The flower was you <br>상처뿐인 내 삶에 <br>시들지 않는 꽃처럼 <br>여린 너의 그 두 눈에 <br>이젠 길들여진 것 같아 <br>시간이 멈춘 듯 <br>늪에 빠진 것처럼 <br>움직일 수 없어 <br>다가갈 수도 없어 <br>바람이 멈춘 듯 <br>마법에 빠져 버린 듯 <br>향기로운 그 길 끝에서 <br>널 본 것만 같아 <br>Maybe you <br>It's you <br>The flower was you <br>Maybe you <br>It's you <br>The witch was you <br>언제부터였을까 <br>아이처럼 널 따라 <br>웃고 있는 난 <br>계속 걸어가겠지 <br>아득히 먼 꿈속으로 <br>사랑에 취한 듯 <br>그 독이 퍼진 것처럼 <br>숨을 쉴 수 없어 <br>달아날 수도 없어 <br>바람이 멈춘 듯 <br>마법에 갇혀 버린 듯 <br>향기로운 그 길 끝에서 <br>널 본 것만 같아 <br>Maybe you <br>It's you <br>The flower was you <br>Maybe you <br>It's you <br>The witch was you <br>]]></content><category term="박광선" label="박광선"/><category term="시간이 멈춘듯 (Inst.)" label="시간이 멈춘듯 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박광선/시간이_멈춘듯/</id><title>박광선 - 시간이 멈춘듯 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:23:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:23:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EA%B4%91%EC%84%A0/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B0%84%EC%9D%B4_%EB%A9%88%EC%B6%98%EB%93%AF/" title="박광선 - 시간이 멈춘듯 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[끝이 없을 것 같은 <br>잠들지 않는 숲에서 <br>해맑게 웃고 있는 넌 <br>왠지 나조차도 <br>두렵지 않나 봐 <br>깊고 깊은 어둠 속 <br>그 길을 밝혀주는 듯 <br>환하게 웃고 있는 넌 <br>왠지 따사로운 꽃 같아 <br>시간이 멈춘 듯 <br>늪에 빠진 것처럼 <br>움직일 수 없어 <br>다가갈 수도 없어 <br>바람이 멈춘 듯 <br>마법에 빠져 버린 듯 <br>향기로운 그 길 끝에서 <br>널 본 것만 같아 <br>Maybe you <br>It's you <br>The flower was you <br>상처뿐인 내 삶에 <br>시들지 않는 꽃처럼 <br>여린 너의 그 두 눈에 <br>이젠 길들여진 것 같아 <br>시간이 멈춘 듯 <br>늪에 빠진 것처럼 <br>움직일 수 없어 <br>다가갈 수도 없어 <br>바람이 멈춘 듯 <br>마법에 빠져 버린 듯 <br>향기로운 그 길 끝에서 <br>널 본 것만 같아 <br>Maybe you <br>It's you <br>The flower was you <br>Maybe you <br>It's you <br>The witch was you <br>언제부터였을까 <br>아이처럼 널 따라 <br>웃고 있는 난 <br>계속 걸어가겠지 <br>아득히 먼 꿈속으로 <br>사랑에 취한 듯 <br>그 독이 퍼진 것처럼 <br>숨을 쉴 수 없어 <br>달아날 수도 없어 <br>바람이 멈춘 듯 <br>마법에 갇혀 버린 듯 <br>향기로운 그 길 끝에서 <br>널 본 것만 같아 <br>Maybe you <br>It's you <br>The flower was you <br>Maybe you <br>It's you <br>The witch was you <br>]]></content><category term="박광선" label="박광선"/><category term="시간이 멈춘듯" label="시간이 멈춘듯"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리듬킹/안아줘_Inst/</id><title>리듬킹 - 안아줘 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:23:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:23:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%93%AC%ED%82%B9/%EC%95%88%EC%95%84%EC%A4%98_Inst/" title="리듬킹 - 안아줘 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You used to be a faraway star <br>You used to be a faraway star <br>뒤에서 그냥 널 안을때 <br>달콤하게 키스해 줄래 <br>널 위한 멜로딜 만들고 <br>노랠 불러 줄게 <br>너는 그냥 키스해 줄래 <br>문득 밖에 해가 질때 <br>그냥 맘이 힘들때 항상 니 옆엔 나 <br>나를 꼭 안아줄래 <br>나를 꼭 안아줄래 <br>옆에 있어서 좋아 <br>그게 너여서 좋아 <br>이 손 놓지 않을게 <br>나 영원히 약속해 <br>지금 이대로도 좋아 <br>지금 이대로가 좋아 <br>in love with you <br>you used to be a faraway star <br>you used to be a faraway star <br>니가 침대에서 기타를 칠때 <br>달콤하게 키스해 줄게 <br>험한 세상 겁이 날때 <br>그냥 맘이 힘들때 항상 니 옆엔 나 <br>나를 꼭 안아줄래 <br>나를 꼭 안아줄래 <br>옆에 있어서 좋아 <br>그게 너여서 좋아 <br>이 손 놓지 않을게 <br>나 영원히 약속해 <br>지금 이대로도 좋아 <br>지금 이대로가 좋아 <br>I'll aways in love with you <br>in love with you <br>말할게 my baby 니가 나를 봤을때 <br>우 첨부터 너였어 My baby <br>어 예예예 <br>looking for love in my whole life <br>and I found you <br>good night good morning <br>나 영원히 약속해 <br>baby 너와난 이제 우리 둘이 <br>everyday I'm there for you yeah <br>]]></content><category term="리듬킹" label="리듬킹"/><category term="안아줘 (Inst.)" label="안아줘 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리듬킹/Unbeautiful_Remix_Feat_동경/</id><title>리듬킹 - Unbeautiful Remix (Feat. 동경) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:23:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:23:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%93%AC%ED%82%B9/Unbeautiful_Remix_Feat_%EB%8F%99%EA%B2%BD/" title="리듬킹 - Unbeautiful Remix (Feat. 동경) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm dying slowly <br>in deep blue haze I made <br>It's so heavy to keep <br>my eyes shut I can't <br>Hey you curse you <br>we didn't last in love <br>Why you say <br>that I'm sorry sorry <br>Fuck you fuck you <br>I saw you kissing her fuck you <br>Fuck you fuck you <br>our love is over so fuck you <br>I know it's been <br>so long you've gone away <br>I know I have to <br>let you go away <br>Hey you curse you <br>we didn't last in love <br>Why you say <br>that I'm sorry sorry <br>Fuck you fuck you <br>I saw you kissing her fuck you <br>Fuck you fuck you <br>our love is over so fuck you <br>Baby you never leave like a star <br>너는 내 맘속에 항상 빛나 <br>Baby you have appeal like a star <br>어둔 내 맘속에 너는 빛나 <br>Because you <br>나 다시 서봐 날아가 <br>우후 네게로 우후 <br>Baby you <br>내 모습을 봐 날아가 <br>우후 니가 날 우후 잡아줘 <br>She is my woman Yeah <br>She is my woman Yeah <br>She is my woman Yeah <br>She is my woman Yeah <br>She is my woman Yeah <br>She is my woman Yeah <br>She is my woman Yeah <br>She is my woman <br>woman woman woman <br>She is my woman Yeah <br>She is my woman Yeah <br>She is my woman Yeah <br>She is my woman <br>woman woman woman Yeah <br>]]></content><category term="리듬킹" label="리듬킹"/><category term="Unbeautiful Remix (Feat. 동경)" label="Unbeautiful Remix (Feat. 동경)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리듬킹/Unbeautiful_Feat_동경/</id><title>리듬킹 - Unbeautiful (Feat. 동경) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:23:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:23:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%93%AC%ED%82%B9/Unbeautiful_Feat_%EB%8F%99%EA%B2%BD/" title="리듬킹 - Unbeautiful (Feat. 동경) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 지금 널 부셔가고 있어 <br>이제와 새삼 니가 왜 놀래 <br>Hey you I know you <br>we didn't last in love <br>네게 지쳤어 난 <br>I'm sorry <br>꺼져가는 사랑 잡지 않아 <br>Good bye <br>꺼져있어 니 전화긴 항상 <br>Good bye <br>이젠 아무 미련 없어 잘가 <br>다신 널 찾을 일 없어 안가 <br>Hey you I know you <br>we didn't last in love <br>네게 지쳤어 난 <br>I'm sorry <br>꺼져가는 사랑 잡지 않아 <br>Good bye <br>꺼져있어 니 전화긴 항상 <br>Good bye <br>Hey you I know you <br>We didn't last in love <br>네게 지쳤어 난 <br>I'm sorry <br>꺼져가는 사랑 잡지 않아 <br>Good bye <br>꺼져있어 니 전화긴 항상 <br>Good bye <br>꺼져버려 니 마음은 항상 꺼져 <br>꺼져있어 니 전화긴 항상 <br>Good bye <br>]]></content><category term="리듬킹" label="리듬킹"/><category term="Unbeautiful (Feat. 동경)" label="Unbeautiful (Feat. 동경)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리듬킹/안아줘_Remix_Feat_동경/</id><title>리듬킹 - 안아줘 Remix (Feat. 동경) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:23:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:23:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%93%AC%ED%82%B9/%EC%95%88%EC%95%84%EC%A4%98_Remix_Feat_%EB%8F%99%EA%B2%BD/" title="리듬킹 - 안아줘 Remix (Feat. 동경) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나를 꼭 안아줄래 <br>나를 꼭 안아줄래 <br>옆에 있어서 좋아 <br>그게 너여서 좋아 <br>이 손 놓지 않을게 <br>나 영원히 약속해 <br>지금 이대로도 좋아 <br>지금 이대로가 좋아 <br>In love with you In love with you <br>In love with you In love with you <br>나를 꼭 안아 줄래 <br>I’m sober baby you <br>너 뭘 왜긴 너 뭐가 왜긴 너 <br>그냥 왜긴 널 love <br>왜긴 너 잖아 <br>다른 여자는 안 보여 <br>다른 여자는 안 보여줬던 <br>나만의 비밀 하날 말해줄게 Okey <br>너는 잠잘 때 눈을 떠 <br>You don’t know 그게 난 재밌고 <br>귀여워서 사진을 찍어뒀어 <br>매일 봐 In love with you <br>넌 풀 수 있어 내 휴대폰 <br>비밀번혼 니 생일야 <br>나만의 보물을 보여줄게 <br>니 비밀을 풀어 난 지우지 않을래 Love <br>나를 꼭 안아줄래 <br>나를 꼭 안아줄래 <br>옆에 있어서 좋아 <br>그게 너여서 좋아 <br>이 손 놓지 않을게 <br>나 영원히 약속해 <br>지금 이대로도 좋아 <br>지금 이대로가 좋아 <br>In love with you In love with you <br>In love with you In love with you <br>나를 꼭 안아 줄래 <br>]]></content><category term="리듬킹" label="리듬킹"/><category term="안아줘 Remix (Feat. 동경)" label="안아줘 Remix (Feat. 동경)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리듬킹/안아줘_Feat_봉구_of_길구봉구_동경/</id><title>리듬킹 - 안아줘 (Feat. 봉구 of 길구봉구, 동경) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:23:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:23:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%93%AC%ED%82%B9/%EC%95%88%EC%95%84%EC%A4%98_Feat_%EB%B4%89%EA%B5%AC_of_%EA%B8%B8%EA%B5%AC%EB%B4%89%EA%B5%AC_%EB%8F%99%EA%B2%BD/" title="리듬킹 - 안아줘 (Feat. 봉구 of 길구봉구, 동경) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You used to be a faraway star <br>You used to be a faraway star <br>뒤에서 그냥 널 안을때 <br>달콤하게 키스해 줄래 <br>널 위한 멜로딜 만들고 <br>노랠 불러 줄게 <br>너는 그냥 키스해 줄래 <br>문득 밖에 해가 질때 <br>그냥 맘이 힘들때 항상 니 옆엔 나 <br>나를 꼭 안아줄래 <br>나를 꼭 안아줄래 <br>옆에 있어서 좋아 <br>그게 너여서 좋아 <br>이 손 놓지 않을게 <br>나 영원히 약속해 <br>지금 이대로도 좋아 <br>지금 이대로가 좋아 <br>in love with you <br>you used to be a faraway star <br>you used to be a faraway star <br>니가 침대에서 기타를 칠때 <br>달콤하게 키스해 줄게 <br>험한 세상 겁이 날때 <br>그냥 맘이 힘들때 항상 니 옆엔 나 <br>나를 꼭 안아줄래 <br>나를 꼭 안아줄래 <br>옆에 있어서 좋아 <br>그게 너여서 좋아 <br>이 손 놓지 않을게 <br>나 영원히 약속해 <br>지금 이대로도 좋아 <br>지금 이대로가 좋아 <br>I'll aways in love with you <br>in love with you <br>말할게 my baby 니가 나를 봤을때 <br>우 첨부터 너였어 My baby <br>어 예예예 <br>looking for love in my whole life <br>and I found you <br>good night good morning <br>나 영원히 약속해 <br>baby 너와난 이제 우리 둘이 <br>everyday I'm there for you yeah <br>]]></content><category term="리듬킹" label="리듬킹"/><category term="안아줘 (Feat. 봉구 of 길구봉구, 동경)" label="안아줘 (Feat. 봉구 of 길구봉구, 동경)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/Holy_War/</id><title>Alicia_Keys - Holy War - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:24:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:24:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/Holy_War/" title="Alicia_Keys - Holy War - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If war is holy and sex is obscene <br>Then we got it twisted <br>in this lucid dream <br>Baptized in boundaries <br>schooled in sin <br>Divided by difference <br>sexuality and skin <br>So we can hate each other <br>and fear each other <br>We can build these walls <br>between each other <br>Baby blow by blow <br>and brick by brick <br>Keep yourself locked in <br>yourself locked in <br>We can hate each other <br>and fear each other <br>We can build these walls <br>between each other <br>Baby blow by blow <br>and brick by brick <br>Keep yourself locked in <br>yourself locked <br>Maybe we should love somebody <br>Maybe we could care a little more <br>Maybe we should love somebody <br>Instead of polishing <br>the bombs of holy war <br>What if sex was holy <br>and war was obscene <br>And it wasn't twisted <br>what a wonderful dream <br>Living for love unafraid of the end <br>Forgiveness is the only <br>real revenge <br>So we can heal each other <br>and fill each other <br>We can break these walls <br>between each other <br>Baby blow by blow <br>and brick by brick <br>Keep yourself open yourself open <br>We can heal each other <br>and fill each other <br>We can break these walls <br>between each other <br>Baby blow by blow <br>and brick by brick <br>Keep yourself open you open <br>Maybe we should love somebody <br>Maybe we could care a little more <br>Maybe we should love somebody <br>Instead of polishing <br>the bombs of holy war <br>What if love was holy <br>and hate obscene <br>We should give life to <br>this beautiful dream <br>Cause peace and love ain't so far <br>If we nurse our wounds <br>before they scar <br>Nurse our wounds before they scar <br>]]></content><category term="Alicia Keys" label="Alicia Keys"/><category term="Holy War" label="Holy War"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alma/Dye_My_Hair_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>Alma - Dye My Hair (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:24:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:24:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alma/Dye_My_Hair_Acoustic_Ver/" title="Alma - Dye My Hair (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1] <br>You better mark my words <br>I'm not that kinda girl <br>To keep my voice unheard, oh no <br>You better mark my words <br>I don't get hit and hurt <br>No bullets pierce my eyes shut <br><br>[Pre-Chorus] <br>But there's something in the way I act around you <br>Tryna turn your head <br>Laugh at jokes that I don't get <br>But there's something in the way I act around you <br>The way I feel about you <br>Not a thing I wouldn't do <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>You got that mad power, the sweet and sour <br>You won't cut me loose <br>There's nothing that I wouldn't do <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you, yeah <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>You got that mad power, the sweet and sour <br>You won't cut me loose <br>There's nothing that I wouldn't do <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>Don't buy me fancy things <br>Don't buy me any drinks <br>I pay for my own sins, oh yeah <br>I was raised to be free <br>Got my independency <br>Why do I get so weak? <br><br>[Pre-Chorus] <br>But there's something in the way I act around you <br>Tryna turn your head <br>Laugh at jokes that I don't get <br>But there's something in the way I act around you <br>The way I feel about you <br>Not a thing I wouldn't do <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>You got that mad power, the sweet and sour <br>You won't cut me loose <br>There's nothing that I wouldn't do <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you, yeah <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>You got that mad power, the sweet and sour <br>You won't cut me loose <br>There's nothing that I wouldn't do <br>There's nothing that I wouldn't do <br>There's nothing that I wouldn't do <br>Nothing I won't do, no, no, no]]></content><category term="Alma" label="Alma"/><category term="Dye My Hair (Acoustic Ver.)" label="Dye My Hair (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alma/Dye_My_Hair/</id><title>Alma - Dye My Hair - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:24:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:24:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alma/Dye_My_Hair/" title="Alma - Dye My Hair - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not that kinda girl <br>To keep my voice unheard <br>To carefully pick words, oh no <br>I'm not that kinda girl <br>To easily get hurt <br>No bullets pierce my eyes shut <br><br>But there's something in the way I act around you <br>Tryna turn your head <br>Laugh at jokes that I don't get <br>There is something in the way I act around you <br>The way I feel about you <br>Not a thing I wouldn't do <br><br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>You got that mad power, the sweet and sour <br>You won't cut me loose <br>There's nothing that I wouldn't do <br><br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>You got that mad power, the sweet and sour <br>You won't cut me loose <br>There's nothing that I wouldn't do oh <br><br>Don't buy me fancy things <br>Don't buy me any drinks <br>I pay for my own self, oh yeah <br>I was raised to be free <br>Got my independency <br>Why do I get so weak <br><br>'Cause there's something in the way I act around you <br>Tryna turn your head <br>Laugh at jokes that I don't get <br>There is something in the way I act around you <br>The way I feel about you <br>Not a thing I wouldn't do <br><br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>You got that mad power, the sweet and sour <br>And you won't cut me loose <br>There's nothing that I wouldn't do <br><br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>You got that mad power, the sweet and sour <br>And you won't cut me loose <br>There's nothing that I wouldn't do oh <br><br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>You got that mad power, the sweet and sour <br>So how I could I refuse <br>There's nothing that I wouldn't do oh <br><br>But there's something in the way I act around you <br>Around you, around you <br>But there's something in the way I act around you <br>The way I feel about you <br>Not a thing I wouldn't do <br><br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>You got that mad power, the sweet and sour <br>You won't cut me loose <br>There's nothing that I wouldn't do oh <br><br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you <br>You got that mad power, the sweet and sour <br>So how could I refuse <br>There's nothing that I wouldn't do oh <br>I will dye my hair blonde for you]]></content><category term="Alma" label="Alma"/><category term="Dye My Hair" label="Dye My Hair"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Allan_Rayman/Tennessee/</id><title>Allan_Rayman - Tennessee - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T15:25:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T15:25:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Allan_Rayman/Tennessee/" title="Allan_Rayman - Tennessee - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Take me down, my Tennessee <br>I'm high and dry, don't follow me <br><br>Take me down, my Tennessee <br>I'm high and dry, don't follow me <br>Love me twice, then run from me <br>Well, this boy, he needs no company <br>This life is sharp like Pittsburgh steel <br>Another dart with my piss warm ale <br>It may be tough, don't follow me <br>This boy, he needs no company <br>No company needed <br>I find comfort on my own thought <br>I'm through with palm reading, no, no <br>It couldn't give me what I don't got <br>I don't want a lifestyle like you, not me <br>Well, I'm a simple kind of man <br>With a simple kind of plan <br>Like to keep it lowkey <br>This is my time, my money <br>I'll spend it how I want, son <br>This is my drink, my lungs <br>I'll die when I want, son <br>And don't follow <br>I don't see eye to eye with society <br>And I'm a lost boy, forever young <br>Don't expect an apology <br><br>She loves me still <br>And I don't know, I don't know <br>I don't know why <br>My girl, she loves me still <br>She loves me still <br>And I don't know, I don't know <br>I don't know why <br>My girl, she loves me still <br><br>She want a James Dean rebel <br>White shirt, blue jeans <br>Damn, Lana Del Rey <br>Look what you've done to these teens <br>Well this is something for the fathers who don't know better <br>Goodnight, Daddy <br>Your girl's falling for the bad guy <br>Saw the car, she don't know better <br>So get the shotgun ready, y'all <br>This a different type of go getter <br>There's something rotten in Denmark <br>When the punks are getting bold with her <br>Oh, I'm no good, I'm no good <br>Not me, not me <br>Please don't follow <br><br>She loves me still <br>And I don't know, I don't know <br>I don't know why <br>My girl, she loves me still <br>She loves me still <br>And I don't know, I don't know <br>I don't know why <br>My girl, she loves me still]]></content><category term="Allan Rayman" label="Allan Rayman"/><category term="Tennessee" label="Tennessee"/></entry></feed>