<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:37:01+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/문효심/화초도_많고_많다/</id><title>문효심 - 화초도 많고 많다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:11:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:11:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B8%ED%9A%A8%EC%8B%AC/%ED%99%94%EC%B4%88%EB%8F%84_%EB%A7%8E%EA%B3%A0_%EB%A7%8E%EB%8B%A4/" title="문효심 - 화초도 많고 많다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[배에 얹저 실고 보니 <br>크기가 수레 같고 <br>행취가 진동 커늘 <br>본국으로 돌아와 <br>재물을 분배 허는디 <br>도선주는 재물을 <br>마다 허고 <br>그 꽃봉을 차지허여 <br>후원에 두었구나 <br>그때여 천자 황후 <br>홀연 붕하시사 <br>천자께옵서는 납비하기 <br>뜻이 없고 <br>각지 기화요초를 <br>걷어 들여 <br>황극전 널흔 뜰 <br>여기저기 심어 놓고 <br>주야로 구경을 허시는디 <br>이것이 바로 화초 <br>타령이던 것이었다 <br>화초도 많고 많다 <br>팔월 부용 군자련 <br>만당추수으 홍련화 <br>암향부동 월향원 <br>소식 전턴 한 매화 <br>진시유랑 거후재난 <br>붉어 있다고 복숭꽃 <br>구월 구일 용산음 <br>소죽신 국화꽃 <br>삼천제자를 강론을 허니 <br>행단 춘풍으 은행 꽃 <br>이화만지 불개문허니 <br>장신궁중 배꽃이요 <br>천태산 들어 가니 <br>양변게 작약이요 <br>원정부지 이별허니 <br>옥창 옥연의 앵도화 <br>촉국한을 못 이기여 <br>제혈허든 두견화 <br>이화노황 개관화 <br>홍국백국 사개화 <br>동원도리 편시춘 <br>목동요지가 행화촌 <br>월중단계 무삼경 <br>달 가운데 계수나무 <br>백일홍 영산홍 <br>외철죽 진달화 <br>난초 파초 오미자 치자 <br>감과유자 <br>석류 능나 능금 포도 <br>머루 어름 <br>대추 각색화초 <br>가진 행과 <br>좌우로 심었난디 <br>향풍이 건듯 불면 <br>벌 나부 새 짐생들이 <br>지지 울어서 춤을 춘다 <br>]]></content><category term="문효심" label="문효심"/><category term="화초도 많고 많다" label="화초도 많고 많다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/문효심/북을_두리둥둥/</id><title>문효심 - 북을 두리둥둥 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:11:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:11:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B8%ED%9A%A8%EC%8B%AC/%EB%B6%81%EC%9D%84_%EB%91%90%EB%A6%AC%EB%91%A5%EB%91%A5/" title="문효심 - 북을 두리둥둥 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루는 옥황상제께서 <br>사해용왕을 또 다시 불러 <br>하교하시되 <br>심효제 방년이 늦어가니 <br>어서 급히 인당수로 환송하야 <br>인간의 귀한 배필을 정해주라 <br>용왕 등이 수명허고 내려와 <br>심청을 환송 헐제 <br>꽃한봉을 조화있게 만들어 <br>그 가운데 심청을 모시고 <br>양대 선녀로 시위허고 <br>조석지공과 찬수범절 <br>금은보패를 많이 넣고 <br>용왕과 각궁 선녀들이 모다 나와 <br>작별허고 돌아서니 <br>이난 곳 인당수라 <br>용왕의 조화 인지라 <br>바람이 분들 움직이며 <br>비가 온들 젖을 소냐 <br>주야로 둥덩 떠 있을제 <br>그때여 남경장사 선인들이 <br>억십만금 퇴를 내어 <br>본국으로 돌아오는디 <br>인당수를 당도허니 <br>심효제의 효행이 홀연 감동되야 <br>제물을 정히 차려놓고 <br>심효제 넋을 한번 <br>위로 허고 가는듸 <br>반 소리요 반 신앙호것다 <br>북을 두리둥둥 울리면서 <br>넋이야 넋이로구나 <br>이 넋이 뉘 넋인고 <br>오장원으 낙상허든 <br>공명으 넋도 아니요 <br>삼년 무우간의 <br>초희왕의 넋도 아니요 <br>부친 눈을 띠우랴고 <br>삼백석으 몸이 팔려 <br>인당수 제수 되신 <br>심낭자으 넋이로구나 <br>넋이라도 오셨거든 <br>많이 흠향허옵소서 <br>제물을 물에 풀고 <br>눈물 씻고 바라보니 <br>난데없난 꽃 한송이 <br>해상에 둥실 떠있거날 <br>도사공이 보고 허는 말이 <br>허허 저것이 금이냐 <br>금이란 말씀이 당치 않소 <br>옛날 진평이가 <br>범아부를 잡을랴고 <br>황금 사만근을 <br>초군중의 흩텄쓰니 <br>무슨 금이 되오리까 <br>그러면 저것이 옥이냐 <br>옥이란 말씀도 당치않소 <br>옥출곤강 아니거든 <br>옥 한 쪽이 되오리까 <br>그러면 저게 해당화냐 <br>해당화란 말씀 당치않소 <br>명사십리 아니거든 <br>해당화 어이 되오리까 <br>그러면 무엇인고 <br>가까이 가서 보자 <br>저어라 저어 <br>어기야 뒤여 <br>저어가니 <br>행취 진동허고 <br>오색채운이 어렸구나 <br>]]></content><category term="문효심" label="문효심"/><category term="북을 두리둥둥" label="북을 두리둥둥"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/문효심/오색채단/</id><title>문효심 - 오색채단 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:11:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:11:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B8%ED%9A%A8%EC%8B%AC/%EC%98%A4%EC%83%89%EC%B1%84%EB%8B%A8/" title="문효심 - 오색채단 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오색 채단을 <br>기린에다가 가득 실고 <br>벽도화 단계화를 <br>사면에 벌려 꼽고 <br>청학 백학은 전배서고 <br>수궁을 내려오니 <br>용왕도 황급하야 <br>문전에 배례헐제 <br>옥진부인이 들어와 <br>심청손을 부여잡고 <br>니가 나를 모르리라 <br>나는 세상에서 <br>너 낳은 곽씨로다 <br>너의 부친 많이 늙었으리라 <br>나는 죽어 귀인이 되어 <br>광한전 옥진부인이 되었난디 <br>너는 부친 눈 띠우랴고 <br>삼백석으 몸이 팔려 <br>이곳으로 들어 왔다 허기로 <br>너를 보러 내 왔노라 <br>귀와 목이 으젓 헌게 <br>너그 부친 도습허구나 <br>세상에서 못먹든 젖 <br>이제 많이 먹어 보아라 <br>심청 얼굴을 끌어다 <br>가삼 대고 문지르며 <br>아이고 내 자식아 <br>꿈이면 깰까 염려로구나 <br>심청이 그제야 <br>모친인 줄 짐작을 허고 <br>부인의 목을 부여 안고 <br>아이고 어머니 <br>어머니 이것이 꿈이요 생시요 <br>불효여식 청이난 앞 어둔 <br>백발 부친 홀로 두고 나왔는디 <br>외로우신 아버지는 <br>뉘를 의지 허오리까 <br>내 딸 청아 우지를 마라 <br>너는 일후에 너의 부친 다시 만나 <br>즐길 날이 있으리라 <br>광한전 맡은 일이 <br>직분이 허다키로 <br>오래 지체 못 하느니라 <br>요량 소리가 쟁쟁 나더니 <br>오색 채운으로 올라가니 <br>심청이 따라 갈 수도 없고 <br>가는 모친을 우두머니 바라보며 <br>모녀 작별이 또 되는구나 <br>]]></content><category term="문효심" label="문효심"/><category term="오색채단" label="오색채단"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/문효심/위의도_장헐시구/</id><title>문효심 - 위의도 장헐시구 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:11:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:11:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B8%ED%9A%A8%EC%8B%AC/%EC%9C%84%EC%9D%98%EB%8F%84_%EC%9E%A5%ED%97%90%EC%8B%9C%EA%B5%AC/" title="문효심 - 위의도 장헐시구 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그때여 옥황상제께서 <br>사해용왕을 물러 하교 하시되 <br>오날 묘시에 유리국 심효저가 <br>물에 들터이니 <br>착실히 모셨다가 <br>인간으로 환송하라 <br>용왕등이 수명허고 내려와 <br>팔선녀들을 불러 분부하시되 <br>너희는 백옥교를 가지고 <br>인당수를 나가면 <br>인간의 심효제가 물에 들터이니 <br>착실히 모셔 오너라 <br>팔선녀들이 분부듣고 <br>백옥교를 가지고 <br>인당수를 당도허니 <br>때마침 묘시라 <br>그때의 심청이는 물에 드듯 마듯 <br>천지 명랑하고 <br>일월이 졸임커늘 <br>뜻밖에 팔선녀들이 <br>백옥교를 앞에 놓고 <br>예 허여 여짜오되 <br>저희는 남해 용궁시녀로서 <br>부왕의 분부 듣고 <br>소저를 모시러 왔사오니 <br>이 옥교를 타시옵소서 <br>심청이 여짜오되 <br>인간의 미천한 몸으로 <br>어찌 그 옥교를 타오리까 <br>만일 아니 타오시면 <br>저희는 수궁 대 죄를 <br>면치 못 할 것이니 <br>어서 타시옵소서 <br>심청이 마지 못하야 <br>옥교 위에 앉어 놓니 <br>위의도 장헐시구 <br>위의도 장헐시구 <br>천상 선관 선녀들이 <br>심소저를 보랴허고 <br>태을진학을 타고 <br>안기상 구름 타고 <br>적송자는 학을 타 <br>청의 동자 홍의 동자 <br>쌍쌍이 벌였난듸 <br>월궁항아 마고선녀 <br>남악부인 팔선녀들이 <br>좌우로 벌였난듸 <br>풍악을 갖추울 제 <br>왕자진의 봉피래 <br>니나노 나노 불고 <br>곽처사의 죽장고는 <br>쩌지렁 쿵 정쿵 <br>장자방의 옥통소는 <br>띳띠루 띠루 디루 <br>성현자 거문고 <br>둥덩기 둥덩 <br>혜상의 해금이며 <br>곁드려서 노래헐적 <br>낭자한 풍악소리 <br>수궁이 진동 헐 제 <br>수궁 폐궐은 <br>응천상지 삼광이요 <br>곤으 수상은 <br>비수 궁지 오복이라 <br>산호 주렴 백옥한쌍 <br>광채도 찬란허다 <br>주잔을 드릴 적으 <br>세상 음식이 아니라 <br>유리잔 호박병에 <br>천일주 가득 담고 <br>한가운데 삼천벽도를 <br>떵그렇게 꽂았으니 <br>세상에 못 본 바라 <br>삼일에 소연허고 <br>오일에 대연허여 <br>극진히 봉공헌다 <br>]]></content><category term="문효심" label="문효심"/><category term="위의도 장헐시구" label="위의도 장헐시구"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/문효심/한곳_당도하니/</id><title>문효심 - 한곳 당도하니 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:11:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:11:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B8%ED%9A%A8%EC%8B%AC/%ED%95%9C%EA%B3%B3_%EB%8B%B9%EB%8F%84%ED%95%98%EB%8B%88/" title="문효심 - 한곳 당도하니 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한 곳 당도허니 <br>이난 곳 인당수라 <br>광풍이 일어나며 <br>어룡이 싸우난 듯 <br>대천 바다 한 가운데 <br>닻 잃고 노 잃고 <br>용층줄 끊어져 <br>안개 뒤섞어져 <br>진날 갈길은 <br>천리 만리나 남고 <br>사면이 검어 <br>어둑 점그러져 <br>천지 적막헌디 <br>도사공 영좌이하 <br>황황 급급하야 <br>고사 지계를 차린다 <br>섬쌀로 밥 짓고 <br>온소 잡고 동의술 <br>오색 탕수 삼색실과를 <br>방위 찾아서 갈라놓고 <br>산돗 잡아 큰 칼 꽂아 <br>기린듯이 받쳐놓고 <br>도사공 거동보고 <br>의관을 정지쓰고 <br>북 채를 양손의 쥐고 <br>북을 두리둥 두리둥 두리둥 <br>두리둥 두리둥 둥둥둥 <br>두리둥 두리둥 둥둥 <br>헌원씨 배를 모아 <br>이제불통 헌연후의 <br>후생의 본을 받아 <br>다 각기 위업을 허니 <br>막대한 공이 아닌가 <br>하우씨 구년제수 <br>배타고 다사릴제 <br>오복에 장한공수 <br>구주로 돌아들고 <br>오자서 분노할제 <br>노가로 건네주고 <br>해상의 패한 장수 <br>오강으로 돌아들어 <br>어선대지 건네주고 <br>공명의 탈조화는 <br>동남풍 빌어내어 <br>조조으 백만대병 <br>주유로 화공을 허니 <br>배 아니면은 어이허리 <br>그저 북을 두리둥 두리둥 <br>두리둥 두리둥 둥둥둥 <br>두리둥 두리둥 둥둥 <br>주요요 경양허니 <br>도연명의 귀거래 <br>해활허니 고범주난 <br>장한의 강동거요 <br>임술지 추칠월의 <br>소통파 놀아 있고 <br>지국 총총 어사와 허니 <br>고여승유 무정거난 <br>어부질검 계도난이 <br>화장포난 워희월여 채련주요 <br>타고발선 허고보니 <br>상공선이 이 아니냐 <br>그저 북을 두리둥 두리둥 <br>두리둥 두리둥 둥둥둥 <br>두리둥 두리둥 둥둥 <br>우리 선인 스물네명 <br>상고로 위업하야 <br>경세 우경년으 <br>표백 설한을 다니다가 <br>오늘날 인당수 <br>인제수를 드리오니 <br>동해신 아명이며 <br>서해신 거승이며 <br>남해신 축룡이며 <br>북해신 흑룡이며 <br>강한 지장과 <br>천택지군이 <br>하감하여 보옵소서 <br>비렴으로 바람주고 <br>화락으로 인도하야 <br>환란없이 도웁시고 <br>백천만금 퇴를 내어 <br>돛대 위에 봉기 꼽고 <br>봉기 위에 연화 받게 <br>점지허여 주옵소서 <br>고사를 다 모신후에 <br>심청이 물에 들으라 <br>성화 같이 재촉을 허니 <br>심청이 기가 막혀 <br>여보시오 선임네 <br>도화동이 어디쯤이나 있소 <br>도사공이 나서더니 <br>손을 들어서 가르키난디 <br>도화동은 저기 운애만 <br>자욱 헌디가 <br>거기가 도화동이요 <br>심청이 기가 막혀 <br>두손을 합장 허고 <br>뱃장 안에 엎더지며 <br>아이고 아버지 <br>불효여식 청이난 <br>요만끔도 생각을 마옵시고 <br>어서 어서 눈을 떠서 <br>대명천지 다시 보고 <br>좋은디 장가들어 <br>아들 낳고 딸을 낳아 <br>후사를 전케허옵소서 <br>어서 급히 물어 들어라 <br>심청이 거동봐라 <br>바람 맞은 병신처럼 <br>이리 비틀 저리 비틀 <br>정신없이 나서더니 <br>초마자락 무릅쓰고 <br>샛별 같은 눈을 감고 <br>보금이를 아드드드드득 <br>만경창파 갈매기 격으로 <br>떳따 물에가 <br>풍 <br>빠져놓니 <br>행화는 <br>광풍으 흐날리고 <br>명월은 해문에 <br>잠겼도다 <br>영좌도 울고 <br>사공도 울음을 울고 <br>격군 화장이 모다 운다 <br>장사도 좋거니와 <br>우리가 연년이 <br>사람을 사다가 <br>이 물에다가 넣고 가니 <br>이 후사가 어찌 <br>잘 될리가 있것느냐 <br>닻 감어라 <br>어기야 어기야 <br>어기여 어기야 아 어기야 <br>우후 청강 맑은 흥을 <br>묻노라 저 백구야 <br>홍요 월색이 어느 곳고 <br>일강세우 노평생을 <br>너는 어찌 한가 허느냐 <br>범피창파 높이 떠서 <br>도용 도용 떠나간다 <br>]]></content><category term="문효심" label="문효심"/><category term="한곳 당도하니" label="한곳 당도하니"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/문효심/배의_밤이_몇밤이며/</id><title>문효심 - 배의 밤이 몇밤이며 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:11:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:11:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B8%ED%9A%A8%EC%8B%AC/%EB%B0%B0%EC%9D%98_%EB%B0%A4%EC%9D%B4_%EB%AA%87%EB%B0%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%A9%B0/" title="문효심 - 배의 밤이 몇밤이며 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[배의 밤이 <br>몇 밤이며 <br>물으 날이 <br>몇 날이나 되든고 <br>무정헌 사오삭을 <br>물과 같이 흘러가니 <br>금풍삽이 석기허고 <br>옥우곽이 쟁영이라 <br>낙하여 고목 제비허고 <br>추수공장천 일색이라 <br>강안이 귤논 황금이 천편 <br>노화으 풍기허니 <br>백설이 만점이라 <br>신포세류 지난 잎은 <br>만강 추풍 흐날리고 <br>옥루 청풍이 불었난디 <br>외로울사 어선들은 <br>등불을 돋우키고 <br>어가로 화답허니 <br>돋우나니 수심이요 <br>일발 천산에 <br>봉봉이 칼날되여 <br>보이난 것 간장이라 <br>일락장사추색원허니 <br>부지하처 조상군고 <br>송옥으 비추부가 <br>이여서 슬프리요 <br>동녀를 실었으니 <br>진시황의 채약밴가 <br>방사는 없었으나 <br>한무제의 구선인가 <br>지러 내가 죽자허니 <br>선인들이 수직을 허고 <br>살아실려 가랴고 허니 <br>고국이 창망이로구나 <br>]]></content><category term="문효심" label="문효심"/><category term="배의 밤이 몇밤이며" label="배의 밤이 몇밤이며"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/문효심/범피중류/</id><title>문효심 - 범피중류 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:11:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:11:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B8%ED%9A%A8%EC%8B%AC/%EB%B2%94%ED%94%BC%EC%A4%91%EB%A5%98/" title="문효심 - 범피중류 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[심청을 배 안에 싣고 <br>행선을 허여 가는디 <br>범피중류 <br>둥덩실 떠나간다 <br>망망헌 창해이며 <br>탕탕헌 물결이라 <br>백빈주 갈매기는 <br>홍요안으 날아들고 <br>삼강의 기러기는 <br>한수로 돌아든다 <br>요량헌 남은 소리 <br>어적이 여기련만 <br>곡종인불견의 <br>수봉만 푸르렀다 <br>애내성중 만고수는 <br>날로 두고 이름인가 <br>장사를 지내가니 <br>가태부 간 곳 없고 <br>멱라수를 당도허니 <br>굴삼여 어복 충혼 <br>무량도 허시든가 <br>황학루를 당도허니 <br>일모행관 하처시요 <br>연파강상사인수난 <br>최호으 유적이요 <br>봉황대를 돌아드니 <br>삼산은 반락청천외요 <br>이수 중분 백로주는 <br>태백으 놀든데요 <br>심양강 당도허니 <br>백락천 일거후에 <br>비파성도 끊어졌다 <br>적벽강 당도허니 <br>소동파 놀던 풍월 <br>의구허여 있다마는 <br>조맹덕일세 <br>지웅이금의 안재재 <br>월락오제 깊은밤의 <br>고소성외 배를 매니 <br>한산사 쇠북 소리는 <br>객선의 뎅 들리 난 듯 <br>진회수를 당도허니 <br>격강의 상녀들은 <br>망국한을 모르고서 <br>연롱한수 월롱사에 <br>후정화만 부르는구나 <br>악양루 높은 집이 <br>호상으 솟아난 듯 <br>무산에 돋난 달은 <br>동정호로 비쳐오니 <br>상하천광이 <br>거울 속에 푸르렀다 <br>창호산이 아득허니 <br>황능묘 잠겼어라 <br>삼협의 잔나비는 <br>자식을 찾는 슬픈 소리 <br>천객소인으 눈물을 <br>몇몇이나 비젖든가 <br>팔경을 다 본 후로 <br>한곳을 당도허니 <br>양풍이 일어나며 <br>죽림사이로 <br>옥패소리 들리더니 <br>어떠한 두 사람이 <br>선관을 높이 쓰고 <br>신음거려 나오더니 <br>저기 가는 심소저야 <br>나의 말을 듣고가라 <br>창오산붕상수절일허여 <br>죽상체류를 내가 멸이라 <br>천추에 깊은 한을 <br>하소할 곳 없었더니 <br>오늘날 출천대효 <br>너를 보니 오죽이나 <br>흠전 허느냐 <br>요순후 기천년 <br>지금은 천자 어느 뉘며 <br>오현금 남풍시를 <br>지금까지 전허더냐 <br>수로 천리 먼 먼길을 <br>조심허여 잘 가거라 <br>이난 뉜고허니 <br>요녀순처 만고열녀 <br>이비로구나 <br>오강을 바삐 건너 <br>멱라수를 당도허니 <br>광풍이 대작하고 <br>찬 기운이 소삽더니 <br>어떤 신이 나오난디 <br>키는 구척이나 되고 <br>면여 거륜하야 <br>미간이 광활허고 <br>두 눈을 감고 <br>가죽을 무릅쓰고 <br>우루루루루 나오더니 <br>저기가는 심소저야 아아 <br>슬픈 말을 듣고 가라 <br>슬프다 우리 오왕 <br>백비으 참소 듣고 <br>촉루검 날을 쥐어 <br>목 찔러 죽인 후에 <br>가죽으로 몸을 싸 <br>이 물에 던졌더니 <br>장부에 원통함이 <br>월병의 별호험을 <br>내 일찍 눈을 빼여 <br>동문 상에다 달고 왔네 <br>세상에 나가거든 <br>내 눈 찾어 전해주소 <br>천추에 원통헌것 <br>눈 없는 것이 한이로세 <br>올연 간곳 없고 <br>물결만 우르르르 <br>출렁 출렁 <br>또한 두 신이 나오난듸 <br>슬피 통곡 우난 말이 <br>진나라 쇡임입어 <br>삼년 무관의 <br>고국을 바라보며 <br>미귀혼이 되었더니 <br>박랑 퇴성 반겨듣고 <br>속절없는 동정 달에 <br>헛춤만 추었노라 <br>뒤로오난 한사람은 <br>안색이 초췌허고 <br>형용이 고고허니 <br>이난 초나라 굴원이라 <br>죽은지 수천년의 <br>정백이 남어있어 <br>사람으 눈에 와서 보이니 <br>이도 또한 귀신이라 <br>내가 죽을 징조로다 <br>]]></content><category term="문효심" label="문효심"/><category term="범피중류" label="범피중류"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/문효심/따라간다/</id><title>문효심 - 따라간다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:11:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:11:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B8%ED%9A%A8%EC%8B%AC/%EB%94%B0%EB%9D%BC%EA%B0%84%EB%8B%A4/" title="문효심 - 따라간다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하직하고 집으로 돌아오니 <br>부친은 뛰고 궁굴고 <br>선인들 재촉을 허거늘 <br>심청이 하릴없이 <br>동네 어른들께 <br>부친을 의탁허고 <br>길을 떠나는구나 <br>따라간다 따라간다 <br>선인들을 따라간다 <br>끌리난 초마자락을 <br>거듬거듬 걷어 안고 <br>비 같이 흐르난 눈물 <br>옷깃에 모두 다 사무친다 <br>엎더지고 넘어지며 <br>천방지축 따라갈제 <br>건넌말 바라보며 <br>이진사댁 작은 아가 <br>작년 오월 단오야의 <br>앵두 따고 노던 일을 <br>니가 행여 생각느냐 <br>금년 칠월 칠석야의 <br>함끄 결교허자더니 <br>이제는 하릴 없다 <br>상침질 수 놓기을 <br>뉠가 함끄 허자느냐 <br>너히는 양친이 구존허니 <br>모시고 잘 있거라 <br>나는 오날 우리 부친 <br>슬하를 떠나 <br>죽으러 가는 길이로다 <br>동리 남녀노소 없이 <br>눈이 붙게 모다 울고 <br>하나님도 아옵신지 <br>백일은 어디 가고 <br>음운이 자욱허여 <br>청산도 찡끗난듯 <br>초목도 눈물 진듯 <br>휘늘어 져곱든 꽃이 <br>이울고저 빛을 잃고 <br>날아가는 저 제비도 <br>나직이 떠 지지지지 울고 가고 <br>춘조난 다정허여 <br>백반제송 허는 중으 묻노라 <br>저 꾀꼬리 뉘를 이별 허였는지 <br>환우성 지어 울고 <br>뜻밖에 두견이난 <br>귀촉도 귀촉도 불여 귀난 <br>가지 우 앉어 울건 마는 <br>값을 받고 팔린 몸이 <br>내가 어찌 돌아오리 <br>한 곳을 당도 하니 <br>해당화 한송이가 떨어져 <br>심청 얼굴에 부디치니 <br>꽃을 들고 허는 말이 <br>약도춘풍 불해이면 <br>하인취송 낙화래라 <br>한무제 수양 공주 <br>매화장은 있건만은 <br>죽으러 가는 몸이 <br>언제 다시 돌아오리 <br>죽고 싶어 죽으랴 만은 <br>수원수구를 어이허리 <br>질 걷는 줄을 모르고 <br>울며불며 길을 걸어 <br>강변을 당도허니 <br>선두에다 도판을 놓고서 <br>심청을 인도하는구나 <br>]]></content><category term="문효심" label="문효심"/><category term="따라간다" label="따라간다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스틸로빌_Stylo-Bille/Self_Talk_Feat_Hash_Swan/</id><title>스틸로빌_Stylo-Bille - Self Talk (Feat. Hash Swan) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:11:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:11:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B8%EB%A1%9C%EB%B9%8C_Stylo-Bille/Self_Talk_Feat_Hash_Swan/" title="스틸로빌_Stylo-Bille - Self Talk (Feat. Hash Swan) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[달고 살고 있어 타이레놀 <br>이게 절대 근본적인 <br>문제점이 아닌데도 <br>하루를 살려면 의지할 <br>수밖에 없어 약에 <br>요즘 내가 그래 하루 종일 <br>멘탈부터 온 몸이 약해 <br>내가 뭘 잘 못해서인지 <br>신경이 예민한 건지 <br>유일한 그 분도 부정한 <br>내 손을 안 잡아 주셔서인지 <br>선과 악 경계에 <br>딱 꼈나봐 중간에 <br>내가 겁쟁이라서 인건지 <br>무서운 게 당연한 건지 <br>기적을 바라지는 않지만 <br>우리가 다 같이 잘 되길 바래 <br>뱀처럼 지혜롭고 싶지만 <br>절대로 독사가 되서는 안 돼 <br>선을 쌓으려고 했는데 <br>그 밑바닥은 악이 <br>이 끝엔 선과 악 <br>내 판단 없이 <br>기다려 심판이 <br>뭐가 문제인지 <br>너넨 알 것 같아 <br>난 잘 모르겠어 <br>시작부터 끝까지 <br>뭐가 어떻게 된 거야 <br>완전 돌겠어 <br>부르고 불러도 대답은 <br>없지만 따라야돼 <br>그래도 난 그 뒷걸음을 <br>쫒아야 불안하지 않겠어 <br>its a pray for the self <br>pray for the self <br>손을 모으네 <br>talk is cheap <br>but ma soliloquy ain't like that <br>no way <br>녹음되기 전의 말은 <br>개인적인 삶의 고백 <br>yeah 그저 응답을 <br>받도록 깊게 호흡해 <br>Set me free from that worries <br>Make my weakness blurry <br>Just want that peaceful morning <br>errday errday day <br>아 pray for myself <br>손을 모으네 <br>faith my soliloquy aint <br>no cheap no way <br>Why imma do this shit <br>내 마음의 흐름을 따라서 <br>Firstly do it for the respect <br>그건 군자의 마음과 닮아서 <br>livin good life and peace love <br>멋스런 풍류를 탐색해 <br>But I still need Fame and dough <br>이 시대엔 그리 산다네 <br>내 길 맞는진 몰라도 <br>we don't make song for free <br>날 믿어준 식구들 위해 <br>찾아낼거 더 큰 의미 <br>욕심이 많지만 <br>아직 해를 입을 만치 <br>페이 받지도 않았지 <br>갈수록 열망은 커져 <br>도를 번 뒤에 <br>돈을 번다면 죽을 <br>수도 있겠지 hooh <br>바보는 이빨을 약자에게만 대 <br>위정자가 모두 쳐먹는 판국에 <br>야망 있어도 alpha male은 안돼 <br>난 다르게 내 삶을 설계할게 <br>낮은 데 거하는 강 같은 평화 <br>볼펜에 잉크가 흐르듯 살아 <br>급할 수록 돌아 느긋하게 <br>몰라주는구나 소인배와 얌체 <br>pardon my french <br>fuck you all <br>완벽친 않지만 난 더 클 걸 <br>약한 모습대로 <br>one step to heaven <br>난 랩을 쓰고나면 <br>홀로 도 닦어 <br>최고의 선은 일이 끝난 뒤 <br>마시는 한잔 술 <br>내 빅픽쳐엔 <br>야무지게 눌러찍어 <br>피땀색 N O I N 낙관을 <br>its a pray for the self <br>pray for the self <br>손을 모으네 <br>talk is cheap <br>but ma soliloquy ain't like that <br>no way <br>녹음되기 전의 말은 <br>개인적인 삶의 고백 <br>yeah 그저 응답을 <br>받도록 깊게 호흡해 <br>Set me free from that worries <br>Make my weakness blurry <br>Just want that peaceful morning <br>errday errday day <br>아 pray for myself <br>손을 모으네 <br>faith my soliloquy aint <br>no cheap no way <br>I don't wanna think anymore <br>just needa chill out <br>너무 갖고 싶었던 <br>아이팟따위 이제 안비싸 <br>결국 그건 엄말 졸라 샀지 <br>아마 40만원쯤 이었던걸로 <br>기억해 이제야 <br>I'm sorry mom <br>Yeah 이제야 I'm sorry mom <br>내 가사안에는 욕이 다였고 <br>음악은 핑계로 요긴하지 <br>그 누구도 제발 <br>내 세계로 들어오지마라던 <br>20살의 내 진짜 <br>일상은 롤이나 하지 <br>이제 내게 고민 같은 건 <br>fuck It's nothing <br>난 벌기 시작했어 이만치 <br>근데 멀었어 엄만 <br>아직도 힘드니까 <br>'till I can say like <br>엄마 거기까지 <br>엄마가 여기까지라 말하기전에 <br>내가 엄마 거기까지 <br>그때는 가보고 싶은 곳이 <br>있다면 제발 거기가길 <br>Mama 그건 얼마 <br>안 남았을 거야 아마 <br>이건 내 약속이지 <br>사실 내 고민도 아냐 <br>아직 조금 남았어 <br>해왔던 대로 조금만 기다려 <br>지금은 I don't wanna think <br>anymore needa chill out <br>]]></content><category term="스틸로빌 (Stylo-Bille)" label="스틸로빌 (Stylo-Bille)"/><category term="Self Talk (Feat. Hash Swan)" label="Self Talk (Feat. Hash Swan)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gaither_Vocal_Band/Yes_I_Know_Live/</id><title>Gaither_Vocal_Band - Yes, I Know (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:11:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:11:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gaither_Vocal_Band/Yes_I_Know_Live/" title="Gaither_Vocal_Band - Yes, I Know (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come ye sinners, lost and lonely <br>Jesus' blood can make you free. <br>For he saved the worst among you <br>When He saved a wretch like me <br><br>and I know, yes, i know, <br>Jesus' blood can make the vilest sinner clean. <br>and I know, yes, i know, <br>Jesus' blood can make the vilest sinner clean. <br><br>To the faint He giveth power <br>Through the mountains makes a away <br>Findeth water in the desert <br>Turns the night to golden day. <br><br>and I know, yes, i know, <br>Jesus' blood can make the vilest sinner clean. <br>and I know, yes, i know, <br>Jesus' blood can make the vilest sinner clean. <br><br><br>In temptation He is near thee, <br>Holds the powers of Hell at bay. <br>Guides you to the path of safety <br>Gives you grace for every day. <br><br>I't's the blood of Jesus <br>can make you clean. <br>Whoa. The blood of Jesus]]></content><category term="Gaither Vocal Band" label="Gaither Vocal Band"/><category term="Yes, I Know (Live)" label="Yes, I Know (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sheri_Easter/The_Eastern_Gate_Live/</id><title>Sheri_Easter - The Eastern Gate (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:12:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:12:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sheri_Easter/The_Eastern_Gate_Live/" title="Sheri_Easter - The Eastern Gate (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I will meet you in the morning, <br>Just inside the Eastern Gate; <br>Then be ready, faithful pilgrim, <br>Lest with you it be too late. <br><br>I will meet you in the morning, <br> I will meet you in the morning <br>Just inside the Eastern Gate over there; <br>I will meet you in the morning, <br> I will meet you in the morning, <br>I will meet you in the morning over there. <br><br>If you hasten off to glory, <br>Linger near the Eastern Gate, <br>For I’m coming in the morning; <br>So you’ll not have long to wait.]]></content><category term="Sheri Easter" label="Sheri Easter"/><category term="The Eastern Gate (Live)" label="The Eastern Gate (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이현미/언제까지나_너를_사랑해/</id><title>이현미 - 언제까지나 너를 사랑해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:18:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:18:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%98%84%EB%AF%B8/%EC%96%B8%EC%A0%9C%EA%B9%8C%EC%A7%80%EB%82%98_%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4/" title="이현미 - 언제까지나 너를 사랑해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자장 자장 자장 자장 <br>지장 자장 자장 자장 <br>너를 사랑해 언제까지나 <br>너를 사랑해 어떤 일이 닥쳐도 <br>내가 살아 있는 한 <br>너는 늘 나의 귀여운 아기 <br><br>사랑해요 어머니 언제까지나 <br>사랑해요 어머니 <br>어떤 일이 닥쳐도 <br>내가 살아 있는 한 <br>당신은 늘 나의 어머니 <br><br>너를 사랑해 언제까지나 <br>너를 사랑해 어떤 일이 닥쳐도 <br>내가 살아 있는 한 <br>너는 늘 나의 귀여운 아기 <br>자장 자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 자장]]></content><category term="이현미" label="이현미"/><category term="언제까지나 너를 사랑해" label="언제까지나 너를 사랑해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성범/비가_내리면/</id><title>김성범 - 비가 내리면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:18:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:18:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B2%94/%EB%B9%84%EA%B0%80_%EB%82%B4%EB%A6%AC%EB%A9%B4/" title="김성범 - 비가 내리면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비가 내리면 고개 들어 하늘을 봐 <br>나뭇잎에 떨어지는 빗방울 맺히네 <br>비가 내리면 서두르지 않아도 돼 <br>시간이 머뭇거리고 <br>슬그머니 생각나는 <br>솔향기가 나는 그 곳 <br><br>비가 내리면 눈을 감고 있어도 돼 <br>풀잎 위에 떨어지는 빗소리 들어봐 <br>비가 내리면 서두르지 않아도 돼 <br>시간이 느리게 가고 <br>내가 감싸 안긴 느낌 <br>숲 향기가 짙은 그 곳 <br><br>비가 내 생각을 머금었나봐]]></content><category term="김성범" label="김성범"/><category term="비가 내리면" label="비가 내리면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이현미/아가야/</id><title>이현미 - 아가야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:19:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:19:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%98%84%EB%AF%B8/%EC%95%84%EA%B0%80%EC%95%BC/" title="이현미 - 아가야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아가야 앞 산 너머 가자꾸나 <br>깊은 골짜기 막아도 <br>찔레가 막으면 헤치고 가자꾸나 <br>높은 산마루 막아도 <br>얼씨구 절씨구 넘어야 한단다 <br>닐리리 닐리리야 <br><br>아가야 앞 산 너머 가자꾸나 <br>나비가 너울너울 날아다닌단다 <br>닐니리 닐리리야 <br>아아아아 럴럴 <br>닐리리 닐리리야]]></content><category term="이현미" label="이현미"/><category term="아가야" label="아가야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김참들/봄까치꽃/</id><title>김참들 - 봄까치꽃 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:19:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:19:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%B0%B8%EB%93%A4/%EB%B4%84%EA%B9%8C%EC%B9%98%EA%BD%83/" title="김참들 - 봄까치꽃 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[봄까치꽃 피었네 <br>봄 소식을 데려 왔다네 봄까치꽃 <br>나는 그 애가 생각나네 <br>기다리고 기다린다고 <br>소식은 오지 않을 것을 <br>뻔히 알면서 기다리네 <br>봄까치꽃 피었네 <br><br>봄까치꽃 피었네 <br>봄 소식을 데려 왔다네 봄까치꽃 <br>그 애가 가르쳐준 봄꽃 <br>기다리고 기다린다고 <br>소식은 오지 않을 것을 <br>뻔히 알면서 기다리네 <br>봄까치꽃 피었네]]></content><category term="김참들" label="김참들"/><category term="봄까치꽃" label="봄까치꽃"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/광주_어린이_요들_합창단/멍게_해삼_말미잘/</id><title>광주_어린이_요들_합창단 - 멍게 해삼 말미잘 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:19:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:19:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B4%91%EC%A3%BC_%EC%96%B4%EB%A6%B0%EC%9D%B4_%EC%9A%94%EB%93%A4_%ED%95%A9%EC%B0%BD%EB%8B%A8/%EB%A9%8D%EA%B2%8C_%ED%95%B4%EC%82%BC_%EB%A7%90%EB%AF%B8%EC%9E%98/" title="광주_어린이_요들_합창단 - 멍게 해삼 말미잘 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[달빛에 흘러가는 구름 <br>별빛에 출렁대는 파도 <br>별똥별 떨어지는 바다 <br>하염없이 바라만 보네 <br>호라로우 리야 호라로우 리야 <br>호라레라 로우오우리 <br>호라로우 리야 호라로우 리야 <br>호라레라 로우오우리 <br><br>별빛에 용기를 내어 <br>내 마음 얘기하려했네 <br>그 애의 반짝이는 눈빛 <br>하염없이 바라만보네 <br>호라로우 리야 호라로우 리야 <br>호라레라 로우오우리 <br>호라로우 리야 호라로우 리야 <br>호라레라 로우오우리 <br><br>집으로 돌아오는 길에 <br>사랑해 고백하려했네 <br>그 애가 나를 바라보며 <br>멍게 해삼 말미잘 바보 <br>호라로우 리야 호라로우 리야 <br>호라레라 로우오우리 <br>호라로우 리야 호라로우 리야 <br>호라레라 로우오우리 <br>호로로우 리오로우 요로로우 <br>리오로우 요로로우 리오로우리 <br>호로로우 리오로우 요로로우 <br>리오로우 요로로우 리오오우오]]></content><category term="광주 어린이 요들 합창단" label="광주 어린이 요들 합창단"/><category term="멍게 해삼 말미잘" label="멍게 해삼 말미잘"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한국_어린이_요델_합창단/도깨비빤스_요들/</id><title>한국_어린이_요델_합창단 - 도깨비빤스 요들 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:19:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:19:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EA%B5%AD_%EC%96%B4%EB%A6%B0%EC%9D%B4_%EC%9A%94%EB%8D%B8_%ED%95%A9%EC%B0%BD%EB%8B%A8/%EB%8F%84%EA%B9%A8%EB%B9%84%EB%B9%A4%EC%8A%A4_%EC%9A%94%EB%93%A4/" title="한국_어린이_요델_합창단 - 도깨비빤스 요들 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[홀라로우 에이에이 홀라로우리 <br>홀라로우 에이에이 홀라로우리 <br>홀라로우 에이에이 홀라로우리 <br>홀라로우 휘리리리리 <br>도깨비 빤스는 튼튼해요 <br>질기고도 튼튼해요 <br>호랑이 가죽으로 만들었어요 <br>이천년 입어도 까딱없어요 <br>이천년을 입어도 까딱없다는 <br>질기고도 튼튼한 팬티이야기 <br>할머니랑 함께 부른 도깨비 빤스 <br>다시 한 번 불러본다 <br><br>도깨비 빤스는 더러워요 <br>냄새나요 더러워요 <br>호랑이 가죽으로 만들었어요 <br>이천년 동안이나 안 빨았어요 <br>이천년을 입어도 까딱없다는 <br>냄새나고 더러운 팬티이야기 <br>할머니랑 코를 막고 불렀던 노래 <br>다시 한 번 불러본다]]></content><category term="한국 어린이 요델 합창단" label="한국 어린이 요델 합창단"/><category term="도깨비빤스 요들" label="도깨비빤스 요들"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한국_어린이_요델_합창단/막대기_하나로/</id><title>한국_어린이_요델_합창단 - 막대기 하나로 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:19:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:19:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EA%B5%AD_%EC%96%B4%EB%A6%B0%EC%9D%B4_%EC%9A%94%EB%8D%B8_%ED%95%A9%EC%B0%BD%EB%8B%A8/%EB%A7%89%EB%8C%80%EA%B8%B0_%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EB%A1%9C/" title="한국_어린이_요델_합창단 - 막대기 하나로 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기차도 된다. 자동차도 된다 <br>가랑이에 막대기를 끼워 타자 <br>높은 산 만나면 비행기가 되고 <br>넓은 바다 만나면 배가 된다 <br>막대기 하나면 충분하다 <br>못 갈 곳은 없다 <br>요우리에이리 오우리에이리 <br>요우리에이리 오우리에이리 <br>요우리에이리 <br>오우리에이리 요우 <br>요우리에이리 오우리에이리 <br>요우리에이리 <br>요우 리리리요 에이리 <br>애들아 떠나자 못 갈 곳 없다 <br>막대기 하나면 충분하다 <br>애들아 떠나자 막대기 타고 <br>저 산 넘어 저 우주로]]></content><category term="한국 어린이 요델 합창단" label="한국 어린이 요델 합창단"/><category term="막대기 하나로" label="막대기 하나로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박소연/닷냥이_요들/</id><title>박소연 - 닷냥이 요들 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:19:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:19:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EB%8B%B7%EB%83%A5%EC%9D%B4_%EC%9A%94%EB%93%A4/" title="박소연 - 닷냥이 요들 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[옛날 갓날 깊고 깊은 숲속에서 <br>도깨비 닷냥이가 살았다네 <br>심심한 도깨비가 나무꾼을 만났는데 <br>다짜고짜 말을 걸었대 <br>닷 냥만 꿔 줘. 닷 냥만 꿔 줘 <br>요휘리리 리요 로우오우오우리 <br>닷 냥만 꿔 줘. 닷 냥만 꿔 줘 <br>요휘리리 리요 로우오우오우리 <br><br>맘씨 착한 나무꾼은 돈을 꿔줬대 <br>도깨비 닷냥이와 친구 먹었네 <br>어벙한 도깨비가 나무꾼을 만났을 땐 <br>다짜고짜 돈을 갚았대 <br>닷 냥 받아라 닷 냥 받아라 <br>요휘리리 리요 로우오우오우리 <br>닷 냥 받아라 닷 냥 받아라 <br>요휘리리 리요 로우오우오우리 <br><br>옛날 갓날에 그 나무꾼은 <br>도깨비가 빌린 돈을 갚고 갚으니 <br>부자가 안 될 수가 없었댄단다 <br>도깨비 닷냥이와 친구 될 사람 <br>요휘리리 리요 로우오우오우리 <br>]]></content><category term="박소연" label="박소연"/><category term="닷냥이 요들" label="닷냥이 요들"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인천_알핀로제_어린이합창단/맴맴맴/</id><title>인천_알핀로제_어린이합창단 - 맴맴맴 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:19:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:19:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EC%B2%9C_%EC%95%8C%ED%95%80%EB%A1%9C%EC%A0%9C_%EC%96%B4%EB%A6%B0%EC%9D%B4%ED%95%A9%EC%B0%BD%EB%8B%A8/%EB%A7%B4%EB%A7%B4%EB%A7%B4/" title="인천_알핀로제_어린이합창단 - 맴맴맴 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[온 가족 매미가 감나무에 앉았네 <br>맴 맴맴 맴 맴맴 맴맴맴맴 맴맴맴 <br>하루 종일 한마디로 얘길 해도 즐겁네 <br>맴 맴맴 맴 맴맴 맴맴맴맴 맴맴맴 <br>우리도 매미가 하는 얘길 다 안다네 <br>맴 맴맴 맴 맴맴 맴맴맴맴 맴맴맴 <br>온 가족 매미가 감나무에 앉았네 <br>맴 맴맴 맴 맴맴 맴맴맴맴 맴맴맴 <br>하루 종일 한마디로 얘길 해도 즐겁네 <br>]]></content><category term="인천 알핀로제 어린이합창단" label="인천 알핀로제 어린이합창단"/><category term="맴맴맴" label="맴맴맴"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인천_알핀로제_어린이합창단/도롱뇽/</id><title>인천_알핀로제_어린이합창단 - 도롱뇽 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:19:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:19:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EC%B2%9C_%EC%95%8C%ED%95%80%EB%A1%9C%EC%A0%9C_%EC%96%B4%EB%A6%B0%EC%9D%B4%ED%95%A9%EC%B0%BD%EB%8B%A8/%EB%8F%84%EB%A1%B1%EB%87%BD/" title="인천_알핀로제_어린이합창단 - 도롱뇽 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[도롱뇽은 둘리가 될 수 없다 <br>공룡이 아니니까 <br>알나리 아리아리 깔나리 아리아리 <br>알나리 깔나리 뱅글 돌고 뱅뱅뱅 <br>알나리 아리아리 깔나리 아리아리 <br>알나리 깔나리 뱅글 돌고 뱅뱅뱅 <br><br>도롱뇽은 둘리가 될 수 없다 <br>공룡이 아니니까 <br>도롱뇽은 용도 아니다 <br>불도 뿜을 수 없다 <br><br>도롱뇽은 키가 커도 도롱뇽이다 <br>도롱뇽은 살이 쪄도 도롱뇽이다 <br>]]></content><category term="인천 알핀로제 어린이합창단" label="인천 알핀로제 어린이합창단"/><category term="도롱뇽" label="도롱뇽"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/섬진강_도깨비마을/선생님_맹세/</id><title>섬진강_도깨비마을 - 선생님 맹세 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:19:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:19:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%AC%EC%A7%84%EA%B0%95_%EB%8F%84%EA%B9%A8%EB%B9%84%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%84/%EC%84%A0%EC%83%9D%EB%8B%98_%EB%A7%B9%EC%84%B8/" title="섬진강_도깨비마을 - 선생님 맹세 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[길쭉한 꽃 분꽃 뚱뚱한 꽃 명자꽃 <br>혼자 핀 해바라기 모여 핀 조팝꽃 <br>모습이 달라서 어우러진 재밌는 꽃 <br><br>빨간 꽃 맨드라미 노랑 꽃 양지꽃 <br>하양 꽃 봄맞이꽃 보라 꽃 쑥부쟁이 <br>색깔이 달라서 소중한 재밌는 꽃 <br><br>그래서 모두 이쁜 꽃 우리 반 <br>]]></content><category term="섬진강 도깨비마을" label="섬진강 도깨비마을"/><category term="선생님 맹세" label="선생님 맹세"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Miles/Lovely_Day_Acoustic_Ver_Feat_Soulman/</id><title>Miles - Lovely Day (Acoustic Ver.) (Feat. Soulman) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:20:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:20:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Miles/Lovely_Day_Acoustic_Ver_Feat_Soulman/" title="Miles - Lovely Day (Acoustic Ver.) (Feat. Soulman) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[머리 위로 저문 붉은 햇살이 <br>자꾸 우릴 재촉하는 시간이 <br>괜히 아쉬워서 그래 나 <br>서운해서 그래 나 <br>cause you <br>우리 조금만 더 같이 걸을까 <br>벌써 헤어지긴 아직 이른데 <br>여기 달이 밝을 때까지 <br>밤이 내릴 때까지 <br>with you <br>코끝에 불어오는 바람이 <br>스며드는 향기가 좋아 <br>가득히 쏟아지는 달빛에 <br>너를 안은 이 느낌 좋아 <br>갈색 빛에 물든 거릴 걷다가 <br>점점 느려지는 나의 걸음이 <br>괜히 아쉬워서 그래 나 <br>또 서운해서 그래 나 <br>cause you <br>우리 십분만 더 같이 있을까 <br>지금 보내기는 정말 싫은데 <br>여기 별이 오를 때까지 <br>긴 밤이 내릴 때까지 <br>with you <br>코끝에 불어오는 바람이 <br>스며드는 향기가 좋아 <br>가득히 쏟아지는 달빛에 <br>너를 안은 이 느낌 좋아 <br>문득 지친 날들 속에 <br>서툰 내 사랑이 흔들릴 때도 <br>절대 놓지 않을게 널 <br>잃지 않을게 널 <br>네게 약속해 너를 사랑해 <br>손끝에 닿는 너의 두볼이 <br>스며드는 숨결이 좋아 <br>살며시 눈을 감고 너에게 <br>다가가는 떨림이 좋아 <br>꼭 터질듯 한 이 순간 <br>너의 손을 꼭 잡고 <br>네게 입을 맞추는 <br>your love <br>눈을 맞추고 <br>살짝 입을 맞추는 <br>my love <br>I kiss your lips <br>I kiss your love <br>I kiss your lips <br>I kiss your lips <br>I kiss your love <br>]]></content><category term="Miles" label="Miles"/><category term="Lovely Day (Acoustic Ver.) (Feat. Soulman)" label="Lovely Day (Acoustic Ver.) (Feat. Soulman)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SE_O_세오/LIGHT/</id><title>SE_O_세오 - LIGHT - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:20:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:20:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SE_O_%EC%84%B8%EC%98%A4/LIGHT/" title="SE_O_세오 - LIGHT - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're so beautiful like shining day <br>내 맘에 허락도 없이 너 들어와 <br>우리 함께 많은 걸 나누고파 <br>그대가 있어 나의 세상은 빛이나 <br>정말 난 처음인걸 이런 이끌림 <br>너에게 어느새 다가가고 있어 <br>너는 너무 사랑스러워 <br>나도 내가 왜 이러는 건지 몰라 <br>내가 다가간 만큼 내게로 와줘 <br>나 얼마든지 기다릴 수 있어 <br>You're so beautiful like shining day <br>내 맘에 허락도 없이 너 들어와 <br>우리 함께 많은 걸 나누고파 <br>너도 나와 같은 마음 이길 <br>언젠가 날 받아주겠니 <br>널 바라만 봐도 난 행복해 <br>There is a light and <br>it is shining for you <br>그대가 있어 나의 세상은 빛이나 <br>내가 다가간 만큼 내게로 와줘 <br>나 얼마든지 기다릴 수 있어 <br>You're so beautiful like shining day <br>내 맘에 허락도 없이 너 들어와 <br>우리 함께 많은 걸 나누고파 <br>너도 나와 같은 마음 이길 <br>언젠가 날 받아주겠니 <br>널 바라만 봐도 난 행복해 <br>There is a light and <br>it is shining for you <br>그대가 있어 나의 세상은 빛이나 <br>한걸음 더 또 한걸음 더 <br>조금씩 널 향해가 <br>놀라지 않게 조심스럽게 <br>그렇게 같은 길을 걸어가 <br>두 손을 꼭 잡고서 <br>You're so beautiful like shining day <br>내 맘에 허락도 없이 너 들어와 <br>우리 함께 많은 걸 나누고파 <br>너도 나와 같은 마음 이길 <br>언젠가 날 받아주겠니 <br>널 바라만 봐도 난 행복해 <br>There is a light and <br>it is shining for you <br>그대가 있어 나의 세상은 빛이나 <br>]]></content><category term="SE O (세오)" label="SE O (세오)"/><category term="LIGHT" label="LIGHT"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Calum/Me_Diste_La_Vida/</id><title>Calum - Me Diste La Vida - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:22:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:22:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Calum/Me_Diste_La_Vida/" title="Calum - Me Diste La Vida - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[no puedo, no entiendo <br>te fuistes y ahora no te tengo <br>me pierdo, me enredo <br>pensado en aquellos momentos <br>vividos por ti <br>me hiciste sentir <br>otra ves <br><br>es cierto, lo siento <br>si soy culpable me arrepiento <br>hoy quiero y no puedo <br>decrirte todo lo que yo siento <br>si no estas aqui <br>muero eres parte de mi <br><br>es contigo que se para el tiempo <br>y ahora siento este tormento <br>porque fuiste tu <br>que me dio la ilusion del vivir <br><br>porque me diste la vida <br>no puedo estar contigo otra vez <br>no puedo estar aqui mintiendo <br>en mi soledad <br>solo puedo llorar por ti <br><br>porque me distes la vida <br>me hiciste descubrir batallas perdidas <br>me hiciste que yo fuera el dueno <br>de tu corazon <br>y ahora siento el dolor por ti <br><br>porque me distes la vida <br><br>no quiero, no siento que <br>entiendas todo mis lamentos <br>viniste y te fuiste <br>dejando un alma sin aliento <br>ya solo por ti <br>que puedo vivir otra vez <br><br>es cierto lo siento <br>si soy culpable me arrepiento <br>hoy quiero y no puedo <br>decrirte todo lo que yo siento <br>si no estas aqui <br>muero eres parte de mi <br><br>es contigo que se para el tiempo <br>y ahora siento este tormento <br>porque fuiste tu <br>que me dio la ilusion de vivir <br><br>porque me diste la vida <br>no puedo estar contigo <br>solo, otra vez <br>no puedo estar contigo estar aqui <br>mintiendo en mi soledad <br>solo puedo llorar por ti <br><br>porque me diste la vida <br>me hiciste descubrir batallas perdidas <br>me hiciste que yo fuera el <br>dueno de tu corazon <br>y ahora siento el dolor por ti <br><br>porque me diste la vida]]></content><category term="Calum" label="Calum"/><category term="Me Diste La Vida" label="Me Diste La Vida"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SM16/Work_All_Night_Feat_Redge/</id><title>SM16 - Work All Night (Feat. Redge) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:23:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:23:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SM16/Work_All_Night_Feat_Redge/" title="SM16 - Work All Night (Feat. Redge) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[yeah 삶을 전부 즐기기에 <br>주말은 너무 짧아 <br>현실에 만족하는 <br>친구들의 <br>포부는 다 작아 <br>고난 끝 도착한 <br>주말이 왔어 <br>모두 술잔을 들어 <br>난 기분이 좋아 <br>다 함께 Hi five <br>울리는 베이스 라인 <br>yeah 주말이니깐 꽉 채워 <br>Time line <br>볼륨을 키워 <br>모두 걱정을 비워 <br>고민 마 임마 뭐 이리 <br>생각이 길어 <br>허튼 생각 좀 그만 좀 해 <br>좀더 화끈하게 <br>뜨거운 밤을 보낼래 <br>오늘밤 난 숨 좀 쉬어야 돼 <br>yeah 내 핸드폰이 <br>울리던 간에 난 <br>놀고 싶어 매일 오늘같이 <br>좀더 자유롭게 <br>다 신경 끄고 놀러 갈래 <br>내 행복을 위해서 <br>쿵쾅 드럼라인 위 <br>생각을 갖다 버려 <br>쿵쾅 드럼라인 위 <br>생각을 갖다 버려 <br>walk for night <br>work all night <br>move for life <br>just have good night Yeah <br>walk for night <br>work all night <br>move for life <br>just have good night yeah <br>야 정신차려 임마 <br>지금 시계를 봐 <br>What time is now <br>주말이 벌써 다가왔네 <br>열심히 일한 모두 <br>수고 많았어 <br>지금부터 뭘 해야 되냐고 <br>물어본다면 눈앞에 <br>가득 차있는 술잔부터 <br>비우고 생각해 <br>It time to go to finale <br>우리가 바래왔던 건 그저 <br>잠깐의 여유와 조금의 휴식 <br>지금만큼은 생각을 버릴래 <br>오늘까지만 겁나게 무식한 <br>놈이 될라고 <br>너가 뭐라고 하든 <br>우린 고생했으니까 <br>쉴 필요가 있어 <br>전부다 똑같은 하루의 <br>연속 이였잖아 <br>여기까지 와서 눈치 볼 <br>필요 없잖아 <br>우리가 늘 하는 대로 놀자고 <br>all night long <br>계산은 나중에 고민해 <br>분위기 그대로 <br>쿵쾅 드럼라인 위 <br>생각을 갖다 버려 <br>쿵쾅 드럼라인 위 <br>생각을 갖다 버려 <br>walk for night <br>work all night <br>move for life <br>just have good night Yeah <br>walk for night <br>work all night <br>move for life <br>just have good night yeah <br>walk for night <br>work all night <br>move for life <br>just have good night Yeah <br>walk for night <br>work all night <br>move for life <br>just have good night yeah <br>]]></content><category term="SM16" label="SM16"/><category term="Work All Night (Feat. Redge)" label="Work All Night (Feat. Redge)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cloves/Better_Now_Acoustic/</id><title>Cloves - Better Now (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:25:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:25:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cloves/Better_Now_Acoustic/" title="Cloves - Better Now (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Then I hear you leave <br>And I'm happy <br>Just for a moment I'm free <br>Then it dawns on me <br><br>Then our time has passed <br>Now it won't last <br>And I'm getting nowhere fast <br>That's a fact <br><br>Peace to the night <br>Saw what I was really like <br>Start with a kiss <br>End with a fight <br><br>Peace come and go <br>Acting like you didn't know <br>That I have lost my head <br><br>Oooooooh <br>Oooooooh <br><br>And I'll leave <br>So I know that you have your doubts <br><br>Oooooooh <br>Oooooooh <br><br>And I'll leave <br>But I swear that I'm better now <br><br>Can you honestly <br>Live without me <br>Cause you miss the fire <br>You can't disagree <br><br>Peace to the night <br>Saw what I was really like <br>Start with a kiss <br>End with a fight <br><br>I love a fight <br><br>Ooooooooooh <br>Ooooooooooh <br><br>And I'll leave <br>So I know that you have your doubts <br><br>Oooooooh <br>Oooooooh <br><br>And I'll leave <br>But I swear that I'm better now <br><br>You gots to just find me <br>You know that I'm needy <br>You say Settle down <br>And I said Get the fuck out <br>Burn your pictures, outburst <br>I love the way you acting tough <br>And I'll never be good enough <br>I'm Just too much <br><br>Oooooooh <br>Oooooooh <br><br>Better now]]></content><category term="Cloves" label="Cloves"/><category term="Better Now (Acoustic)" label="Better Now (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Three_Feet_Of_Water/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Three Feet Of Water - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:25:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:25:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Three_Feet_Of_Water/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Three Feet Of Water - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Got a whole lot of years <br>And a whole lot of pain <br>And it all got me here <br>Where the river meets the clay <br>Rewindin' through my past <br>Tryin to find some good <br>But I can't seem to see <br>What mama always could <br><br>And that sun is shinin' down <br>On all my darker days <br>They're comin' to me now <br>As I hear the preacher say <br>In the name of the Son and the Father <br>Can I really leave it all <br>In three feet of water <br><br>I can't unbreak the laws <br>Straighten out the rules I've bent <br>Take the broken dreams and hearts <br>Make 'em all whole again <br>I been carryin' around <br>All the messes that I've made <br>But a few more steps from now <br>They'll all be washed away <br><br>And that sun is shinin' down <br>On all my darker days <br>They're comin' to me now <br>As I hear the preacher say <br>In the name of the Son and the Father <br>Who'd've thought I could leave it all <br>In three feet of water <br>Washin' over me <br>Amazing Grace the choir sings <br>And now I know what mercy's all about <br><br>And that sun is shinin' down <br>And all my darker days <br>They're nowhere to be found <br>All that preacher had to say <br>Was in the name of the Son and the Father <br>Who'd've thought I could leave it all <br>You took my cross so I could leave it all <br>In three feet of water <br>Mmm, in three feet of water <br>Mmm <br><br>So, it's that simple, huh]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Three Feet Of Water" label="Three Feet Of Water"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Were_Gonna_Ride_Again/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - We`re Gonna Ride Again - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:25:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:25:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Were_Gonna_Ride_Again/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - We`re Gonna Ride Again - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[That long gray beard hung down to his chest <br>Ol' long hair was always a mess <br>And the laugh on that man, I'll never forget <br>You could hear him from a mile away <br>Loved his Pabst Blue Ribbon and his cigarettes <br>He'd burn one down, light 'er up again <br>I still see that grin and that ol' HD <br>He'd roll it like he stole the thing <br>You know, I talked to him yesterday <br>I asked him <br><br>How's that steel horse ride on the streets of gold <br>Does the promised land have any ol' back roads <br>Ain't a doubt you've done a burnout on a cloud <br>Knowin' you, you probably laid her down <br>Have you revved it up while the angels sang <br>Did God get on ya, did He take your wings <br>You better have 'em back 'fore I get in <br>'Cause brother, we're gonna ride again <br><br>Alright <br><br>They say blood makes you related <br>But loyalty makes you kin <br>So when I called that man my brother <br>Well, I meant what I said <br>'Cause we were thick as thieves and we were hell on wheels <br>I can't begin to tell ya how it feels <br>But I speak for us all, man it hurts like hell <br>We miss your smilin' face <br>We'll saddle up again one day <br>Until then <br><br>How's that steel horse ride on the streets of gold <br>Does the promised land have any ol' back roads <br>Ain't a doubt you've done a burnout on a cloud <br>Knowin' you, you probably laid her down <br>Have you revved it up while the angels sang <br>Did God get on ya, did He take your wings <br>You better have 'em back 'fore I get in <br>'Cause brother, we're gonna ride again <br><br>Man, you're more than a memory, more than a friend <br>Man, you'll always be family, we'll never forget <br>Gonna see you again someday <br>Hell yeah, we're gonna rock that house <br>When we get through the gates <br>How's that steel horse ride on the streets of gold <br>Does the promised land have any ol' back roads <br>Ain't a doubt you've done a burnout on a cloud <br>Knowin' you, you probably laid her down <br>Have you revved it up while the angels sang <br>Did God get on ya, did He take your wings <br>You better get 'em back 'fore I get in <br>'Cause brother, we're gonna ride again <br><br>We're gonna ride again <br><br>We miss ya, brother]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="We`re Gonna Ride Again" label="We`re Gonna Ride Again"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/The_Devil_Dont_Sleep/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - The Devil Don`t Sleep - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:25:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:25:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/The_Devil_Dont_Sleep/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - The Devil Don`t Sleep - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br>He never shuts his eyes <br>You never hear him creepin' <br>Yeah <br><br>Battle scars on my heart <br>Lord knows this war ain't over, no <br>It's just gettin' started <br>Just when you thought you had him beat <br>He's on your shoulder <br>He's in your ear, he's whisperin' <br>Lyin' again, and again, and again <br>You tell yourself he'll leave you alone <br>You turn your back, and brother man, it's on <br><br>Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br>He never shuts his eyes <br>You never hear him creepin' <br>Heaven knows he's hell bent on me <br>Shackles and chains <br>Thank God that He can break me free <br>'Cause Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br><br>He's at your door, don't let him in <br>He'll lie, he'll steal, he'll kill, he'll win <br>Just ask me, I've been there <br>All you'll have left is a desperate prayer <br>You pray to God He'll save your soul <br>Like He has a thousand times before <br><br>Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br>He never shuts his eyes <br>You never hear him creepin' <br>Heaven knows he's hell bent on me <br>Shackles and chains <br>Thank God that He can break me free <br>'Cause Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br><br>The devil don't sleep, no <br>Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br>He never shuts his eyes <br>You never hear him creepin' <br>Heaven knows he's hell bent on me <br>Shackles and chains <br>Thank God that He can break me free <br><br>Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br>He never shuts his eyes <br>You never hear him creepin' <br>Heaven knows he's hell bent on me <br>Shackles and chains <br>Thank God that He can break me free <br>'Cause Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br><br>The devil don't sleep <br>The devil don't sleep, yeah]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="The Devil Don`t Sleep" label="The Devil Don`t Sleep"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Bullet_In_A_Bonfire/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Bullet In A Bonfire - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:25:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:25:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Bullet_In_A_Bonfire/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Bullet In A Bonfire - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know the stories behind the bruises <br>When I've been the shoulder <br>You've been the reason for her tears <br>And her tellin' you it's over's useless <br>You keep callin' her phone, drivin' by when I'm not here <br>She's beggin' me not to lose my temper <br>Lord, I've tried, but my patience is runnin' thin <br>The best thing you can do is forget her <br>'Cause so help me God, if you ever touch that girl again <br><br>You cross that line, boy and there ain't no comin' back <br>I'm a crazy train, son, and you caught up in the tracks <br>You've got me growlin' like a pit bull, brother <br>I'm about to lock my jaws <br>I'm a time bomb tickin' a real live wire <br>Boy a shot in the dark, I'm a bullet in a bonfire <br>I'm a bullet in a bonfire <br><br>I know you don't know my story <br>But I know your's <br>And you probably should've read a page or two <br>'Cause if you think you're a badass on a lady <br>Boy, you oughta see a grown ass man on a punk ass joke like you <br><br>You cross that line, boy and there ain't no comin' back <br>I'm a crazy train, son, and you caught up in the tracks <br>You've got me growlin' like a pit bull, brother <br>I'm about to lock my jaws <br>I'm a time bomb tickin' a real live wire <br>Boy a shot in the dark, I'm a bullet in a bonfire <br>Yeah, I'm a bullet in a bonfire <br><br>Now, I'm gonna let you think it's over <br>But little do you know, the fun is just about to start <br>'Cause I see you lookin' over your shoulder <br>And I see you tryin' to act like you don't hear my footsteps in the dark <br><br>You cross that line, boy and there ain't no comin' back <br>I'm a crazy train, son, and you caught up in the tracks <br>You've got me growlin' like a pit bull, brother <br>I'm about to lock my jaws <br>I'm a time bomb tickin' a real live wire <br>Boy a shot in the dark, I'm a bullet in a bonfire <br><br>Yeah, I'm a bullet in a bonfire <br>Yeah, I'm a bullet in a bonfire <br>And you think it's over]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Bullet In A Bonfire" label="Bullet In A Bonfire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Outlaw_In_Me/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Outlaw In Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:25:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:25:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Outlaw_In_Me/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Outlaw In Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She says, Baby what's that scar from <br>I said, Girl, you don't wanna know <br>She said, What about this one or that one <br>Girl, that was a long time ago <br>She kisses and traces every one with her hands <br>The look on her face says she understands <br><br>My baby don't try to change me <br>'Cause she knows <br>This is the way that God made me <br>She gets every flaw, my rebel heart, every tattoo, every scar <br>She's in love with the outlaw in me <br><br>She knows I roll with a rough crowd <br>And we get wild time to time <br>She knows I won't lay my guns down <br>I never run from a fight <br><br>My baby don't try to change me <br>She knows <br>This is the way that God made me <br>She gets every flaw, my rebel heart, every tattoo, every scar <br>She's in love with the outlaw in me <br><br>Yeah <br>Alright <br><br>That girl knows that she's got me <br>And prays one day I'll settle down <br>And I just thank God she loves me <br>Even when I don't know how <br><br>My baby don't try to change me <br>She knows <br>This is the way that God made me <br>She gets every flaw, my rebel heart, every tattoo, every scar <br>She's in love with the outlaw in me <br><br>She's in love <br>With the outlaw <br>In me]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Outlaw In Me" label="Outlaw In Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Baby_Be_Crazy/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Baby Be Crazy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:25:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:25:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Baby_Be_Crazy/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Baby Be Crazy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, you know they say <br>They say that I'm a rollin' stone <br>Girl, that boy's a dead end road <br>Yeah, you're better off alone <br>And I know I can't say <br>Girl, I can't say they're wrong <br>I'm pretty set in my ways <br>But maybe it's time that changed <br>And all you wanna know is <br>What's it gonna take <br><br>You'd have to be crazy to love me <br>Oh, but I wish you would <br>You'd have to be outta your mind <br>But deep inside, I think you could <br>Be the only chance in hell to save me from myself <br>So come on save me, oh yeah <br>Baby, be crazy <br><br>I know you say <br>You say you're gonna hang on <br>To this train wreck, baby <br>So you think you're that strong <br>Deep down, what I want <br>I want you to tie me down <br>I want so bad to trust you <br>Baby, don't burn me now <br>All we can do is try <br>I ain't tryin' to say goodbye <br><br>You'd have to be crazy to love me <br>Oh, but I wish you would <br>You'd have to be outta your mind <br>But deep inside, I think you could <br>Be the only chance in hell to save me from myself <br>So come on save me, oh yeah <br>Baby, be crazy <br><br>Yeah, oh <br><br>You'd have to be crazy to love me <br>Oh, but I wish you would <br>You'd have to be outta your damn mind <br>But deep inside, I think you could <br>Be the only chance in hell to save me from myself <br>So come on save me <br>Yeah baby, c'mon save me, yeah <br>Baby, be crazy <br>Baby, be crazy <br>Oh baby, be crazy <br>Yeah, oh]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Baby Be Crazy" label="Baby Be Crazy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Way_Back/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Way Back - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:25:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:25:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Way_Back/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Way Back - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I guess some things never change <br>It's been a while since I been around <br>It still feels like goodbye comin' home <br>To what's left of our hometown <br>Stopped by and I saw momma, first thing she said <br>You know your girl's home too <br>Ain't been in town ten minutes and the grapevine's <br>All about me and you <br>'Cause baby we go <br><br>Way back <br>Me and you and this town <br>We been through it <br>You could say that <br>I'm still the same ol' boy in love <br>With the same ol' flame that got away <br>And never gave my heart back <br>Aww, and that same ol' flame burns <br>Like it was burnin' way back <br><br>It's burnin' way back <br>Got a call from your best friend, Becky <br>Says you're hangin out at her place <br>Guess you heard I was home and you wouldn't mind takin' <br>A ride for old time's sake <br>Pulled up, lost my breath <br>How'd you get more beautiful, lemme getcha door <br>Yeah, that shotgun seat's still yours <br>Your bare feet up on the dashboard <br>Girl, you take me <br><br>Way back <br>Me and you and this town <br>We been through it <br>You could say that <br>I'm still the same ol' boy in love <br>With the same ol' flame that got away <br>And never gave my heart back <br>Aww, and that same ol' flame burns <br>Like it was burnin' way back <br><br>Way back <br>Take a left at the Baptist church <br>Had our first kiss in the back <br>Cross the tracks, take a right where I kissed you goodbye <br>Didn't have to be our last <br>So girl, I came back <br>When it comes to you and me, girl <br>You could say that <br>Goodbye ain't never meant a thing <br>And we go <br><br>Way back <br>Me and you and this town <br>We been through it <br>You could say that <br>I'm still the same ol' boy in love <br>With the same ol' flame that got away <br>And never gave my heart back <br>Aww, and that same ol' flame burns <br>Like it was burnin' way back <br><br>Like it was burnin' way back]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Way Back" label="Way Back"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/In_My_Head/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - In My Head - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:25:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:25:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/In_My_Head/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - In My Head - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, I watched the sun come up on auburn hair across my chest <br>Couple coffee cups with just a little wine left <br>I had to smile 'cause you still got that bottle in your hand <br>Last night's a movie playin' over and over <br>All in my head <br>All in my head, baby <br>We talked for hours, fell in love with everything you said <br>About our exes, about Jesus in between some sips <br>You said so sexy, with your lips about an inch away <br>You wanna kiss me, don't you, whaddaya say <br>You're in my head <br>All in my head, baby <br><br>You got me thinkin' crazy, this ain't me, I know where it ends <br>And this has got too good to be true written all over it <br>I'm takin' this leap of faith, if I go down in flames <br>We made a memory that won't go away <br>You're in my head <br>All in my head, baby <br><br>You sleep so pretty up against me in this truck bed <br>Your little hand's inside of mine, and it's a perfect fit <br>And I'm in love with you all over me in every way <br>And I wouldn't be sayin' this if you were awake <br>You're in my head <br>All in my head, baby <br><br>You got me thinkin' crazy, this ain't me, I know where it ends <br>And this has got too good to be true written all over it <br>I'm takin' this leap of faith, if I go down in flames <br>We made a memory that won't go away <br>You're in my head <br>All in my head, baby <br><br>When you woke up, I saw you smile when you looked back at me <br>Said you missed me, I forgot how to breathe <br>You're in my head <br><br>What am I gon' do with you <br>You're in my head <br><br>You got me thinkin' crazy, this ain't me, I know where it ends <br>And this has got too good to be true written all over it <br>I'm takin' this leap of faith, if I go down in flames <br>We made a memory that won't go away <br>You're in my head <br>All in my head, baby <br><br>You're in my head <br>All in my head]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="In My Head" label="In My Head"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Tried_To_Tell_Ya/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Tried To Tell Ya - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:25:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:25:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Tried_To_Tell_Ya/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Tried To Tell Ya - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's four in the mornin', under ol Georgia <br>Blue lights in the rearview <br>Your blue eyes wide open like <br>Boy, what you tryin' to do <br><br>I think that left turn lost em <br>And it's turnin' you on <br>You're climbin' over the console <br>So I'm guessin' it's on <br><br>All right, all right You're lovin' this fast lane life <br>Don't lie, don't lie You don't wanna say goodnight <br><br>I tried to tell ya I was crazy <br>Tried to tell ya that I lost my mind <br>Tried to tell ya I was nothin' but trouble, oh babe <br>Yeah, but baby you thought I was a liar <br>Now you got yourself a situation and got ya fallen for a renegade <br>You can't blame meif you try, you'll never change me <br>Yeah Itried to tell ya I was crazy <br><br>Middle of the night, I'm outside in your drive and baby let's go <br>Didn't call or nothin', just showed up and told you East Diamond Road <br>Got you head over heels girl, ain't this a trip <br>Just ridin' round, yeah you're lovin' this bad boy shit <br><br>Itried to tell ya I was crazy <br>Tried to tell ya that I lost my mind <br>Tried to tell ya I was nothin' but trouble, oh babe <br>Yeah, but baby you thought I was a liar <br>Now you got yourself a situation and had ya fallen for a renegade <br>You can't blame meif you tried, never save me <br>Yeah Itried to tell ya I was crazy <br><br>All right, all right You're lovin' this fast lane life <br>Don't lie, don't lie You don't wanna say goodnight <br>All right, all right And I think I want this right <br>The life, the life And I'll never say goodbye <br><br>Itried to tell ya I was crazy <br>Tried to tell you I was outta my mind <br>Tried to tell you I was nothin' but trouble, baby <br>Yeah but baby, you saved my life <br>Now we got ourselves a situation <br>And now you're runnin' with a renegade <br>You can't blame me She never tried to change me <br>Yeah I'll admit it I was crazy]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Tried To Tell Ya" label="Tried To Tell Ya"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Its_About_To_Get_Dirty/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - It`s About To Get Dirty - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:25:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:25:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Its_About_To_Get_Dirty/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - It`s About To Get Dirty - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Weatherman says it's gonna rain <br>Don't worry girl won't change a thing <br>Yeah we still got plans tonight <br>We gonn' kick it, dancin', givin' baby rain or shine <br><br>Leave your Sunday best at home <br>Be last time you wear what you got on <br>Bikini top cut off jeans <br>Damn, baby girl you know you lookin' mean <br><br>She said how we gonna make it through the mudhole <br>Whatch ya think I got swampers on my truck for <br><br>It's about to get dirty in the dirty south <br>'Bout to show you what it's all about <br>Don't worry, there's a rowdy crowd <br>We ain't scared, we still throwin' down <br><br>We gonna tap that keg <br>Locked at five <br>We gonna' crank that country <br>Pass out shots <br>And get thirsty <br><br>Let it rain, let it rain, let it rain <br>It's about to get dirty <br><br>There's just somethin' 'bout a good old flood <br>Watching that red clay turn to mud <br>Slinging up, slam past the doors <br>Like a new paint job on a 4x4 <br><br>Girl you gonna have a good ol' time <br>Can't let a little bit of rain change your mind <br>Let your hair down, coffin boots <br>For once in your life let yourself cut loose <br><br>Gonna get muddy from head to toe <br>Cleanin' off, skinny dipping in the swimming hole <br><br>It's about to get dirty in the dirty south <br>'Bout to show you what it's all about <br>Don't worry, there's a rowdy crowd <br>We ain't scared, we still throwin' down <br><br>We gonna tap that keg <br>Locked at five <br>We gonna' crank that country <br>Pass out shots <br>And get thirsty <br><br>Let it rain let it rain let it rain <br>It's about to get dirty <br><br>Girl your whole life's 'bout to change <br>Bad times and muddy water let me hear you say <br>Let it rain, let it rain, let it rain <br><br>It's about to get dirty in the dirty south <br>'Bout to show you what it's all about <br>Don't worry, there's a rowdy crowd <br>We ain't scared, we still throwin' down <br><br>We gonna tap that keg <br>Locked at five <br>We gonna' crank that country <br>Pass out shots <br>And get thirsty <br><br>Let it rain, let it rain, let it rain <br>Everybody get thirsty <br>Let it rain, let it rain, let it rain <br>Listen 'bout to get dirty <br>Listen 'bout to get dirty <br>C'mon <br><br>Nasty]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="It`s About To Get Dirty" label="It`s About To Get Dirty"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Bro_Code/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Bro Code - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:25:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:25:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Bro_Code/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Bro Code - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look atcha, girl <br>Standin' in my doorway <br>Rockin' them curls <br>And them cut off daisies, man <br>She called me up <br>Can I come over, boy <br>I'm bored to death <br>And I'm all alone <br>And <br><br>She only drinks when she's lonely <br>She only gets stoned when you ain't home <br>And I know bro code and I ain't breakin' it <br>But bro, you got yourself a situation, bro <br>You better get your girl home, boy <br>You better take yourself home, boy <br>You better tell her you love her, you need her <br>'Cause if you don't, she's 'bout to be long gone, bro <br><br>I opened the door <br>And she gets to talkin' <br>Talkin' 'bout he's controllin' me <br>And tryin to hold me down <br>It's gettin old, man <br>She's ready to roll, man <br>And I don't want to say <br>I told you so, man <br>'Cause <br><br>She only drinks when she's lonely <br>She only gets stoned when you ain't home <br>And I know bro code and I ain't breakin' it <br>But bro, you got yourself a situation, bro <br>You better get your girl home, boy <br>You better take yourself home, boy <br>You better tell her you love her, you need her <br>'Cause if you don't, she's 'bout to be long gone, bro <br><br>Better show that girl a good time <br>If you don't it's gon' be goodbye <br>And if you take it for granted <br>You hand her to another man <br>It's a matter of time, bro <br>It's a matter of time <br><br>Now, I know it ain't my business <br>But I gotta insist that <br>If this was somebody else <br>Your deal is already finished because <br>Bro code goes out the window <br>Just be glad it's me lettin' you know, bro <br>'Cause <br><br>She only drinks when she's lonely <br>She only gets stoned when you ain't home <br>And I know bro code and I ain't breakin' it <br>But bro, you got yourself a situation, bro <br>You better get your girl home, boy <br>You better take yourself home, boy <br>You better tell her you love her, you need her <br>'Cause if you don't, she's 'bout to be long gone, bro <br><br>Better show that girl a good time <br>If you don't it's gon' be goodbye <br>And if you take it for granted <br>You hand her to another man <br>It's a matter of time, bro <br>It's a matter of time, bro]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Bro Code" label="Bro Code"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Smokin_Gun/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Smokin` Gun - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:25:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:25:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Smokin_Gun/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Smokin` Gun - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's 2 AM and that cell phone's ringin' <br>Yeah, sounds like you been sippin' on somethin' <br>It was in the way I heard you say, hey baby <br>Yeah, you 'bout as subtle as a freight train comin' <br>And I know what's next <br>You'll be knockin' on my door <br>Standin' there in that dress <br>What are you waitin' for <br><br>Pull the trigger on a point blank kiss <br>This close you better never miss <br>Heart beatin' like a bullet into my chest <br>Bitin' my lip and wreckin' my bed <br>But Cinderella never sees the sun <br>You'll be gone before mornin' comes <br>Like to love, but you love to run <br>You're too hot to hold <br>Baby, you're a smokin' gun <br><br>Yeah, you think you got it like Tony Montana <br>Callin' these shots like the world is yours <br>And you got me hooked, but let me turn them tables <br>I ain't the only one comin back for more <br>Little smile on your face <br>You're beggin' me to play along <br>So, if we're sayin' it's a game <br>Then I'm guessin' this is game on <br><br>Pull the trigger on a point blank kiss <br>This close you better never miss <br>Heart beatin' like a bullet into my chest <br>Bitin' my lip and wreckin' my bed <br>But Cinderella never sees the sun <br>You'll be gone before mornin' comes <br>Like to love, but you love to run <br>You're too hot to hold <br>Baby, you're a smokin' gun <br><br>You're like a forty four mag with one bullet in it <br>It's a dangerous game, but I can't help but spin it <br>Knowin' one day it's gonna end bad <br>But it's too late, I got it cocked back <br><br>Pull the trigger on a point blank kiss <br>This close you better never miss <br>Heart beatin' like a bullet into my chest <br>Bitin' my lip and wreckin' my bed <br>But Cinderella never sees the sun <br>You'll be gone before mornin' comes <br>Like to love, but you love to run <br>You're too hot to hold <br>Baby, you're a smokin' gun <br><br>Yeah <br>Pull the trigger]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Smokin` Gun" label="Smokin` Gun"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/You_Could_Be_That_Girl/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - You Could Be That Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:25:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:25:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/You_Could_Be_That_Girl/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - You Could Be That Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well I'm looking for a Bonnie <br>Lookin' for a PIC <br>A lil partner in crime <br>Come hell or high water <br>She's down <br>She's ridin with me <br>Lil miss watch for blue lights <br>While I drive, you can hold that45 <br>Go down in a blaze of glory <br>I always loved that story <br><br>Now, you could be that <br>You could be that <br>You could be that girl <br>And I can see that good girl gone bad <br>You could be that girl <br><br>I bet your daddy said you could be anything <br>Anything you wanted to be ha <br>Bet he never saw a renegade comin' <br>You're a lady <br>You know how to hit your knees <br>I need a girl who knows the good Lord <br>I need a girl who's gonna pray for me <br>Yeah <br><br>You could be that <br>You could be that <br>You could be that girl <br>And I can see that good girl gone bad <br>You could be that girl <br><br>Hot as a pistol <br>You got that rebel potential <br>Hop on this ol' moto'cycle <br>Baby, let's make it official <br>Let's ride <br><br>Baby girl let's ride <br><br>You could be that <br><br>You could be that <br><br>You could be that girl <br><br>And I can see that good girl gone bad <br>You could be that girl <br><br>Yeah <br><br>Yeah you could you be <br>What I need <br>Hey baby, you can be mine <br>Ohh <br>You could be that girl <br>Ohhh <br>I can see that]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="You Could Be That Girl" label="You Could Be That Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/The_Weekend/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - The Weekend - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:25:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:25:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/The_Weekend/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - The Weekend - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tick tock I'm on the clock <br>And I'm feeling like this job's <br>Just 9 to 5 ing my life away <br>It's like I'm back in school <br>And I'm in the last class <br>And I'm passing time until the bell rang <br>Having visions of summertime <br>But wait a minute, this is later tonight <br>Trying to make some tailgating song <br>Up in the moonlight and by the way <br>It's payday <br><br>Live it up for the weekend <br>Pull it up, have the time of your life <br>Take a shot for the regret <br>Double up and it's bound <br>To get double wild <br>Hey ladies let your hair down <br>We know ain't nobody scared now, hell nah <br>Do your thing like it's spring break <br>Wake and bake and we at it again <br>Live it up for the weekend <br><br>Backwoods looking like Panama City <br>Bunch of jacked up trucks and bikinis <br>Got a yeti full of good ideas <br>Ain't worried about driving gonna stay right here <br><br>Live it up for the weekend <br>Pull it up, have the time of your life <br>Take a shot for the regret <br>Double up and it's bound <br>To get double wild <br>Hey ladies let your hair down <br>We know ain't nobody scared now, hell nah <br>Do your thing like it's spring break <br>Wake and bake and we at it again <br>Live it up for the weekend <br><br>Somebody said somethin' 'bout church on Sunday, Amen <br>Somebody said somethin' 'bout work on Monday <br>Don't say it again <br><br>Live it up for the weekend <br>Pull it up, have the time of your life <br>Take a shot for the regret <br>Double up and it's bound <br>To get double wild <br>Hey ladies let your hair down <br>We know ain't nobody scared now, hell nah <br>Do your thing like it's spring break <br>Wake and bake and we at it again <br>Live it up for the weekend <br><br>Live it up <br>Live it up for the weekend, c'mon <br>Live it up <br>Live it up for the weekend <br>Live it up <br>Live it up for the weekend <br>Live it up <br>Live it up for the weekend]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="The Weekend" label="The Weekend"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/The_Ones_That_Like_Me/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - The Ones That Like Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:26:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:26:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/The_Ones_That_Like_Me/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - The Ones That Like Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh yeah <br>Ain't gonna lie, I can count on both hands <br>My down to ride 'til the day I die friends <br>To get them, I'd like to think <br>That I'm few and far between <br>Guys like me, you want in an alley with ya <br>Up a creek, ain't a doubt I'm gonna paddle with ya <br>Go to bat, go to church, go to battle with ya <br>They can say what they want about me, but <br><br>The ones that need me got me <br>The ones that doubt me can't stop me <br>Even the ones that said forget him <br>You can bet they ain't forgot me <br>Either wanna hit me or hold me <br>Those that hate me don't know me <br>And the ones that don't trust anybody trust me <br>Yeah, the ones that like me love me <br><br>Speak my mind, don't mind who's listenin' <br>I'll ask forgiveness, 'fore I ask permission <br>Least with me you know what you're gettin' <br>You may not get a thing about me, but <br><br>The ones that need me got me <br>The ones that doubt me can't stop me <br>Even the ones that said forget him <br>You can bet they ain't forgot me <br>Either wanna hit me or hold me <br>Those that hate me don't know me <br>And the ones that don't trust anybody trust me <br>Yeah, the ones that like me love me <br><br>Yeah, they love me <br>And I ain't perfect, I'm a simple man <br>I got a sinner's mind, but I can fold my hands <br>I ain't afraid to pray and I do know who I am, yeah <br><br>And the ones that need me got me <br>Ones that doubt me can't stop me <br>Even the ones that said forget him <br>Bet your ass they ain't forgot me <br>Either wanna hit me or hold me <br>Those that hate me don't know me <br>And the ones that don't trust anybody trust me <br>Yeah, the ones that like me love me <br><br>The ones that like me love me <br><br>And if you don't <br>Probably a pretty good chance I don't like you either]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="The Ones That Like Me" label="The Ones That Like Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Rockin_Chairs/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Rockin` Chairs - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:26:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:26:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Rockin_Chairs/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Rockin` Chairs - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Now and then I see old timers talkin' <br>All day long relivin' them good ol' days <br>Like it never gets old <br>And it's the same old stories <br>Got me wonderin' if it's going to be us one day <br>Better live this one life we got oh <br><br>'Cause these are the days <br>That are going to fly by like lightning so they say <br>These are the nights yeah <br>The good times that we left the wild side out to play <br>These are the Sunday mornings <br>We talked to the Lord, get right with the man upstairs <br><br>Get back to rock it out <br>So we can say we were there <br>When we talk about it <br>In our rockin' chairs <br><br>C'mon ya'll we got memories to make <br>Some cold beers to drink <br>And some songs we gotta live out loud <br>Going to be some good hearts breakin' <br>Bunch of mistakes <br>Maybe some day we'll figure it out <br>But right now it's all about <br>Going all the way <br><br>These are the days <br>That are going to fly by like lightning so they say <br>These are the nights yeah <br>The good times that we left the wild side out to play <br>These are the Sunday mornings <br>We talked to the Lord, get right with the man upstairs <br><br>Get back to rock it out <br>So we can say we were there <br>When we talk about it <br>In our rockin' chairs <br>In our rockin' chairs <br><br>We gotta crank it up to ten and then some <br>Go way too far <br>Too fast, too hard <br>And have too much fun <br><br>These are the days <br>That are going to fly by like lightning, so they say <br>These are the times of our lives <br>We ain't got none to waste <br><br>These are the days <br>That are going to fly by like lightning so they say <br>These are the nights yeah <br>The good times that we left the wild side out to play <br>These are the Sunday mornings <br>We talked to the Lord, get right with the man upstairs <br><br>Get back to rock it out <br>So we can say we were there <br>When we talk about it <br>In our rockin' chairs <br>In our rockin' chairs <br>In our rockin' chairs]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Rockin` Chairs" label="Rockin` Chairs"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/You_Promised_Demo/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - You Promised (Demo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:26:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:26:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/You_Promised_Demo/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - You Promised (Demo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She was crying out my name <br>Standing in the driveway <br>Little bare feet wearing her cotton dress in my way <br>I still see the rain chasing tears down her face <br><br>It was back in October when I said it's over and hid <br>Behind the door <br>Behind the shame of my conviction <br>Beside myself <br>Beside some empty pill prescription <br><br>Can hear her screamin' now <br>No baby don't, you making my heart hurt <br>Don't say those words <br>Take it back <br>You know you don't mean that <br>You swore when I wore your ring <br>It meant forever <br>I've got it on baby <br>How can you say I lost it <br>Oh, you promised <br><br>Started crying while I was sleeping <br>Waking up and reaching out <br>To a bed as empty as the heart inside my chest <br>So I gathered up some pictures <br>Said I had some things to give her <br>I let her read a letter <br>I had written her to give her on the day we tied the knot <br>I saw the tears <br>I saw them fall as she read the part of my growing old <br>I heard her words <br>I heard her say it'll never work <br><br>And hit my knees and cried <br>No baby don't you're making my heart hurt <br>Don't say those words <br>Take it back <br>You know you don't mean that <br>You swore when you wore my ring <br>It meant forever <br>You've got it on baby <br>How can you say you lost it <br>Yeah and you promised <br><br>We were different people then <br>Look at all the hateful things we've said <br>And I'm just as guilty <br>But girl that's no way to be <br>Take it easy baby I'm still broken <br>Memories enough to tear me wide open <br>When you see me girl you curse my name <br>Makes me wanna say <br><br>No, no baby don't <br>You're making my heart hurt <br>Don't say those words <br>Take it back <br>You know you don't mean that <br>You know when you wore my ring <br>We said forever <br>But you took it off baby <br>Safe to say we're through <br>No matter what you do <br>You know I'll always love you <br>Well I have to <br>'Cause I promised]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="You Promised (Demo)" label="You Promised (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Three_Feet_Of_Water/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Three Feet Of Water - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:26:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:26:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Three_Feet_Of_Water/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Three Feet Of Water - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Got a whole lot of years <br>And a whole lot of pain <br>And it all got me here <br>Where the river meets the clay <br>Rewindin' through my past <br>Tryin to find some good <br>But I can't seem to see <br>What mama always could <br><br>And that sun is shinin' down <br>On all my darker days <br>They're comin' to me now <br>As I hear the preacher say <br>In the name of the Son and the Father <br>Can I really leave it all <br>In three feet of water <br><br>I can't unbreak the laws <br>Straighten out the rules I've bent <br>Take the broken dreams and hearts <br>Make 'em all whole again <br>I been carryin' around <br>All the messes that I've made <br>But a few more steps from now <br>They'll all be washed away <br><br>And that sun is shinin' down <br>On all my darker days <br>They're comin' to me now <br>As I hear the preacher say <br>In the name of the Son and the Father <br>Who'd've thought I could leave it all <br>In three feet of water <br>Washin' over me <br>Amazing Grace the choir sings <br>And now I know what mercy's all about <br><br>And that sun is shinin' down <br>And all my darker days <br>They're nowhere to be found <br>All that preacher had to say <br>Was in the name of the Son and the Father <br>Who'd've thought I could leave it all <br>You took my cross so I could leave it all <br>In three feet of water <br>Mmm, in three feet of water <br>Mmm <br><br>So, it's that simple, huh]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Three Feet Of Water" label="Three Feet Of Water"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Were_Gonna_Ride_Again/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - We`re Gonna Ride Again - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:26:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:26:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Were_Gonna_Ride_Again/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - We`re Gonna Ride Again - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[That long gray beard hung down to his chest <br>Ol' long hair was always a mess <br>And the laugh on that man, I'll never forget <br>You could hear him from a mile away <br>Loved his Pabst Blue Ribbon and his cigarettes <br>He'd burn one down, light 'er up again <br>I still see that grin and that ol' HD <br>He'd roll it like he stole the thing <br>You know, I talked to him yesterday <br>I asked him <br><br>How's that steel horse ride on the streets of gold <br>Does the promised land have any ol' back roads <br>Ain't a doubt you've done a burnout on a cloud <br>Knowin' you, you probably laid her down <br>Have you revved it up while the angels sang <br>Did God get on ya, did He take your wings <br>You better have 'em back 'fore I get in <br>'Cause brother, we're gonna ride again <br><br>Alright <br><br>They say blood makes you related <br>But loyalty makes you kin <br>So when I called that man my brother <br>Well, I meant what I said <br>'Cause we were thick as thieves and we were hell on wheels <br>I can't begin to tell ya how it feels <br>But I speak for us all, man it hurts like hell <br>We miss your smilin' face <br>We'll saddle up again one day <br>Until then <br><br>How's that steel horse ride on the streets of gold <br>Does the promised land have any ol' back roads <br>Ain't a doubt you've done a burnout on a cloud <br>Knowin' you, you probably laid her down <br>Have you revved it up while the angels sang <br>Did God get on ya, did He take your wings <br>You better have 'em back 'fore I get in <br>'Cause brother, we're gonna ride again <br><br>Man, you're more than a memory, more than a friend <br>Man, you'll always be family, we'll never forget <br>Gonna see you again someday <br>Hell yeah, we're gonna rock that house <br>When we get through the gates <br>How's that steel horse ride on the streets of gold <br>Does the promised land have any ol' back roads <br>Ain't a doubt you've done a burnout on a cloud <br>Knowin' you, you probably laid her down <br>Have you revved it up while the angels sang <br>Did God get on ya, did He take your wings <br>You better get 'em back 'fore I get in <br>'Cause brother, we're gonna ride again <br><br>We're gonna ride again <br><br>We miss ya, brother]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="We`re Gonna Ride Again" label="We`re Gonna Ride Again"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/The_Devil_Dont_Sleep/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - The Devil Don`t Sleep - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:27:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:27:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/The_Devil_Dont_Sleep/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - The Devil Don`t Sleep - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br>He never shuts his eyes <br>You never hear him creepin' <br>Yeah <br><br>Battle scars on my heart <br>Lord knows this war ain't over, no <br>It's just gettin' started <br>Just when you thought you had him beat <br>He's on your shoulder <br>He's in your ear, he's whisperin' <br>Lyin' again, and again, and again <br>You tell yourself he'll leave you alone <br>You turn your back, and brother man, it's on <br><br>Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br>He never shuts his eyes <br>You never hear him creepin' <br>Heaven knows he's hell bent on me <br>Shackles and chains <br>Thank God that He can break me free <br>'Cause Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br><br>He's at your door, don't let him in <br>He'll lie, he'll steal, he'll kill, he'll win <br>Just ask me, I've been there <br>All you'll have left is a desperate prayer <br>You pray to God He'll save your soul <br>Like He has a thousand times before <br><br>Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br>He never shuts his eyes <br>You never hear him creepin' <br>Heaven knows he's hell bent on me <br>Shackles and chains <br>Thank God that He can break me free <br>'Cause Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br><br>The devil don't sleep, no <br>Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br>He never shuts his eyes <br>You never hear him creepin' <br>Heaven knows he's hell bent on me <br>Shackles and chains <br>Thank God that He can break me free <br><br>Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br>He never shuts his eyes <br>You never hear him creepin' <br>Heaven knows he's hell bent on me <br>Shackles and chains <br>Thank God that He can break me free <br>'Cause Lord knows the devil don't sleep <br><br>The devil don't sleep <br>The devil don't sleep, yeah]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="The Devil Don`t Sleep" label="The Devil Don`t Sleep"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Bullet_In_A_Bonfire/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Bullet In A Bonfire - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:27:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:27:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Bullet_In_A_Bonfire/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Bullet In A Bonfire - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know the stories behind the bruises <br>When I've been the shoulder <br>You've been the reason for her tears <br>And her tellin' you it's over's useless <br>You keep callin' her phone, drivin' by when I'm not here <br>She's beggin' me not to lose my temper <br>Lord, I've tried, but my patience is runnin' thin <br>The best thing you can do is forget her <br>'Cause so help me God, if you ever touch that girl again <br><br>You cross that line, boy and there ain't no comin' back <br>I'm a crazy train, son, and you caught up in the tracks <br>You've got me growlin' like a pit bull, brother <br>I'm about to lock my jaws <br>I'm a time bomb tickin' a real live wire <br>Boy a shot in the dark, I'm a bullet in a bonfire <br>I'm a bullet in a bonfire <br><br>I know you don't know my story <br>But I know your's <br>And you probably should've read a page or two <br>'Cause if you think you're a badass on a lady <br>Boy, you oughta see a grown ass man on a punk ass joke like you <br><br>You cross that line, boy and there ain't no comin' back <br>I'm a crazy train, son, and you caught up in the tracks <br>You've got me growlin' like a pit bull, brother <br>I'm about to lock my jaws <br>I'm a time bomb tickin' a real live wire <br>Boy a shot in the dark, I'm a bullet in a bonfire <br>Yeah, I'm a bullet in a bonfire <br><br>Now, I'm gonna let you think it's over <br>But little do you know, the fun is just about to start <br>'Cause I see you lookin' over your shoulder <br>And I see you tryin' to act like you don't hear my footsteps in the dark <br><br>You cross that line, boy and there ain't no comin' back <br>I'm a crazy train, son, and you caught up in the tracks <br>You've got me growlin' like a pit bull, brother <br>I'm about to lock my jaws <br>I'm a time bomb tickin' a real live wire <br>Boy a shot in the dark, I'm a bullet in a bonfire <br><br>Yeah, I'm a bullet in a bonfire <br>Yeah, I'm a bullet in a bonfire <br>And you think it's over]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Bullet In A Bonfire" label="Bullet In A Bonfire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Outlaw_In_Me/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Outlaw In Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:27:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:27:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Outlaw_In_Me/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Outlaw In Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She says, Baby what's that scar from <br>I said, Girl, you don't wanna know <br>She said, What about this one or that one <br>Girl, that was a long time ago <br>She kisses and traces every one with her hands <br>The look on her face says she understands <br><br>My baby don't try to change me <br>'Cause she knows <br>This is the way that God made me <br>She gets every flaw, my rebel heart, every tattoo, every scar <br>She's in love with the outlaw in me <br><br>She knows I roll with a rough crowd <br>And we get wild time to time <br>She knows I won't lay my guns down <br>I never run from a fight <br><br>My baby don't try to change me <br>She knows <br>This is the way that God made me <br>She gets every flaw, my rebel heart, every tattoo, every scar <br>She's in love with the outlaw in me <br><br>Yeah <br>Alright <br><br>That girl knows that she's got me <br>And prays one day I'll settle down <br>And I just thank God she loves me <br>Even when I don't know how <br><br>My baby don't try to change me <br>She knows <br>This is the way that God made me <br>She gets every flaw, my rebel heart, every tattoo, every scar <br>She's in love with the outlaw in me <br><br>She's in love <br>With the outlaw <br>In me]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Outlaw In Me" label="Outlaw In Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Baby_Be_Crazy/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Baby Be Crazy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:27:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:27:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Baby_Be_Crazy/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Baby Be Crazy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, you know they say <br>They say that I'm a rollin' stone <br>Girl, that boy's a dead end road <br>Yeah, you're better off alone <br>And I know I can't say <br>Girl, I can't say they're wrong <br>I'm pretty set in my ways <br>But maybe it's time that changed <br>And all you wanna know is <br>What's it gonna take <br><br>You'd have to be crazy to love me <br>Oh, but I wish you would <br>You'd have to be outta your mind <br>But deep inside, I think you could <br>Be the only chance in hell to save me from myself <br>So come on save me, oh yeah <br>Baby, be crazy <br><br>I know you say <br>You say you're gonna hang on <br>To this train wreck, baby <br>So you think you're that strong <br>Deep down, what I want <br>I want you to tie me down <br>I want so bad to trust you <br>Baby, don't burn me now <br>All we can do is try <br>I ain't tryin' to say goodbye <br><br>You'd have to be crazy to love me <br>Oh, but I wish you would <br>You'd have to be outta your mind <br>But deep inside, I think you could <br>Be the only chance in hell to save me from myself <br>So come on save me, oh yeah <br>Baby, be crazy <br><br>Yeah, oh <br><br>You'd have to be crazy to love me <br>Oh, but I wish you would <br>You'd have to be outta your damn mind <br>But deep inside, I think you could <br>Be the only chance in hell to save me from myself <br>So come on save me <br>Yeah baby, c'mon save me, yeah <br>Baby, be crazy <br>Baby, be crazy <br>Oh baby, be crazy <br>Yeah, oh]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Baby Be Crazy" label="Baby Be Crazy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Way_Back/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Way Back - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:27:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:27:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Way_Back/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Way Back - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I guess some things never change <br>It's been a while since I been around <br>It still feels like goodbye comin' home <br>To what's left of our hometown <br>Stopped by and I saw momma, first thing she said <br>You know your girl's home too <br>Ain't been in town ten minutes and the grapevine's <br>All about me and you <br>'Cause baby we go <br><br>Way back <br>Me and you and this town <br>We been through it <br>You could say that <br>I'm still the same ol' boy in love <br>With the same ol' flame that got away <br>And never gave my heart back <br>Aww, and that same ol' flame burns <br>Like it was burnin' way back <br><br>It's burnin' way back <br>Got a call from your best friend, Becky <br>Says you're hangin out at her place <br>Guess you heard I was home and you wouldn't mind takin' <br>A ride for old time's sake <br>Pulled up, lost my breath <br>How'd you get more beautiful, lemme getcha door <br>Yeah, that shotgun seat's still yours <br>Your bare feet up on the dashboard <br>Girl, you take me <br><br>Way back <br>Me and you and this town <br>We been through it <br>You could say that <br>I'm still the same ol' boy in love <br>With the same ol' flame that got away <br>And never gave my heart back <br>Aww, and that same ol' flame burns <br>Like it was burnin' way back <br><br>Way back <br>Take a left at the Baptist church <br>Had our first kiss in the back <br>Cross the tracks, take a right where I kissed you goodbye <br>Didn't have to be our last <br>So girl, I came back <br>When it comes to you and me, girl <br>You could say that <br>Goodbye ain't never meant a thing <br>And we go <br><br>Way back <br>Me and you and this town <br>We been through it <br>You could say that <br>I'm still the same ol' boy in love <br>With the same ol' flame that got away <br>And never gave my heart back <br>Aww, and that same ol' flame burns <br>Like it was burnin' way back <br><br>Like it was burnin' way back]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Way Back" label="Way Back"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/In_My_Head/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - In My Head - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:27:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:27:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/In_My_Head/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - In My Head - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, I watched the sun come up on auburn hair across my chest <br>Couple coffee cups with just a little wine left <br>I had to smile 'cause you still got that bottle in your hand <br>Last night's a movie playin' over and over <br>All in my head <br>All in my head, baby <br>We talked for hours, fell in love with everything you said <br>About our exes, about Jesus in between some sips <br>You said so sexy, with your lips about an inch away <br>You wanna kiss me, don't you, whaddaya say <br>You're in my head <br>All in my head, baby <br><br>You got me thinkin' crazy, this ain't me, I know where it ends <br>And this has got too good to be true written all over it <br>I'm takin' this leap of faith, if I go down in flames <br>We made a memory that won't go away <br>You're in my head <br>All in my head, baby <br><br>You sleep so pretty up against me in this truck bed <br>Your little hand's inside of mine, and it's a perfect fit <br>And I'm in love with you all over me in every way <br>And I wouldn't be sayin' this if you were awake <br>You're in my head <br>All in my head, baby <br><br>You got me thinkin' crazy, this ain't me, I know where it ends <br>And this has got too good to be true written all over it <br>I'm takin' this leap of faith, if I go down in flames <br>We made a memory that won't go away <br>You're in my head <br>All in my head, baby <br><br>When you woke up, I saw you smile when you looked back at me <br>Said you missed me, I forgot how to breathe <br>You're in my head <br><br>What am I gon' do with you <br>You're in my head <br><br>You got me thinkin' crazy, this ain't me, I know where it ends <br>And this has got too good to be true written all over it <br>I'm takin' this leap of faith, if I go down in flames <br>We made a memory that won't go away <br>You're in my head <br>All in my head, baby <br><br>You're in my head <br>All in my head]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="In My Head" label="In My Head"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Tried_To_Tell_Ya/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Tried To Tell Ya - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:27:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:27:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Tried_To_Tell_Ya/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Tried To Tell Ya - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's four in the mornin', under ol Georgia <br>Blue lights in the rearview <br>Your blue eyes wide open like <br>Boy, what you tryin' to do <br><br>I think that left turn lost em <br>And it's turnin' you on <br>You're climbin' over the console <br>So I'm guessin' it's on <br><br>All right, all right You're lovin' this fast lane life <br>Don't lie, don't lie You don't wanna say goodnight <br><br>I tried to tell ya I was crazy <br>Tried to tell ya that I lost my mind <br>Tried to tell ya I was nothin' but trouble, oh babe <br>Yeah, but baby you thought I was a liar <br>Now you got yourself a situation and got ya fallen for a renegade <br>You can't blame meif you try, you'll never change me <br>Yeah Itried to tell ya I was crazy <br><br>Middle of the night, I'm outside in your drive and baby let's go <br>Didn't call or nothin', just showed up and told you East Diamond Road <br>Got you head over heels girl, ain't this a trip <br>Just ridin' round, yeah you're lovin' this bad boy shit <br><br>Itried to tell ya I was crazy <br>Tried to tell ya that I lost my mind <br>Tried to tell ya I was nothin' but trouble, oh babe <br>Yeah, but baby you thought I was a liar <br>Now you got yourself a situation and had ya fallen for a renegade <br>You can't blame meif you tried, never save me <br>Yeah Itried to tell ya I was crazy <br><br>All right, all right You're lovin' this fast lane life <br>Don't lie, don't lie You don't wanna say goodnight <br>All right, all right And I think I want this right <br>The life, the life And I'll never say goodbye <br><br>Itried to tell ya I was crazy <br>Tried to tell you I was outta my mind <br>Tried to tell you I was nothin' but trouble, baby <br>Yeah but baby, you saved my life <br>Now we got ourselves a situation <br>And now you're runnin' with a renegade <br>You can't blame me She never tried to change me <br>Yeah I'll admit it I was crazy]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Tried To Tell Ya" label="Tried To Tell Ya"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Its_About_To_Get_Dirty/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - It`s About To Get Dirty - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:27:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:27:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Its_About_To_Get_Dirty/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - It`s About To Get Dirty - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Weatherman says it's gonna rain <br>Don't worry girl won't change a thing <br>Yeah we still got plans tonight <br>We gonn' kick it, dancin', givin' baby rain or shine <br><br>Leave your Sunday best at home <br>Be last time you wear what you got on <br>Bikini top cut off jeans <br>Damn, baby girl you know you lookin' mean <br><br>She said how we gonna make it through the mudhole <br>Whatch ya think I got swampers on my truck for <br><br>It's about to get dirty in the dirty south <br>'Bout to show you what it's all about <br>Don't worry, there's a rowdy crowd <br>We ain't scared, we still throwin' down <br><br>We gonna tap that keg <br>Locked at five <br>We gonna' crank that country <br>Pass out shots <br>And get thirsty <br><br>Let it rain, let it rain, let it rain <br>It's about to get dirty <br><br>There's just somethin' 'bout a good old flood <br>Watching that red clay turn to mud <br>Slinging up, slam past the doors <br>Like a new paint job on a 4x4 <br><br>Girl you gonna have a good ol' time <br>Can't let a little bit of rain change your mind <br>Let your hair down, coffin boots <br>For once in your life let yourself cut loose <br><br>Gonna get muddy from head to toe <br>Cleanin' off, skinny dipping in the swimming hole <br><br>It's about to get dirty in the dirty south <br>'Bout to show you what it's all about <br>Don't worry, there's a rowdy crowd <br>We ain't scared, we still throwin' down <br><br>We gonna tap that keg <br>Locked at five <br>We gonna' crank that country <br>Pass out shots <br>And get thirsty <br><br>Let it rain let it rain let it rain <br>It's about to get dirty <br><br>Girl your whole life's 'bout to change <br>Bad times and muddy water let me hear you say <br>Let it rain, let it rain, let it rain <br><br>It's about to get dirty in the dirty south <br>'Bout to show you what it's all about <br>Don't worry, there's a rowdy crowd <br>We ain't scared, we still throwin' down <br><br>We gonna tap that keg <br>Locked at five <br>We gonna' crank that country <br>Pass out shots <br>And get thirsty <br><br>Let it rain, let it rain, let it rain <br>Everybody get thirsty <br>Let it rain, let it rain, let it rain <br>Listen 'bout to get dirty <br>Listen 'bout to get dirty <br>C'mon <br><br>Nasty]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="It`s About To Get Dirty" label="It`s About To Get Dirty"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Bro_Code/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Bro Code - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:27:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:27:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Bro_Code/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Bro Code - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look atcha, girl <br>Standin' in my doorway <br>Rockin' them curls <br>And them cut off daisies, man <br>She called me up <br>Can I come over, boy <br>I'm bored to death <br>And I'm all alone <br>And <br><br>She only drinks when she's lonely <br>She only gets stoned when you ain't home <br>And I know bro code and I ain't breakin' it <br>But bro, you got yourself a situation, bro <br>You better get your girl home, boy <br>You better take yourself home, boy <br>You better tell her you love her, you need her <br>'Cause if you don't, she's 'bout to be long gone, bro <br><br>I opened the door <br>And she gets to talkin' <br>Talkin' 'bout he's controllin' me <br>And tryin to hold me down <br>It's gettin old, man <br>She's ready to roll, man <br>And I don't want to say <br>I told you so, man <br>'Cause <br><br>She only drinks when she's lonely <br>She only gets stoned when you ain't home <br>And I know bro code and I ain't breakin' it <br>But bro, you got yourself a situation, bro <br>You better get your girl home, boy <br>You better take yourself home, boy <br>You better tell her you love her, you need her <br>'Cause if you don't, she's 'bout to be long gone, bro <br><br>Better show that girl a good time <br>If you don't it's gon' be goodbye <br>And if you take it for granted <br>You hand her to another man <br>It's a matter of time, bro <br>It's a matter of time <br><br>Now, I know it ain't my business <br>But I gotta insist that <br>If this was somebody else <br>Your deal is already finished because <br>Bro code goes out the window <br>Just be glad it's me lettin' you know, bro <br>'Cause <br><br>She only drinks when she's lonely <br>She only gets stoned when you ain't home <br>And I know bro code and I ain't breakin' it <br>But bro, you got yourself a situation, bro <br>You better get your girl home, boy <br>You better take yourself home, boy <br>You better tell her you love her, you need her <br>'Cause if you don't, she's 'bout to be long gone, bro <br><br>Better show that girl a good time <br>If you don't it's gon' be goodbye <br>And if you take it for granted <br>You hand her to another man <br>It's a matter of time, bro <br>It's a matter of time, bro]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Bro Code" label="Bro Code"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Smokin_Gun/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Smokin` Gun - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:27:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:27:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Smokin_Gun/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Smokin` Gun - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's 2 AM and that cell phone's ringin' <br>Yeah, sounds like you been sippin' on somethin' <br>It was in the way I heard you say, hey baby <br>Yeah, you 'bout as subtle as a freight train comin' <br>And I know what's next <br>You'll be knockin' on my door <br>Standin' there in that dress <br>What are you waitin' for <br><br>Pull the trigger on a point blank kiss <br>This close you better never miss <br>Heart beatin' like a bullet into my chest <br>Bitin' my lip and wreckin' my bed <br>But Cinderella never sees the sun <br>You'll be gone before mornin' comes <br>Like to love, but you love to run <br>You're too hot to hold <br>Baby, you're a smokin' gun <br><br>Yeah, you think you got it like Tony Montana <br>Callin' these shots like the world is yours <br>And you got me hooked, but let me turn them tables <br>I ain't the only one comin back for more <br>Little smile on your face <br>You're beggin' me to play along <br>So, if we're sayin' it's a game <br>Then I'm guessin' this is game on <br><br>Pull the trigger on a point blank kiss <br>This close you better never miss <br>Heart beatin' like a bullet into my chest <br>Bitin' my lip and wreckin' my bed <br>But Cinderella never sees the sun <br>You'll be gone before mornin' comes <br>Like to love, but you love to run <br>You're too hot to hold <br>Baby, you're a smokin' gun <br><br>You're like a forty four mag with one bullet in it <br>It's a dangerous game, but I can't help but spin it <br>Knowin' one day it's gonna end bad <br>But it's too late, I got it cocked back <br><br>Pull the trigger on a point blank kiss <br>This close you better never miss <br>Heart beatin' like a bullet into my chest <br>Bitin' my lip and wreckin' my bed <br>But Cinderella never sees the sun <br>You'll be gone before mornin' comes <br>Like to love, but you love to run <br>You're too hot to hold <br>Baby, you're a smokin' gun <br><br>Yeah <br>Pull the trigger]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Smokin` Gun" label="Smokin` Gun"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/You_Could_Be_That_Girl/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - You Could Be That Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:27:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:27:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/You_Could_Be_That_Girl/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - You Could Be That Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well I'm looking for a Bonnie <br>Lookin' for a PIC <br>A lil partner in crime <br>Come hell or high water <br>She's down <br>She's ridin with me <br>Lil miss watch for blue lights <br>While I drive, you can hold that45 <br>Go down in a blaze of glory <br>I always loved that story <br><br>Now, you could be that <br>You could be that <br>You could be that girl <br>And I can see that good girl gone bad <br>You could be that girl <br><br>I bet your daddy said you could be anything <br>Anything you wanted to be ha <br>Bet he never saw a renegade comin' <br>You're a lady <br>You know how to hit your knees <br>I need a girl who knows the good Lord <br>I need a girl who's gonna pray for me <br>Yeah <br><br>You could be that <br>You could be that <br>You could be that girl <br>And I can see that good girl gone bad <br>You could be that girl <br><br>Hot as a pistol <br>You got that rebel potential <br>Hop on this ol' moto'cycle <br>Baby, let's make it official <br>Let's ride <br><br>Baby girl let's ride <br><br>You could be that <br><br>You could be that <br><br>You could be that girl <br><br>And I can see that good girl gone bad <br>You could be that girl <br><br>Yeah <br><br>Yeah you could you be <br>What I need <br>Hey baby, you can be mine <br>Ohh <br>You could be that girl <br>Ohhh <br>I can see that]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="You Could Be That Girl" label="You Could Be That Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/The_Weekend/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - The Weekend - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:27:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:27:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/The_Weekend/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - The Weekend - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tick tock I'm on the clock <br>And I'm feeling like this job's <br>Just 9 to 5 ing my life away <br>It's like I'm back in school <br>And I'm in the last class <br>And I'm passing time until the bell rang <br>Having visions of summertime <br>But wait a minute, this is later tonight <br>Trying to make some tailgating song <br>Up in the moonlight and by the way <br>It's payday <br><br>Live it up for the weekend <br>Pull it up, have the time of your life <br>Take a shot for the regret <br>Double up and it's bound <br>To get double wild <br>Hey ladies let your hair down <br>We know ain't nobody scared now, hell nah <br>Do your thing like it's spring break <br>Wake and bake and we at it again <br>Live it up for the weekend <br><br>Backwoods looking like Panama City <br>Bunch of jacked up trucks and bikinis <br>Got a yeti full of good ideas <br>Ain't worried about driving gonna stay right here <br><br>Live it up for the weekend <br>Pull it up, have the time of your life <br>Take a shot for the regret <br>Double up and it's bound <br>To get double wild <br>Hey ladies let your hair down <br>We know ain't nobody scared now, hell nah <br>Do your thing like it's spring break <br>Wake and bake and we at it again <br>Live it up for the weekend <br><br>Somebody said somethin' 'bout church on Sunday, Amen <br>Somebody said somethin' 'bout work on Monday <br>Don't say it again <br><br>Live it up for the weekend <br>Pull it up, have the time of your life <br>Take a shot for the regret <br>Double up and it's bound <br>To get double wild <br>Hey ladies let your hair down <br>We know ain't nobody scared now, hell nah <br>Do your thing like it's spring break <br>Wake and bake and we at it again <br>Live it up for the weekend <br><br>Live it up <br>Live it up for the weekend, c'mon <br>Live it up <br>Live it up for the weekend <br>Live it up <br>Live it up for the weekend <br>Live it up <br>Live it up for the weekend]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="The Weekend" label="The Weekend"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/The_Ones_That_Like_Me/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - The Ones That Like Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:27:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:27:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/The_Ones_That_Like_Me/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - The Ones That Like Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh yeah <br>Ain't gonna lie, I can count on both hands <br>My down to ride 'til the day I die friends <br>To get them, I'd like to think <br>That I'm few and far between <br>Guys like me, you want in an alley with ya <br>Up a creek, ain't a doubt I'm gonna paddle with ya <br>Go to bat, go to church, go to battle with ya <br>They can say what they want about me, but <br><br>The ones that need me got me <br>The ones that doubt me can't stop me <br>Even the ones that said forget him <br>You can bet they ain't forgot me <br>Either wanna hit me or hold me <br>Those that hate me don't know me <br>And the ones that don't trust anybody trust me <br>Yeah, the ones that like me love me <br><br>Speak my mind, don't mind who's listenin' <br>I'll ask forgiveness, 'fore I ask permission <br>Least with me you know what you're gettin' <br>You may not get a thing about me, but <br><br>The ones that need me got me <br>The ones that doubt me can't stop me <br>Even the ones that said forget him <br>You can bet they ain't forgot me <br>Either wanna hit me or hold me <br>Those that hate me don't know me <br>And the ones that don't trust anybody trust me <br>Yeah, the ones that like me love me <br><br>Yeah, they love me <br>And I ain't perfect, I'm a simple man <br>I got a sinner's mind, but I can fold my hands <br>I ain't afraid to pray and I do know who I am, yeah <br><br>And the ones that need me got me <br>Ones that doubt me can't stop me <br>Even the ones that said forget him <br>Bet your ass they ain't forgot me <br>Either wanna hit me or hold me <br>Those that hate me don't know me <br>And the ones that don't trust anybody trust me <br>Yeah, the ones that like me love me <br><br>The ones that like me love me <br><br>And if you don't <br>Probably a pretty good chance I don't like you either]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="The Ones That Like Me" label="The Ones That Like Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Rockin_Chairs/</id><title>Brantley_Gilbert - Rockin` Chairs - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:27:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:27:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brantley_Gilbert/Rockin_Chairs/" title="Brantley_Gilbert - Rockin` Chairs - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Now and then I see old timers talkin' <br>All day long relivin' them good ol' days <br>Like it never gets old <br>And it's the same old stories <br>Got me wonderin' if it's going to be us one day <br>Better live this one life we got oh <br><br>'Cause these are the days <br>That are going to fly by like lightning so they say <br>These are the nights yeah <br>The good times that we left the wild side out to play <br>These are the Sunday mornings <br>We talked to the Lord, get right with the man upstairs <br><br>Get back to rock it out <br>So we can say we were there <br>When we talk about it <br>In our rockin' chairs <br><br>C'mon ya'll we got memories to make <br>Some cold beers to drink <br>And some songs we gotta live out loud <br>Going to be some good hearts breakin' <br>Bunch of mistakes <br>Maybe some day we'll figure it out <br>But right now it's all about <br>Going all the way <br><br>These are the days <br>That are going to fly by like lightning so they say <br>These are the nights yeah <br>The good times that we left the wild side out to play <br>These are the Sunday mornings <br>We talked to the Lord, get right with the man upstairs <br><br>Get back to rock it out <br>So we can say we were there <br>When we talk about it <br>In our rockin' chairs <br>In our rockin' chairs <br><br>We gotta crank it up to ten and then some <br>Go way too far <br>Too fast, too hard <br>And have too much fun <br><br>These are the days <br>That are going to fly by like lightning, so they say <br>These are the times of our lives <br>We ain't got none to waste <br><br>These are the days <br>That are going to fly by like lightning so they say <br>These are the nights yeah <br>The good times that we left the wild side out to play <br>These are the Sunday mornings <br>We talked to the Lord, get right with the man upstairs <br><br>Get back to rock it out <br>So we can say we were there <br>When we talk about it <br>In our rockin' chairs <br>In our rockin' chairs <br>In our rockin' chairs]]></content><category term="Brantley Gilbert" label="Brantley Gilbert"/><category term="Rockin` Chairs" label="Rockin` Chairs"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KFlay/Black_Wave/</id><title>KFlay - Black Wave - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:28:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:28:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KFlay/Black_Wave/" title="KFlay - Black Wave - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Black wave coming, will it hit <br>I can taste the fear, yeah, it's written on my lips <br>Sipping on a cold one, waiting on the rinse <br>Woke up with an omen tatted on my wrist <br>Black wave coming, will it drop <br>I can see the fear, yeah, it's written on the wall <br>Who you gonna trust when the killer is the cop <br>Fire in my bloodstream, water in my lungs <br><br>Waiting on a black wave, running in a rat maze <br>Shaking in my own cage, what do I believe, I believe <br>Waiting on a black wave, living under bad days <br>Shaking in my own cage, what do I believe <br>Stumbling down the street <br>I swear to God, you don't wanna test me <br>Don't test me <br><br>Black wave blocking out the sun <br>Baby, when you go down, ain't no coming up <br>Thought that you were safe but nobody ever was <br>Choking on a diamond, poison in your lungs <br>At the end, guess we're all just animals <br>At the end, is it all just greed <br>When the ocean crash down, who you gonna call <br>Hold your breath, hold your breath, counting 1, 2 <br><br>Waiting on a black wave, running in a rat maze <br>Shaking in my own cage, what do I believe, I believe <br>Waiting on a black wave, living under bad days <br>Shaking in my own cage, what do I believe <br>Stumbling down the street <br>I swear to God, you don't wanna test me <br>Don't test me <br>Don't test me <br><br>How did a girl like me end up in a world so mean <br>How did a girl like me end up in a world so mean <br><br>Don't test me <br>Don't test me <br>Don't test me]]></content><category term="K.Flay" label="K.Flay"/><category term="Black Wave" label="Black Wave"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정영화/회복의_은혜/</id><title>정영화 - 회복의 은혜 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:28:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:28:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%98%81%ED%99%94/%ED%9A%8C%EB%B3%B5%EC%9D%98_%EC%9D%80%ED%98%9C/" title="정영화 - 회복의 은혜 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[회복의 은혜가 <br>흘러가네 <br>샘물과 같이 <br>흘러서 넘치네 <br>당신을 통해서 <br>주님 약속하신 <br>회복의 은혜가 <br>감사와 찬송이 되리라 <br>감사와 찬송이 되리라 <br>회복의 축복이 <br>퍼져가네 <br>우리를 통하여 <br>흐르고 흐르네 <br>너와 날 위하여 <br>대신 지신 <br>십자가 바라보며 <br>승리의 노래를 부르리 <br>오늘도 찬송하며 살리라 <br>회복의 축복이 <br>퍼져가네 <br>우리를 통하여 <br>흐르고 흐르네 <br>너와 날 위하여 <br>대신 지신 <br>십자가 바라보며 <br>승리의 노래를 부르리 <br>오늘도 찬송하며 살리라 <br>오늘도 찬송하며 살리라 <br>]]></content><category term="정영화" label="정영화"/><category term="회복의 은혜" label="회복의 은혜"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HUS_허밍어반스테레오/MWAH_Inst/</id><title>HUS_허밍어반스테레오 - MWAH (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:29:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:29:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HUS_%ED%97%88%EB%B0%8D%EC%96%B4%EB%B0%98%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A4/MWAH_Inst/" title="HUS_허밍어반스테레오 - MWAH (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마지막 남은 피자 조각처럼 <br>당신을 위해 싸울 거야 <br>살면서 사고는 많이 쳤어도 <br>조각 같은 널 만난 것은 <br>후회 안 해 절대 안 해 <br>만나는 순간부터 <br>마음을 열게 하는 여자야 <br>안아줘야 할지 <br>팔씨름을 해야 할지 모를 Mystery <br>만나는 순간부터 <br>마음을 열게 하는 여자야 <br>마치 홀아비 기억 속 <br>아내처럼 모든 게 완벽해 <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>그리도 싫던 당근 주스조차 <br>당신을 위해 마실 거야 Drink <br>그래서 건강한 나의 단백질 주스를 <br>너에게 채워 줄 거야 다 모두 다 줄 거야 <br>만나는 순간부터 <br>마음을 열게 하는 여자야 <br>안아줘야 할지 <br>팔씨름을 해야 할지 모를 Mystery <br>만나는 순간부터 <br>마음을 열게 하는 여자야 <br>마치 홀아비 기억 속 <br>아내처럼 모든 게 완벽해 <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>]]></content><category term="HUS (허밍어반스테레오)" label="HUS (허밍어반스테레오)"/><category term="MWAH (Inst.)" label="MWAH (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HUS_허밍어반스테레오/MWAH_므와/</id><title>HUS_허밍어반스테레오 - MWAH (므와) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:29:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:29:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HUS_%ED%97%88%EB%B0%8D%EC%96%B4%EB%B0%98%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A4/MWAH_%EB%AF%80%EC%99%80/" title="HUS_허밍어반스테레오 - MWAH (므와) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마지막 남은 피자 조각처럼 <br>당신을 위해 싸울 거야 <br>살면서 사고는 많이 쳤어도 <br>조각 같은 널 만난 것은 <br>후회 안 해 절대 안 해 <br>만나는 순간부터 <br>마음을 열게 하는 여자야 <br>안아줘야 할지 <br>팔씨름을 해야 할지 모를 Mystery <br>만나는 순간부터 <br>마음을 열게 하는 여자야 <br>마치 홀아비 기억 속 <br>아내처럼 모든 게 완벽해 <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>그리도 싫던 당근 주스조차 <br>당신을 위해 마실 거야 Drink <br>그래서 건강한 나의 단백질 주스를 <br>너에게 채워 줄 거야 다 모두 다 줄 거야 <br>만나는 순간부터 <br>마음을 열게 하는 여자야 <br>안아줘야 할지 <br>팔씨름을 해야 할지 모를 Mystery <br>만나는 순간부터 <br>마음을 열게 하는 여자야 <br>마치 홀아비 기억 속 <br>아내처럼 모든 게 완벽해 <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>Hey You 머리부터 발끝까지 모두 <br>Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah Mwah <br>]]></content><category term="HUS (허밍어반스테레오)" label="HUS (허밍어반스테레오)"/><category term="MWAH (므와)" label="MWAH (므와)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NCT_DREAM/Chewing_Gum_泡泡糖/</id><title>NCT_DREAM - Chewing Gum (泡泡糖) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:30:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:30:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NCT_DREAM/Chewing_Gum_%E6%B3%A1%E6%B3%A1%E7%B3%96/" title="NCT_DREAM - Chewing Gum (泡泡糖) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c C-c-c-c-c-c <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>shi shui rang di qiu yao zhu wo <br>de fan bu xie <br>jiu shi ni <br>yong li xiang kua chu jiao bu <br>que nian zai yuan dian kuai dian <br>xian xing <br>zen me dou shuai tuo bu diao mei <br>ban fa jie jue <br>nian tai jin <br>yuan lai shi gang tu diao de pao <br>pao tang gao gui <br>gei wo xiao xin <br>ni bei wo shi xian zhua zhu xia <br>de lian se bian lan <br>wo bian kan bian kao jin ni xia <br>de ni xiang tao kai <br>wo shuang yan zui zhong zhe ni <br>yi dian ye bu kun nan <br>dan wei he sheng qi de ni hui <br>zhe me de ke ai <br>pao pao ni he wo geng da geng da <br>dan bie chui po <br>bu pa ni shi <br>rou ruan de Chewing Gum <br>xiao xin xiao xin kao jin kao <br>jin ni de xuan wo <br>kuai bao zha de wo <br>ji xian de Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c C-c-c-c-c-c <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>wo ai de Chewing Gum <br>wei shen me wo men zong shi shen <br>qi de yu jian <br>wo he ni <br>bu guan shi bus hi zou zai tong <br>yang de lu xian <br>rang wo hao qi <br>hao xiang wen ni chi de tang shi <br>suan hai shi tian <br>kao jin ni <br>ke shi yong zhe wen ti da hua ye <br>tai diu lian <br>dai dai kan ni <br>fang fu chui qi le pao pao chui <br>geng da chui geng da <br>wo de nao dai bei chui man dou <br>shi ni dou shi ni <br>dai dai de kan ta peng zhang yue <br>da jiu yue tou ming <br>tou ming dao mei you ban fa yin <br>cang zhu wo de xin <br>pao pao ni he wo geng da geng da <br>dan bie chui po <br>bu pa ni shi <br>rou ruan de Chewing Gum <br>xiao xin xiao xin kao jin kao <br>jin ni de xuan wo <br>bie chui po ni shi <br>tian mi de Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c C-c-c-c-c-c <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>tian mi de Chewing Gum <br>kuai nian zai wo xin jian <br>Chewing Gum <br>Chewing Gum <br>Chewing Gum <br>Chew you like Chewing Gum <br>nian zhe wo de kou xiang tang <br>wo shang yin la tai xiang yao <br>bei ni nian zhe <br>xi yin wo de gan jue zhe yang <br>you na yang <br>chui zhe bao zha zai xin li Like <br>Chewing Gum Chewing Gum <br>You’re my Chewing Gum <br>bu neng ye bu xiang bai tuo Girl <br>pao pao ni he wo shi wo yao ni <br>huo ni yao wi <br>shui ying shui shu <br>ke ai de Chewing Gum <br>hu zuo hu you kao jin kao jin wo <br>de xuan wo <br>xi huan zhe gan jue <br>wo ai ni Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c C-c-c-c-c-c <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>wo ai de Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c C-c-c-c-c-c <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>tian mi de Chewing Gum <br>]]></content><category term="NCT DREAM" label="NCT DREAM"/><category term="Chewing Gum (泡泡糖)" label="Chewing Gum (泡泡糖)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NCT_DREAM/Chewing_Gum/</id><title>NCT_DREAM - Chewing Gum - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:30:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:30:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NCT_DREAM/Chewing_Gum/" title="NCT_DREAM - Chewing Gum - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c C-c-c-c-c-c <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>내 까만 스니커즈를 지금 멈추게 <br>만든 너 <br>범인은 어서 나와 좋은 말할 때 <br>빨리 나와 <br>끈적한 발이 떨어지지 않는 게 <br>조금 전 <br>뱉은 지 얼마 안 된 것이 분명해 <br>딱 기다려 <br>넌지시 마주치는 시선이 어색해 <br>천천히 다가가자 딴 곳을 보는 걸 <br>역시 널 찾아내긴 어렵지 않았어 <br>그런데 화내기엔 너무나 예쁜 너 <br>풍선 불어 봐 누가 누가 더 커질까 <br>자신 있어 <br>부드런 Chewing Gum <br>조심스레 네게 네게 더 다가가 <br>터질 듯 부푼 <br>내 맘은 Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c C-c-c-c-c-c <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>너는 내 Chewing Gum <br>신기해 자꾸 마주치고 있잖아 <br>너와 나 <br>매일 똑같은 길을 같이 걷잖아 <br>신경 쓰여 <br>궁금해 너란 애는 어떤 아인지 <br>다가가 <br>언제쯤 말을 걸까 고민하게 돼 <br>너만 보면 <br>공기가 들어간 듯 갈수록 커져가 <br>내 맘이 너로 가득 채워진 것 같아 <br>커지면 커질수록 점점 투명해져 <br>내 맘을 이제 더는 숨길 수도 없게 <br>풍선 불어 봐 누가 누가 더 커질까 <br>자신 있어 <br>부드런 Chewing Gum <br>조심스레 네게 네게 더 다가가 <br>분위길 잡고 <br>너는 내 Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c C-c-c-c-c-c <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>달콤한 Chewing Gum <br>내 맘에 붙어라 <br>Chewing Gum <br>Chewing Gum <br>Chewing Gum <br>Chew you like Chewing <br>검 딱지처럼 붙어줘 <br>중독 있어 너라는 거 <br>끈적해 끌리는 것 같애 너무 다양해 <br>내 마음에 터트려줄래 <br>Like Chewing Gum Chewing Gum <br>You’re my 주인공 쉽게 떼낼 수 없는 Girl <br>함께 있어 봐 누가 누가 더 원할까 <br>내기할까 <br>달콤한 Chewing Gum <br>장난스레 네게 네게 난 다가가 <br>예감이 좋아 <br>너는 내 Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c C-c-c-c-c-c <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>너는 내 Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>C-c-c-c-c-c C-c-c-c-c-c <br>C-c-c-c-c-c-Chewing Gum <br>달콤한 Chewing Gum <br>]]></content><category term="NCT DREAM" label="NCT DREAM"/><category term="Chewing Gum" label="Chewing Gum"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NCT_DREAM/덩크슛_Dunk_Shot/</id><title>NCT_DREAM - 덩크슛 (Dunk Shot) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:30:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:30:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NCT_DREAM/%EB%8D%A9%ED%81%AC%EC%8A%9B_Dunk_Shot/" title="NCT_DREAM - 덩크슛 (Dunk Shot) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주문을 외워보자 <br>유난히 고요하던 <br>밤 하늘을 바라보다가 <br>유성처럼 떨어지는 별을 봤지 <br>떨어지는 별을 보고 <br>가슴속의 소원을 빌면 <br>영화처럼 현실이 된다는 얘기 <br>예쁜 여자 친구와 <br>빨간 차도 갖고 싶었지만 <br>너무나 원했던 것은 <br>그 누구도 모를 거야 <br>덩크슛 한 번 할 수 있다면 <br>내 평생 단 한 번만이라도 <br>얼마나 짜릿한 그 기분을 느낄까 <br>주문을 외워보자 <br>야발라바히야 야발라바히야 <br>주문을 외워보자 oh yeah <br>야발라바히야모하이마모하이루라 <br>꿈을 꾸었던 것일까 <br>주위엔 아무도 없는데 <br>내 발 옆엔 주홍색 공 하나 덜렁 <br>예쁜 여자 친구와 <br>빨간 차도 갖고 싶었지만 <br>너무나 원했던 것은 <br>그 누구도 모를 거야 <br>덩크슛 한 번 할 수 있다면 <br>내 평생 단 한 번만이라도 <br>얼마나 짜릿한 그 기분을 느낄까 <br>주문을 외워보자 <br>야발라바히야 야발라바히야 <br>주문을 외워보자 oh yeah <br>야발라바히야모하이마모하이루라 <br>It’s a Dunk Shot <br>oh 예전부터 봐왔었던 <br>확실해진 내 초점으로 <br>Go on no more second guessing <br>그냥 믿고 Jump <br>멀어보기만 했던 게 이제 내 코앞 <br>거의 됐어 거의 닿았으니까 좀만 더 <br>Don’t wait for the whistle blow <br>You make your own call <br>그냥 내 맘대로 <br>덩크슛 한 번 할 수 있다면 <br>내 평생 단 한 번만이라도 <br>얼마나 짜릿한 그 기분을 느낄까 <br>주문을 외워보자 <br>야발라바히야 야발라바히야 <br>한번 더 될 때까지 oh yeah <br>야발라바히야모하이마모하이루라 <br>오에오아오 아 <br>오에오아 oh yeah <br>오에오아오 아 <br>오에오아 <br>야발라바히야모하이마모하이루라 <br>]]></content><category term="NCT DREAM" label="NCT DREAM"/><category term="덩크슛 (Dunk Shot)" label="덩크슛 (Dunk Shot)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NCT_DREAM/最後的初戀_My_First_and_Last/</id><title>NCT_DREAM - 最後的初戀 (My First and Last) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:30:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:30:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NCT_DREAM/%E6%9C%80%E5%BE%8C%E7%9A%84%E5%88%9D%EF%A6%90_My_First_and_Last/" title="NCT_DREAM - 最後的初戀 (My First and Last) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[oh maybe maybe <br>ai qing yi jing zhuang shang wo de tou <br>chu le ni yan qian shen me dou mei you <br>dao di xian zai shi bu shi dui <br>de shi hou <br>rang ai de jian she zhong xiong kou <br>lian ai xiao shuo ju qing zhen <br>shi de shang yan le <br>xin tiao sheng xiang dao shu zai <br>bao zha bian yuan <br>oh tie chu xun ren qi shi xiang <br>zhao shi he de zi yan <br>ni yi zhan ju wo de xin tian <br>bu guan wo shen zai he chu yong <br>yuan dou ji zhu shi zui chu <br>xiang ai na yi mu <br>zhe yi bei zi dou yao xin wu <br>pang wu ni jiu shi wei yi wo zui <br>hou de chu lian <br>Let's talk about love <br>Let me talk about love <br>Yeah I'm talking about you <br>Yeah I'm talking about you <br>mei ge ren dou shuo <br>wo hai ke yi xuan ze <br>No ni jiu shi zui hou <br>My baby baby <br>chu lian shi wo na shou de ke mu <br>yi ding hui kao qu zui duo de <br>xian mu <br>zhua zhu chu lian qing chu di tu <br>de hei wu <br>yi qi zhi dao zui hou sheng chu <br>ji shi bu zai wu chi pei ni yi <br>qi tiao wu <br>xin zang bu you zi zhu gen sui <br>zhe ta bu <br>gan jue you dian huang hu yan <br>qian fu gai yi pian wu <br>wo kan zhe ni sha sha xing fu <br>bu guan wo shen zai he chu yong <br>yuan dou ji zhu shi zui chu <br>xiang ai na yi mu <br>zhe yi bei zi dou yao xin wu <br>pang wu ni jiu shi wei yi wo zui <br>hou de chu lian <br>You you it’s you you girl <br>yi tian tian geng jia qing chu <br>bu xiang ku nao bu xiang zuo pan <br>you gu <br>No more other waiting <br>bu shi tao lu All I want is you <br>you you <br>bu guan xiang qian xiang hou bu <br>guan xiang zuo xiang you <br>shi ni dou shi ni zai na li wo <br>de chu kou zhao bu dao chu kou <br>kuai hui guo tou xiang zuo xiang <br>you dou zhao bu dao ru kou <br>hui qu de lu ye mo hu ni xiang <br>mi gong ba wo kun zhu <br>bu guan wo shen zai he chu yong <br>yuan dou ji zhu shi zui chu <br>xiang ai na yi mu <br>zhe yi bei zi dou yao xin wu <br>pang wu ni jiu shi wei yi wo zui <br>hou de chu lian <br>wo zui chu zui hou de chu lian <br>wo zui hou de chu lian <br>wo zui chu zui hou de chu lian <br>wo zui hou de chu lian <br>wo zui chu zui hou de chu lian <br>wo zui hou de chu lian <br>wo zui chu zui hou de chu lian <br>wo zui hou de chu lian <br>]]></content><category term="NCT DREAM" label="NCT DREAM"/><category term="最後的初戀 (My First and Last)" label="最後的初戀 (My First and Last)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NCT_DREAM/마지막_첫사랑_My_First_and_Last/</id><title>NCT_DREAM - 마지막 첫사랑 (My First and Last) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:30:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:30:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NCT_DREAM/%EB%A7%88%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%89_%EC%B2%AB%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_My_First_and_Last/" title="NCT_DREAM - 마지막 첫사랑 (My First and Last) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[oh maybe maybe <br>이건 사랑일지도 몰라 <br>이미 내 눈에는 너만 보여 난 <br>아직 아닐 거라 겁을 먹어도 <br>oh 내게도 온 것 같아 <br>책에 적힌 글자들이 현실이 돼 <br>가슴이 곧 터져 버릴 것 같아 <br>oh 아냐 어떤 말로도 설명할 수 없어 <br>그래 나에겐 너뿐이야 <br>내가 어디 있어도 꿈속에서도 <br>oh 나에겐 너뿐이야 <br>남은 인생을 걸고 말할게 <br>두 번은 없어 넌 나의 마지막 <br>Let's talk about love <br>Let me talk about love <br>Yeah I'm talking about you <br>Yeah I'm talking about you <br>다 내게 말해 <br>기회는 더 있다고 <br>아냐 내겐 너뿐 <br>My baby baby <br>처음이라고 모르지 않아 <br>모두 우릴 부러워하게 될 걸 <br>첫사랑이 끝까지 이어지는 <br>그 기회를 잡은 거야 <br>클럽에서 춤을 꼭 추지 않아도 <br>내 심장은 너와 춤을 추는 걸 <br>알딸딸한 게 뭔지 난 아직 모르지만 <br>너에게 취한 것 같아 <br>내가 어디 있어도 꿈속에서도 <br>oh 나에겐 너뿐이야 <br>남은 인생을 걸고 말할게 <br>두 번은 없어 넌 나의 마지막 <br>You you it’s you you girl <br>점점 확실해져 너 <br>더 이상은 고민하기 싫어 <br>No more other waiting <br>그냥 너야 All I want is you you you <br>앞뒤로 살펴봐도 좌우로 살펴봐도 <br>너란 사람은 대체 출구가 없어 <br>출구가 없어 <br>다 되돌려 앞뒤 좌우를 살펴 <br>입구를 찾아도 <br>돌아가는 길을 찾을 수가 없어 <br>난 네게 갇혀 <br>내가 어디 있어도 꿈속에서도 <br>oh 나에겐 너뿐이야 <br>남은 인생을 걸고 말할게 <br>두 번은 없어 넌 나의 마지막 <br>넌 나의 나의 마지막 <br>내 마지막 첫사랑 <br>넌 나의 나의 마지막 <br>내 마지막 첫사랑 <br>넌 나의 나의 마지막 <br>내 마지막 첫사랑 <br>넌 나의 나의 마지막 <br>내 마지막 첫사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="NCT DREAM" label="NCT DREAM"/><category term="마지막 첫사랑 (My First and Last)" label="마지막 첫사랑 (My First and Last)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더_브릿지_The_Bridge/시간이_지나가도/</id><title>더_브릿지_The_Bridge - 시간이 지나가도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:30:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:30:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94_%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80_The_Bridge/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B0%84%EC%9D%B4_%EC%A7%80%EB%82%98%EA%B0%80%EB%8F%84/" title="더_브릿지_The_Bridge - 시간이 지나가도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[조금은 무뎌진 듯하죠 <br>눈물 속에 살던 난데 <br>요즘은 덤덤한 내 모습에 <br>마음이 아파오죠 <br>사랑했는데 <br>어떻게 이렇게 끝나 <br>하루도 잊지 못해요 <br>시간이 지나가도 그대로인데 <br>사랑했던 그대 두고서 <br>떠날 수가 없는데 <br>언제나 이 자리에 <br>있다는 걸 기억해 <br>늘 항상 너의 뒤에서 <br>난 기다릴게 <br>요즘은 덤덤한 내 모습에 <br>마음이 아파오죠 <br>사랑했는데 <br>어떻게 이렇게 끝나 <br>하루도 잊지 못해요 <br>시간이 지나가도 그대로인데 <br>사랑했던 그대 두고서 <br>떠날 수가 없는데 <br>언제나 이 자리에 <br>있다는 걸 기억해 <br>늘 항상 너의 뒤에서 <br>난 기다릴게 <br>사랑해 우리 아름답던 <br>사랑을 어떻게 지우니 <br>하루가 짧았었던 <br>우리였어 어떻게 <br>시간이 지나가도 그대로인데 <br>사랑했던 그대 두고서 <br>떠날 수가 없는데 <br>언제나 이 자리에 <br>있다는 걸 기억해 <br>늘 항상 너의 뒤에서 <br>난 기다릴게 <br>]]></content><category term="더 브릿지 (The Bridge)" label="더 브릿지 (The Bridge)"/><category term="시간이 지나가도" label="시간이 지나가도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SUPERBEE/Pattern_Feat_Tiger_JK_Double_K_Junoflo_myunDo/</id><title>SUPERBEE - Pattern (Feat. Tiger JK, Double K, Junoflo, myunDo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:31:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:31:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SUPERBEE/Pattern_Feat_Tiger_JK_Double_K_Junoflo_myunDo/" title="SUPERBEE - Pattern (Feat. Tiger JK, Double K, Junoflo, myunDo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Finally i made it <br>그게 나잖아 like eyday <br>이제 17년생 아가들은 <br>벌띠야 올핸 내 해 <br>야 기억나네 <br>스물둘 계란머리 <br>소년 둘 맨땅에 쿵 <br>홍대앞거리 작업방에 푸고 <br>바랜 꿈이 현실로 빛 발했구 <br>오늘 i met JK <br>내 image hyung <br>doesn't care anything <br>주노플로형 got juno's flow <br>바로 전화걸어 <br>ryoji형 한테 brrr <br>미술관보다 훨 큰 그림 그려 <br>IQ 검사기도 못 투영 <br>해 내 머리 속 돈벌이 <br>인출하러가 3D 프린트로 치징 <br>All i do is feel good music <br>허나 너를 위한 것은 아냐 <br>내 Rap은 내가 최고란 <br>불편한 주제들을 다루잖아 <br>yeah that's why i'm doing it <br>but 니 빡에 퓨즈선이 빠지잖어 <br>탓은 마 난 나를 위해 하고 <br>가족들하고 모든 밥을 나눠 <br>I'm bout that gHood life gHood <br>life <br>get my money then call it a night <br>if you don't know it's really <br>cause you ain't about this life <br>이때쯤 터 터 터 <br>터트려주는 역전 샴페인 <br>배로 받는 복 <br>여기는 근하신년 everyday <br>I'm bout that gHood life gHood <br>life <br>get my money then call it a night <br>if you don't know it's really <br>cause you ain't about this life <br>이때쯤 터 터 터 <br>터트려주는 역전 샴페인 <br>배로 받는 복 <br>여기는 근하신년 everyday <br>Too many 짭's <br>Too many 탈을 쓴 <br>Too many two faced <br>Too many lies <br>Too many Anderson Varaja <br>Too many Hollywood action <br>Too many flobs <br>Too many 랩퍼's <br>Too many wangsters <br>Too many wanna be's <br>wanna be gangster <br>Too many 쎈척 <br>쓰여진 character <br>카메라 켜지면 <br>변하는 acters <br>Man I just can't pretend <br>맨날 다 똑같은 니들 얘기 <br>I just can't relate <br>놔줄께 내 랩 주사 맞고 <br>정신차려 붓기 빼 <br>화면빨 잘 받아야 앞으로 <br>쭉 계속 연예인 놀이해 <br>너네들은 카페에서 <br>떠드는 아줌마들보다 <br>말이 더 많아 <br>Never asked for your history <br>별로 관심은 없어 <br>너에 대한 상황 <br>Yeah JUNO a young god <br>외계인에서 받은 이 영감 <br>드문 주파수를 타고 <br>다른 차원으로 이동해 <br>남은 기운에 <br>이미 난 준비됐어 <br>불행들 안 미안해 <br>CCTV 처럼 뒷담화 잡아내 <br>See me <br>better hold your breath <br>니 기저귀들이나 <br>가서 갈아내 <br>낑킹 나는 왕이 돼 <br>But still never take a holiday <br>I'm proud to say <br>That my money flowing straight <br>Wsup <br>I'm bout that gHood life gHood <br>life <br>get my money then call it a night <br>if you don't know it's really <br>cause you ain't about this life <br>이때쯤 터 터 터 <br>터트려주는 역전 샴페인 <br>배로 받는 복 <br>여기는 근하신년 everyday <br>I'm bout that gHood life gHood <br>life <br>get my money then call it a night <br>if you don't know it's really <br>cause you ain't about this life <br>이때쯤 터 터 터 <br>터트려주는 역전 샴페인 <br>배로 받는 복 <br>여기는 근하신년 everyday <br>날 조준하려 들지말어 <br>니들 머리카락만 <br>더 들켜 얘 <br>왜 못 벌어서 날 미워해 <br>보니 지 나잇값두 <br>못 벌어 얜 <br>그거 대출도 못 받어야 <br>아냐 얘 거 내 책임 woo <br>그렇게 해선 can't get it <br>야 찔리면 너만 솥되지 woo <br>#암해피 미세먼지까지 <br>기뻐 sniffin <br>증명하라니 니 검사를 <br>내가 왜 받어 지금 2017 <br>태도는 뭔 태도 태권도도 <br>배울시간 없어 <br>ah you 90's kid <br>의식있는 척하는 건 좋은데 <br>멍청하면 마이너스지 ya <br>면도 역시 <br>That's what yall gon say <br>when the verse is over <br>내가 마지막인데엔 <br>다 이유가 있어 <br>8 bars enough yo <br>cuz I bring my A game <br>all the time 24 7 errday <br>Been like this <br>since way way way way <br>before I even got famous <br>Saw it saw it saw it coming <br>Told you I be gettin hunnids <br>y'all thought young gimchi <br>just bluffin <br>Young gimchis making dough <br>from nothing <br>82 life I'm about it <br>It ain't over said JK 사장님 <br>It's over when I say so <br>and Imma keep doin this thang <br>man you know that I got it <br>I'm bout that gHood life gHood <br>life <br>get my money then call it a night <br>if you don't know it's really <br>cause you ain't about this life <br>이때쯤 터 터 터 <br>터트려주는 역전 샴페인 <br>배로 받는 복 <br>여기는 근하신년 everyday <br>I'm bout that gHood life gHood <br>life <br>get my money then call it a night <br>if you don't know it's really <br>cause you ain't about this life <br>이때쯤 터 터 터 <br>터트려주는 역전 샴페인 <br>배로 받는 복 <br>여기는 근하신년 everyday <br>]]></content><category term="SUPERBEE" label="SUPERBEE"/><category term="Pattern (Feat. Tiger JK, Double K, Junoflo, myunDo)" label="Pattern (Feat. Tiger JK, Double K, Junoflo, myunDo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리틀_뮤즈/한민족_희망/</id><title>리틀_뮤즈 - 한민족 희망 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:31:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:31:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%ED%8B%80_%EB%AE%A4%EC%A6%88/%ED%95%9C%EB%AF%BC%EC%A1%B1_%ED%9D%AC%EB%A7%9D/" title="리틀_뮤즈 - 한민족 희망 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한민족 희망 한 핏줄 자손 <br>우리의 소원은 통일 <br>우리의 소원은 통일 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아라리요 <br>아리랑 고개로 넘어간다 <br>위대한 한글을 쓰는 우리는 <br>한민족 한반도 한겨레 <br>힘차게 뻗어간 태백산맥 <br>풍부한 자원과 힘을 가졌다 <br>금강산 설악산 화려한 자연 <br>예술 문화 경제 체육이 뭉치면 <br>아리랑 세계에 울려 퍼지리라 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아라리요 <br>아리랑 고개로 넘어간다 <br>우리나라 좋아 <br>근데 걱정이 있지 <br>반쪽 짜리 나라 <br>우리나라 밖에 없지 <br>너 너 나 나 너나 나눌 것 없이 <br>합치면 뭐든지 좋아 <br>진짜 통일은 좋아 <br>세계의 길목 우리 한반도 <br>풍습과 음식이 같은 민족 <br>힘차게 뻗어간 태백산맥 <br>풍부한 자원과 힘을 가졌다 <br>두만강 낙동강 화려한 자연 <br>지혜와 사랑의 과학이 뭉치면 <br>아리랑 세계에 울려 퍼지리라 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아라리요 <br>아리랑 고개로 넘어간다 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아라리요 <br>아리랑 고개로 넘어간다 <br>우리의 소원은 통일 <br>]]></content><category term="리틀 뮤즈" label="리틀 뮤즈"/><category term="한민족 희망" label="한민족 희망"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리듬킹/마주치는_눈빛_Offical_Remix/</id><title>리듬킹 - 마주치는 눈빛 (Offical Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:31:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:31:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%93%AC%ED%82%B9/%EB%A7%88%EC%A3%BC%EC%B9%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%88%88%EB%B9%9B_Offical_Remix/" title="리듬킹 - 마주치는 눈빛 (Offical Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You make make make <br>make make make me <br>You make make make <br>You make make make <br>make make make me <br>You make make make <br>마주치는 눈빛 <br>You You make me <br>You You <br>마주치는 눈빛 <br>You make make make make me <br>You make make make <br>You make make make make me <br>You make make make <br>You make make make <br>make make make me <br>You make make make <br>You make make make <br>make make make me <br>You make make make <br>You You make me <br>You You <br>마주치는 눈빛 <br>You make make make <br>make make make me <br>You make make make <br>You make make make <br>make make make me <br>You make make make <br>You make make make <br>make make make me <br>You make make make <br>You make make make <br>make make make me <br>You You make me <br>마주치는 눈빛 <br>눈빛 <br>눈빛 <br>눈빛 <br>마주치는 눈빛 <br>마주치는 눈빛 <br>눈빛 <br>눈빛 <br>눈빛 <br>마주치는 눈빛 <br>]]></content><category term="리듬킹" label="리듬킹"/><category term="마주치는 눈빛 (Offical Remix)" label="마주치는 눈빛 (Offical Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리듬킹/마주치는_눈빛_Feat_이민수_Radio_Edit/</id><title>리듬킹 - 마주치는 눈빛 (Feat. 이민수) (Radio Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:31:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:31:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%93%AC%ED%82%B9/%EB%A7%88%EC%A3%BC%EC%B9%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%88%88%EB%B9%9B_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%EB%AF%BC%EC%88%98_Radio_Edit/" title="리듬킹 - 마주치는 눈빛 (Feat. 이민수) (Radio Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마주치는 눈빛 <br>마주치는 눈빛 <br>We down get down on earth <br>We down get down on earth <br>Fat purse here you <br>I know where you <br>I got it got it <br>마주치는 눈빛 <br>We down get down on earth <br>We down get down on earth <br>Fat purse here you <br>I know where you <br>I got it got it <br>마주치는 눈빛 <br>We down get down on earth <br>Hang on to your hat <br>We down get down on earth <br>Hold on to your pants <br>Fat purse here you go <br>I know where you go <br>I got it got it <br>마주치는 눈빛 <br>You make me feel so high <br>You make me feel so high <br>You make me feel so high <br>You make me <br>마주치는 눈빛 <br>You You make me You You <br>You make make make <br>make make make me <br>You make make make <br>You make make make <br>make make make me <br>You make make make <br>You make make make <br>make make make me <br>You make make make <br>You make make make <br>make make make me <br>You You make me <br>마주치는 눈빛 <br>You make me feel so high <br>You make me feel so high <br>You make me feel so high <br>You make me <br>마주치는 눈빛 <br>I'm dancing all night <br>Music for a better life <br>We dance the whole night through <br>I've got a good life <br>Catching the butterfly <br>We are dancing all night <br>You make me feel so high <br>You make me feel so high <br>You make me feel so high <br>You make me <br>마주치는 마주치는 마주치는 <br>마주치는 눈빛이 <br>]]></content><category term="리듬킹" label="리듬킹"/><category term="마주치는 눈빛 (Feat. 이민수) (Radio Edit)" label="마주치는 눈빛 (Feat. 이민수) (Radio Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리듬킹/Gossip_Feat_류선생/</id><title>리듬킹 - Gossip (Feat. 류선생) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:31:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:31:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%93%AC%ED%82%B9/Gossip_Feat_%EB%A5%98%EC%84%A0%EC%83%9D/" title="리듬킹 - Gossip (Feat. 류선생) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You know I need ya <br>I like ya <br>I want ya so <br>Already told ya <br>I'd like to know ya <br>You know I need ya <br>I like ya <br>I want ya so <br>Already told ya <br>I'd like to know ya <br>give me give me give me <br>give me give me give your love <br>like you like you like you <br>like you like you like you <br>like you girls <br>give me give me give me <br>give me give me give me give your love <br>like you like you like you <br>like you like you like you <br>like you boys <br>You know I need ya <br>I like ya <br>I want ya so <br>Already told ya <br>I'd like to know ya <br>You know I need ya <br>I like ya <br>I want ya so <br>Already told ya <br>I'd like to know ya <br>give me give me give me <br>give me give me give your love <br>like you like you like you <br>like you like you like you <br>like you girls <br>give me give me give me <br>give me give me give me give your love <br>like you like you like you <br>like you like you like you <br>like you boys <br>give me give me give me <br>give me give me give your love <br>like you like you like you <br>like you like you like you <br>like you girls <br>give me give me give me <br>give me give me give me give your love <br>like you like you like you <br>like you like you like you <br>like you boys <br>give me give me give me <br>give me give me give your love <br>like you like you like you <br>like you like you like you <br>like you girls <br>give me give me give me <br>give me give me give me give your love <br>like you like you like you <br>like you like you like you <br>like you boys <br>]]></content><category term="리듬킹" label="리듬킹"/><category term="Gossip (Feat. 류선생)" label="Gossip (Feat. 류선생)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리듬킹/A_Nocturn_Feat_이세라/</id><title>리듬킹 - A Nocturn (Feat. 이세라) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:31:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:31:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%93%AC%ED%82%B9/A_Nocturn_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B8%EB%9D%BC/" title="리듬킹 - A Nocturn (Feat. 이세라) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What's your name <br>rhythmking <br>Oh My darling you <br>Do you like me <br>I love you <br>Oh My darling you <br>Do you like me <br>I love you <br>Oh My darling you <br>Do you like me <br>I love you <br>Oh My darling you <br>Do you like me <br>I love you <br>Oh My darling you <br>Do you like me <br>I love you <br>Oh My darling you <br>Do you like me <br>I love you <br>Do you like me <br>]]></content><category term="리듬킹" label="리듬킹"/><category term="A Nocturn (Feat. 이세라)" label="A Nocturn (Feat. 이세라)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍진영/사랑한다_안한다/</id><title>홍진영 - 사랑한다 안한다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:31:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:31:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%A7%84%EC%98%81/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%9C%EB%8B%A4_%EC%95%88%ED%95%9C%EB%8B%A4/" title="홍진영 - 사랑한다 안한다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날 사랑한다 안한다 <br>사랑한다 안한다 <br>꽃잎 떼어 보는 이 마음 <br>날 사랑한다 안한다 <br>애타는 이내가슴 <br>난 그대 없이 못 산답니다 <br>바람아 나를 어서 데려 가 주렴 <br>내 님 있는 곳으로 <br>달님아 환희 밝게 비추어다오 <br>내 님이 어디 있는지 <br>사는 동안 그리워 눈물 날 때면 <br>내 마음 쉬도록 부르는 이름 <br>서글플 때나 또 속상할 때나 <br>생각나는 오직 한사람 <br>날 사랑한다 안한다 <br>사랑한다 안한다 <br>꽃잎 떼어 보는 이 마음 <br>날 사랑한다 안한다 <br>애타는 이내가슴 <br>난 그대 없이 못 산답니다 <br>세상일에 쫓기며 하룰 살아도 <br>어쩌면 그리 당신 생각이나 <br>되는 일 없을 때 나 마음지칠 때 <br>생각나는 오직 한사람 <br>날 사랑한다 안한다 <br>사랑한다 안한다 <br>꽃잎 떼어 보는 이 마음 <br>날 사랑한다 안한다 <br>애타는 이내가슴 <br>난 그대 없인 못 산답니다 <br>어느 곳이든 갈수 있어요 <br>세상의 어떤 곳이라 해도 <br>슬픈 사랑은 싫어요 <br>아픈 것도 싫어요 <br>내 곁에 와줄수 없나요 <br>날 사랑한다 안한다 <br>애타는 이내가슴 <br>난 그대 없인 못 산답니다 <br>]]></content><category term="홍진영" label="홍진영"/><category term="사랑한다 안한다" label="사랑한다 안한다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김댕/Calendar/</id><title>김댕 - Calendar - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:31:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:31:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%8C%95/Calendar/" title="김댕 - Calendar - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뭐 한 것도 없는데 벌써 <br>달력이 열두 장이 <br>넘어갔네 멈춰 <br>You stay to stay here <br>넌 너무 부지런해 <br>내겐 부질없네 <br>무엇이 무엇이 똑같을까 <br>노랠 부른 아이에게 답해줄까 <br>You stay here <br>어쩜 이리 똑같을까 <br>내 Before after가 <br>연예인 사진 보고 <br>다이어트 한다고 <br>꼭 몸짱이 돼서 <br>여름을 준비하겠다고 <br>끊은 헬스장은 <br>한 열흘쯤 나갔나 <br>악기 하나 정도는 <br>다룰 줄 알아야 해 <br>피아노가 좋을까 <br>아님 기타가 좋을까 <br>고민하다가 <br>왠지 어려워 보여 <br>시간은 참 빨라 빨라 빨라 <br>내 맘과는 참 달라 달라 달라 <br>계절은 올 때마다 <br>I think about <br>낯설어 또 달라 달라 달라 <br>시간은 참 빨라 빨라 빨라 <br>내 맘과는 참 달라 달라 달라 <br>매년 먹는 나이인데도 <br>아닌가 봐 <br>낯설어 또 달라 달라 달라 <br>너는 자꾸 앞서가 <br>Like rabbit but i'm 난 <br>거북아 Don't stay here <br>말해봐도 매일 <br>잡히지 않는 Main <br>맘먹는 건 <br>먹방조차 부럽지 않아 <br>소화가 안돼 <br>할래 내일 <br>맘을 다잡아도 매일 <br>어차피 Stop 삼일 <br>학교를 졸업하면 <br>내가 하고 싶은 일을 <br>마음껏 하며 살아가리라 <br>다짐했던 <br>철없던 자신감은 <br>어디로 사라지고 <br>쳇바퀴 굴러가듯 <br>흘러가는 하루에 <br>SNS 보며 부러워하고 있는 <br>나를 보게 돼 <br>나만 이런 거야 뭐야 <br>시간은 참 빨라 빨라 빨라 <br>내 맘과는 참 달라 달라 달라 <br>계절은 올 때마다 <br>I think about <br>낯설어 또 달라 달라 달라 <br>시간은 참 빨라 빨라 빨라 <br>내 맘과는 참 달라 달라 달라 <br>매년 먹는 나이인데도 <br>아닌가 봐 <br>낯설어 또 달라 달라 달라 <br>달력을 넘기다 보니 <br>어느새 이렇게 <br>시간이 훌쩍 지나가버리고 <br>작년에는 무얼 했을까 <br>올해는 무얼 해볼까 <br>생각하다가 문득 <br>I think about <br>시간은 참 빨라 빨라 빨라 <br>내 맘과는 참 달라 달라 달라 <br>계절은 올 때마다 <br>I think about <br>낯설어 또 달라 달라 달라 <br>시간은 참 빨라 빨라 빨라 <br>내 맘과는 참 달라 달라 달라 <br>매년 먹는 나이인데도 <br>아닌가 봐 <br>낯설어 또 달라 달라 달라 <br>]]></content><category term="김댕" label="김댕"/><category term="Calendar" label="Calendar"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wheezymay/파도앞에_선_우리는/</id><title>Wheezymay - 파도앞에 선 우리는 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:31:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:31:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wheezymay/%ED%8C%8C%EB%8F%84%EC%95%9E%EC%97%90_%EC%84%A0_%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94/" title="Wheezymay - 파도앞에 선 우리는 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[검은 하늘 <br>쏟아지는 빗방울 <br>차가운 바다 <br>온몸을 부딪혀 <br>산산히 조각나 <br>흔적도 찾을 수 없게 <br>미련스런 눈물 쓸어 <br>흔적하나 남지않게 <br>눈앞이 흐려지고 <br>가슴이 메어지고 <br>추억이 흩어지고 <br>시간이 사라진다 <br>눈앞이 흐려지고 <br>가슴이 메어지고 <br>추억이 흩어지고 <br>시간이 사라진다 <br>떨어진다 <br>부서진다 <br>흩어진다 <br>사라진다 <br>떨어진다 <br>부서진다 <br>흩어진다 <br>사라져간다 <br>]]></content><category term="Wheezy`may" label="Wheezy`may"/><category term="파도앞에 선 우리는" label="파도앞에 선 우리는"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이승연/바다/</id><title>이승연 - 바다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:31:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:31:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%B9%EC%97%B0/%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%A4/" title="이승연 - 바다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무도 없는 깊은 바다에 <br>힘든 생각은 필요 없어 <br>가만히 누워 떠내려가다가 <br>더 깊이 내려간다 <br>쫓아오는 파도는 <br>이런 나를 모르는지 <br>날 자꾸만 밖으로 <br>데려가려 하는데 <br>그럴 용기 없다고 <br>수백 번을 도망쳐도 <br>다시 되돌아오는데 <br>날 이해해줘 <br>저 멀리 나는 새들과 <br>난 너무 다르잖아 <br>난 무서워져 <br>갈수록 내 맘이 놀랄 거야 <br>나를 이해해줘 <br>따라오는 새벽은 <br>이런 나를 아는 건지 <br>아득한 그 품으로 <br>안아주려 하는데 <br>그럴 의미 없다고 <br>수백 번을 도망쳐도 <br>다시 되돌아오는데 <br>날 이해해줘 <br>저 멀리 나는 새들과 <br>난 너무 다르잖아 <br>난 무서워져 <br>갈수록 내 맘이 놀랄 거야 <br>나를 이해해줘 <br>내가 흘러갈 수 있게 <br>내가 두려워서 <br>내가 흘러갈 수 있게 <br>난 다르잖아 <br>흘러갈 수 있게 <br>혼자 두지 마 <br>난 흘러가고 싶어 <br>날 이해해줘 <br>저 멀리 나는 새들과 <br>난 너무 다르잖아 <br>난 무서워져 <br>갈수록 내 맘이 놀랄 거야 <br>나를 이해해줘 <br>]]></content><category term="이승연" label="이승연"/><category term="바다" label="바다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/검랑태환/님이여/</id><title>검랑태환 - 님이여 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:32:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:32:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B2%80%EB%9E%91%ED%83%9C%ED%99%98/%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%B4%EC%97%AC/" title="검랑태환 - 님이여 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1.꿈을꿨어요 날 버린 그사람 봤어요 <br> 꿈에서도 나를 버리고 떠나가네요. <br> 우리서로 미워해도 원망하지마 <br> 돌아서서 가는 나를 붙잡지도마 <br> 미련없이 보내 줘야지. <br> 눈물로 하소연해도 <br> 어짜피 가버린 당신 <br> 애걸복걸도 소용없더라 <br> 울어도 보고 빌어도 보고 모두다 소용없더라 <br> 이미 가~버린 님이여~ <br><br>2.꿈을꿨어요 날 버린 그사람 봤어요 <br> 꿈에서도 나를 버리고 떠나가네요. <br> 우리서로 미워해도 원망하지마 <br> 돌아서서 가는 나를 붙잡지도마 <br> 미련없이 보내 줘야지. <br> 눈물로 하소연해도 <br> 어짜피 가버린 당신 <br> 애걸복걸도 소용없더라 <br> 울어도 보고 빌어도 보고 모두다 소용없더라 <br> 이미 가~버린 님이여~]]></content><category term="검랑태환" label="검랑태환"/><category term="님이여" label="님이여"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김윤아/연_Inst/</id><title>김윤아 - 연 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:32:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:32:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9C%A4%EC%95%84/%EC%97%B0_Inst/" title="김윤아 - 연 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꿈에도 그리운 곳 <br>고요한 물빛 <br>새벽이 잦아드네 <br>아스라이 <br>외로운 하늘가에 <br>요요한 달빛 <br>새들이 날아드네 <br>어지러이 <br>흐느끼는 바람에 <br>흩날리는 마음은 <br>다시 못 올 날의 <br>노래가 그리워 <br>흐드러진 꽃이 <br>흩어지는 연이 <br>하염없이 지네 <br>애처로이 지네 <br>아름다운 님이여 <br>언젠가 다시 <br>그 노래 들려주오 <br>꿈에도 그리운 곳 <br>고요한 물빛 <br>가슴에 잦아드네 <br>아스라이 <br>외로운 하늘가에 <br>요요한 달빛 <br>기억이 날아드네 <br>어지러이 <br>흐느끼는 바람에 <br>흩날리는 마음은 <br>다시 못 올 날의 <br>노래가 그리워 <br>흐드러진 꽃이 <br>흩어지는 연이 <br>하염없이 지네 <br>애처로이 지네 <br>아름다운 님이여 <br>언제 그리 <br>다시 돌아가려오 <br>아름다운 님이여 <br>그 노래 들려주오 <br>]]></content><category term="김윤아" label="김윤아"/><category term="연 (Inst.)" label="연 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김윤아/연/</id><title>김윤아 - 연 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:32:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:32:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9C%A4%EC%95%84/%EC%97%B0/" title="김윤아 - 연 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꿈에도 그리운 곳 <br>고요한 물빛 <br>새벽이 잦아드네 <br>아스라이 <br>외로운 하늘가에 <br>요요한 달빛 <br>새들이 날아드네 <br>어지러이 <br>흐느끼는 바람에 <br>흩날리는 마음은 <br>다시 못 올 날의 <br>노래가 그리워 <br>흐드러진 꽃이 <br>흩어지는 연이 <br>하염없이 지네 <br>애처로이 지네 <br>아름다운 님이여 <br>언젠가 다시 <br>그 노래 들려주오 <br>꿈에도 그리운 곳 <br>고요한 물빛 <br>가슴에 잦아드네 <br>아스라이 <br>외로운 하늘가에 <br>요요한 달빛 <br>기억이 날아드네 <br>어지러이 <br>흐느끼는 바람에 <br>흩날리는 마음은 <br>다시 못 올 날의 <br>노래가 그리워 <br>흐드러진 꽃이 <br>흩어지는 연이 <br>하염없이 지네 <br>애처로이 지네 <br>아름다운 님이여 <br>언제 그리 <br>다시 돌아가려오 <br>아름다운 님이여 <br>그 노래 들려주오 <br>]]></content><category term="김윤아" label="김윤아"/><category term="연" label="연"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스티_STi/We_Click/</id><title>스티_STi - We Click - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:33:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:33:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B0_STi/We_Click/" title="스티_STi - We Click - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 처음 만날 때만 해도 <br>왠지 어울리지 <br>않다고 느꼈었는데 <br>어느 순간 참 놀랍게도 <br>너의 모든 곳에 <br>내 모습이 보여 <br>내가 널 닮아간걸까 <br>아님 니가 날 닮아준걸까 <br>Woo Baby 난 이 세상 <br>어떤 누구보다 <br>널 잘 알아 니가 곧 나니까 <br>We Click We Click <br>We Feel The Same Everytime <br>어디에 있어도 <br>널 볼 수 있어 <br>We Click We Click <br>We See The Same All The Time <br>나 같은 사람이 <br>또 있었다니 <br>Wo Wo Wo Wo Wo Wo Woo <br>아침부터 밤까지 <br>하나부터 열까지 <br>또 다른 나를 <br>보는 것 같아 Woo <br>난 널 만나기 전과 후로 <br>왠지 내 인생이 <br>나눠진 것만 같아 <br>가끔 혼자 있을땐 <br>하루종일 감정이 메말라 <br>너도 날 닮았으니까 <br>아마 이 느낌을 잘 알꺼야 <br>Woo Baby 넌 이 세상 <br>어떤 누구보다 <br>날 잘 알아 내가 곧 너니까 <br>We Click We Click <br>We Feel The Same Everytime <br>어디에 있어도 널 볼 수 있어 <br>We Click We Click <br>We See The Same All The Time <br>나 같은 사람이 또 있었다니 <br>Wo Wo Wo Wo Wo Wo Woo <br>아침부터 밤까지 <br>하나부터 열까지 <br>또 다른 나를 <br>보는 것 같아 Oh <br>I'm Your Mirror <br>You're My Mirror <br>서롤 믿어 <br>내가 가진 생각을 <br>I'm Your Shadow <br>You're My Shadow <br>함께라면 새로운 <br>너도 생각했을 때 <br>I'm Your Weather <br>You're My Weather <br>이 기분도 그대로 <br>놀라는 반응까지 비슷해 <br>역시 우린 잘 통하는 <br>We Click We Click <br>위기도 겁내지마 <br>서로가 서로를 지켜주니까 <br>괜찮아 우린 아직 <br>지금보다 나빠질 <br>그런 일들은 없을 것 같아 Oh <br>I'm Your Mirror <br>You're My Mirror <br>서롤 믿어 <br>니가 가진 생각을 <br>I'm Your Shadow <br>You're My Shadow <br>함께라면 새로운 <br>나도 생각했을 때 <br>I'm Your Weather <br>You're My Weather <br>이 기분도 그대로 <br>Umm 넌 또 하나의 나 <br>]]></content><category term="스티 (STi)" label="스티 (STi)"/><category term="We Click" label="We Click"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/팬시_FANXY/섬/</id><title>팬시_FANXY - 섬 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:33:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:33:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8C%AC%EC%8B%9C_FANXY/%EC%84%AC/" title="팬시_FANXY - 섬 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무도 없는 방 혼자 눈을 뜨면 <br>아침에 뭐 먹지 잠깐 고민하고 <br>늘 같은 풍경 속 나무 의자처럼 <br>자리를 바꿔가며 바래져 가네 <br>핸드폰 속에는 여러 개의 창문 <br>두드려 볼 때도 가끔은 있지만 <br>커다란 우주 속을 떠다니듯이 <br>누군가 와 닿기는 어려워 보이네 <br>아주 잠깐 선명해지는 순간 <br>발견해야 해 <br>아주 살짝 맘을 스치는 순간 <br>알아봐야 해 <br>I'm gonna find it <br>I'll find it out <br>꿈을 꾸듯 아스라이 보이는 <br>네게 닿긴 어려워 보이네 <br>나는 섬 <br>푸른 바달 건너야 만나는 섬 <br>작게 보이는 <br>너는 섬 <br>배를 타고 떠나야 닿는 섬 <br>오 오 <br>아무도 없는 밤 잠을 깨면 <br>저 멀리 별빛이 내게 손짓하고 <br>또 다른 우주 속을 헤엄치듯이 <br>고요히 반짝거리는 꿈을 꾸네 <br>아주 잠깐 여길 떠나는 순간 <br>발견해야 해 <br>아주 잠깐 반짝거리는 순간 <br>알아봐야 해 <br>I'm gonna find it <br>I'll find it out <br>너와 나를 가로지른 바다 위를 <br>걸어가는 그런 꿈을 꾸네 <br>나는 섬 <br>푸른 바달 건너야 만나는 섬 <br>작게 보이는 <br>너는 섬 <br>배를 타고 떠나야 닿는 섬 <br>오 오 <br>나는 섬 <br>푸른 바달 건너야 만나는 섬 <br>작게 보이는 <br>너는 섬 <br>배를 타고 떠나야 닿는 섬 <br>]]></content><category term="팬시 (FANXY)" label="팬시 (FANXY)"/><category term="섬" label="섬"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sofy/아주_사적인_편지_Vocal_권서영/</id><title>Sofy - 아주 사적인 편지 (Vocal 권서영) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:33:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:33:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sofy/%EC%95%84%EC%A3%BC_%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%81%EC%9D%B8_%ED%8E%B8%EC%A7%80_Vocal_%EA%B6%8C%EC%84%9C%EC%98%81/" title="Sofy - 아주 사적인 편지 (Vocal 권서영) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흘러갈 계절 속에 <br>지나갈 시간 속에 <br>그렇게 그대도 가겠지 <br>아침의 햇살처럼 <br>밤하늘 저 달처럼 <br>우리도 저물어 가겠지 <br>따듯한 순간들이 <br>무수한 기억들이 <br>조금씩 조금씩 쓰리고 <br>떨리던 목소리도 <br>떨어진 눈물들도 <br>깊숙이 스미네 <br>그대는 그곳에서 <br>이제 난 여기에서 <br>우리를 지운 채로 <br>서로를 묻어두고 <br>각자의 길을 걸어요 <br>]]></content><category term="Sofy" label="Sofy"/><category term="아주 사적인 편지 (Vocal 권서영)" label="아주 사적인 편지 (Vocal 권서영)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keep/눈이_올_것_같아_Prod_By_러블리벗/</id><title>Keep - 눈이 올 것 같아 (Prod. By 러블리벗) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:34:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:34:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keep/%EB%88%88%EC%9D%B4_%EC%98%AC_%EA%B2%83_%EA%B0%99%EC%95%84_Prod_By_%EB%9F%AC%EB%B8%94%EB%A6%AC%EB%B2%97/" title="Keep - 눈이 올 것 같아 (Prod. By 러블리벗) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈이 올 것 같아 <br>꼭 그런 하늘이야 <br>눈이 올 것 같아 <br>꼭 그런 공기야 <br>눈이 올 것 같아 <br>니가 보고싶어 <br>눈이 올 것 같아 <br>니목소리 듣고 싶어 <br>어떻게 하라고 <br>넌 내곁에 없는데 <br>어떻게 하라고 <br>너 날 떠났는데 <br>이렇게 널 찾으면 나 <br>어떻게 하라고 내마음 <br>어쩌려고 이러는건지 <br>눈이 올 것 같아 <br>꼭 그런 기분이야 <br>눈이 올 것 같아 <br>꼭 그런 예감이야 <br>눈이 올 것 같아 <br>니가 보고싶어 <br>눈이 올 것 같아 <br>니 얼굴 보고 싶어 <br>어떻게 하라고 <br>넌 내 옆에 없는데 <br>어떻게 하라고 <br>너 날 버렸는데 <br>이렇게 널 찾아도 나 <br>어쩔수 없는데 내 마음 <br>어쩌려고 이러는 건지 <br>눈 내리면 <br>눈 내리면 <br>눈 내리면 <br>눈 내리면 내리면 <br>눈 내리면 <br>어떻게 하라고 <br>넌 내 곁에 없는데 <br>어떻게 하라고 <br>너 날 떠났는데 <br>이렇게 널 찾으면 <br>나 어떻게 하라고 내 마음 <br>어쩌려고 이러는 건지 <br>눈 내리면 <br>눈 내리면 <br>눈 내리면 <br>눈 내리면 내리면 <br>눈 내리면 <br>눈이 올 것 같아 <br>]]></content><category term="Keep" label="Keep"/><category term="눈이 올 것 같아 (Prod. By 러블리벗)" label="눈이 올 것 같아 (Prod. By 러블리벗)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/타예타/어제까지/</id><title>타예타 - 어제까지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:34:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:34:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%80%EC%98%88%ED%83%80/%EC%96%B4%EC%A0%9C%EA%B9%8C%EC%A7%80/" title="타예타 - 어제까지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어제까지만 해도 <br>너를 떠올리면 <br>하루 온종일 <br>너무나 행복했어 <br>하지만 오늘은 <br>내 마음속에서 <br>널 지워냈어 <br>지금 네 행동 <br>이해가 안 돼 <br>오 이러는 이유가 뭐야 <br>그런 말까지 할 필욘 없어 <br>오 다시 생각해 <br>내가 밉겠지만 <br>마주치는 일 <br>없으면 좋겠어 <br>어제까지는 사랑한다고 <br>오 날 보며 얘기해놓고 <br>오늘 와서는 싫어졌다고 <br>오 말하면 어떡해 <br>지금 네 행동 이해가 안 돼 <br>오 이러는 이유가 뭐야 <br>그런 말까지 할 필욘 없어 <br>오 다시 생각해 <br>]]></content><category term="타예타" label="타예타"/><category term="어제까지" label="어제까지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CHITAKINGS/its_not_your_fault/</id><title>CHITAKINGS - it`s not your fault - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:34:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:34:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CHITAKINGS/its_not_your_fault/" title="CHITAKINGS - it`s not your fault - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잡지 못한 사랑도 <br>우울하게 돌아가고 <br>있는 일상들도 <br>용기 잃은 침묵도 <br>너를 괴롭히고 있는 <br>슬픈 마음들도 <br>오 it’s not your fault <br>오 it’s not your fault <br>막아버린 두 귀도 <br>벙어리가 되어 버린 <br>닫힌 몸짓들도 <br>포기했던 자신도 <br>흘러버린 후회들로 <br>가득한 이 밤 <br>오 it’s not your fault <br>오 it’s not your fault <br>어제 일어난 <br>모든 일들은 <br>오직 너만의 <br>잘못은 아니야 <br>지금부턴 모든 게 <br>괜찮아질 거야 <br>좀 더 너를 <br>사랑하길 바래 <br>오 it’s not your fault <br>오 it’s not your fault <br>오 it’s not your fault <br>오 it’s not your fault <br>오 it’s not your fault <br>오 it’s not your fault <br>]]></content><category term="CHITAKINGS" label="CHITAKINGS"/><category term="it`s not your fault" label="it`s not your fault"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CHITAKINGS/그럴_줄_알았어/</id><title>CHITAKINGS - 그럴 줄 알았어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:34:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:34:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CHITAKINGS/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%B4_%EC%A4%84_%EC%95%8C%EC%95%98%EC%96%B4/" title="CHITAKINGS - 그럴 줄 알았어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 그럴 줄 알았어 <br>어제 일어난 일 <br>달콤한 향기가 <br>우리를 붙잡네 <br>오늘은 어떨까 <br>오늘을 기대해 <br>바뀌지 않았어 <br>여전히 어제와 <br>누군가 말했지 <br>어쩔 수 없다고 <br>그래도 내일은 <br>모르는 거잖아 <br>오늘은 어떨까 <br>오늘을 기대해 <br>바뀌지 않았어 <br>여전히 그대와 <br>사랑을 말했고 <br>또 사랑을 찾았지 <br>하지만 원한 건 <br>빨간색 BMW <br>사랑을 말했고 <br>또 사랑을 찾았지 <br>하지만 원한 건 <br>빨간색 BMW <br>사랑을 말했고 <br>또 사랑을 찾았지 <br>하지만 원한 건 <br>빨간색 BMW <br>]]></content><category term="CHITAKINGS" label="CHITAKINGS"/><category term="그럴 줄 알았어" label="그럴 줄 알았어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이주아/할_수_있어/</id><title>이주아 - 할 수 있어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:34:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:34:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%A3%BC%EC%95%84/%ED%95%A0_%EC%88%98_%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4/" title="이주아 - 할 수 있어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[걱정이 많지 <br>조급하게 생각하진 마 <br>다가가고 있잖아 <br>언젠간 꼭 올 기회에 <br>아직 너는 늦지 않았어 <br>툭툭 털고 일어서는 거야 <br>아직 너는 늦지 않았어 <br>힘을 내봐 해낼 거야 꼭 <br>움츠리지 마 <br>잘못하고 있는 게 아냐 <br>정답은 없는 거야 <br>용기를 내 할 수 있어 <br>아직 너는 늦지 않았어 <br>툭툭 털고 일어서는 거야 <br>아직 너는 늦지 않았어 <br>힘을 내봐 해낼 거야 꼭 <br>오늘의 너의 꿈 <br>내일의 너의 꿈 <br>그 속의 난 언제나 <br>이렇게 널 응원해 <br>아직 너는 늦지 않았어 <br>툭툭 털고 일어서는 거야 <br>아직 너는 늦지 않았어 <br>힘을 내봐 해낼 거야 꼭 <br>]]></content><category term="이주아" label="이주아"/><category term="할 수 있어" label="할 수 있어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PS영준/Dangerous/</id><title>PS영준 - Dangerous - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:35:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:35:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PS%EC%98%81%EC%A4%80/Dangerous/" title="PS영준 - Dangerous - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[poetic S <br>she is dangerous <br>조금 특별한 여자 <br>그래서 더 끌려 <br>조금 도도한 여자 <br>날 미치게 만들어 <br>Dangerous 나도 알아 <br>너는 Dangerous Woman <br>Dangerous 감당할 수 없는 <br>Dangerous Woman <br>I wa a wa a want <br>your love I falling <br>거부할 수 없는 널 난 원해 <br>Lotto 맞을 기분에 <br>혼또니 la papapam <br>you r ma sweet fantasy <br>매일 떨려 Aphrodite <br>Oh ma god <br>Marilyn Monroe의 뒤태 <br>이 game 끝판의 <br>cheatkey를 tell me 나 <br>피 튀기게 싸워 <br>그녈 차지할래 ho <br>넌 나랑 어울려 <br>난 choco 넌 red velvet <br>cupcake Magnolia <br>Ok 돌려 말하긴 suck해 <br>날 홀려 버린 너 <br>오늘밤엔 success <br>나 좀 말려줘 <br>난 지금 정신 못 차리게 <br>흠뻑 젖어버린 아이 <br>아직 덜 익은 unrequited love <br>이래도 내 할 일은 <br>falling in love <br>조금 특별한 여자 <br>그래서 더 끌려 <br>조금 도도한 여자 <br>날 미치게 만들어 <br>Dangerous 나도 알아 <br>너는 Dangerous Woman <br>Dangerous 감당할 수 없는 <br>Dangerous Woman <br>I’m so sorry mama <br>그래도 나는 포기 못해요 <br>I’m so sorry mama <br>이 여자만은 포기 못해요 <br>Dangerous I want your love <br>I want your love <br>Dangerous I want your love <br>I want you ah ah ah want your love <br>니가 보이네 무표정이네 <br>니 머리위로 떨어지는 <br>wine색의 조명이 <br>잘게 부서지네 <br>꽃가루 흩날리며 <br>너란 holic에 다시 <br>퍼져가네 계속 번져가네 <br>넌 계속 Do만 치고 있고 <br>난 me만 쳐 <br>이제 sol직해지자 <br>untouchable girl <br>This life is a little bit scandalous <br>The life of a killer is dangerous <br>너무 위험해 니 말은 <br>remote controler <br>뛰어내리게 돼 <br>나 왜 이런지 몰라 <br>시험에 들지 말게 하옵시며 <br>말라가기 전에 <br>어서 뿌려 spring cooler <br>조금 특별한 여자 <br>그래서 더 끌려 <br>조금 도도한 여자 <br>날 미치게 만들어 <br>Dangerous 나도 알아 <br>너는 Dangerous Woman <br>Dangerous 감당할 수 없는 <br>Dangerous Woman <br>I’m so sorry mama <br>그래도 나는 포기 못해요 <br>I’m so sorry mama <br>이 여자만은 포기 못해요 <br>Dangerous I want your love <br>I want your love <br>Dangerous I want your love <br>I want you I I I want your love <br>]]></content><category term="PS영준" label="PS영준"/><category term="Dangerous" label="Dangerous"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오존_O3ohn/Kalt_Feat_JOONIE/</id><title>오존_O3ohn - Kalt (Feat. JOONIE) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:35:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:35:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EC%A1%B4_O3ohn/Kalt_Feat_JOONIE/" title="오존_O3ohn - Kalt (Feat. JOONIE) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 내 모습이 지쳐 <br>아닌 척 혼자 <br>사라지면 달라질까 <br>난 네 모습이 번져 <br>흐릿하게 <br>But stay against the wall <br>Don't run away from me <br>오 날 붙잡은 손끝이 <br>바라는 걸 알아 <br>내 마음과 다른 몸짓이 <br>향하는 걸 바라봐 <br>오 많고 많은 밤들이 <br>다 무뎌진 날 거치면 <br>옅어질 걸 알아 <br>오 난 내 마른 눈빛이 <br>말하는 걸 알아 <br>멈춰 줘 닿을 거리에 <br>아직 난 널 헤매고 있어 <br>오 날 붙잡은 손끝이 <br>원하는 걸 알아 <br>내 마음과 다른 오늘이 <br>저무는 걸 바라봐 <br>오 많고 많은 날들이 <br>다 무너진 날 삼키면 <br>사라질 걸 알아 <br>오 난 그 마른 별빛이 <br>말하는 걸 알아 <br>]]></content><category term="오존 (O3ohn)" label="오존 (O3ohn)"/><category term="Kalt (Feat. JOONIE)" label="Kalt (Feat. JOONIE)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/심재경/각종_모르쇠/</id><title>심재경 - 각종 모르쇠 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:35:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:35:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%AC%EC%9E%AC%EA%B2%BD/%EA%B0%81%EC%A2%85_%EB%AA%A8%EB%A5%B4%EC%87%A0/" title="심재경 - 각종 모르쇠 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[양심에 따라 숨김 없이 <br>사실대로 증언하겠다는 서약을 <br>있는 그대로의 진실을 <br>자세 바르게 한번 해보세요 <br>말하겠습니다 <br>존재하는 게 맞아요 <br>안 맞아요 의원님 <br>아닙니다 <br>맞죠 <br>알지 못했습니다 <br>영업비밀입니까 <br>제가 알지 못합니다 <br>아이 그니까 그러면 궁금한게 <br>저는 실제로 모릅니다 <br>그걸 어떻게 알았으까 <br>다시 물어 볼게요 <br>존재한다 안한다 예스 노 의원님 <br>전부 모르겠습니다 <br>증인 <br>증인 통화한 사실 있습니까 <br>통화한 기억이 없습니다 <br>이제 그만하시고요 <br>저는 본일이 없고 <br>그래서 알 수가 없고 <br>모조리 거짓말쟁이들입니다 <br>밝히고 싶지가 않습니다 <br>그런데 몰랐다 <br>나이가 들어서 이제 보니까 <br>이제 와서 나이 <br>핑계 대지 마시고요 <br>뭐 제가 못 들었다고 <br>말할 수는 없습니다 <br>제가 웬만해서는 <br>거친 얘기는 <br>안 하는 사람입니다만은 <br>증인 당신께서는 <br>있는 그대로의 진실을 <br>의원님 제가 증인 <br>말하지 않겠습니다 <br>모조리 거짓말쟁이들입니다 <br>]]></content><category term="심재경" label="심재경"/><category term="각종 모르쇠" label="각종 모르쇠"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레드벨/너의_마음/</id><title>레드벨 - 너의 마음 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:36:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:36:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EB%93%9C%EB%B2%A8/%EB%84%88%EC%9D%98_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C/" title="레드벨 - 너의 마음 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가끔은 궁금해지는걸 <br>네 마음 다 알지 못해서 <br>솔직한 마음이 궁금해 <br>날 사랑하는 건지 <br>아무런 문제는 없지만 <br>이렇게 지내고 있는 게 <br>정 때문인 건지 알고 싶어 <br>너의 속마음을 <br>오래 사귀었으니까 <br>그냥 사귀는 거라면 <br>그런 관계는 싫은데 <br>내 마음 이해하겠니 <br>정말 행복하니 진짜로 행복하니 <br>진심을 내게 말해주겠니 <br>널 보면 정말 너무 좋은데 <br>너도 날 보면 그러니 <br>정말 행복하니 진짜로 행복하니 <br>솔직히 내게 말해줘 <br>평생을 함께 할거라면 <br>속마음 이쯤에서 보여줘 <br>그냥 편한 사이 좋지만 <br>열정을 느끼고 싶은데 <br>보이지가 않아 <br>그냥 편한 안식처 같을 뿐 <br>행복한지 궁금해 <br>그냥 웃어 넘기지마 <br>솔직한 마음 말해줘 <br>널 사랑하는 나를 봐 <br>정말 행복하니 진짜로 행복하니 <br>진심을 내게 말해주겠니 <br>널 보면 정말 너무 좋은데 <br>너도 날 보면 그러니 <br>정말 행복하니 진짜로 행복하니 <br>솔직히 내게 말해줘 <br>평생을 함께 할거라면 <br>속마음 이쯤에서 보여줘 <br>행복하니 진짜로 행복하니 <br>진심을 내게 말해주겠니 <br>널 보면 정말 너무 좋은데 <br>너도 날 보면 그러니 <br>정말 행복하니 진짜로 행복하니 <br>솔직히 내게 말해줘 <br>평생을 함께 할거라면 <br>속마음 이쯤에서 보여줘 <br>]]></content><category term="레드벨" label="레드벨"/><category term="너의 마음" label="너의 마음"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/심재경/너무_억울해요/</id><title>심재경 - 너무 억울해요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:36:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:36:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%AC%EC%9E%AC%EA%B2%BD/%EB%84%88%EB%AC%B4_%EC%96%B5%EC%9A%B8%ED%95%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="심재경 - 너무 억울해요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여기는 더 이상 민주주의 <br>특검이 아닙니다 <br>여기는 더 이상 <br>민주주의가 아닙니다 <br>연명하네 연명하네 연명하네 <br>자백을 강요하고 있고 <br>자백을 강요하고 있어요 <br>난 아니라는데 <br>우리를 멸망시키겠다 그러고 <br>우리를 멸망시키려 해요 <br>연명하네 연명하네 연명하네 <br>너무 억울해요 연명 <br>너무 억울해요 연명 <br>너무 억울해요 <br>연명하네 연명하네 연명하네 <br>너무 억울해요 연명 <br>너무 억울해요 연명 <br>너무 억울해요 <br>연명하네 연명하네 연명하네 <br>여기는 더 이상 <br>민주주의가 아닙니다 <br>큰일났네 <br>여기는 더 이상 민주주의 <br>특검이 아닙니다 <br>자백을 강요하고 있어요 <br>연명 <br>난 아니라는데 <br>연명 <br>우리를 멸망시키려 해요 <br>연명하네 연명하네 연명하네 <br>너무 억울해요 연명 <br>너무 억울해요 연명 <br>너무 억울해요 <br>연명하네 연명하네 연명하네 <br>너무 억울해요 연명 <br>너무 억울해요 연명 <br>너무 억울해요 <br>연명하네 연명하네 연명하네 <br>염병 <br>]]></content><category term="심재경" label="심재경"/><category term="너무 억울해요" label="너무 억울해요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동요사랑/고래_가족/</id><title>동요사랑 - 고래 가족 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:36:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:36:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/%EA%B3%A0%EB%9E%98_%EA%B0%80%EC%A1%B1/" title="동요사랑 - 고래 가족 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[고래가족이 헤엄치며 <br>바다를 놀러 다녀요 <br>엄마고래 옆에 있는 <br>새끼가 귀여워 <br><br>아빠고래 어디 있나 <br>둘이서 찾아 다니죠 <br>하늘 위로 물 뿜으며 <br>장난도 치지요 <br><br>아빠고래 찾았나봐 <br>고래가족이 모였네 <br>넓은 바다 헤치며 <br>여행을 간대요 <br>여행을 간대요]]></content><category term="동요사랑" label="동요사랑"/><category term="고래 가족" label="고래 가족"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VOS/웃어_Inst/</id><title>VOS - 웃어 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:36:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:36:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VOS/%EC%9B%83%EC%96%B4_Inst/" title="VOS - 웃어 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쌀쌀하게 바람이 차 <br>감기에 걸릴 것 같은 <br>그런 날이야 <br>커피 한 잔으로 몸을 녹이며 <br>데이트 하고픈 그런 날이야 <br>지난 시간을 돌리고 <br>너를 다시 찾고 싶어 죽겠다 <br>울리지 말걸 그랬다 <br>웃어 그래야 넌 예쁘니까 <br>멀리멀리 떠나도 내 맘 편하게 <br>웃어 울어서 뭐가 좋겠어 <br>가벼운 그리움쯤으로 생각해 <br>잘 살아라 잘 지내라 <br>하루 건너 하루쯤은 <br>그 아무도 모르게 <br>너를 찾고 싶어져 <br>매일 보는 드라마 속에 <br>너를 닮은 사람이라도 <br>찾고 싶어져 <br>머저리 바보 같았던 <br>그때 그 미련함을 후회한다 <br>울리지 말걸 그랬다 <br>웃어 그래야 넌 예쁘니까 <br>멀리멀리 떠나도 내 맘 편하게 <br>웃어 울어서 뭐가 좋겠어 <br>가벼운 그리움쯤으로 생각해 <br>잘 살아라 잘 지내라 <br>사랑은 몸과 마음이 <br>멀어지면 안 되는 법 <br>살다가 울컥하면 <br>현실 속에서 나와 <br>너를 찾고 싶지만 <br>아주 먼 얘기야 <br>웃어 그래야 넌 예쁘니까 <br>멀리멀리 떠나도 내 맘 편하게 <br>웃어 울어서 뭐가 좋겠어 <br>가벼운 그리움쯤으로 생각해 <br>잘 살아라 잘 지내라 <br>잘 살아라 잘 지내라 <br>]]></content><category term="V.O.S" label="V.O.S"/><category term="웃어 (Inst.)" label="웃어 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VOS/웃어/</id><title>VOS - 웃어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:36:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:36:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VOS/%EC%9B%83%EC%96%B4/" title="VOS - 웃어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쌀쌀하게 바람이 차 <br>감기에 걸릴 것 같은 <br>그런 날이야 <br>커피 한 잔으로 몸을 녹이며 <br>데이트 하고픈 그런 날이야 <br>지난 시간을 돌리고 <br>너를 다시 찾고 싶어 죽겠다 <br>울리지 말걸 그랬다 <br>웃어 그래야 넌 예쁘니까 <br>멀리멀리 떠나도 내 맘 편하게 <br>웃어 울어서 뭐가 좋겠어 <br>가벼운 그리움쯤으로 생각해 <br>잘 살아라 잘 지내라 <br>하루 건너 하루쯤은 <br>그 아무도 모르게 <br>너를 찾고 싶어져 <br>매일 보는 드라마 속에 <br>너를 닮은 사람이라도 <br>찾고 싶어져 <br>머저리 바보 같았던 <br>그때 그 미련함을 후회한다 <br>울리지 말걸 그랬다 <br>웃어 그래야 넌 예쁘니까 <br>멀리멀리 떠나도 내 맘 편하게 <br>웃어 울어서 뭐가 좋겠어 <br>가벼운 그리움쯤으로 생각해 <br>잘 살아라 잘 지내라 <br>사랑은 몸과 마음이 <br>멀어지면 안 되는 법 <br>살다가 울컥하면 <br>현실 속에서 나와 <br>너를 찾고 싶지만 <br>아주 먼 얘기야 <br>웃어 그래야 넌 예쁘니까 <br>멀리멀리 떠나도 내 맘 편하게 <br>웃어 울어서 뭐가 좋겠어 <br>가벼운 그리움쯤으로 생각해 <br>잘 살아라 잘 지내라 <br>잘 살아라 잘 지내라 <br>]]></content><category term="V.O.S" label="V.O.S"/><category term="웃어" label="웃어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박정수/아네모네/</id><title>박정수 - 아네모네 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T11:37:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T11:37:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A0%95%EC%88%98/%EC%95%84%EB%84%A4%EB%AA%A8%EB%84%A4/" title="박정수 - 아네모네 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세상에 미운 꽃들은 <br>그윽한 향이 아름답고 <br>예쁘고 고운 꽃들은 <br>열매를 맺지 못한대요 <br>너무나 사랑 했지만 <br>이루지 못한 우리사랑 <br>사랑의 고통 <br>그 아픔 까지도 <br>소중 했어요 <br>나는 어둠 속에 <br>홀로 피는 아네 모네 <br>당신의 그리움에 <br>외로운 남자에요 <br>나는 바람 속에 <br>홀로 우는 아네 모네 <br>당신의 보고픔에 <br>고독한 남자에요 <br>미치게 안고 싶지만 <br>가질 수 없는 그대 사랑 <br>이별의 고통 <br>그 슬픔 까지도 <br>사랑 했어요 <br>나는 어둠 속에 <br>홀로 피는 아네 모네 <br>당신의 그리움에 <br>외로운 남자에요 <br>나는 바람 속에 <br>홀로 우는 아네 모네 <br>당신의 보고픔에 <br>고독한 남자에요 <br>미치게 안고 싶지만 <br>가질 수 없는 그대 사랑 <br>이별의 고통 <br>그 슬픔 까지도 <br>사랑 했어요 <br>]]></content><category term="박정수" label="박정수"/><category term="아네모네" label="아네모네"/></entry></feed>