<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:42:42+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전병훈/한강수타령/</id><title>전병훈 - 한강수타령 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:42:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:42:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EB%B3%91%ED%9B%88/%ED%95%9C%EA%B0%95%EC%88%98%ED%83%80%EB%A0%B9/" title="전병훈 - 한강수타령 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한강수라 깊고 <br>맑은 물에 <br>수상선 타고서 <br>에루화 뱃놀이 가잔다 <br>아아 에헤요 <br>에헤요 어허야 <br>얼사함마 둥게디여라 <br>내사랑아 <br>한강수야 네가 <br>말을 하렴아 <br>눈물둔 영웅이 <br>몇몇줄을 지은고 <br>아아 에헤요 <br>에헤요 어허야 <br>얼사함마 둥게디여라 <br>내사랑아 <br>멀리뵈는 관악산 <br>웅장도 하고 <br>돛단배 두서넛 <br>에루화 한가도 하다 <br>아아 에헤요 <br>에헤요 어허야 <br>얼사함마 둥게디여라 <br>내사랑아 <br>유유히 흐르는 <br>한강물 위에 <br>뗏목위에 노래도 <br>에루화 처량도 하다 <br>아아 에헤요 <br>에헤요 어허야 <br>얼사함마 둥게디여라 <br>내사랑아 <br>조요한 월색은 <br>강심에 어렸는데 <br>술렁술렁 배띄워라 <br>에루화 달맞이 가잔다 <br>아아 에헤요 <br>에헤요 어허야 <br>얼사함마 둥게디여라 <br>내사랑아 <br>노들의 버들은 <br>해마다 푸르른데 <br>한강을 지키던 님 <br>지금은 어디 계신가 <br>아아 에헤요 <br>에헤요 어허야 <br>얼사함마 둥게디여라 <br>내사랑아 <br>]]></content><category term="전병훈" label="전병훈"/><category term="한강수타령" label="한강수타령"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전병훈/양류가/</id><title>전병훈 - 양류가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:42:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:42:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EB%B3%91%ED%9B%88/%EC%96%91%EB%A5%98%EA%B0%80/" title="전병훈 - 양류가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[양류상에 앉은 꾀꼬리 <br>제비만 여겨서 후린다 <br>에후 절사 더덤썩 안고서 <br>아하 요것이 내사랑 <br>양류청청 늘어진 가지 <br>꾀꼴새가 아름답다 <br>에후 절사 더덤썩 안고서 <br>아하 요것이 내사랑 <br>이화도화 난만한데 <br>날아드느니 봉접이라 <br>에후 절사 더덤썩 안고서 <br>아하 요것이 내사랑 <br>양류세지 사사록하니 <br>오류촌이 여기로다 <br>에후 절사 더덤썩 안고서 <br>아하 요것이 내사랑 <br>방초처처 우거진곳에 <br>황봉백접이 춤을춘다 <br>에후 절사 더덤썩 안고서 <br>아하 요것이 내사랑 <br>꽃을 찾는 벌나비는 <br>향기를 쫓아 날아든다 <br>에후 절사 더덤썩 안고서 <br>아하 요것이 내사랑 <br>작작요요 벌나비 쌍쌍 <br>양류청청 꾀꼬리 쌍쌍 <br>에후 절사 더덤썩 안고서 <br>아하 요것이 내사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="전병훈" label="전병훈"/><category term="양류가" label="양류가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전병훈/태평가/</id><title>전병훈 - 태평가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:42:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:42:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EB%B3%91%ED%9B%88/%ED%83%9C%ED%8F%89%EA%B0%80/" title="전병훈 - 태평가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[짜증은 내어서 무엇하나 <br>성화는 바치어 무엇하나 <br>속상한 일도 하도 많으니 <br>놀기도 하면서 살아가세 <br>니나노 닐리리야 <br>닐리리야 니나노 <br>얼싸좋아 얼씨구 좋다 <br>벌나비는 이리저리 펄펄 <br>꽃을 찾아서 날아든다 <br>청사초롱에 불밝혀라 <br>잊었던 낭군이 다시온다 <br>공수래 공수거 하니 <br>아니 노지는 못하리라 <br>니나노 닐리리야 <br>닐리리야 니나노 <br>얼싸좋아 얼씨구 좋다 <br>벌나비는 이리저리 펄펄 <br>꽃을 찾아서 날아든다 <br>장장추야 긴긴밤에 <br>실솔의 소리도 처량하다 <br>님을 그리워 젖는 벼개 <br>어느 누가 알아주리 <br>니나노 닐리리야 <br>닐리리야 니나노 <br>얼싸좋아 얼씨구 좋다 <br>벌나비는 이리저리 펄펄 <br>꽃을 찾아서 날아든다 <br>꽃을 찾는 벌나비는 <br>향기를 쫓아 날아들고 <br>황금같은 꾀꼬리는 <br>버들사이로 왕래한다 <br>니나노 닐리리야 <br>닐리리야 니나노 <br>얼싸좋아 얼씨구 좋다 <br>벌나비는 이리저리 펄펄 <br>꽃을 찾아서 날아든다 <br>]]></content><category term="전병훈" label="전병훈"/><category term="태평가" label="태평가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전병훈/오봉산타령/</id><title>전병훈 - 오봉산타령 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:42:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:42:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EB%B3%91%ED%9B%88/%EC%98%A4%EB%B4%89%EC%82%B0%ED%83%80%EB%A0%B9/" title="전병훈 - 오봉산타령 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오봉산 꼭대기 <br>에루화 돌배나무는 <br>가지가지 꺾어도 <br>에루화 모양만 나누나 <br>에헤요 어허야 <br>영산홍록의 봄바람 <br>오봉산 제일봉에 <br>백학이 춤추고 <br>단풍 진 숲 속엔 <br>새 울음도 처량타 <br>에헤요 어허야 <br>영산 홍록의 봄바람 <br>그윽한 준봉에 <br>한 떨기 핀 꽃은 <br>바람에 휘날려 <br>에루화 간들거리네 <br>에헤요 어허야 <br>영산홍록의 봄바람 <br>오봉산 꼭대기 <br>채색 구름이 뭉게뭉게 <br>만학의 연무는 <br>에루화 아롱아롱 <br>에헤요 어허야 <br>영산 홍록의 봄바람 <br>오봉산 꼭대기 홀로 섰는 <br>노송남근 광풍을 못 이겨 <br>에루화 반춤만 춘다 <br>에헤요 어허야 <br>영산 홍록의 봄바람 <br>]]></content><category term="전병훈" label="전병훈"/><category term="오봉산타령" label="오봉산타령"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전병훈/베틀가/</id><title>전병훈 - 베틀가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:42:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:42:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EB%B3%91%ED%9B%88/%EB%B2%A0%ED%8B%80%EA%B0%80/" title="전병훈 - 베틀가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[베틀을 놓세 베틀을 놓세 <br>옥난간에다 베틀을 놓세 <br>에헤요 베짷는 아가씨 <br>사랑노래 베틀에 <br>수심만 지누나 <br>반공중에 걸린 저 달은 <br>바디장단에 다 넘어간다 <br>에헤요 베짷는 아가씨 <br>사랑노래 베틀에 <br>수심만 지누나 <br>양덕맹산 중세포요 <br>길주명천 세북포로다 <br>에헤요 베짷는 아가씨 <br>사랑노래 베틀에 <br>수심만 지누나 <br>닭아 닭아 우지를 마라 <br>이 베 짷기가 다 늦어 간다 <br>에헤요 베짷는 아가씨 <br>사랑노래 베틀에 <br>수심만 지누나 <br>이 베를 짜서 누구를 주나 <br>바디 칠 손 눈물이로다 <br>에헤요 베짷는 아가씨 <br>사랑노래 베틀에 <br>수심만 지누나 <br>]]></content><category term="전병훈" label="전병훈"/><category term="베틀가" label="베틀가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전병훈/사발가/</id><title>전병훈 - 사발가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:42:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:42:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EB%B3%91%ED%9B%88/%EC%82%AC%EB%B0%9C%EA%B0%80/" title="전병훈 - 사발가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[금수강산 삼천리 <br>풍년이 오니 <br>한 사발 두 사발 <br>함포 고복이라 <br>에헤요 어허야 어여라난다 <br>디여라 허송세월 말어라 <br>열두 주름 치마폭 <br>갈피갈피 맺힌 설움이 <br>초생달이 기울면 <br>줄줄이 쌍쌍이 눈물이라 <br>에헤요 어허야 어여라난다 <br>디여라 허송세월 말어라 <br>일망무제 너른 들에 <br>가득히 심은 곡식은 <br>농업보국 다한 후에 <br>학발 양친을 봉양하세 <br>에헤요 어허야 어여라난다 <br>디여라 허송세월 말어라 <br>시냇가에 빨래소린 <br>오드락 똑딱 나구요 <br>아롱아롱 버들잎은 <br>정든 님 얼굴을 가리누나 <br>에헤요 어허야 어여라난다 <br>디여라 허송세월 말어라 <br>석탄백탄 타는데 <br>연기만 펄펄 나구요 <br>이내 가슴 타는데 <br>연기도 김도 안 난다 <br>에헤요 어허야 어여라난다 <br>디여라 허송세월 말어라 <br>]]></content><category term="전병훈" label="전병훈"/><category term="사발가" label="사발가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전병훈/청춘가/</id><title>전병훈 - 청춘가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:42:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:42:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EB%B3%91%ED%9B%88/%EC%B2%AD%EC%B6%98%EA%B0%80/" title="전병훈 - 청춘가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이팔청춘에 소년 몸 되어서 <br>문명의 학문을 닦아를 봅시다 <br>청춘 홍안을 네 자랑 말어라 <br>덧없는 세월에 백발이 되누나 <br>요지일월은 순지건곤 이요 <br>태평성대가 여기로구나 <br>동두천 소요산 약수대 꼭대기 <br>홀로선 소나무 날같이 외롭다 <br>여울에 바둑돌 부딪껴 희고요 <br>이내 몸 시달려 백발이 되누나 <br>세월이 가기는 흐르는 물 같고 <br>인생이 늙기는 바람결 같구나 <br>]]></content><category term="전병훈" label="전병훈"/><category term="청춘가" label="청춘가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전병훈/창부타령/</id><title>전병훈 - 창부타령 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:42:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:42:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EB%B3%91%ED%9B%88/%EC%B0%BD%EB%B6%80%ED%83%80%EB%A0%B9/" title="전병훈 - 창부타령 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[백구야 나지 마라 <br>너를 잡을 내 아니로다 <br>성상이 버리시매 <br>너를 좇아 예 왔노라 <br>나물 먹고 물을 마시고 <br>팔을 베고 누웠으니 <br>대장부의 살림살이 <br>요만 허며는 넉넉하지 <br>일촌 간장 맺힌 설움에 <br>부모님 생각 뿐이로다 <br>얼씨구 얼씨구 지화자 좋아 <br>아니 놀지는 못하리라 <br>만리창공은 하운이 흩어지고 <br>무산 십이봉은 월색도 유정터라 <br>님이라면 다 다정하며 <br>이별이라고 다슬 소냐 <br>이별 마자 지은 맹세를 <br>태산 같이 믿었더니 <br>태산이 허망이 무너질 줄 <br>어느 가인이 알아 줄 거냐 <br>얼씨구나 지화자 좋네 <br>아니 놀지는 못하리라 <br>아니 놀지는 못하리라 <br>공도라니 백발이요 <br>면치 못할 건 죽엄이로구나 <br>천황지황 인황시며 <br>실로 황제가 복희씨라 <br>성덕이 없어 봉해씨며 <br>말 잘하는 소진 장이도 <br>육국 제황을 다 달랬으나 <br>염라대왕은 못 달래어 <br>한번 죽엄을 못 면하시고 <br>그러하신 영웅이야 <br>죽어 사정이라도 있건마는 <br>우리 초로 인생이야 <br>한번 가며는 영절이라 <br>얼씨구나 지화자 좋네 <br>아니 놀지는 못하리라 <br>우연히 길을 갈 적에 <br>이상한 새가 울음을 운다 <br>무슨 새가 울랴마는 <br>적벽화전이 비운이라 <br>하야구구 진터를 보고 <br>설리 통곡 하는 모양 <br>사람의 인정치고는 <br>차마 어찌 볼 수가 있느냐 <br>일후에 남 되고 보면 <br>후회 막급이 있으리로다 <br>얼씨구 얼씨구 지화자자 좋아 <br>아니 놀지는 못하리라 <br>]]></content><category term="전병훈" label="전병훈"/><category term="창부타령" label="창부타령"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전병훈/노랫가락/</id><title>전병훈 - 노랫가락 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:42:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:42:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EB%B3%91%ED%9B%88/%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%AB%EA%B0%80%EB%9D%BD/" title="전병훈 - 노랫가락 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[충신은 만조정이요 <br>효자열녀는 가가재라 <br>화형제 낙처자하니 <br>붕우유신 하오리라 <br>우리도 성주 모시고 <br>태평성대를 누리리라 <br>저 달은 떠서 대장이 되고 <br>견우주성은 후군 이로다 <br>동자야 너는 바삐 가서 <br>향군 젓대를 갖추어라 <br>저 해가 떳다 지는 대로 <br>향군결단을 하러 갈까 <br>송악산 나리는 안개 <br>용수봉의 궂은비 되어 <br>선죽교 맑은 물에 <br>원앙선을 띄워놓고 <br>밤중만 월색을 쫓아 <br>완월장취 <br>왔소 나 여기 왔소 <br>천리타향에 나 여기 왔소 <br>바람에 날려를 왔나 <br>구름 속에 쌓여왔나 <br>아마도 나 여기 온 것은 <br>임 보려고 <br>]]></content><category term="전병훈" label="전병훈"/><category term="노랫가락" label="노랫가락"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피에스_PS/그래_그대는/</id><title>피에스 (P.S) - 그래 그대는 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:54:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:54:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EC%97%90%EC%8A%A4_PS/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%98_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%8A%94/" title="피에스 (P.S) - 그래 그대는 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대가 참 생각나는 하루 <br>유난히 더 흐려지는 하늘 <br>지겹지도 않아 <br>구름이 덮힌 듯 먹먹한 이 기분 <br>그때가 참 그려지는 오늘 <br>눈앞이 더 흐려지는 나를 <br>지겹지도 않아 <br>다른 사람에게 <br>빠져 있는 널 지금도 <br>나만 이렇게 <br>그래 그대는 아직도 여전히 날 <br>사랑하지 않는다고 했잖아 <br>그래 그대는 <br>다른 어떤 그 약속도 <br>이젠 다 필요 없다고 <br>같은 말을 하고 있잖아 내게 <br>그래 그대는 <br>그래 그대는 아직도 여전히 날 <br>사랑하지 않는다고 했잖아 <br>그래 그대는 <br>다른 어떤 그 약속도 <br>이젠 다 필요 없다고 <br>같은 말을 하고 있잖아 내게 <br>그래 그대는 <br>그대가 참 생각나는 하루 <br>유난히 더 흐려지는 하늘 <br>]]></content><category term="피에스 (P.S)" label="피에스 (P.S)"/><category term="그래 그대는" label="그래 그대는"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hash_Swan/혼선_Bonus_Track/</id><title>Hash Swan - 혼선 (Bonus Track) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:57:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:57:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hash_Swan/%ED%98%BC%EC%84%A0_Bonus_Track/" title="Hash Swan - 혼선 (Bonus Track) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let me drive on this avenue <br>Let me smoke on this avenue <br>Let me think on this avenue <br>오늘만큼은 나 혼자 <br>even she never know <br>나는 너를 기억해 <br>근데 잘 살고 있는 <br>너는 나를 잊었네 <br>미안해 네 소식 <br>더 보기에는 피곤해 <br>우리는 딱 그 정도였지 <br>차라리 편해 <br>그건 됐고 저기 있잖아 <br>우리 집은 남부럽지 <br>않게 살아 <br>누가 뭐라 해 그건 <br>내 복이잖아 <br>근데 복이라기엔 <br>울 엄마 돈이잖아 <br>생각이 많아 아마 <br>혼선이 됐나 봐 <br>Let me drive on this avenue <br>Let me smoke on this avenue <br>Let me think on this avenue <br>오늘만큼은 나 혼자 <br>even she never know <br>Yeah <br>쓸데없는 고민이 많어 <br>별거 아닌 일에도 <br>솔직히 너무 억울한 걸 <br>근데 있잖아 내가 <br>살면서 제일 억울한 건 <br>날 배신한 그 새끼도 <br>할테거든 억울한 척 <br>Yeah I know I know <br>원래 산다는 거 자체가 <br>다 자이로 자이로 <br>어차피 내 선에서 <br>해결 못할 일이라 <br>고민인 거지 맞어 <br>난 그냥 지금을 살어 <br>Let me drive on this avenue <br>Let me smoke on this avenue <br>Let me think on this avenue <br>오늘만큼은 나 혼자 <br>even she never know <br>Let me drive on this avenue <br>Let me smoke on this avenue <br>Let me think on this avenue <br>오늘만큼은 나 혼자 <br>even she never know <br>]]></content><category term="Hash Swan" label="Hash Swan"/><category term="혼선 (Bonus Track)" label="혼선 (Bonus Track)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hash_Swan/소름_돋았어/</id><title>Hash Swan - 소름 돋았어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:57:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:57:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hash_Swan/%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%84_%EB%8F%8B%EC%95%98%EC%96%B4/" title="Hash Swan - 소름 돋았어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[많이 늘어났네 지출이 <br>굳이 노리지 않아도 돼 비수기 <br>누군 바뀐 내 생활에 심술이 <br>나있을 때 기내식을 주문해 <br>speak English <br>많이 늘어났네 지출이 <br>굳이 노리지 않아도 돼 비수기 <br>누군 바뀐 내 생활에 심술이 <br>나있을 때 체크인을 하지 <br>speak English <br>U U wanna do it like me <br>저 여자앤 <br>wanna do it like her <br>but do it like bitch <br>요즘 내 고민은 <br>고민도 아닌 게 많지 <br>대체 뭘까 도끼형 <br>4억짜리 차의 바퀸 <br>U wanna do it like me <br>저 여자앤 <br>wanna do it like her <br>but do it like bitch <br>I'm gonna drivin' <br>with ma Porsche I be <br>내가 볼 수 없던 그곳까지 <br>스쿠버 다이빙 <br>Yeah 길거리를 걸어가다 보면 <br>이 사람들은 너무도 젊어 <br>근데 그 사람들에게 <br>조차도 난 젊어 <br>근데 얘넨 내 젊음보다 <br>내 옷이 부러워 <br>이젠 시계로 시간을 <br>보면 허세가 되고 <br>면허가 없어 느끼는 <br>카카오 블랙 기사의 배려 <br>근데 안되겠어 내년에 <br>어떤 차를 사게 될까 <br>궁금하지 <br>이 가산 내 팔로워들에겐 <br>카페베네 베너 <br>Let me speak one more <br>Yeah I gotta do that <br>Yeah I gotta do that <br>넌 내게 예전에도 꿈 깨라며 <br>충고했지 이제 네가 술 깨 <br>이제 없어 초췌 딱히 <br>없어도 Gold chainz <br>카페에 앉아 데이트를 하는 <br>내 모습은 흰 모자와 <br>왼팔의 타투 오른손에 Rolex <br>I got chills <br>많이 늘어났네 지출이 <br>굳이 노리지 않아도 돼 비수기 <br>누군 바뀐 내 생활에 심술이 <br>나있을 때 기내식을 주문해 <br>speak English <br>많이 늘어났네 지출이 <br>굳이 노리지 않아도 돼 비수기 <br>누군 바뀐 내 생활에 심술이 <br>나있을 때 체크인을 하지 <br>speak English <br>U U wanna do it like me <br>저 여자앤 <br>wanna do it like her <br>but do it like bitch <br>요즘 내 고민은 <br>고민도 아닌 게 많지 <br>대체 뭘까 도끼형 <br>4억짜리 차의 바퀸 <br>U wanna do it like me <br>저 여자앤 <br>wanna do it like her <br>but do it like bitch <br>I'm gonna drivin' <br>with ma Porsche I be <br>내가 볼 수 없던 그곳까지 <br>스쿠버 다이빙 <br>엄마는 저축을 해야 된대 <br>Yeah I get it <br>근데 언제나 충동이란 게 <br>내 안에 있지 <br>괜찮아 바뀐 지출의 <br>보장은 금붕어인 내가 <br>외워버린 계좌에 있지 <br>Yeah I made it <br>Ma Ambition <br>그건 1년 남은 내 여권에 <br>도장을 다 찍는 거 <br>잔고를 다 비우면 <br>어차피 또 들어올 거야 <br>조금은 식은땀이 흘러도 <br>For My Mother Girl <br>Father and 건 또 홈즈 <br>Don't worry I don't forget <br>미래의 ma son and daughter <br>난 우선 지금 더 멋있게 <br>살기 위해 돈을 벌어 <br>내가 멋있게 사는 법은 <br>저들과 함께 사는 거기도 <br>해서 난 돈을 벌어 <br>I got chills <br>많이 늘어났네 지출이 <br>굳이 노리지 않아도 돼 비수기 <br>누군 바뀐 내 생활에 심술이 <br>나있을 때 기내식을 주문해 <br>speak English <br>많이 늘어났네 지출이 <br>굳이 노리지 않아도 돼 비수기 <br>누군 바뀐 내 생활에 심술이 <br>나있을 때 체크인을 하지 <br>speak English <br>U U wanna do it like me <br>저 여자앤 <br>wanna do it like her <br>but do it like bitch <br>요즘 내 고민은 <br>고민도 아닌 게 많지 <br>대체 뭘까 도끼형 <br>4억짜리 차의 바퀸 <br>U wanna do it like me <br>저 여자앤 <br>wanna do it like her <br>but do it like bitch <br>I'm gonna drivin' <br>with ma Porsche I be <br>내가 볼 수 없던 그곳까지 <br>스쿠버 다이빙 <br>잘 봤지 <br>내 실패를 보려는 널 낚았지 <br>머지않은 날에 <br>공연장은 꽉 찼지 <br>Oh Jesus I got chills <br>I got chills and U got chills <br>난 불만이라고는 <br>지금 있을 수가 없지 <br>22 to 23 난 요즘 <br>돈을 버는 내게 돋아나 소름 <br>많이 늘어났네 지출이 <br>굳이 노리지 않아도 돼 비수기 <br>누군 바뀐 내 생활에 심술이 <br>나있을 때 기내식을 주문해 <br>speak English <br>많이 늘어났네 지출이 <br>굳이 노리지 않아도 돼 비수기 <br>누군 바뀐 내 생활에 심술이 <br>나있을 때 체크인을 하지 <br>speak English <br>U U wanna do it like me <br>저 여자앤 <br>wanna do it like her <br>but do it like bitch <br>요즘 내 고민은 <br>고민도 아닌 게 많지 <br>대체 뭘까 도끼형 <br>4억짜리 차의 바퀸 <br>U wanna do it like me <br>저 여자앤 <br>wanna do it like her <br>but do it like bitch <br>I'm gonna drivin' <br>with ma Porsche I be <br>내가 볼 수 없던 그곳까지 <br>스쿠버 다이빙 <br>]]></content><category term="Hash Swan" label="Hash Swan"/><category term="소름 돋았어" label="소름 돋았어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hash_Swan/Whitney_Feat_The_Quiett_Dok2/</id><title>Hash Swan - Whitney (Feat. The Quiett, Dok2) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:57:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:57:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hash_Swan/Whitney_Feat_The_Quiett_Dok2/" title="Hash Swan - Whitney (Feat. The Quiett, Dok2) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[촬영 촬영 그때 <br>차비도 엄마 돈 <br>마지막 상암동 <br>도착 후 잔고는 만원 <br>진짜 아슬했지 <br>겨우겨우 도착했던 망원 <br>근데 이젠 관심도 없어 <br>엄마의 코란도 코란도 <br>2년 전 노래방의 탬버린은 <br>네 누나의 연예인이 돼버리지 <br>또 상상 속 애인이 <br>돼버린 지금 난 <br>인생이 아주 트램펄린 <br>요즘 내 기분은 <br>우주에 있는 듯해 <br>할리우드의 맷 데이먼이지 <br>큰 무대 위에서 마시는 물은 <br>나름 시원하네 페퍼민트 <br>내 날이 밝았네 여전히 <br>생각은 잘 안 해 <br>내가 입는 옷 정품 문의는 <br>내 계좌에다가 해 <br>I saw Naver clip chernobyl <br>I need more words bullet <br>for Naver bitch <br>But I got credit card <br>and full paperbills <br>근데 여전히 또 <br>나이가 제일 어리지 <br>I’m Swan 내겐 <br>내일도 내일의 내일도 <br>매일이 매일이 <br>Payday again <br>백조의 상징은 <br>내가 될래 이제 <br>Swarovski necklace의 패 <br>경고를 미리 해 <br>여긴 콰형이 있어서 <br>안 하면 넌 게이 되네 <br>Yeah My name is HASH <br>인정해 그때는 내가 좀 어렸지 <br>난 돌아왔네 with more quality <br>너희들은 아직도 멀었지 <br>어차피 떨어질 놈들은 버려 shiiit <br>got my whole squad with me <br>I'll always love yall like whitney <br>I'll always love yall like whitney <br>got my whole squad with me <br>I'll always love yall <br>like whitney whitney whitney <br>I'll always love yall <br>like whitney whitney whitney <br>I'll always love yall <br>like whitney whitney whitney <br>got my whole squad <br>with me with me <br>Yeah im a baller baller <br>I would never fall off fall off <br>Euro yen dollar <br>날려 구름을 갈러 <br>Holla 난 랩 하나로 발러 <br>네 친구 크루도 like pablo <br>Escobar style로 plata o plomo <br>난로에 돈 갔다 박어 <br>이렇게 해쉬스완처럼 <br>차분한 톤으로 랩하니 <br>참 편하니 좋네 <br>이러면 난 하루종일 <br>랩할 수 있을 듯 <br>하지만 이건 내가 아니니 <br>stop hol up hol up <br>let bring it back to my own shit <br>illionaire ambition shout out <br>to the homie hash swan <br>그래 평일엔 녹음 <br>주말에는 공연하고 다시 녹음 <br>서울에선 잘 안 놀아 <br>일을 싹 마친 후에 <br>다른 나라 가서 <br>편안하게 놀구 <br>돌아오면 다시 기계처럼 일해 <br>고장 나면 새 좋은 <br>버전으로 내가 오구 <br>조금도 마가 뜰 틈 없이 <br>느슨 해질 때쯤 또 바짝 쪼구 <br>오후 오전 상관 없이 im up <br>가끔 지쳐도 받아들여 나의 업 <br>난 겁먹지 않아 먹는 거라곤 <br>최고급 스시 사시미 <br>patron life style putas <br>Let’s get this motha fuckin money <br>to the fullest big check check <br>check <br>인정해 그때는 내가 좀 어렸지 <br>난 돌아왔네 with more quality <br>너희들은 아직도 멀었지 <br>어차피 떨어질 놈들은 버려 shiiit <br>got my whole squad with me <br>I'll always love yall like whitney <br>I'll always love yall like whitney <br>got my whole squad with me <br>I'll always love yall <br>like whitney whitney whitney <br>I'll always love yall <br>like whitney whitney whitney <br>I'll always love yall <br>like whitney whitney whitney <br>got my whole squad <br>with me with me <br>]]></content><category term="Hash Swan" label="Hash Swan"/><category term="Whitney (Feat. The Quiett, Dok2)" label="Whitney (Feat. The Quiett, Dok2)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hash_Swan/난여자가너무좋아_Feat_Silly_Boot/</id><title>Hash Swan - 난여자가너무좋아 (Feat. Silly Boot) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:57:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:57:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hash_Swan/%EB%82%9C%EC%97%AC%EC%9E%90%EA%B0%80%EB%84%88%EB%AC%B4%EC%A2%8B%EC%95%84_Feat_Silly_Boot/" title="Hash Swan - 난여자가너무좋아 (Feat. Silly Boot) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I love girls girls girls <br>난 여자가 너무 좋아 <br>근데 너를 처음 본 날 <br>너가 너무 이쁜 거야 <br>I love girls more than money and sex <br>근데 이제 너야 <br>만약 너도 내가 좋다면 <br>나는 지금 안 받아 이 전화 <br>내 손은 너의 단추 위 <br>근데 언제나 그렇듯이 <br>너가 한 수 위 <br>괜찮아 같이 있을 수 <br>있다면 잠만 자지 <br>선비처럼 필요 없지 <br>삿갓이 <br>그래 나는 그래 <br>너가 원하는 대로 <br>물론 내 아래 힘줄엔 <br>힘이 들어가 두 배로 <br>그대로 눈 감어 <br>왜냐면 내 인내력의 <br>정도가 내 스스로 <br>너의 가치를 매기는 거 같아 <br>I don't wanna lose ur mind <br>I don't wanna lose ur mind <br>우린 매일 붙어있어 할 <br>필요 없게 하려고 안부전화 <br>Yeah 너가 날 <br>조금이라도 미워하면 <br>어쩌나 해 넌 아니 이런 <br>내 속사정 물론 아냐 <br>그 속 사정은 <br>대충 입고 나와 지노 형이 <br>시간이 아깝다 했어 <br>근데 우리가 가진 시간보다 <br>네 치마가 더 짧아서 <br>다시 들어가야겠어 <br>우리는 훨씬 이전에 <br>서로 처음 알았어 아마도 <br>그래야 더 영화라서 <br>난 너를 가장 멋지게 봐 <br>네가 멋진 만큼 네 옆에 있는 <br>나도 멋진 남자가 <br>되어가는 걸 알아서 <br>I love girls girls girls <br>난 여자가 너무 좋아 <br>근데 너를 처음 본 날 <br>너가 너무 이쁜 거야 <br>I love girls more than money and sex <br>근데 이제 너야 <br>만약 너도 내가 좋다면 <br>나는 지금 안 받아 이 전화 <br>I love girls girls girls No I did <br>I love girls girls girls No I did <br>I love girls more than money and sex <br>근데 이제 너야 <br>근데 너가 너무 이쁜 거야 <br>I love girls girls girls <br>I love girls girls girls <br>난 여자가 너무 좋아 <br>그 중에서도 네가 <br>예쁜 걸로 손꼽아 <br>I love girls more than money <br>girls girls more than car <br>역시 세상 일은 모르는 거야 <br>너와 내가 만난 건 로또야 <br>내가 너에게 빠졌듯이 <br>너도 나에게 금세 빠져 <br>우린 원래 금사빠가 아냐 <br>근데 이번엔 우리가 달라졌어 <br>네가 담배를 피고 싶으면 펴 <br>술을 마시고 싶으면 마셔 <br>물어보지 말고 <br>네가 클럽에 가고 싶으면 가 <br>네가 자퇴를 하고 싶으면 해 <br>물어보지 말고 <br>근데 난 거짓말이 싫어 <br>날 속이는 건 싫어 <br>그렇다고 너에게 억지로 <br>진실을 말하라 하기도 싫어 <br>널 함부로 판단하는 <br>생각은 버릴 거야 <br>non-judgemental <br>너에게 배운 거니까 <br>널 거리에서 봤을 때 <br>다른 놈이 함께 있어도 <br>화부터 내지 않잖아 그러니까 <br>I love girls girls girls <br>난 여자가 너무 좋아 <br>근데 너를 처음 본 날 <br>너가 너무 이쁜 거야 <br>I love girls more than money and sex <br>근데 이제 너야 <br>만약 너도 내가 좋다면 <br>나는 지금 안 받아 이 전화 <br>I love girls girls girls No I did <br>I love girls girls girls No I did <br>I love girls more than money and sex <br>근데 이제 너야 <br>근데 너가 너무 이쁜 거야 <br>I love girls girls girls <br>]]></content><category term="Hash Swan" label="Hash Swan"/><category term="난여자가너무좋아 (Feat. Silly Boot)" label="난여자가너무좋아 (Feat. Silly Boot)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hash_Swan/Daily_Look_Feat_Silly_Boot/</id><title>Hash Swan - Daily Look (Feat. Silly Boot) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:57:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:57:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hash_Swan/Daily_Look_Feat_Silly_Boot/" title="Hash Swan - Daily Look (Feat. Silly Boot) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 기분인 것 같아 <br>Very good <br>이런 서울이라면 <br>Better than cali mood <br>벤츠를 플러스하려 해 <br>내 데일리룩에 <br>너의 학교 <br>앞에서 대기 중 <br>이 기분인 것 같아 <br>Very good <br>서교동 가운데서 <br>보는 naked moon <br>남들이 보는 <br>나의 데일리룩 <br>그건 비싼 옷과 차 <br>너도 있네 늘 <br>Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah <br>그것들은 고정 <br>Errday day day <br>네 크롭탑은 <br>알렉산더 웨 웨 웽 <br>네 동기들의 룩은 <br>fail fail fail <br>넌 네 인스타에 <br>내 이름을 해쉬태그 해 <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>My Daily Look <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>My Daily Look <br>Yeah 오늘의 데일리 룩 <br>슈프림 베이프 <br>아디다스 Maybe good <br>그게 네이비든 <br>or 베이지든 간에 <br>매일의 포인트는 <br>내 옆에 너에게 있지 늘 <br>매번 놀라서 보면 <br>이 상황은 진짜 <br>꿈이 아니곤 해 <br>누구는 너와 연락한다며 <br>무리하기도 해 <br>그래서 가끔 네 휴대폰엔 <br>불이 나기도 해 <br>널 이쁘게 보는 게 <br>나뿐이 아니라 피곤해 <br>내가 버는 돈이 <br>많아질수록 바뀌는 건 <br>옷이지 오로지 <br>피로가 번진 내 눈인데 <br>넌 내 소리샘을 <br>들을 필요가 없지 <br>이 기분인 것 같아 <br>Very good <br>이런 서울이라면 <br>Better than cali mood <br>벤츠를 플러스하려 해 <br>내 데일리룩에 <br>너의 학교 <br>앞에서 대기 중 <br>이 기분인 것 같아 <br>Very good <br>서교동 가운데서 <br>보는 naked moon <br>남들이 보는 <br>나의 데일리룩 <br>그건 비싼 옷과 차 <br>너도 있네 늘 <br>Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah <br>그것들은 고정 <br>Errday day day <br>네 크롭탑은 <br>알렉산더 웨 웨 웽 <br>네 동기들의 룩은 <br>fail fail fail <br>넌 네 인스타에 <br>내 이름을 해쉬태그 해 <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>My Daily Look <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>My Daily Look <br>옷을 사네 이전엔 <br>비쌌는데 이런 <br>간에 기별도 <br>안가네 이건 <br>사지 니꺼 그 <br>크롭 아래 치골 <br>다른 여자들은 안 보여 <br>마치 달의 뒷면 <br>My Daily Daily <br>입었네 너의 옷 <br>근데 너도 오늘 입고 있네 <br>역시 나의 옷 <br>그럼 둘이 있을 때 <br>난 한마디 <br>오늘은 Kid ink 처럼 <br>I like you when u nasty <br>넌 내 오늘 내일의 <br>매일의 데일리 룩 <br>또 타지에서 <br>너조차도 알아보는 <br>사람들을 보며 느껴 <br>Yea U finally feel like <br>Sean yea U finally famous <br>Yea We finally famous <br>이 기분인 것 같아 <br>Very good <br>이런 서울이라면 <br>Better than cali mood <br>벤츠를 플러스하려 해 <br>내 데일리룩에 <br>너의 학교 <br>앞에서 대기 중 <br>이 기분인 것 같아 <br>Very good <br>서교동 가운데서 <br>보는 naked moon <br>남들이 보는 <br>나의 데일리룩 <br>그건 비싼 옷과 차 <br>너도 있네 늘 <br>Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah <br>그것들은 고정 <br>Errday day day <br>네 크롭탑은 <br>알렉산더 웨 웨 웽 <br>네 동기들의 룩은 <br>fail fail fail <br>넌 네 인스타에 <br>내 이름을 해쉬태그 해 <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>My Daily Look <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>My Daily Look <br>It is our daily look uh <br>I'm dressin' my baby boo up <br>She's sexy as fuck hallelujah <br>Other bitches are damn screwed up <br>My gf is bad and bourgeois <br>We live like we on a yacht <br>We live like we on a yacht <br>We live like we on a yacht <br>이 기분인 것 같아 <br>Very good <br>이런 서울이라면 <br>Better than cali mood <br>벤츠를 플러스하려 해 <br>내 데일리룩에 <br>너의 학교 <br>앞에서 대기 중 <br>이 기분인 것 같아 <br>Very good <br>서교동 가운데서 <br>보는 naked moon <br>남들이 보는 <br>나의 데일리룩 <br>그건 비싼 옷과 차 <br>너도 있네 늘 <br>Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah <br>그것들은 고정 <br>Errday day day <br>네 크롭탑은 <br>알렉산더 웨 웨 웽 <br>네 동기들의 룩은 <br>fail fail fail <br>넌 네 인스타에 <br>내 이름을 해쉬태그 해 <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>My Daily Look <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>My Daily Look <br>]]></content><category term="Hash Swan" label="Hash Swan"/><category term="Daily Look (Feat. Silly Boot)" label="Daily Look (Feat. Silly Boot)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hash_Swan/백조의_호수/</id><title>Hash Swan - 백조의 호수 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:58:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:58:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hash_Swan/%EB%B0%B1%EC%A1%B0%EC%9D%98_%ED%98%B8%EC%88%98/" title="Hash Swan - 백조의 호수 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[돈 벌 시간이야 <br>I bring 구창모 <br>내 젊음의 샘을 채울 <br>1hunnit trillion $ <br>팔라스 맨투맨 안엔 <br>비싼 반팔 bape with camo <br>백조를 버는 백조다 <br>내 호수는 바다로 <br>돈 벌 시간이야 <br>I bring 구창모 <br>내 젊음의 샘을 채울 <br>1hunnit trillion $ <br>팔라스 맨투맨 안엔 <br>비싼 반팔 bape with camo <br>백조를 버는 백조다 <br>내 호수는 바다로 <br>Swan Swan Swan <br>내 호수는 젊음의 샘 <br>어쩌면 관광지가 <br>돼버릴 거야 탑승 수속해 <br>수많은 협찬은 널린 <br>믹스테이프 무료해 <br>IMF 울 엄마가 판 금은 <br>돌아왔지 내 손목에 <br>좀 더 우아하게 <br>돈과 마주 앉았네 <br>이제 운이 부합할 때쯤 <br>구아방에서 아우디 R8 <br>Fuck ur virus shit <br>내 투자가 이겼지 <br>내 실패를 외치던 <br>친구들에게는 서프라이즈 <br>난 말해 마치 <br>10월 31일 Halo WIN <br>Yea I feel so good <br>내 호수엔 Mo and 효은 <br>그리고 역시도 있지 <br>홈즈 and ma 1llonaire Rollie up <br>그래 여긴 백조의 호수 <br>어쩌면 강 어쩌면 바다 <br>Do u wanna drink <br>this shit 이게 내 질문 <br>I really need to hear Fosho <br>돈 벌 시간이야 <br>I bring 구창모 <br>내 젊음의 샘을 채울 <br>1hunnit trillion $ <br>팔라스 맨투맨 안엔 <br>비싼 반팔 bape with camo <br>백조를 버는 백조다 <br>내 호수는 바다로 <br>돈 벌 시간이야 <br>I bring 구창모 <br>내 젊음의 샘을 채울 <br>1hunnit trillion $ <br>팔라스 맨투맨 안엔 <br>비싼 반팔 bape with camo <br>백조를 버는 백조다 <br>내 호수는 바다로 <br>한 달 용돈 30만원에서 <br>이제 월 70만원의 <br>월셋방에 자취 <br>근데 아직 빚진 <br>내 5년을 갚기는 턱이 없지 <br>비웃네 펠리컨이 <br>Yeah I’m good <br>and good at all <br>난 그때 그대로 <br>변한 거라면 내 이름이 deposit <br>2시간쯤 걸리는 16 마딘 <br>이제 싸게 먹혀도 <br>몇백의 단위 <br>Oh get that fuckin’ mula <br>for ma 호수 <br>get that doe on ma pocket <br>Wanna answer Mama’s call <br>22에 찬 시계엔 <br>11개의 다이아와 Gold <br>질려버린 봄베이 대신 <br>사는 사이다와 coke <br>그래 여기는 백조의 호수 <br>난 헤엄치고 싶네 억 <br>백억을 넘어 <br>백조의 호수에서 <br>그때쯤 되면 젊음이 <br>내조했어 라 말할걸 <br>내 젊음의 샘 <br>동시에 백조의 호수 <br>돈 벌 시간이야 <br>I bring 구창모 <br>내 젊음의 샘을 채울 <br>1hunnit trillion $ <br>팔라스 맨투맨 안엔 <br>비싼 반팔 bape with camo <br>백조를 버는 백조다 <br>내 호수는 바다로 <br>돈 벌 시간이야 <br>I bring 구창모 <br>내 젊음의 샘을 채울 <br>1hunnit trillion $ <br>팔라스 맨투맨 안엔 <br>비싼 반팔 bape with camo <br>백조를 버는 백조다 <br>내 호수는 바다로 <br>]]></content><category term="Hash Swan" label="Hash Swan"/><category term="백조의 호수" label="백조의 호수"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hash_Swan/누가/</id><title>Hash Swan - 누가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T08:58:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T08:58:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hash_Swan/%EB%88%84%EA%B0%80/" title="Hash Swan - 누가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아직도 418 17엔 찬물이 <br>그렇다고 내 옷이 <br>어떻게 가품이니 <br>너흰 내가 버는 돈이 <br>얼마냐 묻지 <br>이봐 내 하루는 <br>너무 바쁘지 <br>나의 시기로 <br>가고 있네 난 이미 <br>원하는 대로 내 인생의 <br>흐름은 R=VD Flow <br>mama worries <br>그건 돈도 내 밥벌이도 <br>아니라 겨우 내가 쓰는 <br>가사 심의뿐 <br>Who got the swag <br>Who got the moves <br>돈 많단 네 오빤 구라였군 <br>내 주변에 누가 부자였든 <br>걔가 번 게 아니면 추하거든 <br>I got the swag I got the moves <br>I got the Rolex I got the SUPs <br>조만간에 U say He got the Benz <br>Now Who got the swag <br>Who got the moves <br>누가 해 대체 <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 날 대체해 <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 got a Benz <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 got a chance <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 해 대체 <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 날 대체해 <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 got a swag <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>벌어보니 대부분은 <br>구라 구라 구라 <br>Yea I smoke but 몸에 밴 <br>현찰의 비린내 <br>사진을 찍을 때 <br>내 형들은 많이 심심해 <br>난 작년과 다를 게 없는 <br>걸음걸이로 걸어 <br>그것마저 넌 신기해 <br>난 이미 SWAG 벌스 하나로 <br>Swan got the Illionaire <br>Bitch I don't fuck with u <br>이게 멋없다고 하면 <br>과연 누가 반년 만에 <br>got a lot of feat even <br>with seven honeymoon <br>내 인생이 운이라 <br>생각해서 서러워 넌 <br>그럼 자격 없으니까 <br>Bitch shut the fuck up <br>그럼 이제 <br>누가 해 대체 <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 날 대체해 <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 got a Benz <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 got a chance <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 해 대체 <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 날 대체해 <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 got a swag <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>벌어보니 대부분은 <br>구라 구라 구라 <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>누가 누가 누가 <br>]]></content><category term="Hash Swan" label="Hash Swan"/><category term="누가" label="누가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤찬/엄마야/</id><title>윤찬 - 엄마야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:11:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:11:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%B0%AC/%EC%97%84%EB%A7%88%EC%95%BC/" title="윤찬 - 엄마야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[에 헤에헤야 데 헤에헤야 <br>나 죽어서도 못 잊을 <br>아름다운 이름이여 <br>엄마야 보고프면 어떡해 <br>엄마야 그리우면 어떡해 <br>엄마야 외로우면 어떡해 <br>엄마야 꽃이 지면 어떡해 <br>에 헤에헤야 데 헤에헤야 <br>나 미워해도 괜찮다 하신 <br>말씀 아파요 <br>엄마야 해가 지면 어떡해 <br>엄마야 달이 뜨면 어떡해 <br>엄마야 나도 따라 갈 테야 <br>엄마야 꽃이 피면 어떡해 <br>엄마야 보고프면 어떡해 <br>엄마야 그리우면 어떡해 <br>엄마야 외로우면 어떡해 <br>엄마야 꽃이 지면 어떡해 <br>]]></content><category term="윤찬" label="윤찬"/><category term="엄마야" label="엄마야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤찬/가자_가자/</id><title>윤찬 - 가자 가자 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:11:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:11:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%B0%AC/%EA%B0%80%EC%9E%90_%EA%B0%80%EC%9E%90/" title="윤찬 - 가자 가자 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가자 가자 아다다 다다다다 <br>사나이 가는 길 <br>사나이 가는 길이 험하다 해서 <br>돌아갈 순 없잖아 <br>넘어져도 가고 쓰러져도 간다 <br>사나이 가는 길 <br>가자 가자 같이 가자 <br>내 인생의 파도를 타고 <br>부르스도 좋고 지루박도 좋다 <br>갈 때까지 한번 가보자 <br>세상살이 고달프고 힘이 들어도 <br>한 번 죽지 두 번 죽느냐 <br>후회 없이 가자 아름답게 가자 <br>사나이 가는 길 <br>가자 가자 아다다 다다다다 <br>사나이 가는 길 <br>사나이 가는 길이 험하다 해서 <br>돌아갈 순 없잖아 <br>넘어져도 가고 쓰러져도 간다 <br>사나이 가는 길 <br>가자 가자 같이 가자 <br>내 인생의 파도를 타고 <br>부르스도 좋고 지루박도 좋다 <br>갈 때까지 한번 가보자 <br>세상살이 고달프고 힘이 들어도 <br>한 번 죽지 두 번 죽느냐 <br>후회 없이 가자 아름답게 가자 <br>사나이 가는 길 <br>가자 가자 아다다 다다다다 <br>사나이 가는 길 <br>가자 가자 아다다 다다다다 <br>사나이 가는 길 <br>]]></content><category term="윤찬" label="윤찬"/><category term="가자 가자" label="가자 가자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박원/기다리지_말아요/</id><title>박원 - 기다리지 말아요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:11:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:11:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9B%90/%EA%B8%B0%EB%8B%A4%EB%A6%AC%EC%A7%80_%EB%A7%90%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94/" title="박원 - 기다리지 말아요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[연락이 안 돼도 <br>의심하지 말아요 <br>답장이 조금 늦는 건 <br>바쁜 일이 있겠죠 <br>흔들리지 말아요 <br>당신의 마음을 <br>가끔 너무 바쁜 날 <br>당신도 있잖아요 <br>당신이 먼저 <br>그 사람보다 더 <br>좋아하는 게 뭐 어때요 <br>당신이 좀 더 초조하고 <br>조심스러워진다고 해도 <br>연락을 기다리지 말아요 <br>전화기만 쳐다보지 말아요 <br>기다리지 말아요 <br>당신의 사랑을 <br>그 사람도 당신의 <br>마음과 똑같아요 <br>다만 오늘 하루 <br>너무 바빠 그러는 거예요 <br>그럴 때 당신이 보낸 <br>연락을 받는다면 <br>어떨 거 같아요 <br>말 안 해도 알겠죠 <br>아주 조금 먼저 <br>그 사람보다 더 <br>표현하는 게 뭐 어때요 <br>헷갈리고 초조하고 <br>조심스러워진다고 해도 <br>연락을 기다리지 말아요 <br>don’t wait in for your love <br>전화기만 쳐다보지 말아요 <br>don’t wait in for <br>기다리지 말아요 <br>당신의 사랑을 <br>먼저 연락해요 <br>좋아할 거예요 <br>사랑을 기다리지 말아요 <br>don’t wait in for your love <br>저번처럼 또 <br>놓치면 안 돼요 <br>don’t wait in for <br>기다리지 말아요 <br>당신의 사랑을 <br>먼저 연락해요 <br>좋아할 거예요 <br>]]></content><category term="박원" label="박원"/><category term="기다리지 말아요" label="기다리지 말아요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Milli/Levitate/</id><title>Kid Milli - Levitate - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:12:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:12:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Milli/Levitate/" title="Kid Milli - Levitate - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[애초에 관심이 없어 <br>니 의류 <br>bitch tryna fuck with me <br>많아 그런 부류 <br>뭘 원하는진 모르겠어도 <br>쟤네에게 쓸 돈은 <br>전혀 난 <br>levitate levitate levitate <br>인마 저 gossip의 니들 <br>관심 갖는걸 내게 들이대면 <br>곤란해지는 건 니 여자아님 친구 <br>됐고 나 <br>levitate levitate levitate levitate <br>cozy boys reppin that <br>이건 석인 beat <br>just music 사무실에 <br>껴있는 놈팽이 <br>눈치없냐고 물음 <br>슁스형의 left hand <br>에 니 턱주가리 <br>levitate levitate <br>행사 없지만 <br>돈은 챙겨 난 벌어 <br>gucci 한달에 <br>세개 사고 또 tokyo <br>미래 사장님들은 <br>미리알아야해 내 돈은 <br>전부 압구정으로 <br>bit levitate levitate <br>levitate levitate <br>내 앉은키 210 <br>난 장난해 with cozyboys <br>오를때에 오를때에 <br>i pop that bottle rock that shirts <br>술따고 입혀 그녀 skirts <br>i dont need no conversation <br>i dont need your phone number <br>even 여자여도 <br>fuck that fuck'em <br>여기 보구 말해 봐 <br>내 여친 얼굴 보면 <br>넌 열등감에 <br>so i dont need your verse <br>i dont need your Lip Service <br>i mean i dont need a bunch <br>of sucker sucker ninjas <br>딴일 알아봐 나도 봤어 <br>알바천국 but 2년됐네 <br>i mean 난 이제 술잔 <br>깔 필요가 없네 <br>y'all bitches ain't fuck <br>with my fam <br>같아도 느낌이 different <br>내가 frontman <br>ambassador flowin <br>넌 player on the bench <br>니 곡들으면 우리 반응 <br>embarrassing undercover gang <br>북한 느낌 azian <br>근데 내 출신 <br>south korea man like 평양 <br>냉 보다 mcdonald levitate <br>i rap tight fetty wap <br>내 차에타 내려봐 <br>내 chainz 다 very rare <br>levitate 내 상태 <br>내 꽃신 gucci mane <br>난 영원해 juicy j <br>always workin <br>waka flocka flame <br>내 ksubi jeans 내 silva rang <br>keep fresh like my grillz <br>못마땅한 너넨 왕따지 <br>니가 앞서는거 딱 판매지 <br>salesman no 아티스트 <br>all i know is dope shit all <br>i know is $ all <br>i know is cloth shit <br>all i know is 비행기 <br>time that mean i levitated <br>levitate levitate <br>내 앉은키 210 <br>난 장난해 with cozyboys <br>오를때에 오를때에 <br>i pop that bottle rock that shirts <br>술따고 입혀 그녀 skirts <br>]]></content><category term="Kid Milli" label="Kid Milli"/><category term="Levitate" label="Levitate"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Milli/End_clothing_Feat_Hash_Swan/</id><title>Kid Milli - End clothing (Feat. Hash Swan) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:12:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:12:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Milli/End_clothing_Feat_Hash_Swan/" title="Kid Milli - End clothing (Feat. Hash Swan) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[600달러 짜리 rafs <br>on my feet with a light <br>이건 너무 신었더니 <br>불이 다닳았어 <br>so 그제 pink raf <br>또 샀지 이미 bruh <br>u dont even look like me <br>난 또 알아봤어 <br>black gang 한국의 Diplomats <br>we're singin like Dipset Anthem <br>ride out in my rental fuckin <br>car 안에서 apple <br>music을 키고 end clothing에 <br>가서 난 바구니 담았어 <br>근데 또 딱히 난 이런거 <br>없어도 안달라 질거고 uh <br>버스 타고 40분 걸려서 <br>갔잖아 매일 난 홍대에 <br>빨간머리 였고 <br>10:41 찍을 적에 <br>별로 약속도 없지만 <br>무작정 난 갔지 귀엔 이얼폰이 <br>그때에도 i ain't not corny <br>쟤네들 아직도 발전이 없이 <br>yo swerv ya what ioa한테 <br>call call callin <br>내 랩의 느낌은 stripes <br>and stars chillin and ball ball <br>ballin <br>이제 갖고싶던게 <br>내 손에 내 몸에 <br>bish all my thang is forign now <br>i need a what where i going <br>Rollin' down the freeway swervin <br>don't worry <br>Rollin' down the freeway swervin <br>don't worry <br>오른손에 lean cocktail <br>핸들을 쥐었지 <br>오른손에 lean cocktail <br>핸들을 쥐었지 <br>Rollin' down the freeway swervin <br>don't worry <br>Rollin' down the freeway swervin <br>don't worry <br>왼손에는 marlboro gold <br>shopping bag oh my <br>왼손에는 marlboro gold <br>핸들을 쥐었지 <br>man im swervin <br>Yeah 2년을 신었을거야 <br>그 아디다스 <br>곰팡이 필 새도 없었지 <br>신발은 관심밖이었던게 <br>유일하게 엄마가 내게 <br>고마웠던 일이었을 걸 <br>Now I got a new Rick <br>on ma feet <br>Fuck money Fuck rules <br>Fuck fame and Fuck errbody <br>외치던 18인데 now 2천만원 <br>on ma body <br>아마 생각이 많이 바뀐듯 해 <br>그 생각할틈도 없잖아 <br>200만원인데 20분에 <br>Ayyy Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah <br>천명이 목표였던 <br>인스탄 거의 1hunnit K <br>이제 거리를 걸면 <br>누구에겐 비호감 <br>미안 내 하루미팅만 몇개더라 <br>날 싫어하는게 너네 월세방 <br>보증금보다 비싼 시계때문인가 <br>뭐 뭐가됐던 됐어 <br>지금 중요한건 <br>새로운 계좌의 개설 <br>from 내 시간을 사려는 <br>사람들의 payment <br>좆까 너네 개소리 <br>Rollin' down the freeway swervin <br>don't worry <br>Rollin' down the freeway swervin <br>don't worry <br>오른손에 lean cocktail <br>핸들을 쥐었지 <br>오른손에 lean cocktail <br>핸들을 쥐었지 <br>Rollin' down the freeway swervin <br>don't worry <br>Rollin' down the freeway swervin <br>don't worry <br>왼손에는 marlboro gold <br>shopping bag oh my <br>왼손에는 marlboro gold <br>핸들을 쥐었지 <br>man im swervin <br>]]></content><category term="Kid Milli" label="Kid Milli"/><category term="End clothing (Feat. Hash Swan)" label="End clothing (Feat. Hash Swan)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Milli/Haneda/</id><title>Kid Milli - Haneda - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:12:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:12:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Milli/Haneda/" title="Kid Milli - Haneda - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[bit you gotta learn <br>넌 아무것도 몰라 <br>get yours <br>스타일도 없으면서 <br>how get dough <br>swaggin from the <br>엄마 용돈 nah ain't F with y'all <br>너네 좀 보고 배워야 해 <br>씨잼 or osa I ain't frontin <br>this is a kid milli <br>better than your shit <br>livin like gucci life 꽃길 <br>만 걸어 넌 벗는 게 좋지 <br>그 역겨운 통굽은 clone shit <br>5년뒤 정도 랩퍼의 proto type이 나야 <br>나 니 지식 얇아 okamoto <br>한대만 피고 난 돌면 돼 <br>니가 낸 best hit song의 better thing <br>black gang I'm reppin u know <br>it haters gon hate I know that <br>좆만큼 버는 돈 뺏기기 싫어 <br>애들 견제하는 선배 <br>F that I'll make money <br>절대 I never no <br>act like a bit 쟤네 속년들 <br>나는 다 보여 kid milli as known <br>as bis killa 합법적인 murder <br>henada Chattanooga <br>can we go can we chill <br>henada Chattanooga <br>can we go can we chill <br>I can go there anytime <br>when I want this is how I <br>live 알아 둬야 지금 <br>bish 난 작년에 <br>학생 근데 이젠 너의 <br>연구 대상 됐어 all my Fin fam <br>is illegal cuz 니 여자의 papi <br>이제 월급 안 받지 <br>바뀐 내 삶을 묻는 걔 <br>한텐 아무 말도 안 했어 <br>나는 내가 사는 대로 ride <br>그러다 보니까 지금 왔어 <br>이런 거야 삶은 말야 <br>니가 완전히 카피할 수 <br>있는 게 없다고 <br>머저리 멍청이 랩펀 <br>이 현실을 조금도 모르니 <br>goose 됐어 <br>랩만 하고 음악 못하는 너가 <br>악수 청함 I be like who's that <br>내 단면이 단줄 아는 게 <br>니 문제 bit you're not <br>my enermy motherFer <br>신경 안 쓰고 난 poppin <br>price tag 고개 숙여 봐 <br>인마 prada on my feet 잘 봐 <br>I blow my paper in the ginza <br>undercover that's my outfit <br>야 chewbacca on my chest <br>곧 목걸이 다 금 돼 <br>한 줄 쓰는 것도 버겁잖아 <br>넌 아닌 척 하다가 나랑 얘기해 <br>보면은 들키고 울 건데 pshh <br>내 가산 real 넌 잘 만든 fiction <br>내 삶은 real 넌 reality show <br>henada Chattanooga <br>can we go can we chill <br>henada Chattanooga <br>can we go can we chill <br>I can go there anytime <br>when I want this is how I <br>live 알아 둬야지 지금 <br>]]></content><category term="Kid Milli" label="Kid Milli"/><category term="Haneda" label="Haneda"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Milli/Time_Looping_Feat_BewhY/</id><title>Kid Milli - Time Looping (Feat. BewhY) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:12:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:12:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Milli/Time_Looping_Feat_BewhY/" title="Kid Milli - Time Looping (Feat. BewhY) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm addicted to nico since 11 <br>또 아직 학생감성 <br>포르노 좋아한대두 <br>여전히 옷에 미쳐 돈을 물처 <br>럼 날려 이런 취미 없이 <br>뭔 재미야 친구야 <br>난 바뀐 게 전혀 없어 <br>일주일의 모든 밤은 똑같다니깐 <br>지루한 비트 drum 처럼 <br>time도 loop 된다니까 <br>right 그럼 난 <br>이 상탤 즐겨야 돼 <br>싫어도 어쩌겠어 <br>난 있는 척 하긴 싫어 <br>we're not gonna take it like <br>Twisted Sister 그래 <br>transurf swings 형의 말 따라 <br>읽은 그 책에 다 있었어 <br>난 원한 건 결국엔 가졌어 <br>또 결국엔 이뤄 <br>요즘에 모든 랩퍼들은 <br>안달났지만 다 <br>쥐고 있는 건 mic 아닌 iphone <br>이건 real talk <br>people talk shit <br>but 걔네 말 무겐 instagram <br>쟤 의견 어차피 넘 가벼워 <br>제껴 I don't giva giva <br>fuck about 니 모든 opinion <br>입 잠궈 인마 일상 <br>routine이 같은걸 착각마 <br>time은 무한이 아냐 <br>loop loop loop 시계가 돌아 <br>look look look 쟤넨 똑같아 <br>니 오빠들 걔네 다 <br>별것도 없어 진짜 <br>bad news 1 니 fan이 <br>날 들을 때 생겨 that's like <br>time looping <br>time looping <br>time looping <br>time looping <br>time looping <br>time looping <br>time looping <br>time looping <br>FL kick n snare <br>loop 처럼 반복되는 일상 <br>요즘엔 새로운 게 필요해 <br>하루 종일 난 고민만 <br>선택해야 할 것들이 너무 많아 <br>결정했냐 묻지마 <br>아직이라고 말하기가 <br>이젠 입이 아파 <br>내 아이폰은 맨날 ring ding dong <br>섭외전화 가득 이제 난 <br>매니저가 무지 필요 <br>회사라고 안 했어 <br>요즘은 소속되기 두려워 <br>싫은 소리하기 스트레스 받고 꽤 <br>힘들어 혼자가 편한 것 같지만 <br>외롭기도 해 가끔 <br>근데 이런 내가 자주 <br>멋지다고 생각을 하곤 해 <br>혼자서 여기까지 왔어 <br>사실 주님의 가호 <br>잊어버린다면 난 끝인걸 알어 <br>날 사랑해주는 이들 <br>생각하기도 바쁜데 <br>날 욕하는 이들조차 <br>사랑하려고 하지만 <br>아직은 벅차 견뎌야지 <br>난 세상에서 제일 커질 테니깐 <br>loop loop loop 시계가 돌아 <br>look look look 쟤넨 똑같아 <br>니 오빠들 걔네 다 <br>별것도 없어 진짜 <br>bad news 1 니 fan이 <br>날 들을 때 생겨 that's like <br>time looping <br>time looping <br>time looping <br>time looping <br>time looping <br>time looping <br>time looping <br>time looping <br>]]></content><category term="Kid Milli" label="Kid Milli"/><category term="Time Looping (Feat. BewhY)" label="Time Looping (Feat. BewhY)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Milli/MARUHAN/</id><title>Kid Milli - MARUHAN - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:12:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:12:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Milli/MARUHAN/" title="Kid Milli - MARUHAN - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[wear undercover <br>where is my gold chain <br>wear parda shoe <br>where is my gold chain <br>wear my raf simons <br>wear 그림 그린 tee <br>maruhan shit maruhan bish <br>I'm going straight to the cash <br>I'm going straight to the cash <br>I'm going straight to the cash <br>I'm going straight to the cash <br>I just wanna free <br>I just wanna cash <br>I just want a real friend <br>I just wanna love <br>내겐 너 눈 보여 <br>그래서 너가 올 때 <br>나는 이미 도착해있어 <br>you better call the cops <br>I'm about to run up on your block <br>dope shit I make everyday <br>but ain't selling <br>400만원 내 <br>outfit 어디든 간에 <br>I make it rain <br>feel like playboi carti 야 <br>258-2번지 매일 we're stackin <br>even 내 여자친군 너보다 야망 높지 <br>우린 먼저 계획 전에 play <br>너네 plan 총도 안 쐈는데 <br>끝 꿈이 꿈인 채로 썩지 <br>go to the 칭코 <br>in tokyo with nobody slot <br>땡김 쏟아진 거 <br>모으고 난 뒤로 빼지 <br>돈 얘기 안 해도 돼 <br>but vision 없어 <br>보인다면 get the fuck off <br>니들끼리 저기서 놀아야 해 <br>욕심 전에 우린 그릇도 넓혀야 해 <br>shout out bewhy <br>암 것도 없는 날 돠준 거를 <br>나는 잊을 리가 없지 <br>cozy boys we ride man <br>always we're talkin bout <br>business plan <br>when I spit that shit <br>니들 뇌 속에 내 메시지는 <br>열등감이 됐어 내껀 내꺼 <br>sapporo 에서 눈을 퍼 내 <br>class 두 배로 <br>bruh we gon make it in a second tho <br>돈 많을수록 많아 문제도 <br>근데 내가 볼 땐 <br>없을 때가 더 많아 보여 후 <br>그래서 땡기는 거야 더 <br>fuck other ninjas gon be broke <br>I don't break cake with 니 squad <br>bitches got nothing <br>so I'm going straight to the cash <br>내 rap 다시 back <br>to the basic y'all heard <br>It's about time It's about time <br>It's about time It's about time <br>wear undercover <br>where is my gold chain <br>wear parda shoe <br>where is my gold chain <br>wear my raf simons <br>wear 그림 그린 tee <br>maruhan shit maruhan bish <br>I'm going straight to the cash <br>I'm going straight to the cash <br>I'm going straight to the cash <br>I'm going straight to the cash <br>I got some flow <br>I got some drank <br>in my cup call your friend <br>couple hyein seo on my body <br>couple gucci rags <br>I got some money <br>got some cloth <br>I'm flexin on your face <br>여기 저기 now I'm switchin lane <br>switchin lane 거의 날 보지도 못해 <br>I got some bead and some jin <br>I got some news <br>내 시간 팔아서 예금 I get that <br>I'm in chitose sushi <br>uobei fuck your opinion <br>cash man cash man <br>then I need that <br>너넨 먹고 살 걱정 해 <br>나는 다음 걱정해 <br>그게 우리 차이고 <br>you know you ain't fuck with me <br>bitch tryna fuck with them <br>뒤로 들어가서 <br>나는 니 여자랑 I kick back <br>but first thing first <br>어쨌던지 얻는 건 <br>안 거절하니깐은 <br>우린 put in work <br>개처럼 일해 또 개처럼 써 <br>근데 왕처럼 마시는 건 <br>우리야 너넨 nope <br>I ain't clubin but <br>when I back club <br>니가 줄이나 설 때 <br>너네 지나쳐 도장 찍었어 <br>already eat that sukiyaki kid mill <br>from the bottom <br>I'll rap till I stack milli <br>아직도 멀었어 <br>but I fuck with 니 rapstar <br>tax free receipt 내 passport <br>난 자랑할 위치 아니래 쟤네 말 <br>그건 나를 바꿀 수가 없어 <br>내려놔야해 그건 도움이 안돼 <br>니 life style 에 <br>bish 후엔 time files man <br>I spend in the maruhan damn <br>I spend with my girlfriend damn <br>wear undercover <br>where is my gold chain <br>wear parda shoe <br>where is my gold chain <br>wear my raf simons <br>wear 그림 그린 tee <br>maruhan shit maruhan bish <br>I'm going straight to the cash <br>I'm going straight to the cash <br>I'm going straight to the cash <br>I'm going straight to the cash <br>니가 버는 돈은 그거 내 시간 <br>니가 버는 구슬 그거 내 시간 <br>니 스타일 그거 전부 내 시간 <br>인마 니가 버는 돈은 그거 내 시간 <br>니가 버는 돈은 그거 내 시간 <br>니가 버는 구슬 그거 내 시간 <br>니 스타일 그거 전부 내 시간 <br>인마 니가 버는 돈은 그거 내 시간 <br>]]></content><category term="Kid Milli" label="Kid Milli"/><category term="MARUHAN" label="MARUHAN"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Milli/ccccall/</id><title>Kid Milli - ccccall - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:12:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:12:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Milli/ccccall/" title="Kid Milli - ccccall - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[when you call me i can go there <br>look around when i using <br>my bible for a road map <br>than i feel like Macy Wiseman 아 <br>you pussy is my palace <br>i means <br>you pussy is my palace <br>that means a lot to me <br>today i woke up in tokyo <br>i roll up one <br>like a flacko and <br>i be driving in a car <br>it feels good <br>when the sun down <br>i'm just searching brand new gucci <br>im just sitting in toyota <br>just trying to get to you <br>just wanna met your mama <br>these rappers ain't s you know that <br>these rappers ain't s you know that <br>]]></content><category term="Kid Milli" label="Kid Milli"/><category term="ccccall" label="ccccall"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Milli/Family_business_Feat_Swings/</id><title>Kid Milli - Family business (Feat. Swings) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:12:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:12:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Milli/Family_business_Feat_Swings/" title="Kid Milli - Family business (Feat. Swings) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I give a fuck about <br>what they do <br>I ain't you <br>and life is painful <br>when you don't have <br>friends to save you <br>that's why I take care of <br>family business <br>I don't fuck average bitches <br>I only fuck with the best <br>I'm not impressed by these <br>dick heads who settle for less <br>grown men acting their <br>age that get my respect <br>cuz if we gonna shine <br>we gon shine together <br>your gain is mine and <br>you know I'm sharing <br>mine it's never <br>just me myself and I <br>I take care of them <br>and I got that reputation <br>it's basic I am <br>a family guy <br>I damage outsiders <br>who try to infiltrate <br>and we're not intimidated <br>by these motherfuckers <br>you're my brother from <br>another mother <br>as far as loyalty goes <br>you are my brother's brother <br>so fuck everybody else <br>they just fuck us over <br>no more new faces <br>let's go and run em over <br>family business <br>paper chase paper chase <br>my family chasin <br>paper paper chase <br>싸게 구해 비싸게 팔어 <br>하루 팔아 밤에 나눠 <br>chasin dream &amp; chasin won <br>chasin what <br>chasin dream &amp; chasin cloth <br>chasin what <br>chasin dream &amp; chasin yen <br>chasin ticket boi <br>light in my wallet <br>my brain's full of plan boi <br>i don't give a fuck about <br>what they do I ain't you <br>y'all rappers dance wit me <br>i got a gun in my throat fool <br>쟤네 머리에 침 놔주는게 <br>내 familly business bitch im <br>going straight to the top <br>내 moving groovy하게 so i'm <br>undercover gang <br>난소문도 없이 달려 <br>내게 보이는 모든 것이 <br>돈이고 없는 너에게 콜하 <br>지 못해 <br>F these bunch of hoes 예 <br>hoes be talkin like <br>저 오빠 같은 rapper 가 <br>좋고 뭐고 F i overdosed on <br>money 또 난 모든 cloth <br>family business stackin dough <br>YEN or WON 난 뽑아 표 <br>woke up in chuo ku <br>i wanna some <br>masterpieces 이미있지 <br>what's the business <br>ballin spaldin spendin <br>for the glitch F your business <br>매일해 내 일 내 일은 daily <br>니 일은 내일해 <br>bit im braggin braggin bout <br>내 chainz and dresses <br>racing track in japan now <br>im swithin lane 내 <br>몫은 내꺼 아직도 <br>reppin black gang badasskid <br>kid milli gettin fuckin <br>better bitches u na mean <br>예의 차려야해 <br>니가 나를 부를때면 <br>sacai is My kind of outfit <br>kolor boost on my feet <br>어설픈 놈은 첨 봤지 이거 <br>but they don't know bout it <br>family business <br>paper chase paper chase <br>my family chasin <br>paper paper chasin <br>싸게 구해 비싸게 팔어 <br>하루 팔아 밤에 나눠 <br>chasin dream &amp; chasin won <br>chasin what <br>chasin dream &amp; chasin cloth <br>chasin what <br>chasin dream &amp; chasin yen <br>chasin ticket boi <br>light in my wallet <br>my brain's full of plan boi <br>]]></content><category term="Kid Milli" label="Kid Milli"/><category term="Family business (Feat. Swings)" label="Family business (Feat. Swings)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조용훈/이별이_다가올_때/</id><title>조용훈 - 이별이 다가올 때 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:13:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:13:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%9A%A9%ED%9B%88/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84%EC%9D%B4_%EB%8B%A4%EA%B0%80%EC%98%AC_%EB%95%8C/" title="조용훈 - 이별이 다가올 때 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[시간이 흐르듯 <br>흐르는 맘도 막을 수는 없어 <br>시간이 흐르듯 <br>흐르는 맘도 막을 수는 없어 <br>한 순간 한 순간 <br>요인이 되고 이유가 되어 <br>순간이라는 이 시간과 <br>지금이라는 이 순간들을 <br>만들어 내는 것 뿐 <br>서툰 미소가 머금어진 <br>그저 행복했다는 한 마디 말 <br>그리고 그리고 <br>감정이 담겨진 <br>손끝이 맞닿여진 <br>악수 그것 뿐 <br>한 순간 한 순간 <br>감정이 되고 행동이 되어 <br>순간이라는 이 시간과 <br>지금이라는 이 순간들을 <br>만들어 내는 것 뿐 <br>서툰 미소가 머금어진 <br>그저 사랑했다는 한 마디 말 <br>그리고 그리고 <br>감정이 담겨진 <br>가슴이 맞닿여진 <br>그것 뿐 <br>그것 뿐 <br>그것 뿐 <br>]]></content><category term="조용훈" label="조용훈"/><category term="이별이 다가올 때" label="이별이 다가올 때"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/놀자/Love_Bed/</id><title>놀자 - Love Bed - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:13:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:13:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%86%80%EC%9E%90/Love_Bed/" title="놀자 - Love Bed - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[혹시 기억하니 <br>그때 처음 <br>만났던 그날에 <br>첫눈에 반했는데 <br>너는 몰랐겠지만 <br>아름다웠어 그날에 <br>넌 너무나 예뻐서 <br>Kiss 하고 싶었어 <br>하루 종일 <br>너와 함께 할래 <br>오 아낌없이 <br>모두 네게 줄래 <br>Everynight <br>너의 귓가에 살며시 <br>너를 품에 안고 <br>속삭 일래 사랑해 <br>Looking your eyes <br>Touching the body <br>오늘밤 너를 너를 <br>너를 너를 원해 <br>하루를 다 <br>너를 위해 준비한 <br>Couple Love bed <br>Couple Love bed <br>Whenever wakeup <br>in the morning <br>I think the first you <br>오늘도 태양은 어김없이 <br>그녀인듯 눈부셔 <br>네가 없는 내 삶은 <br>창살 없는 감옥 <br>정처 없이 떠도는 <br>방황 하는 영혼 <br>오 대기대기해 <br>기대 기대한 This night <br>Special and amazing tonight <br>이 밤이 다가기 전에 <br>라면 먹고 갈래 <br>너와 나누어 먹어 <br>Is white love bed <br>함께 하는 오늘이 <br>ma birth day <br>So sweet my baby <br>and touch my body <br>부드럽게 다가가 <br>secret party <br>나는 느껴 판타지 <br>물론 화이트셔츠는 <br>필요 없지 <br>Checking some body <br>둘만이 즐기는 공간에 <br>눈 가네 뿅 하고 <br>취해 버린 둘만 <br>반해버린 Tonight <br>너라면 All right <br>Looking your eyes <br>Touching the body <br>오늘밤 너를 너를 <br>너를 너를 원해 <br>하루를 다 <br>너를 위해 준비한 <br>Couple Love bed <br>Couple Love bed <br>구름위에 둘이 <br>사랑하는 우리 <br>반짝이는 별이 <br>쏟아져 우리 사이로 <br>구름위에 둘이 <br>사랑하는 우리 <br>반짝이는 별이 <br>Let’s do this again <br>Looking your eyes <br>Touching the body <br>오늘밤 너를 너를 <br>너를 너를 원해 <br>하루를 다 <br>너를 위해 준비한 <br>Couple Love bed <br>Couple Love bed <br>]]></content><category term="놀자" label="놀자"/><category term="Love Bed" label="Love Bed"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/옥상거지/Montauk/</id><title>옥상거지 - Montauk - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:13:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:13:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A5%EC%83%81%EA%B1%B0%EC%A7%80/Montauk/" title="옥상거지 - Montauk - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[끝없는 도로 위 <br>끝없이 펼쳐지던 <br>끝없는 사막 너머로 <br>끝없는 바다에 <br>끝없이 요란스런 <br>끝없는 파도 너머로 <br>우린 질문을 던지며 <br>대답을 기다려 왔어 <br>우리 두 손을 내밀어 <br>누군가 손잡아 주길 <br>바랬던 쉽게 바래져 버린 <br>파랬던 그 바다의 기억과 <br>말했던 내게 말했던 <br>너의 파랬던 <br>눈동자 속의 바다 <br>쉼 없는 도로 위 <br>쉼 없이 펼쳐지던 <br>쉼 없는 여행의 끝에 <br>쉼 없는 바다 위 <br>쉼 없이 요란스런 <br>쉼 없는 파도의 끝에 <br>우린 맘을 문지르며 <br>조약돌을 줍곤 했어 <br>우리 두 손에 가득한 <br>마음 고이 전해주길 <br>바랬던 쉽게 바래져 버린 <br>파랬던 그 바다의 기억과 <br>말했던 내게 말했던 <br>너의 파랬던 <br>눈동자 속의 바다 <br>]]></content><category term="옥상거지" label="옥상거지"/><category term="Montauk" label="Montauk"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/규영_Kyu_Young/Play_To_Chill/</id><title>규영 (Kyu Young) - Play To Chill - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:13:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:13:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B7%9C%EC%98%81_Kyu_Young/Play_To_Chill/" title="규영 (Kyu Young) - Play To Chill - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그래 난 놀면서 일해 <br>가지말자 집에 <br>확인하자 미래 <br>우린 즐기며 준비해 <br>성공과 즐거움은 비례 <br>압박은 반비례 <br>아빠는 날 이해 못해도 <br>이미 올라탔어 위에 <br>기분은 마치 반지하서 <br>슁스형의 메세나 <br>아마추어는 끓여 익혀 <br>습득했어 베테랑 <br>내 모든 곡은 세련됐어 <br>아마 학생 때 기억으론 <br>두꺼운 노트나 책엔 안 <br>나오는 얘기 <br>나도 세뇌당할 뻔 <br>왜냠 나도 그렇듯이 <br>대학교 캠퍼스 <br>로망이 있었고 <br>영어 단어를 뻐끔 <br>중 고딩들아 늦기전에 <br>시스템에 fuck'em <br>난 내 하나밖에 <br>없는 청춘을 <br>하기싫은 일로 <br>낭비하기 싫거든 <br>내가 맞다고 한 건 <br>당연히 맞거든 <br>남 간섭 좋아하는 <br>넌 who are you <br>play to Chill <br>yo mother fucking bounce yeah <br>errbody mo fucking bounce yeah <br>play to Chill <br>yo mother fucking bounce yeah <br>errbody mo fucking bounce yeah <br>play to Chill <br>yo mother fucking bounce yeah <br>errbody mo fucking bounce yeah <br>play to Chill <br>yo mother fucking bounce yeah <br>errbody mo fucking bounce yeah <br>내 flow는 날카로워 <br>마치 겐지나 리퍼 <br>line이 이해안감 <br>오버워치로 널 pick up <br>내 방안의 바탕화면의 <br>수십개의 비커 <br>더 놀고 자고 what <br>닥터페퍼나 마실 걸 <br>투잡으로 투자해 <br>투자해서 부자해 <br>다시 부자해서 투자해 <br>돌고도는 주사위 <br>roll of the dice <br>매일 이래 <br>욕하기 보단 나의 <br>파이나 챙길래 <br>그래 homeless style <br>잃을 거 없이 웃자고 <br>police style <br>더 시끄럽게 굴자고 <br>이 groove 안 또 <br>이 move 안 <br>좀 더 발칙하고 <br>야한 영화를 틀자고 <br>난 내 멋대로 살래 평생 <br>구지 해서 뭐해 <br>견제나 경쟁 <br>너가 내가 싫담 <br>뭐 어째야겠어 <br>난 그냥 더 <br>벌어서 멋져야겠어 <br>play to Chill <br>yo mother fucking bounce yeah <br>errbody mo fucking bounce yeah <br>play to Chill <br>yo mother fucking bounce yeah <br>errbody mo fucking bounce yeah <br>play to Chill <br>yo mother fucking bounce yeah <br>errbody mo fucking bounce yeah <br>play to Chill <br>yo mother fucking bounce yeah <br>errbody mo fucking bounce yeah <br>가만히 앉아있기보단 <br>움직였어 난 <br>안좋은 일을 부르던 <br>지겨운 악순환 <br>감사함을 느껴 <br>난 종교도 없지만 <br>너가 이 느낌에 <br>적응 안됨 먹어야해 청심환 <br>아직까지 걔와 같이 <br>가는 넌 좀 쉬어 <br>갈때까지 가보자고 <br>좋은 vibe 이어 <br>랩은 너무 쉬워 <br>하늘에 내 자린 비었 <br>시동걸어 면허 없이 <br>올려 기어 기어 기어 <br>어린 시절 기억은 기억 <br>but 그 때가 그리워 <br>맘에 든 장난감 갖던 <br>해서 돌아왔어 <br>맘대로 beat에 붓칠해 <br>난 맛이 간 피카소 <br>니가 말하던 재능 <br>대신 노력이 날 알아봤어 <br>직업이 취미고 <br>취미로 결국 놀아 <br>위치를 지켜 어차피 <br>인생은 돌고 돌아 <br>17년은 내꺼야 <br>질투는 집어넣어 <br>Kyu young <br>i'm a young gunna <br>]]></content><category term="규영 (Kyu Young)" label="규영 (Kyu Young)"/><category term="Play To Chill" label="Play To Chill"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Astroboy/Richards_Mille_Run_Feat_Diano/</id><title>Astroboy - Richard`s Mille Run (Feat. Diano) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:13:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:13:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Astroboy/Richards_Mille_Run_Feat_Diano/" title="Astroboy - Richard`s Mille Run (Feat. Diano) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can’t wait for me to blow up <br>I can’t wait for you to show up <br>Showin’ up in my Goyard <br>I can’t wait for me to show off <br>I can’t wait for you to blow up <br>Showin’ up in my Goyard <br>말했잖아 언젠가는 <br>내가 돈을 벌 때 <br>24시간이 모자라 <br>my birthday <br>Everyday 매일 매일 놀아도 <br>it never ends <br>저 멀리 푸른 초원 위에 <br>언젠간 만날 그녀를 위해 <br>그림 같은 집을 짓고 <br>I’ll be waitin’ <br>countin’ money yeah <br>Now that’s the life <br>Vetements Lagerfeld <br>Gucci Louis V <br>Yeezy on my feet <br>Easy tease <br>She be gettin’ G’s <br>어느 날에는 <br>YSL 까만 데님에 <br>Alexander Wang <br>탑 신발 Hermes <br>Aye aye 오래 기다렸지 <br>Oh yeah 미친 듯 달렸지 <br>그날에 나를 보면 <br>그날에 너를 보면 <br>How you like it now <br>Ooh Ah <br>Hmm Mille Run <br>Ooh Ah <br>Hmm Mille Run <br>Ooh Ah <br>Hmm Mille Run <br>Mille Run <br>Ooh Ah <br>Hmm Mille Run <br>Ooh Ah <br>Hmm Mille Run <br>Ooh Ah <br>Hmm Mille Run <br>어렸었을 때 가끔 <br>내가 어른이 된다면 어떨지 <br>그림을 그리고는 했지 손에 쥔 <br>Microphone의 색은 golden <br>그런 나를 비웃던 아이들 <br>지금은 어떻게 <br>잘살고 있을지 yeah <br>I made this song for you <br>To prove my dream came true <br>I don’t really fear <br>when I’m running <br>I don’t need no love <br>when I’m stunting <br>이제 와서 가식 떨지마 <br>속이 다 보이니까 <br>십원 한 장 아깝다던 너 <br>when I was falling <br>Oh yeah 오래 기다렸지 <br>Aye aye 죽어라 달렸지 <br>그날에 나를 보면 <br>그날에 너를 보면 <br>Now you take it back <br>Ooh Ah <br>Hmm Mille Run <br>Ooh Ah <br>Hmm Mille Run <br>Ooh Ah <br>Hmm Mille Run <br>Ooh Ah <br>Hmm Mille Run <br>Ooh Ah <br>Hmm Mille Run <br>Ooh Ah <br>Hmm Mille Run <br>I never wanted more <br>Just wanted bit of love <br>Now I can’t take no more <br>Never gonna runaway <br>Tell me baby can <br>you see me now <br>‘Cause I see you <br>My life <br>My life <br>My life is ready to hold you <br>]]></content><category term="Astroboy" label="Astroboy"/><category term="Richard`s Mille Run (Feat. Diano)" label="Richard`s Mille Run (Feat. Diano)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Hold_Back_The_River/</id><title>Wet Wet Wet - Hold Back The River - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:17:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:17:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Hold_Back_The_River/" title="Wet Wet Wet - Hold Back The River - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stop your pretending <br>Listen to what I've got to say <br>How your head's went away <br>Only here for a day <br>And that grave I just made <br>Is for me when I get paid <br><br>Won't you wait a while <br>Move to blue <br>Sometimes people don't want to say <br>Old time dancers don't die that way <br>See that grave I've just made <br>It's for me when I get paid <br><br>Somebody's got to hold back the river <br>Somebody like you <br><br>Do you love and surrender <br>Sometimes I feel like I can remember <br>I think it's fair to mention <br>About the days when I get paid <br><br>Somebody's got to hold back the river <br>Somebody like you <br>Somebody's got to hold back the river <br>Somebody like you <br><br>I want a little loving <br>I told you all to listen <br>But you never liked what you heard <br>I take what I am given <br>This may sound absurd <br>I share a double vision <br>Starting the transition <br><br>Hey where's Jimmy Jazz <br>Steady on the scales <br><br>I told you to listen <br>I told you to listen <br><br>Somebody's got hold back the river <br>Somebody like you <br>Somebody's got to hold back the river <br>Somebody like you <br><br>You know that somebody <br>You know that somebody <br>You know that somebody <br>But it ain't you]]></content><category term="Wet Wet Wet" label="Wet Wet Wet"/><category term="Hold Back The River" label="Hold Back The River"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Maggie_May/</id><title>Wet Wet Wet - Maggie May - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:17:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:17:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Maggie_May/" title="Wet Wet Wet - Maggie May - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wake up maggie I think I've got something to say to you <br>It's late september and I really should be back at school <br>I know I keep you amused <br>But I feel I'm being used <br>Oh maggie I couldn't have tried any more <br><br>You led me away from home <br>Just to save you from being alone <br>You stole my heart and that's what really hurts <br><br>The morning sun when it's in your face really shows your age <br>But that don't worry me none, in my eyes you're everything <br>I laughed at all your jokes <br>My love you didn't need to coax <br>Oh maggie I couldn't have tried any more <br><br>You led me away from home <br>Just to save you from being alone <br>You stole my heart and that's a pain I could do without <br><br>All I needed was a friend to lend a guiding hand <br>You turned into a lover and mother what a lover <br>You wore me out <br>All you did was wreck my bed <br>And in the morning kick me in the head <br>Oh maggie I couldn't have tried any more <br><br>You led me away from home <br>Just to save you from being alone <br>You stole my heart I couldn't leave you if I tried <br><br>I suppose I could collect my books and get on back to school <br>Or steal my daddy's cue and make a living out of playing pool <br>Find myself a rock and roll band <br>That needs a helping hand <br>Oh maggie I wish I'd never seen your face <br><br>You made a first class fool out of me <br>Now I'm as blind as a fool can be <br>You stole my heart but I love you anyway]]></content><category term="Wet Wet Wet" label="Wet Wet Wet"/><category term="Maggie May" label="Maggie May"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Keys_To_Your_Heart/</id><title>Wet Wet Wet - Keys To Your Heart - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:17:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:17:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Keys_To_Your_Heart/" title="Wet Wet Wet - Keys To Your Heart - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You might say <br>You don't love me <br>That might be right <br>Say that you wanted me <br>Say that you needed me <br>Say that you wanted me <br><br>And I said now hold me <br>Please hold me <br>Make this seem right <br>All through the night <br>I said hold me <br>Please hold me <br>Yes you can try just a little <br>For you to make it right <br><br>Holding on for so long <br>Gets me the keys to your heart <br><br>So let me take a little while <br>To tell you about heaven, heaven in my life <br>It could be a secret <br>It could be a lie <br>It's a case of holding on til I die <br><br>Now I said now hold me <br>Please hold me <br>Make this seem right <br>All through the night <br>And I said now hold me <br>Please hold me <br>Yes you can try just a little <br>For you to make it right <br><br>Holding on for so long <br>Gets me the keys to your heart <br>Holding on for so long <br>Gets me the keys to your heart <br><br>And I said now hold me <br>Please hold me <br>Yes you can try just a little <br>Please try just a little <br>Please try and you will see <br><br>Holding on for so long <br>Gets me the keys to your heart <br>Holding on for so long <br>Gets me the keys to your heart <br>You gotta give a little <br>To get the keys to your heart <br>Gets me the keys to your heart]]></content><category term="Wet Wet Wet" label="Wet Wet Wet"/><category term="Keys To Your Heart" label="Keys To Your Heart"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/I_Wish/</id><title>Wet Wet Wet - I Wish - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:17:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:17:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/I_Wish/" title="Wet Wet Wet - I Wish - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come on up, hey little darling <br><br>That was the way when I first met you baby <br>You weren't right for me <br>I didn't really care <br>Act quite naturally <br><br>She said <br>Went on a boat going down by the river <br>Plenty more supplies <br>Seen a lot of planes going up in the air <br><br>Do you ever get the feeling <br>That you want to fly like a bird in the sky <br><br>Hey lucille, you'll be the talk of the town <br>Lucille hey, you'll be the talk of the town <br>She met a young man called johnnie <br>He played a little mean guitar <br><br>No matter how hard I try <br>I want to fly like a bird in the sky <br>I want to fly like a bird in the sky <br><br>I wish I could take time <br>I wish oh I wish so hard <br>I wish I could take time <br>I wish oh I wish so hard <br><br>Living the night, doing it wrong <br><br>It's a little lonely without you <br>The feeling was strong <br>The world was holding on <br>I want to be on my own <br><br>I wish I could take time <br>I wish oh I wish so hard <br>I wish I could take time <br>I wish oh I wish so hard <br><br>Won't you stay with me <br><br>Take from me what I take form you <br>You can take from me what I find in you <br><br>Come on, tell me, tell me, tell me <br><br>I wish I could take time <br>I wish oh I wish so hard <br>Hey, I wish I could take time <br>I wish oh I wish so hard <br><br>Say I can't get by without your love <br>Say I can't get by without your love <br><br>Say I can't get by without your love <br>Say I can't get by without your love <br><br>I wish I could take time <br>I wish oh I wish so hard <br>I wish I could take time <br>I wish oh I wish so hard <br><br>I wish I could take time <br>I wish oh I wish so hard]]></content><category term="Wet Wet Wet" label="Wet Wet Wet"/><category term="I Wish" label="I Wish"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Youve_Had_It/</id><title>Wet Wet Wet - You`ve Had It - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:17:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:17:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Youve_Had_It/" title="Wet Wet Wet - You`ve Had It - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Where have you got to lately <br>Where are you going to be <br>And i thought about it yesterday now baby <br>It's in my cuts now baby <br>As deep as yours <br>And the scars from this are gonna last for ever <br>And ever <br><br>You've had it <br>What you're getting from me <br>You've had it <br>Now what's it going to be <br>You've had it <br>What you're getting from me <br>But all i wanna do is be with you <br><br>Now that you've got me baby <br>You're just as sharp as me <br>And i'm glad you've cut me off <br>Writing my lies on the back of your hand <br>Tearing me up and watching you land <br>Sitting your heart on the sofa with me <br><br>You've had it <br>But you're getting to me <br>Now what's it going to be <br>But you're getting to me <br>Now what's it going to be <br>You've had it <br>But all i wanna do is be with you <br><br>Where have you got to baby <br>Cos look what you've done <br>And you know that this goes <br>On and on and on and on <br><br>You've had it <br>What you're getting from me <br>You've had it <br>But you're getting to me <br>You've had it <br><br>You've had it <br>What you're getting from me <br>You've had it <br>But you're getting to me <br>You've had it <br>What you're getting to me <br>You've had it <br>But all i wanna to is be with you]]></content><category term="Wet Wet Wet" label="Wet Wet Wet"/><category term="You`ve Had It" label="You`ve Had It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Broke_Away/</id><title>Wet Wet Wet - Broke Away - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:17:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:17:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Broke_Away/" title="Wet Wet Wet - Broke Away - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was born by the river <br>So I know where the river runs dry <br>I couldn't last forever <br><br>Accused just for living <br>But I know that the living was right <br>I couldn't last forever <br>Look at me making movies <br>Making living like I've never lived before <br><br>And the people wanting out of the river <br>Like a poor boy really should <br><br>Now I can sit and stand it <br>Like other people do <br>What you do for me I'll do for you, yeah <br><br>Now I can sit and stand it <br>Like other people do <br>What is blue for me, is blue for you <br><br>There's a man who I know <br>You know he's got a fist full of dirty dollars <br>And I know they won't last forever <br>Does he really know what people are saying <br>Always feeling sure what he is there saying <br>But the other's disappear he was alone <br><br>Now I can sit and stand it <br>Like other people do <br>What you do for me I'll do for you <br><br>Now I can sit and stand it <br>Like other people do <br>What is blue for me, is blue for you <br><br>I go back to the river <br>Cause I know where the river runs dry <br>I couldn't last forever <br>Take the night making movies <br>Like a villain never ever seen the night of day <br>Don't you know that I can't last forever <br><br>Now I can sit and stand it <br>Like other people do <br>What you do for me I'll do for you <br><br>Now I can sit and stand it <br>Like other people do <br>What is blue for me, is blue for you <br><br>Now I can sit and stand it <br>Like other people do <br>What is blue for me, is kind of blue for you, yeah <br><br>Hello I'm going down <br>You know I don't want to wear no pretty crown <br>Help people I'm going down]]></content><category term="Wet Wet Wet" label="Wet Wet Wet"/><category term="Broke Away" label="Broke Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Blue_For_You/</id><title>Wet Wet Wet - Blue For You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:17:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:17:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Blue_For_You/" title="Wet Wet Wet - Blue For You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was born by the river <br>So I know where the river runs dry <br>I couldn't last forever <br><br>Accused just for living <br>But I know that the living was right <br>I couldn't last forever <br>Look at me making movies <br>Making living like I've never lived before <br><br>And the people wanting out of the river <br>Like a poor boy really should <br><br>Now I can sit and stand it <br>Like other people do <br>What you do for me I'll do for you, yeah <br><br>Now I can sit and stand it <br>Like other people do <br>What is blue for me, is blue for you <br><br>There's a man who I know <br>You know he's got a fist full of dirty dollars <br>And I know they won't last forever <br>Does he really know what people are saying <br>Always feeling sure what he is there saying <br>But the other's disappear he was alone <br><br>Now I can sit and stand it <br>Like other people do <br>What you do for me I'll do for you <br><br>Now I can sit and stand it <br>Like other people do <br>What is blue for me, is blue for you <br><br>I go back to the river <br>Cause I know where the river runs dry <br>I couldn't last forever <br>Take the night making movies <br>Like a villain never ever seen the night of day <br>Don't you know that I can't last forever <br><br>Now I can sit and stand it <br>Like other people do <br>What you do for me I'll do for you <br><br>Now I can sit and stand it <br>Like other people do <br>What is blue for me, is blue for you <br><br>Now I can sit and stand it <br>Like other people do <br>What is blue for me, is kind of blue for you, yeah <br><br>Hello I'm going down <br>You know I don't want to wear no pretty crown <br>Help people I'm going down]]></content><category term="Wet Wet Wet" label="Wet Wet Wet"/><category term="Blue For You" label="Blue For You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Cant_Stand_The_Night/</id><title>Wet Wet Wet - Can`t Stand The Night - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:17:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:17:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Cant_Stand_The_Night/" title="Wet Wet Wet - Can`t Stand The Night - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here I am <br>I want you to know that I understand <br>What it is you're giving me <br><br>I've got it all brand new <br><br>Here we are <br>Put up a show of hands <br>But I've got the feeling that <br>They don't know what they're gonna do <br><br>We don't live there no more <br>We've got the room on the second floor <br>Oh, we don't live there no more <br><br>Stay with me heartache so I can keep it right <br>Another day with the heartache <br>You know I can't stand the night <br><br>Think about the people in the foreign lands <br>Think about the dirty money in my hands <br>Think I know the reason why it doesn't work out right <br>Think of all the needy with a helping hand <br>Think of all the greedy people in our land <br>Think they know the reason why it doesn't work out right <br><br>I don't live there no more <br>I've got the suite on the penthouse floor <br>Oh, I don't live there no more <br><br>Stay with me heartache so I can keep it right <br>Another day with the heartache <br>You know I can't stand the night <br>Stay with me heartache so I can keep it right <br>Another day with the heartache <br>You know I can't stand the night <br><br>I don't live there no more <br>I've got the suite on the penthouse floor <br>Oh, I don't live there no more <br><br>See my pride <br>Been looking for it once or twice <br>Lost my pride <br>I'm really gonna make it right <br><br>I don't live there no more <br>I've got no room on the penthouse floor <br>Oh, I don't live there no more <br><br>Stay with me heartache so I can keep it right <br>Another day with the heartache <br>You know I can't stand the night <br>Stay with me heartache so I can keep it right <br>Another day with the heartache <br>You know I can't stand the night]]></content><category term="Wet Wet Wet" label="Wet Wet Wet"/><category term="Can`t Stand The Night" label="Can`t Stand The Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Sweet_Surrender/</id><title>Wet Wet Wet - Sweet Surrender - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:17:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:17:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wet_Wet_Wet/Sweet_Surrender/" title="Wet Wet Wet - Sweet Surrender - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey little fella, get your show together <br>I was listening in before <br>Now I don't care no more <br><br>Look around now (look around now) <br>It's always that it's gonna get me down <br>It's only begun <br><br>One look is all it took <br>I remember that sweet surrender <br>I recall, do you <br>That sweet surrender <br><br>Sweet surrender <br><br>My determination <br>Came creeping across the nation <br>Sure mistake for anyone <br>So you can't take home everyone <br>Cause it's only just begun <br><br>One look is all it took <br>To remember that sweet surrender <br>I recall, do you <br>That sweet surrender <br><br>I don't know, I don't care <br>Cause I'm living without you baby <br>Even when I know what's going on <br>Yeah it only took, one look, one glance <br>To set my heart for romance <br>Do you believe my sweet surrender <br><br>My sweet surrender <br><br>Hey little fella, now your show's together <br>I never wanted you to listen before <br>So why should I walk out the door <br>Stick around now (stick around now) <br>And so the story goes on through the night <br>It's only begun <br><br>One look is all it took <br>I remember that sweet surrender <br>Do you recall, cause I do <br>My sweet surrender <br><br>I don't know, I don't care <br>Cause I'm living without you baby <br>Even when I know what's going on <br>Yeah all it takes, one look, one glance <br>To set my heart for romance <br>One look is all it took <br>My sweet surrender <br><br>That sweet surrender <br>One look is all it took to remember <br>(I don't know and I don't care)]]></content><category term="Wet Wet Wet" label="Wet Wet Wet"/><category term="Sweet Surrender" label="Sweet Surrender"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/All_Time_Low/Dirty_Laundry/</id><title>All Time Low - Dirty Laundry - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:19:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:19:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/All_Time_Low/Dirty_Laundry/" title="All Time Low - Dirty Laundry - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't believe in saints <br>They never make mistakes <br>I know it's not my place <br>Who am I to tell you <br>that you need to change <br>Her closet’s such a mess <br>Filled up with <br>all the skeletons she's kept <br>Nobody's perfect I confess <br>But she's perfect enough <br>Without ever dressing up <br>Dirty laundry is piling in her room <br>She's got her secrets <br>Yea I got mine too <br>I don't care about what you did <br>Only care about what we do <br>Dirty laundry looks good on you <br>Now here's some honesty <br>Sometimes I trip over your history <br>Wish I could change my mind <br>But it's the things I shouldn't see <br>That always catch my eye <br>Dirty laundry is piling in her room <br>She's got her secrets <br>Yea I got mine too <br>I don't care about what you did <br>Only care about what we do <br>Dirty laundry looks good on you <br>Dirty laundry is piling in her room <br>She's got her secrets <br>Yea I got mine too <br>I don't care about what you did <br>Only care about what we do <br>Dirty laundry <br>looks good on you <br>Dirty laundry <br>looks good on you <br>Dirty laundry <br>looks good on you <br>It looks good on you <br>]]></content><category term="All Time Low" label="All Time Low"/><category term="Dirty Laundry" label="Dirty Laundry"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rhiannon_Giddens/Come_Love_Come/</id><title>Rhiannon Giddens - Come Love Come - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:23:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:23:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rhiannon_Giddens/Come_Love_Come/" title="Rhiannon Giddens - Come Love Come - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Chorus] <br>Come love come, the road lies low <br>The way is long and hard I know <br>Come love come, the road lies free <br>I'll wait for you in Tennessee <br><br>[Verse] <br>When I was four, my loving mam <br>Was cornered by the boss's man <br>She turned her head and got struck down <br>They buried her in the cold cold ground <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Come love come, the road lies low <br>The way is long and hard I know <br>Come love come, the road lies free <br>I'll wait for you in Tennessee <br><br>[Verse] <br>When I was twelve, my father dear <br>Was strong of arm and free of fear <br>Until the day he raised his hand <br>Then he was sold to Alabam' <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Come love come, the road lies low <br>The way is long and hard I know <br>Come love come, the road lies free <br>I'll wait for you in Tennessee <br>[Verse] <br>I was sixteen found my bloom <br>And found my man, we jumped the broom <br>We pledged each other the rest of our lives <br>And on Saturday nights we were man and wife <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Come love come, the road lies low <br>The way is long and hard I know <br>Come love come, the road lies free <br>I'll wait for you in Tennessee <br><br>[Verse] <br>I was eighteen, bugles called <br>The boys in blue came o'er the wall <br>I took my chance and followed free <br>They led the way to Tennessee <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Come love come, the road lies low <br>The way is long and hard I know <br>Come love come, the road lies free <br>I'll wait for you in Tennessee <br><br>[Verse] <br>Here I sit in a tiny shack <br>With thirteen others at my back <br>I've sent you word, so all I can do <br>Is wait, and wait, and wait, and wait, and wait... <br>And wait for you <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Come love come, the road lies low <br>The way is long and hard I know <br>Come love come, the road lies free <br>I'll wait for you in Tennessee <br><br>Come love come, the road lies low <br>The way is long and hard I know <br>Come love come, the road lies free <br>I'll wait for you in Tennessee <br><br>I'll wait for you <br>I'll wait for you <br>I'll wait for you <br>I'll wait for you]]></content><category term="Rhiannon Giddens" label="Rhiannon Giddens"/><category term="Come Love Come" label="Come Love Come"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Home_Again_In_My_Heart/</id><title>The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Home Again In My Heart - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:25:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:25:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Home_Again_In_My_Heart/" title="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Home Again In My Heart - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One in a million in a lonely town <br>Two hundred people trying to keep me down <br>I've taken all I can, I ain't lookin' back. <br>Small town boy in a back yard lot <br>Can't make a living with the luck I've got <br>I'm gonna leave it all, I ain't looking back. <br><br>That's the way I remember, it seemed to me when I was young. <br>But I can still see the leaves slowly fall to the ground <br>And the snow on the trees as the winter comes down. <br>Still I go home again in my heart. <br><br>My father worked hard on the railroad track; <br>37 years cut across his back <br>He gave it all he had for what he believed. <br>Like every other kid that came before <br>I grew up believing there was something more <br>And I still believe, I still believe. <br><br>That's the way I remember, it seemed to me when I was young. <br>But I can still see the leaves slowly fall to the ground <br>And the snow on the trees as the winter comes down. <br>Still I go home again in my heart. <br><br>But I can still see the lightning on a warm summer night <br>And the rain on the roof when I close my eyes; <br>I can still hear us laughing on the front porch in the dark. <br>There are days when I know that I've traveled so far <br>That I'll never find the road leading back to the start <br>Still I go home again in my heart <br>Still I go home again in my heart <br>In my heart, in my heart]]></content><category term="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band" label="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band"/><category term="Home Again In My Heart" label="Home Again In My Heart"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Down_That_Road_Tonight/</id><title>The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Down That Road Tonight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:25:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:25:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Down_That_Road_Tonight/" title="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Down That Road Tonight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Seems like lately we're losin' touch <br>Work to hard and worry too much <br>I think it's time for me and you <br>To get back to what we used to do <br>We'd steal away on a Saturday night <br>Meet in the field when the time was right <br>Just us two and a starry sky <br>Felt like paradise <br><br>I said Ooh Baby goin' down that road tonight <br>I said it's too crazy need to hold each other tight <br>Thinkin' maybe the moon stills shines as bright <br>Like it did back then, it'll shine again <br>Down that road tonight <br><br>Remember all the songs that we used to know <br>Dancin' in the dark to the radio <br>Lost in the rythmn, kickin' up some heat <br>The memories are still so sweet <br>Time's gone by but it's plain to see <br>I still love you and you still love me <br>Let's shake these troubles put 'em all aside <br>C'mon we're gonna take that ride <br><br>I said Ooh Baby goin' down that road tonight <br>I said it's too crazy need to hold each other tight <br>Thinkin' maybe the moon stills shines as bright <br>Like it did back then, it'll shine again <br>Down that road tonight <br>Down that road <br><br>[repeat to fade]]]></content><category term="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band" label="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band"/><category term="Down That Road Tonight" label="Down That Road Tonight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Face_On_The_Cutting_Room_Floor/</id><title>The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Face On The Cutting Room Floor - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:25:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:25:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Face_On_The_Cutting_Room_Floor/" title="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Face On The Cutting Room Floor - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She's history <br>No one would give her a star on the walk <br>She'd have a hundred if pillows could talk <br>Where have I seen her before? <br>She's the face on the cutting room floor <br><br>It's no mystery <br>Acting in school at the tenderest age <br>Lit up the room when she stepped on the stage <br>Came to la for some more <br>She's the face on the cutting room floor <br><br>She had visions of contracts <br>And thousands of people in line <br>To see her; <br>Knocking on door after door after all of this time <br>Now she's not sure <br><br>Up in hollywood <br>Stayed with an agent she met in a bar <br>Laughed when he told her he'd make her a star <br>Where has she heard that before? <br>She's the face on the cutting room floor <br><br>One night he told her that she'd never get anywhere <br>In her clothes <br>That's what it takes to play movieland musical chairs <br>Now she knows <br><br>Goodbye hollywood <br>Leaving tonight on the 2:30 'hound <br>Sunrise or sunset she won't be around <br>But they'll replace her with so many more <br>She's the face on the cutting room floor <br>Poor little face on the cutting room floor]]></content><category term="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band" label="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band"/><category term="Face On The Cutting Room Floor" label="Face On The Cutting Room Floor"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Babys_Got_A_Hold_On_Me_Album_Ver/</id><title>The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Baby`s Got A Hold On Me (Album Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:25:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:25:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Babys_Got_A_Hold_On_Me_Album_Ver/" title="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Baby`s Got A Hold On Me (Album Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sittin' on the front porch tryin' to keep a still <br>Baby's looking finer than a fifty dollar bill <br>Pretty blue eyes and it isn't hard to see that baby's got a hold on me <br><br>Long blonde hair down the middle of her back <br>She's got the keys to her daddy's cadillac <br>Got every little thing that I'm ever gonna need <br>Baby's got a hold on me <br>Got a hold on <br>Got a hold on me <br>Got a hold on <br>Baby's got a hold on me <br><br>We got a full tank of gas, lookin' for a thrill <br>A 3-day weekend, alot of time to kill <br>Put the top down but we're never gonna freeze <br>Cause baby's got a hold on me <br>got a hold on <br>got a hold on me <br>got a hold on <br>Baby's got a hold on me <br><br>Theer's a full moon shining on a Carolina night <br>Driving my girl cross the interstate line <br>Gotta a preacher waiting and that's how it's gonna be <br>Cause baby's got a hold on me <br>Got a hold on <br>got a hold on me <br>got a hold on <br>Baby's gotta hold on me <br>gotta hold on [x3] <br>Baby's gotta hold on me [x3]]]></content><category term="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band" label="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band"/><category term="Baby`s Got A Hold On Me (Album Ver.)" label="Baby`s Got A Hold On Me (Album Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Fishin_In_The_Dark_Album_Ver/</id><title>The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Fishin` In The Dark (Album Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:25:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:25:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Fishin_In_The_Dark_Album_Ver/" title="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Fishin` In The Dark (Album Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lazy yellow moon comin' up tonite <br>shinin' thru the trees <br>Crickets are singin' and lightning bugs <br>are floatin on the breeze <br>Baby get ready..... <br><br>Across the field where the creek turns back by the ole stone road <br>I'm gonna take you to a special place that nobody knows <br>Baby get ready.....OooooooOooo <br><br>You and me going fishing in the dark <br>Lying on our backs and counting the stars <br>Where the cool grass grows. <br>Down by the river in the full moon light <br>We'll be fallin' in love in the middle of the night <br>Just movin' slow... <br><br>Stayin' the whole night thru, feels so good to be with you... <br><br>Spring is almost over and the summer's comin' <br>the days are gettin' long <br>Waited all winter for the time to be right, just to take you along <br>Baby get ready..... <br><br>And it don't matter if we sit forever and the fish don't bite <br>Jump in the river and cool ourselves from the heat of the night <br>Baby get ready.....OoooooooOoo <br><br>[Repeat the CHORUS (x3)] <br><br>You and me going fishin in the dark!]]></content><category term="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band" label="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band"/><category term="Fishin` In The Dark (Album Ver.)" label="Fishin` In The Dark (Album Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/I_Love_Only_You/</id><title>The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - I Love Only You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:25:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:25:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/I_Love_Only_You/" title="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - I Love Only You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I like to drink my beer <br>Spend time with the boys <br>After work, to down a few <br>Is something I enjoy <br>And sometimes I stay out too late <br>Yes I know it's true <br>But I love only you. <br><br>And I like to take life easy <br>Work out in the yard <br>Sleep late on the weekends <br>After an all-night game of cards <br>And drivin' my old chevy <br>On a sunday afternoon <br>But I love only you <br><br>I like my old guitar <br>And I'd like to be a star and shine on you <br>I'd like to write a song <br>The whole world could sing along <br>I love only you <br><br>I like my old memories <br>The girls I used to know <br>Some of them still have a place <br>My mind likes to go <br>Of all the ones I've cared for <br>Lord knows there's been a few <br>But I love only you <br>Honey, I love only you.]]></content><category term="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band" label="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band"/><category term="I Love Only You" label="I Love Only You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Workin_Man_Nowhere_To_Go/</id><title>The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Workin` Man (Nowhere To Go) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:25:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:25:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Workin_Man_Nowhere_To_Go/" title="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Workin` Man (Nowhere To Go) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sittin' alone in the dark <br>Wastin' my time in a park <br>'Cause I've got <br>Nowhere to go <br><br>Had me a job 'til the market fell out <br>Tried hard to borrow but there was no help <br>Now I've got <br>Nowhere to go <br><br>I need a job for these two hands <br>I'm a workin' man <br>With nowhere to go <br><br>One last look at my land <br>Auctioneer with his gavel in hand <br>And he says, "It's got to go" <br><br>Worked this piece all my life <br>It broke my heart and it took my wife <br>Now I've got nothing to show <br><br>I need a job for these two hands <br>I'm a workin' man <br>With nowhere to go <br><br>Wandered aimless in the city <br>With my dirt workin' boots <br>And my old straw hat in hand <br><br>Singing a song by Woody Guthrie <br>This land is your land <br>It ain't my land <br><br>I'm a workin' man <br>With nowhere to go <br><br>I was born to the sunrise <br>Breaking back all day <br>Now I've got <br>Something to say <br><br>I am broke but not broken <br>And I am not alone <br>'Cause there's a lot of folks <br>With nowhere to go <br><br>Are they ever gonna understand <br>You can't leave a workin' man <br>Nowhere to go <br><br>Are they ever gonna understand <br>You can't leave a workin' man <br>Nowhere to go <br><br>Nowhere to go <br>Nowhere to go <br>Nowhere to go <br>Nowhere to go]]></content><category term="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band" label="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band"/><category term="Workin` Man (Nowhere To Go)" label="Workin` Man (Nowhere To Go)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Oh_What_A_Love_Album_Ver/</id><title>The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Oh What A Love (Album Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:25:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:25:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Oh_What_A_Love_Album_Ver/" title="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Oh What A Love (Album Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh what a love, that'll bind the wounds of a loss and heal my heart <br>Oh what a love, to cast away the pain <br>Oh what a love, that'll bear for me the cost of a brand new start <br>Oh what a love, to let me begin again <br><br>Oh what a life, that'll brighten up the corners of a lonely life <br>Oh what a life, to cast away the rain <br>Oh what a life to remove the gloom I face in the dark alone <br>Oh what a life, I believe I can see again <br><br>I remember the day <br>We walked on the beach till sunset, then we sang <br>And the songs we played were a promise of love that'll last beyond the grave <br><br>Oh what a song, learned from the sea taught slowly to the young <br>Oh what a song, to cast away the rain <br>Oh what a song, to break the bonds of fear and still the sound <br>Oh what a song, I believe I can sing again <br><br>I remember the day we met at a place of hope, I took what you gave <br>And the words we'd say were a promise of love that'll honor beyond the grave <br><br>[Chorus]]]></content><category term="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band" label="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band"/><category term="Oh What A Love (Album Ver.)" label="Oh What A Love (Album Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Ive_Been_Lookin/</id><title>The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - I`ve Been Lookin` - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:25:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:25:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Ive_Been_Lookin/" title="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - I`ve Been Lookin` - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been lookin' for a love <br>Someone to hold as I lay sleeping <br>I'm not talking about someone who's scared of promises or keeping 'em <br>I'm just looking for a love to stand the test of time <br>I've been lookin' for someone to be all mine <br><br>I had too much lonely <br>I need a one and only <br>Someone I can care about and call my own <br>Well in true tradition <br>Without an intermission <br>We'll still be together when the kids are grown. <br><br>I've been lookin for a love <br>Someone to hold as I lay sleeping <br>I'm not talking about someone who's scared of promises or keeping 'em <br>I'm just lookin' for a love to stand the test of time <br>I've been looking for someone to be all mine. <br><br>I've been lookin for a love <br>Someone to hold as I lay sleeping <br>I'm not talking about someone who's scared of promises or keeping 'em <br>I'm just looking for a love to stand the test of time <br>I've been looking for someone to be all mine. <br><br>I've been looking for some one to be all mine. <br>I've been looking for some one to be all mine. <br>I've been looking for some one to be all mine. <br><br>I've been lookin for a love <br>Someone to hold as I lay sleeping <br>I'm not talking about someone who's scared of promises or keeping 'em <br>I'm just looking for a love to stand the test of time <br>I've been looking for someone to be all mine.]]></content><category term="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band" label="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band"/><category term="I`ve Been Lookin`" label="I`ve Been Lookin`"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Cadillac_Ranch/</id><title>The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Cadillac Ranch - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:25:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:25:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Cadillac_Ranch/" title="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Cadillac Ranch - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There she sits buddy just a gleamin' in the sun <br>There to greet a workin' man when his day is done <br>I'm gonna pack my pa, and I'm gonna pack my aunt <br>I'm gonna take 'em down to the Cadillac ranch <br><br>Eldorado fins, white walls and skirts; <br>Drives just like a little bit of heaven here on Earth <br>So when I die buddy throw my body in the back <br>Take me to the junkyard, in my Cadillac <br><br>Cadillac, Cadillac <br>Long and dark <br>Shiny and black <br>Open up your engines, let 'em roar <br>Tearin' up the highway like a big ol' dinosaur <br><br>James Dean in a Mercury '49 <br>Junior Johnson's runnin' in the woods of Caroline <br>Even Burt Reynolds in a black Trans Am <br>All gonna meet down at the Cadillac ranch <br><br>Cadillac, Cadillac <br>Long and dark <br>Shiny and black <br>Open up your engines, let 'em roar <br>Tearin' up the highway like a big ol' dinosaur <br><br>Hey little girlie in the blue jeans so tight <br>Driving all alone in a Colorado night <br>You're my last love, baby you're my last chance <br>Don't let 'em take me down to the Cadillac ranch <br><br>Cadillac, Cadillac <br>Long and dark <br>Shiny and black <br>Open up your engines, let 'em roar <br>Tearin' up the highway like a big ol' dinosaur <br><br>Cadillac, Cadillac <br>Long and dark <br>Shiny and black <br>Open up your engines, let 'em roar <br>Tearin' up the highway like a big ol' dinosaur]]></content><category term="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band" label="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band"/><category term="Cadillac Ranch" label="Cadillac Ranch"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Stand_A_Little_Rain/</id><title>The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Stand A Little Rain - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:25:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:25:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Stand_A_Little_Rain/" title="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Stand A Little Rain - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dark cloud is coming <br>Headed straight for your heart <br>Might get just a little bit crazy, baby <br>Might try to tear us apart <br><br>When the storm blows over <br>Only the true love remains <br>If we're ever gonna see a rainbow <br>We have to stand a little rain <br><br>Everybody wants love to be easy <br>But it's never been that way <br>Each love starts out with blue skies <br>Sometimes those blue skies turn grey <br><br>When the storm blows over <br>Only the strong love remains <br>If we're ever gonna see a rainbow <br>We have to stand a little rain <br><br>The thunder rolls <br>And the lightning strikes <br>Hold on, darling <br>It's gonna be alright <br><br>'Cause when the storm blows over <br>Only the true love remains <br>If we're ever gonna see a rainbow <br>We have to stand a little rain <br><br>If we're ever gonna see a rainbow <br>We have to stand a little rain]]></content><category term="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band" label="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band"/><category term="Stand A Little Rain" label="Stand A Little Rain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Partners_Brothers_And_Friends/</id><title>The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Partners, Brothers And Friends - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:25:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:25:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Partners_Brothers_And_Friends/" title="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Partners, Brothers And Friends - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The promoter says he wants to cancel <br>'Cause there ain't enough tickets sold <br>The air conditioner on the bus just broke <br>And I can't shake this cold <br>The single lost the bullet <br>The singer's losin' his wife <br>Well, I might be crazy but I wouldn't change <br>A single thing about this life <br><br>Sometimes we feel like champions <br>Sometimes we just can't win <br>Sometimes our records hit the top of the charts <br>Or the discount bargain bins <br>Through almost 20 years of touring <br>We've remained partners, brothers and friends <br>Well, we keep it together 'cause we're sure we're gonna be <br>Big time before it all ends <br><br>Just as long as Johnny's got his fiddle <br>And Jimmy's got his drums along <br>Then Jeffrey and me and Bobby will be <br>Singing all our favorite songs <br>Catch the fire from the folks in the front row <br>Fan the flames as the beat gets strong <br>It's great to be a part of something so good <br>That's lasted so long <br><br>Well I saw a story in the paper <br>Suddenly the band's big news <br>The critics all like our records just fine <br>But they seem a bit confused <br>Is it folk or rock or country <br>Whoa, seems like everybody cares but us <br>So just leave us an early wakeup call <br>So we don't miss the bus <br><br>Just as long as Johnny's got his fiddle <br>And Jimmy's got his drums along <br>Then Jeffrey and me and Bobby will be <br>Singing all our favorite songs <br>We'll catch the fire from the folks in the front row <br>Fan the flames as the beat gets strong <br>It's great to be a part of something so good <br>That's lasted so long <br><br>The band says it can't stand my latest song <br>It's too personal <br>But my first wife's second marriage blew up <br>They had to get the dang thing annulled <br>Well, if that ain't something to sing about <br>Well you tell me what is <br>And we'll give it a beat and put it on the street <br>And we just might have another hit <br><br>Just as long as Johnny's got his banjo <br>And Jimmie's got his harps along <br>Then Jeffrey and me and Bobby will be <br>Singing all our favorite songs <br>We'll catch the fire from the folks in the front row <br>Fan the flames as the beat gets strong <br>It's great to be a part of something so good <br>That's lasted so long <br>Yeah, it's great to be a part of something so good <br>That's lasted so long <br><br>[Chorus]]]></content><category term="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band" label="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band"/><category term="Partners, Brothers And Friends" label="Partners, Brothers And Friends"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Modern_Day_Romance/</id><title>The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Modern Day Romance - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:25:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:25:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Modern_Day_Romance/" title="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Modern Day Romance - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We met on the highway, she flagged me down <br>Had a flat on her stingray with nobody around <br>I helped her out, she said climb in <br>So I ditched my ol truck just to see where the party would end. <br><br>We spent the weekend in reno in the honeymoon suite <br>Never saw the casino, barely took time to eat. <br>I never dreamed she would take me this far <br>But by sunday that lady had taken a hold of my heart. <br><br>It's a modern day romance, a new kind of game <br>With no time to slow dance in the fast lane. <br>I tried to love her without any strings <br>But a modern day romance has left me some old-fashioned pain. <br><br>She never said good-bye, just a note by the phone <br>Said "thanks for the good times, but it's time to move on." <br>Well I'm out here walkin' with my thumb in the air <br>Wondering where she might've gone and why I even care. <br><br>It's a modern day romance; old fashioned pain]]></content><category term="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band" label="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band"/><category term="Modern Day Romance" label="Modern Day Romance"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/High_Horse/</id><title>The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - High Horse - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:25:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:25:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/High_Horse/" title="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - High Horse - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Get up on your high horse, woman <br>Get up on your high horse now <br>And get up on your high horse, woman <br>I'll make it up to you somehow <br><br>Moonlit shadow, she starts a trippin' firelight <br>Jumpin' the trees lyin' across the right of way <br>Silvery mornin' it glistens down the valley <br>But she don't stop 'til we ride the night away <br><br>Get up on your high horse, woman <br>Get up on your high horse now <br>Get up on your high horse, woman <br>I'll make it up to you somehow <br><br>Blonde braids tangle at the misty break of mornin' <br>Catchin' light through a dusty window pane <br>Lost in lust, in denial of the warnin' <br>She digs her heels in this stallion's flank again <br><br>Get up on your high horse, woman <br>Get up on your high horse now <br>Get up on your high horse, woman <br>I'll make it up to you somehow <br><br>Get up on your high horse, woman <br>You paid the price, you get to play <br>Get up on your high horse, woman <br>You're gonna ride to the break of day <br><br>To the break of day <br>To the break of day <br>To the break of day <br><br>Get up on your high horse, woman <br>Get up on your high horse now <br>Get up on your high horse, woman <br>I'll make it up to you somehow <br><br>Get up on your high horse, woman <br>You paid the price, you get to play <br>Get up on your high horse, woman <br>You're gonna ride to the break of day]]></content><category term="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band" label="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band"/><category term="High Horse" label="High Horse"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Long_Hard_Road_The_Sharecroppers_Dream/</id><title>The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Long Hard Road (The Sharecropper`s Dream) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:25:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:25:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Nitty_Gritty_Dirt_Band/Long_Hard_Road_The_Sharecroppers_Dream/" title="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band - Long Hard Road (The Sharecropper`s Dream) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Way back in my memory there's a scene that I recall <br>Of a little run-down cabin in the woods <br>Where my dad never promised that our blue moon would turn gold <br>But he laid awake nights wishin' that it would. <br><br>When the world was on our radio, hard work was on our minds. <br>We lived our day-to-day in plain dirt fashion <br>With ol' overalls and cotton balls all strapped across your back <br>Man, it's hard to make believe there ain't nothing wrong. <br><br>But momma kept the Bible read and daddy kept our family fed <br>And somewhere in between I must have grown <br>Cause someday I was dreamin' that a song that I was singin' <br>Takes me down the road to where I want to go. <br>Now I know, it's a long hard road <br><br>Sometimes I remember when I stay up late at night <br>When the sun-up came, we got up and went <br>In the shadows of a working' day, our moonlight hours spent <br>Singin' songs along with Gramma's radio. <br><br>Now I'm beatin' down a ol' blacktop road, sleepin' in a sack <br>Livin' in my memories all in vain <br>'Cause those city lights ain't all that bright, compared to what its like <br>To see lightning bugs go dancin' in the rain. <br><br>Momma played the guitar then, and daddy made the saw blade bend <br>And raindrops played the tin roof like a drum. <br>But I just kept on dreamin' that a song that I was singin' <br>Takes me down the road to where my name is known. <br><br>Now I'm gone, and its a long hard road <br>Yes, I know, Its a long hard road.]]></content><category term="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band" label="The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band"/><category term="Long Hard Road (The Sharecropper`s Dream)" label="Long Hard Road (The Sharecropper`s Dream)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Tiny_Men/</id><title>Tripping Daisy - Tiny Men - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Tiny_Men/" title="Tripping Daisy - Tiny Men - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[These little tiny men crawl on me <br>They can be loud at times <br>All I ever wished would come to me <br>In apple orchards filled with golden eggs <br>And people stand around in socks thinking that's it's bad <br>But I will be older soon to take what I need from you <br>All this and more I see would come to me in apple orchards <br>Filled with golden eggs and people stand around in thoughts of Thinking that it's bad <br>Bubble made imagination took me for a ride <br>Where wonder plays a magic game and I learn how to fly <br>But I will be older soon to take what I need from you <br>All this and more I see. I need <br>Tried hard to make it until making it got worse <br>I hope it gets better]]></content><category term="Tripping Daisy" label="Tripping Daisy"/><category term="Tiny Men" label="Tiny Men"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/About_The_Movies/</id><title>Tripping Daisy - About The Movies - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/About_The_Movies/" title="Tripping Daisy - About The Movies - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Figured it out before I'm a teen, humming along the washing machine <br>Making some faces I made a scene, no one around to see how green <br>Run away, run away scream <br>I saddle my thoughts for the big machine <br>That is why that's the way we watch the movies <br>In some silly way life begins to change <br>That's the way we watch the movies <br>In some silly way life begins to change for you <br>You're old enough <br>Life begins to change <br>Lift up my fork and celebrate ease <br>Liquid enough, liquid it seems <br>Walking on pillows I learn how to sleep <br>Somehow I feel what flies seem to breathe <br>Run away, run away dream <br>I like all the flights on the big machine <br>That is why that's the way we watch the movies <br>In some silly way life begins to change <br>That's the way we watch the movies <br>In some silly way life begins to change for you <br>You're old enough <br>Life begins to break <br>Come on out. I've got a secret <br>Time will let you in <br>And if you want you can have a secret <br>Time will let you through <br>Come on out <br>You've gotta see it <br>Time to let you in <br>And if you want you can ride with me <br>If the wind is right the wind is free <br>I knew it then <br>I knew it well <br>Like a pilot diving down wishing well <br>I know it's better when the weather changes your hair <br>Fifteen paces a mile an hour, it's gotta feel good <br>Sucking a slurpee for ultimate power, it's gotta feel good <br>Fighting, you're back when you feel like a coward <br>It's gotta feel good <br>And everything's moving at the ultimate speed <br>Believe it <br>That's the way we watch the movies <br>In some silly way life begins to change]]></content><category term="Tripping Daisy" label="Tripping Daisy"/><category term="About The Movies" label="About The Movies"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/8_Ladies/</id><title>Tripping Daisy - 8 Ladies - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/8_Ladies/" title="Tripping Daisy - 8 Ladies - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Eight ladies drink going faster that their mighty lovin' razorshark <br>Reach for the tree, when you drink <br>Falling faster's when you're in a car <br>Slowly melts the eyes, causing spots <br>You know the kind rolling down <br><br>The forearm dripping from their eye, from their eye <br>Yeah they're dripping from their eye, you and I <br>Eight ladies sinking]]></content><category term="Tripping Daisy" label="Tripping Daisy"/><category term="8 Ladies" label="8 Ladies"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Pillar/</id><title>Tripping Daisy - Pillar - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Pillar/" title="Tripping Daisy - Pillar - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you know you're down <br>When you're looking in <br>And you know your heart has your only friend <br>Don't you know that life, it can take some time to get it real <br>Too far gone for people to ever change your mind <br>You better get a bit closer to the one that makes you bright <br>It's all you've got and you know where to go <br>It's like the magic that you need <br>You know the one <br>Stuck on top is mighty low <br>Twice as far as the blanket that won't let you go <br>It's all you can do that makes you whole <br>Twice as far as the lights that went off in time <br>It's all in your head if you think you're a <br>Lie, you're twice as good as Mars and Mars is outta sight <br>It's all that you do that lets you know <br>Stuck on top makes me down inside <br>See it in your eyes <br>Now I know why you are so vacant <br>I want what's missing there <br>A place you hide <br>Now I notice why I'm high <br>I almost shake it <br>I mean it's everywhere <br>All the days I waited <br>If I could reach you, you know I'd wanna see you there]]></content><category term="Tripping Daisy" label="Tripping Daisy"/><category term="Pillar" label="Pillar"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Human_Contact/</id><title>Tripping Daisy - Human Contact - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Human_Contact/" title="Tripping Daisy - Human Contact - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey borrow my mind. Oxygen relaxes, by the way we float <br>Amd talkin' invites you just to see a nose up close <br>It gives you what you need the most. Human contact is needed. There's something to touchin'. There's something about the way we feel <br>Leave your high hopes on full dedication <br>Keep your moods above the sink <br>Take a breath just because you think it's neat <br>Life has a lot of weather and whether or not it's you and me]]></content><category term="Tripping Daisy" label="Tripping Daisy"/><category term="Human Contact" label="Human Contact"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Geeareohdoubleyou/</id><title>Tripping Daisy - Geeareohdoubleyou - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Geeareohdoubleyou/" title="Tripping Daisy - Geeareohdoubleyou - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Geeareohdoubleyou -- grow <br>I know because you are here, and we live by the sun <br>You know why <br>Til' someone comes down and takes all of the fun <br>I know that you feel the same <br><br>You don't owe me, you owe superworld <br>I'd like to take you for a ride, yeah <br>I loved the days when we were younger then, and rainbows caught us <br><br>G.R.O.W. -- that spells 'grow' <br>I know because you are here, and we live by the sun <br>You know why <br>Til' someone comes down and takes all the fun <br>Well, I know that you feel the same <br><br>I can see the stars, they're brighter than you <br>You are a lucky fellow <br>I can see your heart, it's brighter than you <br>I have seen lovely weather <br>I have seen the stars, they're much more brighter than you]]></content><category term="Tripping Daisy" label="Tripping Daisy"/><category term="Geeareohdoubleyou" label="Geeareohdoubleyou"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Your_Socks_Have_No_Name/</id><title>Tripping Daisy - Your Socks Have No Name - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Your_Socks_Have_No_Name/" title="Tripping Daisy - Your Socks Have No Name - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's all that you do that carries you through <br>And the power that you receive destroys you <br>So you take little gun and you zap em' cause all <br>You ever wanted was the truth <br>It's always the same way when <br>You walk and you breathe <br>You walk into me <br>You walk and you blink when you walk into me <br>You walk and then scream <br>Get out of town said the man to the crowd <br>My doppler radar predicts a breeze of long hands <br>So I'm not just hanging around while they laugh about it <br>I got places to be and the sky's the limit <br>No more bowling on arrows for me <br>Cause all you ever wanted was glue <br>It's always the same when you walk in the rain <br>You walk and complain <br>Your socks have no name so you stop the parade <br>No more walking today]]></content><category term="Tripping Daisy" label="Tripping Daisy"/><category term="Your Socks Have No Name" label="Your Socks Have No Name"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Mechanical_Breakdown/</id><title>Tripping Daisy - Mechanical Breakdown - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Mechanical_Breakdown/" title="Tripping Daisy - Mechanical Breakdown - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was born in a self-styled crusader in an amazing race of human elevators <br>It's risky <br>You know how it is <br>Up and down all day long, you take a route but the route is wrong <br>It's tricky <br>You know how it is <br><br>So you and me are going out tonight <br>And there's fifty million ways to move around, so let's make it right <br>Yeah, you and me are going out tonight <br>And there's fifty million ways to get it wrong, so let's get it right <br><br>Looks like mechanical breakdown <br>It's wonderful being so soft all around <br>Looks like a miracle laydown <br>It's wonderful being so close to the ground]]></content><category term="Tripping Daisy" label="Tripping Daisy"/><category term="Mechanical Breakdown" label="Mechanical Breakdown"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Bandaids_Tm_For_Hire/</id><title>Tripping Daisy - Bandaids Tm For Hire - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Bandaids_Tm_For_Hire/" title="Tripping Daisy - Bandaids Tm For Hire - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Some bleed too much <br>Some things are touched <br><br>Take the time to fix yourself all up <br>Taking time helps with your luck <br>You can bleed on the other hand <br>Talkin' makes an easy chair a friend <br>Crawling places just to stand <br>You can feed your mouth a plan <br><br>Some bleed too much <br>I've seen it flood <br><br>You can set yourself on fire <br>Burning's good when you're burnin' wood <br>It tastes the same with an overbite <br>Breathing makes it easy to deny <br>Sure is fun to sing about life <br><br>How much longer can this last? <br>My tooth is loose]]></content><category term="Tripping Daisy" label="Tripping Daisy"/><category term="Bandaids Tm For Hire" label="Bandaids Tm For Hire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Sonic_Bloom/</id><title>Tripping Daisy - Sonic Bloom - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Sonic_Bloom/" title="Tripping Daisy - Sonic Bloom - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love gets inside of you <br>It makes me invisible <br><br>And I will continue to hang on super love, a sonic bloom <br>A total emotionless excuse <br>I can't believe it happened to me <br>The magic's in my heart, believe me... <br><br>Rushing through my electrical phase <br>I found a place to hide when you're away <br>Almost caught myself a breath <br>I touched your hand, I lost myself instead <br>I wanna be just as good <br>I wanna make it better <br>I wanna see you sideways <br>I wanna make it better <br><br>When love gets inside of you <br>It makes me invincible <br>And I can't believe this happened to me...]]></content><category term="Tripping Daisy" label="Tripping Daisy"/><category term="Sonic Bloom" label="Sonic Bloom"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Field_Day_Jitters/</id><title>Tripping Daisy - Field Day Jitters - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tripping_Daisy/Field_Day_Jitters/" title="Tripping Daisy - Field Day Jitters - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wondering jets inside of me <br>I've got the field day jitters, wet matches and a bottle of Mr. Clean <br>I'm a nervous wreck in the shape of a test <br>I figure it's all about giving <br>Causing all of the brain to slip into frame and visit the space that it gives me for sleep <br><br>Wondering jets inside of me <br>I've got the field day jitters <br>I'm an open nest, a paper address <br>I can get lost in just living <br>Blowing thoughts of regret <br>You'll never forget the feeling of falling and breaking <br><br>This is me, your glue gun's dream <br>A map of every road, a friend that drops his nose <br>But this can't be -- I'm a cracking machine <br>My will is to hold and my creed is to be the unbreakable me <br>Now it's time to fill up all the cracks in me <br>No stopping, no stopping, no stopping <br>It's what I want, it's what I see <br>That I'm unbreakable, capable, breakable <br>Bye-bye, never any doubt in me...]]></content><category term="Tripping Daisy" label="Tripping Daisy"/><category term="Field Day Jitters" label="Field Day Jitters"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/영락/꽃/</id><title>영락 - 꽃 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%81%EB%9D%BD/%EA%BD%83/" title="영락 - 꽃 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[괜찮을 줄 알았어 <br>우린 영원히 <br>함께라 믿었는데 <br>뭐가 그리 급해서 <br>나를 이렇게 빨리 <br>떠나 간거야 <br>내 품에 잠든 널 볼 때 <br>네가 없다는 건 <br>생각지도 못했어 <br>이젠 모든 날들이 <br>없던 날처럼 <br>혼자 익숙해 지겠지 <br>항상 집에 오면 <br>반겨주던 너 <br>내가 화를 내도 <br>안겨주던 너 <br>고마워 내 삶에 <br>머물러줘서 <br>이제 널 가슴에 묻을게 <br>오늘 이 밤이 지나면 <br>내일이 다시 <br>오늘이 되길 빌겠지 <br>항상 집에 오면 <br>반겨주던 너 <br>내가 화를 내도 <br>안겨주던 너 <br>고마워 내 삶에 <br>머물러줘서 <br>이제 널 가슴에 묻을게 <br>마지막 널 만나는 길 <br>이별을 예감했어 <br>이제 너를 놔 줄 <br>준비를 하잖아 <br>괜찮아 질 거야 <br>슬픔도 무뎌질 거야 <br>널 견딜 수 있을까 <br>마지막 하지 못한 말 <br>미안해 고마워 누구보다 <br>]]></content><category term="영락" label="영락"/><category term="꽃" label="꽃"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/찰리킴/별똥별/</id><title>찰리킴 - 별똥별 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B0%B0%EB%A6%AC%ED%82%B4/%EB%B3%84%EB%98%A5%EB%B3%84/" title="찰리킴 - 별똥별 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[별똥별이 우리 <br>둘이 빌었던 <br>소원이 이뤄지도록 <br>저 멀리 멀리 하얀 <br>꼬리 그리며 날아가 <br>별똥별이 우리 <br>둘이 빌었던 <br>소원이 이뤄지도록 <br>저 멀리 멀리 하얀 <br>꼬리 그리며 날아가 <br>잘 봐 놓치지 말고 <br>밤하늘이 넓으니까 <br>나눠서 볼까 <br>나는 여기부터 저기 <br>너는 저기부터 여기 <br>은박 돗자리 깔고 <br>누워서 밤하늘을 <br>두리번 두리번거리다 <br>어느 새 같은 곳을 <br>보는 순간 <br>별똥별이 우리 <br>둘이 빌었던 <br>소원이 이뤄지도록 <br>저 멀리 멀리 하얀 <br>꼬리 그리며 날아가 <br>별똥별이 우리 <br>둘이 빌었던 <br>소원이 이뤄지도록 <br>저 멀리 멀리 하얀 <br>꼬리 그리며 날아가 <br>힘내잔 말에 <br>힘 빠질 때쯤 <br>그 어떤 말조차 <br>허무해질 때쯤 <br>별똥별이 우리 <br>둘이 빌었던 <br>소원이 이뤄지도록 <br>저 멀리 멀리 하얀 <br>꼬리 그리며 날아가 <br>별똥별이 우리 <br>둘이 빌었던 <br>소원이 이뤄지도록 <br>저 멀리 멀리 하얀 <br>꼬리 그리며 날아가 <br>다 누구나 할 수 있는데 <br>하지 말라 한 적 없는데 <br>마치 자격이 없는 것처럼 <br>포기하길 강요받고 <br>내 몫이 아니라 여겼던 <br>소원 단 하나 <br>별똥별이 우리 <br>둘이 빌었던 <br>소원이 이뤄지도록 <br>저 멀리 멀리 하얀 <br>꼬리 그리며 날아가 <br>별똥별이 우리 <br>둘이 빌었던 <br>소원이 이뤄지도록 <br>저 멀리 멀리 하얀 <br>꼬리 그리며 날아가 <br>별똥별이 우리 <br>둘이 빌었던 <br>소원이 이뤄지도록 <br>저 멀리 멀리 하얀 <br>꼬리 그리며 날아가 <br>]]></content><category term="찰리킴" label="찰리킴"/><category term="별똥별" label="별똥별"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Work/</id><title>Dumbfoundead - Work - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Work/" title="Dumbfoundead - Work - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I was 15 <br>they said Get on dat real shit <br>Stop rappin’ 'bout the moon <br>there ain't no room <br>for that Neil shit <br>They just assume <br>that I'm in my room <br>With posters of galaxies <br>and that's why I'm closer to fantasy <br>Nah brotha <br>It wasn't spaceships I heard <br>Only screams of her <br>Her meanin’ my mother <br>father was slurrin’ his words <br>So when I wrote words like space <br>It's metaphor for safe and stars <br>are better places <br>Get it <br>Both of my parents didn't <br>The language barriers <br>kept them from knowing <br>anything about me <br>All the things that I'd <br>tell them would sound American <br>I sell them so why <br>would they ever doubt me <br>I will continue my journey <br>until my late teens <br>An out of body <br>experience I would take 3 <br>Sniffin’ smokin’ <br>havin’ myself a space dream <br>Feelin’ alone <br>can't connect to <br>all of these earthlings <br>What's a man <br>without his word <br>If we ain't got a bond then <br>what's it all worth <br>I can tell you the truth <br>but damn the truth hurts <br>As long as I'm livin’ <br>Imma give you my word <br>Word <br>If I said I meant it <br>and Imma do it do it <br>If I said I meant it <br>and Imma do it do it <br>If I said I meant it <br>and Imma do it do it <br>What's a man without his word <br>When I turned 20 <br>they told me Get on dat hard shit <br>We don't want to hear about <br>all of dat broken heart shit <br>Money over bitches is <br>all I heard heard <br>falling in love <br>was only for herbs herbs <br>So I spit about <br>stealin’ your girl and <br>how she want me <br>Way I'm beatin’ dat <br>pussy up soundin’ hella thirsty <br>Then it occurred <br>that it ain't her <br>dat I wanted <br>But the validation of all <br>of my G's on the curb <br>All dat shit dat I rapped about <br>My dad he had acted out <br>The secret women dat prevented <br>us from a happy house <br>As long as it was catchy <br>I turned it into a chorus <br>Pretendin’ dat my momma <br>and sister would just ignore it <br>So I yelled <br>bitches bitches bitches <br>Words becomin’ <br>contradictions <br>'dictions 'dictions <br>Now I can't label it a fiction <br>It's sounded too convincin’ <br>It is what it is <br>when you say it with conviction <br>What's a man <br>without his word <br>If we ain't got a bond then <br>what's it all worth <br>I can tell you the truth <br>but damn the truth hurts <br>As long as I'm livin’ <br>Imma give you my word <br>Word <br>If I said I meant it <br>and Imma do it do it <br>If I said I meant it <br>and Imma do it do it <br>If I said I meant it <br>and Imma do it do it <br>What's a man without his word <br>They find real life borin’ <br>Fantasy is corny <br>Afraid of explorin’ <br>need someone to do it for 'em <br>Fake shit do sound <br>real when it's recorded <br>So that fake shit sells <br>to this country every mornin’ <br>And the real shit fails <br>and gets put inside for storage <br>But the real will prevail <br>when the country's in mournin’ <br>Word <br>When you don't mean it <br>you say Word <br>Word <br>All it's become is <br>just a four letter word <br>What's a man <br>without his word <br>If we ain't got a bond then <br>what's it all worth <br>I can tell you the truth <br>but damn the truth hurts <br>As long as I'm livin’ <br>Ima give you my word <br>Word <br>What's a man without his word <br>]]></content><category term="Dumbfoundead" label="Dumbfoundead"/><category term="Work" label="Work"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Drinking_Alone_Feat_Anderson_Paak/</id><title>Dumbfoundead - Drinking Alone (Feat. Anderson .Paak) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Drinking_Alone_Feat_Anderson_Paak/" title="Dumbfoundead - Drinking Alone (Feat. Anderson .Paak) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Drinking all alone <br>Feeling like an outcast <br>Going through my phone <br>Looking for a quick smash <br>Drink me down to the last call <br>And hold me down cuz I can’t walk <br>I hate the feel of being thirsty <br>So make me feel like you want me <br>And ohhh this bottle <br>I should just leave it alone <br>I shouldn't be drinking alone <br>You bringin’ out the worst in me <br>Bringin’ out the thirst in me <br>Burpin' off the Bourbon writin’ <br>verses sounding nursery <br>Slurrin' while I’m cursin’ like <br>Why the fuck are you hurtin’ me <br>Fuck it you ain’t worth it <br>I’m invincible I’m Hercules <br>She ask me why I’m callin’ then <br>Advises me to go to sleep <br>It’s a problem <br>when you’re drunk you're <br>Bumpin’ Jodeci <br>sober in the mornin’ <br>Still horney <br>it’s like I need some help <br>Lookin’ at my twitter <br>did I really play myself <br>Not again <br>I can’t keep the bottled in <br>Pinot Grigio got me <br>emo like No common sense <br>take my phone <br>I need some self-control <br>All this drinkin’ drinkin’ <br>Got me in my zone <br>I know I’m wrong <br>Drink me down to the last call <br>And hold me down cuz I can’t walk <br>I hate the feel of being thirsty <br>So make me feel like you want me <br>And ohhh this bottle <br>I should just leave it alone <br>I shouldn't be drinking alone <br>Yo it’s always after two <br>When I’ll be textin’ you <br>Saying something casual <br>To make not sexual <br>You know what it is <br>You ain't a stupid chick <br>I’m just punchin’ in for <br>After hours functionin’ <br>Like how I’m stylin’ on you <br>Drunk dialin’ on you <br>Malibu and pineapple <br>Gettin’ island on you <br>Feelin’ thirsty and I’m <br>tryna to get hydrated <br>Holla at your boy <br>And you’re tryin’ to get violated <br>Pupils getting dilated <br>I’m a annihilated <br>Sendin’ out hi baby’s <br>With a little smiley face <br>Girl come by my place <br>And take another shot <br>I ain't a player <br>I just crush a lot <br>Say the night is over <br>Ever fall from sober <br>Take a ride in this taxi <br>And maybe I can sleep over <br>Say what you doing <br>What you doin’ <br>What you doin’ girl <br>What you doin’ <br>What you doin’ <br>What you doin’ girl <br>What you doin’ <br>What you doin’ <br>What you doin’ girl <br>What you doin’ <br>What you doin’ girl <br>Drink me down to the last call <br>And hold me down cuz I can’t walk <br>I hate the feel of being thirsty <br>So make me feel like you want me <br>And ohhh this bottle <br>I should just leave it alone <br>I shouldn't be drinking alone <br>Drinking all alone <br>Feeling like an outcast <br>Going through my phone <br>Looking for a quick smash <br>Drinking all alone <br>Feeling like an outcast <br>Going through my phone <br>Looking for a quick smash <br>Drinking all alone <br>Feeling like an outcast <br>Going through my phone <br>Looking for a quick smash <br>Drinking all alone <br>Feeling like an outcast <br>Going through my phone <br>Looking for a quick smash <br>Drinking all alone <br>Feeling like an outcast <br>Going through my phone <br>Looking for a quick smash <br>]]></content><category term="Dumbfoundead" label="Dumbfoundead"/><category term="Drinking Alone (Feat. Anderson .Paak)" label="Drinking Alone (Feat. Anderson .Paak)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Its_Not_You_Feat_David_Choi/</id><title>Dumbfoundead - It`s Not You (Feat. David Choi) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:31:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:31:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Its_Not_You_Feat_David_Choi/" title="Dumbfoundead - It`s Not You (Feat. David Choi) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want what I used I to feel <br>I need a boost or a refill <br>I know it's selfish of me <br>To want to break up and rebuild <br>Yo old love has gotten cold love <br>Up down that rocky road love <br>We lost that rock n roll love <br>Bossonova box of roses <br>Where'd we go wrong <br>never saw it comin’ <br>Sky was the limit <br>never thought we would plummet <br>Now we lie to each other <br>never keep it one hundred <br>I don't want to be around <br>to witness what this is becomin’ <br>comin comin <br>It's been crazy baby lately <br>Life has been so bitter tastin’ <br>Let's be strangers <br>just keep walkin’ <br>I'll make it easy it's not you it's me <br>Don't mean to be this way <br>I know it sounds cliche <br>Don't have much else to say <br>It's not you it's me <br>No need for you to blame <br>I'll take it anyway <br>I'll carry on the shame <br>It's not you it's me <br>Famous last words <br>Now you're looking at me like <br>Save it man <br>Those are the words <br>of a heart breaker <br>Also known as the world's <br>most dangerous man <br>Break ups are the <br>same as aimin’ a stainless <br>Until that thing go blam <br>Thought that it'd be painless <br>But love is a language <br>I don't understand <br>In the beginning <br>I was in it to chase <br>I was something out the wilderness <br>now give me a taste <br>Movin’ in for the kill <br>with no minute to waste <br>Killin’ mistakes slow and steady <br>always wins the race <br>Pile full of photographs <br>phone full of texts <br>Burn all the proof then <br>move on to the next <br>I know it sounds harsh <br>but the quicker you forget <br>Is the quicker <br>you'll find happiness <br>Let’s go <br>It's been crazy baby lately <br>Life has been so bitter tastin’ <br>Let's be strangers <br>just keep walkin’ <br>I'll make it easy it's not you it's me <br>Don't mean to be this way <br>I know it sounds cliche <br>Don't have much else to say <br>It's not you it's me <br>No need for you to blame <br>I'll take it anyway <br>I'll carry on the shame <br>It's not you it's me <br>Don't mean to be this way <br>I know it sounds cliche <br>Don't have much else to say <br>It's not you it's me <br>Day 1 you were fine as shit <br>Banging body and designer fits <br>Day 30 you were mine and shit <br>We were hangin’ out <br>all the time good shit <br>Day 100 fightin’ over minor shit <br>But I still ended up <br>stickin’ 'round this bitch <br>Years gone by and I'm tired of shit <br>Sorry love I gotta call it quits <br>]]></content><category term="Dumbfoundead" label="Dumbfoundead"/><category term="It`s Not You (Feat. David Choi)" label="It`s Not You (Feat. David Choi)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Korean_Jesus/</id><title>Dumbfoundead - Korean Jesus - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:32:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:32:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Korean_Jesus/" title="Dumbfoundead - Korean Jesus - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Back from being black balled <br>Here to slap all them stupid <br>cats doin’ bath salts <br>Korean Jesus droppin’ <br>panties to the asphalt <br>Got them Asian bitches gettin’ <br>freaky to them trap songs <br>Baptized with the water <br>in the glass bong <br>Turned water into soju <br>got your facts wrong <br>If you tryin’ to learn <br>I teach a junior <br>college class on it <br>Pass around a basket <br>put a couple racks on it <br>Took me 20 years to grow <br>this fuckin’ goatee <br>It'll take another 40 years <br>for you to shave it off me <br>I'm on that sensei swag <br>with the wise look <br>Chicks dig it even make <br>the nuns wanna dry hump <br>Never drive drunk <br>but I do it high as hell <br>Cruisin’ in Koreatown <br>might as well <br>I’m Adele bitter at my ex <br>Ima tell <br>The world about her Ft. Lauderdale <br>pictures of her breasts next <br>Chillin’ in the bat cave <br>stackin mad tracks <br>I ain't never had a half day <br>Your shit's wack you should <br>smash on the backspace <br>Fuck all your videos <br>I’d rather watch the ads play <br>Gotten more ass <br>than them ads <br>for them axe sprays <br>Sprained my damn back <br>trynna do the latest dance craze <br>Dopin’ up with Lance <br>pedalin’ dat good man made <br>Take two of these <br>and it’ll leave you <br>in a trance daze <br>K Town Jesus <br>rockin’ open toed Adidas <br>Rollin Zig Zags and reefer <br>with a big bag of Cheez Its <br>It’s beanie season <br>I don’t need a fuckin’ reason <br>No matter the degrees <br>if it’s heated or its freezin’ <br>Back but I never left <br>heaven sent raps <br>from the devil’s breath <br>Leanin’ to the left <br>like a treble clef <br>respect don’t get <br>your panties in a knot <br>Buddha blessed <br>with Muhammad tryin’ <br>to hotbox with Gods <br>You don't know <br>who Korean Jesus is <br>Whatyou stupid <br>or something <br>The man who turned <br>water into soju <br>you don't know who he is <br>You think somebody <br>better than Korean Jesus <br>He is the reason <br>why Asian people are so cheap <br>He took a single loaf <br>of bread and fish <br>and fed a thousand people <br>You try and do that shit <br>Bitch why don't you try <br>and walk on water <br>Fuck Criss Angel <br>Korean Jesus saves you <br>like Korean people <br>save ziplock bags after one use <br>He is forever with me <br>like a kimchi stain <br>on a white t shirt <br>Korean Jesus was <br>the original K Town hipster <br>wearing sandals and a full beard <br>You're welcome <br>]]></content><category term="Dumbfoundead" label="Dumbfoundead"/><category term="Korean Jesus" label="Korean Jesus"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Fck_It_Feat_Anderson_Paak_Nina_Katsuya__Murs/</id><title>Dumbfoundead - Fck It (Feat. Anderson .Paak, Nina Katsuya &amp; Murs) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:32:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:32:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Fck_It_Feat_Anderson_Paak_Nina_Katsuya__Murs/" title="Dumbfoundead - Fck It (Feat. Anderson .Paak, Nina Katsuya &amp; Murs) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fuck it <br>So many names <br>so many faces <br>I could have had the things <br>a different way but fuck it <br>And if I stay <br>bad habits would remain <br>Stuck in the same play <br>so fuck it <br>What am I supposed to do <br>What am I supposed to do <br>What am I supposed to do <br>Yeah <br>It's hard to understand <br>I've been through <br>so many phases <br>and different lands <br>Sometimes I wonder <br>if I'm on the right path <br>Or if I made a blunder <br>and missed my chance <br>Momma said I gotta pray and fast <br>But my old head told me <br>it was simple mathematics <br>And god ain't gonna give me <br>more than what I can stand <br>So as long as I'm standin’ <br>I got a chance to put my brand <br>on this planet <br>Can't go out like my pops did <br>Drinking liquor <br>‘til his liver got spots in it <br>It's like I only knew him <br>for a hot minute <br>But every time we talk <br>it was long in it <br>The ghost from his past <br>still haunts him <br>I could tell by the responses <br>that I got from him <br>And on his last days <br>he left a message <br>singin’ a song <br>But when I finally tried to call <br>he was gone <br>So many names <br>so many faces <br>I could have had the things <br>a different way but fuck it <br>And if I stay <br>bad habits would remain <br>Stuck in the same play so fuck it <br>What am I suppose to do <br>What am I suppose to do <br>What am I suppose to do <br>Fuck it man <br>I've seen the places <br>that they've never seen <br>The view is different <br>when you're sittin’ <br>on a mezzanine <br>You see the bigger picture <br>wave ya on a couple blocks <br>Look through the negatives <br>then you figure out <br>what to crop <br>Can't escape Babylon <br>I gotta tatted arm <br>But now I'm on that digital <br>while you moving that analog <br>You sitting you praying <br>while the enemy's <br>prayin’ on you <br>You must be tripping <br>thinking god has a magic wand <br>Brah Korean Jesus ain't <br>got time for your shit <br>He on the other line <br>with a million other kids <br>You seeing the good life <br>through Instagram flicks <br>The filters we've applied <br>as blood tears and sweat <br>I ain't your competition <br>nor am I your enemy <br>You shouldn't be feeling <br>jealousy looking at my twitter <br>feed <br>While I'm on this killing spree <br>it's killing me you ain't <br>We were homies <br>till you chose to play it safe <br>So many names <br>so many faces <br>I could have had the things <br>a different way but fuck it <br>And if I stay <br>bad habits would remain <br>Stuck in the same play <br>so fuck it <br>What am I supposed to do <br>What am I supposed to do <br>What am I supposed to do <br>The only thing I never could <br>do was lose for you <br>The way it's turning out <br>I wish I could choose for you <br>This life truly is sink or swim <br>Hey you can fuck around <br>and drown trying to think for them <br>You don't begin a journey <br>ending in the same place <br>You make some distant <br>to the finish <br>it's the human race <br>You running on the clock <br>they're gunning for your spot <br>So much pain in your past <br>that you don't wanna stop <br>I was dead broke depressed <br>and on prescription drugs <br>Headed towards a tier <br>in the county <br>with the Crips and Bloods <br>Slanging texts <br>in front of different clubs <br>Until my name started <br>getting buzzed <br>And when you hear the buzz <br>it's time to take flight <br>I hit the road <br>and all the haters <br>saw was brake lights <br>So when you tell me <br>that I've changed <br>it's a compliment <br>How could I not <br>when I done rocked <br>on every continent <br>So many names <br>so many faces <br>I could have had the things <br>a different way but fuck it <br>And if I stay <br>bad habits would remain <br>Stuck in the same play <br>so fuck it <br>What am I supposed to do <br>What am I supposed to do <br>What am I supposed to do <br>]]></content><category term="Dumbfoundead" label="Dumbfoundead"/><category term="Fck It (Feat. Anderson .Paak, Nina Katsuya &amp; Murs)" label="Fck It (Feat. Anderson .Paak, Nina Katsuya &amp; Murs)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Wine_Feat_Wax__Anderson_Paak/</id><title>Dumbfoundead - Wine (Feat. Wax &amp; Anderson .Paak) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:32:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:32:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Wine_Feat_Wax__Anderson_Paak/" title="Dumbfoundead - Wine (Feat. Wax &amp; Anderson .Paak) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Met a little PYT <br>But just to play it safe <br>I had to see ID <br>She 19 all up on my D I C <br>Old enough to hit it <br>too young to be my queen <br>A ghetto princess <br>I met her on 6th and Alvarado <br>She fuckin’ up in junior college <br>drinking 40 bottles <br>Already got a bunch of dumbass <br>tats that she'll regret <br>Butterflies Chinese letters <br>and the name of her ex <br>Silver tongue ring <br>she such a cute thing <br>Couldn't name a single member <br>of the Wu Tang <br>Thinkin’ she's so mature <br>she got her own car <br>She's so independent <br>give her a gold star <br>Callin’ me condescending <br>I'm the one who taught <br>her that word <br>Dumb as a bird <br>lucky that she got <br>a bottom on her <br>It must have been <br>straight out of high school <br>when she turned bad <br>Doin’ things that make me wonder <br>Where'd she learn dat <br>Two worlds collide <br>Met her on Franklin and Vine <br>You gon' get me caught up <br>Girl you're too young <br>to drink the wine <br>It's not bad but it's not right <br>She wanna run me all night <br>Damn it I'm caught up <br>Girl you're too young <br>to drink the wine <br>She got the body of a woman <br>brain of a girl <br>Not yet schooled <br>in the ways of the world <br>Lookin’ fine <br>and lyin’ at the front door <br>It's only the second time <br>she's been to a club before <br>She got her ID from her older <br>and uglier sister <br>Hands it to the bouncer hopin’ <br>that he won't study the picture <br>She's lucky he missed her <br>Then she rolls inside <br>with her chin up <br>Ready to get lit up <br>Pretendin’ that she's not a teen <br>But a shot of Beam <br>turns her straight <br>from Prom queen <br>to drama queen <br>In the corner <br>cryin’ about her ex dude <br>I know the game <br>I'm already on my next move <br>I'll hit it once <br>but there ain't gon' be <br>no dinner datin’ <br>When 9/11 happened <br>she was finger paintin’ <br>I ain't hatin’ <br>I'm just not relatin’ <br>Man I hope <br>she wasn't ovulatin’ <br>Damn <br>Two worlds collide <br>Met her on Franklin and Vine <br>You gon' get me caught up <br>Girl you're too young <br>to drink the wine <br>It's not bad but it's not right <br>She wanna run me all night <br>Damn it I'm caught up <br>Girl you're too young <br>to drink the wine <br>Took the shorty to a function <br>my homies were lovin’ her <br>But all the other girls <br>were buggin’ like <br>Look at her <br>Ew look at that skirt <br>what a little slut <br>I could tell that they <br>just jealous <br>cause she got a bigger butt <br>She way cooler <br>and always down <br>to party 'til the AM <br>While all the girls my age <br>they now want to stay in <br>Complainin’ how good men <br>are hard to find <br>But my girl the only thing <br>on mind is findin’ <br>A party and bullshit <br>And party and bullshit <br>And party and bullshit <br>I love the way <br>that you ain't givin’ a fuck <br>Two worlds collide <br>Met her on Franklin and Vine <br>You gon' get me caught up <br>Girl you're too young <br>to drink the wine <br>It's not bad but it's not right <br>She wanna run me all night <br>Damn it I'm caught up <br>Girl you're too young <br>to drink the wine <br>]]></content><category term="Dumbfoundead" label="Dumbfoundead"/><category term="Wine (Feat. Wax &amp; Anderson .Paak)" label="Wine (Feat. Wax &amp; Anderson .Paak)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Growing_Young/</id><title>Dumbfoundead - Growing Young - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:32:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:32:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Growing_Young/" title="Dumbfoundead - Growing Young - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yo be a man John be a man <br>Used to get them Marlboros for dad <br>It made me feel grown <br>Didn’t know the problems he had <br>But he was real gone <br>When he had the bottle in hand <br>He was just dead wrong <br>Promised that I wouldnever <br>grow up and be him <br>But I never grew up at all <br>And now I’m womanizin’ <br>and cheatin’ <br>drinkin’ heavily in the pm <br>Havin myself a monsters ball <br>just like my pa <br>My girl lookin’ the same <br>way my mom did <br>Smeared make up tears <br>under her eyelids <br>Generations of havin’ <br>a down ass chick <br>But we always end up <br>fuckin’ up that shit <br>Pointin’ fingers at all <br>of my male figures <br>The only thing gettin’ bigger <br>is makin’ ‘bout six figures <br>And everybody just shut up <br>when I put it on my tab <br>Ain't it sad when a Visa’s <br>the only credit you have huh <br>But that’s just John <br>and that’s how he is <br>That’s the only way people <br>come into my defense <br>But that’s just wrong <br>but that’s how it is <br>And it be helpin’ me get away <br>with alotta of shit <br>Alotta shit alotta shit <br>I wish somebody really <br>gave me a whole of shit <br>But they on the dick <br>yeah they on my dick <br>now my ego is gettin’ <br>bigger than Moby Dick <br>They see the videos <br>they see the hero <br>They take a mess <br>and paint a mural <br>Edit out the a hole <br>put in the b roll <br>Render the clips <br>and you got pure gold <br>Shoutout to B tho <br>that’s mi amigo <br>kept me in check <br>when I was actin’ like a divo <br>When I was Steve O <br>he made me Steve Jobs <br>I’m a CEO <br>now look at me ma <br>Now look at me ma <br>I’m on my grown shit <br>when I mean grown <br>I mean takin’ care <br>of my own shit <br>Now look at me pa <br>this is some grown shit <br>now what you taught <br>me forget it <br>I flipped the whole script <br>now look at me girl <br>I’m on grown shit <br>what I’m sayin’ <br>I mean it my word is golden <br>everything I’m sayin’ <br>you’re probably thinkin’ <br>no shit <br>I shoulda known this already <br>but I’m ready now <br>]]></content><category term="Dumbfoundead" label="Dumbfoundead"/><category term="Growing Young" label="Growing Young"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/10_Rounds_Feat_Nina_Katusya/</id><title>Dumbfoundead - 10 Rounds (Feat. Nina Katusya) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:32:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:32:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/10_Rounds_Feat_Nina_Katusya/" title="Dumbfoundead - 10 Rounds (Feat. Nina Katusya) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Somebody <br>tell 'em we in town <br>plus we got plenty of <br>trees to go around <br>Came up from the <br>hood the hood <br>I'm so proud <br>When I say I'm good <br>I'm good for ten rounds <br>Ten <br>Two shots and a mixer <br>Two-o'clock in the after-hours <br>I was too hood for them hipsters <br>Two drops <br>when I'm poppin' molly's <br>I raise the volume <br>close my eyelids <br>off them hybrids autopilot <br>How did I flip <br>this lifestyle <br>Green lights take flight <br>like a night owl <br>Savage gotta have it <br>Catch me in the cab <br>gettin' blown like the cannon <br>Look no hands <br>Goin' H.A.M. on a bad chick <br>Said she got a man <br>so this shit never happened <br>It's the ruler <br>tatted like the Yakuza <br>Flyer then parashutas <br>and wavy as barracudas <br>Turn this party into a nudest <br>colony with a pool of <br>Bitches giving me <br>medulla oblongata <br>I'm a school her <br>Somebody <br>tell em we in town <br>plus we got plenty of <br>trees to go around <br>Came up from the <br>hood the hood <br>I'm so proud <br>When I say I'm good <br>I'm good for ten rounds <br>Ten rounds <br>at least ten rounds <br>Then we give a show <br>at least ten thou' <br>Came up from the <br>hood the hood <br>I'm so proud <br>When I say I'm good <br>I'm good for ten rounds <br>Neighborhood king <br>oh you know me right <br>Late nights spent <br>at the corners <br>until the mornin' light <br>You don't blow tree <br>but ya rollin' right <br>You just want to <br>take a photo right <br>OK fresh in my white <br>Nike prototypes <br>So what's the guest list <br>We kickin' down <br>the door tonight <br>Man you fuckin' <br>with the best-est <br>I'd be wrong if I said <br>I wasn't takin' someone <br>home tonight <br>Drinkin' to the bottom of the <br>bottle and you bet <br>your bottom dollar <br>that she come into the condo <br>She a Spanish mama <br>goin' through some drama <br>with her man <br>now she callin' me her sancho <br>Somebody <br>tell em we in town <br>plus we got plenty of <br>trees to go around <br>Came up from the <br>hood the hood <br>I'm so proud <br>When I say I'm good <br>I'm good for ten rounds <br>Ten rounds <br>at least ten rounds <br>Then we give a show <br>at least ten thou' <br>Came up from the <br>hood the hood <br>I'm so proud <br>When I say I'm good <br>I'm good for ten rounds <br>Fresh in my white <br>Nike prototypes <br>So what's the guest list <br>We kickin' down <br>the door tonight <br>Man you fuckin' <br>with the best-est <br>I'd be wrong if I said <br>I wasn't takin' somethin' <br>home tonight <br>Fresh in my white <br>Nike prototypes <br>So what's the guest list <br>We kickin' down <br>the door tonight <br>Man you fuckin' <br>with the best-est <br>I'd be wrong if I said <br>I wasn't takin' somethin' <br>home tonight <br>Somebody <br>tell 'em we in town <br>plus we got plenty of <br>trees to go around <br>Came up from the <br>hood the hood <br>I'm so proud <br>When I say I'm good <br>I'm good for ten rounds <br>Ten rounds <br>at least ten rounds <br>Then we give a show <br>at least ten thou' <br>Came up from the <br>hood the hood <br>I'm so proud <br>When I say I'm good <br>I'm good for ten rounds <br>Somebody <br>tell 'em we in town <br>plus we got plenty of <br>trees to go around <br>]]></content><category term="Dumbfoundead" label="Dumbfoundead"/><category term="10 Rounds (Feat. Nina Katusya)" label="10 Rounds (Feat. Nina Katusya)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/New_Chick/</id><title>Dumbfoundead - New Chick - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:32:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:32:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/New_Chick/" title="Dumbfoundead - New Chick - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Girl I need to drop you <br>Because on the real <br>you're too high school <br>Yellin' on my voicemail <br>Why you gotta be so hostile <br>I'm lookin' for a love life <br>You addicted to them <br>club lights <br>Way you're always <br>in my face though <br>Man it's almost like you <br>love fights <br>By the way <br>I hate your guy friends <br>Did you have to invite them <br>Actually your girls too <br>Chickenheads <br>never like them <br>Why the hell you <br>always broke boo <br>But always got a pair <br>of dope shoes <br>Oh you need to borrow <br>money right <br>Girl you're turnin' <br>into old news <br>I need a new chick <br>I need a new chick <br>I need a new chick <br>I need a new chick <br>Why we never have sex yo <br>Can I get some head though <br>You know a man has needs <br>Bullshittin' about strep throat <br>Got me feelin' mad stressed <br>Always bringin' up <br>the past tense <br>Now I understand <br>your last ex <br>And why he bounced <br>like a bad check <br>Feelin' frustrated <br>lookin' for an upgrade <br>Current situation got me <br>boilin' in my blood veins <br>Out to find a new chick <br>Down to earth <br>cool chick <br>Have a future with her <br>start a tribe like Q-Tip <br>I could be your Phife <br>Dawg love <br>My last chick ain't even know <br>who Phife Dawg was <br>I was like Oh what <br>How we gon' get along <br>If you don't know any songs <br>on Midnight Marauders <br>But your iPod's lookin' <br>so straight <br>Goin' down your playlist <br>think I found my soul mate <br>It's been only four dates <br>and you're so much cooler <br>Why the hell did I wait <br>should've broken up sooner <br>Damn <br>I never knew a love like this <br>My last girl never showed <br>me love like this <br>She ain't never go to <br>my shows or bump my shit <br>But you <br>you love my shit <br>I need a new chick <br>I need a new chick <br>I need a new chick <br>I need a new chick <br>On and on this shit goes <br>The homies tell me go on <br>and leave her alone <br>I'll be god damned <br>she got the best dome <br>best dome <br>best dome <br>Back and forth in my ear <br>Always on the verge of <br>burstin' in tears <br>Even got the nerve to <br>flirt with my peers <br>But you got the best dome <br>best dome <br>I need a new chick <br>Woo Ah <br>I need a new chick <br>I need a <br>You got the best dome <br>]]></content><category term="Dumbfoundead" label="Dumbfoundead"/><category term="New Chick" label="New Chick"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/SCRAM/</id><title>Dumbfoundead - S.C.R.A.M - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:32:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:32:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/SCRAM/" title="Dumbfoundead - S.C.R.A.M - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Scrizzy scrizzy S.C.R.A.M <br>Threw on a white T <br>and 501 jeans <br>Jammed everything <br>I can in my pockets <br>car keys <br>With a box of backwoods <br>weed card and my visa <br>I would never leave <br>the crib without these <br>bruh <br>Made my way out <br>my building <br>full of crackheads <br>Picked an eighth up <br>from the rasta <br>with the fat dreads <br>Couple daps now <br>I'm 'bout to go <br>and stack bread <br>Cause a closed mouth <br>don't get fed <br>that's what dad said <br>With that said <br>met up with the homie Breezy <br>Grabbed breakfast <br>got my eggs over-easy <br>Started plottin' 'bout the <br>next few months <br>Got a tour and an album <br>so we gotta move <br>son <br>They out to chit-chat <br>til the sky pitch black <br>But I'm busy S.C.R.A.M <br>Holla back <br>Scrizzy S.C.R.A.M <br>Goin' heavy on the man <br>I'm goin' heavy on the man <br>Scrizzy scrizzy scram scrizzy <br>Scrizzy scrizzy scram <br>Scrizzy scram <br>Crooked letter C ram <br>I'm goin' heavy on the man <br>Scrizzy scrizzy scram scrizzy <br>Scrizzy scrizzy scram <br>Headed to my whip <br>give the valet man a tip <br>When I see a group of kids <br>and they askin' for a flick <br>So I pose they get close <br>but they takin' hella <br>minutes though <br>Let me guess <br>camera setting was on video <br>Traffic on the 10 <br>get a call from my friend <br>While I'm talkin' on the phone <br>get pulled over by a pig <br>Like a dick he wrote a ticket <br>but I ain't losin' time at all <br>S.C.R.A.M <br>middle finger <br>while I'm drivin' off <br>To the studio <br>put him in a rap <br>Put his first middle <br>last name <br>number on his badge <br>That's a wrap mix it down <br>then release the fuckin' track <br>Scrizzy S.C.R.A.M <br>don't tell me to relax <br>They out to chit-chat <br>til the sky pitch black <br>But I'm busy S.C.R.A.M <br>Holla back <br>Scrizzy S.C.R.A.M <br>Goin' heavy on the man <br>I'm goin' heavy on the man <br>Scrizzy scrizzy scram scrizzy <br>Scrizzy scrizzy scram <br>Scrizzy scram <br>Crooked letter C ram <br>I'm goin' heavy on the man <br>Scrizzy scrizzy scram scrizzy <br>Scrizzy scrizzy scram <br>Okay we vibin' off the demo <br>I'm mobbin' with my kin folk <br>I made a left on Pico <br>To swoop this little nympho <br>We headed to the function <br>I love this bitch's steelo <br>I took her to the key club <br>We cut a gang of people <br>Easy access <br>homie I'm that good <br>Trees and capsules <br>liquor with handles <br>She's an actress <br>little miss Hollywood <br>Scenes on my mattress <br>iPhone classics <br>Damn isn't S.C.R.A.M <br>life fantastic <br>I said damn <br>don't we got a flight to catch <br>In the mornin' <br>drop the chick off <br>then I dips off <br>I'd rather listen to my hit song <br>They out to chit-chat <br>til the sky pitch black <br>But I'm busy S.C.R.A.M <br>Holla back <br>Scrizzy S.C.R.A.M <br>Goin' heavy on the man <br>I'm goin' heavy on the man <br>Scrizzy scrizzy scram scrizzy <br>Scrizzy scrizzy scram <br>Scrizzy scram <br>Crooked letter C ram <br>I'm goin' heavy on the man <br>Scrizzy scrizzy scram scrizzy <br>Scrizzy scrizzy scram <br>]]></content><category term="Dumbfoundead" label="Dumbfoundead"/><category term="S.C.R.A.M" label="S.C.R.A.M"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Stairs_Intro/</id><title>Dumbfoundead - Stairs Intro - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:32:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:32:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Stairs_Intro/" title="Dumbfoundead - Stairs Intro - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Went from the corner store <br>to family cornerstone <br>My father was a rolling stone <br>Mother mi corazon <br>Chino off of Normandy <br>no need for Rosetta Stone <br>Chicanos took me in and <br>treated me as if I was their own <br>Young legend in the <br>shadows of K-Town <br>Under-appreciated <br>but my greatness <br>was space bound <br>I held it down for <br>my people at a time <br>When my people looked at me <br>like I was out my damn mind <br>I forgive 'em <br>all the lows provided me <br>higher livin' <br>Now the haters on the low <br>they be asking me <br>how I'm livin' <br>Things sure have changed <br>since '04 <br>Now I'm travelin' to places <br>that I'd seen in brochures <br>Yellow kid with the beanie <br>in the summer <br>But never hot-headed <br>kept it cool I'm a lover <br>Smooth Asian brother <br>mustache lookin' butter <br>Can't walk a block <br>without a fan sayin' <br>What up <br>What up player <br>I'm livin' like a mayor <br>Trying to hijack the airwaves <br>call me Con Air <br>Never took a shortcut man <br>I took the long stairs <br>Now blonde haired chicks <br>on my dick like John Mayer <br>Used to bum rides off <br>the homies' Hyundai <br>Hit the lab with a big dream <br>and a junk drive <br>Now I got a whip <br>looking' like I stunt drive <br>Smoking blunts high <br>middle fingers to the one time <br>Yeah you see me <br>on the web like Charlotte <br>Racking up the views <br>not knowin' what I started <br>Numbers look retarded <br>like mainstream artists <br>Your boy did it all on his own <br>while uncharted <br>People still ask your brother <br>Are we there yet <br>We ain't even close <br>cause my momma <br>in a hairnet <br>If you're feelin' me then <br>put one in the air vent <br>Longer that I walk up <br>the higher that these stairs get <br>]]></content><category term="Dumbfoundead" label="Dumbfoundead"/><category term="Stairs Intro" label="Stairs Intro"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/미세스_플라워_Mrs_Flower/엄마의_겨울_위에서_Inst/</id><title>미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower) - 엄마의 겨울 위에서 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:32:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:32:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AF%B8%EC%84%B8%EC%8A%A4_%ED%94%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9B%8C_Mrs_Flower/%EC%97%84%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%98_%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8_%EC%9C%84%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C_Inst/" title="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower) - 엄마의 겨울 위에서 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아아 아아 차가운 그 바람 <br>아아 아아 깊은 곳 불어와 <br>오늘 만난 하루의 <br>모든 시간 속에서 <br>소중한 일 행복한 일 <br>가득 넘치기를 <br>따뜻한 마음으로 <br>아름다운 생각으로 <br>너의 눈빛 너의 모든 말 <br>가득 차기를 <br>사랑해 또 사랑해 또또또 사랑해 <br>사랑해 더 사랑해 더더더 사랑해 <br>사랑해 또 사랑해 또또또 사랑해 <br>사랑해 더 사랑해 더더더 사랑해 <br>사랑해 또 사랑해 또또또 사랑해 <br>사랑해 더 사랑해 더더더 사랑해 <br>사랑해 또 사랑해 또또또 사랑해 <br>사랑해 더 사랑해 더더더 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower)" label="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower)"/><category term="엄마의 겨울 위에서 (Inst.)" label="엄마의 겨울 위에서 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/미세스_플라워_Mrs_Flower/나는_세상의_주인공_Inst/</id><title>미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower) - 나는 세상의 주인공 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:32:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:32:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AF%B8%EC%84%B8%EC%8A%A4_%ED%94%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9B%8C_Mrs_Flower/%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81%EC%9D%98_%EC%A3%BC%EC%9D%B8%EA%B3%B5_Inst/" title="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower) - 나는 세상의 주인공 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[선생님 난 어떤 아인가요 <br>선생님 난 무얼 잘하나요 <br>주인공이 난 되고 싶어요 <br>하지만 세상은 나를 알지 못해요 <br>아이야 넌 이미 주인공이야 <br>아이야 넌 뭐든지 할 수 있어 <br>꿈이 있고 희망도 있어 <br>손을 펴 세상을 향해 뻗어 나가렴 <br>난 친구처럼 <br>피아노를 잘 치지도 <br>친구처럼 공부를 <br>잘 하지도 않는 걸요 <br>넌 친구보다 <br>특별한 게 분명 있단다 <br>친구처럼 날개를 <br>활짝 펴고 나아가렴 <br>아이야 넌 이미 주인공이야 <br>정말인가요 <br>아이야 넌 세상의 꽃이란다 <br>믿기지가 않아요 <br>남들에게 꽃이 아닌 <br>네 삶의 꽃이 되렴 <br>네 삶의 주연이 되렴 <br>넌 이미 주인공이야 <br>난 친구처럼 <br>피아노를 잘 치지도 <br>친구처럼 공부를 <br>잘 하지도 않는 걸요 <br>넌 친구보다 <br>특별한 게 분명 있단다 <br>친구처럼 날개를 <br>활짝 펴고 나아가렴 <br>아이야 넌 이미 주인공이야 <br>정말인가요 <br>아이야 넌 세상의 꽃이란다 <br>믿기지가 않아요 <br>남들에게 꽃이 아닌 <br>네 삶의 꽃이 되렴 <br>네 삶의 주연이 되렴 <br>진정한 너를 찾아봐 <br>네가 무얼 원하는지 <br>세상을 향해 손을 펴 <br>너는 세상의 주인공 <br>넌 이미 주인공이야 <br>정말인가요 <br>아이야 넌 세상의 꽃이란다 <br>믿기지가 않아요 <br>남들에게 꽃이 아닌 <br>네 삶의 꽃이 되렴 <br>네 삶의 주연이 되렴 <br>넌 이미 주인공이야 <br>나는 세상의 주인공 <br>]]></content><category term="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower)" label="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower)"/><category term="나는 세상의 주인공 (Inst.)" label="나는 세상의 주인공 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/미세스_플라워_Mrs_Flower/별이_빛나는_밤_Inst/</id><title>미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower) - 별이 빛나는 밤 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:32:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:32:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AF%B8%EC%84%B8%EC%8A%A4_%ED%94%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9B%8C_Mrs_Flower/%EB%B3%84%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B9%9B%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%B0%A4_Inst/" title="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower) - 별이 빛나는 밤 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[별이 빛나는 밤 별이 빛나는 밤에 <br>우리는 어떤 꿈을 이야기할까 <br>별이 빛나는 밤 별이 빛나는 밤에 <br>이렇게 너와 단둘이 얘기해 <br>매일매일이 꿈처럼 펼쳐져 <br>오늘도 잘했어 내일은 어떨까 <br>너와 하고픈 게 너무도 많은 오늘 <br>못다한 얘길 나눌래 <br>어두운 구름이 우리를 가려도 <br>놀라지마 지나갈 거야 <br>저기 까만 밤에도 <br>별이 있어 우릴 비춰 <br>네 눈에 빛이 가득해 <br>별이 빛나는 밤 별이 빛나는 밤에 <br>우리는 어떤 꿈을 이야기할까 <br>별이 빛나는 밤 별이 빛나는 밤에 <br>이렇게 너와 단둘이 얘기해 <br>재잘재잘 재잘재잘 재잘재잘 <br>재잘재잘 재잘재잘 재잘재잘 <br>너와 함께 빠리라빠루 <br>재잘재잘 재잘재잘 재잘재잘 <br>재잘재잘 재잘재잘 재잘재잘 <br>너와 단둘이 얘기해 <br>별이 빛나는 밤 별이 빛나는 밤에 <br>우리는 어떤 꿈을 이야기할까 <br>별이 빛나는 밤 별이 빛나는 밤에 <br>이렇게 너와 단둘이 얘기해 <br>오늘도 너와 함께 얘기해 <br>]]></content><category term="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower)" label="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower)"/><category term="별이 빛나는 밤 (Inst.)" label="별이 빛나는 밤 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/미세스_플라워_Mrs_Flower/엄마의_겨울_위에서/</id><title>미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower) - 엄마의 겨울 위에서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:32:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:32:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AF%B8%EC%84%B8%EC%8A%A4_%ED%94%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9B%8C_Mrs_Flower/%EC%97%84%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%98_%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8_%EC%9C%84%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C/" title="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower) - 엄마의 겨울 위에서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아아 아아 차가운 그 바람 <br>아아 아아 깊은 곳 불어와 <br>오늘 만난 하루의 <br>모든 시간 속에서 <br>소중한 일 행복한 일 <br>가득 넘치기를 <br>따뜻한 마음으로 <br>아름다운 생각으로 <br>너의 눈빛 너의 모든 말 <br>가득 차기를 <br>사랑해 또 사랑해 또또또 사랑해 <br>사랑해 더 사랑해 더더더 사랑해 <br>사랑해 또 사랑해 또또또 사랑해 <br>사랑해 더 사랑해 더더더 사랑해 <br>사랑해 또 사랑해 또또또 사랑해 <br>사랑해 더 사랑해 더더더 사랑해 <br>사랑해 또 사랑해 또또또 사랑해 <br>사랑해 더 사랑해 더더더 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower)" label="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower)"/><category term="엄마의 겨울 위에서" label="엄마의 겨울 위에서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/미세스_플라워_Mrs_Flower/나는_세상의_주인공/</id><title>미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower) - 나는 세상의 주인공 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:32:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:32:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AF%B8%EC%84%B8%EC%8A%A4_%ED%94%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9B%8C_Mrs_Flower/%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81%EC%9D%98_%EC%A3%BC%EC%9D%B8%EA%B3%B5/" title="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower) - 나는 세상의 주인공 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[선생님 난 어떤 아인가요 <br>선생님 난 무얼 잘하나요 <br>주인공이 난 되고 싶어요 <br>하지만 세상은 나를 알지 못해요 <br>아이야 넌 이미 주인공이야 <br>아이야 넌 뭐든지 할 수 있어 <br>꿈이 있고 희망도 있어 <br>손을 펴 세상을 향해 뻗어 나가렴 <br>난 친구처럼 <br>피아노를 잘 치지도 <br>친구처럼 공부를 <br>잘 하지도 않는 걸요 <br>넌 친구보다 <br>특별한 게 분명 있단다 <br>친구처럼 날개를 <br>활짝 펴고 나아가렴 <br>아이야 넌 이미 주인공이야 <br>정말인가요 <br>아이야 넌 세상의 꽃이란다 <br>믿기지가 않아요 <br>남들에게 꽃이 아닌 <br>네 삶의 꽃이 되렴 <br>네 삶의 주연이 되렴 <br>넌 이미 주인공이야 <br>난 친구처럼 <br>피아노를 잘 치지도 <br>친구처럼 공부를 <br>잘 하지도 않는 걸요 <br>넌 친구보다 <br>특별한 게 분명 있단다 <br>친구처럼 날개를 <br>활짝 펴고 나아가렴 <br>아이야 넌 이미 주인공이야 <br>정말인가요 <br>아이야 넌 세상의 꽃이란다 <br>믿기지가 않아요 <br>남들에게 꽃이 아닌 <br>네 삶의 꽃이 되렴 <br>네 삶의 주연이 되렴 <br>진정한 너를 찾아봐 <br>네가 무얼 원하는지 <br>세상을 향해 손을 펴 <br>너는 세상의 주인공 <br>넌 이미 주인공이야 <br>정말인가요 <br>아이야 넌 세상의 꽃이란다 <br>믿기지가 않아요 <br>남들에게 꽃이 아닌 <br>네 삶의 꽃이 되렴 <br>네 삶의 주연이 되렴 <br>넌 이미 주인공이야 <br>나는 세상의 주인공 <br>]]></content><category term="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower)" label="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower)"/><category term="나는 세상의 주인공" label="나는 세상의 주인공"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/미세스_플라워_Mrs_Flower/별이_빛나는_밤/</id><title>미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower) - 별이 빛나는 밤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:32:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:32:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AF%B8%EC%84%B8%EC%8A%A4_%ED%94%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9B%8C_Mrs_Flower/%EB%B3%84%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B9%9B%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%B0%A4/" title="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower) - 별이 빛나는 밤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[별이 빛나는 밤 별이 빛나는 밤에 <br>우리는 어떤 꿈을 이야기할까 <br>별이 빛나는 밤 별이 빛나는 밤에 <br>이렇게 너와 단둘이 얘기해 <br>매일매일이 꿈처럼 펼쳐져 <br>오늘도 잘했어 내일은 어떨까 <br>너와 하고픈 게 너무도 많은 오늘 <br>못다한 얘길 나눌래 <br>어두운 구름이 우리를 가려도 <br>놀라지마 지나갈 거야 <br>저기 까만 밤에도 <br>별이 있어 우릴 비춰 <br>네 눈에 빛이 가득해 <br>별이 빛나는 밤 별이 빛나는 밤에 <br>우리는 어떤 꿈을 이야기할까 <br>별이 빛나는 밤 별이 빛나는 밤에 <br>이렇게 너와 단둘이 얘기해 <br>재잘재잘 재잘재잘 재잘재잘 <br>재잘재잘 재잘재잘 재잘재잘 <br>너와 함께 빠리라빠루 <br>재잘재잘 재잘재잘 재잘재잘 <br>재잘재잘 재잘재잘 재잘재잘 <br>너와 단둘이 얘기해 <br>별이 빛나는 밤 별이 빛나는 밤에 <br>우리는 어떤 꿈을 이야기할까 <br>별이 빛나는 밤 별이 빛나는 밤에 <br>이렇게 너와 단둘이 얘기해 <br>오늘도 너와 함께 얘기해 <br>]]></content><category term="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower)" label="미세스 플라워 (Mrs. Flower)"/><category term="별이 빛나는 밤" label="별이 빛나는 밤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루하_Luha/언니야_오빠야/</id><title>루하 (Luha) - 언니야 오빠야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:32:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:32:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%ED%95%98_Luha/%EC%96%B8%EB%8B%88%EC%95%BC_%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%A0%EC%95%BC/" title="루하 (Luha) - 언니야 오빠야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언니야 <br>당신은 최고랍니다 <br>힘든 세상살이 <br>가슴에 안고 음 <br>언제나 따스한 <br>햇살같은 사람 <br>세상에서 제일 <br>예쁜 여자랍니다 <br>지나간 시간들 <br>후회하지 말아요 <br>우리네 인생사 <br>바람 같잖아요 <br>힘들었던 날들일랑 <br>저 강물에 버리고 <br>우리 함께 손을 잡고 <br>노래를 불러봐요 <br>나에겐 누구보다 <br>멋지고 아름다운 <br>우리 우리 언니랍니다 <br>오빠야 <br>당신은 최고랍니다 <br>거센 바람에도 <br>꺾이지 않죠 음 <br>언제나 듬직한 <br>바위같은 사람 <br>세상에서 제일 <br>멋진 남자랍니다 <br>지나간 시간들 <br>후회하지 말아요 <br>우리네 인생사 <br>바람 같잖아요 <br>힘들었던 날들일랑 <br>저 강물에 버리고 <br>우리 함께 손을 잡고 <br>노래를 불러봐요 <br>나에겐 누구보다 <br>멋지고 아름다운 <br>우리 우리 오빠랍니다 <br>우리 언니 오빠랍니다 <br>]]></content><category term="루하 (Luha)" label="루하 (Luha)"/><category term="언니야 오빠야" label="언니야 오빠야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/써드_third/Big_Wave/</id><title>써드 (third) - Big Wave - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:33:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:33:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8D%A8%EB%93%9C_third/Big_Wave/" title="써드 (third) - Big Wave - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이젠 좀 잠잠하다 싶어 <br>이젠 이젠 <br>하루 종일 헤집어 놓고 <br>away go away <br>매일 듣던 노랜 오늘따라 <br>so fed up so fed up <br>매일 먹던 BIGWAVE 는 오늘따라 <br>so bitter so bitterness <br>소리 없이 찾아온 <br>일렁임이 나를 삼켜 <br>무턱대고 찾아온 <br>일렁임이 나를 삼켜 <br>그럼 나는 눈을 감고 <br>진정되기를 기다려 <br>그런 나를 모르는 넌 <br>what should i do <br>Big wave surge up in ma mind and <br>in ma head rushing down d down <br>Big wave surge up in ma mind and <br>in ma head <br>Big wave surge up in ma mind and <br>in ma head rushing down d down <br>Big wave surge up in ma mind and <br>in ma head <br>아무 일도 없단 듯이 <br>난 그저 난 그저 <br>태연한 척 지나쳐 봐도 <br>no way no no no way <br>내 시선은 멋대로 <br>into your face <br>into your laugh <br>네 시선은 여전히 <br>look over me over me <br>이유 없이 찾아온 <br>일렁임이 나를 삼켜 <br>거대한 몸짓에 <br>한없이 난 작아만 져 <br>그럼 나는 눈을 감고 <br>열을 세고 또 기다려 <br>그런 나를 모르는 넌 <br>what should i do <br>Big wave surge up in ma mind and <br>in ma head rushing down d down <br>Big wave surge up in ma mind and <br>in ma head <br>Big wave surge up in ma mind and <br>in ma head rushing down d down <br>Big wave surge up in ma mind and <br>in ma head <br>네 곁에서 맴돌아 봤자 <br>쳐다보지도 않을걸 알아 <br>끝내 난 잡을 수가 없는 건지 <br>네 목소리 니 흔적이 <br>하나 둘씩 사라져가는지 <br>이제 다시 <br>go back to your place <br>Big wave surge up in ma mind and <br>in ma head rushing down d down <br>Big wave surge up in ma mind and <br>in ma head rushing down d down <br>Big wave surge up in ma mind and <br>in ma head <br>Big wave surge up in ma mind and <br>in ma head rushing down d down <br>Big wave surge up in ma mind and <br>in ma head <br>Big wave a big wave <br>Big wave a big wave <br>]]></content><category term="써드 (third)" label="써드 (third)"/><category term="Big Wave" label="Big Wave"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Manu_Crook/Assumptions/</id><title>Manu Crook$ - Assumptions - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:33:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:33:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Manu_Crook/Assumptions/" title="Manu Crook$ - Assumptions - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>Ready x2 <br><br>Check <br><br>I do not like all the bum shit <br>I do not fuck with the nonsense <br>All of the bitches they think that they know me but all of them assumptions <br>You are not part of my fraction <br>I turn up to turn up the function x3 <br><br>They throwing some dirt on my name <br>Bitch I ain't part of your game <br>All of the bullshit <br>All the involvement <br>Honestly I'm so ashamed <br>Switching these bitches like flows yeah <br>I can not save any hoe yeah <br>Hanging around with these white girls <br>Is like we just making it snow yeah <br><br>I do not like all the bum shit <br>I do not fuck with the nonsense <br>All of the bitches they think that they know me but all of them assumptions <br>You are not part of my fraction <br>I turn up to turn up the function x3 <br><br>They know I don't surf but already on top of the wave <br>They know it's my turf so you walking the way that I pave <br>The way that I sway, like it's in the morning <br>Records I'm droppin' will never be boring <br>Records I'm droppin' is part of the story <br>Records on records, that shit is so awesome <br>x <br>I got the vision like go pro <br>Ballin' so hard I could go pro <br>Working the stick like a pogo <br>She back it up for me in slow mo <br>She work work work work you'd think she Riri <br>Do me dirt dirt dirt dirt, you'd think she Riri <br><br>I do not like all the bum shit <br>I do not fuck with the nonsense <br>All of the bitches they think that they know me but all of them assumptions <br>You are not part of my fraction <br>I turn up to turn up the function x3 <br><br>We turn up to turn up yeah <br>You know how this shit go <br>With the squad and we so litttttttt <br>You know how this shit go <br><br>I keep a sum to myself <br>Can't get a hold of myself <br>I got these bitches they tryna finesse me I'm already feeling myself <br>I'm just so sick of the favors <br>Time to be cold like a glacier <br>Gotta stay sharp like a razor <br>Saving the game I'm the savior <br>x <br>Assumptions, assumptions <br>Don't come here bluffing <br>That he say that she say <br>That shit mean nothing <br>x2 <br><br>I do not like all the bum shit <br>I do not fuck with the nonsense <br>All of the bitches they think that they know me but all of them assumptions <br>You are not part of my fraction <br>I turn up to turn up the function x3]]></content><category term="Manu Crook$" label="Manu Crook$"/><category term="Assumptions" label="Assumptions"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/블루_BLOO/Better/</id><title>블루 (BLOO) - Better - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:33:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:33:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8_BLOO/Better/" title="블루 (BLOO) - Better - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[햇빛이 지는 밤 밑에 칵테일 <br>Rocking Christian Dior <br>청순한 face 밑에 빨간색 dress <br>Let me take you out on a tour <br>눈을 맞춘 다음에 <br>팔짱을 낀 다음에 <br>손목에 금팔찌를 흔들어 <br>연예인들처럼 <br>you are fucking with the best <br>조수석에 앉아 <br>We should drive around <br>노란 노을이 비추는 <br>HollyWood sign <br>달이 밝은 오늘 밤엔 <br>따자 너의 outfit과 <br>어울리는 붉은색 wine <br>앵두 같은 입술에 <br>담배를 물어 <br>라이터에 비춘 <br>너의 두 눈이 울어 <br>더 깊어 지기 전에 <br>빨간 불을 빨리 붙여 <br>잊기 전에 다시 한번 <br>니 이름을 물어 <br>창문을 바라보며 <br>두 눈을 감은 뒤에 <br>내 무릎 위에 앉지 <br>빈 잔을 바라보며 <br>살포시 웃은 뒤에 <br>와인 병을 들어 따르지 <br>I’m feeling better <br>I’m feeling better <br>창문을 바라보며 <br>두 눈을 감은 뒤에 <br>내 무릎 위에 앉지 <br>I've been looking at you all day <br>거의 다 끝난 bombay <br>내 머리 위에 스냅백을 벗겨준 <br>너의 눈동잔 Black <br>나를 잊어주길 바래 <br>우리 같이 했던 파티 <br>네게 해줄 말은 I’m sorry <br>but 결국엔 넌 나의 mistake <br>조수석에 앉아 <br>We should drive around <br>노란 노을이 비추는 <br>HollyWood sign <br>달이 밝은 오늘 밤엔 <br>따자 너의 outfit과 <br>어울리는 붉은색 wine <br>앵두 같은 입술에 <br>담배를 물어 <br>라이터에 비춘 <br>너의 두 눈이 울어 <br>더 깊어 지기 전에 <br>빨간 불을 빨리 붙여 <br>잊기 전에 다시 한번 <br>니 이름을 물어 <br>창문을 바라보며 <br>두 눈을 감은 뒤에 <br>내 무릎 위에 앉지 <br>빈 잔을 바라보며 <br>살포시 웃은 뒤에 <br>와인 병을 들어 따르지 <br>I’m feeling better <br>I’m feeling better <br>창문을 바라보며 <br>두 눈을 감은 뒤에 <br>내 무릎 위에 앉지 <br>창문을 바라보며 <br>두 눈을 감은 뒤에 <br>내 무릎 위에 앉지 <br>창문을 바라보며 <br>두 눈을 감은 뒤에 <br>내 무릎 위에 앉지 <br>I’m feeling better <br>I’m feeling better <br>창문을 바라보며 <br>두 눈을 감은 뒤에 <br>내 무릎 위에 앉지 <br>창문을 바라보며 <br>두 눈을 감은 뒤에 <br>내 무릎 위에 앉지 <br>창문을 바라보며 <br>두 눈을 감은 뒤에 <br>내 무릎 위에 앉지 <br>]]></content><category term="블루 (BLOO)" label="블루 (BLOO)"/><category term="Better" label="Better"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/가비엔제이/뻔한_멜로_Inst/</id><title>가비엔제이 - 뻔한 멜로 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:33:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:33:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%80%EB%B9%84%EC%97%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4/%EB%BB%94%ED%95%9C_%EB%A9%9C%EB%A1%9C_Inst/" title="가비엔제이 - 뻔한 멜로 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[착각하지마 애써봤자 <br>여기까지야 <br>돌아보지마 우리 그만 <br>아프게 하자 <br>며칠 울면 돼 펑펑 울면 돼 <br>시간이 약이잖아 <br>날 내버려 둬 괜찮아지겠지 <br>한두 번도 아닌 이별 <br>왜 이렇게 눈물 나니 <br>잊을 거라고 울지 말라고 <br>내게 말해줄래요 <br>얼마나 더 아파 봐야 <br>이 뻔한 멜로 끝이 나니 <br>슬픈 사랑 얘기 <br>다시는 안 할래 <br>웃어주지마 이럼 <br>내가 흔들리잖아 <br>변명하지마 그럼 <br>내가 비참하잖아 <br>내 맘 다칠까 니 맘 편할까 <br>맘에 없는 거짓말 <br>그냥 떠나줘 여기서 끝내자 <br>한두 번도 아닌 이별 <br>왜 이렇게 눈물 나니 <br>잊을 거라고 울지 말라고 <br>내게 말해줄래요 <br>얼마나 더 아파 봐야 <br>이 뻔한 멜로 끝이 나니 <br>슬픈 사랑 얘기 <br>다시는 안 할래 <br>근데 그립다 그립다 그립다 <br>나만 왜 이러는데 <br>그 잘난 추억이 질긴 미련이 <br>다시 너를 부르잖아 <br>다들 하는 그런 사랑 <br>나만 혼자 힘든 거니 <br>지나간다고 행복 하라고 <br>내게 말해줄래요 <br>얼마나 더 이별해야 <br>이 뻔한 멜로 끝이 날까 <br>슬픈 사랑 얘기 <br>다시는 안 할래 <br>]]></content><category term="가비엔제이" label="가비엔제이"/><category term="뻔한 멜로 (Inst.)" label="뻔한 멜로 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/가비엔제이/슈비루비룹/</id><title>가비엔제이 - 슈비루비룹 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:33:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:33:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%80%EB%B9%84%EC%97%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4/%EC%8A%88%EB%B9%84%EB%A3%A8%EB%B9%84%EB%A3%B9/" title="가비엔제이 - 슈비루비룹 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루에 세 번씩 매일 연락해서 <br>오늘 뭐해 물을 거야 <br>하루에 하나씩 하트 눌러볼까 <br>니가 괜히 오해하게 <br>여친 있는 남자 좋아함 안 된대 <br>그건 나도 아는데 어어 <br>내가 왜 이러지 나 정말 이상해 <br>내 맘 주체가 안돼 <br>웃는 게 좋아 너와 눈 맞출 때면 <br>내 맘이 녹을 것만 같아 <br>너에게 한 뼘 두 뼘 가까울수록 <br>난 숨이 멎을 것만 같아 <br>슈비루비룹 말려줘요 <br>슈비루비룹 말려줘요 <br>슈비루비룹 요즘 내가 <br>정신이 나갔나봐 <br>슈비루비룹 어떡하죠 <br>슈비루비룹 어떡하죠 <br>슈비루비룹 제발 나 좀 <br>꿈에서 깨워줘요 <br>특별히 예쁜 날 몰래 찾아가서 <br>너를 놀래켜 볼 거야 <br>귀여운 눈웃음 살짝 건네볼까 <br>니 눈빛이 흔들리게 <br>니 옆에 그녀가 예뻐 죽겠나봐 <br>맘엔 불이 나는데 어어 <br>넌 행복한가봐 사랑꾼인가봐 <br>맘엔 틈이 없잖아 <br>웃는 게 좋아 너와 눈 맞출 때면 <br>내 맘이 녹을 것만 같아 <br>너에게 한 뼘 두 뼘 가까울수록 <br>난 숨이 멎을 것만 같아 <br>슈비루비룹 말려줘요 <br>슈비루비룹 말려줘요 <br>슈비루비룹 요즘 내가 <br>정신이 나갔나봐 <br>슈비루비룹 어떡하죠 <br>슈비루비룹 어떡하죠 <br>슈비루비룹 제발 나 좀 <br>꿈에서 깨워줘요 <br>내가 미쳤지 나도 아는데 <br>내 맘 내 맘 같지 않아 <br>안 된다고 해도 멈추라고 해도 <br>니가 좋아 어떡해 <br>고백해 볼까 말까 어질어질해 <br>내 하룬 온통 너뿐인데 <br>이런 날 알까 몰라 눈치가 없니 <br>내꺼하고 싶단 말야 <br>슈비루비룹 말려줘요 <br>슈비루비룹 말려줘요 <br>슈비루비룹 요즘 내가 <br>정신이 나갔나봐 <br>슈비루비룹 어떡하죠 <br>슈비루비룹 어떡하죠 <br>슈비루비룹 제발 나 좀 <br>꿈에서 깨워줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="가비엔제이" label="가비엔제이"/><category term="슈비루비룹" label="슈비루비룹"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/가비엔제이/우리_사이/</id><title>가비엔제이 - 우리 사이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:33:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:33:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%80%EB%B9%84%EC%97%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EC%82%AC%EC%9D%B4/" title="가비엔제이 - 우리 사이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 그러는데 <br>왜 까칠한 건데 내게 <br>비꼬지 좀 마 <br>투덜대지 좀 마 정말 <br>가끔 웃는 모습에 <br>가슴 뛰게 좋을 때도 있지만 <br>우리 사이 정말 왜 이러니 <br>어쩌다 연인처럼 <br>좋다가도 제자리야 <br>사탕처럼 달콤해도 <br>잠시 뿐야 <br>이게 뭐야 또 투닥투닥 <br>어떻게 할지를 몰라 <br>아직은 사랑한단 말은 <br>이른 우리 사이 <br>좋아한단 말은 <br>듣고 싶은 사이 <br>이봐 날봐 좀 웃어줄래 <br>어떻게 내 맘을 몰라 <br>참 우리 사이 <br>그러지 좀 마 <br>상처 주지 좀 마 내게 <br>니가 아픈 걸 보면 <br>괜히 맘이 가고 걱정되지만 <br>우리 사이 정말 왜 이러니 <br>어쩌다 연인처럼 <br>좋다가도 제자리야 <br>사탕처럼 달콤해도 <br>잠시 뿐야 <br>이게 뭐야 또 투닥투닥 <br>어떻게 할지를 몰라 <br>아직은 사랑한단 말은 <br>이른 우리 사이 <br>좋아한단 말은 <br>듣고 싶은 사이 <br>이봐 날봐 좀 웃어줄래 <br>어떻게 내 맘을 몰라 <br>참 우리 사이 <br>우리 정말 이상해 <br>뭐가 그리 복잡해 <br>맘은 그게 아닌데 <br>왜 헷갈리는데 <br>솔직할 때도 됐잖아 <br>내 맘 알 때도 됐잖아 <br>밉다가도 보고 싶은 <br>너란 남자 <br>귀찮아도 생각나는 <br>너란 여자 <br>사실 말야 좋아하나봐 <br>내 입이 맘 같지 않아 <br>참 미치겠어 <br>아직은 사랑한단 말은 <br>이른 우리 사이 <br>좋아한단 말은 <br>듣고 싶은 사이 <br>이봐 날봐 좀 웃어줄래 <br>어떻게 내 맘을 몰라 <br>참 우리 사이 <br>]]></content><category term="가비엔제이" label="가비엔제이"/><category term="우리 사이" label="우리 사이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/가비엔제이/미안했을까/</id><title>가비엔제이 - 미안했을까 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:33:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:33:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%80%EB%B9%84%EC%97%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4/%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%88%ED%96%88%EC%9D%84%EA%B9%8C/" title="가비엔제이 - 미안했을까 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[헤어지던 날 <br>니가 내게 던지던 말 <br>일분일초도 <br>너랑 있고 싶지 않아 <br>불꽃 같던 날 <br>한순간에 식어 버린 넌 <br>꼭 그렇게 그렇게 <br>그래야만 했니 <br>잘 지냈을까 <br>조금은 미안했을까 <br>몇 마디로 우리 <br>정리할 만큼 쉽니 <br>진짜였을까 <br>혹시 넌 후회했을까 <br>홧김에 그런 거라면 <br>이럴 맘 아니었다면 <br>늦은 밤 문득 <br>문자 한 번 올법한데 <br>몇 달이 가도 <br>연락 없는 니가 미워 <br>아닐 거라고 <br>다를 거라 믿었었는데 <br>넌 뻔하게 뻔하게 <br>그래야만 했니 <br>잘 지냈을까 <br>조금은 미안했을까 <br>몇 마디로 우리 <br>정리할 만큼 쉽니 <br>진짜였을까 <br>혹시 넌 후회했을까 <br>홧김에 그런 거라면 <br>이럴 맘 아니었다면 <br>말은 안 해도 <br>너도 아팠을 거야 <br>그래도 너무 하잖아 <br>우리 사랑이긴 했었니 <br>나도 너처럼 <br>널 싫어할래도 안돼 <br>울고 있던 날 <br>한번은 돌아봤을까 <br>그때로 돌아간다면 <br>니가 날 안아줬다면 <br>얘기해줄래 <br>그때 정말 왜 그랬니 <br>조금이라도 내게 <br>미안하긴 했니 <br>]]></content><category term="가비엔제이" label="가비엔제이"/><category term="미안했을까" label="미안했을까"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/가비엔제이/먹고_자고_그리워하고/</id><title>가비엔제이 - 먹고 자고 그리워하고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:33:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:33:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%80%EB%B9%84%EC%97%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4/%EB%A8%B9%EA%B3%A0_%EC%9E%90%EA%B3%A0_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9B%8C%ED%95%98%EA%B3%A0/" title="가비엔제이 - 먹고 자고 그리워하고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[매일 눈뜨자마자 전화기만 <br>혹시 문자가 왔을까 <br>아닌데 또 기댈 하지 <br>세수를 하고 머리를 감고 <br>오늘은 또 뭘 먹을까 <br>몇 번을 봤던 영화를 봐도 <br>뭐를 해도 너 뿐야 <br>먹고 자고 그리워하고 <br>눈만 뜨면 니 생각하고 <br>이게 뭐야 괜찮댔 잖아 <br>정말 나빴어 <br>웃고 울고 널 미워하고 <br>쉴 새 없이 하룰 보내도 <br>자고 나면 아직도 너야 <br>결국 난 이래 <br>그래 괜찮게 잘 지내 <br>누가 봐도 좋을 만큼 <br>살 것도 없이 쇼핑을 하고 <br>이곳 저곳 걸어보고 <br>친구를 불러 수달 떨어도 <br>하루의 끝은 너야 <br>먹고 자고 그리워하고 <br>눈만 뜨면 니 생각하고 <br>이게 뭐야 괜찮댔 잖아 <br>정말 나빴어 <br>웃고 울고 널 미워하고 <br>쉴 새 없이 하룰 보내도 <br>자고 나면 아직도 너야 <br>결국 난 이래 <br>넌 넌 어떻게 지내는지 <br>내 내 걱정은 하는 건지 <br>넌 내 습관이 되고 <br>하루 종일 날 따라와 <br>거봐 나 이럴 줄 알았어 <br>이별한테 질 줄 알았어 <br>붙잡을 걸 더 크게 울 걸 <br>다 너 때문야 <br>꿈을 꿔도 다 니가 되고 <br>하룰 온통 너로 보내고 <br>어김없이 오늘도 너야 <br>내일도 너야 <br>]]></content><category term="가비엔제이" label="가비엔제이"/><category term="먹고 자고 그리워하고" label="먹고 자고 그리워하고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/가비엔제이/뻔한_멜로/</id><title>가비엔제이 - 뻔한 멜로 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:33:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:33:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%80%EB%B9%84%EC%97%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4/%EB%BB%94%ED%95%9C_%EB%A9%9C%EB%A1%9C/" title="가비엔제이 - 뻔한 멜로 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[착각하지마 애써봤자 <br>여기까지야 <br>돌아보지마 우리 그만 <br>아프게 하자 <br>며칠 울면 돼 펑펑 울면 돼 <br>시간이 약이잖아 <br>날 내버려 둬 괜찮아지겠지 <br>한두 번도 아닌 이별 <br>왜 이렇게 눈물 나니 <br>잊을 거라고 울지 말라고 <br>내게 말해줄래요 <br>얼마나 더 아파 봐야 <br>이 뻔한 멜로 끝이 나니 <br>슬픈 사랑 얘기 <br>다시는 안 할래 <br>웃어주지마 이럼 <br>내가 흔들리잖아 <br>변명하지마 그럼 <br>내가 비참하잖아 <br>내 맘 다칠까 니 맘 편할까 <br>맘에 없는 거짓말 <br>그냥 떠나줘 여기서 끝내자 <br>한두 번도 아닌 이별 <br>왜 이렇게 눈물 나니 <br>잊을 거라고 울지 말라고 <br>내게 말해줄래요 <br>얼마나 더 아파 봐야 <br>이 뻔한 멜로 끝이 나니 <br>슬픈 사랑 얘기 <br>다시는 안 할래 <br>근데 그립다 그립다 그립다 <br>나만 왜 이러는데 <br>그 잘난 추억이 질긴 미련이 <br>다시 너를 부르잖아 <br>다들 하는 그런 사랑 <br>나만 혼자 힘든 거니 <br>지나간다고 행복 하라고 <br>내게 말해줄래요 <br>얼마나 더 이별해야 <br>이 뻔한 멜로 끝이 날까 <br>슬픈 사랑 얘기 <br>다시는 안 할래 <br>]]></content><category term="가비엔제이" label="가비엔제이"/><category term="뻔한 멜로" label="뻔한 멜로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정기고/Let_Me_Love_You/</id><title>정기고 - Let Me Love You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:33:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:33:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B8%B0%EA%B3%A0/Let_Me_Love_You/" title="정기고 - Let Me Love You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[첨 마주 볼 때 <br>난 알았어 <br>언젠가 이렇게 <br>마주칠 줄 알았어 <br>틈만 생기면 보고파서 <br>꽉 차 있던 주말에 <br>약속도 비웠어 <br>다른 여자와 달라 <br>특별하단 말 <br>너무 많이 들어서 <br>조금 지겹겠지만 <br>가볍게 생각하지마 <br>지금 진지하니까 <br>더 고민 말고 <br>날 고르면 돼 <br>아침에 눈을 뜨면 <br>곁에 있어줄게 <br>잠 못 드는 밤엔 <br>널 꼭 안아줄게 <br>Just let me love you <br>이제 살짝 고개만 <br>끄덕이면 돼 <br>요새는 무슨 일을 해도 <br>니 생각에 빠져 <br>집중을 못 하겠어 <br>하루가 길고 지루해도 <br>니 목소리면 모든 게 <br>괜찮아지는 걸 <br>다른 남자와 다르지 <br>않을 거란 말 <br>너무 급하게 하지 말고 <br>천천히 더 지켜봐 <br>가볍게 생각하지 마 <br>지금 진지하니까 <br>더 고민 말고 <br>웃어주면 돼 <br>아침에 눈을 뜨면 <br>곁에 있어줄게 <br>잠 못 드는 밤엔 <br>널 꼭 안아줄게 <br>Just let me love you <br>이제 살짝 고개만 <br>끄덕이면 돼 <br>I I wanna fall in love <br>한 걸음만 더 <br>가까이 와 줘 <br>I I wanna fall in love <br>그대로 내 곁에 <br>있어줄래 <br>아침에 눈을 뜨면 <br>곁에 있어줄게 <br>잠 못 드는 밤엔 <br>널 꼭 안아줄게 <br>Just let me love you <br>이제 살짝 고개만 <br>끄덕이면 돼 <br>아침에 눈을 뜨면 <br>곁에 있어줄게 <br>잠 못 드는 밤엔 <br>널 꼭 안아줄게 <br>Just let me love you <br>이제 살짝 고개만 <br>끄덕이면 돼 <br>]]></content><category term="정기고" label="정기고"/><category term="Let Me Love You" label="Let Me Love You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동요마을/전갈송/</id><title>동요마을 - 전갈송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T09:33:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T09:33:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%84/%EC%A0%84%EA%B0%88%EC%86%A1/" title="동요마을 - 전갈송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[전갈은 너무 무서워 독침 쏘는 무서운 전갈 <br>네쌍의 다리가 있고 가재처럼 생긴 전갈 <br><br>갈고리 모양 독침 사냥할 때 쓴다지요 <br>전갈을 조심하세요 어둠 속에 숨어있어요 <br><br>전갈은 무시무시해 꼬리에는 독침이 있죠 <br>종류도 천개가 넘고 모양도 참 다양하지요 <br><br>물리면 큰일나요 전갈 독침 조심해요 <br>전갈은 무시무시해 보면 바로 도망치세요 <br><br>전갈은 너무 무서워 독침 쏘는 무서운 전갈 <br>네쌍의 다리가 있고 가재처럼 생긴 전갈 <br><br>갈고리 모양 독침 사냥할 때 쓴다지요 <br>전갈을 조심하세요 어둠 속에 숨어있어요 <br><br>전갈은 무시무시해 꼬리에는 독침이 있죠 <br>종류도 천개가 넘고 모양도 참 다양하지요 <br><br>물리면 큰일나요 전갈 독침 조심해요 <br>전갈은 무시무시해 보면 바로 도망치세요]]></content><category term="동요마을" label="동요마을"/><category term="전갈송" label="전갈송"/></entry></feed>