<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T21:02:43+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전우진/Strong_Korea/</id><title>전우진 - Strong Korea - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:10:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:10:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%9A%B0%EC%A7%84/Strong_Korea/" title="전우진 - Strong Korea - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아름다운 금수강산에 <br>따뜻한 온기 가득하고 <br>푸르른 저 대지 위에는 <br>열정의 생명 넘쳐난다 <br>온갖 시련 속을 <br>버티고 일어나 <br>한 걸음 두 걸음 전진하여 <br>희망찬 미래의 <br>뜨거운 불꽃이 <br>만방에 활활 타오른다 <br>영원 하라 대한민국 <br>영원 하라 대한민국 <br>뿌리 깊은 강한 의지 속에 <br>끝없이 빛날 것임을 <br>온갖 시련 속을 <br>버티고 일어나 <br>한 걸음 두 걸음 전진하여 <br>희망찬 미래의 <br>뜨거운 불꽃이 <br>만방에 활활 타오른다 <br>영원 하라 대한민국 <br>영원 하라 대한민국 <br>뿌리 깊은 강한 의지 속에 <br>끝없이 빛날 것임을 <br>영원 하라 대한민국 <br>영원 하라 대한민국 <br>뿌리 깊은 강한 의지 속에 <br>끝없이 빛날 것임을 <br>]]></content><category term="전우진" label="전우진"/><category term="Strong Korea" label="Strong Korea"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brain_Orgasm/Starlights_Falling/</id><title>Brain Orgasm - Starlight`s Falling - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:10:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:10:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brain_Orgasm/Starlights_Falling/" title="Brain Orgasm - Starlight`s Falling - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[look Starlight's falling <br>look Starlight's falling <br>긴밤 어느새 훌쩍커버린 <br>시선 너머에 <br>큰 눈동자가 비쳐서 <br>별길 주행하는 내 맘담아 <br>I'm there here <br>you're there here <br>this moment <br>I'm there here <br>you're there here <br>this moment on the earth <br>my god <br>멈춰선 내겐 들려요 <br>별들이 내리는 이끌림 <br>I can feel <br>I hear star's way <br>I hear star's way way <br>starlight's falling no staying <br>when you've staying for a day <br>I have been just looking your life <br>think if we don't have gravity <br>rising sun and falling stars <br>are staying there always <br>they're waiting for my breathing <br>oh I see there is forever forever <br>rising on your head <br>rising sun and falling stars <br>are staying there always <br>they're waiting for my breathing <br>oh I see there is forever forever <br>rising on your head <br>I'm styling <br>I'm telling you and I know <br>Staying there's greater <br>than rising <br>I'm styling <br>I'm telling you and I know <br>Staying there's greater <br>than rising <br>I'm styling <br>I'm telling you and I know <br>Staying there's greater <br>than rising <br>I'm styling <br>I'm telling you and I know <br>Staying there's greater <br>than rising <br>]]></content><category term="Brain Orgasm" label="Brain Orgasm"/><category term="Starlight`s Falling" label="Starlight`s Falling"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sustain/눈길/</id><title>Sustain - 눈길 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:11:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:11:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sustain/%EB%88%88%EA%B8%B8/" title="Sustain - 눈길 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[겨울쯤이였나 <br>우리가 만난 그 계절이 <br>눈이 내렸었지 <br>네가 내 손을 <br>잡아 주었던 그날 <br>난 소중했던 <br>너와의 기억 속에서 <br>미련하게 남아 있잖아 <br>눈이 내릴 때면 <br>너와의 그 추억이 <br>점점 내려와 <br>하얀 눈길에 <br>하나 둘씩 쌓여 <br>내 맘 머물게 하네 <br>불빛 하나 남은 <br>좁은 골목길 <br>가로등 아래 <br>너와 손을 잡던 <br>그때 우리에겐 <br>봄이 온 것만 같았지 <br>눈이 내릴 때면 <br>너와의 그 추억이 <br>점점 내려와 <br>하얀 눈길에 <br>하나 둘씩 쌓여 <br>내 맘 머물게 하네 <br>눈이 내릴 때면 <br>너와의 그 추억이 <br>점점 내려와 <br>하얀 눈길에 <br>하나 둘씩 쌓여 <br>내 맘 머물게 하네 <br>]]></content><category term="Sustain" label="Sustain"/><category term="눈길" label="눈길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZEEBOMB/어젯밤_길을_걷다/</id><title>ZEEBOMB - 어젯밤 길을 걷다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:11:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:11:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZEEBOMB/%EC%96%B4%EC%A0%AF%EB%B0%A4_%EA%B8%B8%EC%9D%84_%EA%B1%B7%EB%8B%A4/" title="ZEEBOMB - 어젯밤 길을 걷다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어젯밤 길을 걷다 <br>니 생각이 났어 <br>꽃을 향하는 나비처럼 <br>거부 할 수 없었지 <br>내 눈에 아른거려 <br>수저도 못 들겠어 <br>내 맘이 아파 너무 아파도 <br>티는 내기 싫었어 <br>웃고만 싶은 걸 <br>갖고만 싶은 걸 yeah <br>니 손을 잡고 싶어 <br>나는 미쳐 있나 봐 <br>처음 널 보는 순간 <br>시간이 멈췄어 <br>시간이 멈췄는데 <br>왜 내 심장은 쿵쾅 뛸까 <br>한 발짝 두 발짝 <br>니가 내 곁에 왔어 <br>나는 한 발짝 물러섰어 <br>심장 소리가 들릴 까 봐 <br>뽀뽀하고 싶은 걸 <br>Baby Sexy한 걸 yeah <br>니 손을 잡고 싶어 <br>나는 미쳐 있나 봐 <br>오 나는 미쳐 있나 봐 yeah <br>]]></content><category term="ZEEBOMB" label="ZEEBOMB"/><category term="어젯밤 길을 걷다" label="어젯밤 길을 걷다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/곰PD/Return/</id><title>곰PD - Return - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:11:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:11:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B0PD/Return/" title="곰PD - Return - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그 곳에 니가 있다면 돌아갈게 <br>아무일 없던 것처럼 손 내밀게 <br>아직 늦지 않았다면 돌아갈게 <br>두 눈에 고인 눈물 닦아줄게 <br>결국 난 혼자야 이렇게 <br>눈을 감았다 뜨면 달라질까 <br>다가가려 해봤던 걸음과 <br>잡아보려 내밀었던 손은 <br>저 멀리 더 멀리 떠나가 <br>아무 것도 할 수 없단 말야 <br>너의 모든 게 아프게 해서 <br>저 멀리 더 멀리 <br>떠나가 희미하게 <br>기억하고 있다면 돌아갈게 <br>부서진 약속이지만 지켜볼게 <br>결국 난 혼자야 이렇게 <br>고개를 돌려도 아직은 <br>아직은 눈물이 나 <br>다가가려 해봤던 걸음과 <br>잡아보려 내밀었던 손은 <br>저 멀리 더 멀리 떠나가 <br>아무 것도 할 수 없단 말야 <br>너의 모든 게 아프게 해서 <br>저 멀리 더 멀리 <br>떠나가 희미하게 <br>]]></content><category term="곰PD" label="곰PD"/><category term="Return" label="Return"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/프로퍼_Proper/스물아홉/</id><title>프로퍼 (Proper) - 스물아홉 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:11:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:11:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%84%EB%A1%9C%ED%8D%BC_Proper/%EC%8A%A4%EB%AC%BC%EC%95%84%ED%99%89/" title="프로퍼 (Proper) - 스물아홉 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지금보다 어릴 때 <br>그러니까 말하자면 <br>이제 막 이십 대 <br>가 됐을 때 난 한번도 <br>내 젊음에 대해서 <br>조금도 의심해 <br>본적이 없네 당연히 <br>나 역시 이게 <br>영원하지 않다는 건 <br>머리로는 이해 했지만 <br>뭐랄까 <br>단순히 이해 한 것과 <br>몸으로 느껴 깨닫는단 <br>것 사이엔 <br>큰 차이가 있더라 <br>그냥 다르단 얘기네 <br>가진걸 잃어버리는 것 <br>생각해 본적도 없어 <br>왜냐면 이건 그저 <br>너무나 당연하게 <br>내게 주어 졌으니까 <br>언젠간 날 떠나간단 <br>간단한 사실을 <br>눈 앞에 두고 애써 부정 <br>한 거야 떠나 보내고 난 뒤야 <br>떠났다는 걸 안거야 <br>애초부터 가진 게 아닌 <br>잠시 빌렸을 뿐인데 <br>이미 멀어지는 중인데 <br>마치 내일도 여전히 <br>젊을 거라 믿고 산 거야 <br>한가지 확실한 건 <br>여긴 절대 <br>완벽한 건 없다는 것 <br>산다는 것은 원래 <br>미리 해볼 수도 <br>다시 고칠 수도 <br>없는 거니까 짊어지고 <br>사는 법을 배워야 해 <br>매번 우린 몇 가지의 <br>선택지 앞에 <br>못 해본 것 못 가본 곳 <br>못 가진 것 따위에 <br>미련을 갖지만 <br>그것만큼 무의미한 <br>일이 없네 잊으며 <br>사는 법을 알아야 해 <br>지나간 시간을 돌아볼 때 <br>내가 생각해 봐도 <br>정말로 골 때리는 짓을 <br>많이 했네 <br>약간의 추억과 대부분의 <br>아쉬움과 미련 그리고 후회 <br>처음엔 수많은 가능성들이 <br>존재했지만 시간의 흐름에 <br>하나씩 퇴색되었고 <br>그 많은 일들이 <br>다 일어날 만큼 <br>어렸지만 아무 일도 <br>일어나지 않았지 <br>웃기게도 결국엔 <br>약간의 방황과 <br>약간의 무기력함 <br>기대와 달랐던 세상에 대한 <br>이 무력감 <br>자라난 실망감에 <br>자연스럽게 잉여가 되어 <br>유유히 부유 <br>산다는 건 대체 뭘까 <br>독이 돼버린 나 자신에 <br>대한 과대평가 <br>지키지 못한 다짐들에 <br>실패한 기억과 <br>너무 싸게 처분한 젊음이란 <br>기회 그저 그런 성과 <br>나이 먹는다는 게 이리 쉬웠나 <br>한가지 확실한 건 <br>여긴 절대 <br>완벽한 건 없다는 것 <br>산다는 것은 원래 <br>미리 해볼 수도 <br>다시 고칠 수도 <br>없는 거니까 짊어지고 <br>사는 법을 배워야 해 <br>매번 우린 몇 가지의 <br>선택지 앞에 <br>못 해본 것 못 가본 곳 <br>못 가진 것 따위에 <br>미련을 갖지만 <br>그것만큼 무의미한 <br>일이 없네 잊으며 <br>사는 법을 알아야 해 <br>지나간 일은 지나간 일 <br>아쉬운 것들 아쉬운 대로 <br>두고 걸어가길 <br>알잖아 산다는 건 <br>그런 것들과의 불가피한 <br>동행과도 같아 <br>내키지 않아도 <br>그다지 참고 가야 해 <br>길이 험할수록 앞을 봐야지 <br>약간의 추억 그리고 <br>대부분의 시간낭비 <br>그 와중에 얻은 몇 가지 <br>상기 할만한 레쓴 <br>나의 이십 대가 남긴 <br>흔적들 잊지 말고 <br>앞을 비춰가길 <br>]]></content><category term="프로퍼 (Proper)" label="프로퍼 (Proper)"/><category term="스물아홉" label="스물아홉"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이지이/별_하나/</id><title>이지이 - 별 하나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:12:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:12:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80%EC%9D%B4/%EB%B3%84_%ED%95%98%EB%82%98/" title="이지이 - 별 하나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[반짝이며 빛을 내는 예쁜 별 하나 <br>나도 그런 별이 되고 싶었어 <br>울렁이는 긴 하루에 <br>끝에 다다르면 <br>고갤 들어 힘을 내요 나를 위로해 <br>밤하늘은 너무 깜깜한 건지 <br>눈길 주는 사람 하나 없어도 <br>오늘은 더 빛을 낼 거야 <br>더 반짝일게 <br>가끔 힘에 부쳐 구름 뒤에 숨어도 <br>그 누구도 찾지 않는 <br>희미한 거리를 <br>환하게 비춰 줄 꺼야 걱정 마 <br>밤하늘은 너무 깜깜한 건지 <br>눈길 주는 사람 하나 없어도 <br>오늘은 더 빛을 낼 거야 <br>더 반짝일게 <br>가끔 힘에 부쳐 구름 뒤에 숨어도 <br>그 누구도 찾지 않는 <br>희미한 거리를 <br>환하게 비춰 줄 꺼야 걱정 마 <br>꿈을 꾸고 있어요 <br>내가 살아가는 이유죠 <br>빛이 다 할 때까지 <br>오늘은 꼭 빛나고 싶어 <br>나 별이 될게 <br>지친 하루 끝에 힘이 돼 주는 스타 <br>그 누구도 찾지 않는 이 거리에서 <br>환하게 빛을 낼 거야 걱정 마 <br>]]></content><category term="이지이" label="이지이"/><category term="별 하나" label="별 하나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스페이스카우보이_SPACECOWBOY/헤어져야_하는_이유_Feat_리차드파커스_Project_PLUTO_Remix/</id><title>스페이스카우보이 (SPACECOWBOY) - 헤어져야 하는 이유 (Feat. 리차드파커스) (Project PLUTO Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:14:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:14:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8E%98%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4%EC%B9%B4%EC%9A%B0%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4_SPACECOWBOY/%ED%97%A4%EC%96%B4%EC%A0%B8%EC%95%BC_%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%9D%B4%EC%9C%A0_Feat_%EB%A6%AC%EC%B0%A8%EB%93%9C%ED%8C%8C%EC%BB%A4%EC%8A%A4_Project_PLUTO_Remix/" title="스페이스카우보이 (SPACECOWBOY) - 헤어져야 하는 이유 (Feat. 리차드파커스) (Project PLUTO Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[설명해선 안 되는 <br>많은 얘기가 있어 <br>나를 떠나야 하는 <br>너의 이유들처럼 <br>이해하기 싫은 얘기들이 있어 <br>나는 이대로 좋아 <br>소리 나지 않아도 <br>들리는 말이 있어 <br>니가 꺼내려 하는 <br>지금 그 얘기처럼 <br>듣고 싶지 않은 얘기들이 있어 <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Nothing's ever new <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Nothing's ever new <br>Don't tell <br>Nothing's ever new <br>Don't tell <br>Nothing's ever new <br>손에 닿지 않아도 <br>느껴지는 게 있어 <br>차디차게 식혀진 <br>지금 니 마음처럼 <br>그냥 두고 싶은 많은 것이 있어 <br>그게 아름답거든 <br>밀어 넣으려 해도 <br>드러나는 게 있어 <br>누가 봐도 우스운 <br>지금 내 눈물처럼 <br>어쩔 수가 없는 많은 것이 있어 <br>다 이런 거잖아 <br>다 이런 거잖아 <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Nothing's ever new <br>Nothing's ever new <br>Nothing's ever new <br>Don't tell <br>]]></content><category term="스페이스카우보이 (SPACECOWBOY)" label="스페이스카우보이 (SPACECOWBOY)"/><category term="헤어져야 하는 이유 (Feat. 리차드파커스) (Project PLUTO Remix)" label="헤어져야 하는 이유 (Feat. 리차드파커스) (Project PLUTO Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스페이스카우보이_SPACECOWBOY/헤어져야_하는_이유_Feat_리차드파커스_SPACECOWBOY_Deep_Future_Remix/</id><title>스페이스카우보이 (SPACECOWBOY) - 헤어져야 하는 이유 (Feat. 리차드파커스) (SPACECOWBOY Deep Future Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:14:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:14:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8E%98%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4%EC%B9%B4%EC%9A%B0%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4_SPACECOWBOY/%ED%97%A4%EC%96%B4%EC%A0%B8%EC%95%BC_%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%9D%B4%EC%9C%A0_Feat_%EB%A6%AC%EC%B0%A8%EB%93%9C%ED%8C%8C%EC%BB%A4%EC%8A%A4_SPACECOWBOY_Deep_Future_Remix/" title="스페이스카우보이 (SPACECOWBOY) - 헤어져야 하는 이유 (Feat. 리차드파커스) (SPACECOWBOY Deep Future Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[설명해선 안 되는 <br>많은 얘기가 있어 <br>나를 떠나야 하는 <br>너의 이유들처럼 <br>이해하기 싫은 얘기들이 있어 <br>나는 이대로 좋아 <br>소리 나지 않아도 <br>들리는 말이 있어 <br>니가 꺼내려 하는 <br>지금 그 얘기처럼 <br>듣고 싶지 않은 얘기들이 있어 <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Nothing's ever new <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Nothing's ever new <br>나는 이대로 좋아 <br>소리 나지 않아도 <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Nothing's ever new <br>나는 이대로 좋아 <br>소리 나지 않아도 <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>이해하기 싫은 <br>손에 닿지 않아도 <br>느껴지는 게 있어 <br>차디차게 식혀진 <br>지금 니 마음처럼 <br>그냥 두고 싶은 많은 것이 있어 <br>그게 아름답거든 <br>밀어 넣으려 해도 <br>드러나는 게 있어 <br>누가 봐도 우스운 <br>지금 내 눈물처럼 <br>어쩔 수가 없는 많은 것이 있어 <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Nothing's ever new <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Nothing's ever new <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>소리 나지 않아도 <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Nothing's ever new <br>나는 이대로 좋아 <br>소리 나지 않아도 <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>이해하기 싫은 <br>]]></content><category term="스페이스카우보이 (SPACECOWBOY)" label="스페이스카우보이 (SPACECOWBOY)"/><category term="헤어져야 하는 이유 (Feat. 리차드파커스) (SPACECOWBOY Deep Future Remix)" label="헤어져야 하는 이유 (Feat. 리차드파커스) (SPACECOWBOY Deep Future Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스페이스카우보이_SPACECOWBOY/헤어져야_하는_이유_Feat_리차드파커스_Original_Track/</id><title>스페이스카우보이 (SPACECOWBOY) - 헤어져야 하는 이유 (Feat. 리차드파커스) (Original Track) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:14:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:14:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8E%98%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4%EC%B9%B4%EC%9A%B0%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4_SPACECOWBOY/%ED%97%A4%EC%96%B4%EC%A0%B8%EC%95%BC_%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%9D%B4%EC%9C%A0_Feat_%EB%A6%AC%EC%B0%A8%EB%93%9C%ED%8C%8C%EC%BB%A4%EC%8A%A4_Original_Track/" title="스페이스카우보이 (SPACECOWBOY) - 헤어져야 하는 이유 (Feat. 리차드파커스) (Original Track) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[설명해선 안 되는 <br>많은 얘기가 있어 <br>나를 떠나야 하는 <br>너의 이유들처럼 <br>이해하기 싫은 얘기들이 있어 <br>나는 이대로 좋아 <br>소리 나지 않아도 <br>들리는 말이 있어 <br>니가 꺼내려 하는 <br>지금 그 얘기처럼 <br>듣고 싶지 않은 얘기들이 있어 <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>손에 닿지 않아도 <br>느껴지는 게 있어 <br>차디차게 식혀진 <br>지금 니 마음처럼 <br>그냥 두고 싶은 많은 것이 있어 <br>그게 아름답거든 <br>밀어 넣으려 해도 <br>드러나는 게 있어 <br>누가 봐도 우스운 <br>지금 내 눈물처럼 <br>어쩔 수가 없는 많은 것이 있어 <br>다 그런 거잖아 좀 뻔하긴 해도 <br>한 사람은 꼭 <br>초라하게 남겨지는 거 <br>다 잊을 거잖아 <br>지나간 많은 사랑들처럼 <br>I have many things to lie <br>like I'm getting over you <br>For me and you <br>For me and you <br>I'll lie to you <br>that I'm getting over you <br>For me and you <br>I will make it true <br>Even though it's so not true <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Nothing's ever new <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Nothing's ever new <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Nothing's ever new <br>Nothing's ever new <br>Don't tell Don't say <br>Nothing's ever new <br>]]></content><category term="스페이스카우보이 (SPACECOWBOY)" label="스페이스카우보이 (SPACECOWBOY)"/><category term="헤어져야 하는 이유 (Feat. 리차드파커스) (Original Track)" label="헤어져야 하는 이유 (Feat. 리차드파커스) (Original Track)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김우진/Your_Favorite_Song/</id><title>김우진 - Your Favorite Song - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:14:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:14:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9A%B0%EC%A7%84/Your_Favorite_Song/" title="김우진 - Your Favorite Song - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너와 나 우리 <br>둘 만을 위한 <br>이 순간 네가 <br>내게 다가와 <br>좀처럼 어떤 <br>말도 못한 채 <br>망설이는 내게 <br>살며시 수줍은 <br>고백을 하네 <br>I love you I want you <br>I really need you <br>I care about you <br>I love you I want you <br>I really need you <br>I care about you <br>오늘 밤 내 손에 <br>네 손을 맡긴 채 <br>행복한 이 꿈 속을 <br>함께 거닐래 <br>시시한 농담에도 <br>환하게 웃어주는 네게 <br>다가가 나즈막히 <br>속삭여 주네 <br>I love you I want you <br>I really need you <br>I care about you <br>I love you I want you <br>I really need you <br>I care about you <br>I love you <br>I love you <br>I love you <br>]]></content><category term="김우진" label="김우진"/><category term="Your Favorite Song" label="Your Favorite Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/차우_Chawoo/점점/</id><title>차우 (Chawoo) - 점점 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:14:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:14:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B0%A8%EC%9A%B0_Chawoo/%EC%A0%90%EC%A0%90/" title="차우 (Chawoo) - 점점 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[요즘은 어떤 노래를 들어봐도 <br>아무런 감정조차 <br>느껴지질 않는걸 <br>이상해 나이가 들어갈수록 점점 <br>또 점점 나는 무감각 해져가 <br>그래 그땐 정말 그랬었지 <br>뭐든지 하면 다 될 줄 <br>알았었는데 그땐 그랬지 <br>그때는 정말 그랬었지 <br>이젠 내가 뭐하고 사는지도 몰라 <br>자유롭게 살고 싶어 <br>놀고 싶을 때는 놀고 <br>일하고 싶을 때만 <br>일하면서 살고 싶어 <br>친구들도 만나고 <br>여행도 많이 다니고 <br>부모님과 시간도 <br>보내면서 살고 싶어 <br>못다한 어제에 치이고 <br>마주한 오늘에 또 치이고 <br>이리저리 정신 없이 <br>치이고 치이다 <br>떠밀려간 곳은 외로운 섬이고 <br>나만 혼자 멍하니 서있고 <br>왜 점점 자꾸 멀어지는 걸까 <br>그래 그땐 정말 그랬었지 <br>뭐든지 하면 다 될 줄 <br>알았었는데 그땐 그랬지 <br>그때는 정말 그랬었지 <br>이젠 내가 뭐하고 사는지도 몰라 <br>자유롭게 살고 싶어 <br>놀고 싶을 때는 놀고 <br>일하고 싶을 때만 <br>일하면서 살고 싶어 <br>친구들도 만나고 <br>여행도 많이 다니고 <br>부모님과 시간도 <br>보내면서 살고 싶어 <br>자유롭게 살고 싶어 <br>놀고 싶을 때는 놀고 <br>일하고 싶을 때만 <br>일하면서 살고 싶어 <br>친구들도 만나고 <br>여행도 많이 다니고 <br>부모님과 시간도 <br>보내면서 살고 싶어 <br>난 맘 편히 살고 싶어 <br>]]></content><category term="차우 (Chawoo)" label="차우 (Chawoo)"/><category term="점점" label="점점"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/4x/Secret_Night/</id><title>4x - Secret Night - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:15:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:15:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/4x/Secret_Night/" title="4x - Secret Night - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[혹시 내 마음 <br>들켜버릴까 난 몰라 <br>그대의 옅은 숨소리에 <br>내맘 계속 두근대 <br>터질 것 같아 열이나네요 <br>SO HOT 그대가 <br>다가올때면 <br>부드러운 손길에 <br>YOU MAKE ME 마쉬멜로우 <br>SO SWEET <br>조금씩 더 달콤하게 <br>아무도 몰래 <br>내맘 가져가요 <br>너땜에 너땜에 <br>견딜 수 없는 밤 <br>이 밤 둘만의 <br>SECRET NIGHT <br>OH OH OH OH <br>이 밤을 그대에게 줄게요 <br>TONIGHT IS SECRET NIGHT <br>TONIGHT IS SECRET NIGHT <br>이런 내 마음 <br>알고있는지 난 몰라 <br>모르는 척 말고 <br>이제 내맘을 좀 알아줘 <br>날 언제까지 기다리게 해 <br>SO HOT 그대가 다가올때면 <br>부드러운 손길에 <br>YOU MAKE ME 마쉬멜로우 <br>SO SWEET <br>조금씩 더 달콤하게 <br>아무도 몰래 <br>내맘 가져가요 <br>너땜에 너땜에 <br>견딜 수 없는 밤 <br>이 밤 둘만의 <br>SECRET NIGHT <br>OH OH OH OH <br>이 밤을 그대에게 줄게요 <br>TONIGHT IS SECRET NIGHT <br>TONIGHT IS SECRET NIGHT <br>HEY BOY <br>너 어딜 보고있니 <br>어서 내게 말해줘 <br>네 마음을 <br>TELL ME TELL ME <br>TELL ME 내게 속삭여줘 <br>LOVE ME LOVE ME <br>LOVE ME LOVE ME <br>THE SECRET NIGHT <br>너땜에 너땜에 <br>견딜 수 없는 밤 <br>이 밤 둘만의 <br>SECRET NIGHT <br>OH OH OH OH <br>이 밤을 그대에게 줄게요 <br>TONIGHT IS SECRET NIGHT <br>TONIGHT IS SECRET NIGHT <br>]]></content><category term="4x" label="4x"/><category term="Secret Night" label="Secret Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/지금_이_순간의_노래/</id><title>Wes H.Q - 지금 이 순간의 노래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:16:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:16:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/%EC%A7%80%EA%B8%88_%EC%9D%B4_%EC%88%9C%EA%B0%84%EC%9D%98_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="Wes H.Q - 지금 이 순간의 노래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너를 품에 안고 <br>시간이 멈추기를 기도했어 <br>지금 이 순간의 감동을 <br>간직할 길은 없는 걸까 <br>서로 가야 할 길을 <br>떠나가겠지 <br>그곳 어딘가에도 <br>같은 모습의 행복이 있을까 <br>우린 항상 조금 늦은 채로 <br>서로의 모습이 다른 채로 <br>그렇게 시작되는 시간의 <br>차이를 보여주며 우는 걸까 <br>이게 우리 삶일까 <br>사라진 뒤에 맞이하는 일이 <br>그래 그래서 긴 시간 <br>맺지 못하고 지금에 온 걸까 <br>널 잊지는 못해 <br>처음 본 순간을 잊지는 못해 <br>많은 날이 가도 <br>내 마음은 너의 체온을 <br>꼭 안고 있겠지 <br>너를 품에 안고 <br>시간이 멈추기를 기도했어 <br>지금 이 순간의 감동을 <br>간직할 길은 없는 걸까 <br>안녕 내 사랑아 <br>눈이 시리도록 아름다운 <br>멋진 그림처럼 이 순간을 영원히 <br>걸어두고 볼 거야 <br>내 마음에 <br>안녕 내 사랑아 <br>눈이 시리도록 아름다운 <br>멋진 그림처럼 이 순간을 영원히 <br>걸어두고 볼 거야 <br>내 마음에 <br>안녕 내 사랑아 <br>내 사랑아 <br>내 사랑아 <br>안녕 내 사랑아 <br>내 사랑아 <br>내 사랑아 <br>안녕 내 사랑아 <br>내 사랑아 <br>내 사랑아 <br>안녕 내 사랑아 <br>내 사랑아 <br>내 사랑아 <br>]]></content><category term="Wes H.Q" label="Wes H.Q"/><category term="지금 이 순간의 노래" label="지금 이 순간의 노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/달/</id><title>Wes H.Q - 달 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:16:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:16:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/%EB%8B%AC/" title="Wes H.Q - 달 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너의 뒷모습 본 적이 없어 <br>그 차가운 그늘을 숨겼지 <br>부드러운 그 미소에 취해 <br>그걸 알려고도 하지 않았지 <br>점점 멀어지네 <br>점점 멀어지네 <br>서로 마주 바라보는 것만으로 <br>우린 행복하게 살 줄 알았지 <br>내가 보고 싶은 것만 보고 있을 때 <br>얼어버린 그림자를 짊어지고 <br>점점 멀어지네 <br>점점 멀어지네 <br>사랑이 지네 <br>내 사랑이 지네 <br>그렇게 되기 위해 만난 이별도 <br>있는 건가 봐 <br>나를 보고 다르게 웃을 때마다 <br>나는 왜 알아채지 못했을까 <br>같이 걸으려 기를 쓰는 발걸음 <br>붉은색 덧칠해진 검푸른 입술을 <br>점점 멀어지네 <br>점점 멀어지네 <br>점점 멀어지고 있네 <br>멀어지는 <br>달 <br>오 저 달이 지네 <br>]]></content><category term="Wes H.Q" label="Wes H.Q"/><category term="달" label="달"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/Beautiful_X/</id><title>Wes H.Q - Beautiful X - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:16:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:16:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/Beautiful_X/" title="Wes H.Q - Beautiful X - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[거친 얼굴에 그어진 바람의 길 <br>병든 시선이 흘러간 눈물의 길 <br>잿빛 유령과 싸웠던 모험의 길 <br>이젠 지쳐 쉬는 그대를 찾으리 <br>오 나의 Beautiful X <br>흘러간 날을 만나는 꿈 <br>오 나의 Beautiful X <br>나의 하늘을 열어줄 꿈 <br>반항의 여름 보내고 남은 것은 <br>차가워진 벼랑 끝에 <br>서 있었던 위태로움 <br>그대 그림자 안에서 위로 받을 <br>맑은 소년의 마음 모두 드리리 <br>오 나의 Beautiful X <br>흘러간 날을 만나는 꿈 <br>오 나의 Beautiful X <br>나의 하늘을 열어줄 꿈 <br>그 동안 많이 외로웠겠지 <br>거대한 힘과 싸워왔던 나날들이 <br>이제는 혼자가 아니야 <br>이젠 <br>그대가 보이네 <br>오 나의 Beautiful X <br>흘러간 날을 만나는 꿈 <br>오 나의 Beautiful X <br>나의 하늘을 열어줄 꿈 <br>나의 Beautiful X <br>나의 Beautiful X <br>나의 Beautiful X <br>나의 Beautiful X <br>나의 Beautiful X <br>나의 Beautiful X <br>나의 Beautiful X <br>]]></content><category term="Wes H.Q" label="Wes H.Q"/><category term="Beautiful X" label="Beautiful X"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/가면의_스타/</id><title>Wes H.Q - 가면의 스타 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:16:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:16:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/%EA%B0%80%EB%A9%B4%EC%9D%98_%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80/" title="Wes H.Q - 가면의 스타 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘은 어떤 모습을 <br>입어야 하는 걸까 <br>새로 산 표정이나 <br>자랑이나 할까 <br>오 나는 가면의 스타 <br>속이 나오지 않게 꼭 싸매야지 <br>혹시나 삐져 나온 값이 떨어지지 <br>오 나는 가면의 스타 <br>늙지 않는 가면을 가지리라 <br>늙지 않는 가면을 가지리라 <br>늙지 않는 가면을 가지리라 <br>늙지 않는 가면을 <br>가지고 또 가지리라 <br>오 나는 가면의 스타 <br>]]></content><category term="Wes H.Q" label="Wes H.Q"/><category term="가면의 스타" label="가면의 스타"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/스무번의_봄/</id><title>Wes H.Q - 스무번의 봄 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:16:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:16:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/%EC%8A%A4%EB%AC%B4%EB%B2%88%EC%9D%98_%EB%B4%84/" title="Wes H.Q - 스무번의 봄 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가야 할 길을 잃었지 <br>시린 스무번의 봄을 보내고 <br>어지러웠던 여행길 <br>나는 무얼 보고 싶었던 걸까 <br>슬픈 로렐라이 들려오는 길 <br>오 나의 마지막이 온 것 같아 <br>너는 그 꿈을 이루어 <br>푸른 바람과 <br>살아가길 바래 <br>매혹의 로렐라이 <br>너도 듣게 되겠지 <br>그땐 더 크게 노랠 불러봐 <br>하늘로 흩어질 사랑과 <br>너의 날개를 녹여낼 눈물 <br>그 모든 아픔을 안을 때 <br>그토록 찾던 꿈이 올 거야 <br>난 이루지 못했던 <br>이 여행의 끝까지 가 <br>너는 그 꿈을 이루어 <br>푸른 바람과 살아가길 바래 <br>]]></content><category term="Wes H.Q" label="Wes H.Q"/><category term="스무번의 봄" label="스무번의 봄"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/My_Screen/</id><title>Wes H.Q - My Screen - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:16:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:16:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/My_Screen/" title="Wes H.Q - My Screen - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[창밖의 웃음들이 흘러와 <br>작은 날 휘감고 <br>어둡고 깊은 <br>공간으로 던지네 <br>어느 쪽으로 가도 <br>이상할 게 없는 어둠 <br>너무 두렵고 너무 설레 <br>어디엔가 그대가 있겠지 <br>이미 별이 돼버린 사랑 <br>모든 곳에 추억을 비추리 <br>깊고 찬란한 <br>어둠은 My screen <br>사나운 비바람이 <br>몰아치는 별이 보이네 <br>이곳에 혹시 <br>내 꿈이 숨어 있을까 <br>무서운 곳 같지만 <br>지나면 괜찮을 거야 <br>떠나온 곳도 그랬으니 <br>어디엔가 그대가 있겠지 <br>이미 별이 돼버린 사랑 <br>모든 곳에 추억을 비추리 <br>깊고 찬란한 <br>어둠은 My screen <br>긴 추억들을 <br>비추자 한곳으로 <br>숨을 막아버린 <br>검은 하늘 위로 <br>어디엔가 <br>어디엔가 그대가 있겠지 <br>이미 별이 돼버린 사랑 <br>모든 곳에 추억을 비추리 <br>깊고 찬란한 <br>어둠은 My screen <br>깊고 찬란한 <br>어둠은 My screen <br>]]></content><category term="Wes H.Q" label="Wes H.Q"/><category term="My Screen" label="My Screen"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/태양의_소리/</id><title>Wes H.Q - 태양의 소리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:16:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:16:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/%ED%83%9C%EC%96%91%EC%9D%98_%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC/" title="Wes H.Q - 태양의 소리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하늘을 밀어버린 <br>도시에 밤이 내려오네 <br>당신과 나를 셈할 시간 <br>얼마만큼의 환상을 팔았는지 <br>또 다시 들리는 태양의 소리 <br>칼날 같은 시간을 차네 <br>]]></content><category term="Wes H.Q" label="Wes H.Q"/><category term="태양의 소리" label="태양의 소리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/외계인이_주고_간_꽃/</id><title>Wes H.Q - 외계인이 주고 간 꽃 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:16:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:16:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/%EC%99%B8%EA%B3%84%EC%9D%B8%EC%9D%B4_%EC%A3%BC%EA%B3%A0_%EA%B0%84_%EA%BD%83/" title="Wes H.Q - 외계인이 주고 간 꽃 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[외계인이 내려와 <br>내게 꽃을 주고 갔네 <br>사람 붐빈 길 위에 <br>나는 얼어 버렸다네 <br>난 설명할 수는 없는 일 <br>모두 나와 거리를 두고 <br>사나운 기운의 <br>눈으로 날 보네 <br>다음 날 난 <br>내 이름을 들고 <br>발가벗겨 던져졌네 <br>도무지 알 수 없는 일 <br>죽일 듯이 털어대네 <br>왜 모두 믿으려 <br>하지를 않을까 <br>원하는 답이 <br>대체 무얼까 <br>수만가지 답을 구할 <br>머리가 난 없어 <br>오 시간은 <br>모두를 지우고 <br>꽃을 준 그도 <br>지워 질 테지 <br>그와 나와 꽃도 <br>모두 시들어 가지 <br>당신에게 가장 <br>중요한 건 무언가 <br>내가 받은 꽃의 이름이 <br>기억은 나는가 <br>당신에게 가장 <br>중요한 건 무언가 <br>내가 받은 꽃의 이름이 <br>기억은 나는가 <br>]]></content><category term="Wes H.Q" label="Wes H.Q"/><category term="외계인이 주고 간 꽃" label="외계인이 주고 간 꽃"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/One_World/</id><title>Wes H.Q - One World - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:16:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:16:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/One_World/" title="Wes H.Q - One World - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 목을 물기 전 너는 <br>가볍게 말했지 <br>C'est la vie <br>너와 같은 피를 <br>가지게 되면 <br>친구가 된다 했지 <br>당신의 목이 탐스러워 <br>당신의 목이 탐스러워 <br>당신의 목이 탐스러워 <br>당신의 목이 탐스러워 <br>눈이 빨개지고 <br>이빨이 간지러워 <br>너와 같은 <br>미끈한 모습으로 <br>사람들을 홀려 <br>여리고 하얀 목을 <br>많이 물어오라 하네 <br>One world <br>그 하나를 위해서 <br>근데 궁금한 게 생각났어 <br>그때 내 몫은 얼마나 되지 <br>당신의 목이 탐스러워 <br>그때 내 몫은 얼마나 되지 <br>당신의 목이 탐스러워 <br>그때 내 몫은 얼마나 되지 <br>당신의 목이 탐스러워 <br>그때 내 몫은 얼마나 되지 <br>당신의 목이 탐스러워 <br>]]></content><category term="Wes H.Q" label="Wes H.Q"/><category term="One World" label="One World"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/낙산_공원/</id><title>Wes H.Q - 낙산 공원 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:16:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:16:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/%EB%82%99%EC%82%B0_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9B%90/" title="Wes H.Q - 낙산 공원 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[낙산공원에 올라서면 <br>내 발끝 아래 밟힌 세상들과 <br>핏빛 노을 속에 남아 있는 <br>삶을 바라보며 <br>고이고이 접어 날려버린 <br>지난 옛사랑의 흔적과 <br>내 옆의 사랑이 주는 <br>미쳐버릴 듯한 이 외로움 <br>지치운 나를 바라보며 <br>심장을 건네준 용기 <br>하지만 그댈 밀어내는 <br>주저하고 흔들리는 내 눈빛 <br>푸르른 오늘 밤하늘 아래도 <br>얼마나 많은 낯선 사람들이 <br>처음과는 다르게 변해버린 <br>숨차는 사랑을 <br>보내고 바라보며 <br>시린 바람을 한숨 먹고 <br>내뱉지 않기 위해 <br>얼마나 울어댈까 <br>텅 빈 내 가슴을 활짝 열어 <br>심장을 건네줄 용기 <br>가지지 못한 이 시간과 <br>그대를 떠나리 <br>그대를 떠나리 그대를 떠나리 <br>그대를 떠나면 또 어디서 <br>쉴 수 있을까 <br>숨이 차오른 여기보다 <br>더 높은 곳으로 가면 <br>그대와 가진 추억들이 <br>잊혀질까 <br>텅 빈 내 가슴을 활짝 열어 <br>심장을 건네줄 용기 <br>가지지 못한 이 시간과 <br>그대를 떠 <br>그대를 떠 <br>그대를 떠나리 <br>그대를 떠나리 <br>그대를 떠나리 <br>그대를 떠나리 <br>그대를 떠나리 <br>]]></content><category term="Wes H.Q" label="Wes H.Q"/><category term="낙산 공원" label="낙산 공원"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/My_Sweet_Soul/</id><title>Wes H.Q - My Sweet Soul - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:16:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:16:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/My_Sweet_Soul/" title="Wes H.Q - My Sweet Soul - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그림자를 따라갔지 <br>Don't know why <br>검은 숲의 가운데로 <br>Takes a while <br>황금빛의 널 보았고 <br>Make me smile <br>미친 듯이 춤을 췄지 <br>You and I <br>너와 부딪치며 <br>여름을 이겼고 <br>검은 숲이 숨겨놓은 <br>Empty hole <br>서롤 빌린 계절 <br>우리만 아는 비밀 <br>네가 타버린 뒤 남은 <br>My sweet soul <br>너는 누구였을까 <br>I don't care <br>느려진 오후를 버틸 <br>Sad affair <br>검은 숲의 가운데로 <br>Need some air <br>이 밤의 추억을 담을 <br>Everywhere <br>너와 부딪치며 <br>여름을 이겼고 <br>검은 숲이 숨겨놓은 <br>Empty hole <br>서롤 빌린 계절 <br>우리만 아는 비밀 <br>네가 타버린 뒤 남은 <br>My sweet soul <br>그림자를 따라갔지 <br>Don't know why <br>검은 숲의 가운데로 <br>Takes a while <br>황금빛의 널 보았고 <br>Make me smile <br>미친 듯이 춤을 췄지 <br>You and I <br>너와 부딪치며 <br>여름을 이겼고 <br>검은 숲이 숨겨놓은 <br>Empty hole <br>서롤 빌린 계절 <br>우리만 알고 <br>네가 타버린 뒤 남은 <br>My sweet soul <br>]]></content><category term="Wes H.Q" label="Wes H.Q"/><category term="My Sweet Soul" label="My Sweet Soul"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/오늘을_닮은_밤/</id><title>Wes H.Q - 오늘을 닮은 밤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:16:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:16:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wes_HQ/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98%EC%9D%84_%EB%8B%AE%EC%9D%80_%EB%B0%A4/" title="Wes H.Q - 오늘을 닮은 밤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[조금 벗어나니 <br>밤은 더 맑고 흔적은 밝아 <br>그곳은 지금까지 <br>쉬어야 할 때를 알지 못하고 <br>오늘을 더 닮아 가고 있네 <br>오늘을 더 닮아 가고 있네 <br>내일도 오늘을 닮겠지 <br>어두웠던 적이 없으니 <br>내 이름의 의미와 <br>이 두 손의 모습은 멀어지고 <br>붉은 리본 두른 <br>내 웃음을 건넬 때도 <br>오늘을 닮았어 <br>오늘을 더 닮아 가고 있네 <br>오늘을 더 닮아 가고 있네 <br>내일도 오늘을 닮겠지 <br>어두웠던 적이 없으니 <br>이곳을 떠나자 <br>단잠을 자러 가자 <br>조금 벗어나니 <br>밤은 더 맑고 <br>내 흔적이 밝아 오네 <br>당신의 품으로 가고 있어 <br>당신의 품으로 <br>당신의 품으로 가고 있어 <br>당신의 품으로 <br>내가 편히 잘 수 있는 곳 <br>그대의 품 속으로 <br>눈부신 아침이 오는 곳 <br>]]></content><category term="Wes H.Q" label="Wes H.Q"/><category term="오늘을 닮은 밤" label="오늘을 닮은 밤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/그리고너_악단/Phone/</id><title>그리고너 악단 - Phone - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:17:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:17:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EA%B3%A0%EB%84%88_%EC%95%85%EB%8B%A8/Phone/" title="그리고너 악단 - Phone - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무 말 없이 떠나가네 <br>이렇게 비 오는 저녁에 <br>마치 이별공식처럼 <br>그래 90년대처럼 <br>이런 방식은 싫어 <br>그리워할 게 이렇게 많은데 <br>남겨진 게 무슨 죄인데 <br>다시 전화를 걸어 <br>내게 말을 해줘 <br>다시 돌아와 준다고 <br>Lady lady lady <br>Don't leave me leave me <br>leave me baby <br>다시 생각해줘 <br>내가 잘못했어 <br>나를 바라보는 <br>그 눈빛 그대로 <br>다정한 손길로 <br>남겨진 어깨 위 <br>슬픔 거두어줄래 <br>아무 말 없이 떠나가는데 <br>남겨진 게 무슨 죄인데 <br>다시 전화를 걸어 <br>내게 말을 해줘 <br>다시 돌아와 준다고 <br>Lady lady lady <br>Don't leave me leave me <br>leave me baby <br>다시 생각해줘 <br>내가 잘못했어 <br>나를 바라보는 <br>그 눈빛 그대로 <br>다정한 손길로 <br>남겨진 어깨 위 <br>슬픔 거두어줄래 <br>Lady lady lady <br>Don't leave me leave me <br>leave me baby <br>슬픔 거두어줄래 <br>]]></content><category term="그리고너 악단" label="그리고너 악단"/><category term="Phone" label="Phone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김지원/오직_주님만/</id><title>김지원 - 오직 주님만 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:17:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:17:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%80%EC%9B%90/%EC%98%A4%EC%A7%81_%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98%EB%A7%8C/" title="김지원 - 오직 주님만 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[연약한 나를 통하여 <br>찬양 받고자 하시는 주님 <br>큰 은혜에 큰 사랑에 <br>고개를 들 수가 없어요 <br>선한 것 없는 내게 <br>주를 찬양하라 말씀하시니 <br>그 감사의 내 눈물이 <br>마르지 않게 하소서 <br>내게 주셨던 은혜 <br>늘 기억하며 <br>겸손하고 담대하게 <br>내 입술의 찬양을 통하여 <br>오직 주님만 드러나기를 <br>내가 무엇이기에 주님은 <br>이렇게 넉넉한 마음으로 <br>날 품으시고 용서하시는 <br>주님의 그 사랑 한없네 <br>내게 주셨던 은혜 <br>늘 기억하며 <br>겸손하고 담대하게 <br>내 입술의 찬양을 통하여 <br>오직 주님만 드러나기를 <br>내겐 아무 능력이 없어요 <br>주님 없인 <br>아무 것도 못해요 <br>내 삶을 돌아보니 <br>나의 모든 일들이 <br>내 힘으로 한 것 <br>아님 알게 하시네 <br>내게 주셨던 은혜 <br>늘 기억하며 <br>겸손하고 담대하게 <br>내 입술의 찬양을 통하여 <br>오직 주님만 드러나기를 <br>내게 주셨던 은혜 <br>늘 기억하며 <br>겸손하고 담대하게 <br>내 입술의 찬양을 통하여 <br>오직 주님만 드러나기를 <br>오직 주님만 드러나기를 <br>]]></content><category term="김지원" label="김지원"/><category term="오직 주님만" label="오직 주님만"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/캐리_다이아몬드_Carry_Diamond/Sky_Line/</id><title>캐리 다이아몬드 (Carry Diamond) - Sky Line - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:18:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:18:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BA%90%EB%A6%AC_%EB%8B%A4%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%84%EB%AA%AC%EB%93%9C_Carry_Diamond/Sky_Line/" title="캐리 다이아몬드 (Carry Diamond) - Sky Line - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm in the sky high <br>I see the sky line <br>이 City의 빌딩은 like <br>너무나 멋진 equlizer <br>미친듯이 움직이는 <br>Car People Money Signal <br>쌓이는 부 미래의 Move <br>feel the good dem vibes more <br>We can't stop crazy signal <br>We can't stop crazy signal <br>We can't stop crazy signal <br>We can't stop crazy signal <br>Put ur hands up <br>put ur fuc**** hands up <br>Put ur hands up <br>put ur fuc**** hands up <br>Make Some Noise <br>I see the sky line <br>이 바닥에선 죽는 패 <br>벼랑 끝이라도 <br>Don't be scare <br>바닥을 겨서 너를 높게 <br>다 만들어 내는 최선책 <br>i'm a Leonardo da Vinci <br>이 system을 싹다 해부했지 <br>올리는 game 올리는 game <br>sky line 에선 내가 Main <br>We can't stop crazy signal <br>We can't stop crazy signal <br>We can't stop crazy signal <br>We can't stop crazy signal <br>Put ur hands up <br>put ur fuc**** hands up <br>Put ur hands up <br>put ur fuc**** hands up <br>Make Some Noise <br>I see the sky line <br>]]></content><category term="캐리 다이아몬드 (Carry Diamond)" label="캐리 다이아몬드 (Carry Diamond)"/><category term="Sky Line" label="Sky Line"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alpha_Da_One/Ride_Like_Me/</id><title>Alpha Da One - Ride Like Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:18:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:18:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alpha_Da_One/Ride_Like_Me/" title="Alpha Da One - Ride Like Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[창문을 다 열고 느껴 봐 달리는 차들 I ain't bluffin' <br>feelin like I'm in Cali 보이니? my car is jumpin' <br>지금 시간은 열시 시계바늘은 정지 <br>(I'mma drive all day) 땅거미가 질 때까지 <br><br>잠시도 멈추지 말고 마음을 편히 <br>좌석을 젖히고 누워봐 the handle is on me <br>광주 부산 서울까지 Crew의 맞댄 두 주먹이 <br>떨어지지 않게 so now ma big shit is poppin <br><br>open car는 아냐 but no one deals wit me <br>지나가는 딴 drivers 우릴 지켜보지 <br>I got the gospel of hiphop 또 높이 든 손 <br>like the statue of liberty no remedy <br><br>for ballers 음악을 높이곤 뜨겁게 <br>we ain't smoke we ain't drink 허나 정신없지 <br>깡패인 척 안 해도 난 국가 공인된 gangsta <br>목적지는 fan들로 붐벼 like in Terminal <br><br><br>창 밖으로 손을 내 <br>움켜 쥐는 작은 바람 <br>모두가 쳐다봐도 다들 ride like me <br><br>덜컹대는 차체에 <br>출렁이는 음악 소리 <br>모두 ride like me ride like me <br>모두 keep ridin like me <br><br><br>기나긴 길을 따라 나아가 <br>끊이지 않도록 이 모여드는 lime light <br>음악을 틀어 let's go back to 89 or 90 <br>Run DMC or SugarHill Gang이 장식하지 <br><br>Let's turn it up for the stage volume은 max 오늘만은 we rockin <br>비탈길 위 라도 keep pumpin <br>음악들 mixdown한 이 track <br>오디오가 망가지도록 틀어놓을 수 밖에 <br><br>with ma crew and homies I ain't need even a break <br>가짜 swag은 fake &amp; fake No we dont care <br>그냥 있는 대로 달려 타이어는 flat <br>어두워진 밤 허나 got light of the car <br><br>now (Vin처럼 달리고 난 Paul처럼 걸어 <br>널리 깔린 길들에 지평선은 멀어) <br>하늘이 감싸 쥔 땅이 여기 나만의 track <br>이 높이를 유지해, keep riding like me <br><br><br>창 밖으로 손을 내 <br>움켜 쥐는 작은 바람 <br>모두가 쳐다봐도 다들 ride like me <br><br>덜컹대는 차체에 <br>출렁이는 음악 소리 <br>모두 ride like me, ride like me <br>모두 keep ridin like me <br><br>Keep movin' keep ridin' <br>Keep going on and on <br>Keep movin' keep ridin' <br>Keep going on and on <br>Keep movin' keep ridin' <br>Keep going on and on <br>Keep movin' keep ridin' <br>Keep going on and on]]></content><category term="Alpha Da One" label="Alpha Da One"/><category term="Ride Like Me" label="Ride Like Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노상현/걷다/</id><title>노상현 - 걷다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:18:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:18:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EC%83%81%ED%98%84/%EA%B1%B7%EB%8B%A4/" title="노상현 - 걷다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[늘 그렇게 혼자 <br>그 자릴 지키고 <br>또 그렇게 다시 <br>만날 수가 없어도 <br>걷고 걷는 이 거리가 <br>이제는 익숙해져 <br>이제는 이 시간이 <br>어색하지 않아 <br>혼자도 잘 지내는지 <br>벌써 어색하지도 않은지 <br>그저 걷다 걷다 걷다 보면 <br>어느새 또다시 그 자리로 <br>발걸음을 옮겨 <br>네가 있던 그 자리로 가서 <br>또다시 걷다 걷다 걷다 보면 <br>또다시 그 자리로 <br>그 자리로 다시 <br>걷고 걷는 이 거리가 <br>이제는 익숙해져 <br>어느새 이 시간이 <br>어색하지 않아 <br>혼자도 잘 지내는지 <br>벌써 어색하지도 않은지 <br>그저 걷다 걷다 걷다 보면 <br>어느새 또다시 그 자리로 <br>발걸음을 옮겨 <br>네가 있던 그 자리로 가서 <br>또다시 걷다 걷다 걷다 보면 <br>또다시 그 자리로 <br>그 자리로 다시 <br>한 걸음 또 한 걸음씩 걷다 <br>너에게 다가가 <br>소리쳐 또 불러봐도 <br>그 자리 그대로 <br>그렇게 이젠 더 이상 <br>보이지가 않아 <br>그래도 걷는다 <br>그 자리 그대로 <br>혼자도 잘 지내는지 <br>벌써 어색하지도 않은지 <br>그저 걷다 걷다 걷다 보면 <br>어느새 또다시 그 자리로 <br>발걸음을 옮겨 <br>네가 있던 그 자리로 가서 <br>또다시 걷다 걷다 걷다 보면 <br>또다시 그 자리로 <br>그 자리로 다시 <br>]]></content><category term="노상현" label="노상현"/><category term="걷다" label="걷다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/여울비/마음결/</id><title>여울비 - 마음결 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:21:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:21:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%AC%EC%9A%B8%EB%B9%84/%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C%EA%B2%B0/" title="여울비 - 마음결 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[단단히 굳어진 내 마음을 <br>맘대로 빚을 수 있다면 <br>내 마음 물결 같이 <br>흘러갔으면 좋겠어 <br>비좁고 단단한 바위틈도 <br>억세고 거친 풀 사이도 <br>아무런 막힘 없이 <br>흘러 다니는 것처럼 <br>모래 같이 거친 내 마음을 <br>맘대로 빚을 수 있다면 <br>내 마음 비단 같이 <br>보드라우면 좋겠어 <br>누구의 손길이 닿더라도 <br>부드럽게 감싸 주기를 <br>누구의 어깨든지 <br>포근히 감싸 안기를 <br>누구나 반겨주는 꽃처럼 <br>해지는 저녁놀처럼 <br>내 마음 한 켠에 다 쉬어가기를 <br>내 마음 마음결 되기를 <br>단단히 굳어진 내 마음을 <br>맘대로 빚을 수 있다면 <br>내 마음 물결 같이 <br>흘러갔으면 좋겠어 <br>마음 둘 곳 없는 사람들도 <br>내 곁에서 편히 쉬기를 <br>그렇게 내 마음이 <br>마음결이 되기를 <br>정말 그럼 좋겠어 <br>]]></content><category term="여울비" label="여울비"/><category term="마음결" label="마음결"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/Everything_Will_Be_Just_Fine/</id><title>Lypura - Everything Will Be Just Fine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:27:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:27:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/Everything_Will_Be_Just_Fine/" title="Lypura - Everything Will Be Just Fine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All these days without love <br>All these days without perspective <br>All these days as I walk blind <br>Live your lives without feeling alive <br>When will this all will be fine <br>When will this all will be fine <br>As my mother always said <br>If one door closes another opens <br>When will this all will be fine <br>When will this all will be fine <br>As my brother always said <br>As my brother always said in the end everything will be just fine]]></content><category term="Lypura" label="Lypura"/><category term="Everything Will Be Just Fine" label="Everything Will Be Just Fine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/Light/</id><title>Lypura - Light - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:27:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:27:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/Light/" title="Lypura - Light - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I need myself to be the strength of widows <br>I need myself to be as fearless as intruders <br>I need reason and patience <br>I need me to be the owner of hearts who lost true love <br>I need to know that you and I will be together <br>until the last light swallows us whole <br>swallows you and me <br>if you are still believing in our dreams <br>let me be sure that I am not being erased <br>loneliness caused by despondency and vice versa <br>loneliness caused by despondency and vice versa]]></content><category term="Lypura" label="Lypura"/><category term="Light" label="Light"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/A_Fortress_-_Builder/</id><title>Lypura - A Fortress - Builder - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:28:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:28:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/A_Fortress_-_Builder/" title="Lypura - A Fortress - Builder - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Was it really worth the effort <br>when you think of it <br>was it <br>when, sometimes these days of waiting trying seem horrible to build a fortress likewise relieving <br>it is negligently packed with explosives <br>for all the times I felt queasy <br>I'm still in for it]]></content><category term="Lypura" label="Lypura"/><category term="A Fortress - Builder" label="A Fortress - Builder"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/Growing/</id><title>Lypura - Growing - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:28:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:28:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/Growing/" title="Lypura - Growing - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wished this night would never end <br>but time didn't stand still <br>cold blue fingers are giving up to warmth again <br>will I ever feel again <br>I'm too pensive to get up <br>I've left you feeling neglected <br>and so I am now <br>everyone is growing older <br>my fingers getting colder <br>I'm too sad to cry <br>I'm too sad to die]]></content><category term="Lypura" label="Lypura"/><category term="Growing" label="Growing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/A_Lost_Harmony/</id><title>Lypura - A Lost Harmony - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:28:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:28:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/A_Lost_Harmony/" title="Lypura - A Lost Harmony - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And I labor and struggle to keep this from falling apart <br>and sometimes and old richness resonates <br>And I labor and struggle to keep this from falling apart <br>I labor and struggle <br>A lost harmony I'm so worn out <br>A lost harmony I'm so worn out <br>Labor Struggle <br>A lost A loss A lost harmony I'm so worn out <br>Labor Struggle]]></content><category term="Lypura" label="Lypura"/><category term="A Lost Harmony" label="A Lost Harmony"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/Aberration_From_Path/</id><title>Lypura - Aberration From Path - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:28:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:28:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/Aberration_From_Path/" title="Lypura - Aberration From Path - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You promised me that we, too <br>would get through this together <br>this darkens everything like unkind clouds <br>four days until everything will be crashing down <br>two days later your heart stopped beating <br>your lungs ripped apart <br>your entrails eviscerated <br>you are an empty body <br>just like my mind]]></content><category term="Lypura" label="Lypura"/><category term="Aberration From Path" label="Aberration From Path"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/Weak/</id><title>Lypura - Weak - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:28:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:28:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/Weak/" title="Lypura - Weak - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You didn't look like yourself anymore <br>when I walked into this room <br>well lit are these you looked still the hands <br>so weak I learned so much from <br>the sun was pouring in <br>are these still the hands I learned so much from <br>are these still the same eyes <br>when they don't know me anymore <br>are these still the hands I learned so much from <br>I still ask myself how it feels <br>when giving up really seems like an option <br>I left you alone don't give up, don't give up <br>I left you alone don't give up, don't give up <br>Alone in this room <br>when I'd give up everything <br>I've been, would you remember me <br>I left you alone remember me, remember me <br>I left you alone remember me, remember me <br>Alone in this room <br>when I'd give up everything <br>I've been, would you remember me <br>I left you alone don't give up, remember me <br>I left you alone don't give up, remember me <br>I knew for long that this is unavoidable <br>and I still ask myself how it feels to be alone <br>and I left you alone in this room <br>but as far as I know <br>you never left me]]></content><category term="Lypura" label="Lypura"/><category term="Weak" label="Weak"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/Prerequisite/</id><title>Lypura - Prerequisite - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:28:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:28:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lypura/Prerequisite/" title="Lypura - Prerequisite - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How can I explain <br>for myself <br>without explanation <br>without any words <br>without explanation <br>without any thought <br>without explanation <br>without any words <br>without explanation <br>without love, love, love <br>no one knows but me <br>I don't know <br>don't know <br>know <br>now <br>no <br>how can I think when all thoughts are gone]]></content><category term="Lypura" label="Lypura"/><category term="Prerequisite" label="Prerequisite"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/멜로운즈/Remember/</id><title>멜로운즈 - Remember - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:28:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:28:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A9%9C%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B4%EC%A6%88/Remember/" title="멜로운즈 - Remember - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그곳에 있던 건 오직 너와 나 뿐 <br>여전히 남아 맴돌던 <br>너의 추억과 그 향기 <br>언제나 마음 졸이던 건 <br>너 아닌 나뿐 <br>잊을 수 없어 잊혀지기만 <br>바라는 그 향기 <br>그만 이제는 <br>사라져 주오 <br>그만 이제는 <br>떠나가 주오 <br>떠나가 내게서 떠나가 <br>I can never have you then <br>사라져 내게서 사라져 <br>I can never find you then <br>그만 이제는 사라져 주오 <br>그만 이제는 떠나가 주오 <br>우리의 답은 이미 그곳에 있었지 <br>외면되고 회피되어져 <br>단지 너와 날 가둬둔 그 추억 속에 <br>그렇게도 마음 졸이던 건 <br>너 아닌 나뿐 <br>그만 이제는 사라져 주오 <br>그만 이제는 떠나가 주오 <br>떠나가 내게서 떠나가 <br>I can never have you then <br>사라져 내게서 사라져 <br>I can never find you then <br>떠나가 내게서 떠나가 <br>I can never have you then <br>사라져 내게서 사라져 <br>I can never find you then <br>그곳에 있던 건 오직 너와 나 뿐 <br>여전히 남아 맴돌던 <br>너의 추억과 그 향기 <br>]]></content><category term="멜로운즈" label="멜로운즈"/><category term="Remember" label="Remember"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/잠잠한_미소/</id><title>The Unclerock - 잠잠한 미소 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:29:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:29:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/%EC%9E%A0%EC%9E%A0%ED%95%9C_%EB%AF%B8%EC%86%8C/" title="The Unclerock - 잠잠한 미소 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여기에서 우리 함께 <br>위로를 나누며 <br>잠잠한 미소를 짓네 <br>마음속엔 항상 <br>느끼며 있었지 <br>간절한 소망을 <br>얼마나 우린 이 시간을 <br>함께하려 했던가 <br>울고 웃던 시간에 <br>마음속엔 항상 <br>느끼며 있었지 <br>간절한 소망을 <br>눈감으며 찾으려 했던 행복 <br>눈을 뜨고 본건 아름다움 <br>이젠 느낄 수 있어 <br>여기에서 우리 함께 <br>위로를 나누며 <br>잠잠한 미소를 짓네 <br>고요했던 하늘은 <br>소리를 내면서 <br>촉촉히 땅을 적시네 <br>]]></content><category term="The Unclerock" label="The Unclerock"/><category term="잠잠한 미소" label="잠잠한 미소"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/갈릴리_노을/</id><title>The Unclerock - 갈릴리 노을 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:29:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:29:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/%EA%B0%88%EB%A6%B4%EB%A6%AC_%EB%85%B8%EC%9D%84/" title="The Unclerock - 갈릴리 노을 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[큰 하늘 바라보는 세계 속에 <br>하얗던 작품 하나 불타오네 <br>갈릴리로 <br>깊은 자욱하나 남은 자리 <br>작은 울타리에서 <br>바람은 불어오다 조용하고 <br>파도는 불을 피해 달려오고 <br>나에게는 <br>그의 자리 보고 싶어 소리치네 <br>작은 울타리에서 <br>아주 멀리 가고 싶은 마음 하나 <br>주고받은 얘기 속은 뜨거워져 <br>하늘 마냥 뜨거워져 가고 싶어 <br>갈릴리로 <br>Woo Woo Woo <br>이 땅은 얘기 속에 순종하고 <br>보라 빛 걸음마다 놀라우며 <br>아주 없는 얘기들 <br>지금 보여 남은 자욱 <br>갈릴리 노을에서 <br>ah <br>]]></content><category term="The Unclerock" label="The Unclerock"/><category term="갈릴리 노을" label="갈릴리 노을"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/같이_살아/</id><title>The Unclerock - 같이 살아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:29:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:29:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%B4_%EC%82%B4%EC%95%84/" title="The Unclerock - 같이 살아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[버려진 날 두고 <br>어딜 가려하는지 <br>뼈 속까지 <br>차가운 바람처럼 <br>머무는 곳 없는 <br>너는 지금 또 어디 가는가 <br>여기도 저기도 <br>너 쉴 곳 있니 <br>알 수 없는 고통 속에 <br>허덕이며 살아가고 있는가 <br>Oh Oh <br>우린 왜 저들처럼 <br>살 수 없는 가 <br>따뜻한 불 빛 아래 <br>이젠 너무 지쳐서 <br>쓰러 질 꺼야 <br>사랑의 손길 없다면 <br>나그네 나그네 <br>나그네 나그네 <br>새로워진 삶을 <br>다시 살 수 있다면 <br>고통 속에 허덕이는 <br>우리 같이 외로움에 <br>지쳐 있는 <br>사람들을 불러서 <br>같이 살아 같이 살아 <br>어 이야 어 어이야 <br>띠 따띠따따 <br>쿵따닥따 쿵따닥따 <br>띠 따띠따따 <br>쿵따닥따 쿵따다닥따 <br>어 이야 어 어이야 <br>어 이야 어 어이야 <br>]]></content><category term="The Unclerock" label="The Unclerock"/><category term="같이 살아" label="같이 살아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/Wine/</id><title>The Unclerock - Wine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:29:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:29:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/Wine/" title="The Unclerock - Wine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하고 싶었던 얘기 <br>Eum <br>또 니가 듣고 싶었던 얘기 <br>Eum <br>와인 속에 비쳐진 내 마음 <br>Eum <br>붉게 붉게 익은 물든 내 마음 <br>Eum <br>뭐든 용서 할 거야 <br>아무런 미련도 없이 <br>U Wine <br>U Wine <br>저기 저 하늘은 마냥 붉은색 <br>Wine <br>너와 난 이렇게 마주 보며 <br>Wine <br>사랑 사랑 우리들의 많은 사랑 <br>Wine <br>심심찮게 격은 우리의 다툼 <br>Wine <br>뭐든 용서 할거야 <br>아무런 미련도 없이 Ye Ye <br>말해 말해 <br>하고 싶은 얘기들 <br>가슴깊이 가슴깊이 <br>바라는 것들을 <br>말해 말해 <br>가슴 아픈 얘기들 <br>난 정말 이젠 정말 <br>다 말해 버릴꺼야 <br>뭐든 용서 할거야 <br>아무런 미련도 없이 Ae Ae <br>말해 말해 <br>하고 싶은 얘기들 <br>가슴깊이 가슴깊이 <br>바라는 것들을 <br>말해 말해 <br>가슴 아픈 얘기들 <br>난 정말 이젠 정말 <br>말해 버릴꺼야 <br>U Wine <br>U Wine <br>U Wine <br>]]></content><category term="The Unclerock" label="The Unclerock"/><category term="Wine" label="Wine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/웃음_잊지_말아요/</id><title>The Unclerock - 웃음 잊지 말아요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:29:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:29:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/%EC%9B%83%EC%9D%8C_%EC%9E%8A%EC%A7%80_%EB%A7%90%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94/" title="The Unclerock - 웃음 잊지 말아요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[행복한 시간을 위해 <br>노래하는 이여 <br>무엇이 그댈 막는다 해도 <br>웃음 잊지 말아요 <br>잊을 수 없는 <br>소중한 나의 친구여 <br>무엇이 그댈 막는다 해도 <br>웃음 잊지 말아요 <br>저기 메아리에 <br>실려 오는 노래 소리를 <br>마음을 열어 <br>들어 보세요 <br>모든 것이 그댈 위해 <br>만들어진 것 <br>아무도 그대에게서 <br>뺏을 수 없어요 <br>그건 사라질 수 없어요 <br>어둠 속 일지라도 <br>밝은 아침이래도 <br>그 소리를 <br>간직하고 있어줘 woo <br>저기 메아리에 <br>실려 오는 노래 소리를 <br>마음을 열어 들어 보세요 <br>모든 것이 그댈 위해 <br>만들어 진 것 <br>아무도 그대에게서 <br>뺏을 수 없어요 <br>그건 사라질 수 없어요 <br>어둠 속 일지라도 <br>밝은 아침이래도 <br>그 소리를 <br>간직하고 있어줘 U <br>세월 지나가도 <br>WU 메아린 <br>언제까지나 들릴 꺼야 <br>멈추지 않는 노래 <br>어디에나 <br>U <br>잊을 수 없는 <br>소중한 나의 친구여 <br>무엇이 그댈 막는다 해도 <br>그 꿈 잊지 말아요 <br>]]></content><category term="The Unclerock" label="The Unclerock"/><category term="웃음 잊지 말아요" label="웃음 잊지 말아요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/A_Man/</id><title>The Unclerock - A Man - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:29:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:29:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/A_Man/" title="The Unclerock - A Man - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A MAN <br>아하 그래 나는 A MAN <br>A MAN <br>아하 그래 너도 A MAN <br>A MAN <br>그래 너도 나도 A MAN <br>A MAN <br>우리 새 세상을 맞이해 <br>나는 최면술사 나는 최면술사 <br>넌 이미 걸려있지 <br>넌 이미 걸려있지 <br>나를 부인해봐 나를 부인해봐 <br>더 깊이 빠질 거야 <br>더 깊이 빠질 거야 <br>사랑을 느껴봐 사랑을 느껴봐 <br>사랑을 느껴봐 사랑을 느껴봐 <br>아무것도 두렵지 않는 <br>아무것도 두렵지 않는 <br>사랑을 느껴봐 사랑을 <br>느껴봐 <br>느껴봐 <br>느껴봐 <br>새로운 움직임이 있어 <br>가까이 오는 것 가까이 오는 것 <br>더 가까이 오는 변화를 느껴봐 <br>온갖 식물도 느끼는 <br>그런 느낌 말고 <br>온갖 동물도 느끼는 <br>그런 느낌 말고 <br>A MAN A MAN <br>A MAN A MAN <br>A MAN A MAN <br>A MAN A MAN <br>A MAN <br>A MAN <br>이제 열려지는 세상 <br>A MAN <br>너와 내가 만들어가는 세상 <br>A MAN <br>니도 너도 나도 A man <br>A MAN <br>우리 새 세상을 맞이해 <br>느껴봐 <br>느껴봐 <br>새로운 움직임이 있어 <br>가까이 오는 것 가까이 오는 것 <br>더 가까이 오는 변화를 느껴봐 <br>A MAN A MAN <br>A MAN A MAN <br>A MAN A MAN <br>A MAN A MAN <br>A MAN A MAN <br>]]></content><category term="The Unclerock" label="The Unclerock"/><category term="A Man" label="A Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/갈증/</id><title>The Unclerock - 갈증 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:29:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:29:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/%EA%B0%88%EC%A6%9D/" title="The Unclerock - 갈증 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ah Ah Ah Ah <br>거리엔 많은 사람이 있네 <br>하늘엔 하얀 구름이 있네 <br>다른 모습으로 <br>언제나 변해가는 세상 <br>새로운 위로를 받기 위해 <br>만들어가네 <br>갈증으로 가득 찬 이곳엔 <br>또 다른 허상을 만들어만 가고 <br>진정한 자유가 필요한 이곳엔 <br>또 다른 구속들만이 늘어 가네 <br>Ah Ah Ah Ah <br>Ah Ah Ah Ah <br>모든 게 과해버린 세상 <br>사랑보다 커져버린 것들 <br>뿐이네 <br>갈증으로 가득 찬 이곳엔 <br>또 다른 허상을 만들어만 가고 <br>진정한 자유가 필요한 이곳엔 <br>또 다른 구속들 만이 늘어가네 <br>Ah 내가 필요한 건 <br>Ah 다른 게 아니야 <br>Ah 사랑만이 이 갈증을 <br>Ah 해소할 수 있을 거야 <br>Ah Ah Ah Ah <br>]]></content><category term="The Unclerock" label="The Unclerock"/><category term="갈증" label="갈증"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/솥_바꾸로_오소_부제__삶의_후렴/</id><title>The Unclerock - 솥 바꾸로 오소 (부제: 삶의 후렴) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:30:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:30:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Unclerock/%EC%86%A5_%EB%B0%94%EA%BE%B8%EB%A1%9C_%EC%98%A4%EC%86%8C_%EB%B6%80%EC%A0%9C__%EC%82%B6%EC%9D%98_%ED%9B%84%EB%A0%B4/" title="The Unclerock - 솥 바꾸로 오소 (부제: 삶의 후렴) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[솥 바꾸로 오소 <br>냄비 바꾸로 오소 <br>쌔리 다 찌그진 <br>솥이나 냄비 바꾸로 오소 <br>고물 TV나 라디오 사요 <br>아줌마요 머하능교 <br>고물 갖고 와서 <br>양은 그릇 바까가소 <br>다 깨싸진 쓰레기통이나 <br>못쓰는 바가지 갖고 오소 <br>쌔리 다 깨싸진 쓰레기통이나 <br>못쓰는 바가지 갖고 오소 <br>솥 바꾸로 오소 냄비 바꾸로 오소 <br>솥 바꾸로 오소 냄비 바꾸로 오소 <br>기분이 어떨 땐 <br>모여질 때가 있어 그럴 땐 <br>사방에 뭔가를 찾고 싶지 않나 <br>채소와 과일을 놓은 <br>작은 가게들이 있고 <br>그 옆엔 생선들과 <br>조그만 잡화도 널려있지 <br>골목길을 돌아 가다 보면 <br>작은 시장 하나가 나오는데 <br>여기저기에다 자리 깔고 <br>물건들을 팔고 있다 <br>산나물 캐다 파는 할머니는 <br>머리 머리 속에 <br>막걸리 생각 가득하고 <br>저기 저 멀리서 들려오는 <br>그윽한 삶의 후렴 삶의 후렴 <br>후렴 후렴 후렴 후렴 <br>Ha 골목길을 <br>돌아 가다 보면 보면 <br>작은 시장 하나가 나오는데 <br>여기저기에다 자리 깔고 <br>물건들을 팔고 있다 <br>산나물 캐다 파는 할머니는 <br>머리 머리 속에 <br>막걸리 생각 가득하고 <br>저기 저 멀리서 들려오는 <br>그윽한 삶의 후렴 삶의 후렴 <br>후렴 후렴 후렴 후렴 <br>난 왠지 화려한 네온들 보다 <br>복잡한 시장의 모습이 좋을까 <br>요란한 소리 <br>질서 없이 들려오지만 <br>소박한 마음 느낄 수 있어 <br>우 우 어릴 적 일들이 자꾸 생각나 <br>동전 하나로 배불리 먹었던 <br>풍성한 시장의 먹거리 생각나 <br>아아이야 <br>야이야이야이야이야 이야 <br>엄마 따라 엄마 따라 <br>왔던 아이 아이 <br>긴 머리 긴 머리 <br>그 아이 아이 그 아이 아이 <br>그 아이가 생각나 <br>Ha 골목길을 <br>돌아가다 보면 보면 <br>작은 시장 하나가 나오는데 <br>여기저기에서 자리 깔고 <br>물건들을 팔고 있다 <br>산나물 캐다 파는 할머니는 <br>머리 머리 속에 <br>막걸리 생각 가득하고 <br>저기 저 멀리서 들려오는 <br>그윽한 삶의 후렴 삶의 후렴 <br>후렴 후렴 후렴 후렴 <br>솥 바꾸로 오소 <br>냄비 바꾸로 오소 <br>양산계란이 왔습니다 <br>화장지 한 다발에 750원 <br>공장생산 가격으로 <br>판매하고 있습니다 <br>알이 통통하고 껍질 야무집니다 <br>아줌마요 머하능교 <br>고물 갖고 와서 <br>양은그릇 바까가소 <br>사이소 <br>]]></content><category term="The Unclerock" label="The Unclerock"/><category term="솥 바꾸로 오소 (부제: 삶의 후렴)" label="솥 바꾸로 오소 (부제: 삶의 후렴)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안소은/꿈이로다/</id><title>안소은 - 꿈이로다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:38:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:38:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%80/%EA%BF%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%A1%9C%EB%8B%A4/" title="안소은 - 꿈이로다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꿈이로다 꿈이로다 <br>꿈이로다 꿈이로다 <br>그대와의 이별이 꿈이로다 <br>꿈깨이니 또 꿈이요 <br>깨인꿈도 꿈이련만 <br>꿈에나서 꿈에 살고 <br>꿈에 죽어가는 인생 <br>사랑하는 그대 그대 <br>그 꿈속에서 볼 수 있기를 <br>봇물처럼 깊으리라 <br>가을 달처럼 놓으리라 <br>별처럼 빛나리라 <br>돌처럼 굳으리라 그대 <br>보고싶고 그리울 때 <br>꿈이 아니면 어이보리 <br>꿈이라고 생각을 말고 <br>자주 보이면 <br>그대와의 일생을 함께 보내리 <br>꿈이로다 꿈이로다 꿈이로다 <br>사랑하는 그대 그대 <br>그 꿈속에서 볼 수 있기를 <br>봇물처럼 깊으리라 <br>가을 달처럼 놓으리라 <br>별처럼 빛나리라 <br>돌처럼 굳으리라 그대 <br>나의 사랑 그리운님 <br>꿈이 아니면 어이보리 <br>꿈이라고 생각을 말고 <br>그대 내게 있어주면 <br>일생을 함께 보내리 <br>꿈이로다 꿈이로다 꿈이로다 <br>꿈이로다 꿈이로다 <br>그대와의 이별이 꿈이로다 <br>꿈이로다 꿈이로다 <br>]]></content><category term="안소은" label="안소은"/><category term="꿈이로다" label="꿈이로다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안소은/희로애락_눈물타령/</id><title>안소은 - 희로애락 눈물타령 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:38:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:38:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%80/%ED%9D%AC%EB%A1%9C%EC%95%A0%EB%9D%BD_%EB%88%88%EB%AC%BC%ED%83%80%EB%A0%B9/" title="안소은 - 희로애락 눈물타령 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[맨몸으로 험한 세상 태어나서 <br>일단 뻑적지근하게 울었것다 <br>배고파서 울고 똥쌌다고 울고 <br>지 엄마는 우는 모습 쳐다보며 <br>맴 아파서 울고 걱정 되서 울고 <br>어떻게 해줄까 몰라서 우네 <br>눈물 나게 기쁜 세상 <br>눈물 나게 슬픈 세상 <br>기뻐서 울고 열 받아서 울고 <br>짠 해서 울고 즐거워서 울어 <br>좀 더 자라 동무들과 어울리면 <br>얻어터져서 울고 서운해서 울고 <br>혼나서 울고 챙피 해서 우네 <br>사랑을 하면서도 삐져서 울고 <br>헤어져서 울고 다시 만나 울고 <br>차서 울고 차여서도 우네 <br>눈물 나게 기쁜 세상 <br>눈물 나게 슬픈 세상 <br>기뻐서 울고 열 받아서 울고 <br>짠 해서 울고 즐거워서 울어 <br>기뻐서 울고 열 받아서 울고 <br>짠 해서 울고 즐거워서 울어 <br>이렇듯이 우리네 인생사 <br>기뻐서도 울고 슬퍼서도 울고 <br>기쁨 노여움 슬픔 즐거움 속에 <br>살아가는디 <br>인간이 백 년을 산다고 해도 <br>병든 날과 잠든 날 <br>걱정근심을 다 제하고 나면 <br>단 사십도 못살 인생 <br>한번 사는 인생 <br>아까운 청춘이 가기 전에 <br>희로애락으로 즐겁게 지내보자 <br>기뻐서 웃고 열 받아도 웃고 <br>짠 해도 웃고 즐거워서 웃어 <br>기뻐서 웃고 열 받아도 웃고 <br>짠 해도 웃고 즐거워서 웃어 <br>쾌지나 칭칭나네 <br>쾌지나 칭칭나네 <br>쾌지나 칭칭나네 <br>쾌지나 칭칭나네 <br>]]></content><category term="안소은" label="안소은"/><category term="희로애락 눈물타령" label="희로애락 눈물타령"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안소은/가시리오/</id><title>안소은 - 가시리오 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:38:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:38:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%80/%EA%B0%80%EC%8B%9C%EB%A6%AC%EC%98%A4/" title="안소은 - 가시리오 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[빗 소리 바람 소리 <br>이 모든 게 님의 소리 <br>내 가슴 속 깊이 있는 <br>그대 추억들과 흔적이 <br>살아 숨쉬고 있죠 <br>그대 가시리오 가시리오 <br>놓으리오 놓으리오 <br>그대 가시리오 놓으리오 <br>그대 가시는 길 <br>행복하게 빌어 드리리오 <br>아무리 지우려고 해도 <br>지울 수 없는 흔적 <br>그대 그리며 살죠 <br>그대 가시리오 가시리오 <br>놓으리오 놓으리오 <br>그대 가시리오 놓으리오 <br>그대 가시는 길 행복하게 <br>저 달과 저 별이 <br>내 맘 같이 밝게 <br>비춰 드리리오 <br>그대 가시리오 가시리오 <br>놓으리오 놓으리오 <br>그대 가시리오 놓으리오 <br>그대 가시는 길 <br>행복하게 빌어 드리리오 <br>아 아 아 <br>빌어 드리리오 <br>]]></content><category term="안소은" label="안소은"/><category term="가시리오" label="가시리오"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안소은/새야새야_파랑새야/</id><title>안소은 - 새야새야 파랑새야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:38:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:38:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%80/%EC%83%88%EC%95%BC%EC%83%88%EC%95%BC_%ED%8C%8C%EB%9E%91%EC%83%88%EC%95%BC/" title="안소은 - 새야새야 파랑새야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새야 새야 파랑새야 <br>녹두 밭에 앉지 마라 <br>새야 새야 파랑새야 <br>높이 높이 날아라 <br>새야 새야 날아라 <br>새야 새야 날아라 <br>높이 높이 날아라 <br>새야 새야 날아라 <br>너의 꿈을 향해 <br>높이 날아라 <br>파랑 빛이 아름다운 <br>너의 모습 보여라 <br>너의 꿈을 향해 <br>높이 날아라 <br>새야 새야 파랑새야 <br>새야 새야 파랑새야 <br>새야 새야 날아라 <br>새야 새야 날아라 <br>높이 높이 날아라 <br>새야 새야 날아라 <br>너의 꿈을 향해 <br>높이 날아라 <br>너의 빛나는 꿈을 위해 <br>높이 높이 날아라 <br>푸른 하늘에 너의 빛이 <br>더 빛나도록 <br>빛이 나는 새야 <br>높이 나는 새야 <br>]]></content><category term="안소은" label="안소은"/><category term="새야새야 파랑새야" label="새야새야 파랑새야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안소은/널_그리다/</id><title>안소은 - 널 그리다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:38:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:38:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%80/%EB%84%90_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EB%8B%A4/" title="안소은 - 널 그리다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그리다 널 그리다 <br>그리다 널 그리다 <br>연분홍 저고리 <br>남길동 소매 <br>나 입기 좋고요 <br>너 보기 좋구나 <br>그리다 널 그리다 <br>그리다 널 그리다 <br>가마채 잡고서 <br>힐난 질 말고 <br>나 시집 간데로 <br>엄살이 오소래 <br>그리다 널 그리다 <br>그리다 널 그리다 <br>나 시집 간데로 <br>엄살이 오면 <br>때 묻은 버선에 <br>볼 받아 줌세나 <br>그리다 널 그리다 <br>그리다 널 그리다 <br>담장 밑에다 <br>집 짓고 살아도 <br>그리워 살기는 <br>매일반이로다 <br>그리다 널 그리다 <br>그리다 널 그리다 <br>그리다 널 그리다 <br>그리다 널 그리다 <br>널 그리다 널 <br>그리다 널 그리다 <br>]]></content><category term="안소은" label="안소은"/><category term="널 그리다" label="널 그리다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안소은/사랑가/</id><title>안소은 - 사랑가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:38:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:38:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%80/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EA%B0%80/" title="안소은 - 사랑가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이리 오너라 업고 놀자 <br>이리 오너라 이리 오너라 <br>업고 놀자 이리 오너라 <br>이리 오너라 업고 놀자 <br>이리 오너라 사랑 사랑 <br>내 사랑 내 사랑이야 <br>사랑 사랑 내 사랑 <br>내 사랑이로구나 <br>사랑 사랑 내 사랑아 <br>그대 내 사랑 <br>그대 내 사랑이로다 <br>이리 보아도 내 사랑 <br>저리 보아도 내 사랑 <br>아무리 보아도 내 사랑 <br>그대는 나의 사랑 <br>그대 그대 생각 만으로 <br>그대 생각만으로 <br>나는 행복해 <br>그대 내곁에 <br>있어줘서 고마워요 <br>모든 것 주고 싶은 그대 <br>그대는 내 사랑 나의 사랑 <br>그대 그대 생각 만으로 <br>그대 생각만으로 <br>나는 행복해 <br>그대 내곁에 <br>있어줘서 고마워요 <br>모든 것 주고 싶은 그대 <br>영원히 함께 해요 <br>그대는 나의 사랑 <br>나의 사랑 나의 사랑 <br>세상이 내게 준 <br>가장 멋진 선물 <br>그대 세상이 내게 준 <br>가장 멋진 선물 <br>그대 나의 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="안소은" label="안소은"/><category term="사랑가" label="사랑가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안소은/다시_만날_그때/</id><title>안소은 - 다시 만날 그때 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:38:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:38:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%80/%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C_%EB%A7%8C%EB%82%A0_%EA%B7%B8%EB%95%8C/" title="안소은 - 다시 만날 그때 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[먼 길 달려온 지금 <br>아직 마음에 님은 남아 <br>다시 나를 멈추게 하고 <br>멀리 떠나온 이 길에 <br>님의 흔적 곳곳에 남아 <br>아직 나를 슬프게 하네 <br>그곳 어딘가에서 <br>나를 보는 별이 되어 <br>밝게 빛나고 있는지 <br>그곳 어딘가에서 <br>이별 없이 행복하게 <br>살고 있는지 <br>님아 내님아 <br>사랑하는 내님아 <br>아련한 추억 속에 <br>웃고 있는 님아 <br>님아 내님아 <br>사랑하는 내님아 <br>우리 다음 생애 <br>다시 만나면 <br>아픔 없는 세상에서 <br>슬픔 없는 세상에서 <br>다시 만나길 <br>아 님아 내님아 <br>사랑하는 내님아 <br>아련한 추억 속에 <br>웃고 있는 님아 <br>님아 내님아 <br>사랑하는 내님아 <br>우리 다음 생애 <br>다시 만나면 <br>아픔 없는 세상에서 <br>슬픔 없는 세상에서 <br>다시 만나길 <br>님아 내님아 <br>사랑하는 내님아 <br>아련한 추억 속에 <br>웃고 있는 님아 <br>님아 내님아 <br>사랑하는 내님아 <br>우리 다음 생애 <br>다시 만나면 <br>아픔 없는 세상에서 <br>슬픔 없는 세상에서 <br>다시 만나길 <br>그곳 어딘가에서 <br>이젠 나를 <br>기억하지 못 하더라도 <br>그곳 어딘가에서 <br>이젠 나를 <br>기다리지 않아도 <br>이미 내맘에 <br>그댄 별이 되었네 <br>]]></content><category term="안소은" label="안소은"/><category term="다시 만날 그때" label="다시 만날 그때"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안소은/倚閭之望歌_의려지망가/</id><title>안소은 - 倚閭之望歌 의려지망가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:38:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:38:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%80/%E5%80%9A%E9%96%AD%E4%B9%8B%E6%9C%9B%E6%AD%8C_%EC%9D%98%EB%A0%A4%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%9D%EA%B0%80/" title="안소은 - 倚閭之望歌 의려지망가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람이 지나 <br>눈을 감으면 <br>아련했던 순간이 <br>가슴속을 스치고 <br>하루 또 하루 <br>세월이 흘러 <br>움켜잡은 기억을 <br>하나둘씩 펴보네 <br>검붉은 바다 <br>휘휘 돌아서 <br>멀고 또 먼 길을 가네 <br>일렁이는 물결 <br>잠시라도 멈추어 주면 <br>님 편히 갈까 <br>노란 꽃이 하얗게 지면 <br>내 마음 눈물 꽃 피네 <br>훠이 새야 님 보거든 <br>잘 가거라 전해주오 <br>뒤돌아보면 보일 것 같아 <br>내리는 빗속에 <br>우두커니 서있네 <br>하루 또 하루 <br>세월이 흘러 <br>혹시라도 내 생각 <br>부디 하지 마소서 <br>혹시라도 내 생각 <br>부디 하지 마소서 <br>]]></content><category term="안소은" label="안소은"/><category term="倚閭之望歌 의려지망가" label="倚閭之望歌 의려지망가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안소은/아리랑_내님이_있는_그곳/</id><title>안소은 - 아리랑 내님이 있는 그곳 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:38:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:38:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%80/%EC%95%84%EB%A6%AC%EB%9E%91_%EB%82%B4%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%B4_%EC%9E%88%EB%8A%94_%EA%B7%B8%EA%B3%B3/" title="안소은 - 아리랑 내님이 있는 그곳 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아리랑 아리랑 아리랑 <br>고개를 넘어 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아리랑 <br>고개를 넘어 <br>내님이 있는 그곳으로 <br>나는 넘어가리 <br>내님이 있는 그곳 <br>내님이 있는 그곳으로 <br>나는 가리 넘어 넘어 가리 <br>그곳 나는 넘어가리 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아리랑 <br>고개를 넘어 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아리랑 <br>고개를 넘어 <br>내님이 있는 그곳으로 <br>나는 넘어가리 <br>너 어 어어 <br>너 어 어어 어 <br>너 어 어 어 어 어어 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아리랑 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아리랑 <br>아리랑 아리랑 <br>꽃향기 가득한 그곳 <br>내님이 머무는 그곳 <br>추억이 가득한 그곳 <br>그립고 보고 싶은 내님 <br>내님이 있는 그곳으로 <br>나는 넘어 가리 <br>내님이 있는 그곳으로 <br>나는 넘어 가리 <br>]]></content><category term="안소은" label="안소은"/><category term="아리랑 내님이 있는 그곳" label="아리랑 내님이 있는 그곳"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안소은/갈까부다/</id><title>안소은 - 갈까부다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:38:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:38:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%80/%EA%B0%88%EA%B9%8C%EB%B6%80%EB%8B%A4/" title="안소은 - 갈까부다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[갈까부다 갈까부다 <br>임 따라서 갈까부다 <br>그대가 있는 그곳 <br>어딘지 알 수는 없지만 <br>오늘도 그대의 생각에 <br>눈물이 나네 <br>바람도 쉬어 넘고 <br>구름도 쉬어 넘는 <br>해동청 보라매 <br>다 쉬어 넘는 다 쉬어 넘는 <br>동설령 고개라도 <br>하늘의 직녀성은 <br>은하수가 막혔어도 <br>일년 일도 보건만은 <br>우리님 계신 곳은 <br>무슨 물이 막혔간디 <br>이다지도 오 오 못 보는고 <br>일년 일도 보건만은 <br>우리님 계신 곳은 <br>무슨 물이 막혔간디 <br>이다지도 오 오 못 보는고 <br>갈까부다 갈까부다 <br>임 따라서 갈까부다 <br>]]></content><category term="안소은" label="안소은"/><category term="갈까부다" label="갈까부다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안소은/신사철가/</id><title>안소은 - 신사철가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:38:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:38:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%80/%EC%8B%A0%EC%82%AC%EC%B2%A0%EA%B0%80/" title="안소은 - 신사철가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한달 두달 석달 흘러 흘러 <br>한 절기 지나가면 봄이로세 <br>봄이 오면 이산 저산 꽃놀이 가세 <br>가세 가세 어서 가세 봄맞이 가세 <br>봄이 왔네 봄이 왔네 <br>봄이 왔네 봄이 왔네 <br>앞동산 진달래는 <br>송이송이 방긋 웃고 <br>뒷동산 꾀꼬리는 <br>아름답게 노래하고 <br>우리네들 가슴속에 새 봄이 왔네 <br>한달 두달 석달 흘러 흘러 <br>한 절기 지나가면 여름 일세 <br>여름 오면 물놀이 가세 <br>고기잡이 가세 <br>가세 가세 어서 가세 <br>고기잡이 가세 <br>여름 왔네 여름 왔네 <br>여름 왔네 여름 왔네 <br>여름 여름 여름 여름 여름이 왔네 <br>여름 오면 도라지 꽃 <br>어여쁘게 웃음짓고 <br>벌 나비도 좋아라 춤을 추고 <br>보슬비 뚜르르르르 <br>내리는디 단꿈만 꾸네 <br>한달 두달 석달 흘러 흘러 <br>한 절기 지나가면 가을 일세 <br>가을 오면 이산 저산 <br>단풍놀이 가세 <br>유정한 친구 벗네와 <br>단풍놀이 가세 <br>가을이 왔네 가을이 왔네 <br>가을이 왔네 가을이 왔네 <br>황파만경 오곡물결 <br>넘실넘실 파도치네 <br>달 밝은 밤 목동들에 <br>피리소리 구성지다 <br>우리 모두 다 같이 춤을 추세 어이 <br>이렇듯이 봄이 오면 <br>이산 저산 꽃놀이도 가고 <br>여름 되면 물놀이도 허고 <br>가을되면 단풍구경과 춤도 추고 <br>겨울은 또 어떠헌고 <br>삼천리 이 강산에 <br>백설이 휘날리며 <br>송이 송이 송이마다 백발이니 <br>어찌 아니 즐거울 수 있겠느냐 <br>춘하추동 사시절이 좋을씨구 <br>모진 바람 눈서리에 <br>거침없는 저 송죽아 <br>눈송이는 은빛인데 <br>너는 어이 푸르더냐 <br>가세 가세 어서가세 <br>사철놀이 찾어가세 <br>가세 가세 어서가세 <br>사철놀이 찾어가세 <br>너도나도 찾어가세 <br>사철놀이 찾어가세 <br>춘하추동 좋을씨구 <br>우리강산 좋을씨구 <br>삼천리 이 강산에 좋을씨구 <br>]]></content><category term="안소은" label="안소은"/><category term="신사철가" label="신사철가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안소은/춘향아리/</id><title>안소은 - 춘향아리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:38:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:38:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%80/%EC%B6%98%ED%96%A5%EC%95%84%EB%A6%AC/" title="안소은 - 춘향아리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아리랑 아리랑 아라리요 <br>아리랑 고개로 넘어 간다 <br>내가 만일 임 못 본채 <br>옥중의 혼이 되어도 <br>생각나는 것은 <br>보고 싶은 임뿐이라 <br>춘향 마음 그 누가 알아주리 <br>생각나는 것은 <br>보고 싶은 임뿐이라 <br>내가 만일 임 못 본채 <br>옥중의 혼이 되어도 <br>생각나는 것은 <br>보고 싶은 임뿐이라 <br>춘향 마음 그 누가 알아주리 <br>생각나는 것은 <br>보고 싶은 임뿐이라 <br>춘향 마음 그 누가 알아주리 <br>생각나는 것은 <br>보고 싶은 임뿐이라 <br>생각나는 것은 <br>보고 싶은 임뿐이라 <br>나를 버리고 가시는 임은 <br>십 리도 못 가서 발병 난다 <br>십 리도 못 가서 발병 난다 <br>]]></content><category term="안소은" label="안소은"/><category term="춘향아리" label="춘향아리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Speakerbox/</id><title>Wiley - Speakerbox - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:39:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:39:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Speakerbox/" title="Wiley - Speakerbox - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[That's where we are <br>right now fam <br>And like everyone <br>in your crew is just like <br>tunnel vision <br>It's family <br>it's what we care about or nothing <br>Like literally <br>there is no money <br>that record labels can <br>offer us no more it's dead <br>It's just there's no point <br>I've achieved tings <br>I was dreamin' of <br>Step on the stage <br>start reelin' off <br>Yo when I'm goin' <br>better see me off <br>Well not everybody's <br>gonna be the boss <br>If you look into my face <br>gonna see a boss <br>If you look into the crowd <br>you will see a mosh <br>Do my ting like Marley <br>and Peter Tosh <br>It's Eskiboy <br>in your speakerbox <br>I know my name's bigger <br>than I make out <br>I used to push buj <br>with the flake out <br>We had the first 110s <br>that ever came out <br>I would book a New York flight <br>get the plane out <br>Wanna get my name out <br>we ain't got the same clout <br>Went through a bag of shit <br>that they're payin' out <br>I had my watch <br>and my bracelet <br>and chains out <br>Realised that's dead <br>right then is when had <br>to get my brain out <br>We ain't on the same shit <br>I'm tellin' everyone <br>we don't shot the same brick <br>You got the pellets <br>I'm a grime kid <br>Face it the pavement knows me <br>basically everythin' <br>I know it showed me <br>Blud we ain't <br>from the same strip <br>On my strip nah look <br>get a face lift <br>Drugs on the staircase <br>drugs in the bait lift <br>every day I weight lift <br>Cops and robbers <br>wanna take it <br>I hate it <br>I've achieved tings <br>I was dreamin' of <br>Step on the stage <br>start reelin' off <br>Yo when I'm goin' <br>better see me off <br>Well not everybody's <br>gonna be the boss <br>If you look into my face <br>gonna see a boss <br>If you look into the crowd <br>you will see a mosh <br>Do my ting like Marley <br>and Peter Tosh <br>It's Eskiboy <br>in your speakerbox <br>Made my street money <br>then I done a Phaze One <br>Me and Danny S decide <br>to make one <br>Club banger street banger <br>on the stations <br>Gettin' played every day <br>it's in heavier rotation <br>I'm nationwide by now <br>people see the energy <br>and take some <br>Stars in the sky yeah <br>I made some <br>But how could <br>I be here without <br>Biggin' up Maxwell <br>and Luke and Jason <br>Yo hear me on the sets <br>'cause I grace 'em <br>Me and Dizzee made <br>it an occupation <br>Came from a council estate <br>I know 'em all <br>you can name 'em <br>I was outside in the cold <br>it was rainin' <br>Standin' on stairs chattin' <br>shit about the pagans <br>Nuttin' don't phase us <br>nuttin' don't phase 'em <br>You got a top boy on your side <br>Nobody rates him <br>I'm chillin' like <br>I've achieved tings <br>I was dreamin' of <br>Step on the stage <br>start reelin' off <br>Yo when I'm goin' <br>better see me off <br>Well not everybody's <br>gonna be the boss <br>If you look into my face <br>gonna see a boss <br>If you look into the crowd <br>you will see a mosh <br>Do my ting like Marley <br>and Peter Tosh <br>It's Eskiboy <br>in your speakerbox <br>I've achieved tings <br>I was dreamin' of <br>Step on the stage <br>start reelin' off <br>Yo when I'm goin' <br>better see me off <br>Well not everybody's <br>gonna be the boss <br>If you look into my face <br>gonna see a boss <br>If you look into the crowd <br>you will see a mosh <br>Do my ting like Marley <br>and Peter Tosh <br>It's Eskiboy <br>in your speakerbox <br>De wole ah wan' can't test <br>when I wile out <br>I ain't gotta have a gang <br>when I ride out <br>I just get my mind right <br>then I slide out <br>'Cause if you're bait <br>one don will talk <br>and everybody's <br>gonna find out <br>I can bring a style out <br>Showcase the style <br>I put a vibe out <br>Pass me the water <br>I got a dry mouth <br>After that I spray a couple fire <br>bars <br>make a shook spitter hide out <br>They ain't got the same drive <br>Do my ting at night <br>or in the day time <br>Don't matter what time it is <br>I make time <br>And I have a Haze time <br>and a break time <br>In a dance gyal <br>a wine up your waistline <br>Everybody goin' mad <br>to the bassline <br>Sippin' on a one drink <br>at the same time <br>I power up around April <br>and May times <br>then I have a great time <br>I've achieved tings <br>I was dreamin' of <br>Step on the stage <br>start reelin' off <br>Yo when I'm goin' <br>better see me off <br>Well not everybody's <br>gonna be the boss <br>If you look into my face <br>gonna see a boss <br>If you look into the crowd <br>you will see a mosh <br>Do my ting like Marley <br>and Peter Tosh <br>It's Eskiboy <br>in your speakerbox <br>There's no point in sayin' <br>these numbers to us anymore <br>because we've seen them yeah <br>So now everyone's head's <br>on puttin' this thing on the map <br>in a way that all the kids <br>of today never have to go <br>through what we went through <br>]]></content><category term="Wiley" label="Wiley"/><category term="Speakerbox" label="Speakerbox"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kathryn_Joseph/The_Coming/</id><title>Kathryn Joseph - The Coming - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:39:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:39:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kathryn_Joseph/The_Coming/" title="Kathryn Joseph - The Coming - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[growed a baby in her in the stead of me <br>baby it was in her and you <br>lay still in me oh my god won't help me <br>cos I'm doned wrong and <br>rightly all the leaves of fallen cover <br>what is passed the coming <br>and the calling of what this is at last <br>oh my god won't help me <br>cos I'm doned wrong and rightly]]></content><category term="Kathryn Joseph" label="Kathryn Joseph"/><category term="The Coming" label="The Coming"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kathryn_Joseph/The_Blood/</id><title>Kathryn Joseph - The Blood - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:39:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:39:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kathryn_Joseph/The_Blood/" title="Kathryn Joseph - The Blood - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[cock and bone is all it took for <br>my love to be mis put like a light <br>out in the dark darker hole of <br>darker heart like a load off in my <br>mouth and un wanted after birth <br>and i hear your babys here your <br>babys here your babys hear your <br>babies like a mouth full salt and <br>sweet and you wanted me to eat <br>like a light out in the dark dark <br>er whole of darker parts like a <br>ship all in did sail to the death <br>of tooth and nail and I hear your <br>babys here your babys here your <br>babys hear your babies and the <br>wind will blow and the seed be <br>sown and the made of blood is the <br>only loved]]></content><category term="Kathryn Joseph" label="Kathryn Joseph"/><category term="The Blood" label="The Blood"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/The_Message_Album_Ver_Feat_Mary_J_Blige__Rell/</id><title>Dr. Dre - The Message (Album Ver.) (Feat. Mary J. Blige &amp; Rell) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:43:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:43:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/The_Message_Album_Ver_Feat_Mary_J_Blige__Rell/" title="Dr. Dre - The Message (Album Ver.) (Feat. Mary J. Blige &amp; Rell) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This one is for my brother, Tyree, RIP <br>A message to God <br><br>Since you finishing em early, what possessed you to start him <br>We made a vow later we'll regret til death do us part <br>Lord, I thought we was made for each other <br>You shouldn't connect those, made to be taken away from each other <br>Now what I'm supposed to do I'm only half the man that I was <br>I'll never last, cause my better half is up there with you <br>You knew what you was doing when you made us, so with all due respect <br>You coulda forgave him, you didn't have to take him <br>He can take the game with him, cause he defines the word <br>The one who puts the G in it, who you think put me in it <br>I'm feeling like my whole world is blinded, wondering why <br>Crying, pouring out my heart, pouring out liquor behind it <br>We fought like brothers, something we never should do <br>We coulda used time spent arguing telling the truth <br>He had talent too I had plans on watching him grow <br>Don't know what hurts more, seeing him leave, or watching him go <br><br>Listen, listen, listen Listen <br>Listen, listen, listen Better listen <br>Listen, listen, listen <br>Listen <br><br>If you wan' know why Why I live my life <br>The way that I do Cause I got to get this money <br>So don't worry about me Cause I know my way around <br>I'm just hustlin' everyday, runnin' this race, makin' this paper <br><br>You's a soldier, you're probably packing heat up there <br>Met up with homies from the street, and got deep up there <br>If you only knew the way I felt before they ruined the crew <br>I thought I learned from Eazy, now I'm going through it with you <br>We lost a thug, a son, and a father <br>I spoke to your son, the other day, and told him Uncle Dre got him <br>The Lord must be accidentally pulling your file <br>Cause I'm still paging you, 911, straight in denial <br>Prayin' you get it, but no man can choose the card he was dealt <br>You either quit, or you gon' play it like you get it <br>I done been through all emotions, from in shock, to keeping a poker face <br>To straight breaking down and showing all emotions <br>I'm anxious to believe in real G's don't cry <br>If that's the truth, then I'm realizing I ain't no gangsta <br>It's just not me, but you know I'mma always ride wit you <br>I miss you, sometimes I wish I just died with you <br><br>Listen, listen, listen Listen <br>Listen, listen, listen Better listen <br>Listen, listen, listen <br>Listen7469635 <br><br>If you wan' know why Why I live my life <br>The way that I do Cause I got to get this money <br>So don't worry about me Cause I know my way around <br>I'm just hustlin' everyday, runnin' this race, makin' this paper <br><br>Listen <br>If you don't know why I you gotta listen up right now <br>Listen, listen, listen, listen <br>Listen, listen <br>Listen, listen, children, listen <br>I'm tryin to tell you somethin' good <br>Don't get caught up in the hood, yeah <br>If you don't know why <br>You gotta find out the reason why <br>Brother, brother <br><br>Oh, you're Doctor Dre Ha ha, are you a real doctor dude <br>I mean like, you know, can you prescribe some drugs for me man <br>Come on dude, I'll split whatever I get with ya, okay Hahahaha <br>Ah, the chronic]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="The Message (Album Ver.) (Feat. Mary J. Blige &amp; Rell)" label="The Message (Album Ver.) (Feat. Mary J. Blige &amp; Rell)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Bang_Bang_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman__Knoc-Turnal/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Bang Bang (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Knoc-Turn`al) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:43:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:43:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Bang_Bang_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman__Knoc-Turnal/" title="Dr. Dre - Bang Bang (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Knoc-Turn`al) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Everywhere I go, all I ever seem to hear is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>No matter where I go, all I ever seem to see is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>Everywhere I go, all I ever seem to hear is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>No matter where I go, all I ever seem to see is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br><br>Everyday it's the same thing, LA ain't changed <br>Niggas still playa hating, but Dre ain't changed <br>I'm just a lot smarter now <br>Cause these niggas is banging ten times harder now <br>Niggas bringing they ass up in the wrong part of town <br>Better turn their car around <br>Rolling the window down Hey can we talk it out <br>Nah, get the fuck out <br>Johnny got a shotgun <br>And he ain't even strong enough to cock one <br>Fuck trying to job hunt <br>Niggas got AK's <br>Niggas is way crazier than Dre was back in his NWA days <br>Niggas spray strays and shoot without looking <br>Niggas walk by and blast, without leaving a footprint <br>I think the attitudes are twice as worst <br>It takes half the time to get your whole life reversed <br>Always trying to play Rambo with they ammo <br>Make a nigga wanna stay in family mode <br><br>Everywhere I go, all I ever seem to hear is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>No matter where I go, all I ever seem to see is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>Everywhere I go, all I ever seem to hear is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>No matter where I go, all I ever seem to see is <br>BANG BANG <br><br>Late nights is full of lead that whistles as it goes by <br>Murder arrives, anytime <br>Bullets take flight when the fo' five ignites <br>Some hearts skip a beat, some get blew out, and never re light <br>With you in the site of youngsters with automatics <br>Busting on shit to lay everything down even tourists to non affiliates <br>These days, gun play is official with green lights on every block <br>Though the sign tells you too it's not best to stop <br>On every corner, Cali niggas are dumping <br>You'll be shaking your soul loose from the box at the coroner's <br>Making death not so foreign to ya <br>Niggas got Rugers and M14's with enough ammo to leave <br>An armored truck Swiss cheese <br>I've learned to stay away from house parties <br>I've seen too many go and end up absent without leaving <br>Ain't no warm welcomings <br>My eyes have witnessed the bend in on <br>Nights that don't sleep, and fireworks until dawn <br><br>Everywhere I go, all I ever seem to hear is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>No matter where I go, all I ever seem to see is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>Everywhere I go, all I ever seem to hear is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>No matter where I go, all I ever seem to see is <br>BANG BANG <br><br>Now tell me, what the fuck is this man <br>Niggas doing brothers in worse than the Klan <br>Can't even stand <br>In front of your building and chill without yielding <br>Twelve year old children that kill, blood spilling <br>Thugs be illing, unnecessary slugs filling the sky <br>Usually drilling the one that wasn't willing to die <br>Yes sir, in the Killing Field I got my life preserver <br>And I'll do my time for murder <br>These niggas got the nerve to question me <br>'Bout the colors that I got on <br>I see that red dot on your knot <br>'Bout to get your whole crew shot on <br>A Soldier of Fortune, I'm the wrong man to plot on <br>Took him out on the spot before he even got on my hit list <br>Peep this <br>I cock back, you bow down <br>Bust round, bloody the ground <br>Retaliation sounds like this <br><br>Everywhere I go, all I ever seem to hear is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>No matter where I go, all I ever seem to see is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>Everywhere I go, all I ever seem to hear is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>No matter where I go, all I ever seem to see is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>Everywhere I go, all I ever seem to hear is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>No matter where I go, all I ever seem to see is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>Everywhere I go, all I ever seem to hear is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG <br>No matter where I go, all I ever seem to see is <br>BANG BANG BANG BANG]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Bang Bang (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Knoc-Turn`al)" label="Bang Bang (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Knoc-Turn`al)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Ackrite_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Ackrite (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:43:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:43:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Ackrite_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman/" title="Dr. Dre - Ackrite (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's fuckin ackrite <br>Question is can I get some Know what I'm saying <br>Ack rite, bitch <br>When I see you in the spot, you just act right, you know what I'm saying <br>When I yank you by the fuckin' arm <br>Don't be looking at a nigga crazy <br>Just give up the digits and be the fuck out, you know what I'm saying <br>Let me break it down for y'all <br><br>It was just one of those days <br>When I wanted to catch sunrays <br>It's fun to gitt blunted on a Sunday afternoon <br>Nigga Bathed and got groomed, grabbed the gat for misbehavors <br>And the chocolate flavored boom, lost in hip hop tunes <br>Zoom zoom like the Commodores <br>Wonder will we have drama or, end up clowning whores <br>Round up four good to go girls <br>Like them Barbary Coast girls, riding shotgun, baby <br>I be postin all world in the ride <br>Sipping 151 done gave me too much pride to back down <br>Soon as we get to The Beach I'mma put my fuckin mack down <br>I'm playin lead, not the background <br>It's time to put Bronson on the map now <br>Walk with my hand on my Johnson, crack a smile <br>Cuties peep my style, if I don't get some ackrite <br>I'mma have to ack wild <br><br>Blunt in my left hand, drink in my right <br>Strap by my waistline, cause niggas don't fight <br>Sucker free for life, so you better think twice <br>Aight And a give a nig' some ackrite <br>I'm the type of nigga playa haters don't like <br>Snatchin' up your honey for some late night hype <br>And snobby ass bitches get slapped out of spite <br>Aight So give a nig' some ackrite, right <br><br>Uhhhhh drink kicking in, I'm stimulated <br>For those that don't know big words I'm FUCKIN FADED <br>Eighty three degrees, ease to a shaded spot <br>Our first spot was cool till some gangsters made it hot <br>Now we plot and pose <br>Plus we watchin hoes, with lots of flesh exposed <br>Getting swarmed by those type of niggas <br>With no game but brown nose <br>So I impose only like pros can <br>Yo, is this your man No <br>Grab the bitch's hand, I'm Hittman <br>Bling Gold chain gleam <br>You're very eligible for my summer league team <br>Maybe too extreme cause the sister got steamed <br>Then Miss Thing tried to scream on my brethren <br>I got mad, spit phlegm on the name <br>Stefan, tattooed on her arm <br>Ho you ain't the bomb, must be a dyke <br>Gitcho' lips swoll, or give a nig' some ackrite <br><br>Blunt in my left hand, drink in my right <br>Strap by my waistline, cause niggas don't fight <br>Sucker free for life, so you better think twice <br>And a give a nig' some ackrite <br>I'm the type of nigga playa haters don't like <br>Snatchin' up your honey for some late night hype <br>And snobby ass bitches get slapped out of spite <br>So give a nig' some ackrite, right <br><br>Fronting on the ack rite, causing me to act up <br>Good Samaritans save that ho from getting slapped up <br>My homies crack up at the scene I made <br>Yo my actions ain't serene when a nigga's on fade <br>If it wasn't for the one time brigade <br>I woulda sprayed at the hooker tramp <br>As cops parade I'm afraid it's time to break camp <br>Make tracks, where else can we go to take hoes <br>From fake macks *CAR HORN* Aiyyo, chase them girls <br>In that black Maxima, the passenger, almost fractured her <br>Neckbone, looking back at us <br>Plus, they on the dick cause the Caddy's plush <br>They blush, I bumrush the huss, with the largest crush <br>Try to swing an ep tonight so I don't have to keep in touch <br>Keep it on hush without the tippin' <br>Macking interrupted by some niggas set tripping <br>Clip in the strap, I showed these niggas how to act <br><br>Blunt in my left hand, drink in my right <br>Strap by my waistline, cause niggas don't fight <br>Sucker free for life, so you better think twice <br>And a give a nig' some ackrite <br>I'm the type of nigga playa haters don't like <br>Snatchin' up your honey for some late night hype <br>And snobby ass bitches get slapped out of spite <br>So give a nig' some ackrite, right]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Ackrite (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman)" label="Ackrite (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Housewife_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman__Kurupt/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Housewife (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Kurupt) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:43:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:43:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Housewife_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman__Kurupt/" title="Dr. Dre - Housewife (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Kurupt) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Now this, this is one of them occasions <br>Where the homies not doin it right <br>I mean he found him a ho that he like <br>But you can't make a ho a housewife <br>And when it all boils down you gonna find in the end <br>A bitch is a bitch, but a Dogg is a man's best friend <br>So what you found you a ho that you like <br>But you can't make a ho a housewife wife <br><br>I mostly sold dick while I packed a gold clip <br>Worked my money maker, she got paper, she bout to trip <br>Where the fuck is my money I cannot G guilty <br>You pimpin strong, but comin home, to sheets that be filthy <br>She on the dillzy, I take advantage <br>All up in them panties, I got this bitch speakin Spanish <br>I'm mannish get yo' nails out my back <br>Slut I'm bout to nut and get up, go scrub yo' cat <br>Learn the player rules, this is how a player do <br>Might not be a freak, but she got on the choosin shoes <br>Dollar signs are folded, I can't control it <br>Tryin to leave her, beeper just exploded <br>She sweatin me, won't let me, broad turned fraud <br>Now she on this dick huh, got her turnin tricks huh <br>Man it's a trip I don't trip I'm in yo' Lexus flexin <br>I left her up in Dallas, Texas, ass down <br><br>Now this, this is one of them occasions <br>Where the homies not doin it right <br>I mean he found him a ho that he like <br>But you can't make a ho a housewife <br>And when it all boils down you gonna find in the end <br>A bitch is a bitch, but a Dogg is a man's best friend <br>So what you found you a ho that you like <br>But you can't make a ho a housewife wife <br><br>Naw ho ain't short for honey, almost had to wail her like Bunny <br>Tellin tales of bein pregnant, catchin Nordstrom sales with abortion money <br>I spotted her, seen her with my nigga when I shot at her <br>Now we got beef, he caught up in the ho's erotica <br>Exotic she's psychotic, rockin his Nautica <br>Soon he'll need antibiotics sucka bitch <br>Name a sexual disease, she got it like Sam Goody <br>You be like, Damn how could she hit me off with chlamydia <br>Fool I pity ya <br>We live in the city of ballers <br>With more bounce and in a Zapp, she will doo wa ditty ya <br>Prettier to grittier, the wittier can get her <br>To the Hotel, Niko, on some Sauve shit like Rico <br>That's when I caught a Vision like Coleco <br>A high post ho, a perfect way for me to keep dough <br>Huh, have her sellin ass on Bronson Ave and Pico <br><br>At the ho tel, mo tel, or the Holiday Inn say what nigga <br>I said if that bitch keep fuckin up beotch then we'll fuck her friends <br>I said I dip, dive, what can I say <br>Niggas need to stop fuckin with OJ <br>Some niggas bang Blood, some niggas bang Crip <br>And bitches ain't shit but hoes and tricks <br>I had a dream of hoes, I had to screen my hoes <br>I seen my hoes in all kinds of clothes <br>Lil' Almond Joy, I truly enjoy <br>If you blew my balls, right through my drawers <br>Come back to the mansion, chill at the spot <br>From the way she was blowin, I know she does it a lot <br>I have a eight and a half, nine and three quarters <br>The ho started callin when I started boss ballin <br>Gimme some head, gimme some ass uh huh <br>Gimme some cash, pass it to Daz <br>Pass it to Snoop, or pass it to Nate <br>See hoes eat dick like eggs and steak <br>It ain't shit new, I thought you knew what <br>I knew you would, you wish you could <br>Break a G down, break me down <br>But I'mma see you on the rebound what what DP style <br><br>Now this, this is one of them occasions <br>Where the homies not doin it right <br>I mean he found him a ho that he like <br>But you can't make a ho a housewife <br>And when it all boils down you gonna find in the end <br>A bitch is a bitch, but a Dogg is a man's best friend <br>So what you found you a ho that you like <br>But you can't make a ho a housewife wife]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Housewife (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Kurupt)" label="Housewife (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Kurupt)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Pause_4_Porno_Album_Ver_Edited/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Pause 4 Porno (Album Ver.) (Edited) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:43:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:43:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Pause_4_Porno_Album_Ver_Edited/" title="Dr. Dre - Pause 4 Porno (Album Ver.) (Edited) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ya'll ready to get nasty <br>Yeah <br>Shit Yeah Oh <br>Damn Oh, that pussy is good tho <br>Oh, shit <br>It's good <br>Oh Oh <br>Fuck, you hurtin' me bitch Oh shit <br>Oh Oh, yeah you're da bitch, beotch <br>Fuck <br>Oh Oh shit <br>You're hurtin' me <br>Damn <br>You're hurtin' me <br>Damn Oh <br>Damn <br>You're makin' my pussy sore, bastard Oh shit <br>Oh, my nuts <br>Aww, Fuck me Oh Fuck <br>Oh shit yo' face Oh <br>Oh, damn, damn, damn, oh, shit, oh <br>Fuckin in my eyes, bastard <br>Shit Ohhh Ohhh DAMN <br>Oh, shit I can't see Ohhh <br>Oh, shit Oh, shit <br>Fuck Whore Ahhh <br>Damn, that shit was good <br>Ahhh, oh shit <br>Ohhh, my god <br>Ohhhh ohhhh ohhhh <br>Damn <br>Oh, that shit feels so good <br>Ohhh ohhh ohhh <br>Shit <br>Oh, get the fuck up Oh, get the fuck up now <br>Oh you fucked the shit out of us <br>Fuckin' big dick bastard Oh shit Aight <br>Oh shit Aight, chill, chill, chill, give me five minutes, damn <br>Well, get the fuck up <br>Jake, hurry up, cause you know I gotta get home to my nigga cause you know <br>You know you gots to get some at home, hahaha <br>You know I'm lovin that big <br>Ooooh, shit <br>Ha ha what You got a problem <br>Man, fuck your man, know what I'm sayin <br>I'm Jake Steed Bitch <br>What Who you callin' a bitch <br>You Bitch]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Pause 4 Porno (Album Ver.) (Edited)" label="Pause 4 Porno (Album Ver.) (Edited)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Some_LA_Niggaz_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman_Ms_Roq_Knoc-Turnal_Time_Bomb_Koka_Kambon_Defari_MC_Ren__Xzibit/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Some L.A. Niggaz (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Ms. Roq, Knoc-Turn`al, Time Bomb, Koka Kambon, Defari, MC Ren &amp; Xzibit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:43:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:43:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Some_LA_Niggaz_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman_Ms_Roq_Knoc-Turnal_Time_Bomb_Koka_Kambon_Defari_MC_Ren__Xzibit/" title="Dr. Dre - Some L.A. Niggaz (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Ms. Roq, Knoc-Turn`al, Time Bomb, Koka Kambon, Defari, MC Ren &amp; Xzibit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah nigga, MC Ren up in this motherfucker <br>West West y'all <br>Yeah, LA niggas <br>LA niggas rule the world nigga <br>Y'all niggas gotta recognize, yaknahmsayin <br>Niggas don't wanna peep game, yaknahmsayin <br>But this shit come all the way back around here <br>My nigga Dre, droppin' heat box on y'all bitch ass <br>Yaknahmsayin You gotta recognize <br>LA niggas, connected all over the motherfucking world, nigga <br>Recognize this peep game <br><br>Now in my younger days I used to sport a rag <br>Backpack full of cans plus a four four mag <br>G'd up from the feet up <br>Blue'd up from the shoe up's how I grew up <br>Loc'n, smokin' and drinkin' til we threw up threw up <br>At Leimert Park, taggin', hittin' fools up <br>Ditching my class, just to fuck yo' school up <br>You don't wanna blast, nigga tuck yo' tool up <br>But don't sleep, y'all niggas quick to shoot you <br>Now there's another motherfucker with no future <br>But Time Bomb much smoother when I maneuver, dope like Cuba <br>Got em jumpin Disciples to the Hoover <br><br>I'm coming Straight Outta Compton with a loose cannon <br>Smoke big green, call it Bruce Banner <br>Watch your manners, at last another blast from the top notch <br>From way back with the pop rocks, I pop lock witcha <br>Picture this, Dr Dre twisting wit Tha Liks <br>And Hittman bought a fix <br>Don't trip, it's a Time Bomb in this bitch <br>Here it tick tick tick tick *BOOM* <br>Wait a minute it's on, I tell it like a true mackadelic <br>Weed and cocaine sold separate, check it <br>From sundown to sunup clown and run up <br>The Aftermath'll be two in your gut, nigga what <br><br>We roll deep, smoke on weed drink and pack heat <br>Requirements for survival each day in LA <br>It don't stop, we still mash in hot pursuit from the cops <br>Analyze why we act this way in LA <br><br>Gimme that mic fool, it's a West coast jack move <br>They call me Hitt cause I spit like gats do <br>Cock me back <br>Bust caps for my Macz Crew, at Fairfax <br>Who used to wear Air Max shoes, that's true <br>But I grew up where niggas jack you, harass you <br>Blast you, for that set you claim where you from <br>Mash on you for your Turkish chain, CK BK <br>Blue'd up or flame, I ran wit a gang <br>I helped niggas get, jacked for they Dana Dane's <br>My pants hang below my waistline <br>I look humble wanna rumble yeah yeah <br>I bang though, like Vince Carter from the baseline <br>Don't waste my time <br>Fuck a scrap in killa Cali, AK's and 9's <br>One time's, sun shines, and fine ass bitches <br>Hawaiian Thai, drive bys, six fo's on switches <br><br>I was raised in the hood called WHAT THE DIF' <br>Where the brothers in the hood, refused to go Hollywood <br>Slugs for the fuck of it <br>Anybody hatin' on us can suck a dick <br>If I catch you touching mine you catch a flat line, dead on the floor <br>Better than yours, driving away gettin' head from a whore <br>It's AvireX to the Z <br>Fuckin' with me might get you banned from TV <br>Cassette and CD it's all mine the whole nine the right time <br>Multiply, we don't die, the streets don't lie <br>What, so neither do I, I'm bad for your health <br>Like puttin' a pistol up to your face and blastin' yourself <br><br>Five in the mornin', burglars at my do' <br>Glock forty five in my dresser drawer <br>Let 'em come in BLAOW he see the thunder roll <br>Roll with niggas, who buy fifths by the fo' <br>And brew's by the case <br>SLAP YOU in the face with the bass, Dr Dre laced <br>Likwit Kings wit Sedans and gold rings <br>Haters fold the style, but can't find no openings <br><br>We roll deep, smoke on weed drink and pack heat <br>Requirements for survival each day in LA <br>It don't stop, we still mash in hot pursuit from the cops <br>Analyze why we act this way in LA <br><br>In LA <br><br>That's how we ride <br>That's how we ride <br>That's how we ride <br>That's how we ride]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Some L.A. Niggaz (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Ms. Roq, Knoc-Turn`al, Time Bomb, Koka Kambon, Defari, MC Ren &amp; Xzibit)" label="Some L.A. Niggaz (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Ms. Roq, Knoc-Turn`al, Time Bomb, Koka Kambon, Defari, MC Ren &amp; Xzibit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Ed-Ucation_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman__Ms_Roq/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Ed-Ucation (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Ms. Roq) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:43:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:43:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Ed-Ucation_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman__Ms_Roq/" title="Dr. Dre - Ed-Ucation (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Ms. Roq) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Aww they say uhh <br> a black man is a pimp <br>Well let me tell you the biggest pimp <br>On planet motherfuckin Earth, is her momma <br>It's her MOMMA that told her <br>Get a man that got a good job gurl <br>Make sure he got a good car gurl <br>Make sure he can take you out and buy you somethin gurl <br>What happened to just fallin in love with a nigga with a bus pass <br> just cause you love the nigga <br>But I'm the pimp motherfucker <br>I gotta be the player <br><br>Biggest hoes, on planet Earth <br> are walkin through the motherfuckin neighborhood <br>You KNEW when you got with the nigga he already had a woman <br>You knew he already had a family <br>But you fucked him anyway <br>And then when you thought you gon' lose the nigga <br>You went and got pregant didn't you bitch, DIDN'T YOU <br>THE OL' KEEP A NIGGA BABY <br>And then when the nigga ain't around, what do you tell the child <br>Aww that nigga ain't shit, that's why yo' daddy ain't here <br>Cause that nigga ain't shit <br>How bout bein a woman, and tellin the kid the truth <br>That yo' momma, you was a ho <br>TELL THE KID <br>Momma was a ho, I was weekend pussy <br>I had you to keep the nigga, it didn't work out <br>That's why he ain't here but he a good nigga <br>Cause he take care of his REAL family <br>I was just a dumb bitch, tryin to keep, a nigga that I wanted]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Ed-Ucation (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Ms. Roq)" label="Ed-Ucation (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Ms. Roq)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Murder_Ink_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman__Ms_Roq/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Murder Ink (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Ms. Roq) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:43:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:43:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Murder_Ink_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman__Ms_Roq/" title="Dr. Dre - Murder Ink (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Ms. Roq) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When darkness be closin in <br>I motivate, with the howlin wind <br>With a list of chosen men, frozen in sin <br>Knowin that your end is beginnin <br>Swift silent and deadly <br>There's no defending my plots, I know your every movement <br>For six months I watch, coulda gotchu at your baby's mother's house <br>Even at your down low weed spot <br>But the backdrop, wasn't flattering enough <br>I didn't want people gathering and stuff ? <br>Snapshots of blood splattering from the snuff <br>Here puff this here, while I figure which way, to split yo' wig <br>Right now you as nervous, as a Farmer John pig <br>As I dig into my tragic bag, take out the HK <br>Twist on the silencer, insert the thirty shot mag ? <br>Bullet stuck to his brain like a magnet <br>Skull in fragments, I leave the cleanup to Dragnet <br><br>This is anybody MURDERAHHH <br>To fuckin everybody MURDERAHHH <br>Nigga all y'all MURDERAHHH <br>Uh, uh, for real <br>You'll fuck around and get killed <br>This is anybody MURDERAHHH <br>Motherfuckin everybody MURDERAHHH <br>Yeah nigga all y'all MURDERAHHH <br>Uh, uh, for real <br>You'll fuck around and get killed <br><br>Peeped all the stash drop and exchange of the dough <br>Lurkin through the turf, think how I'mma just work <br>Give em chase to the crib and yo he properly laced <br>Stepped out the car, put my steel, to the side of his face <br>Murder this the fuckin Case, rob this nigga and shake <br>The fuckin spot cause in a few it's gon' be crawlin with cops <br>Who's the bad bitch now, you crept on, paid the piper <br>Who'da thought a sexy bitch could be a murderous sniper <br>Detrimental to your health, shoulda learned yo' lesson <br>But it's too late nigga bye bye, better count yo' blessings <br>I been watchin you watchin me, yeah you ballin <br>Was, nigga now you finger fucked and steady fallin <br>A thug wit no love, but bitch niggas die fast <br>Thug niggas die young oh what you thought you would last <br>Blast two shots to the dome, slide back to the pad <br>And jack my nigga off, til his dick get soft <br>Resume the wifey boo shit, cause yo my man don't know <br>That his bitch is straight ill, servin ass with fo'fo' <br><br>I'm a motherfuckin MURDERAHHH <br>Bitch this is anybody MURDERAHHH <br>Yeah nigga all y'all MURDERAHHH <br>Uh, uh, for real <br>You'll fuck around and get killed <br>I'm a motherfuckin MURDERAHHH <br>Uhh bitch this is anybody MURDERAHHH <br>Yeah nigga all y'all MURDERAHHH <br>Uh, uh, for real <br>You'll fuck around and get killed]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Murder Ink (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Ms. Roq)" label="Murder Ink (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman &amp; Ms. Roq)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/The_Car_Bomb_Album_Ver_Edited/</id><title>Dr. Dre - The Car Bomb (Album Ver.) (Edited) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:44:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:44:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/The_Car_Bomb_Album_Ver_Edited/" title="Dr. Dre - The Car Bomb (Album Ver.) (Edited) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And now, the car bomb <br><br>Yo, re re, come on man, let's get the fuck up out of here, man <br>All right baby, all right speedy, I'm coming, damn <br>Took a motherfuckin' hour to get dressed <br>I told you I was gonna be here over this motherfucker <br>I wanna be in and out, now, don't fuck around over here <br>And baby, I'm lookin' good, all right, I'm lookin' good <br>I'm sayin', fuck that man, I'm tryin' to get the fuck up out of here, man <br>All right, all right, I'm comin' damn shit <br>Yo, yo, yo, hold it, hold it, whassup, this shit <br>You know the people right there <br>You know those motherfuckers right there <br>No nigga, I don't know, you paranoid <br>What the fuck they lookin' at I'm sayin' you ain't seen <br>The motherfuckers ridin' past lookin' all at me and shit <br>Nigga, you trippin', now you trippin', nigga you trippin' <br>Let's go, scary ass nigga you high or somethin', let's keep <br>Man, fuck that man, get in the car, man aw, goddamn <br>Told you don't fuck around over here and shit <br>Whatever <br>Uh uh <br>Damn, what the fuckin' up with this shit <br>You didn't put no gas in this raggedy motherfucker, goddamn <br>I just got a tune up the other day, man, my shit and all that <br>Hahaha, ain't this a bitch, pined out Pete let's keep, oh my goodness <br>Man, shut the fuck up, let me start my motherfuckin' shit <br>Fuck you, nigga, take me]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="The Car Bomb (Album Ver.) (Edited)" label="The Car Bomb (Album Ver.) (Edited)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Bi____Ni__az_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman_Six-Two__Snoop_Dogg/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Bi*** Ni**az (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Six-Two &amp; Snoop Dogg) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:44:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:44:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Bi____Ni__az_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman_Six-Two__Snoop_Dogg/" title="Dr. Dre - Bi*** Ni**az (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Six-Two &amp; Snoop Dogg) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Some good ass weed <br>Check it out Dog this game is a motherfuckin' trip man <br>Word on the streets, everybody always tryin' to run up on me hollerin' about <br>Word on the streets is, this nigga said this <br>Man, I don't give a fuck about what that nigga said man <br>That's what's wrong with you niggas <br>You niggas is just like bitches <br>Ho ass niggas, talk too motherfuckin' much Speak <br>Stay to your own, get your own you know what I'm saying' <br>Be independent, nigga <br>Biatch <br><br>Yeah <br>Bitch niggas Bitch niggas <br>Bitch niggas Bitch niggas <br>Bitch ass niggas Beotch <br>Bitch niggas Bitch niggas <br>Yeah, I'm talkin' about you Beotch <br>Bitch niggas <br>And you too Biatch <br>Hmm, Dogg <br><br>I meet mo' bitch niggas than hoes, look here <br>And I really don't know, but that's just how it go damn <br>Dogg, so many niggas like to keep up shit <br>And just like a bitch beotch niggas be talkin' shit nigga <br>Smilin' in my face and then they blast me in the back ka ka ka ka ka <br>Niggas stay strapped from way back, cause paybackwill <br>Make niggas wanna pop that shit <br>If you ain't ready for the game uh uh nigga stop that shit <br>We rock that shit, my nigga Dre, drop that shit right <br>No mo' talkn', I'm walkin' and I'm poppin' the clip <br>Glock on the hip, set trippin', drippin' and shit <br>If you act like a bitch nigga nigga you get smacked like a bitch <br><br>Bitch niggas, bitch niggas Bitch niggas <br>There niggas don't know what the fuck is goin' on <br>Yo Dogg, check it, kick back <br>Let me holler at these niggas for a minute <br><br>Straight off the streets of chaos and no pity <br>The aggravated, makin' these punk motherfuckers hate it <br>Compton is the city I'm from <br>Can't never leave the crib without a murder wea pon <br>Huh, I can't live my life on broke no mo' <br>And most of these fools ain't shit but cutthroats <br>They smile in a nigga face, and for what <br>They got the game all fucked up, and want my thing fucked up <br>I done learned a lot, seen a whole lot <br>The top notch nigga, I'm fiendin' for that spot <br>Now peep game on what Six Deuce told me <br><br>These niggas after yo' paper, Dr D R E wha <br>And these punk ass hoes is lookin' for dough <br>You gotta watch your homeboys, cause a nigga never know <br>Oh, they'll be around, but when yo' paper get low <br>Just like Master P said, There they go, there they go <br>Bitch niggas uh huh <br><br>Attention all personnel <br>Stop scheamin', and lookin' hard <br>Stop scheamin', and an, and an an, and and lookin' hard <br><br>Bitch nigga, a bitch nigga <br>Bitch nigga, hella bitch nigga <br>You's a bitch nigga, motherfucker bitch nigga <br>A bitch nigga a bitch nigga <br>A bitch nigga <br><br>I know yo' type, so much bitch in you, if it was slightly darker <br>Lights was little dimmer my dick be stuck up in yo' windpipe <br>Hmm, you'd rather blow me than fight, I'm from the old school <br>Like Romey Rome homey yo, you owe me the right <br>To slap you, like the bitch that you are, been wantin' to cap you <br>Every since you was mad doggin' me with that bitch in yo' car <br>Fool, Who do you think you are Mr Big Stuff <br>Man, you shit on Hitt, get yo' shit bust, plus <br>Pistol whipped, cover it up, use yo' bitch's blush <br>Mr Powder Puff yo', bark ain't loud enough, huh <br>I know Chihuahuas that's mo' rah rah, ha ha <br>I have to laugh Dre, I bet he take bubble baths <br>You don't want no trouble with the Aftermath staff, trust me <br>Doggy Dogg, Diggy Doctor plus me <br>No you's a busta slash hussy, soft as a hush puppy <br>Must we break you down to estrogen most hated specimen <br>A bitch nigga <br><br>Stop scheamin', and lookin' hard <br>Stop stop stop scheamin', and lookin' hard <br>Stop stop ah op op stop sch sch scheamin' and lookin' hard <br>Stop stop ah op op stop sch sch scheamin' and lookin' hard <br>Stop scheamin' an an an an an and lookin' hard???????????????? <br>Stop scheamin', and lookin' hard <br>Stop schea scheamin', and lookin' hard <br>Stop scheamin', and and and stop scheamin', and lookin' hard]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Bi*** Ni**az (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Six-Two &amp; Snoop Dogg)" label="Bi*** Ni**az (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Six-Two &amp; Snoop Dogg)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Lets_Get_High_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman_Ms_Roq__Kurupt/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Let`s Get High (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Ms. Roq &amp; Kurupt) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:44:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:44:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Lets_Get_High_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman_Ms_Roq__Kurupt/" title="Dr. Dre - Let`s Get High (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Ms. Roq &amp; Kurupt) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All these niggas and all these hoes in here <br>Somebody here gon' fuck <br>All these niggas and all these hoes in here <br>Somebody here gon' fuck <br>All these niggas and all these hoes in here <br>Somebody here gon' fuck <br>All these niggas and all these hoes in here <br>Somebody here gon' fuck <br><br>Talking that, walking that, spitting at hoes <br>Smoking this, drinking that, gittin' at hoes <br>Fuck this I'm hitting that I'm hitting em both <br>Have one riding dick, one licking my toes <br>When I'm loving these hoes there ain't no love involved <br>No hugs, no kisses <br>Bear rugs, bare britches <br>Rare bitches like them hoes in them Blacktail pictures <br>Bitch jumped off my dick <br>Is that Dre over there <br><br>Yeah, I just took some Ecstasy <br>Ain't no telling what the side effects could be <br>All these fine bitches equal sex to me <br>Plus I got this bad bitch laying next to me <br>No doubt, sit back on the couch <br>Pants down, rubber on, set to turn that ass out <br>Laid the bitch out, then I put it in her mouth <br>Pulled out, nutted on a towel and passed out <br><br>Come on let's get high, high <br>Let's get high, high <br>Come on let's get high, high <br>Let's get high, all my ladies <br>Let's get high, high <br>High, high <br>Let's get high, high <br>Come on let's get high <br><br>I make the four hop <br>Pull up at the spot <br>Weed by the barrels in my G'd up apparel <br>Stomping in the party <br>Kurupt, Young Gotti <br>I'm fucking something in this bitch <br>Hit 'em with some gangsta shit <br>Put something in your mouth bitch real tasty <br>I'm looking real saucy in my gangsta ass Staceys <br>Hit the party, ease up, Kurupt with an ounce an' <br>Got all the hoes in this motherfucker bouncing <br>Down to <br><br>YO WHATTUP SCRAM JONES <br>Mel Man what's cracking <br>Whassup wit all these ol' punk ass hoes in here <br><br>Nigga what, I'm a hustling bitch <br>I like them get rich niggas <br>Them hit the switch niggas <br>Niggas bout the sex and which bitch to hit next <br>While I'm kicking my game and collecting them checks <br>Got all y'all niggas vexed to fuck this triple X rated ho <br>You say you ain't eat it, you ate it though <br>Roq don't stop, can't be dropping no drawers <br>To the niggas how you figure got you shitting in yours <br>Yeah, little dicks always running they mouth <br>While a bitch is better off to masturbate and be out <br>All you bitches up in here know what I'm talkin about <br>Get the loot, get the ice <br>Fuck the wife, no doubt <br>Trying to live lavish <br>Marry a big dick and stay carried <br>Holla back at them niggas that hollered at me <br>Pop the Cris' <br>Whip the six and shit <br>And have all y'all niggas limp when I twist my shit <br>Yeah, bitch ass niggas]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Let`s Get High (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Ms. Roq &amp; Kurupt)" label="Let`s Get High (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Ms. Roq &amp; Kurupt)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/The_Next_Episode_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Snoop_Dogg/</id><title>Dr. Dre - The Next Episode (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Snoop Dogg) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:44:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:44:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/The_Next_Episode_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Snoop_Dogg/" title="Dr. Dre - The Next Episode (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Snoop Dogg) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[La da da da dahh <br>It's the motherfuckingone and only D O double G Snoop Dogg <br>La da da da dahh <br>You know I'm mobbin' with the D R E <br>You know who's back up in this motherfucker <br>What what what what <br>So blaze the weed up then <br>Blaze it up, blaze it up <br>Just blaze that shit up, nigga <br>Yeah, 'sup, Snoop <br><br>Top Dogg, bite 'em all, nigga, burn the shit up <br>D P G C, my nigga, turn that shit up <br>C P T, L B C, yeah, we hooking back up <br>And when they bang this in the club, baby, you got to get up <br>Thug niggas, drug dealers, yeah, they giving it up <br>Lowlife, yo' life, boy, we living it up <br>Taking chances while we dancing in the party for sure <br>Slip my ho a forty fo' and she got in the back do' <br>Bitches looking at me strange, but you know I don't care <br>Step up in this motherfucker just a swanging my hair <br>Bitch, quit talking, Crip walk, stay down with the set <br>Take a bullet with some dick and take this dope from this jet <br>Out of town, put it down for the Father of Rap <br>And if yo' ass get cracked, bitch, shut yo' trap <br>Come back, get back, that's the part of success <br>If you believe in the S you'll be relievin' your stress <br><br>La da da da dahhh <br>It's the motherfucking DRE Dr Dre, motherfucker <br>La da da da dahhh <br>You know I'm mobbin' with the D O double G <br><br>Straight off the fucking streets of C P T <br>King of the beats, you ride to 'em in your Fleet Fleetwood <br>Or Coupe DeVille rolling on dubs <br>How you feeling whoopty whoop, nigga what <br>Dre and Snoop chronic'd out in the 'llac <br>With Doc in the back, sippin' on 'gnac <br>Clip in the strap, dipping through hoods what hoods <br>Compton, Long Beach, Inglewood <br>South Central out to the westside it's California Love <br>This California bud got a nigga gang of pub <br>I'm on one, I might bail up in the Century Club <br>With my jeans on, and my team strong <br>Get my drink on, and my smoke on <br>Then go home with something to poke on <br>Loc, it's on for the two triple oh <br>Coming real, it's the next episode <br><br>Hold up, hey <br>For my niggas who be thinking we soft, we don't play <br>We gonna rock it 'til the wheels fall off <br>Hold up, hey <br>For my niggas who be acting too bold, take a seat <br>Hope you ready for the next episode <br>Hey, hey, hey, hey <br><br>Smoke weed every day]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="The Next Episode (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Snoop Dogg)" label="The Next Episode (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Snoop Dogg)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Forgot_About_Dre_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Eminem/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Forgot About Dre (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Eminem) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:44:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:44:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Forgot_About_Dre_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Eminem/" title="Dr. Dre - Forgot About Dre (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Eminem) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Y'all know me, still the same OG, but I been low key <br>Hated on by most these niggas with no cheese <br>No deals and no G's, no wheels and no keys <br>No boats, no snowmobiles, and no skis <br>Mad at me 'cause I can finally afford <br>To provide my family with groceries <br>Got a crib with a studio and it's all full of tracks <br>To add to the wall full of plaques <br>Hanging up in the office in back of my house like trophies <br>Did y'all think I'ma let my dough freeze Ho please <br>You better bow down on both knees <br>Who you think taught you to smoke trees <br>Who you think brought you the oldies <br>Eazy E's, Ice Cubes, and DOC's, the Snoop D O double G's <br>And the group that said Mothafuck the police <br>Gave you a tape full of dope beats <br>To bump when you stroll through in your hood <br>And when your album sales wasn't doing too good <br>Who's the Doctor they told you to go see <br>Y'all better listen up closely <br>All you niggas that said that I turned pop or The Firm flopped <br>Y'all are the reason that Dre ain't been getting no sleep <br>So fuck y'all, all of y'all If y'all don't like me, blow me <br>Y'all are gonna keep fucking around with me <br>And turn me back to the old me <br><br>Nowadays, everybody wanna talk <br>Like they got somethin' to say <br>But nothin' comes out when they move their lips <br>Just a bunch of gibberish <br>And motherfuckers act like they forgot about Dre <br>Nowadays, everybody wanna talk <br>Like they got somethin' to say <br>But nothin' comes out when they move their lips <br>Just a bunch of gibberish <br>And motherfuckers act like they forgot about Dre <br><br>So what do you say to somebody you hate <br>Or anyone tryin' to bring trouble your way <br>Wanna resolve things in a bloodier way <br>Just study a tape of NWA <br>One day I was walking by <br>With a Walkman on, when I caught a guy <br>Give me an awkward eye <br>And I strangled him up in the parking lot with his Karl Kani <br>I don't give a fuck if it's dark or not <br>I'm harder than me tryin' to park a Dodge <br>When I'm drunk as fuck <br>Right next to a humongous truck in a two car garage <br>Hoppin' out with two broken legs, trying to walk it off <br>Fuck you too, bitch Call the cops <br>I'ma kill you and them loud ass motherfuckin' barking dogs <br>And when the cops came through <br>Me and Dre stood next to a burnt down house <br>With a can full of gas and a hand full of matches <br>And still weren't found out Right here <br>From here on out, it's the Chronic II <br>Starting today and tomorrow's anew <br>And I'm still loco enough <br>To choke you to death with a Charleston Chew <br>Slim Shady, hotter than a set of twin babies <br>In a Mercedes Benz with the windows up <br>When the temp goes up to the mid 80s <br>Callin' men ladies, sorry, Doc, but I been crazy <br>There's no way that you can save me <br>It's okay, go with him, Hailie Dada <br><br>Nowadays, everybody wanna talk <br>Like they got somethin' to say <br>But nothin' comes out when they move their lips <br>Just a bunch of gibberish <br>And motherfuckers act like they forgot about Dre <br>Nowadays, everybody wanna talk <br>Like they got somethin' to say <br>But nothin' comes out when they move their lips <br>Just a bunch of gibberish <br>And motherfuckers act like they forgot about Dre <br><br>If it was up to me, you motherfuckers would stop coming up to me <br>with your hands out, looking up to me <br>Like you want somethin' free <br>When my last CD was out, you wasn't bumpin' me <br>But now that I got this little company <br>Everybody wanna come to me like it was some disease <br>But you won't get a crumb from me <br>'Cause I'm from the streets of Compton <br>I told 'em all, all them little gangstas <br>Who you think helped mold 'em all <br>Now you wanna run around talkin' bout guns <br>Like I ain't got none what, you think I sold 'em all <br>'Cause I stay well off <br>Now all I get is hate mail all day saying Dre fell off <br>What, 'cause I been in the lab with a pen and a pad <br>Tryin' to get this damn label off <br>I ain't havin' that, this is the millennium of Aftermath <br>It ain't gonna be nothin' after that <br>So give me one more platinum plaque <br>And fuck rap, you can have it back <br>So where's all the Mad Rappers at <br>It's like a jungle in this habitat <br>But all you savage cats know that I was strapped with gats <br>While you were cuddling a Cabbage Patch <br><br>Nowadays, everybody wanna talk <br>Like they got somethin' to say <br>But nothin' comes out when they move their lips <br>Just a bunch of gibberish <br>And motherfuckers act like they forgot about Dre <br>Nowadays, everybody wanna talk <br>Like they got somethin' to say <br>But nothin' comes out when they move their lips <br>Just a bunch of gibberish <br>And motherfuckers act like they forgot about Dre]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Forgot About Dre (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Eminem)" label="Forgot About Dre (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Eminem)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Light_Speed_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Light Speed (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:44:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:44:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Light_Speed_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman/" title="Dr. Dre - Light Speed (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, yo whassup <br>My name is Dre <br>Can I blaze some chronic witchu <br><br>Nigga what FO' SHO' <br>Roll that shit up <br><br>Hell yeah, still Alwayz Into Somethin' <br>Heart still in Compton <br>The comp can't oppose, dope Cali platinum classicals <br>Introduced you to my Doggs, that don't love hoes <br>And Firm Fiascoes assholes <br>Fucked you up with my last video, tuxed up <br>Doing a tango <br>And cash, always in my grasp <br>Came up in the game wearin' khakis not kangols, stranglin' hoes <br>When asked about it in most interviews I just laugh <br>Now I vacate with hoes with a gang of ass <br>One feedin' me mangoes, the other lightin' my hash <br>Rap tabloids write Dre's light in the ass what <br>Came home uptight, ready to mash <br>Like a gas pedal, get on that '64 Chevy level <br>AK 47 heavy metal <br>Who say Dre ain't ghetto Just whistle like a tea kettle <br>I throw three at you, tell me if you see devils <br>Cause we rebels over here, I smell chronic in the air <br>That means we takin' over this year <br>You hear <br><br>Chronic, two thousand <br>ONE <br>That means we takin' over this year, ya hear <br><br>Light Speed, blazin' Chronic through the galaxy <br>Hydro, doja, chocolate Thai weed <br>Or we might be sippin' on gin or Hennessey <br>Fuck that, where that new shit, The Chronic Iced Teas <br><br>I hang among hustlers, that slang and Hoo bang Bronson <br>When bustaz roll through, can't fuck with my bold crew <br>We will hold you captive and bust <br>Cause gangbangin' is the active, activity <br>Where I be livin', B, there ain't no Liberty Statue <br>Hope you got your gat, don't let them catch you <br>Slippin', without yours, it's warfare outdoors <br>Ambulance, violent uproars <br>Trash niggas takin' out like chores <br>I meet whores on tours <br>Jeanie's hot as pepper so I sip, champagne on stormy shores <br>B on some hardcore, pornographic <br>Toting Austrian firearms that's made out of plastic <br>In these drastic surroundings, it be sounding like Lebanon <br>Makin' fools RETREAT like Megatron and Starscream <br>Oh yeah I scream on stars <br>That get loot then crossover like Kareem Abdul Jabbar <br>Get out your car son, that's how I came to bougie niggas <br>At Bar One, it's either that or make front page stardom <br>I'm the Golden Child, chased by Sardo Numpsay <br>But God's my bulletproof, it's hard to shoot me, you hear <br><br>By the time you see him <br>That means it's real fuckin' hard to shoot me, you hear <br><br>Light Speed, blazin' Chronic through the galaxy <br>Hydro, doja, chocolate Thai weed <br>Or we might be sippin' on gin or Hennessey <br>Fuck that, where that new shit, The Chronic Iced Teas]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Light Speed (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman)" label="Light Speed (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Bar_One_Album_Ver_Edited/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Bar One (Album Ver.) (Edited) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:44:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:44:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Bar_One_Album_Ver_Edited/" title="Dr. Dre - Bar One (Album Ver.) (Edited) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Damn girl, it is hotter than a motherfucker up in here <br>You got that right <br>I need to go to the bar and get me a drink, please <br>Yes <br>Hello <br>Yeah, what the fuck you want <br>Hmm <br>Let me get a Cosmo <br>What the fuck you want <br>Damn, I'll have an apple martini <br>This motherfucker drunk as a mother <br>Thirsty bitches <br>This a drunken ass nigga <br>Oh, ooh, shit girl, those niggas are looking over here <br>Oh shit, don't look, don't look <br>Damn, what's up, what they look like though <br>Shit, shit, damn, they look, they look aight <br>They fuckable What's up, is they fuckable or what <br>Shh, chill out, chill out <br>What <br>Here they come <br>What <br>Here they come Chill out Damn]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Bar One (Album Ver.) (Edited)" label="Bar One (Album Ver.) (Edited)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Whats_The_Difference_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Eminem__Xzibit/</id><title>Dr. Dre - What`s The Difference (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Eminem &amp; Xzibit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:44:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:44:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Whats_The_Difference_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Eminem__Xzibit/" title="Dr. Dre - What`s The Difference (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Eminem &amp; Xzibit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What's the difference between me and you <br>What's the difference between me and you <br><br>Back when Cube was rolling with Lorenzo in a Benzo <br>I was bangin' with a gang of instrumentals <br>Got the pens and pencils <br>Got down to business, but sometimes <br>The business end of this shit can turn your friends against you <br>But you was a real nigga, I could sense it in you <br>I still remember the window of the car that you went through <br>That's fucked up, but I'll never forget the shit we been through <br>And I'ma do whatever it takes to convince you <br>Cause you my nigga Doc, and Eazy I'm still wit'chu <br>Fuck the beef, nigga I miss you and that's just being real wit'chu <br>You see the truth is <br>Everybody wanna know how close me and Snoop is <br>And who I'm still cool with <br>Then I got these fake ass niggas I first blew with <br>Claimin' that they non violent, talkin' like they voice sample <br>Spit venom in interviews, speaking on reunions <br>Move units, then talk shit and we can do this <br>Until then I ain't even speaking your name <br>Just keep my name outta yo' mouth and we can keep it the same, nigga <br>It ain't that I'm too big to listen to the rumors <br>It's just that I'm too damn big to pay attention to 'em <br>That's the difference <br><br>What's the difference between me and you <br>You talk a good one <br>But you don't do what you supposed to do <br>I act on what I feel and never deal with emotions <br>I'm used to living big dog style and straight coasting <br>What's the difference between me and you <br>You talk a good one <br>But you don't do what you supposed to do <br>I act on what I feel and never deal with emotions <br>I'm used to living big dog style and straight coasting <br><br>Yo I stay with it, while you try to perpetrate and play with it <br>Never knew about the next level until Dre did it yeah <br>I stay committed while you motherfuckers baby sitted <br>I smash you critics like a overhand right from Riddick yeah <br>Come and get it, shitted on villains by the millions <br>I be catchin' bitches while bitches be catching feelings <br>So what the fuck am I supposed to do <br>I pop bottles and hot hollow points at each and all of you c'mon <br>A heartless bastard, high and plastered <br>My style is like the reaction from too much acid <br>Never come down, pass it around if you can't handle it <br>Hang Hollywood niggas by they Soul Train laminates <br>What's the difference between me and you what <br>About five bank accounts <br>Three ounces and two vehicles <br>Until my death, I'm Bangladesh <br>I suggest you hold yo' breath 'til ain't none left <br>Yo that's the difference <br><br>What's the difference between me and you <br>You talk a good one <br>But you don't do what you supposed to do <br>I act on what I feel and never deal with emotions <br>I'm used to living big dog style and straight coasting <br>What's the difference between me and you <br>You talk a good one <br>But you don't do what you supposed to do <br>I act on what I feel and never deal with emotions <br>I'm used to living big dog style and straight coasting <br><br>Aight, hold up, hold up <br>Stop the beat a minute <br>I got somethin' to say <br>Dre, I wanna tell you this shit right now <br>While this fucking weed is in me <br>What the fuck <br>I don't know if I ever told you this, but I love you dawg <br>I got your motherfucking back Right just know this shit <br>Slim, I don't know if you noticed it <br>But I've had your back from day one, nigga <br>Let's blow this bitch <br>I mean it dawg <br>You ever need somebody offed <br>Whose throat is it <br>Well if you ever kill that Kim bitch <br>I'll show you where the ocean is <br>Well that's cool, and I appreciate the offer <br>But if I do decide to really murder my daughter's momma <br>I'ma sit her up in the front seat and put sunglasses on her <br>And cruise around with her for seven hours through California <br>And have her wavin' at people, hi, then drop her off on the corner <br>At the police station and drive off honkin' the horn for her <br>Raw dawg, get your arm gnawed off, drop the sawed off <br>And beat you with the piece it was sawed off of <br>Fuck blood, I wanna see some lungs coughed up <br>Get shot up in the hot tub 'til the bubbles pop up <br>In they nose and cough snot up, mucus in hot water <br>That's for trying to talk like The Chronic was lost product <br>That's for even thinking of having them thoughts thought up <br>You better show some respect whenever the Doc's brought up <br>So what's the difference between us We can start at the penis <br>Or we can scream I just don't give a fuck and see who means it <br><br>What's the difference between me and you <br>You talk a good one <br>But you don't do what you supposed to do <br>I act on what I feel and never deal with emotions <br>I'm used to living big dog style and straight coasting <br>What's the difference between me and you <br>You talk a good one <br>But you don't do what you supposed to do <br>I act on what I feel and never deal with emotions <br>I'm used to living big dog style and straight coasting <br><br>What's the difference between me and you]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="What`s The Difference (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Eminem &amp; Xzibit)" label="What`s The Difference (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Eminem &amp; Xzibit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Xxplosive_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman_Six-Two_Nate_Dogg__Kurupt/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Xxplosive (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Six-Two, Nate Dogg &amp; Kurupt) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:44:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:44:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Xxplosive_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman_Six-Two_Nate_Dogg__Kurupt/" title="Dr. Dre - Xxplosive (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Six-Two, Nate Dogg &amp; Kurupt) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Xxplosive, West coast shit <br>My nigga ish ways attract girls that used to turn they back <br>Causing me to yank they arm and pose like I would do them harm <br>Now I'm saying thank you cause they tell me, my shit's the bomb <br>Xxplosive, for my niggas drinking Cognac <br>Smoking weed, always pack <br>More than one firearm, chrome rims, riding on <br>Chronic in your system, let me know my shit's the bomb <br>Xxplosive <br><br>West Coast shit nigga <br>Overdosage imperial pistols ferocious <br>Fuck a bitch don't tease bitch, strip tease bitch <br>Eat a bowl of these bitch gobble the dick <br>Hoes forgot to eat a dick can shut the fuck up <br>Gobble and swallow a nut up <br>Shut up and get my cash <br>Backhanded, pimp slapped backwards and left stranded <br>Just pop ya collar, pimp convention, hoes for a dollar <br>Six Deuce in a plush, six deuce impala <br>Pimping hoes from Texas to Guatemala <br>Bitch niggas pay for hoes, just to lay with hoes <br>Relax one night, and pay to stay with hoes <br>Captain 'Save 'em all day', well save this dick <br>Bitch nigga, you more of a bitch than a bitch <br>You ain't into hitting pussy or hitting the switch <br>You into hitting bitches all for the grip <br>You punk bitch <br><br>All my real doggs still kick it with me <br>All my down hoes still tricking with me <br>All the true gangstas know <br>Nate ain't never love no ho <br>All the hoodrats still shake it for me <br>All my true fans still checking for me <br>All the real smokers know <br>Nate ain't passing nothing but dro indeed <br>Real trees, chronic leaves, no seeds <br>When I met you last night baby <br>Before I blew your mind <br>I thought we had a chance, lady <br>No more, now that I'm sober you ain't that fine <br>Don't wanna treat you wrong <br>Don't wanna lead you on <br>Here baby hit the bong <br>While the West Coast rolls along <br>While we, still making gangsta hits <br>You'll be, still jocking gangsta dicks <br>Damn girl you think you're slick <br>Somebody better get this bitch, this bitch <br><br>I got these freaky hoes <br>Clapping they hands, stomping they feet <br>Every now and then they put they mouth on me <br>Nowadays a G like me can't even call it <br>A 23 year old pussy fiend and freakaholic <br>Pimping bitches on the regular, I put that on the G <br>A hustler and a player, nowadays it pays to be <br>Let me drop some shit about this bitch I used to know <br>She gave your boy the head and said don't let nobody know <br>A bonafide pro, I had to grab the ho <br>She got freaky in your '64, I skeeted in her throat <br>Been knowing the ho for four days, pimping repays <br>And I bet you didn't know that she go both ways <br>She ate her best friend, I left them hoes at the mote' <br>They be beeping me and shit, but we don't kick it no mo' <br>Them hot hoes is fiending, they on the nuts <br>But bitch, I'm out your pussy when I nut, fo' real <br><br>Explosive]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Xxplosive (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Six-Two, Nate Dogg &amp; Kurupt)" label="Xxplosive (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman, Six-Two, Nate Dogg &amp; Kurupt)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Big_Egos_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Big Ego`s (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:44:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:44:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Big_Egos_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Hittman/" title="Dr. Dre - Big Ego`s (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Los Angeles approach control <br>This is Cessna 0281 Echo 1193, over <br>Cessna 81 Echo, accept approach control, roger, go ahead <br>Cessna 81 Echo is over the Compton Airport, 52 at 5,000 <br>Requesting ground controlled approach to Los Angeles Airport, over <br>81 Echo, Los Angeles approach control, roger <br>Radar identification turn right, heading <br>0 3 0 <br><br>I got mo' class than most of them, ran with the best of them <br>Forgave the less of 'em and blazed at the rest of them <br>What can I say Cal i for ni a <br>Where niggas die every day over some shit they say <br>Disconnected from the streets forever <br>As long as I got a Beretta, nigga, I'm down for whateva <br>I roll with my shit off safety, for niggas that been hating me lately <br>And the bitches that wanna break me <br>If Cali blew up, I'd be in the Aftermath <br>Bumping gangsta rap shit, down to blast for cash <br>Cause from Eazy E, to DOC, to DPG <br>Started from that SOB, DRE <br>Like Dub C I'm rich rolling, pistol holding <br>Pockets swole nigga, that's how I'm rolling <br>Put the flame to the killer nigga <br>Worldwide homicide mob figure in the building, for real <br>I'm hitting switches, making bitches eat bitches <br>See me grab my dick every time I pose for pictures <br>I own acres, floor seats watching The Lakers <br>I'm cool with eses who got AK's in cases <br><br>Dedicated to all of those with big ego's <br>Never faking, we get the dough and live legal <br>Haters hate this, we sip the Mo' and yank the Heezos <br>Niggas play this in their Rovers, Jeeps and Regals <br>Dedicated to all of those with big ego's <br>Never faking, we get the dough and live legal <br>Haters hate this, we sip the Mo' and yank the Heezos <br>Bitches play this in their Benzes, Jeeps and Geos <br><br>I'll bust a Mr Toughy, slash a Smoovy Doovy <br>Crashin' Flex on Tuesdays, harassing hoes at movies <br>Passing by with Uzis, like who you aiming at <br>That shady bitch and that bitch nigga that was claiming that <br>Rat a tat tat <br>automatic gunfire and screaming, followed by tires peeling <br>I don't sympathize for wack hoes and wimpy guys <br>You gotta recognize Hittman is an enterprise <br>Cali pride, Bronson rider South Central ised <br>The Henny got me energized, smoke the guys <br>Tryna focus on mines, poke they eyes out, I'm LA's loc'est <br>Hope they don't have to find out the hard way <br>Like snitch niggas in the pen that get hit when the guards look the other way <br>We hitting hard Hittman and Dre <br>You playing games I suggest you know the rules <br>We putting guns to fools, make you run yo jewels <br>Take yo honey and cruise to the Snooty and snooze, cop booze <br>Pop coochie 'til the nut oozes, you shouldn't fuck with crews <br>That's sick, The Aftermath is we rule shit <br>I'm Big Hitt, don't confuse me with no other, bout to blow, motherfucker <br><br>Dedicated to all of those with big ego's <br>Never faking, we get the dough and live legal <br>Haters hate this, we sip the Mo' and yank the Heezos <br>Niggas play this in their Rovers, Jeeps and Regals <br>Dedicated to all of those with big ego's <br>Never faking, we get the dough and live legal <br>Haters hate this,we sip the Mo' and yank the Heezos <br>Bitches play this in their Benzes, Jeeps and Geos <br><br>You look like AC Green, bitch don't call here anymore <br>With feet like Ben Vereen's, bitch don't call here anymore <br>No no, no no <br>What up It's Hittman <br>I ain't at the crib right now <br>So you can leave your name and number after the beep <br>Unless it's Tammie's ugly ass I ain't fucking with you]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Big Ego`s (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman)" label="Big Ego`s (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Hittman)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Still_DRE_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Snoop_Dogg/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Still D.R.E. (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Snoop Dogg) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:44:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:44:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Still_DRE_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Snoop_Dogg/" title="Dr. Dre - Still D.R.E. (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Snoop Dogg) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, nigga, I'm still fucking with ya <br>Still waters run deep <br>Still Snoop Dogg and D R E, '99 nigga <br>Guess who's back <br>Still doing that shit, huh, Dre <br>Oh for sho', check me out <br><br>It's still Dre Day nigga, AK nigga <br>Though I've grown a lot, can't keep it home a lot <br>'Cause when I frequent the spots that I'm known to rock <br>You hear the bass from the truck when I'm on the block <br>Ladies, they pay homage, but haters say Dre fell off <br>How, nigga My last album was The Chronic <br>They want to know if he still got it <br>They say rap's changed, they wanna know how I feel about it <br>If you ain't up on thangs <br>Dr Dre is the name, I'm ahead of my game <br>Still puffin' my leaves <br>Still fuck with the beats, still not lovin' police <br>Still rock my khakis with a cuff and a crease <br>Still got love for the streets, reppin' 213 for life <br>Still the beats bang, still doing my thang <br>Since I left ain't too much changed, still <br><br>I'm representing for them gangstas all across the world <br>Still hittin' them corners in them lo lo's, girl <br>Still taking my time to perfect the beat <br>And I still got love for the streets, it's the D R E <br>I'm representing for them gangstas all across the world <br>Still hittin' them corners in them lo lo's, girl <br>Still taking my time to perfect the beat <br>And I still got love for the streets, it's the D R E <br><br>Since the last time you heard from me I lost some friends <br>Well, hell, me and Snoop, we dippin' again <br>Kept my ear to the streets <br>Signed Eminem, he's triple platinum, doing 50 a week <br>Still, I stay close to the heat <br>And even when I was close to defeat, I rose to my feet <br>My life's like a soundtrack I wrote to the beat <br>Treat rap like Cali weed I smoke 'til I sleep <br>Wake up in the AM, compose a beat <br>I bring the fire 'til you're soaking in your seat <br>It's not a fluke, it's been tried, I'm the truth <br>Since Turn Out the Lights from the World Class Wreckin Cru <br>I'm still at it, after mathematics <br>In the home of drive bys and ak matics <br>Swap meets, sticky green, and bad traffic <br>I dip through, then I get skin, D R E <br><br>I'm representing for them gangstas all across the world <br>Still hittin' them corners in them lo lo's, girl <br>Still taking my time to perfect the beat <br>And I still got love for the streets, it's the D R E <br>I'm representing for them gangstas all across the world <br>Still hittin' them corners in them lo lo's, girl <br>Still taking my time to perfect the beat <br>And I still got love for the streets, it's the D R E <br><br>It ain't nothing but more hot shit <br>Another classic CD for y'all to vibe with <br>Whether you're cooling on the corner with your fly bitch <br>Laid back in the shack, play this track <br>I'm representing for the gangstas all across the world <br>Still Hittin' them corners on the lo lo's, girl <br>I'll break your neck, damn near put your face in your lap <br>Niggas try to be the king, but the ace is back <br>So if you ain't up on thangs <br>Dr Dre be the name, still running the game <br>Still, got it wrapped like a mummy <br>Still ain't trippin', love to see young blacks get money <br>Spend time out the hood, take they moms out the hood <br>Hit my boys off with jobs, no more living hard <br>Barbeques every day, driving fancy cars <br>Still gon' get mine regardless <br><br>I'm representing for them gangstas all across the world <br>Still hittin' them corners in them lo lo's, girl <br>Still taking my time to perfect the beat <br>And I still got love for the streets, it's the D R E <br>I'm representing for them gangstas all across the world <br>Still hittin' them corners in them lo lo's, girl <br>Still taking my time to perfect the beat <br>And I still got love for the streets, it's the D R E <br>I'm representing for them gangstas all across the world <br>Still hittin' them corners in them lo lo's, girl <br>Still taking my time to perfect the beat <br>And I still got love for the streets, it's the D R E <br><br>Right back up in ya mothafuckin' ass <br>9 5 plus four pennies Add that shit up <br>D R E right back up on top of thangs <br>Smoke some with your dog <br>No stress, no seeds, no stems, no sticks <br>Some of that real sticky icky icky <br>Ooh wee Put it in the air, oh, you's a fool DR]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Still D.R.E. (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Snoop Dogg)" label="Still D.R.E. (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Snoop Dogg)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/F____You_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Devin_a_k_a_The_Dude__Snoop_Dogg/</id><title>Dr. Dre - F*** You (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Devin a/k/a The Dude &amp; Snoop Dogg) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:44:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:44:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/F____You_Album_Ver_Edited_Feat_Devin_a_k_a_The_Dude__Snoop_Dogg/" title="Dr. Dre - F*** You (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Devin a/k/a The Dude &amp; Snoop Dogg) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hi baby <br>I know you're under a lot of pressure at your work and all <br>And I do understand <br>You have no idea how much I understand <br>But you also don't have any idea how much I love you <br>I love you so much <br>I think about you I feel you in my arms <br>I miss you I miss you terribly <br>I've just always wanted someone like you in my life <br>I love you so much that I'd do anything <br>I'd do anything <br>I'll be your perfect woman for you <br><br>I just wanna fuck bad bitches <br>All them nights I never had bitches <br>Now I'm all up in that ass bitches <br>Mad at your boyfriend, ain't 'cha <br>You'se a bad girl, gotta spank ya <br>Gotta thank ya for that head clinic <br>Explicit, hella photogenic <br>And tell your friends where the dick's at <br>Where they can get hit and won't get back to they soulmate <br>Before you kiss 'em use Colgate <br>She swallowed it, yeah the bitch took the whole eight <br>And ran with it, then let Mel Man hit it <br>And Hitman hit it damn bitches <br>Man, this is what I'm talkin about <br>Chicken head, chicken fed, with a dick in yo mouth <br>Out and about with your nigga like it never took place <br>Airtouched Next time you need a taste <br><br>I just wanna fuck you <br>No touching and rubbing girl <br>You've got a husband who loves you <br>Don't need you all in mine <br>I just wanna fuck you <br>We can't be kissing and hugging girl <br>You've got a husband who loves you <br>You need to give him your quality time <br><br>You got the number, it's on you to make the call <br>You know I come quick help you redecorate your walls <br>Cut your backyard, don't have to act hard to get the cock <br>And if I'm going too far, I take it out and wipe it off <br>And put it back up, and keep going <br>You tryin to hide it from your husband but I know he be knowin <br>That your pussy's been tampered with <br>Then you show him the new trick <br>Of how you can make it smoke a cancer stick <br>You be workin it like a dancer, bitch it's hard on me <br>Not to give you all of my time that you wanted <br>You can give me some head, but keep the breakfast in bed <br>I'd rather spend my morning digging through some records instead <br>But, tonight I guess it'd be aight if we can touch bases <br>Hook up somewhere and exchange some Fuck Faces <br>I know your man's looking for ya <br>He's always trying to run ya <br>Don't worry bout me handcuffing girl <br>Cause I just wanna <br><br>Fuck witchu <br>On the sneak tip, on some creep shit <br>So whatcha gon' do, you freak bitch <br>You acting like you don't do dicks <br>That's the kinda bitch I hate fuckin with <br>Baby was a virgin, that's what she said <br>So I gave her some Hennessy, she gave me some head <br>I fucked her on the floor so I wouldn't mess up my bed <br>Then Lil' half dead put his dick on her head <br>Take that bitch home and give her a bone <br>And give her the number to my cellular phone <br>Now she's blowing up my pager, the shit's gettin major <br>A favor for a favor, this dick is what I gave her <br>Something to go by and bitches know why <br>Stuff dick in they mouth and then I'm out see ya <br>24 7, Dre, Snoop and Devin <br>We serving these hoes and never loving these hoes <br><br>I just wanna fuck you <br>No touching and rubbing girl <br>You've got a husband who loves you <br>Don't need you all in mine <br>I just wanna fuck you <br>We can't be kissing and hugging girl <br>You've got a husband who loves you <br>You need to give him your quality time]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="F*** You (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Devin a/k/a The Dude &amp; Snoop Dogg)" label="F*** You (Album Ver.) (Edited) (Feat. Devin a/k/a The Dude &amp; Snoop Dogg)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/The_Watcher_Album_Ver_Edited/</id><title>Dr. Dre - The Watcher (Album Ver.) (Edited) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:44:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:44:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/The_Watcher_Album_Ver_Edited/" title="Dr. Dre - The Watcher (Album Ver.) (Edited) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Things just ain't the same for gangstas <br>Times is changing, young niggas is aging <br>Becoming OGs in the game and changing <br>To make way for these new names and faces <br>But the strangest things can happen from rapping <br>When niggas get wrapped up in image and acting <br>Niggas get capped up and wrapped in plastic <br>Zipped up in bags when it happens, that's it <br>I've seen 'em come, I've watched 'em go <br>Watched 'em rise, witnessed it and watched 'em blow <br>Watched 'em all blossom and watched 'em grow <br>Watched the lawsuits when they lost the dough <br>Best friends and money I lost them both <br>Went visited niggas in the hospital <br>It's all the same shit all across the globe <br>I just sit back and watch the show <br><br>Everywhere that I go <br>Ain't the same as befo' The watcher <br>People I used to know <br>Just don't know me no mo' The watcher <br>But everywhere that I go <br>I got people I know The watcher <br>Who got people they know <br>So I suggest you lay low I watch <br><br>I moved out of the hood for good, you blame me <br>Niggas aim mainly at niggas they can't be <br>But niggas can't hit niggas they can't see <br>I'm out of sight, now I'm out of they dang reach <br>How would you feel if niggas wanted you killed <br>You'd probably move to a new house on a new hill <br>And choose a new spot, if niggas wanted you shot <br>I ain't a thug, how much 2Pac in you you got <br>I ain't no bitch, neither <br>It's either my life or your life and I ain't leaving, I like breathing <br>Nigga, we can go round for round <br>Clip for clip, shit, fo' pound for pound <br>Nigga, if you really want to take it there, we can <br>Just remember that you fucking with a family man <br>I got a lot more to lose than you, remember that <br>When you wanna come and fill these shoes <br><br>Everywhere that I go <br>Ain't the same as befo' The watcher <br>People I used to know <br>Just don't know me no mo' The watcher <br>But everywhere that I go <br>I got people I know The watcher <br>Who got people they know <br>So I suggest you lay low I watch <br><br>Things just ain't the same for gangstas <br>Cops is anxious to put niggas in handcuffs <br>They wanna hang us, see us dead, or enslave us <br>Keep us trapped in the same place we was raised in <br>Then they wonder why we act so outrageous <br>Run around stressed outand pull out gauges <br>Cause every time you let the animal out cages <br>It's dangerous to people who look like strangers <br>But now we got a new era of gangstas <br>Hustlers and youngsters living amongst us <br>Lookin' at us, now calling us busters <br>Can't help but reminisce back when it was us <br>Nigga, we started this gangsta shit <br>And this the motherfucking thanks I get <br>It's funny how time flies <br>I'm just having fun just watching it fly by <br><br>Everywhere that I go <br>Ain't the same as befo' The watcher <br>People I used to know <br>Just don't know me no mo' The watcher <br>But everywhere that I go <br>I got people I know The watcher <br>Who got people they know <br>So I suggest you lay low I watch <br><br>The watcher <br>The watcher <br>The watcher <br>The watcher <br>The watcher <br>The watcher]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="The Watcher (Album Ver.) (Edited)" label="The Watcher (Album Ver.) (Edited)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Lolo_Intro_Album_Ver_Edited/</id><title>Dr. Dre - Lolo (Intro) (Album Ver.) (Edited) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:44:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:44:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dr_Dre/Lolo_Intro_Album_Ver_Edited/" title="Dr. Dre - Lolo (Intro) (Album Ver.) (Edited) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Goddamn, wassup, nigga <br>Oh, shit <br>Wassup <br>Hey, that motherfucker clean <br>Who was that <br>Hey, that's Dre, nigga, that's the <br>Look at that shit <br>Hangin' that motherfucker, goddamn <br>That nigga chromed out up under that motherfucker <br>Hangin' on the bumper X <br>Hey, hang that shit <br><br>What up, Dr Dre]]></content><category term="Dr. Dre" label="Dr. Dre"/><category term="Lolo (Intro) (Album Ver.) (Edited)" label="Lolo (Intro) (Album Ver.) (Edited)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jazz_Cartier/Tempted/</id><title>Jazz Cartier - Tempted - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:50:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:50:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jazz_Cartier/Tempted/" title="Jazz Cartier - Tempted - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah we've been mixin' too much <br>All my emotions are numb <br>Feel like I can't get enough <br>Nah, if you keep dancin' on me <br>Girl, we've been mixin' too much <br>All my emotions are numb <br>Feel like I can't get enough <br>Nah, if you keep dancin' on me <br><br>Girl, I'll be tempted to touch <br>Tempted to touch <br>Feel like I can't get enough <br>If you keep dancin' on me <br>Girl, I'll be tempted to touch <br>Tempted to touch <br>It's like we alone in this club <br>If you keep dancin' on me <br><br>Girl I'll be tempted to touch <br>I think I just fell in love <br>It may be you or the drugs <br>But we need some more in our cups <br>And so call me when you're lonely <br>Yeah, and I leave from the homies <br>Ooh, ooh, I heard you love it when the light's out <br>Say the word, baby I can hit the right spot, true <br>All night I've been ready for you <br>Your girl told you, Make a move, they've been tellin' me too <br>Yeah, you not dealin' with no regular dude <br>You got niggas lyin' to you, but I'm tellin' the truth <br><br>So shorty swing my way <br>Yeah, come be my Ashanti <br>Hennessy, you can hydrate <br>You're not dealin' with no lightweight <br><br>Yeah we've been mixin' too much <br>All my emotions are numb <br>Feel like I can't get enough <br>Nah, if you keep dancin' on me <br>Girl we've been mixin' too much <br>All my emotions are numb <br>Feel like I can't get enough <br>Nah, if you keep dancin' on me <br><br>Girl, I'll be tempted to touch <br>Tempted to touch <br>Feel like I can't get enough <br>If you keep dancin' on me <br>Girl, I'll be tempted to touch <br>Tempted to touch <br>It's like we alone in this club <br>If you keep dancin' on me <br>Girl, I'll be <br><br>Ride it, baby, drive it like you stole it <br>Lose control, but please don't lose your focus <br>Findin' love in clubs is always hopeless <br>Wine your waist and I'll go with the motion <br>I know you're not materialistic <br>Come closer, I can't keep my distance <br>Come over, maybe we can keep it consistent <br>With your makeup on my shirt, neck covered in lipstick, ooh <br>We been at it all night, now you in the mood <br>Really can't wait to see you in the nude <br>So let me know what you finna do <br>I'll let you start me then I'll finish you <br><br>So shorty swing my way <br>Yeah, come be my Ashanti <br>Hennessy, you can hydrate <br>You're not dealin' with no lightweight <br><br>Yeah we've been mixin' too much <br>All my emotions are numb <br>Feel like I can't get enough <br>Nah, if you keep dancin' on me <br>Girl, we've been mixin' too much <br>All my emotions are numb <br>Feel like I can't get enough <br>Nah, if you keep dancin' on me <br><br>Girl, I'll be tempted to touch <br>Tempted to touch <br>Feel like I can't get enough <br>If you keep dancin' on me <br>Girl, I'll be tempted to touch <br>Tempted to touch <br>It's like we alone in this club <br>If you keep dancin' on me <br>Girl, I'll be]]></content><category term="Jazz Cartier" label="Jazz Cartier"/><category term="Tempted" label="Tempted"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mass_Avenue_매스애비뉴/널_보낸_후/</id><title>Mass Avenue (매스애비뉴) - 널 보낸 후 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:50:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:50:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mass_Avenue_%EB%A7%A4%EC%8A%A4%EC%95%A0%EB%B9%84%EB%89%B4/%EB%84%90_%EB%B3%B4%EB%82%B8_%ED%9B%84/" title="Mass Avenue (매스애비뉴) - 널 보낸 후 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어제 일처럼 환하네 이 순간처럼 <br>날 보며 웃는 그 얼굴 <br>이제는 날 보지 않아 <br>멀어져 가는 별처럼 흐려져가네 <br>우리 아름답던 시간 어느새 <br>이젠 지난 일이야 발버둥쳐 봐도 <br>모두 잊혀질 일들 <br>생각 없이 뱉은 말들 <br>상처되어 남을 말들 <br>모두 가슴에 남아 <br>널 보내며 흘린 눈물 <br>멈추지 않을 그 눈물 <br>아직 내 맘에 흘러 <br>멀어져 가는 별처럼 흐려져가네 <br>우리 아름답던 시간 어느새 <br>이젠 지난 일이야 발버둥쳐 봐도 <br>모두 잊혀질 일들 <br>생각 없이 뱉은 말들 <br>상처되어 남을 말들 <br>모두 가슴에 남아 <br>널 보내며 흘린 눈물 <br>멈추지 않을 그 눈물 <br>아직 내 맘에 흘러 <br>내가 했던 모든 말들 <br>우리 나눈 모든 말들 <br>지난 일 아니라면 <br>아직 남아있는 온기 <br>잊혀질 리 없는 향기 <br>상처가 아니라면 <br>]]></content><category term="Mass Avenue (매스애비뉴)" label="Mass Avenue (매스애비뉴)"/><category term="널 보낸 후" label="널 보낸 후"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mass_Avenue_매스애비뉴/Special_Day/</id><title>Mass Avenue (매스애비뉴) - Special Day - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:50:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:50:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mass_Avenue_%EB%A7%A4%EC%8A%A4%EC%95%A0%EB%B9%84%EB%89%B4/Special_Day/" title="Mass Avenue (매스애비뉴) - Special Day - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[분명 틀림없이 잘 맞추고 <br>잠든 것 같은데 <br>간밤에 누가 와서 끈 건가요 <br>나의 알람은 <br>제대로 씻지도 못하고 <br>뛰어 나왔는데 <br>정 없는 저 버스는 날 두고 <br>그냥 떠나죠 <br>정말이지 도와주지 않는 <br>나의 일상이 <br>생각대로 되지 않는 <br>나의 하루라도 <br>니가 있어 하나도 <br>힘들지 않은 <br>a very special day <br>a very special day <br>너를 향해 달려가며 맡는 <br>시원한 공기 <br>어디선가 들려오는 <br>너의 노랫소리 <br>힘든 하루 하지만 <br>니가 만드는 <br>a very special day <br>a very special day <br>딱히 눈에 띄게 잘 못한 것 <br>없는 것 같은데 <br>오늘따라 왜 이럴까 <br>가만있는 나만 뭐라죠 <br>정말이지 도와주지 않는 <br>나의 일상이 <br>생각대로 되지 않는 <br>나의 하루라도 <br>니가 있어 하나도 <br>힘들지 않은 <br>a very special day <br>a very special day <br>너를 향해 달려가며 맡는 <br>시원한 공기 <br>어디선가 들려오는 <br>너의 노랫소리 <br>힘든 하루 하지만 <br>니가 만드는 <br>a very special day <br>a very special day <br>너와 함께 하는 하루가 <br>a very special day <br>누구와도 바꿀 수가 없는 <br>you are precious <br>힘든 하루 하지만 <br>니가 만드는 <br>a very special day <br>a very special day <br>]]></content><category term="Mass Avenue (매스애비뉴)" label="Mass Avenue (매스애비뉴)"/><category term="Special Day" label="Special Day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mass_Avenue_매스애비뉴/혼란/</id><title>Mass Avenue (매스애비뉴) - 혼란 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:50:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:50:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mass_Avenue_%EB%A7%A4%EC%8A%A4%EC%95%A0%EB%B9%84%EB%89%B4/%ED%98%BC%EB%9E%80/" title="Mass Avenue (매스애비뉴) - 혼란 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 모르겠어 너의 맘을 <br>도무지 나에겐 이해가지 않아 <br>내게는 사랑이 너에겐 아니라니 <br>같은 시간 속에 있었던 우리 <br>아니었니 <br>우 우 <br>내가 이상한거니 아니면 혹시 <br>너에게 <br>멍하니 너의 뒷모습만 <br>내 모습 이상해보여 작아지네 <br>아무도 잡지 못하고 허공만 <br>내 손은 둘 곳을 잃어 힘들어져 <br>내가 이상한거니 아니면 혹시 <br>너에게 <br>멍하니 너의 뒷모습만 <br>내 모습 이상해보여 작아지네 <br>아무도 잡지 못하고 허공만 <br>내 손은 둘 곳을 잃어 힘들어져 <br>]]></content><category term="Mass Avenue (매스애비뉴)" label="Mass Avenue (매스애비뉴)"/><category term="혼란" label="혼란"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pat_Deville/Right_Round/</id><title>Pat Deville - Right Round - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:50:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:50:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pat_Deville/Right_Round/" title="Pat Deville - Right Round - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You spin my head right round, right round <br>When you go down, when you go down down <br><br>You spin my head right round, right round <br>When you go down, when you go down down <br><br>Hey, walk out that house with my swagger <br>Hop in there with dough, I got places to go <br>People to see, time is precious <br>I looked at my Cartier, out of control <br>Just like my mind where I'm goin' <br>No women, no shorties, no nothin' my clothes <br>No stoppin' now, my Pirellis on froze <br>I like my jewelry that's always on cold <br>I know the storm is comin' <br>My pockets keep tellin' me it's gonna shower <br>Call up my homies, it's on <br>Then popin tonight cause it's meant to be ours <br>We keep a fade away shot <br>'Cause we ballin' this Platinum Patron every hour <br>Lil mama, I owe you just like the flowers <br>Girl you the truth with all that goodie power <br><br>You spin my head right round, right round <br>When you go down, when you go down down <br><br>You spin my head right round, right round <br>When you go down, when you go down down <br><br>From the top of the pole I watch her go down <br>She got me throwin' my money around <br>Ain't nothin' more beautiful to be found <br>It's goin' down down <br>From the top of the pole I watch her go down <br>She got me throwin' my money around <br>Ain't nothin' more beautiful to be found <br>It's goin' down down <br><br>Shorty must know I'm the man <br>My money love her like a number one fan <br>Don't open my mouth, let her talk to my fans <br>My Benjamin Franklins <br>A couple of grands, I got rubber bands <br>My paper planes makin' her dance <br>Get dirty on like the spot on my hand <br>We buildin' castles that's made out of sand <br>She's amazin', fire blazin' <br>Hotter than Cajun, girl won't you move a lil' closer <br>Time to get paid, it's maximum wage <br>That body belong on a poster <br>I'm in a daze, that body is wavin' at me <br>Like, Damn it, I told ya <br>You wanna show like a gun out of holster <br>Tell me whatever and I'll be your chauffeur <br><br>You spin my head right round, right round <br>When you go down, when you go down down <br><br>You spin my head right round, right round <br>When you go down, when you go down down <br><br>From the top of the pole I watch her go down <br>She got me throwin' my money around <br>Ain't nothin' more beautiful to be found <br>It's goin' down down <br>From the top of the pole I watch her go down <br>She got me throwin' my money around <br>Ain't nothin' more beautiful to be found <br>It's goin' down down <br><br>I'm spendin' my money, I'm out of control <br>Somebody help me she takin' my bank roll <br>But I'm king of the club and I'm wearin' the crown <br>Poppin' these bottles, touchin' these models <br>Watchin' they asses go down down <br><br>You spin my head right round, right round <br>When you go down, when you go down down <br><br>You spin my head right round, right round <br>When you go down, when you go down down <br><br>You spin my head right round, right round <br>When you go down, when you go down down <br><br>You spin my head right round, right round <br>When you go down, when you go down down]]></content><category term="Pat Deville" label="Pat Deville"/><category term="Right Round" label="Right Round"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최유리_YOORI/Song_Of_Songs/</id><title>최유리 (YOORI) - Song Of Songs - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:53:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:53:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9C%A0%EB%A6%AC_YOORI/Song_Of_Songs/" title="최유리 (YOORI) - Song Of Songs - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[겨울 지나던 밤 <br>봄이 틔운 마음 사랑이 <br>수줍던 얼굴 <br>날 향한 눈빛이 아니어도 <br>내 사랑 그대여 <br>그 눈을 들어 나를 봐줘요 <br>그대만 바라보고 있던 날 <br>무너지던 그대 애태웠던 밤 <br>하나뿐인 사랑 <br>그대여 그 문을 열어 <br>내게 와줘요 <br>그대만 바라보고 있던 날 <br>아침의 빛 달 같은 그대여 <br>오 아름다운 사람 <br>내린 비 그치고 <br>환한 빛 비추면 <br>그 모든 게 그댈 위한 <br>나의 선물 <br>]]></content><category term="최유리 (YOORI)" label="최유리 (YOORI)"/><category term="Song Of Songs" label="Song Of Songs"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤지원/설레요/</id><title>윤지원 - 설레요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:55:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:55:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A7%80%EC%9B%90/%EC%84%A4%EB%A0%88%EC%9A%94/" title="윤지원 - 설레요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[설레요 <br>그대와 함께 있으면 설레요 <br>너무나도 좋아요 <br>두 눈 마주 보면 설레요 <br>좋네요 너랑 나랑 두 손 잡은 <br>그 손이 너무 좋네요 <br>설레요 <br>같이 있는 이 순간이 설레요 <br>별 헤는 밤 <br>내 눈앞에 펼쳐진 절경 <br>하늘에 수많이 놓이는 <br>별들과 너의 숨결 <br>그 안에서 헤엄치는 <br>상상을 했어 <br>너라는 아이와 영원히 함께 <br>같은 곳을 걸을 땐 <br>어떤 기분일까 <br>설레었던 난데 <br>지금은 넌 너무 상큼해졌어 <br>나 몰래 어린애들 <br>만나는 건 아닌지 <br>시시콜콜한 농담을 해도 <br>다 받아주는 바다 같은 아이 <br>그런 너랑 사귀고 있다니 <br>난 정말 행운아 인가 봐 <br>스물여섯 <br>한참 아무것도 몰랐고 <br>자신감만 앞서나가던 그때 <br>내게 운명처럼 다가온 그대 <br>자연스레 친구 옆에 있었던 너 <br>사실 널 만나러 가는 길은 <br>아니었었어 <br>난 감정을 숨겼지만 <br>장난스럽게 내비쳤었지 <br>내 수줍은 감정을 <br>설레요 <br>그대와 함께 있으면 설레요 <br>너무나도 좋아요 <br>두 눈 마주 보면 설레요 <br>좋네요 너랑 나랑 두 손 잡은 <br>그 손이 너무 좋네요 <br>설레요 <br>같이 있는 이 순간이 설레요 <br>그대 내게 보여졌던 <br>그 순간부터 우리 <br>강하게 이끌렸지 <br>그때 그 순간 잠시 <br>멈칫했었던 우리 <br>그때부터였나 봐 맞지 <br>그치 그랬지 <br>숨기고 숨겼던 내 얼굴 <br>내 감정을 <br>그땐 너도 알고는 <br>있었을 거야 <br>이 오빠 언제 고백하나 <br>조금 늦었지 내가 감정에 조금 <br>서투른 편이거든 <br>그러니 우리 이제 사귈래 baby <br>겁이 없었던 난데 <br>딴 데 가지 마 내 옆에만 있어줘 <br>라고 속으로 외쳤던 난데 <br>갑자기 생겼어 용기가 <br>더 이상 끌 필요가 없어서 <br>말했어 사귀자고 <br>그날이 추운 겨울이었지 아마 <br>그때 우리 온도는 뜨거웠었어 <br>한참을 바라봤지 <br>세상에 너와 나만 있듯이 <br>타올랐어 그때부터 <br>눈 오던 어느 날 <br>첫사랑에 감정을 <br>깨워준 영화와 함께 <br>속도는 급속도로 발전돼 <br>속도 모르고 <br>지내왔을 때 완 다르게 <br>손잡고 눈 맞으며 <br>고백했었어 사랑해 <br>설레요 <br>그대와 함께 있으면 설레요 <br>너무나도 좋아요 <br>두 눈 마주 보면 설레요 <br>좋네요 너랑 나랑 두 손잡은 <br>그 손이 너무 좋네요 <br>설레요 <br>같이 있는 이 순간이 설레요 <br>그대 내게 보여졌던 <br>그 순간부터 우리 <br>강하게 이끌렸지 <br>그때 그 순간 잠시 <br>멈칫했었던 우리 <br>그때부터였나 봐 <br>맞지 그치 그랬지 <br>설레요 <br>그대 아름다운 미소 때문에 <br>같이 있는 밤거린 <br>별로만 가득해 <br>손잡고 너의 체온을 느낄 땐 <br>작고 가녀린 손 마디로 <br>전해오는 따뜻함에 <br>또다시 설레네 <br>그대 아름다운 미소 때문에 <br>나 여기서 한참 설레이고 있었네 <br>기다림은 날 설레게 해 <br>마치 널 기다리는 망부석처럼 <br>한 곳에만 있었네 <br>설레요 <br>그대와 함께 있으면 설레요 <br>너무나도 좋아요 <br>두 눈 마주 보면 설레요 <br>좋네요 너랑 나랑 두 손잡은 <br>그 손이 너무 좋네요 <br>설레요 <br>같이 있는 이 순간이 설레요 <br>그대 내게 보여졌던 <br>그 순간부터 우리 <br>강하게 이끌렸지 <br>그때 그 순간 잠시 <br>멈칫했었던 우리 <br>그때부터였나 봐 <br>맞지 그치 그랬지 <br>언제까지나 <br>너의 손을 건넬 나이기에 <br>그때까지나 <br>너와 함께 갈 거야 <br>언제까지나 <br>너의 손을 건넬 나이기에 <br>그때까지나 <br>너와 함께 갈 거야 <br>내 머리 흰머리가 <br>다 채워질 때까지 <br>]]></content><category term="윤지원" label="윤지원"/><category term="설레요" label="설레요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lauren_Alaina/Queen_Of_Hearts/</id><title>Lauren Alaina - Queen Of Hearts - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:56:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:56:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lauren_Alaina/Queen_Of_Hearts/" title="Lauren Alaina - Queen Of Hearts - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let's play it straight <br>No need to wait <br>Just place your bet on me <br>You never know what ace you got <br>Half hiding up your sleeve <br>Before you make your next move <br>Honey, you better think it through <br>Love's a game but you choose <br>So don't play it like a fool <br><br>Cause I'm right here <br>In the palm of your hand <br>Right now, baby go all in <br>Slow down before you lose your chance to win <br>Don't throw it all away <br>You underestimate what you got <br>Love is worth the wait <br>Take a shot <br>Don't be so quick to fold your cards <br>You just might have <br>A Queen of Hearts <br><br>Even though I think your poker face is kinda cute <br>Just let it go, cause we both know <br>You can't hide the truth <br>Boy you might look tough <br>But I wanna know the real you <br>And yeah I'm calling your bluff <br>And I can see right through <br><br>Cause I'm right here <br>In the palm of your hand <br>Right now, baby go all in <br>Slow down before you lose your chance to win <br>Don't throw it all away <br>You underestimate what you got <br>Love is worth the wait <br>Take a shot <br>Don't be so quick to fold your cards <br>You just might have <br>A Queen of Hearts <br><br>Give in to me <br>Don't you wanna be <br>Don't you wanna be my <br>Don't you wanna be my <br>Don't you wanna be my king <br>Wanna be my king <br>Wanna be my king <br><br>Cause I'm right here <br>In the palm of your hand <br>Baby, go all in <br>Before you lose your chance to win <br>Don't you wanna win <br><br>Cause I'm right here <br>In the palm of your hand <br>Right now, baby go all in <br>Slow down before you lose your chance to win <br>Don't throw it all away, yeah <br>You underestimate what you got <br>Love is worth the wait <br>Take a shot <br>Don't be so quick to fold your cards <br>You just might have <br>A Queen of Hearts <br><br>You just might have <br>A Queen of Hearts <br>You just might have]]></content><category term="Lauren Alaina" label="Lauren Alaina"/><category term="Queen Of Hearts" label="Queen Of Hearts"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Suite_16/Who_I_Wanna_Be/</id><title>Suite 16 - Who I Wanna Be - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:56:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:56:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Suite_16/Who_I_Wanna_Be/" title="Suite 16 - Who I Wanna Be - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wish I was stronger <br>I wish I was brave <br>I wish I made memories <br>instead of mistakes <br>I wanna live longer <br>I wanna be wise <br>I wanna be earnest <br>and sunny day's child <br>But everyday I learn a little more <br>Never knowing what I'm heading for <br>And so I sail, sail away to another land <br>Along this wild rolling sea <br>And though I may, may not know who I really am <br>I can tell, I can tell, I can tell now <br>I can tell, I can tell, I can tell now <br>Who I wanna be <br>I wanna see treasure where other's see trash <br>I wanna find magic in everyday math <br>I'll never stay bitter, I'll never run poor <br>I'll only get better the more I get old <br>Everyday I learn a little more <br>Never knowing what I'm heading for <br>And so I sail, sail away to another land <br>Along this wild rolling sea <br>And though I may, may not know who I really am <br>I can tell, I can tell, I can tell now <br>I can tell, I can tell, I can tell now <br>I'm gonna be stronger <br>I'm gonna be brave <br>I'm gonna make memories <br>Instead of mistakes <br>And so I sail, sail away to another land <br>Along this wild rolling sea <br>And though I may, may not know who I really am <br>I can tell, I can tell, I can tell now <br>I can tell, I can tell, I can tell now <br>I can tell, I can tell, I can tell now <br>Who I wanna be]]></content><category term="Suite 16" label="Suite 16"/><category term="Who I Wanna Be" label="Who I Wanna Be"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/치타_CHEETAH/Style_Diet_Feat_강남/</id><title>치타 (CHEETAH) - Style Diet (Feat. 강남) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T20:56:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T20:56:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B9%98%ED%83%80_CHEETAH/Style_Diet_Feat_%EA%B0%95%EB%82%A8/" title="치타 (CHEETAH) - Style Diet (Feat. 강남) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 신경 쓸게 너무 많아 <br>메이크업 <br>스타일 다이어트 말야 <br>근데 난 알아 넌 말야 <br>Oh You don't give a <br>You don't give a <br>날 위해서 한 걸음 한걸음씩 <br>Style Diet oh Everyday <br>난 언제나 필요해 <br>매일매일 다이어트 <br>어떡해 식욕은 폭발해 <br>like a 다이나마이트 <br>넌 내가 타고났다 생각해 <br>오 아니 아니 넌 몰라 <br>너 모르게 난 노력하는걸 <br>비법 있어요 아니 아니 아니 뭐 <br>즐기며 스쿼트 해 <br>더 많이 많이 많이 more <br>내 삶의 주인이 되는 법 <br>그게 내 자신을 위해서라면 <br>전혀 어렵지 않지 뭐 <br>이렇다 저렇다 말뿐인 비법들 <br>bla bla 나랑은 멀어 <br>사실 별로 신경 안 써 <br>그 누가 뭐라던 <br>맛있게 먹으면 <br>0칼로리 아니에요 <br>엄마의 말씀 시작이 반이래요 <br>난 매일 다시 시작하니까 <br>벌써 반했어요 <br>네 반했어 <br>나한테 뭐라 하는 사람들 <br>어차피 다 남이에요 <br>신경 꺼 내가 알아서 <br>잘해 내 맘이에요 <br>우리 모두 밤 낮 없이 <br>일하고 뛰며 땀 흘리죠 뜨거워 <br>참 아름다운 밤이에요 <br>넌 신경 쓸게 너무 많아 <br>메이크업 <br>스타일 다이어트 말야 <br>근데 난 알아 넌 말야 <br>Oh You don't give a <br>You don't give a <br>날 위해서 한 걸음 한걸음씩 <br>Style Diet oh Everyday <br>이어가지 <br>1step 2step <br>차근차근 <br>서두르는 법이 없는 나의 작은 <br>한 걸음이 언젠가 <br>누군가의 길이 되겠지 <br>배경화면 나로 해놓고 <br>매일 받아 자극 <br>근데 그건 지금 내 모습 <br>괜히 스트레스 <br>받고 방금 어플 켰어 <br>찾고 있지 자극 <br>적인 food 내일 아침 <br>일찍 운동 가지 뭐 무드 있게 <br>한 조각 하고 걱정은 던져 <br>내일을 향해 슛 나이스 샷 <br>Gooood <br>대신 내일 오랜만에 만난 사람들 <br>예뻐졌다 살 빠졌다 <br>함부로 믿으면 안 돼 <br>근데 어머 방심했다 <br>내 손에 이거 뭐야 <br>다시 돌아가는 건 반대 <br>넌 신경 쓸게 너무 많아 <br>메이크업 <br>스타일 다이어트 말야 <br>근데 난 알아 넌 말야 <br>Oh You don't give a <br>You don't give a <br>날 위해서 한 걸음 한걸음씩 <br>Style Diet oh Everyday <br>넌 힘드냐고 묻지만 <br>I say no <br>but I never again <br>다신 그때로 <br>돌아가고 싶지 않아 <br>너 모르게 노력하고 있다고 <br>다 비슷하겠지 yeh <br>걱정 마 넌 너로써 예뻐 뭐 어때 <br>넌 신경 쓸게 너무 많아 <br>메이크업 <br>스타일 다이어트 말야 <br>근데 난 알아 넌 말야 <br>Oh You don't give a <br>You don't give a <br>날 위해서 한 걸음 한걸음씩 <br>Style Diet oh Everyday <br>]]></content><category term="치타 (CHEETAH)" label="치타 (CHEETAH)"/><category term="Style Diet (Feat. 강남)" label="Style Diet (Feat. 강남)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gabriela_Ferreira/Bang_The_Voice_Brasil_2016/</id><title>Gabriela Ferreira - Bang (The Voice Brasil 2016) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T21:00:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T21:00:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gabriela_Ferreira/Bang_The_Voice_Brasil_2016/" title="Gabriela Ferreira - Bang (The Voice Brasil 2016) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Vem na maldade com vontade <br>Chega encosta em mim <br>Hoje eu quero e voce sabe <br>Que eu gosto assim <br><br>Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah <br>Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah <br>Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah <br>Ah, ah, ah, ah <br><br>Bang bang dei meu tiro certo em voce vem <br>Deixa que eu faco acontecer vem <br>Tem que ser assim pra me acompanhar, pra chegar <br>Entao vem vem, nao sou de fazer muita pressao nao <br>Mas eu vou ficar na tua mao e <br>Se voce quiser nao pode vacilar, demorar <br><br>E pra te dominar, virar tua cabeca <br>Eu vou continuar te provocando <br>E pra escandalizar, dar a volta por cima <br>Nao vou parar, ate te ver pirando <br><br>Vem na maldade, com vontade, chega encosta em mim <br>Hoje eu quero e voce sabe que eu gosto assim <br><br>Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah <br>Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah <br>Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah <br>Ah, ah, ah, ah <br><br>Bang bang dei meu tiro certo em voce vem <br>Deixa que eu faco acontecer vem <br>Tem que ser assim pra me acompanhar, pra chegar <br>Entao vem vem, nao sou de fazer muita pressao nao <br>Mas eu vou ficar na tua mao e <br>Se voce quiser nao pode vacilar, demorar <br><br>E pra te dominar, virar tua cabeca <br>Eu vou continuar te provocando <br>E pra escandalizar, dar a volta por cima <br>Nao vou parar, ate te ver pirando <br><br>Vem na maldade, com vontade, chega encosta em mim <br>Hoje eu quero e voce sabe que eu gosto assim <br><br>Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah <br>Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah <br>Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah <br>Ah, ah, ah, ah]]></content><category term="Gabriela Ferreira" label="Gabriela Ferreira"/><category term="Bang (The Voice Brasil 2016)" label="Bang (The Voice Brasil 2016)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Coely/All_I_Do/</id><title>Coely - All I Do - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T21:02:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T21:02:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Coely/All_I_Do/" title="Coely - All I Do - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All I do think of you <br>Day and night that's all I do <br>I can't get you off my mind <br>I think about you all the time <br>All the time girl <br>I can't wait to get to school each day <br>And wait for you to pass my way <br>And bells start to ring <br>Any angel starts to sing <br>Hey that's the girl for you <br>So what are you gonna do <br>Hey little girl I love you so <br>All I do think of you day <br>And night that's all I do <br>I can't get you off my mind <br>I think about you all the time <br>All the time girl <br><br>I've been begun to take the long home <br>Just so I can be alone <br><br>To think of how to say <br>Your fine in ever way <br>Hey I'm in love with you <br>I think the world of you <br><br>Ohh wouldn't you please <br>Please be mine <br>All I do think of you day <br>And night thats all I do <br>I can't get you off my mind <br>I think about you all the time <br>All the time girl <br>Ba ba ba bada ooh <br>Always thinking 'bout you <br>Ba ba ba bada ooh <br>Always thinking 'bout you <br>Ba ba ba bada ooh <br>Always thinking 'bout you <br>Ba ba ba bada ooh <br>Always thinking 'bout you <br>All I do think of you day <br>And night that's all I do <br>I can't get you off my mind <br>I think about you all the time <br>I can't think <br>I can't sleep <br>I can't talk <br>I can't walk <br>I can't do it girl <br>No no no no no no yea yea yea <br>All I do think of you day <br>And night that's all I do <br>I can't get you off my mind <br>I think about you all the time all]]></content><category term="Coely" label="Coely"/><category term="All I Do" label="All I Do"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Adi_L_Hasla/Pelkkii_Voittoi_Feat_Makki__Kube/</id><title>Adi L Hasla - Pelkkii Voittoi (Feat. Makki &amp; Kube) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T21:02:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T21:02:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Adi_L_Hasla/Pelkkii_Voittoi_Feat_Makki__Kube/" title="Adi L Hasla - Pelkkii Voittoi (Feat. Makki &amp; Kube) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Aina jaksaa viela <br>Kiesi pysyy liikkeel vaik on myyrii tiella <br>Ei kukaa taalla kysy paljon matkaa viela <br>Silmaluomet raskaat, sita en kiella <br>Ja naa jabat pysyy satasina <br>Eika naamat liian vakavina <br>Etupenkil hakunila killa <br>Ma ja makki mamutyyleil keikkapakun takatilas <br>Tana vuon tippuu pois turhakkeet <br>Sul on alla otsas mul on tuplavee <br>Nyt niilta palaa sulakkeet <br>ala syyta muit jos ei putkeen sun ura mee <br>Et voi tata pommii purkaa <br>Status nousee, hatus taas uutta sulkaa <br>Heitettii ne siemenet multaan <br>Nyt kaikki talla trakil myyny platinaa tai kultaa <br><br>Me ollaan vihdoin taalla <br>Viedaan kermat paalta <br>Kerro mulle hei naatsa <br>Otetaa pelkkii voittoi <br><br>Ketka vikana nauraa <br>Taysosumia naulaa <br>Jalometallia kaulaan <br>Tanavuon pelkkii voittoi <br><br>Jos raha puhuu, mun flow on kassavirtaa <br>Stadi tayn selan rasvaajia <br>Mun sana painaa tonnin, sa voit punnita <br>Sun hommat kyykkas mut hei, onks se mun vika <br>Jokatoinen polttaa siltoi ku kaloreit <br>Samaa aikaa ylitan kaikki mun tavotteet <br>Menestys muutti mun talouden <br>Ollu nii kauan tien paal ne ilmotti mut kadonneeks <br>Kadun mies, vielki sama mies <br>Vaik luen kauppalehtee guccin sandaaleis <br>Seitteman kultaa, kolme platinaa <br>Edelleenki tyomaal laulaa mun makita <br>Jos haluut teha pankkii se vaatii munaa <br>Juoksen tata paskaa nii et lenkkarit sulaa <br>Ja koko helvetin Suomi huutaa mun nimee <br>Ei huolii, ei murheit, zero fucks given <br><br>Me ollaan vihdoin taalla <br>Viedaan kermat paalta <br>Kerro mulle hei naatsa <br>Otetaa pelkkii voittoi <br><br>Ketka vikana nauraa <br>Taysosumia naulaa <br>Jalometallia kaulaan <br>Tanavuon pelkkii voittoi <br><br>Tana vuon purppura dunkkaa hotelleissa, kube tules ku galaxy note seiska <br>Ei ne pysty stoppaa mun nousuu <br>Ma katkon niilt siivet ku ne ois lokkei mun propelleissa <br>Tana vuon se on pelkkii voittoi <br>Pojat haki kultaa ilman radiosoittoi <br>Fuckboyt flowaa fiktioo <br>Mun tyyli realismi joo oon rappigeimin Tolstoi <br>ala sanoi boy et ma en oo graindannu <br>ala sano etten oo tieta uudelleen raivannu <br>Sa et tuo mitaa tahan geimiin <br>Ne unohtaa sut mut ne muistaa aina mut <br>Tana vuon en raaputa tyhjii arpoi <br>Pokkoo pesaa koska oon hakannu niit halkoi <br>Tana vuon vahemman perunoit enemman mangoi <br>Tana vuon vahemman loskaa enemman rantoi <br><br>Me ollaan vihdoin taalla <br>Viedaan kermat paalta <br>Kerro mulle hei naatsa <br>Otetaa pelkkii voittoi <br><br>Ketka vikana nauraa <br>Taysosumia naulaa <br>Jalometallia kaulaan <br>Tanavuon pelkkii voittoi]]></content><category term="Adi L Hasla" label="Adi L Hasla"/><category term="Pelkkii Voittoi (Feat. Makki &amp; Kube)" label="Pelkkii Voittoi (Feat. Makki &amp; Kube)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소피야_Sophiya/나를_위해_Inst/</id><title>소피야 (Sophiya) - 나를 위해 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T21:02:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T21:02:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%ED%94%BC%EC%95%BC_Sophiya/%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9C%84%ED%95%B4_Inst/" title="소피야 (Sophiya) - 나를 위해 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 과거와 싸움을 멈춘다 <br>거센 바람에 난 날린다 <br>색종이가 접히는 것처럼 <br>나의 자국들이 포옹 해준다 <br>이 슬픔이 될 때까지 <br>나를 위해 살아가는 난 <br>이제 아름다운 세상과 하나되어 <br>오랜 새로운 여행을 떠난다 <br>굳은 희망이 <br>손에 닿을 듯한 날이다 <br>난 이제야 좀 알 것 같지만 <br>매일 새로운 마음 가져 <br>내 씨앗이 민들레 꽃처럼 <br>어디 닿아도 피를 기다려 <br>아침햇살 볼 때까지 <br>나를 위해 살아가는 난 <br>이제 아름다운 세상과 하나되어 <br>오랜 새로운 여행을 떠난다 <br>굳은 희망이 손에 닿을 듯한 <br>나는 웃음을 찾아본다 <br>행복을 잡아본다 <br>매일 오르막 길이지만 <br>나의 밝음을 향해간다 <br>난 만족을 선택한다 <br>인생은 내 선물이기에 <br>나를 위해 살아가는 난 <br>이제 아름다운 세상과 하나되어 <br>나를 위해 살아가는 난 <br>이제 아름다운 세상과 하나되어 <br>오랜 새로운 여행을 떠난다 <br>굳은 희망이 손에 <br>붙잡을 준비 안에 <br>기회는 오늘뿐 <br>나의 날이다 <br>]]></content><category term="소피야 (Sophiya)" label="소피야 (Sophiya)"/><category term="나를 위해 (Inst.)" label="나를 위해 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소피야_Sophiya/나를_위해/</id><title>소피야 (Sophiya) - 나를 위해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T21:02:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T21:02:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%ED%94%BC%EC%95%BC_Sophiya/%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9C%84%ED%95%B4/" title="소피야 (Sophiya) - 나를 위해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 과거와 싸움을 멈춘다 <br>거센 바람에 난 날린다 <br>색종이가 접히는 것처럼 <br>나의 자국들이 포옹 해준다 <br>이 슬픔이 될 때까지 <br>나를 위해 살아가는 난 <br>이제 아름다운 세상과 하나되어 <br>오랜 새로운 여행을 떠난다 <br>굳은 희망이 <br>손에 닿을 듯한 날이다 <br>난 이제야 좀 알 것 같지만 <br>매일 새로운 마음 가져 <br>내 씨앗이 민들레 꽃처럼 <br>어디 닿아도 피를 기다려 <br>아침햇살 볼 때까지 <br>나를 위해 살아가는 난 <br>이제 아름다운 세상과 하나되어 <br>오랜 새로운 여행을 떠난다 <br>굳은 희망이 손에 닿을 듯한 <br>나는 웃음을 찾아본다 <br>행복을 잡아본다 <br>매일 오르막 길이지만 <br>나의 밝음을 향해간다 <br>난 만족을 선택한다 <br>인생은 내 선물이기에 <br>나를 위해 살아가는 난 <br>이제 아름다운 세상과 하나되어 <br>나를 위해 살아가는 난 <br>이제 아름다운 세상과 하나되어 <br>오랜 새로운 여행을 떠난다 <br>굳은 희망이 손에 <br>붙잡을 준비 안에 <br>기회는 오늘뿐 <br>나의 날이다 <br>]]></content><category term="소피야 (Sophiya)" label="소피야 (Sophiya)"/><category term="나를 위해" label="나를 위해"/></entry></feed>