<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:17:25+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Locomotive/The_moment_Feat_김꽃/</id><title>Locomotive - The moment (Feat. 김꽃) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:03:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:03:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Locomotive/The_moment_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EA%BD%83/" title="Locomotive - The moment (Feat. 김꽃) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[순간을 기억해 <br>조금씩 스며들어가 <br>잠깐의 이끌림 <br>빠르게 날 흔들어가 <br>멈춰버린 시간 <br>찰나의 너 그래 너 <br>절대 잊지마 <br>모든 게 사라진대도 <br>난 너이길 원해 <br>너의 눈빛과 설레임 <br>난 너이길 원해 <br>순간을 믿어 <br>지금을 기억해 <br>스치듯 손끝이 닿으면 <br>잠깐의 뜨거움 <br>우리들 사라져도 좋아 <br>멈춰버린 시간 <br>그 안의 너 그래 너 <br>계속 생각해 <br>아무런 이유 없어도 <br>난 너이길 원해 <br>너의 눈빛과 설레임 <br>난 너이길 원해 <br>순간을 믿어 <br>내 것이여 야해 <br>너의 눈빛과 설레임 <br>난 너로 가득해 <br>순간을 믿어 <br>너만 있으면 돼 <br>너의 눈빛과 설레임 <br>난 너여야만 해 <br>순간을 믿어 <br>]]></content><category term="Locomotive" label="Locomotive"/><category term="The moment (Feat. 김꽃)" label="The moment (Feat. 김꽃)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지투_G2/Young__Alive/</id><title>지투 (G2) - Young &amp; Alive - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:03:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:03:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%ED%88%AC_G2/Young__Alive/" title="지투 (G2) - Young &amp; Alive - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[첫끼엔 샴페인 <br>축복받은 삶 <br>사람들과 손을 위로 짠해 <br>어디를 가도 잃지 않아 <br>지켜 나의 멋 <br>바쁜 삶에 익숙해져 <br>채워가는 달력 <br>나는 젊고 유능해 <br>먹혔지 나의 방식 <br>꿈을 꾸던게 <br>지금은 나의 현실 <br>의심했던 애들은 <br>배 아파해 아야 <br>너넨 시기하고 <br>나는 일을해 그게 차이야 <br>만족을 못해 갈수록 <br>커져가 욕심 <br>여자보다 돈 돈보다는 <br>가족 내 고집 <br>바뀐것은 인터넷에 <br>나의 소식 <br>몇가지는 수정하고 <br>지켜가는 초심 <br>만취해 공연때 <br>나의 팀은 분위기를 돋구지 <br>nice life what I'm living <br>고딩때부터 꿈꿔왔던 dream <br>잘 놀고 먹고 살며 <br>getting cream <br>Superstar young and alive <br>버릇없는 삶 <br>아직은 젊은 나이 <br>young and reckless <br>Commas on my numbers <br>Gold links for my necklace <br>Superstar young and alive <br>버릇없는 삶 <br>아직은 젊은 나이 <br>young and reckless <br>Commas on my numbers <br>Gold links for my necklace <br>매니져 형이 <br>나를 데리러와 <br>나는 물어보지 <br>오늘은 어디로가 <br>인터뷰 tv쇼 <br>아님 공연장 <br>항상 준비되있으니까 어디든가 <br>아무리 바빠도 <br>주체할 수가 없어 흥 <br>한곳에 머물지 않아 <br>언제나 이동중 <br>비행기 타고 <br>슝 날아가는 기분 <br>매일이 payday <br>신나는 내 인생 <br>Positive vibes only <br>쌓이는 색 종이 <br>Ben Frank 세종대왕 <br>나의 homies <br>눈뜨자마자 아침부터 <br>돈이 날 부르는 소리 <br>그 소리들로 인해 <br>해결되는 나의 고민 <br>메뉴 볼 필요 없어 <br>제일 비싼걸로 시켜 <br>김사 기도 하며 짠을 하지 <br>thank you jesus <br>쓰는듯이 벌어 버는듯이 써 <br>Superstar life <br>난 버릇이 없어 <br>Superstar young and alive <br>버릇없는 삶 <br>아직은 젊은 나이 <br>young and reckless <br>Commas on my numbers <br>Gold links for my necklace <br>Superstar young and alive <br>버릇없는 삶 <br>아직은 젊은 나이 <br>young and reckless <br>Commas on my numbers <br>Gold links for my necklace <br>]]></content><category term="지투 (G2)" label="지투 (G2)"/><category term="Young &amp; Alive" label="Young &amp; Alive"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/빈지노_Beenzino/Up_up_and_away_Prod_By_Shimmy_Twice/</id><title>빈지노 (Beenzino) - Up up and away (Prod By Shimmy Twice) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:03:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:03:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%88%EC%A7%80%EB%85%B8_Beenzino/Up_up_and_away_Prod_By_Shimmy_Twice/" title="빈지노 (Beenzino) - Up up and away (Prod By Shimmy Twice) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Came up in the spot <br>looking extra fly <br>before the day i die <br>Imma touch the <br>Came up in the spot <br>looking extra fly <br>before the day i die <br>Imma touch the <br>Came up in the spot <br>How can i not touch the sky <br>Came up in the spot <br>How can i not touch the sky <br>그 당시에는 없었지 아이폰이 <br>지디 또한 연습생 <br>wasn't iconic <br>또 팔로알토형의 <br>발자국이 닿았던 <br>2004로부터 내 핫 <br>데뷔까지 걸린 시간 4년 <br>반짝 떴었다면 <br>Daily apartment을 <br>어떻게 설명하며 <br>아까워를 어떻게 사람들이 <br>기억을 할 수 있을까 <br>생각해보면 나의 <br>행보와 엇 비슷한 <br>애는 찾기 어려워 <br>actor는 넘쳐 <br>다들 최고라 말하지만 <br>결국 compromised <br>그래 이해는 돼 참다가 <br>배가 고픈 나머지 <br>앨범보다 먼저 <br>내세울게 없었나봐 <br>어이쿠 오핸 마 my friend <br>그런 너의 성공이 나도 반갑네 <br>다만 그곳은 내가 안간 데 <br>다만 이곳은 너가 오고 싶어도 <br>결국에 못 와본데야 <br>I'm going up up and away <br>I'm going up up and away <br>Nothing has changed but swag <br>I'm going up up and away <br>I'm going up up and away <br>Nothing has changed but my life <br>I love my life <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>How can i not love <br>I love my life <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>how can i not love <br>i love my <br>그때쯤 살만해졌지 살짝 <br>24:26 had some hits <br>I made it look easy <br>지금도 아무나 <br>해낼 수 없는 일을 해서 <br>얻어낸 지금의 <br>내 이름은 어느날 <br>없어 질수 있는게 아냐 <br>안투라지의 life style <br>그 예가 나야 <br>음악에만 가있던 초점은 <br>이제 예술에 와있어 <br>길거리부터 전시장까지 <br>so many i phones <br>내 resume는 그냥 랩퍼에 <br>국한되기엔 조금 아쉽네 <br>다음 챕터로 넘어가기 위해 <br>12년전으로 I time traveled <br>and i’m back with jazzy fact yo <br>누가 최곤지 팩트로 <br>폭행해줄께 yo <br>잠은 여전히 없지 <br>I’m always awake yo <br>I'm on to the next one <br>I'm going up up and away <br>I'm going up up and away <br>Nothing has changed but swag <br>I'm going up up and away <br>I'm going up up and away <br>Nothing has changed but my life <br>I love my life <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>How can i not love <br>I love my life <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>How can i not love <br>I love my <br>Came up in the spot <br>looking extra fly <br>before the day i die <br>Imma touch the <br>Came up in the spot <br>looking extra fly <br>before the day i die <br>Imma touch the <br>Came up in the spot <br>How can i not touch the sky <br>]]></content><category term="빈지노 (Beenzino)" label="빈지노 (Beenzino)"/><category term="Up up and away (Prod By Shimmy Twice)" label="Up up and away (Prod By Shimmy Twice)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dok2/Put_it_down_Feat_김효은_창모/</id><title>Dok2 - Put it down (Feat. 김효은, 창모) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:04:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:04:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dok2/Put_it_down_Feat_%EA%B9%80%ED%9A%A8%EC%9D%80_%EC%B0%BD%EB%AA%A8/" title="Dok2 - Put it down (Feat. 김효은, 창모) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Am I a superstar <br>Am I a hero just because <br>I've been in that supercar <br>When you're feeling down <br>everything is superfar <br>All you gotta know you ain't gotta <br>worry about a thing just put it down <br>just put it down just put it down <br>이땅에 태어나서 태어 날때부터 <br>완벽히 다 빼어난 사람어딨어 <br>복잡한 도시 위를 뛰다 보면 <br>어디로 가는지 <br>도대체 뭣 때문에 난 여기서 <br>날 위한 삶에 누굴 위해 <br>살고있는지도 많이 가끔은 <br>헷갈릴 때가 있어 <br>이제는 휘청거릴 내가 <br>아니라고 생각될 때 마침 또 <br>엇갈릴 때가 있어도 <br>뭐 어쩌겠냔거지 <br>한참을 입장 바꿔 <br>생각해보면 다 뻔히 <br>내 짧은 생각들과 나의 욕심 <br>Gotta Put it down <br>내가 내려놓는 동시에 <br>다시올려 놓아야할 <br>me myself and I <br>At the end of the day <br>I gotta be my self and fly away <br>from all these worry and thoughts <br>잠시 잊고 살던 머릿속을 스치는 quotes <br>Am I a superstar <br>Am I a hero just because <br>I've been in that supercar <br>When you're feeling down <br>everything is superfar <br>All you gotta know you ain't gotta <br>worry about a thing just put it down <br>just put it down just put it down <br>첫 번째 뮤빈 코사무이섬에서 <br>내가 양동근 님 아니 형과 <br>술 한 잔을 할 수 있을 진 <br>어떻게 알았겠어 <br>난 지금 너무 아프고 <br>이 취함이 내일 또 깨면 <br>아닌 척 해 아무것도 <br>솔직히 나도 신기하고 과분해 <br>저 여잘 가둘래 <br>내 어장안에 이리 와줄래 지금 좀 <br>알았다고 해 <br>니가 해야 될 말은 나중에 <br>여기 이틀 더 있다 가 한국에 <br>다시 a.m.b.i.t.i.o.n <br>일리네어 형들 옆에 붙어있다니 <br>이 기분을 너희가 뭘 알겠니 <br>그래 나도 걱정했지 my ambition <br>콰이엇 형이 해준 말을 <br>핑계로 괜찮다고 여지껏 <br>행복 할 줄만 알았네 <br>엄만 여전히 가난해 <br>더 이상 머린 상상 안 해 <br>여기 날씬 내일도 창창해 <br>톨제이 형께 감사해 <br>Am I a superstar <br>Am I a hero just because <br>I've been in that supercar <br>When you're feeling down <br>everything is superfar <br>All you gotta know you ain't gotta <br>worry about a thing just put it down <br>just put it down just put it down <br>난 이 도시 외곽 출신 <br>마을의 난 항상 <br>이러한 류의 꿈을 꾸었지 <br>저 대도시의 star가 돼 어두운 밤을 <br>비추는 꿈 현실이 되어가 <br>I'm mr. so bright 혹 mr. mr. hustler <br>바닥에서 위 난 <br>물리법칙을 거슬러 <br>꽤나 어린 나이에 <br>무릎을 꿇어봤으니 <br>실패는 내게 nothin <br>come to me one more time bring it on <br>받았어 재능이란 세례 <br>들어가 대도시 안 game에 <br>쥔 것도 없이 태어난 애이기에 <br>덤비는 것만이 <br>얻는 법이란걸 아네 이젠 <br>진짜로 돈 벌어 불러 날 곧 거물 <br>행복히 할거야 <br>내 동네친구놈 모두 <br>도시는 알아봐 날 비춘 빌딩 불 <br>꿈속에 들어가 마천루를 달려 in the coupe <br>Am I a superstar <br>Am I a hero just because <br>I've been in that supercar <br>When you're feeling down <br>everything is superfar <br>All you gotta know you ain't gotta <br>worry about a thing just put it down <br>just put it down just put it down <br>]]></content><category term="Dok2" label="Dok2"/><category term="Put it down (Feat. 김효은, 창모)" label="Put it down (Feat. 김효은, 창모)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레디_Reddy/너라도_Feat_김보아_Of_SPICA/</id><title>레디 (Reddy) - 너라도 (Feat. 김보아 Of SPICA) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:04:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:04:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EB%94%94_Reddy/%EB%84%88%EB%9D%BC%EB%8F%84_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EB%B3%B4%EC%95%84_Of_SPICA/" title="레디 (Reddy) - 너라도 (Feat. 김보아 Of SPICA) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그게 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 나는 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 <br>난 젊고 능력 있어 <br>아직까지 ya <br>영원하길 바래 이 <br>모든 것들이 ya <br>묶이는 게 싫어 나는 그게 너라도 <br>어젯밤에 만난 여자들의 전화도 <br>오늘이 지나면 안 받을 거야 <br>니가 보고 싶은데 그냥 참을 거야 <br>깊어지기 싫어 그게 너라도 <br>아프기는 싫어 그게 너라도 <br>헤어지고 또 누군가를 만나도 <br>다시 또 아파질 걸 다들 알아도 <br>깨져버릴 사랑 같은 걸 <br>다시 말하고 <br>아무렇지 않게 웃잖아 <br>내일 보자고 <br>시간이 지나면 괜찮을 걸 알아도 <br>나는 못하겠어 너랑 깊어지는 거 <br>가벼운 게 낫지 그러면 아마도 <br>나중에 내가 너를 <br>놓아주기 쉬울걸 <br>그게 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 나는 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 <br>니가 나를 바라볼 때 <br>모든 것이 선명해져 <br>내게서 돌아설 때면 <br>그대 온기가 흩어져 <br>나를 바라보는 너의 눈빛은 날 <br>외롭게 하지 <br>어서 나를 안아줘 <br>아무도 모르게 <br>시간이 가 tic toc tic toc <br>흘러가 도망가듯이 <br>모두 잊어버려 <br>한 번만 더 날 안아줘 <br>모두 잊을 수 있게 <br>Baby 너는 <br>영원히 내 손 꼭 잡아줘 <br>그게 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 나는 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 <br>시간이 지나면 괜찮을 걸 알아도 <br>나는 못하겠어 너랑 깊어지는 거 <br>가벼운 게 낫지 그러면 아마도 <br>나중에 내가 너를 <br>놓아주기 쉬울걸 <br>그게 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 나는 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 <br>]]></content><category term="레디 (Reddy)" label="레디 (Reddy)"/><category term="너라도 (Feat. 김보아 Of SPICA)" label="너라도 (Feat. 김보아 Of SPICA)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서사무엘_Samuel_Seo/ENTOURAGE/</id><title>서사무엘 (Samuel Seo) - ENTOURAGE - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:04:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:04:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EC%82%AC%EB%AC%B4%EC%97%98_Samuel_Seo/ENTOURAGE/" title="서사무엘 (Samuel Seo) - ENTOURAGE - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[간혹 곁에 있는 <br>사람들에 질리기도 해 <br>마주 앉아 있기 <br>따분해 질때도 있고 <br>다만 그때만큼은 편안해 <br>지는것도 사실이니 <br>Let them be a part of you <br>Let them be a part of you <br>Let them be a part of you <br>Let them be a part of you <br>지금 나와 같이 걷는 <br>사람이 많아 보이고 <br>언제 그중 누가 <br>멀어져 있을진 몰라도 <br>그건 뭐 알 바 아냐 <br>CUZ NOW WE’RE <br>ALL GOIN TOGETHER TO <br>Somewhere we've never been <br>거기엔 뭐가 있을지 <br>몰라도 그건 <br>must be something <br>that we’ve never seen <br>in our lives <br>하나 확실한건 <br>그게 뭐가 됐건 <br>돌아보면 웃길거고 <br>우린 그걸 즐기고 있어 <br>아무것도 걱정할 <br>필요가 없지 <br>우린 그냥 즐기고 있어 <br>We’re just enjoying our lives <br>We’re just enjoying our lives <br>We’re just enjoying our lives <br>We’re just enjoying our lives <br>가끔 작은 일에 <br>기분 상할 때 있어 <br>다만 움직일 땐 <br>서롤 보며 깨있어 <br>등을 마주대고 <br>편히 기댈 수 있기에 <br>맘을 다잡고선 <br>내일을 준비할 수 있어 <br>기쁜 하루이길 바래 <br>너의 하루도 <br>너의 사람들과 <br>행복하길 바래 <br>누군가가 곁에 <br>있는것은 당연한게 아냐 <br>무뎌지지말고 감사하며 <br>좀 더 즐겨 <br>Let them be a part of you <br>Let them be a part of you <br>Let them be a part of you <br>Let them be a part of you <br>We’re just enjoying our lives <br>We’re just enjoying our lives <br>We’re just enjoying our lives <br>We’re just enjoying our lives <br>Somewhere we've never been <br>거기엔 뭐가 있을지 <br>몰라도 그건 <br>must be something <br>that we’ve never seen <br>in our lives <br>]]></content><category term="서사무엘 (Samuel Seo)" label="서사무엘 (Samuel Seo)"/><category term="ENTOURAGE" label="ENTOURAGE"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/에디킴/2NIGHT/</id><title>에디킴 - 2NIGHT - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:04:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:04:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%90%EB%94%94%ED%82%B4/2NIGHT/" title="에디킴 - 2NIGHT - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[baby when we go <br>to the party day <br>달리자 잠든 도시의 밤 <br>조금 늦었지 금방 갈게 <br>울리는 <br>phone call <br>재촉 그만해 <br>오늘 우리가 함께 <br>그려나갈 이 밤에 <br>수많은 색깔들을 <br>나는 chill 할거야 <br>지나가는 터널의 <br>빛들은 오렌지색 <br>오늘은 다시 <br>돌아오지 않을 거야 <br>Under the moonlight <br>Everyday I feel alright <br>waiting for tonight <br>모두 함께 춤추자 <br>I just wanna get it tonight <br>and you and you <br>I just wanna leave tonight <br>with you with you <br>오늘 밤은 편하게 할래 <br>멋을 부리는 건 피할게 <br>나도 사람이고 <br>어린데 가식 떠는 건 <br>좋게 할 수가 없는 것 같아 <br>왜 오늘은 야자수가 되려 해 <br>시끄러운 것은 피해 <br>바람을 맞으며 달릴래 <br>그래 이 도시를 <br>내 섬으로 만들어 <br>뿌리내리고 <br>집을 지어 <br>조용하게 파티해 <br>Oh no 난 내가 좋아하는 <br>사람들만 초대하고 <br>누워 별을 보며 <br>바람으로 샤워해 <br>그리고 내 잎으로 <br>옷을 만들어 입고 <br>열매를 따서 마시지 <br>진탕 취해 빠져 <br>너도 같은 생각을 <br>하고 있음 해 <br>나는 이게 좋아 <br>우리 같이 느낄래 <br>아마 오늘 같은 날은 <br>오지 않을 거야 <br>계속 내 옆에 있어줘 <br>기분을 나누자 okay <br>Under the moonlight <br>Everyday I feel alright <br>waiting for tonight <br>모두 함께 춤추자 <br>I just wanna get it tonight <br>and you and you <br>I just wanna leave tonight <br>with you with you <br>]]></content><category term="에디킴" label="에디킴"/><category term="2NIGHT" label="2NIGHT"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dok2/The_Good_Feat_Hash_swan/</id><title>Dok2 - The Good (Feat. Hash swan) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:04:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:04:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dok2/The_Good_Feat_Hash_swan/" title="Dok2 - The Good (Feat. Hash swan) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want the good life <br>걱정은 다 버려 <br>The good life <br>더 높이 손 뻗어 <br>The good life <br>성공을 다 거둬 <br>La la la la la la la <br>I want the good life <br>걱정은 다 버려 <br>The good life <br>더 높이 손 뻗어 <br>The good life <br>성공을 다 거둬 <br>La la la la la la la <br>심각하게 살아뭐해 <br>사사건건 알아뭐해 <br>세상의 저울에 <br>니 자신 달아 뭐해 <br>친구가 먼저 성공한다면 <br>그냥 하라고해 <br>정상에 먼저 가고 싶다면 <br>그럼 가라고해 <br>우린 뛰어가지 <br>않아도 돼 <br>모두가 같은 곳을 <br>당연한듯 바라볼때 <br>I gotta go get my own <br>Grinding and hustle on <br>우린 우리 뜻대로 <br>즐기면서 살아도돼 <br>심각하게 살아 뭐해 <br>잘 살아보겠다 한다면 <br>피곤할땐 잠깐쯤은 <br>눈을 감아도 돼 <br>전재산을 털어 <br>어디든지 가봐도 돼 <br>어리기에 뭘해도 <br>삶의 끝은 아직 까마득해 <br>어차피 곧 도달할걸 알어 <br>그럼 따라오는게 돈 <br>실팬 미래를 빛낼 <br>한 컷 다 시나리오 <br>It is so good Forever young <br>완벽한 삶에는 <br>젊음이 소품 <br>I want the good life <br>걱정은 다 버려 <br>The good life <br>더 높이 손 뻗어 <br>The good life <br>성공을 다 거둬 <br>La la la la la la la <br>I want the good life <br>걱정은 다 버려 <br>The good life <br>더 높이 손 뻗어 <br>The good life <br>성공을 다 거둬 <br>La la la la la la la <br>불가능은 없어야하는게 <br>또 우리의 주의 <br>네가 자신있다면 <br>신경쓸 필요 없지 굳이 <br>야망이 커지면 높아져야지 <br>약속의 수위 <br>부자가 되겠다는 <br>내 가사도 극사실주의 <br>생각보다 간단해 답 <br>우린 알고 있단거지 <br>허세와 야망의 차이 <br>WOW 훗날 가장 뻔한 질문에 <br>가장 뻔하게 <br>답 할 수 있어야지 <br>Yea I’m fine and u <br>Who Me Im feelin great <br>Chillin at the belvedere <br>illionaire <br>Ambition in the buildin <br>hash swan wattup <br>야망만을 믿고 <br>우린 젊음을 다 걸어 <br>어려운게 문제라면 <br>답답해할 일 없이 <br>그냥 즐기다보면 <br>적들에게 패 할일 없이 <br>내말은 업신여기면 <br>지나갈 시련과 고생 <br>Life roll coasting u kno <br>what im saying <br>I want the good life <br>걱정은 다 버려 <br>The good life <br>더 높이 손 뻗어 <br>The good life <br>성공을 다 거둬 <br>La la la la la la la <br>I want the good life <br>걱정은 다 버려 <br>The good life <br>더 높이 손 뻗어 <br>The good life <br>성공을 다 거둬 <br>La la la la la la la <br>I want the good life <br>걱정은 다 버려 <br>The good life <br>더 높이 손 뻗어 <br>The good life <br>성공을 다 거둬 <br>La la la la la la la <br>I want the good life <br>걱정은 다 버려 <br>The good life <br>더 높이 손 뻗어 <br>The good life <br>성공을 다 거둬 <br>La la la la la la la <br>]]></content><category term="Dok2" label="Dok2"/><category term="The Good (Feat. Hash swan)" label="The Good (Feat. Hash swan)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/혁오_HYUKOH/MASITNONSOUL/</id><title>혁오 (HYUKOH) - MASITNONSOUL - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:04:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:04:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%98%81%EC%98%A4_HYUKOH/MASITNONSOUL/" title="혁오 (HYUKOH) - MASITNONSOUL - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[술이 물이 되고 <br>물이 불이 되는 한 잔에 <br>부리부리하던 <br>우리 눈이 열려 한 잔에 <br>둘이 셋이 되고 <br>셋이 넷이 되는 한 잔에 <br>우리들이 부은 술이 <br>불이 돼서 뜨겁네 <br>술이 물이 되고 <br>물이 술이 되어버렸네 <br>부리부리하던 <br>눈을 부려봐도 똑같네 <br>둘이 셋이 되고 <br>셋이 넷이 되는 첫 잔에 <br>우리들이 부은 술이 <br>불이 돼서 뜨겁네 <br>보리 술이 소리 없이 <br>우리 잔에 담기네 <br>구리 구리하던 무리들이 <br>잔을 들치네 <br>둘이 셋인지 셋이 넷인진 <br>모르겠지만 <br>우리들이 부은 술이 <br>아직까진 뜨겁네 <br>집에 가는 줄이 <br>멀리 멀리 길이 되어도 <br>우리 둘이 집이 멀다 해도 <br>나는 마시리 <br>우리들이 그리 술이 <br>굳이 좋은 이유는 <br>유리잔에 술이 <br>술이 아닌 달릴 술이니 <br>매일 매일 매일 <br>매일 매일 여기 모여 <br>매일 매일 매일 <br>매일 매일 여기 모여 <br>매일 매일 매일 <br>매일 매일 여기 모여 <br>매일 매일 매일 <br>매일 매일 여기 모여 <br>]]></content><category term="혁오 (HYUKOH)" label="혁오 (HYUKOH)"/><category term="MASITNONSOUL" label="MASITNONSOUL"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/밀라노/맞아_우리_헤어졌지/</id><title>밀라노 - 맞아 우리 헤어졌지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:04:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:04:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%80%EB%9D%BC%EB%85%B8/%EB%A7%9E%EC%95%84_%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%ED%97%A4%EC%96%B4%EC%A1%8C%EC%A7%80/" title="밀라노 - 맞아 우리 헤어졌지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기억이 안 나 <br>아니 생각도 안 나 <br>네가 어땠었는지 <br>그때는 넌 분명히 <br>날 사랑하는 눈빛이었는데 <br>나를 보고 있어도 <br>다른 곳을 보는 것 같은 <br>너의 그 차가운 눈빛이 <br>너무 다른 사람처럼 <br>나를 밀어내서 <br>한참 멍하니 서서 있다가도 <br>눈물이 흘러 뭐지 <br>슬프진 않은데 <br>맞아 우리 헤어졌지 그랬었지 <br>바로 어제 헤어진 것 같아 <br>혼자 있는 게 <br>이젠 익숙해 <br>너와 있던 그 시간이 <br>마치 거짓말처럼 <br>아무 일도 없었던 듯이 그래 <br>사랑하긴 했을까 <br>아니 사랑이긴 했을까 <br>이렇게 바보같이 <br>나 혼자만 사랑했나 <br>아직도 난 사랑하나 <br>한참 멍하니 서서 있다가도 <br>눈물이 흘러 뭐지 <br>슬프진 않은데 <br>맞아 우리 헤어졌지 그랬었지 <br>너 떠난 지 일 년이 되던 날 <br>]]></content><category term="밀라노" label="밀라노"/><category term="맞아 우리 헤어졌지" label="맞아 우리 헤어졌지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/틴트_먹는_남자/Temptation/</id><title>틴트 먹는 남자 - Temptation - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:04:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:04:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8B%B4%ED%8A%B8_%EB%A8%B9%EB%8A%94_%EB%82%A8%EC%9E%90/Temptation/" title="틴트 먹는 남자 - Temptation - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[차가운 너의 시선을 보는 일이 <br>내겐 그 어떤 외로움과도 <br>같은 시간들 <br>사람들의 시선을 <br>의식하지도 못한 채 <br>나의 시린 발걸음은 <br>너에게로 가는 걸 <br>It`s temptation <br>무슨 표정을 지을지 모른 채로 <br>나는 너의 품에 안겨서 <br>또 많은 시간을 <br>너무 따스한 <br>너의 온기에 한껏 취해서 <br>점점 멀어지는 <br>너의 향기를 그려 본다 <br>Through your scene <br>Nobody know that I see <br>난 너무 어렵지도 않아 <br>내겐 니가 정말 필요한 걸 <br>Don`t you know that I can <br>다 알아 너도 나를 원해 <br>어서 내게 <br>단념 할 수 없었던 <br>그 날의 난 너를 기억 하네 <br>이제 나를 받아줘 <br>오늘이 지나면 워 난 <br>잊을 수가 없었어 <br>그 날의 너의 향기마저도 <br>내게 너란 사람이 또 <br>나를 흔들어 <br>always I crave your temptation <br>Nobody know that I see <br>난 너무 어렵지도 않아 <br>내겐 니가 정말 필요한 걸 <br>Don`t you know that I can <br>다 알아 너도 나를 원해 <br>어서 내게 <br>give me love together <br>다가 갈 수 없었어 그땐 <br>이제와 무슨 소용이 있어 <br>어쩔 수가 없었어 그날 <br>그 어떤 변명도 난 <br>단념 할 수 없었던 <br>그 날의 난 너를 기억 하네 <br>이제 나를 받아줘 <br>오늘이 지나면 워 난 <br>잊을 수가 없었어 <br>그 날의 너의 향기마저도 <br>내게 너란 사람이 또 <br>나를 흔들어 오 난 <br>바라보기만 했던 <br>그 날의 난 너를 유혹 하네 <br>이젠 나를 안아줘 <br>오늘 밤 너에게 난 치명적인 <br>It`s temptation <br>]]></content><category term="틴트 먹는 남자" label="틴트 먹는 남자"/><category term="Temptation" label="Temptation"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Don_Marco/Chup_Chups_Feat_Maboos_LoLa_Korean_Ver/</id><title>Don Marco - Chup Chups (Feat. Maboos, LoLa) (Korean Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:04:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:04:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Don_Marco/Chup_Chups_Feat_Maboos_LoLa_Korean_Ver/" title="Don Marco - Chup Chups (Feat. Maboos, LoLa) (Korean Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한잔 들이킨 다음 <br>down된 내 마음을 <br>up 시키며 준비운동 끝 uh <br>알콜이 들어가니 <br>긴장이 풀어지고 <br>피가 돌지 느낌 <br>so good uh <br>내 잔이 비는 순간 <br>우진이 넌 죽어 <br>널 산체로 부검 <br>so 계속해서 부어부어 <br>따러따러 마셔 마셔 <br>내일 따윈없어 <br>we gon' party <br>like a mo' fucka <br>we gon' party <br>like a mo' fucka <br>오늘 밤에는 너를 먹어 <br>like a mo' fucka <br>내 눈에 찍힌 이상 <br>오늘 집에 못가 <br>아까부터 지켜봤지 <br>mocca색 네 다리 <br>네 바디 라인 <br>탐험 하고싶어 <br>너의 속을 들어갈래 <br>난 오늘 악마의 소굴 <br>u got me so hard <br>so I'll fuck u so hard <br>그정도는 기본 예절 <br>pour me some hard shit <br>오늘 mami 너를 원해 <br>wut u think ma <br>chup chups Imma lick you <br>like chupa chups <br>chup chups <br>strawberry blueberry <br>달콤한 너는 마치 <br>나의 lollipop <br>너 때문에 밤새 tongue out <br>땀이 범벅되지 않게 <br>놀아볼까 why not <br>불은 끄지마 <br>cuz I wanna see your body go <br>Mira mami 말해봐 <br>오늘밤 너가 원하는거 <br>let it out <br>나와 함께라면 <br>들어줄께 모두다 <br>아무것도 걱정마 <br>그러니 조금 더 <br>가까이 다가와 <br>딱 붙어 머리부터 발끝까지 <br>땀에 흠뻑 적셔 <br>화끈하게 털어 <br>dale duro no pare freak it damn <br>위아래로 up and down <br>천천히 온몸으로 느껴 날 <br>밤이 깊어가면 갈수록 <br>올라가는 자신감 <br>going HAM <br>hard as a motherfucker <br>눈치보지말고 내려놔 <br>break it down rompo <br>pump pump pump <br>날이 밝아지면 <br>이미 내품안에 네여자 <br>집에가기 싫다고 <br>울고불고 난리나 <br>Oye mami suelta y aprieta <br>chup chups suelta y aprieta <br>chup chups aprieta la boca <br>rebota no pares muevela la cola <br>Yo te meto hot fire <br>el tigre enlocado <br>vroom vroom te levanta <br>se que te gusta sticky paleta <br>damelo no te hagas la santa <br>Yo te meto hot fire <br>trilingo chupeta mami te alocas <br>se que tu buscas sticky paleta <br>damelo no te hagas la santa <br>Pero papi que sucio tu nasty <br>flow humpty dumty moja party <br>dirty tu sabe me encanta <br>ay papi damelo baby <br>Ya te meto right now <br>el tigre enlocado <br>vroom vroom te levanta <br>se que te gusta sticky paleta <br>dimelo no te hagas la sota <br>Si mi papi que rico que tasty <br>tu flow bien sucio bien crazy <br>dirty fuego candela <br>oye Don Marco damelo baby <br>]]></content><category term="Don Marco" label="Don Marco"/><category term="Chup Chups (Feat. Maboos, LoLa) (Korean Ver.)" label="Chup Chups (Feat. Maboos, LoLa) (Korean Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Don_Marco/Chup_Chups_Feat_LoLa/</id><title>Don Marco - Chup Chups (Feat. LoLa) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:04:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:04:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Don_Marco/Chup_Chups_Feat_LoLa/" title="Don Marco - Chup Chups (Feat. LoLa) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Mira mira quien llego a la fiesta <br>el Corlatinflow ponte lista <br>ya tu sabes agarro los bumpers <br>rompo pump pump y <br>las nena lo saben <br>tocala ponte fiera <br>mami bien wild <br>dale vale todo lo que <br>tu quieras get down <br>mojadita te veo buen wet <br>no pare sigue el perreo <br>Oye mami suelta y aprieta <br>chup chups suelta y aprieta <br>chup chups aprieta la boca <br>rebota no pares muevela la cola <br>Oye mami suelta y aprieta <br>chup chups suelta y aprieta <br>chups chup aprieta la boca <br>rebota no pares muevela la cola <br>Yo te meto hot fire <br>trilingo chupeta mami te alocas <br>se que tu buscas sticky paleta <br>damelo no te hagas la santa <br>Pero papi que sucio tu nasty <br>flow humpty dumty moja party <br>dirty tu sabe me encanta <br>ay papi damelo baby <br>Vamos mi gente a romper la pista <br>choque toquen toque choquen <br>salta mi loba la noche no para <br>agarrala saca tu gangster <br>put it on ya mi chinky <br>monster esta pegao <br>abusalo sacudelo ya amarralo <br>hey bae dont stop sigue el perreo <br>Desemvuelta date la vuelta <br>chup chups sexy coqueta <br>chup chups aprietala gata <br>brinca tu sabe muevela la cola <br>Desemvuelta date la vuelta <br>chup chups sexy coqueta <br>chup chups aprietala gata <br>brinca tu sabe muevela la cola <br>Ya te meto right now <br>el tigre enlocado <br>vroom vroom te levanta <br>se que te gusta sticky paleta <br>dimelo no te hagas la sota <br>Si mi papi que rico que tasty <br>tu flow bien sucio bien crazy <br>dirty fuego candela <br>oye don marco damelo baby <br>Yo te meto hot fire <br>trilingo chupeta mami te alocas <br>se que tu buscas sticky paleta <br>damelo no te hagas la santa <br>Pero papi que sucio tu nasty <br>flow humpty dumty moja party <br>dirty tu sabe me encanta <br>ay papi damelo baby <br>Ya te meto right now <br>el tigre enlocado <br>vroom vroom te levanta <br>se que te gusta sticky paleta <br>dimelo no te hagas la sota <br>Si mi papi que rico que tasty <br>tu flow bien sucio bien crazy <br>dirty fuego candela <br>oye don marco damelo baby <br>]]></content><category term="Don Marco" label="Don Marco"/><category term="Chup Chups (Feat. LoLa)" label="Chup Chups (Feat. LoLa)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최민준/23/</id><title>최민준 - 23 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:04:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:04:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EB%AF%BC%EC%A4%80/23/" title="최민준 - 23 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루살이 지겹고 치여도 <br>인생살이 버겁고 지쳐도 <br>주름살이 생기고 말아도 <br>웃으면서 내일 <br>뭐할지 생각하고 <br>자며 꿈들 꾸자고 <br>아직은 내가 스물셋 <br>철없는 꼬마아이셔 <br>맥주를 마시긴 하는데 <br>젤리랑 같이 아이셔 <br>아직은 내가 스물셋 <br>철없는 꼬마아이셔 <br>소주를 마시긴 하는데 <br>젤리랑 같이 아이써 <br>다들 이렇게 사는걸까 <br>적어도 내 주변 사람들은 <br>다 그냥 그렇게 <br>살아가는 중이야 <br>내가 잘하고 있는걸까 <br>아마도 유재석이 그랬어 <br>내일 뭐하지 <br>내일 뭐하지 했었다고 <br>그 얘기를 내가 <br>다시 쓰는 중이야 <br>3년만 더 고생하자 <br>우리엄마 말씀하신지 <br>3년째인 지금 5년만 <br>더 고생하자 <br>말씀하시고 <br>이제 그만 <br>고생하셨음 좋겠는데 <br>아직은 내가 스물셋 <br>철없는 꼬마아이셔 <br>맥주를 마시긴 하는데 <br>젤리랑 같이 아이셔 <br>아직은 내가 스물셋 <br>철없는 꼬마아이셔 <br>소주를 마시긴 하는데 <br>젤리랑 같이 아이써 <br>늘어가 게으름이 <br>아무것도 사랑하기 <br>힘들어져 <br>뜨겁지도 차갑지도 <br>이러다 꿈도 <br>희망도 잃을지도 <br>아니 잊었다고 <br>다시 떠올려도 <br>사랑은 젊을때 <br>많이들 해보라고 <br>동틀때까지 먹고 <br>마시고 놀아 <br>아침공기 상쾌해 <br>집으로 돌아가 <br>하루살이 지겹고 치여도 <br>인생살이 버겁고 지쳐도 <br>주름살이 생기고 말아도 <br>웃으면서 내일 뭐할지 생각하고 <br>자며 꿈들 꾸자고 <br>]]></content><category term="최민준" label="최민준"/><category term="23" label="23"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조관우/겨울이야기_Part2_Inst/</id><title>조관우 - 겨울이야기 Part.2 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:05:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:05:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EA%B4%80%EC%9A%B0/%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC%EA%B8%B0_Part2_Inst/" title="조관우 - 겨울이야기 Part.2 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[들렸었나요 <br>그 때 그 겨울 노래 <br>두 손 차던 계절에 <br>흰 눈 오던 날 <br>그대 흔적 꺼내며 <br>다시 내게 돌아오라던 <br>하얗게 하얗게 내리면 <br>어느새 흐른 뜨거운 눈물로 <br>부르고 부르면 볼 수 있다고 <br>매 겨울마다 그대를 부르네요 <br>아름답네요 <br>추억속의 그대는 <br>그 미소 참 따뜻하네요 <br>많이 변했겠죠 <br>그대와 나 모두가 <br>하지만 가슴은 아는지 <br>하얗게 하얗게 내리면 <br>어느새 흐른 뜨거운 눈물로 <br>부르고 부르면 볼 수 있다며 <br>기다리는 나 이렇게 <br>이 겨울지나 또 봄이 오면 <br>모두 다 녹아버릴까 <br>얼어붙게 만들었죠 눈물로 <br>하얗게 하얗게 내리면 <br>그리워 그리워 찾겠죠 <br>다시 찾겠죠 <br>눈물로 바꾼 그대와의 기억 <br>부르고 불러도 볼 순 없나요 <br>눈빛 마주칠 한 순간 만이라도 <br>]]></content><category term="조관우" label="조관우"/><category term="겨울이야기 Part.2 (Inst.)" label="겨울이야기 Part.2 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/명왕성에버랜드/여기가_내_집이니_그건_여행이었지/</id><title>명왕성에버랜드 - 여기가 내 집이니 그건 여행이었지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:06:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:06:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AA%85%EC%99%95%EC%84%B1%EC%97%90%EB%B2%84%EB%9E%9C%EB%93%9C/%EC%97%AC%EA%B8%B0%EA%B0%80_%EB%82%B4_%EC%A7%91%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%88_%EA%B7%B8%EA%B1%B4_%EC%97%AC%ED%96%89%EC%9D%B4%EC%97%88%EC%A7%80/" title="명왕성에버랜드 - 여기가 내 집이니 그건 여행이었지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어둑해질 무렵 <br>가로등은 빛났다 <br>귀에 꽂은 음악은 <br>아무것도 말해주지 않았다 <br>나는 오늘 여행을 <br>마치고 돌아왔다 <br>어둑해질 무렵 <br>여행은 끝났다 <br>혼자인 채 <br>카메라도 없이 <br>남은 기억만 고스란히 남아 <br>눈이 오면 오는 대로 <br>또 바람 불면 부는 대로 <br>어느 빗소리로 떠올리겠지 <br>여행이 아닌 어느 날 <br>그냥 길거리였다 <br>아니 바다였다 산이었다 <br>아니 그게 뭐였든지 <br>난 여행하길 관뒀으니까 <br>더 이상 어떤 이야기 이길 <br>멈췄으니까 <br>어두워질 무렵 <br>여행은 끝났다 <br>갑자기 <br>그러나 서서히 묵직하게 <br>돌아오기 싫어 한숨 쉬었지만 <br>여기가 내 집이니 <br>그건 여행이었지 <br>혼자인 채 <br>카메라도 없이 <br>남은 기억만 고스란히 남아 <br>눈이 오면 오는 대로 <br>또 바람불면 부는 대로 <br>혼자인 채 <br>카메라도 없이 <br>남은 기억만 고스란히 남아 <br>눈이 오면 오는 대로 <br>또 바람불면 부는 대로 <br>어느 빗소리로 떠올리겠지 <br>여행이 아닌 어느 날 <br>]]></content><category term="명왕성에버랜드" label="명왕성에버랜드"/><category term="여기가 내 집이니 그건 여행이었지" label="여기가 내 집이니 그건 여행이었지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조연/갈망_Feat_토닉케이/</id><title>조연 - 갈망 (Feat. 토닉케이) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:08:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:08:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%97%B0/%EA%B0%88%EB%A7%9D_Feat_%ED%86%A0%EB%8B%89%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4/" title="조연 - 갈망 (Feat. 토닉케이) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 그토록 바래왔던 갈망은 <br>내가 그토록 찾아왔던 갈망은 <br>주님 바로 당신이란 걸 <br>나는 이제 알 것 같아요 <br>주님 내 곁에 찾아오셔서 <br>나의 영혼을 꼭 안아주소서 <br>내가 그토록 <br>내가 그토록 갈망했던 <br>사랑은 주님 <br>바로 당신이란 걸 <br>나를 죄와 사망에서 건지신 <br>예수 주님 <br>한 분만을 노래합니다 <br>내가 그토록 <br>내가 그토록 갈망했던 <br>사랑은 주님 <br>바로 당신이란 걸 <br>나를 죄와 사망에서 건지신 <br>예수 주님 <br>한 분만을 노래합니다 <br>어떤 권세도 어떤 유혹도 <br>어떤 권세도 우릴 해할 수 없죠 <br>어떤 핍박도 어떤 유혹도 <br>어떤 권세도 우릴 해할 수 없죠 <br>내가 그토록 <br>내가 그토록 갈망했던 <br>사랑은 주님 <br>바로 당신이란 걸 <br>나를 죄와 사망에서 건지신 <br>예수 주님 <br>한 분만을 노래합니다 <br>내가 그토록 <br>내가 그토록 갈망했던 <br>사랑은 주님 <br>바로 당신이란 걸 <br>나를 죄와 사망에서 <br>건지신 예수 주님 <br>한 분만을 노래합니다 <br>갈망합니다 <br>]]></content><category term="조연" label="조연"/><category term="갈망 (Feat. 토닉케이)" label="갈망 (Feat. 토닉케이)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Flosstradamus/Prison_Riot/</id><title>Flosstradamus - Prison Riot - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:08:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:08:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Flosstradamus/Prison_Riot/" title="Flosstradamus - Prison Riot - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I came in this bitch to sweat <br>I came in this bitch to wild the fuck out <br>I came in this bitch to turn up <br><br>Shit, me and my niggas in here fucked up <br>Ain't no tellin' what we're gonna do when the fuckin' bass drops <br>Fuck it <br>Act up like a mothafuckin' prison riot <br><br>Fuck it <br><br>Put your middle fingers up, if you don't give a fuck <br>Middle fingers up, cause you don't give a fuck <br>Put your middle fingers up, if you don't give a fuck <br>Middle fingers up if you don't give a fuck <br><br>I came in this bitch to fuckin' rave <br>I came in this bitch to smoke the fuck out <br>I came in this bitch to get plurnt <br><br>Shit, me and my niggas in here fucked up <br>Ain't no tellin' what we're gonna do when the fuckin' bass drops <br>Fuck it <br>Act up like a mothafuckin' prison riot riot, riot, riot <br><br>Fuck it <br><br>Put your middle fingers up, if you don't give a fuck <br>Middle fingers up, cause you don't give a fuck <br>Put your middle fingers up, if you don't give a fuck <br>Middle fingers up if you don't give a fuck]]></content><category term="Flosstradamus" label="Flosstradamus"/><category term="Prison Riot" label="Prison Riot"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나들목교회/더불어_함께/</id><title>나들목교회 - 더불어 함께 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:08:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:08:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%93%A4%EB%AA%A9%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C/%EB%8D%94%EB%B6%88%EC%96%B4_%ED%95%A8%EA%BB%98/" title="나들목교회 - 더불어 함께 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[더불어 함께 이 길을 가네 <br>혼자라면 외롭고 힘들었을 이 길 <br>더불어 함께 이 길을 가네 <br>지켜보며 세워주는 이들과 함께 <br>더불어 함께 이 길을 가네 <br>혼자라면 거칠고 모나게 살아갈 <br>더불어 함께 이 길을 가네 <br>그의 형상 닮아가는 이들과 함께 <br>이제 더 이상 <br>나만의 세계 구하지 않으리 <br>더불어 함께 살며 <br>그 분의 나라 드러내리 <br>이제 더 이상 <br>나만의 세계 구하지 않으리 <br>더불어 함께 살며 <br>그 분의 나라 드러내리 <br>더불어 함께 이 길을 가네 <br>이천년 동안 계속 이어져 온 이 길 <br>더불어 함께 이 길을 가네 <br>그의 나라 올 때까지 이어질 이 길 <br>더불어 함께라면 <br>외롭지 않아 이길 <br>혼자서 라면 절대 못 갔을 이 길 <br>지켜보며 세워주는 이들과 함께 <br>그의 형상 닮아가는 당신과 함께 <br>나만의 세계 나만의 이익 <br>나만의 기쁨 구하지 않아 <br>그분의 나라 그분의 가치 <br>나타내리라 <br>그의 나라 올 때까지 <br>그의 나라 임할 때까지 <br>더불어 함께 이 길을 가네 <br>이제 더 이상 <br>나만의 세계 구하지 않으리 <br>더불어 함께 살며 <br>그 분의 나라 드러내리 <br>이제 더 이상 <br>나만의 세계 구하지 않으리 <br>더불어 함께 살며 <br>그 분의 나라 드러내리 <br>더불어 함께 이 길을 가네 <br>이천년 동안 계속 이어져 온 이 길 <br>더불어 함께 이 길을 가네 <br>그의 나라 올 때까지 이어질 이 길 <br>더불어 함께 이 길을 가네 <br>이천년 동안 계속 이어져 온 이 길 <br>더불어 함께 이 길을 가네 <br>그의 나라 올 때까지 이어질 이 길 <br>그의 나라 올 때까지 이어질 이 길 <br>그의 나라 올 때까지 이어질 이 길 <br>]]></content><category term="나들목교회" label="나들목교회"/><category term="더불어 함께" label="더불어 함께"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나들목교회/복이라/</id><title>나들목교회 - 복이라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:08:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:08:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%93%A4%EB%AA%A9%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C/%EB%B3%B5%EC%9D%B4%EB%9D%BC/" title="나들목교회 - 복이라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주님과 함께 하는 것이 복이라 <br>주님의 마음 아는 것이 축복이라 <br>주님과 함께 걷는 것이 복이라 <br>주님의 사랑 노래함이 행복이라 <br>주님과 함께 하는 것이 복이라 <br>주님의 마음 아는 것이 축복이라 <br>주님과 함께 걷는 것이 복이라 <br>주님의 사랑 노래함이 행복이라 <br>주님 주신 복이라 <br>주님 주신 복이라 <br>]]></content><category term="나들목교회" label="나들목교회"/><category term="복이라" label="복이라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나들목교회/축복합니다/</id><title>나들목교회 - 축복합니다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:08:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:08:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%93%A4%EB%AA%A9%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C/%EC%B6%95%EB%B3%B5%ED%95%A9%EB%8B%88%EB%8B%A4/" title="나들목교회 - 축복합니다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[축복합니다 당신의 새로운 시작 <br>사랑으로 다시 태어난 <br>당신을 축복합니다 <br>응원합니다 당신의 새로운 도전 <br>믿음으로 다시 일어선 <br>당신을 응원합니다 <br>축복합니다 당신의 새로운 시작 <br>사랑으로 다시 태어난 <br>당신을 축복합니다 <br>응원합니다 당신의 새로운 도전 <br>믿음으로 다시 일어선 <br>당신을 응원합니다 <br>홀로 걸어왔던 길 <br>이젠 주님과 함께 <br>외롭고 힘든 세상 <br>이젠 우리와 함께 걸어요 <br>기대합니다 당신의 새로운 내일 <br>사랑으로 다시 태어난 <br>당신을 기대합니다 <br>홀로 걸어왔던 길 <br>이젠 주님과 함께 <br>외롭고 힘든 세상 <br>이젠 우리와 함께 걸어요 <br>기대합니다 당신의 새로운 내일 <br>사랑으로 다시 태어난 <br>당신을 기대합니다 <br>사랑으로 다시 태어난 <br>당신을 축복합니다 <br>]]></content><category term="나들목교회" label="나들목교회"/><category term="축복합니다" label="축복합니다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나들목교회/들어주소서_우리_기도를/</id><title>나들목교회 - 들어주소서 우리 기도를 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:08:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:08:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%93%A4%EB%AA%A9%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C/%EB%93%A4%EC%96%B4%EC%A3%BC%EC%86%8C%EC%84%9C_%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EA%B8%B0%EB%8F%84%EB%A5%BC/" title="나들목교회 - 들어주소서 우리 기도를 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[들어 주소서 우리 기도를 <br>평화의 주님 선하신 하나님 <br>받아 주소서 우리 마음을 <br>평화의 주님 선하신 하나님 <br>빚어 주소서 우리의 삶을 <br>평화의 주님 선하신 하나님 <br>평화의 주님 선하신 하나님 <br>아멘 <br>]]></content><category term="나들목교회" label="나들목교회"/><category term="들어주소서 우리 기도를" label="들어주소서 우리 기도를"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나들목교회/사랑과_진실이_눈을_맞추고/</id><title>나들목교회 - 사랑과 진실이 눈을 맞추고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:09:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:09:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%93%A4%EB%AA%A9%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EA%B3%BC_%EC%A7%84%EC%8B%A4%EC%9D%B4_%EB%88%88%EC%9D%84_%EB%A7%9E%EC%B6%94%EA%B3%A0/" title="나들목교회 - 사랑과 진실이 눈을 맞추고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑과 진실이 <br>눈을 맞추고 <br>정의와 평화가 <br>입을 맞추리라 <br>땅에서는 진실이 <br>돋아나오고 <br>하늘에선 정의가 <br>굽어보리라 <br>사랑과 진실이 <br>눈을 맞추고 <br>정의와 평화가 <br>입을 맞추리라 <br>땅에서는 진실이 <br>돋아나오고 <br>하늘에선 정의가 <br>굽어보리라 <br>야훼께서 복을 <br>내리시리니 <br>우리 땅이 <br>열매를 맺어 주리라 <br>야훼께서 복을 <br>내리시리니 <br>우리 땅이 <br>열매를 맺어 주리라 <br>정의가 당신 앞을 <br>걸어 나가고 <br>평화가 그 발자취를 <br>따라가리라 <br>정의가 당신 앞을 <br>걸어 나가고 <br>평화가 그 발자취를 <br>따라가리라 <br>주의 평화가 <br>야훼께서 복을 <br>내리시리니 <br>우리 땅이 열매를 <br>맺어 주리라 <br>야훼께서 복을 <br>내리시리니 <br>우리 땅이 열매를 <br>맺어 주리라 <br>정의가 당신 앞을 <br>걸어 나가고 <br>평화가 그 발자취를 <br>따라가리라 <br>정의가 당신 앞을 <br>걸어 나가고 <br>평화가 그 발자취를 <br>따라가리라 <br>정의가 당신 앞을 <br>걸어 나가고 <br>평화가 그 발자취를 <br>따라가리라 <br>주의 평화가 <br>주의 정의가 <br>주의 사랑이 <br>주의 진실이 <br>주의 평화가 <br>주의 정의가 <br>주의 사랑이 <br>주의 진실이 <br>주의 평화가 <br>]]></content><category term="나들목교회" label="나들목교회"/><category term="사랑과 진실이 눈을 맞추고" label="사랑과 진실이 눈을 맞추고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나들목교회/하늘가족_우리교회/</id><title>나들목교회 - 하늘가족 우리교회 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:09:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:09:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%93%A4%EB%AA%A9%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C/%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98%EA%B0%80%EC%A1%B1_%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C/" title="나들목교회 - 하늘가족 우리교회 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리는 주의 <br>거룩한 보혈로 세워진 <br>살아 숨 쉬는 교회 <br>예수를 주로 <br>섬기며 살아가네 <br>우린 주님 안에 한 가족 <br>하늘 아버지 <br>우리 안에 계시네 <br>우린 그 날 향한 <br>하늘 가족 <br>아버지여 우릴 도우사 <br>사랑하게 하소서 <br>주의 영광을 보네 <br>우린 하늘의 가족 <br>오 하늘 아버지 <br>이 백성의 아버지 <br>당신의 귀한 <br>아들 보내신 높은 사랑 <br>오 하늘 아버지 <br>이 백성의 아버지 <br>하늘 가족 교회 통하여 <br>이 땅의 백성 고치소서 <br>하늘 아버지 <br>우리 안에 계시네 <br>우린 그 날 향한 <br>하늘 가족 <br>아버지여 우릴 도우사 <br>사랑하게 하소서 <br>주의 영광을 보네 <br>우린 하늘의 가족 <br>오 하늘 아버지 <br>이 백성의 아버지 <br>당신의 귀한 <br>아들 보내신 높은 사랑 <br>오 하늘 아버지 <br>이 백성의 아버지 <br>하늘 가족 교회 통하여 <br>이 땅의 백성 고치소서 <br>이 땅의 교회 치유와 <br>회복 하나 됨을 <br>경험하게 하소서 <br>드러내게 하소서 <br>하늘가족 교회 통하여 <br>이 땅의 모든 백성 <br>깨달을 수 있도록 <br>돌아오게 하소서 <br>오 하늘 아버지 <br>이 백성의 아버지 <br>당신의 귀한 <br>아들 보내신 높은 사랑 <br>오 하늘 아버지 <br>이 백성의 아버지 <br>하늘 가족 교회 통하여 <br>이 땅의 백성 고치소서 <br>이 땅의 백성 <br>이 땅의 백성 <br>고치소서 <br>]]></content><category term="나들목교회" label="나들목교회"/><category term="하늘가족 우리교회" label="하늘가족 우리교회"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나들목교회/나그네들의_하늘잔치/</id><title>나들목교회 - 나그네들의 하늘잔치 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:09:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:09:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%93%A4%EB%AA%A9%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C/%EB%82%98%EA%B7%B8%EB%84%A4%EB%93%A4%EC%9D%98_%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98%EC%9E%94%EC%B9%98/" title="나들목교회 - 나그네들의 하늘잔치 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그저 그렇게 <br>남들만큼만 <br>살아가기에도 <br>힘겨운 세상살이 <br>우릴 부르시어 <br>세상 속에서 <br>나그네로 주님 <br>드러내라 하시네 <br>우리 힘과 지혜로는 <br>해낼 수 없는 <br>고귀한 부르심 <br>그 분의 사랑이 있어 <br>지친 무릎 일으켜 세우네 <br>예배 눈물과 한숨이 <br>기쁨과 찬송으로 <br>변화되는 하늘 잔치 <br>예배 본향을 향하여 <br>힘찬 걸음 내딛는 <br>나그네들의 하늘 잔치 <br>하늘 아버지 함께 하심 <br>우리를 본향까지 <br>우리를 그날까지 붙드시리 <br>그저 그렇게 남들만큼만 <br>살아가기에도 <br>힘겨운 세상살이 <br>우릴 부르시어 세상 속에서 <br>나그네로 주님 <br>드러내라 하시네 <br>우리 힘과 지혜로는 <br>해낼 수 없는 <br>고귀한 부르심 <br>그 분의 사랑이 있어 <br>지친 무릎 일으켜 세우네 <br>예배 눈물과 한숨이 <br>기쁨과 찬송으로 <br>변화되는 하늘 잔치 <br>예배 본향을 향하여 <br>힘찬 걸음 내딛는 <br>나그네들의 하늘 잔치 <br>하늘 아버지 함께 하심 <br>우리를 본향까지 <br>우리를 그날까지 붙드시리 <br>예배 눈물과 한숨이 <br>기쁨과 찬송으로 <br>변화되는 하늘 잔치 <br>예배 본향을 향하여 <br>힘찬 걸음 내딛는 <br>나그네들의 하늘 잔치 <br>예배 눈물과 한숨이 <br>기쁨과 찬송으로 <br>변화되는 하늘 잔치 <br>예배 본향을 향하여 <br>힘찬 걸음 내딛는 <br>나그네들의 하늘 잔치 <br>하늘 아버지 함께 하심 <br>우리를 본향까지 <br>우리를 그날까지 붙드시리 <br>붙드시리 붙드시리 <br>붙드시리 붙드시리 <br>]]></content><category term="나들목교회" label="나들목교회"/><category term="나그네들의 하늘잔치" label="나그네들의 하늘잔치"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나들목교회/하나님의_역사_속에_선_사람들/</id><title>나들목교회 - 하나님의 역사 속에 선 사람들 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:09:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:09:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%93%A4%EB%AA%A9%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C/%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%97%AD%EC%82%AC_%EC%86%8D%EC%97%90_%EC%84%A0_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C%EB%93%A4/" title="나들목교회 - 하나님의 역사 속에 선 사람들 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하늘가족들 함께 모여 <br>주님의 사랑 속에 <br>하나가 되네 <br>주의 말씀이 선포될 때 <br>우리의 영혼 소생하네 <br>하늘가족들 함께 모여 <br>주님의 사랑 속에 <br>하나가 되네 <br>주의 말씀이 선포될 때 <br>우리의 영혼 소생하네 <br>가장 작은 영혼에게 <br>주의 사랑 전하기까지 <br>쉬지 않으시고 <br>일하시는 하나님 <br>우리를 부르시네 <br>주의 복음 전파되고 <br>주님 나라 임하시리 <br>우리의 가난함 속에 <br>우리의 미련함 통해 <br>주님의 지혜가 나타나네 <br>주의 역사 흘러가고 <br>주님께서 다스리리 <br>우리의 깨어짐 속에 <br>우리의 약함을 통해 <br>주님의 강함이 역사하네 <br>가장 작은 영혼에게 <br>주의 사랑 전하기까지 <br>쉬지 않으시고 <br>일하시는 하나님 <br>우리를 부르시네 <br>주의 복음 전파되고 <br>주님 나라 임하시리 <br>우리의 가난함 속에 <br>우리의 미련함 통해 <br>주님의 지혜가 나타나네 <br>주의 역사 흘러가고 <br>주님께서 다스리리 <br>우리의 깨어짐 속에 <br>우리의 약함을 통해 <br>주님의 강함이 역사하네 <br>우리의 깨어짐 속에 <br>우리의 약함을 통해 <br>주님의 강함이 역사하네 <br>]]></content><category term="나들목교회" label="나들목교회"/><category term="하나님의 역사 속에 선 사람들" label="하나님의 역사 속에 선 사람들"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나들목교회/우리의_기도를_통해/</id><title>나들목교회 - 우리의 기도를 통해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:09:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:09:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%93%A4%EB%AA%A9%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EC%9D%98_%EA%B8%B0%EB%8F%84%EB%A5%BC_%ED%86%B5%ED%95%B4/" title="나들목교회 - 우리의 기도를 통해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리의 기도를 통해 <br>오 주여 일하소서 <br>주의 뜻 이루소서 <br>아멘 <br>우리의 기도를 통해 <br>오 주여 일하소서 <br>주의 뜻 이루소서 <br>아멘 <br>우리의 기도를 통해 <br>오 주여 일하소서 <br>주의 뜻 이루소서 <br>아멘 <br>아멘 <br>]]></content><category term="나들목교회" label="나들목교회"/><category term="우리의 기도를 통해" label="우리의 기도를 통해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나들목교회/부르심_그_영원한_소망/</id><title>나들목교회 - 부르심 그 영원한 소망 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:09:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:09:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%93%A4%EB%AA%A9%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C/%EB%B6%80%EB%A5%B4%EC%8B%AC_%EA%B7%B8_%EC%98%81%EC%9B%90%ED%95%9C_%EC%86%8C%EB%A7%9D/" title="나들목교회 - 부르심 그 영원한 소망 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[부르심 그 영원한 소망 <br>어둠에 있던 우리를 <br>빛으로 부르셨네 <br>그리스도와 하나 된 우리는 <br>그와 함께 죽었으며 <br>그와 함께 살겠네 <br>이제 우리가 하나가 되어 <br>주님의 거룩한 교회를 이루리 <br>영원한 그 말씀 순종하여 <br>그 나라 꿈꾸며 함께 걸어가리라 <br>이제 우리가 세상 속에서 <br>하나님 나라의 증인 되어 살리 <br>영원한 생명을 받은 자여 <br>세상이 우리를 통해 주를 보리라 <br>부르심 그 영원한 소망 <br>어둠에 있던 우리를 <br>빛으로 부르셨네 <br>그리스도와 하나 된 우리는 <br>그와 함께 죽었으며 <br>그와 함께 살겠네 <br>이제 우리가 하나가 되어 <br>주님의 거룩한 교회를 이루리 <br>영원한 그 말씀 순종하여 <br>그 나라 꿈꾸며 함께 걸어가리라 <br>이제 우리가 세상 속에서 <br>하나님 나라의 증인 되어 살리 <br>영원한 생명을 받은 자여 <br>세상이 우리를 통해 주를 보리라 <br>이제 우리가 하나가 되어 <br>주님의 거룩한 교회를 이루리 <br>영원한 그 말씀 순종하여 <br>그 나라 꿈꾸며 함께 걸어가리라 <br>이제 우리가 세상 속에서 <br>하나님 나라의 증인 되어 살리 <br>영원한 생명을 받은 자여 <br>세상이 우리를 통해 주를 보리라 <br>영원한 생명을 받은 자여 <br>세상이 우리를 통해 주를 보리라 <br>]]></content><category term="나들목교회" label="나들목교회"/><category term="부르심 그 영원한 소망" label="부르심 그 영원한 소망"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나들목교회/그분의_죽음은/</id><title>나들목교회 - 그분의 죽음은 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:09:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:09:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%93%A4%EB%AA%A9%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C/%EA%B7%B8%EB%B6%84%EC%9D%98_%EC%A3%BD%EC%9D%8C%EC%9D%80/" title="나들목교회 - 그분의 죽음은 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그분의 죽음은 <br>죄에 대함이요 <br>그분의 생명은 <br>의를 위함이라 <br>우리의 죽음도 <br>죄에 대함이요 <br>우리의 생명도 <br>의를 위함이라 <br>그러므로 너희는 <br>죄에 순종치 말고 <br>의의 병기로 드리라 <br>거룩에 이르라 <br>그러므로 너희는 <br>그분께 순종하여 <br>의의 열매를 맺으라 <br>평화를 이루라 <br>그분의 죽음은 <br>죄에 대함이요 <br>그분의 생명은 <br>의를 위함이라 <br>우리의 죽음도 <br>죄에 대함이요 <br>우리의 생명도 <br>의를 위함이라 <br>그러므로 너희는 <br>죄에 순종치 말고 <br>의의 병기로 드리라 <br>거룩에 이르라 <br>그러므로 너희는 <br>그분께 순종하여 <br>의의 열매를 맺으라 <br>평화를 이루라 <br>그러므로 너희는 <br>죄에 순종치 말고 <br>의의 병기로 드리라 <br>거룩에 이르라 <br>그러므로 너희는 <br>그분께 순종하여 <br>의의 열매를 맺으라 <br>평화를 이루라 <br>의의 열매를 맺으라 <br>평화를 이루라 <br>]]></content><category term="나들목교회" label="나들목교회"/><category term="그분의 죽음은" label="그분의 죽음은"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나들목교회/하나님의_꿈_하나님_나라/</id><title>나들목교회 - 하나님의 꿈 하나님 나라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:09:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:09:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%93%A4%EB%AA%A9%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C/%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%98_%EA%BF%88_%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EB%8B%98_%EB%82%98%EB%9D%BC/" title="나들목교회 - 하나님의 꿈 하나님 나라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[태초에 말씀으로 <br>천지를 지으시고 <br>사람에게 다스리라 <br>명하신 하나님 <br>사람들 교만하여 <br>하나님의 꿈을 <br>버리고 떠나갔지만 <br>당신의 역사 속에 <br>한 민족 택하시고 <br>세상 위한 복의 근원 <br>삼으신 하나님 <br>그들도 반역하여 <br>하나님의 꿈을 <br>짓밟고 거부했지만 <br>하나님 나라 <br>역사의 강물을 따라 <br>오늘도 흐른다 <br>하늘로 흐른다 <br>어두운 세상 속에 <br>생명의 참 빛으로 <br>사랑의 주 예수님을 <br>보내신 하나님 <br>세상은 십자가에 <br>하나님의 꿈을 <br>못 박고 거절했지만 <br>부활의 주 메시아 <br>교회를 세우시고 <br>땅 끝까지 그 복음을 <br>전하게 하셨네 <br>하늘 아버지의 꿈 <br>하나님의 나라 <br>교회여 일어나 함께 가자 <br>하나님 나라 <br>역사의 강물을 따라 <br>오늘도 흐른다 <br>하늘로 흐른다 <br>기뻐하라 하나님 나라 <br>이미 오신 약속의 나라 <br>찬양하라 하나님 나라 <br>곧 오실 완전한 나라 <br>선포하라 하나님 나라 <br>이미 오신 평화의 나라 <br>찬양하라 하나님 나라 <br>곧 오실 영원한 나라 <br>선포하라 하나님 나라 <br>이미 오신 평화의 나라 <br>찬양하라 하나님 나라 <br>곧 오실 영원한 나라 <br>하나님의 꿈 <br>하나님 나라 <br>]]></content><category term="나들목교회" label="나들목교회"/><category term="하나님의 꿈 하나님 나라" label="하나님의 꿈 하나님 나라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나들목교회/세상_신을_버리고/</id><title>나들목교회 - 세상 신을 버리고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:09:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:09:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%93%A4%EB%AA%A9%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C/%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81_%EC%8B%A0%EC%9D%84_%EB%B2%84%EB%A6%AC%EA%B3%A0/" title="나들목교회 - 세상 신을 버리고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세상 신을 버리고 <br>하나님께 돌아가 <br>살아계시고 참되신 <br>하나님 섬기며 <br>그 아들 주 예수 <br>오시기 기다리니 <br>그 나라 선사하신 <br>우리 주님 찬양해 <br>믿음의 행위와 <br>사랑의 수고로 <br>우리 주 예수께 둔 <br>소망의 인내로 <br>모든 사람 모든 성도 <br>본이 되리니 <br>그 나라 완성하실 <br>우리 주님 찬양해 <br>서로 위한 쉼 없는 <br>기도와 감사로 <br>앞 선 선배들과 <br>주님을 본 받아 <br>아름다운 이야기 <br>삶으로 이어가니 <br>그 나라 왕이신 <br>우리 주님 찬양해 <br>아름다운 이야기 <br>삶으로 이어가니 <br>그 나라 선사하신 <br>그 나라 완성하실 <br>그 나라 왕이신 <br>우리 주님 찬양해 <br>]]></content><category term="나들목교회" label="나들목교회"/><category term="세상 신을 버리고" label="세상 신을 버리고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나들목교회/주님의_인자가_흐르는_강물처럼/</id><title>나들목교회 - 주님의 인자가 흐르는 강물처럼 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:09:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:09:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%93%A4%EB%AA%A9%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C/%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%9D%B8%EC%9E%90%EA%B0%80_%ED%9D%90%EB%A5%B4%EB%8A%94_%EA%B0%95%EB%AC%BC%EC%B2%98%EB%9F%BC/" title="나들목교회 - 주님의 인자가 흐르는 강물처럼 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주님의 인자가 흐르는 <br>강물처럼 우리에게 <br>낮고 낮은 세상으로 <br>은혜의 강물 흘러가리 <br>주님의 치유가 흐르는 <br>강물처럼 우리에게 <br>깨지고 상한 마음으로 <br>은혜의 강물 흘러가리 <br>주님의 생명이 흐르는 <br>강물처럼 우리에게 <br>하나님 나라 회복하는 <br>은혜의 강물 흘러가리 <br>하나님 나라 회복하는 <br>은혜의 강물 흘러가리 <br>]]></content><category term="나들목교회" label="나들목교회"/><category term="주님의 인자가 흐르는 강물처럼" label="주님의 인자가 흐르는 강물처럼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/슈가_도넛/그날_그_밤_그_겨울/</id><title>슈가 도넛 - 그날 그 밤 그 겨울 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:09:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:09:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%88%EA%B0%80_%EB%8F%84%EB%84%9B/%EA%B7%B8%EB%82%A0_%EA%B7%B8_%EB%B0%A4_%EA%B7%B8_%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8/" title="슈가 도넛 - 그날 그 밤 그 겨울 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 함께한 11월의 노래 <br>바람 차가운 그곳에선 <br>모든 거리는 불빛을 채우네 <br>모인 사람들 두 손 위로 <br>더는 기다릴 수 없어서 <br>더는 지나칠 수 없어서 <br>얼어붙은 거리 위에 <br>우린 멈춰 서있네 <br>닫혀있는 맘이 열리게 <br>내 붉어진 눈과 <br>쉽게 멈추지 않았던 <br>수많은 얘기들로 <br>이내 가득한 <br>낯선 사람들 속에서 <br>끝이 없는 밤을 새우네 <br>놀라운 그 날에 함께했던 밤엔 <br>검은 어둠이 사라졌지 <br>많은 불빛이 거리를 채우네 <br>이젠 꺼지지 않을 만큼 <br>더는 기다릴 수 없어서 <br>더는 지나칠 수 없어서 <br>얼어붙은 거리 위를 <br>우린 함께 걸었지 <br>닫혀있는 맘이 열리게 <br>내 붉어진 눈과 <br>쉽게 멈추지 않았던 <br>수많은 얘기들로 <br>이내 가득한 <br>낯선 사람들 속에서 <br>끝이 없는 밤을 새우네 <br>아름다웠던 또 차디찼던 <br>그날 그 밤 그 겨울의 노래 <br>아름다웠던 또 차디찼던 <br>그날 그 밤 그 겨울의 노래 <br>아름다웠던 또 차디찼던 <br>그날 그 밤 그 겨울의 노래 <br>]]></content><category term="슈가 도넛" label="슈가 도넛"/><category term="그날 그 밤 그 겨울" label="그날 그 밤 그 겨울"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slotface/Shave_My_Head/</id><title>Slotface - Shave My Head - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:09:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:09:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slotface/Shave_My_Head/" title="Slotface - Shave My Head - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I could shave my head for you <br>And make sure you see me do it <br>Throw dishes at your head <br>Cause it's what you were expecting of you pick my bloody head up off the floor <br>Boy they warned you this was not worth fighting for <br>Is this what you thought it would be like maybe baby you thought I'd be crazy <br>I am fine to walk alone <br>I dont need you there to walk me on my hand with hoskies in my phone <br>cause I'd rather put together my IKEA chairs <br>with glasses of red wine to your explaining their design <br>I could beg you not to leave Have you call me on the hour <br>And feign heartbreak every time you leave the room but <br>That all seems like so much work to me, and I'm sorry man I guess that I would rather just be la zy <br>Is this what you thought it would be like Maybe, baby, you thought I'd be crazy <br>I am fine to walk alone <br>I don't need you there to walk me on my handlevaits with <br>hoskies in my phone 'cause I'd rather put together my IKEA chairs with <br>glasses of red wine to your explaining their design <br>I'd never shave my head for you I'd never shave my head for you I'd never shave my head for you]]></content><category term="Slotface" label="Slotface"/><category term="Shave My Head" label="Shave My Head"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slotface/Take_Me_Dancing/</id><title>Slotface - Take Me Dancing - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:09:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:09:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slotface/Take_Me_Dancing/" title="Slotface - Take Me Dancing - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Please take me out dancing this Saturday night <br>Please get me a little drunk I won't ask why <br>Cuz you know how, how I never tried <br>Last time I felt we were too young to understand <br>What it meant when I held your hair and told you, be a man <br>but now I'm much older than I've ever been <br>Now I'm getting]]></content><category term="Slotface" label="Slotface"/><category term="Take Me Dancing" label="Take Me Dancing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cupid/Cupid_Shuffle/</id><title>Cupid - Cupid Shuffle - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:10:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:10:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cupid/Cupid_Shuffle/" title="Cupid - Cupid Shuffle - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Shuffle Cupid Shuffle <br>Cupid Shuffle, Cupid Shuffle <br>Cupid Shuffle, Cupid Shuffle <br>Cupid Shuffle, Cupid Shuffle <br><br>Cupid Shuffle, Cupid Shuffle <br>Cupid Shuffle, Cupid Shuffle <br>Cupid Shuffle, Cupid Shuffle <br>Cupid Shuffle, Cupid Shuffle <br>Come on, come on, come on, and do the <br><br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance do the Cupid dance <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance Come ondon't stop <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance We got brand new dance <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance hey hey <br><br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance we got a brand new dance <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance oh oh oh <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance yeah yeah <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance now let me see ya do that dance <br>new style yeah <br><br>They say I'm a rapper, and I say no <br>They say what you doing tryna do some zydeco hey <br>I just let the music come from my soul <br>So all of my people can stay on the floor ooh ooh <br>They got a brand new dance come on, you gotta move your muscle <br>Brand new dance, it's called the Cupid Shuffle <br>It don't matter if you're young or you're old here we go <br>We gone show you how it go hey hey <br><br>To the right, to the right, to the right, to the right <br>To the left, to the left, to the left, to the left <br>Now kick, now kick, now kick, now kick <br>Now walk it by yourself, now walk it by yourself <br>let me see you do <br><br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance a let me see ya do the cupid <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance woah woah woah woah woah woah woah yeah yeah <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance come on <br><br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance let me see, let me see ya do the cupid <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance do the shuffle baby yeah <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance woah woah oh oh <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance hey hey hey hey yeah yeah <br><br>To the right, to the right, to the right, to the right <br>To the left, to the left, to the left, to the left <br>Now kick, now kick, now kick, now kick <br>Now walk it by yourself, now walk it by yourself <br>let me see you do <br>To the right, to the right, to the right, to the right <br>To the left, to the left, to the left, to the left <br>Now kick, now kick, now kick, now kick <br>Now walk it by yourself, now walk it by yourself <br>let me see you do <br><br>Now you see what I'm talking about <br>I represent for the dirty south <br>Where we known for swinging out <br>I'm gone show you what I'm talking about <br><br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance hey hey <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance a let me see ya do the cupid, shuffle the cupid cupid shuffle <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance the cupid shuffle, the cupid cupid shuffle <br><br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance ooh ooh oh <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance yeah <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance ooh ooh oh oh oh yeah <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>here we go here we go <br><br>To the right, the right, the right, the right, the right <br>The left, the left, the left, the left, the left <br>Now kick, now kick, now come on baby kick <br>Now walk it by yourself, now walk it by yourself <br>now walk wit it <br><br>To the right, the right, the right, the right, the right <br>The left, the left, the left, the left, the left <br>Now kick, now kick, now kick, now kick <br>Now walk it by yourself, now walk it by yourself <br>her we go hey <br><br>And do the cupid shuffle oh oh oh oh oh <br>Cupid Shuffle ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh <br>It's ya boy Cupid C U P the I the D <br>Mr Fat on the track, got another hittin beat <br>here we go hey <br><br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance coem on come on <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance let me see you <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance do your dance <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance hey hey hey <br><br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance we got brand new dance <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance we got brand new sound <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance we got a brand new feel <br>Down, down, do your dance, do your dance We got a brand new style y'all <br><br>You better watch how close we coming uh uh <br>So get ready for the brand new style <br>You better watch how close we coming <br>You got another one Mr Fat uh uh yep]]></content><category term="Cupid" label="Cupid"/><category term="Cupid Shuffle" label="Cupid Shuffle"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VIC/Wobble/</id><title>V.I.C. - Wobble - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:10:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:10:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VIC/Wobble/" title="V.I.C. - Wobble - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, oh, oh, oh <br>All the shawtys in the club <br>Let me see you just <br>Back it up, drop it down <br>Let me see you just <br>Get low n scrub the grown <br>Let me see you just <br>Push it up, push it up <br>Let me see you just <br><br>Wobble baby, wobble baby, wobble baby, wobble yeah x4 <br>Get in there, yeah, yeah x4 <br>Ey big girl make em' back it up, make em' back it up x4 <br><br>I got em' shakin their boobies like congos <br>Man I'm shaking the city like quakes <br>The haters blue the face like gonzo <br>Cause I'm rakin a cake so let's bake <br>I'm taking the game, the games mine <br>Ya'll witness a change it's my time <br>Yea I'm new to the game but ya'll might wanna save ya whack raps daylight saving time <br>I could dance homie, I don't 2 step <br>Ya'll looking at something like a true player <br>A girl told me that a man that could dance might could possibly get down with the tool in his pants <br>Now all my ladies let me see you vibrate <br>And when it's over you ain't gon need ya vibrator <br>Cause I'm a pro, make ya bend ya back low den just pound it real fast just like purkulator <br><br>Wobble baby, wobble baby, wobble baby, wobble yeah x4 <br>Get in there, yeah, yeah x4 <br>Ey big girl make em' back it up, make em' back it up x4 <br><br>Girl wobble it, and I'm a gobble it <br>I see you movin your head, your head bobblin' <br>We can cradle the bed I'm straight rockin it <br>The girls say my head like the head of a rocket ship <br>God damn I'm so explicit, but I can't help it my flow ridiculous <br>Boy got a gift like it gotta be christmas <br>Swag don't miss like he gotta be gifted <br>The girls brought cameras and they want pictures <br>And they gon frame em to see dat nigga <br>Little to the bed while I'm sayin my scriptures <br>Cause I leave ya holy like ya pray in the temple <br>Want beat I move with the led of a pencil <br>And mine won't miss you, goodnight kiss you <br>Take a band back, cause you got pistols <br>And I don't think bounty picker up these issues <br><br>Wobble baby, wobble baby, wobble baby, wobble yeah x4 <br>Get in there, yeah, yeah x4 <br>Ey big girl make em' back it up, make em' back it up x4 <br><br>Mr Collipark <br>Oh, oh, oh, oh <br>All the shawtys in the club <br>Let me see you just <br>Back it up, drop it down <br>Let me see you just <br>Get low n scrub the grown <br>Let me see you just <br>Push it up, push it up <br>Let me see you just <br>Wobble wobble, shake shake it shake it <br>just give it here <br>Wobble wobble, just push it push it <br>just give it here <br>Show me whatcha got show me whatcha got <br>just give it here <br>Show me whatcha got show me whatcha got <br><br>Ey big girl make em' back it up, make em' back it up x4 <br><br>Wait a minute now x4 <br>Wobble baby, wobble baby, wobble baby, wobble yeah x4 <br>Get in there, yeah, yeah x4 <br>Ey big girl make em' back it up, make em' back it up x4]]></content><category term="V.I.C." label="V.I.C."/><category term="Wobble" label="Wobble"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Flo_Rida/My_House/</id><title>Flo Rida - My House - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:10:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:10:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Flo_Rida/My_House/" title="Flo Rida - My House - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Open up the champagne, pop <br>It's my house, come on, turn it up <br><br>Hear a knock on the door and the night begins <br>Cause we done this before so you come on in <br>Make yourself at my home, tell me where you been <br>Pour yourself something cold, baby, cheers to this <br><br>Sometimes you gotta stay in <br>And you know where I live <br>Yeah, you know what we is <br>Sometimes you gotta stay in, in <br><br>Welcome to my house <br>Baby, take control now <br>We can't even slow down <br>We don't have to go out <br>Welcome to my house <br>Play that music too loud <br>Show me what you do now <br>We don't have to go out <br>Welcome to my house <br>Welcome to my house <br><br>Morning comes and you know that you wanna stay <br>Close the blinds, let's pretend that the time has changed <br>Keep our clothes on the floor, open up champagne <br>Let's continue tonight, come on, celebrate <br><br>Sometimes you gotta stay in <br>And you know where I live <br>Yeah, you know what we is <br>Sometimes you gotta stay in, in <br><br>Welcome to my house <br>Baby, take control now <br>We can't even slow down <br>We don't have to go out <br>Welcome to my house <br>Play that music too loud <br>Show me what you do now <br>We don't have to go out <br>Welcome to my house <br>Welcome to my house <br><br>Welcome to my duck off the crib, the spot, the pad <br>But my house is your house if you throwin' it back <br>Excuse me if my home bringing the sad <br>Soon as these happy faces land you can run with the cash <br>Home run, slam dunk, touchdown, pass <br>Mi casa es tu casa so it ain't no holding back <br>Another shot of vodka, you know what's in my glass <br>It's my house, just relax <br><br>Welcome to my house <br>Baby, take control now <br>We can't even slow down <br>We don't have to go out <br>Welcome to my house <br>Play that music too loud <br>Show me what you do now <br>We don't have to go out <br>Welcome to my house <br>Welcome to my house <br><br>Welcome to my house <br>It's my house]]></content><category term="Flo Rida" label="Flo Rida"/><category term="My House" label="My House"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OT_Genasis/Cut_It/</id><title>O.T. Genasis - Cut It - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:10:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:10:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OT_Genasis/Cut_It/" title="O.T. Genasis - Cut It - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cut it, cut it, cut it, cut it <br>Cut it, cut it, cut it, cut it <br>Them bricks is way too hot, you need to cut it <br>Your price is way too high, you need to cut it <br>Cut it, cut it, cut it, cut it <br>Cut it, cut it, cut it, cut it <br>Them bricks is way too hot, you need to cut it <br>Your price is way too high, you need to cut it <br><br>Run up them bands on the regular <br>Hittin' my plug on the celly, yeah <br>Tell my ex bitch that I'm sorry <br>I'm a skate off in the 'Rari <br>Keep 36 by my side <br>I'm a go bake me a pie <br>Keep 45 on my side <br>Fuck with my niggas, you die <br>All of my niggas say blood <br>All of my niggas say cuh <br>OT, I found me a plug <br>I got it straight out the mud <br>Keep it a hundred, no budge <br>I fell in love with the drugs <br>Bustin' it down in the tub <br>Pay me my money in dubs <br>Water whippin', lookin' like I'm fishin' <br>Baseball in kitchen, with my arm I'm pitchin' <br>Rolie on, it's glistenin', now my doner kissin' <br>Niggas steady trippin' so I'm steady grippin' <br>Dirty money on me, got a scale up on me <br>I don't fuck with phony, 'bout to sell a pony <br>All these niggas on me, all these bitches on me <br>Say my price is good, motherfucker, show me <br><br>Cut it, cut it, cut it, cut it <br>Cut it, cut it, cut it, cut it <br>Them bricks is way too hot, you need to cut it <br>Your price is way too high, you need to cut it <br>Cut it, cut it, cut it, cut it <br>Cut it, cut it, cut it, cut it <br>Them bricks is way too hot, you need to cut it <br>Your price is way too high, you need to cut it <br><br>Went and bought a 911 with my trap money <br>A million up but still ain't never touch my rap money <br>I'm out in LA fuckin' with that boy OT <br>Flew to LA, got a plug on that OG <br>You know I've been gettin' money if you know me <br>When I first met my plug, I tote my pistol, hundred Gs <br>I ain't comin' to get it unless you got a hundred piece <br>I don't want it, fuck it, your price, you need to cut it <br>Your ice, you need to tuck it, she fuck with me, she lucky <br>A half a million, all 20s in that Gucci luggage <br>Let's skip the small talk, it's time to talk numbers <br>Young nigga playin' with commas, might go get a Lamb for the summer <br>I've been outchea in these streets all my life hustlin' <br>My nigga beefin' then I'm beefin', wrong or right I'm bustin' <br>My traphouse, I love it <br>Put some Forces on my old school and I had to cut it <br>But should I put a roof in <br><br>Cut it, cut it, cut it, cut it <br>Cut it, cut it, cut it, cut it <br>Them bricks is way too hot, you need to cut it <br>Your price is way too high, you need to cut it <br>Cut it, cut it, cut it, cut it <br>Cut it, cut it, cut it, cut it <br>Them bricks is way too hot, you need to cut it <br>Your price is way too high, you need to cut it]]></content><category term="O.T. Genasis" label="O.T. Genasis"/><category term="Cut It" label="Cut It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/iLoveMemphis/Lean__Dab/</id><title>iLoveMemphis - Lean &amp; Dab - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:10:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:10:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/iLoveMemphis/Lean__Dab/" title="iLoveMemphis - Lean &amp; Dab - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I said I'll show you how I <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br><br>I said I'll show you how I <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br><br>Wake up in the morning then I dab <br>Had to pull up on the block cause today I get to whip <br>And you know my top drop and my car's name is nae nae <br>Had to hit the Quan cause today is a good day <br><br>Slide to the left, slide to the right <br>Walk it to the front, bop it to the back <br>Slide to the left, slide to the right <br>Walk it to the front, bop it to the back <br><br>I said I'll show you how I <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br><br>I said I'll show you how I <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br><br>Slide to the left, slide to the left <br>Slide to the left, hold on hit the folks <br>Slide to the right, slide to the right <br>Slide to the right, make it drop <br>Walk it to the front, walk it to the front <br>Walk it to the front, watch me whip <br>Bop it to the back, bop it to the back <br>Bop it to the back, nae nae, nae nae <br><br>Nah, let me keep going <br>Show you how I lean, then dab <br>Nice shoes, car clean cause it's sunny outside <br>That mean I pull up with my top down <br>I don't have a top now <br>Mama told me never leave the house without my nightgown <br>Mama I'm on BET so I can act hyped now <br>On 'em like the WWE and lay the smackdown <br>That's a lot to handle, how could he manage <br>Mr Hit the Quan went viral, gigantic <br>Hold up wait face it, go ahead pump your brakes fast <br>Always used to dodge cops, riding around with no plate tags <br>But they can never catch me, driving like a taxi <br>Waiting on my taxes, lights camera action <br>Finna play Michael Jackson, Oprah's in a jacket <br>Take it but I'll match it, y'all not in my bracket <br>It's iHeart Memphis but I also love dabbing <br>I done took off on em, I feel like a pilot <br>I done took off on em, I don't care bout the mileage <br>I'm so VIP all I know is private <br>I'll take the steak, the strip, and the salad <br>Cause growing up in Memphis, Tennessee I couldn't have it <br>Now come correct <br><br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br><br>I said I'll show you how I <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br>Lean and dab, lean and dab <br><br>Hit the Quan on em, hit the Quan on em <br>Hit the Quan on em, hit the Quan on em <br>Snap em up, pose, snap em up, pose <br>Snap em up, pose, snap em up, pose <br>Chop a chop chopped salad, chop a chop chop <br>Chop a chop chopped salad, chop a chop chop <br>You can google me, you can google me <br>You can google me, you can google me]]></content><category term="iLoveMemphis" label="iLoveMemphis"/><category term="Lean &amp; Dab" label="Lean &amp; Dab"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dawin/Dessert/</id><title>Dawin - Dessert - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:10:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:10:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dawin/Dessert/" title="Dawin - Dessert - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They can imitate you <br>But they can't duplicate you <br>Cause you got something special <br>That makes me wanna taste you <br>I want it all day long <br>I'm addicted like it's wrong <br>I want it all day long <br>I'm addicted like it's wrong <br><br>They can imitate you <br>But they can't duplicate you <br>Cause you got something special <br>That makes me wanna taste you <br>I want it all day long <br>I'm addicted like it's wrong <br>I want it all day long <br>I'm addicted like it's <br><br>Whatcha gon <br>Whatcha gon do with that dessert <br><br>Murder that, murder that <br>Dancefloor, dancefloor <br><br>Murder that <br>Murder that <br>Murder that <br><br>Are you saving that dessert for me <br>Cause if you are baby <br>You know you could work for me <br>The way you do it causing jealousy <br>But you don't ever gotta worry about the enemy <br>They try to do it like you <br>And they get mad cause they don't do it successfully <br>They try to copy your moves <br>But they don't never ever do it that tastefully <br><br>They can imitate you <br>But they can't duplicate you <br>Cause you got something special <br>That makes me wanna taste you <br>I want it all day long <br>I'm addicted like it's wrong <br>I want it all day long <br>I'm addicted like it's wrong <br><br>They can imitate you <br>But they can't duplicate you <br>Cause you got something special <br>That makes me wanna taste you <br>I want it all day long <br>I'm addicted like it's wrong <br>I want it all day long <br>I'm addicted like it's <br><br>Whatcha gon <br>Whatcha gon do with that dessert <br><br>Murder that, murder that <br>Dancefloor, dancefloor <br><br>Whatcha gon <br>Whatcha gon do with that dessert <br><br>Murder that <br>Murder that <br>Murder that <br><br>Are you saving that dessert for me <br>Cause if you are baby <br>You know you could work for me <br>The way you do it causing jealousy <br>But you don't ever gotta worry about the enemy <br>They try to do it like you <br>And they get mad cause they don't do it successfully <br>They try to copy your moves <br>But they don't never ever do it that tastefully <br><br>They can imitate you <br>But they can't duplicate you <br>Cause you got something special <br>That makes me wanna taste you <br>I want it all day long <br>All day long <br>All day long <br>I want it all day long <br>All day long <br>Whatcha gon <br>Whatcha gon do with that dessert]]></content><category term="Dawin" label="Dawin"/><category term="Dessert" label="Dessert"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SILENTO/Watch_Me/</id><title>SILENTO - Watch Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:10:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:10:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SILENTO/Watch_Me/" title="SILENTO - Watch Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You already know who it is <br>Silento <br>Silento <br>Silento <br>Gonna do it for me <br><br>Now watch me whip Kill it <br>Now watch me nae nae Okay <br>Now watch me whip whip <br>Watch me nae nae Want me do it <br><br>Now watch me whip Kill it <br>Watch me nae nae Okay <br>Now watch me whip whip <br>Watch me nae nae Can you do it <br><br>Now watch me <br><br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh ooh ooh ooh <br><br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh ooh ooh ooh <br><br>x2 <br>Do the stanky leg stank <br>Do the stanky leg stank stank <br>Do the stanky leg stank <br>Do the stanky leg stank stank <br><br>Now break your legs break 'em, break 'em <br>Break your legs break 'em dog <br>Tell 'em break your legs break 'em, break 'em <br>Break your legs break 'em dog <br>Tell 'em break your legs break 'em, break 'em <br>Break your legs break 'em dog <br>Tell 'em break your legs break 'em, break 'em <br>Break your legs break 'em dog <br><br>Now watch me <br>Bop bop bop bop bop bop bop bop bop <br>Now watch me <br>Bop bop bop bop bop bop bop bop bop <br><br>Now watch me whip Kill it <br>Now watch me nae nae Okay <br>Now watch me whip whip <br>Watch me nae nae Want me do it <br><br>Now watch me whip Kill it <br>Watch me nae nae Okay <br>Now watch me whip whip <br>Watch me nae nae Can you do it <br><br>Now watch me <br><br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh ooh ooh ooh <br><br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh ooh ooh ooh <br><br>Now watch me yule Soulja <br>Now watch me superman okay <br>Now watch me yule Soulja <br>Now watch me superman okay <br><br>Now watch me yule Soulja <br>Now watch me superman okay <br>Now watch me yule Soulja <br>Now watch me superman okay <br><br>Now watch me duff, duff, duff, duff, duff, duff, duff, duff Hold on <br>Now watch me duff, duff, duff, duff, duff, duff, duff, duff, duff <br><br>Now watch me <br>Bop bop bop bop bop bop bop bop bop <br>Now watch me <br>Bop bop bop bop bop bop bop bop bop <br><br>Now watch me whip Kill it <br>Now watch me nae nae Okay <br>Now watch me whip whip <br>Watch me nae nae Want me do it <br><br>Now watch me whip Kill it <br>Watch me nae nae Okay <br>Now watch me whip whip <br>Watch me nae nae Can you do it <br><br>Now watch me <br><br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh ooh ooh ooh <br><br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh watch me, watch me <br>Ooh ooh ooh ooh <br>Crank dat]]></content><category term="SILENTO" label="SILENTO"/><category term="Watch Me" label="Watch Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/M_City_JR/Addicted_To_My_Ex/</id><title>M City JR - Addicted To My Ex - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:10:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:10:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/M_City_JR/Addicted_To_My_Ex/" title="M City JR - Addicted To My Ex - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm addicted to flexin' on my old hoes old hoes <br>Hand me downs, they ain't worth more than my old clothes <br>I might fuck her but I keep that on the low low low <br>Oh I keep that on the low low <br>On the low low <br>I think I'm addicted to flexin' on my old hoes <br>I think I'm addicted to flexin' on my old hoes <br>I think I'm addicted to flexin' on my old hoes <br>I think I'm addicted to flexin' on my old hoes <br>Hoes <br>Flexin' on my old <br>Hoes <br>I'm addicted to em' <br><br>I I flex on my ex every time that she text me <br>I'm lookin' like hold up yaaaaaa <br>I know im the shit but she say I ain't shit and my dick is bitch shut up yaaaaaa <br>I'm taking my new bitch places I took her she cannot afford <br>Then I post it on Instagram stuntin' she tryna ignore it <br>You mad or nah yaaaaaa <br>I bought a new whip just in spite of that bitch she be catching the bus <br>Seen her, pretend that I'm pickin' her up <br>When I pulled up I gave her the finger and skuuurt yaaaaaa <br>I bought her a gift didn't return it <br>I took it right back from her <br>I ain't gon neva gon get back with her unless she suck me like dracula <br>Listen I'm telling you <br>I, I see her in public and stunt on a bitch <br>Do you see this coat <br>Why, why keep her around if she just gone drown and jump off the boat <br>I lie, I sent her a text and told her I loved her and sent a reply <br>Sike, she blow up my phone and won't leave me alone so <br>bitch bye yaaaaaa <br><br>I'm addicted to flexin' on my old hoes old hoes <br>Hand me downs, they ain't worth more than my old clothes <br>I might fuck her but I keep that on the low low low <br>Oh I keep that on the low low <br>On the low low <br>I think I'm addicted to flexin' on my old hoes <br>I think I'm addicted to flexin' on my old hoes <br>I think I'm addicted to flexin' on my old hoes <br>I think I'm addicted to flexin' on my old hoes <br>Hoes <br>Flexin' on my old <br>Hoes <br>I'm addicted to em' <br><br>I, I show up to all of her family events cause her momma still love me I love you momma <br>And she got a new nigga so when I pull up he be looking so jelly <br>I hate that nigga <br>If I'm really on tip I might even show up with one of her buddies I fucked her too <br>As soon as she come up to hug me I look and I say bitch what yaaaaa <br>She tell all her friends that I ain't the man bitch, fuck you mean yaaaaa <br>I know that she want me she peep that my roley so fuckin' fleek <br>And speaking of roleys I left her alone cause she wasted my time <br>She tryna come over and fuck but I cannot see her I'm legally blind barely <br>I'm swaggin' listen Linda I'm swaggin' <br>If you had me then you a has been look at me now a young nigga flashin' <br>My new bitches name is Yasmine <br>I never do cuff em' I pass em' like a college exam <br>Bitch I am the man <br>I don't give a damn so bitch bye yaaaaaaa <br><br>I'm addicted to flexin' on my old hoes old hoes <br>Hand me downs, they ain't worth more than my old clothes <br>I might fuck her but I keep that on the low low <br>Oh I keep that on the low low <br>On the low low <br>I think I'm addicted to flexin' on my old hoes <br>I think I'm addicted to flexin' on my old hoes <br>I think I'm addicted to flexin' on my old hoes <br>I think I'm addicted to flexin' on my old hoes <br>Hoes <br>Flexin' on my old <br>Hoes <br>I'm addicted to em' I'm addicted to em']]></content><category term="M City JR" label="M City JR"/><category term="Addicted To My Ex" label="Addicted To My Ex"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/99_Percent/Cake/</id><title>99 Percent - Cake - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:10:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:10:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/99_Percent/Cake/" title="99 Percent - Cake - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1: Flo Rida] <br>You know when I come by, you know what it look like <br>Everything lit, all the girls in free <br>Anybody inside sipping on a good time <br>You ain't gotta rest, they can put it on me <br><br>[Pre-Hook: Flo Rida] <br>When they wanna go off <br>They know when my money show off <br>I don't ever get it one way, yeah <br>Spend it and I get it same day, but hey <br><br>[Hook: Flo Rida] <br>I didn't come here to party <br>I didn't come here to stay <br>I came to leave with somebody <br>I only came for the cake <br>I only came for the cake <br>I only came for the cake <br><br>[Verse 2: 99 Percent] <br>You know what I came for, I'mma throw a bankroll <br>You ain't gotta flex, got your mind on me <br>Go until it's all gone, I don't gotta say no <br>I can blow a check, tell me what it's gon' be <br><br>[Pre-Hook: 99 Percent] <br>When they wanna go off <br>They know when my money show off <br>I don't ever get it one way, yeah <br>Spend it and I get it same day, but hey <br><br>[Hook: 99 Percent] <br>I didn't come here to party <br>I didn't come here to stay]]></content><category term="99 Percent" label="99 Percent"/><category term="Cake" label="Cake"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/iAmDLOW/Do_It_Like_Me/</id><title>iAmDLOW - Do It Like Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:10:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:10:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/iAmDLOW/Do_It_Like_Me/" title="iAmDLOW - Do It Like Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This your boy Dlow, Bop King <br>And I'm about to get with something new for ya'll <br>You know everybody dance and do their thing, but this that bet you can't do it like me challenge <br><br>Ooh, oh <br>Ah, ah <br>Hey, hey, turn up <br>Oh, oh <br>Ah, ah <br>Hey, hey, turn up <br>Oh, oh <br>Ah, ah <br>Hey, hey, turn up <br>Oh, oh <br>Ah, ah <br>Hey, hey, turn up <br><br>Bet you can't Whip like me <br>Can't Milly Rock like me <br>Can't sexy walk like me <br>Can't Hit The Quan like me <br>Bet you can't drop like me <br>Can't Hit The Folks like me <br>Can't Nae Nae like me <br>Can't Dlow Shuffle like me <br><br>Like Nope bet you can't do it like me <br>Bet you can't do it like me <br>Nope bet you can't do it like me <br>Bet you can't do it like me <br>Nope bet you can't do it like me <br>Bet you can't do it like me <br><br>Put your right leg up, left leg up <br>Sit down like your sitting on the steps <br>Look to the left, look to the right <br>Look back at the booty and stare <br>Now twerk, twerk <br>Now twerk, twerk <br>Now twerk, twerk <br>Now twerk, twerk <br><br>I can't take myself when I step up on the scene <br>And all these haters joking cos' they know my swag be mean <br>I can do it by myself or I can do it with my team <br>But when I'm with my brothers we just hit that dream team <br>Now dream team, dream team, dream team <br>I'm like what these haters mean <br>Dream team, dream team, dream team <br>I'm like what these haters mean <br><br>Double tap to the right, double tap to the left <br>Swing your arms three times <br>Do your dance, Do your dance <br>Switch to the other side <br>Bunny hop to the right, Bunny hop to the left <br>Pull to the right two times <br>Look to the left <br>Feel on your chest <br>Now gone break it down, aye <br>Gone break it down, aye <br>Gone break it down, aye <br>Gone break it down <br>I say gone break it down, aye <br>Gone break it down, aye <br>Gone break it down, aye <br>Gone break it down <br>I say gone break it down <br><br>I've been flexing since a youngin' <br>I keep money in my pocket <br>I've been all around the world <br>See them haters they need to stop it <br>Milly rock my bands <br>I just put in the coffin <br>But I don't like to swerve <br>You can watch me Hit The Dolphin <br><br>Oh, oh <br>Ah, ah <br>Hey, hey, turn up <br><br>Oh, oh <br>Ah, ah <br>Hey, hey, turn up <br><br>Oh, oh <br>Ah, ah <br>Hey, hey, turn up <br><br>Oh, oh <br>Ah, ah <br>Hey, hey, turn up]]></content><category term="iAmDLOW" label="iAmDLOW"/><category term="Do It Like Me" label="Do It Like Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DJ_Chose/UNameItChallenge_Beans_Greens_Potatoes_TomatoesYou_Name_It/</id><title>DJ Chose - #UNameItChallenge (Beans, Greens, Potatoes, Tomatoes...You Name It!) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:10:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:10:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DJ_Chose/UNameItChallenge_Beans_Greens_Potatoes_TomatoesYou_Name_It/" title="DJ Chose - #UNameItChallenge (Beans, Greens, Potatoes, Tomatoes...You Name It!) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look <br><br>I got beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Lamb, rams, hog maw <br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Chicken, turkeys, rabbit You name it <br><br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Lamb, rams, hogs, dogs <br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Chicken, turkeys, chicken, turkeys <br><br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Lamb, rams, hog maw <br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Chicken, turkeys, rabbit <br>You name it <br><br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Beans, greens <br>Beans, greens <br>Beans, beans, beans, beans <br><br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Chicken, turkeys, chicken, turkeys <br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Chicken, turkeys, chicken, turkeys <br><br>You name it <br>You name it <br>You name it <br>You name it <br><br>I got beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Lamb, rams, hog maw <br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Chicken, turkeys, rabbit You name it <br><br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Lamb, rams, hog maw <br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Chicken, turkeys, chicken, turkeys <br><br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Lamb, rams, hog maw <br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Chicken, turkeys, rabbit <br>You name it <br><br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Beans, greens <br>Beans, greens <br>Beans, beans, beans, beans <br><br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Chicken, turkeys, chicken, turkeys <br>Beans, greens, potatoes, tomatoes <br>Chicken, turkeys, chicken, turkeys <br><br>You name it <br>You name it <br>You name it <br>You name it]]></content><category term="DJ Chose" label="DJ Chose"/><category term="#UNameItChallenge (Beans, Greens, Potatoes, Tomatoes...You Name It!)" label="#UNameItChallenge (Beans, Greens, Potatoes, Tomatoes...You Name It!)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zay_Hilfigerrr/Juju_On_That_Beat/</id><title>Zay Hilfigerrr - Juju On That Beat - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:10:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:10:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zay_Hilfigerrr/Juju_On_That_Beat/" title="Zay Hilfigerrr - Juju On That Beat - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do that one dance baby <br>That, that one dance <br>Yeah, oh <br>You don't know how to do that <br>Baby do it for your grandma <br>Come on, I'm old and I'm trying to learn it <br>Well yeah, do it <br><br>Oh my God, oh my God Girl ain't that Zay and Zayion <br>Yas <br>Don't both of 'em got a girlfriend <br>Girl I don't care <br>I don't care girl, he still cute <br>Oh yes <br><br>Walked in this party <br>And these girls lookin' at me <br>Skinny jeans on and you know my hair nappy <br>Hey, hey, hey <br>Okay, okay <br>I want y'all do it, do this dance now <br><br>JuJu on that beat <br>JuJu on that beat <br>JuJu on that, JuJu on that, JuJu on that beat <br>Now slide, drop <br>Hit dem folks, don't stop, aye <br>Don't stop, aye <br>Don't stop, aye <br>Running man on that beat, aye <br>Running man on that beat, aye <br>Running man on that beat, aye <br>Running man on that beat <br>Now do your dance, do your dance, do your dance, aye <br>You ugly <br>You your daddy's son <br><br>Aye, aye <br>Do your dance, aye <br>Go crazy, aye <br>Get freaky, aye <br>Let's go, leggo, leggo, leggo, leggo <br>Hey, hey, hey <br>Yea <br><br>Okay we knuckin' and buckin' <br>And ready to fight <br>I got my cousin, he with me <br>And got Lil Zay on the right <br>And I'm a Detroit baby <br>And I don't know nothing else <br>Besides drinking and having parties <br>And having some fun <br>I say look in the mirror <br>What you expect me to do <br>I see a 300 S <br>And got them blacked out rims <br>I mean I like your style <br>I'm on a whole 'nother level <br>If you compare me and you <br>There wouldn't be no comparings <br><br>JuJu on that beat <br>JuJu on that beat <br>JuJu on that, JuJu on that, JuJu on that beat <br>Now slide, drop <br>Hit dem folks, don't stop, aye <br>Don't stop, aye <br>Don't stop, aye <br>Running man on that beat, aye <br>Running man on that beat, aye <br>Running man on that beat, aye <br>Running man on that beat <br>Now do your dance, do your dance, do your dance, aye <br>You ugly <br>You your daddy's son <br><br>JuJu on that beat <br>JuJu on that beat <br>JuJu on that, JuJu on that, JuJu on that beat <br>Now slide, drop <br>Hit dem folks, don't stop, aye <br>Don't stop, aye <br>Don't stop, aye <br>Running man on that beat, aye <br>Running man on that beat, aye <br>Running man on that beat, aye <br>Running man on that beat <br>Now do your dance, do your dance, do your dance, aye <br>You ugly <br>You your daddy's son]]></content><category term="Zay Hilfigerrr" label="Zay Hilfigerrr"/><category term="Juju On That Beat" label="Juju On That Beat"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MF_Doom/Avalanche/</id><title>MF Doom - Avalanche - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MF_Doom/Avalanche/" title="MF Doom - Avalanche - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'd like to start off by thanking our sponsor <br>For financing the parts for this Frankenstein monster <br>Along with my partner who's a bro of few words <br>We did this research for true nerds and two birds <br>Piano do a show, same time watch it <br>And guaranteed to give 'em more than just hock spit <br>MC extraordinaire, technique sort of rare <br>Caught a glare, sure to scare, next week more to share <br>From the most retarded est artists this year and forever <br>Villain 'nem, ya mean big brothers love ya <br>Definitely felonies, telling me <br>Treacherously MC, yelling B, set 'em free <br>Let me see, that strategy's misleading <br>G's all in the freezer with the batteries and Z Rims <br>He, him stalked the concrete with bunion <br>And won't hurt corns when it's on like the stun gun <br>Not so shocking <br>Funyun faced rappers eat rocks, over beatboxing <br>Debunk punks with a stock flow <br>And make them funky fresh with no socks for hocko <br>Madvillain been as high as Kathmandu <br>And tilted to the side like that fat man's shoe <br>Look, not to give a mixed signal <br>The rap game got more toys than Kris Kringle <br>And he's fake, yer ears is not deceiving <br>I can't believe my eyeballs no more than Steveland <br>No wonder, OMFG <br>Snuck him like an unexpected blow from a lefty <br>Caught me, almost shot an eye out <br>Felt good though, even with the cotton dry mouth <br>Time out <br>Okay, time back in <br>Never seen a living human being with black skin <br>What's crackin' Besides smoking trees and wheezing <br>For no reason working like a broken tetrahedron <br>He get paid and get even <br>Building <br>Still get mad when it's time to get v vanilla <br>They thought the Don had gone silent <br>And since deep in the studies he's accepted non violence <br>Don't make him have to skip some classes <br>And open up an old can of whoop ass with the fastness <br>Cut the raw melatonin put a little more in <br>Strip club full of whores and grown men snoring <br>Keep the block sown like Thread and Bobbin Bonus <br>And make sure the seeds know they'd never ever own this <br>Beat a dead pony and sell the corpse for glue <br>Get a portion off the proceeds for the shoe <br>No need to bleed if there's no pig to do <br>Flew a fly flow with the speed of Mr Magoo <br>Blew a wad on a platinum card debit <br>Come back broke as hell ask the god for credit <br>Dead it <br>The mask is like a hand crafted ghillie suit <br>Only if the ladies could see him they'd say he's really cute <br>Hmm <br>Thanks in advance <br>Don't try to be cool now had ya chance <br>Avalanche <br>Rappers is Bagger Vance acting <br>Who need to fix they pants or get smacked by the Mac 10 <br>Or 11, or both <br>Find Jesus, see the reverend take the oath <br>He moves his huge hands in the dark like fate <br>Waitin' for the date to drop the tape like bait]]></content><category term="MF Doom" label="MF Doom"/><category term="Avalanche" label="Avalanche"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/포근한_의자/Joy_To_The_World/</id><title>포근한 의자 - Joy To The World - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8F%AC%EA%B7%BC%ED%95%9C_%EC%9D%98%EC%9E%90/Joy_To_The_World/" title="포근한 의자 - Joy To The World - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Joy to the world <br>The Lord has come <br>Let earth receive her King <br>Let every heart prepare him room <br>And heaven and nature sing <br>And heaven and nature sing <br>And heaven and heaven and <br>nature sing <br>Joy to the earth <br>The Savior reigns <br>Let men their songs employ <br>While fields and floods <br>Rocks hills and plains <br>Repeat the sounding joy <br>Repeat the sounding joy <br>Repeat repeat the sounding joy <br>Joy to the world <br>The Lord has come <br>Let earth receive her King <br>Let every heart prepare him room <br>And heaven and nature sing <br>And heaven and nature sing <br>And heaven and heaven and <br>nature sing <br>Joy to the world <br>Joy to the world <br>Joy to the world <br>Joy to the world <br>Joy to the world <br>Joy to the world <br>Joy to the world <br>Joy to the world <br>Joy to the world <br>Joy Joy Joy to the world <br>Joy to the world <br>Joy to the world <br>Joy to the world <br>Joy to the world <br>Joy to the world <br>Joy to the world <br>Joy to the world <br>]]></content><category term="포근한 의자" label="포근한 의자"/><category term="Joy To The World" label="Joy To The World"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandon_Uranowitz/Falsettoland/</id><title>Brandon Uranowitz - Falsettoland - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandon_Uranowitz/Falsettoland/" title="Brandon Uranowitz - Falsettoland - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[MENDEL] <br>Homosexuals <br>Women with children <br>Short insomniacs <br>We're a teeny tiny band <br>Lovers come and lovers go <br>Lovers live and die fortissimo <br>This is where we take a stand <br>Welcome to Falsettoland]]></content><category term="Brandon Uranowitz" label="Brandon Uranowitz"/><category term="Falsettoland" label="Falsettoland"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/What_Would_I_Do_/</id><title>Christian Borle - What Would I Do? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/What_Would_I_Do_/" title="Christian Borle - What Would I Do? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[MARVIN] <br>What would I do <br>If I had not met you? <br>Who would I blame my life on? <br>Once I was told <br>That all men get what they deserve <br>Who the hell then threw this curve? <br>There are no answers <br>But who would I be <br>If you had not been my friend? <br><br>You're the only one <br>One out of a thousand others <br>Only one my child would allow <br>When I'm having fun <br>You're the one I wanna talk to <br>Where have you been? <br>Where are you now? <br><br>Who would I be <br>If I had not loved you? <br>How would I know what love is? <br>God only knows, too soon <br>I'll remember your faults <br>Meanwhile, though, it's tears and schmaltz <br><br>There are no answers <br>But what would I do <br>If you had not been my friend? <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>All your life you've wanted men <br>And when you got it up to have them <br>Who knew it could end your life? <br><br>[MARVIN]: <br>I left my kid and left my wife <br>To be with you <br>To be insulted by such handsome men <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Do you regret--? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I'd do it again <br>I'd like to believe that I'd do it again <br>And again and again... <br>And <br>What more can I say? <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>What more can I say? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>How am I to face tomorrow? <br><br>[BOTH] <br>After being screwed out of today <br>Tell me what's in store <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Yes, I'd beg or steal or borrow <br>If I could hold you for <br>One hour more <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>One hour more <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>One hour more <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>One hour more <br><br>[BOTH] <br>One hour, one hour more <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>What would I do <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>What would I do <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>If I had not seen you? <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>If I had not seen you? <br><br>[BOTH] <br>Who would I feast my eyes on? <br>Once I was told <br>That good men get better with age <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>We're just gonna skip that stage <br><br>There are no answers <br>But what would I do <br>If you hadn't been my friend? <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>There are no answers <br>But what would I do... <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>No simple answers <br>But what would I do <br>If you had not been <br>My friend <br>My friend <br>My friend]]></content><category term="Christian Borle" label="Christian Borle"/><category term="What Would I Do?" label="What Would I Do?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Falsettos_2016_Broadway_Company/Jasons_Bar_Mitzvah/</id><title>`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company - Jason`s Bar Mitzvah - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Falsettos_2016_Broadway_Company/Jasons_Bar_Mitzvah/" title="`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company - Jason`s Bar Mitzvah - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[JASON] <br>Whizzer, hey! <br>Suddenly it all came clear <br>I said, let's have my bar mitzvah here! <br><br>[MARVIN, TRINA, MENDEL, JASON, CHARLOTTE, CORDELIA] <br>Surprise! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>This was Jason's brilliant idea! <br>And I brought the prayer shall <br><br>[MARVIN, TRINA, MENDEL, JASON, CHARLOTTE, CORDELIA] <br>Ooo <br>It's Jason's bar mitzvah! <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Don't you move <br>Everything will soon be great <br>Close your eyes <br>While we redecorate <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>I'll unwrap the billion hors d'oeuvres <br>And someone, please, eat them <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Photo <br><br>[ALL] <br>Ooo <br>It's Jason's bar mitzvah! <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Lovely, flowers make things lovely <br>Champagne makes things lovely, too <br>Everything's amiss <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Drink up! <br>Anyone for bubbly? <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Probably, it's doubly <br>Useful at a time like this <br>Cheers <br><br>[MENDEL AND WHIZZER] <br>Cheers <br><br>[TRINA] <br>And aren't things lovely? <br>I feel more helpless than I have in years <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Try this on <br>Mendel, get this thing in gear <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Please excuse me <br>If I interfere <br>But I feel that, since I'm the host <br>It's me who should toast him <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, TRINA, MENDEL, CHARLOTTE, CORDELIA] <br>Ooo, ooo <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>To Jason's bar mitzvah! <br><br>[CHARLOTTE] <br>I notified the nurses <br>Told them please to not intrude <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>I passed around the food <br>And dumped some extra food <br>'Cause, Lord knows, we've got plenty <br><br>[CHARLOTTE] <br>She's cooked for some 200 guests <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>We number not that many <br>Actually..., we're seven <br><br>[CHARLOTTE] <br>Maybe it's not dumb <br>The way this whole thing ends <br>The food tastes really yummy <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>Oh, mummy <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Lovely <br><br>[CHARLOTTE AND CORDELIA] <br>The flowers seem to sparkle <br>The candelabra sets the tone <br><br>[TRINA] <br>I must make things <br><br>[CHARLOTTE AND CORDELIA] <br>The wine is very soothing <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Lovely <br><br>[CHARLOTTE AND CORDELIA] <br>Soothes the "something, something" <br>Someone needed soothing <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Put everything <br><br>[CHARLOTTE] <br>I think, perhaps, I'm overdressed <br><br>[TRINA] <br>In its place <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>I think, perhaps, it doesn't matter <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Ready for the <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>That you are <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Band <br><br>[CHARLOTTE AND CORDELIA] <br>Here we are <br>Jason's bar mitzvah looks <br>Like the books <br>Say it should <br><br>[TRINA, CHARLOTTE, AND CORDELIA] <br>Cheers <br><br>[TRINA] <br>And aren't things lovely? <br><br>[CHARLOTTE AND CORDELIA] <br>Everything is lovely <br><br>[TRINA, CHARLOTTE, AND CORDELIA] <br>I feel more helpless than I have in years <br><br>[MENDEL AND WHIZZER] <br>Here he comes <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun <br>Fix his tie <br>Trina, try <br>To make him smile more <br><br>[WHIZZER, TRINA, MENDEL, CHARLOTTE, CORDELIA] <br>Don't know why <br>But he looks like Marvin <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>How did you turn out so great? <br>Who do I thank for the man you've turned into? <br>Kid, do you know <br>How proud I am? <br>If I don't show <br>How proud I am... <br>You hold my dreams <br>Kid, I burst at the seams <br>'Cause of you <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Son of Abraham, Isaac, and Jacob <br>Son of Marvin, Son of Trina, Son of Whizzer, Son of Mendel <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, TRINA, JASON, CHARLOTTE, CORDELIA] <br>And godchild to the lesbians from next door <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Sing <br>Oh, sing <br>Oh, sing <br><br>[JASON] <br>Vie-eme-low yea-o-leh <br>Heh-oh-non vi-low <br>Ah-yis-is-ooh ay-ysi-ro-ale <br>Ha-ooh low toe vo-o-meem aboh]]></content><category term="`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company" label="`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company"/><category term="Jason`s Bar Mitzvah" label="Jason`s Bar Mitzvah"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Andrew_Rannells/You_Gotta_Die_Sometime/</id><title>Andrew Rannells - You Gotta Die Sometime - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Andrew_Rannells/You_Gotta_Die_Sometime/" title="Andrew Rannells - You Gotta Die Sometime - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[WHIZZER] <br>Okay-- <br>When the doctor started using phrases like <br>"You'll pass away" <br>What could i say? <br>I said doctor <br>In plain English <br>Tell me why was I chosen <br>Why me of all men? <br>Doctor, here's the good part <br>At least death means <br>I'll never be scared about dying again <br><br>Let's get on with living while we can <br>And not play dumb <br>Death's gonna come <br>When it does, screw the nerves <br>I'll be eating hors d'oeuvres <br>It's the roll of the dice and no crime <br>You gotta die sometime <br><br>Death is not a friend <br>But I hope in the end <br>He takes me in his arms and lets me hold his face <br>He holds me in his arms and whispers something funny <br>He lifts me in his arms and tells me to embrace <br>His attack <br>Then the scene turns to black <br><br>Life sucks <br>People always hate a loser <br>And they hate lame ducks <br>Screw me and shucks <br>That's it <br>That's the ball game <br>I don't smoke, don't do drugs <br>And then comes the bad news <br>I quit <br>That's the ball game <br>It's the chink in the armor <br>The shit in the karma <br>The blues <br><br>Can I keep my cool despite the urge <br>To fall apart? <br>How should I start? <br>I would cry if I could <br>But it does no damn good <br>To explain I'm a man in my prime <br>You gotta die sometime <br><br>Death's a funny pal <br>With a weird sort of talent <br>He puts his arms around my neck and walks me to the bed <br>He pins me up against the wall and kisses me like crazy <br>The many stupid things I thought about with dread <br>Now delight <br>Then the scene turns to white <br><br>Give me the balls to orchestrate <br>A graceful leave <br>That's my reprieve <br>To go out <br>Without care <br>My head high <br>In the air <br>It's the last little mountain I'll climb <br>I'll climb <br>You gotta die sometime <br>You gotta die sometime <br>You gotta die sometime <br>You gotta die <br>Sometime, sometime <br>Sometime, sometime <br>Somtime, sometime <br>Sometime, sometime]]></content><category term="Andrew Rannells" label="Andrew Rannells"/><category term="You Gotta Die Sometime" label="You Gotta Die Sometime"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tracie_Thoms/Something_Bad_Is_Happening/</id><title>Tracie Thoms - Something Bad Is Happening - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tracie_Thoms/Something_Bad_Is_Happening/" title="Tracie Thoms - Something Bad Is Happening - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[DR. CHARLOTTE(to MARVIN)] <br>Something bad is happening <br>Something very bad is happening <br>Something that kills <br>Something infectious <br>Something that spreads <br>From one man to another]]></content><category term="Tracie Thoms" label="Tracie Thoms"/><category term="Something Bad Is Happening" label="Something Bad Is Happening"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anthony_Rosenthal/Another_Miracle_Of_Judaism/</id><title>Anthony Rosenthal - Another Miracle Of Judaism - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anthony_Rosenthal/Another_Miracle_Of_Judaism/" title="Anthony Rosenthal - Another Miracle Of Judaism - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[JASON] <br>Hello, God <br>I don't think we've ever really spoken <br>If you'd kindly allow <br>How about a miracle now? <br><br>I don't know if you exist <br>I can't hear your fingers snappin' <br>Are you just a big psychiatrist? <br>Or, can you make things not happen? <br><br>Do this for me <br>And I'll get bar mitzvahed <br>In exchange for <br>Could you please make my friend stop dying? <br>I am not naive <br>It won't be easy <br>But if you could make my friend stop dying <br>God <br>That'd be the miracle of Judaism <br>That'd be the miracle of Judaism]]></content><category term="Anthony Rosenthal" label="Anthony Rosenthal"/><category term="Another Miracle Of Judaism" label="Another Miracle Of Judaism"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/Unlikely_Lovers/</id><title>Christian Borle - Unlikely Lovers - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/Unlikely_Lovers/" title="Christian Borle - Unlikely Lovers - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[MARVIN] <br>Who'd believe that we two <br>Would end up as lovers? <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Do you want me to reply? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Him and me, you and I <br>Passionately lovers <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Please don't get morbid <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Right <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>It's just- <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Don't fight <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>That I haven't died yet <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Just stop it <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>I'm sick, but kicking <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Geez <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Alright <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Louise <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Good night <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I'm staying here in this spot <br>Whether you want me to or not <br>I'm staying <br>Here I am, by your side <br>One old horny lover <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Please go home and don't be scared <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>What's the fuss? I'm not scared <br>What good is a lover who's scared? <br>Hit me if you need to <br>Slap my face or hold me till winter <br>Oh, baby, please do <br>I love you too <br>My lover <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Marvin, just go home and turn on TV <br>Drink a little something till you're 'dead' <br>Think of me around <br>Sleeping soundly in our bed <br>Marv, did you hear what I said? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Shut your mouth, go to sleep <br>Time I met a sailor <br>Are you sleeping yet or...? <br>What is what? Whizzer, but <br>I can't help but feeling I've failed <br>Let's be scared together <br>Let's pretend that nothing is awful <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>There's nothing to fear <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>There's nothing to fear' <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Just stay right here <br><br>[MARVIN AND WHIZZER] <br>I love you <br><br>[CHARLOTTE] <br>Shhh. Maybe he's tired <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>Shhh. Maybe he's waiting for us <br><br>[CHARLOTTE] <br>Shhh. Maybe he's waiting for a visit <br><br>[CHARLOTTE AND CORDELIA] <br>Is it a bad time? We'll come back <br>If it's a bad time, we'll come back <br>We'll come in <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Look at us, four old friends <br>Four unlikely lovers <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>We don't know what time will bring <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>I've a clue <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I have too <br><br>[CHARLOTTE AND CORDELIA] <br>Let's look like we haven't <br><br>[MARVIN, CHARLOTTE, AND CORDELIA] <br>And each say nothing <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Sky! <br><br>[CHARLOTTE] <br>It's blue! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I love the sky! <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>I love the trees! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I love bad weather! <br><br>[CHARLOTTE] <br>I love the earth beneath my feet! <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>I love friends that hover! <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, CHARLOTTE, AND CORDELIA] <br>Gee, we love to eat <br>And we need something sweet <br>To love! <br><br>What a group we four are <br>Four unlikely lovers <br>And we vow that we will <br>Buy the farm, arm in arm <br>Four unlikely lovers with heart <br>Let's be scared together <br>Let's pretend that nothing is awful <br><br>[WHIZZER, CHARLOTTE, AND CORDELIA] <br>There's nothing to fear <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>There's nothing to fear <br><br>[WHIZZER, CHARLOTTE, AND CORDELIA] <br>Just stay right here <br>I love you <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I love you <br><br>[WHIZZER, CHARLOTTE, AND CORDELIA] <br>I love you <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I love you <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, CHARLOTTE, AND CORDELIA] <br>Who'd have thought that we four <br>Would end up as lovers]]></content><category term="Christian Borle" label="Christian Borle"/><category term="Unlikely Lovers" label="Unlikely Lovers"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anthony_Rosenthal/Canceling_The_Bar_Mitzvah/</id><title>Anthony Rosenthal - Canceling The Bar Mitzvah - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anthony_Rosenthal/Canceling_The_Bar_Mitzvah/" title="Anthony Rosenthal - Canceling The Bar Mitzvah - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[TRINA] <br>Jason, if you want a Bar Mitzvah <br>God knows, you can have a Bar Mitzvah <br>But I have to know <br>And I have to know now <br>Just what it is you want <br>I've addressed the invitations <br>Here's your chance to give me Hell <br>If you think it's bust <br>Then it's probably just <br>As well <br><br>[JASON] <br>Can't we wait 'til Whizzer gets better? <br>Can't we wait 'til he's out? <br>That's what bar mitzvahs should be all about! <br>Good friends close at hand - <br>Don't you understand? <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>We can't be sure when <br>He'll get better <br>When, or if <br>He'll ever get better <br>But the hall is booked <br>And the band's been retained <br>So, Jason, please <br>What we'll do is your decision <br>There's no right and there's no wrong <br>Just say yes or no <br>And we'll promise to go along <br><br>[JASON] <br>Finally, now, it's all my decision <br>Like it's my bar mitzvah <br>Just like nothing happened <br>Hell, let's have a party <br>Just like nothing happened <br>Why don't you make this dumb decision yourselves <br>Okay? <br>Why don't you make this dumb decision yourselves? <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>We'll have the bar mitzvah? <br><br>[JASON] <br>No <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Then, we'll cancel the bar mitzvah? <br><br>[JASON] <br>No! <br><br>[TRINA AND MENDEL] <br>We'll wait until you make a decision <br><br>[TRINA(spoken)] <br>Now what do we do? <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Why don't we tell him <br>That we don't have the answers? <br>And that life can be grim <br>Life's not all about him <br>And things rarely go according to plan <br>Tell him things happen <br>For no damned good reason <br>And his lack of control <br>Kills what's best in your soul <br>And this is the start <br>To his becoming a man <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Holding to the ground <br>As the ground keeps shifting <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Trying to keep sane <br>As the rules keep changing <br><br>[TRINA AND MENDEL] <br>Keeping up my head <br>As my heart falls out of sight <br>Everything will be alright]]></content><category term="Anthony Rosenthal" label="Anthony Rosenthal"/><category term="Canceling The Bar Mitzvah" label="Canceling The Bar Mitzvah"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Falsettos_2016_Broadway_Company/Days_Like_This/</id><title>`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company - Days Like This - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Falsettos_2016_Broadway_Company/Days_Like_This/" title="`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company - Days Like This - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[WHIZZER] <br>Good morning <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Whizzer, kid, you're looking very good today <br>You had to see yourself a few days back <br>I had a heart attack! <br>Jesus <br>But today you seem to be <br>On the way to recovery! <br>Oh, Whizzer, I want to applaud! <br>It's days like this I almost believe in God <br>Days like this I almost believe <br>In God <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>Hello! <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Hi! Food... <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>Rugelach! <br>Gefilte fish! <br>It's so good, you'd think it's Italian! <br>Also a soup made from chicken <br>That, though un-exotic, is antibiotic! <br>Why, I'm up to my ass <br>In a kosher morass! <br>For aches and croup <br>Try my chicken soup! <br><br>[MARVIN]-------------------------[CORDELIA] <br>Whizzer, kid, you're-------------So, let's begin <br>Looking very good today.-------It's medicine! <br>You had to see yourself --------It could be we're both <br>-----------------------------------Going to cure you <br>A few days back,----------------Me with my soup <br>I had a heart attack!------------She with her medication <br>Jesus!----------------------------Such elation! <br><br>[MARVIN AND CORDELIA] <br>But today you seem to be <br>On the way to recovery! <br>Oh, Whizzer, I want to applaud! <br>It's days like this we almost believe in God <br>Days like this we almost believe <br>In <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>Gefilte fish! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>God! <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>Canadelach! <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Hi <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Hi <br><br>[TRINA] <br>We had trouble parking <br>Just like on our second date <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>I hyperventilate <br>But since I'm parking in the city, I've improved <br>Or else the hydrants moved! <br><br>Go ahead, be good and pissed <br>'How can I help?'' says the wiry psychiatrist! <br><br>[TRINA] <br>He'll make you well! <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Right... <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>I'll make you well! <br><br>[CHARLOTTE AND JASON] <br>Whizzer, hello! <br><br>[JASON] <br>Gee, you look awful <br>I think you need to play some chess <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Jason, sit down and begin <br><br>[JASON] <br>I'll let you win, Whizzer <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Don't let me win <br><br>[JASON] <br>I'll let you win <br><br>[MARV/CHAR]-----[CORDELIA]----[JASON]----------[MEN/TRI] <br>Whizzer, kid,-----Rugelach-------Whizzer--------He'll make <br>You're looking----Gefilte fish-----hello, gee------you well <br>Very good--------so good---------you look-------I'll make <br>Today. You--------you'd think------awful. I--------you well <br>Had to see--------it's Italian-------think you------He'll make <br>Yourself a---------Also a soup------need to-------you well <br>Few days---------that though-------play some----I'll make <br>Back, I had a-----un-exotic----------chess---------you well <br>Heart attack!----is antibiotic <br>Jesus' <br><br>[MARVIN, TRINA, MENDEL, JASON, CHARLOTTE, CORDELIA] <br>But today you seem to be <br>On the way to recovery! <br>Oh, Whizzer, I want to applaud! <br>It's days like this we almost believe in God <br>Days like this we almost believe in God <br>Days like this we almost believe in God <br>Days like this we almost believe <br>In <br><br>[TRINA] <br>What is this? <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>Gefilt-ee fish! <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Gefilt-ah fish <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Right! <br><br>[TRINA] <br>You're looking very good today! <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>Canadelach! <br><br>[ALL] <br>God!]]></content><category term="`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company" label="`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company"/><category term="Days Like This" label="Days Like This"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stephanie_J_Block/Holding_To_The_Ground/</id><title>Stephanie J. Block - Holding To The Ground - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stephanie_J_Block/Holding_To_The_Ground/" title="Stephanie J. Block - Holding To The Ground - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[TRINA] <br>I was sure growing up I would live the life <br>My mother assumed I'd live <br>Very Jewish, very middle-class, and very straight <br>Where healthy men stayed healthy men <br>And marriages were long and great <br>I smile <br>I don't complain <br><br>I'm trying to keep sane as the rules keep changing <br>Families aren't what they were <br>Thank God there's a husband and a child whom I adore <br>But then there's more <br>So many more <br>There's always more <br><br>Life is never what you planned <br>Life is moments you can't understand <br>And that is life <br>I'm plain <br>I don't astound <br><br>I hold to the ground <br>As the ground keeps shifting <br>Keeping my balance square <br>Trying not to care about this man who Marvin loves <br>But that's my life <br>He shared my life <br>Yes, that's my life <br><br>Life is never what you planned <br>Life is moments you can't understand <br>And that is life <br><br>Holding to the ground <br>As the ground keeps shifting <br>Trying to keep sane <br>As the rules keep changing <br>Keeping up my head <br>As my heart falls out of sight <br>Everything will be all right <br>Everything will be all right]]></content><category term="Stephanie J. Block" label="Stephanie J. Block"/><category term="Holding To The Ground" label="Holding To The Ground"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tracie_Thoms/Something_Bad_Is_Happening___More_Racquetball/</id><title>Tracie Thoms - Something Bad Is Happening / More Racquetball - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tracie_Thoms/Something_Bad_Is_Happening___More_Racquetball/" title="Tracie Thoms - Something Bad Is Happening / More Racquetball - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[People might think I'm very dyke-ish <br>I make a big stink when I must, but goddamn <br>I'm just professional, never too nonchalant <br>If I'm a bitch, well, I am what I am! <br><br>Just call me 'Doc', don't call me 'lady' <br>I don't like to talk when I'm losing the game <br>Bachelors arrive sick and frightened <br>They leave weeks later unenlightened <br>We see a trend, but the trend has no name <br><br>Something bad is happening <br>Something very bad is happening <br>Something stinks, something immoral <br>Something so bad that words have lost their meaning! <br>Rumors fly and tales abound <br>Stories echo underground! <br>Something bad <br>Is spreading, spreading, spreading <br>'Round! <br><br>Tell me how it tastes! <br>Tell me if it's good! <br>Tell me, dear, if you'd like seconds- <br><br>Stop! <br><br>Go ahead and wound my pride <br><br>Just stop <br><br>You're feeling very sick inside, well, okay <br>So you've had a bad day <br>I don’t know what to say <br>Look what’s become of my doctor <br><br>She's my doctor <br>And I love her! <br>She's got passion! <br>She's intelligent and, Jesus Christ <br>A doctor! <br>Very wealthy <br>And I love her! <br>Doctor of internal medicine! <br>I'm heartsick you’re unhappy <br><br>Life is crappy <br><br>And you always see <br>The glass half full <br>I'm nervous <br><br>This is fucking ridiculous! <br><br>She's my doctor and I love her! <br>She's got heart! <br><br>My spirits sag when I read the magazines <br>Men dressed in drag, next to their moms <br>Fashion and passion and filler <br>But not a word about the killer <br>I like the ballgowns, but Jesus Christ! <br><br>Something bad is happening! <br><br>Something very bad is happening! <br>Something stinks, something immoral! <br>Something so bad that words have lost their meaning! <br>Rumors fly and tales abound <br>Stories echo underground! <br>Something bad is <br><br>Which she'd never say <br>Little things don't get in her way <br>What can it be? <br>What can it be? <br><br>Spreading, spreading, spreading 'Round! <br><br>Look, a virus has been found! <br>Stories echo underground! Something bad is <br><br>Spreading, spreading, spreading 'Round! <br><br><br>It bounced in <br><br>No, it didn't <br><br>Hit the line, you know it did <br><br>Just begin <br><br>Are you kidding? <br>Who's telling who how to play? <br><br>Let me live, please forgive <br>Me for winning one game <br><br>Serve it up <br><br>I attack! <br><br>Hold it down, keep him back- <br>Something's gone out of whack! <br><br>I hit! <br><br>Ah shit! <br><br>My game! <br>1 2 3 4 <br><br>1 2 3- damn it <br><br>1 2 3 4 <br><br>1 2- <br>Good serve, Marvin <br><br>1 2 3 4 <br><br>1 2- <br>It hit my heel <br><br>Don't be bitter <br><br>No big deal, the game is yours <br><br>It's unreal, you're a quitter! <br><br>I can't go on anymore! <br><br>Be a jerk, my sweet bruiser <br>Try to be a decent loser! <br>At least you could give me that! <br><br>Excuse me? <br>I'm ready to go! <br>I'm ready... <br><br>I'm sorry <br><br>Do you know all I want is you? <br>Anything you do is alright <br>Yes, it's alright <br><br>Everything will be alright <br>Everything will be alright <br>Everything will be alright <br>Everything will be alright]]></content><category term="Tracie Thoms" label="Tracie Thoms"/><category term="Something Bad Is Happening / More Racquetball" label="Something Bad Is Happening / More Racquetball"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/What_More_Can_I_Say_/</id><title>Christian Borle - What More Can I Say? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/What_More_Can_I_Say_/" title="Christian Borle - What More Can I Say? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[MARVIN] <br>It's been hot <br>Also very sweet <br>And I'm not usually indiscreet <br>But when he sparkles <br>The earth begins to sway <br>What more can I say? <br>How can I express <br>How confused am I by our happiness? <br>I can't eat breakfast <br>I barely tie my shoe <br>What more can I do? <br><br>If I say I love him <br>You might think my words come cheap <br>Let's just say <br>I'm glad he's mine awake <br>Asleep <br><br>It's been hot <br>Also, it's been swell <br>More than not <br>It's been more than words can tell <br>I halt <br>I stammer <br>I sing a rondelay <br>What more can I say? <br><br>I'll stay calm <br>Untie my tongue <br>And try to stay <br>Both kind and young <br><br>I was taught <br>Never brag or shout <br>Still it's hot <br>Just like how you read about <br>And also caring <br>And never too uncouth <br>That's the simple truth <br>That's the simple truth <br><br>Can you tell <br>I have been revised? <br>It's so swell <br>Damn it, even I'm surprised <br>We laugh <br>We fumble <br>We take it day by day <br>What more can I say?]]></content><category term="Christian Borle" label="Christian Borle"/><category term="What More Can I Say?" label="What More Can I Say?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandon_Uranowitz/Everyone_Hates_His_Parents/</id><title>Brandon Uranowitz - Everyone Hates His Parents - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandon_Uranowitz/Everyone_Hates_His_Parents/" title="Brandon Uranowitz - Everyone Hates His Parents - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Just look at me <br>I'm a world-class traveler <br>Each Friday night <br>Travel travel travel <br>From her house to his house <br>First take the 104 <br>With my computer <br>I am just a little kid <br>Not a commuter <br>And each Sunday night <br>Mother comes to get me <br>And I hear them fight <br>Everybody's yelling about the bar mitzvah <br>It's not a wrestling match <br>Why are the sweating? <br>It's not a funeral <br>What's so upsetting? <br>It's a celebration <br>Where I get presents <br>But everybody's yelling <br>And everybody's ruining it <br>It's a celebration <br>Where I get richer <br>But everybody's yelling <br>And everybody's ruining it <br>Everybody's ruining it <br>Why, oh, why? <br>What have I done that they'd ruin my bar mitzvah? <br><br>What have I done that we'd ruin this bar mitzvah? <br><br>I want the Applebaums <br>They're lovely, and they like me <br><br>They're boring <br>She just likes the way you dress <br><br>Well, who wouldn't? <br><br>Have the Applebaums <br><br>Screw the Applebaums <br><br>Please don't do this! <br><br>Saul's a jerk <br><br>Have them <br><br>Nix them! <br><br>Long live the Applebaums! <br>Arguing takes work <br><br>I hate this! <br><br>Blame her! <br>This is all a waste <br><br>You're gonna blame me? <br>You have paintings of dicks! <br>Don't talk to me about taste <br><br>Stop! I don't want a bar mitzvah! <br>Okay? I don't want a bar mitzvah! <br><br>What do you mean you don't want a bar mitzvah? <br>What do you mean you don't want a bar mitzvah? <br>How do you think we <br>How do you think we <br>How do you think we feel about that? <br><br>Jason <br>I am agitato grande <br>Jason, I am muy disgutante <br>And muy disappointe <br>And muy nauseatus <br>And me mitzraim <br>Hotzionoo <br>Dayenu <br><br>Everyone hates his parents <br>Don't be ashamed <br>You'll grow up <br>You'll come through <br>You'll have kids <br>And they'll hate you too <br>Oh, everyone hates his parents <br>But, I confess <br>You grow up <br>You get old <br>You hate less <br><br>But I don't want it <br>Nothing that gives them pleasure I'll do <br>I don't want a bar mitzvah <br>Stupid bar mitzvah <br>Any bar mitzvah <br>Would You? <br><br>Everyone hates his parents <br>That's in the Torah <br>It's what history shows <br>In fact, God said to Moses: <br>"Moses, everyone hates his parents <br>That's how it is!" <br>And God knew <br>Because God hated His <br><br>You are going to kill your mother <br>Don't feel guilty, kill your mother <br>Rather than humiliate her <br>Killing your mother <br>Is the merciful thing to do <br><br>Jason, darling, don't get nervous <br>I'm right here, and at your service <br>Look, I'm calm and self-deluded <br>Grateful, 'cause I know <br>You'll do what I pray you'll do <br><br>Go ahead and kill your mother <br><br>Not with guns, but kill your mother <br><br>Rather than humiliate her <br><br>Killing your mother <br>Is the merciful thing to do <br><br>Oh my god <br>Everyone hates his parents <br>Now, I see why! <br>But in time <br>They'll cool out <br>And you'll think <br>They were only fooling <br>It's a strange thing about parents <br>Push turns to shove <br>What was hate <br>Becomes more or less love <br><br>Jason, please see a psychiatrist <br><br>I'm a psychiatrist. Get lost! <br><br>Everyone hates his parents <br>This too shall pass <br>You'll grow up <br><br>I'll come through <br>I'll have kids <br><br>And they'll hate you too <br><br>Oh, Everyone hates his parents <br><br>But kid I guess <br>You'll grow up <br><br>I'll grow up <br><br>You'll get old <br><br>I'll get old <br><br>And hate less <br><br>Flip me! <br><br>You got it! <br><br>Whoo! <br><br>And hate less]]></content><category term="Brandon Uranowitz" label="Brandon Uranowitz"/><category term="Everyone Hates His Parents" label="Everyone Hates His Parents"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Falsettos_2016_Broadway_Company/The_Baseball_Game/</id><title>`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company - The Baseball Game - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Falsettos_2016_Broadway_Company/The_Baseball_Game/" title="`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company - The Baseball Game - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We’re sitting <br>And watching Jason play baseball <br>We’re watching Jason play baseball! <br>We’re watching Jewish boys <br>Who cannot play baseball, play baseball! <br>We’re watching Jewish boys <br>Who cannot play baseball play- <br><br>I hate baseball, I really do! <br>Unlike the rest of you <br>I hate baseball! <br><br>We really wish he’d take this more seriously! <br><br>It's weird how he swings the bat! <br><br>It’s weird how he swings the bat <br>And why does he have to throw like that? <br><br>We’re sitting <br>And watching Jason make errors <br>The most pathetical errors! <br>We’re watching Jewish boys <br>Who almost read Latin <br>Up, battin’ <br>And battin’ bad! <br><br>Remember Sandy Koufax! <br>You can do it if you wanna do it! <br>Take heart from Hank Greenberg! <br>It's not genetic <br>Even you can be copasetic! <br>I think, I think <br>I think you can, I think you can! <br><br>We’re sitting <br>And watching Jason play baseball <br>We’re watching Jason play baseball! <br>We’re watching Jewish boys <br>We’re watching Jewish boys <br>We’re watching- <br>Slide, Jason <br>Slide, Jason! <br>Slide! <br><br>(Whizzer enters) <br><br>What is he doing here? <br><br>What are you doing here? <br><br>Jason asked me to come <br>Since he asked me to come, I came <br><br>Just what I wanted at a Little League game <br>My ex-husband’s ex-lover! <br>Isn’t that what every mother dreams about <br>Having at a Little League game? <br><br>Looking at Whizzer is like eating trayf <br><br>The kid was out! <br>The kid was safe! <br>The kid was out! <br>The kid was safe! <br><br>Hey! <br>I love baseball <br>I love Jason <br>That’s what I’m doing here <br><br>Aw, where the hell did they get that umpire?! <br><br>Look who’s here <br>Say hello <br><br>Hello <br><br>You’re looking sweeter than a donut <br><br>Marvin <br><br>Whizzer <br><br>He’s still queer? <br><br>Am I queer? <br><br>I don’t know! <br><br>Does it matter? <br><br>It’s been so long since I could tell <br>Sit in front of me <br>I wanna see the bald spot! <br>C’mon, c’mon <br>Move in front of me <br>It gives me pleasure to see the bald spot! <br>Since it’s the only <br>Physical imperfection that you've got <br>I wanna see it! <br>I wanna touch it! <br>I wanna run my hands through it! <br><br>We’re sitting <br>And watch the kid as he misses! <br>We’re watching Marvin throw kisses <br>We’re watching sixty-seven pounders <br>Watching Jewish boys in scroungers <br><br>Watching boys feel, boys bat <br>Boys miss, boys at- <br>Watching Jason on deck <br>Swinging the bat! <br><br>Hey, Jason <br><br>Oh, hi Whizzer. Glad you came! <br><br>Keep your head in the box <br>Don’t think of a thing <br>Keep your head in the box <br>Your eye on the ball <br>Take a breath, then let it out <br>And swing! <br><br>Keep your head in the box <br>Don’t think of a thing <br>Keep your head in the box <br>Your eye on the ball <br>Take a breath, then let it out <br>And swing! <br><br>Okay, go get 'em! <br><br>Even bald, he looks good <br><br>Just remember he’s psychotic <br><br>He looks damn good, but he’s cheap as dirt <br><br>Even maniacs can charm <br>Which he does, so beware <br><br>And just be careful <br><br>When he smiles that smile, avoid him <br>Or else sound the alert! <br><br>Whizzer? <br><br>Marvin? <br><br>Think there's any hope for the kid? <br><br>I love Jason, but this is not his venue <br><br>How could I know, without him <br>My life would be boring as shit? <br><br>Jason! You gotta move a little closer to the plate! <br><br>Oh, yes, it is- <br>He’s gonna be hit by the ball! <br><br>Please, God, don’t let me make the same mistake! <br><br>We’re sitting <br>And watching Jason, the batter! <br>We know our cheering won’t matter! <br>It is the very final inning <br>And the other team is winning <br>And there’s two outs, two strikes <br>But the bases are loaded and- <br><br>Could it be possible to see you, or to kiss you <br>Or to give you a call? <br><br>Anything’s possible <br><br>Jason <br>Hit the ball! <br>Run!]]></content><category term="`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company" label="`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company"/><category term="The Baseball Game" label="The Baseball Game"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anthony_Rosenthal/Miracle_Of_Judaism/</id><title>Anthony Rosenthal - Miracle Of Judaism - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anthony_Rosenthal/Miracle_Of_Judaism/" title="Anthony Rosenthal - Miracle Of Judaism - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[JASON] <br>Dot Nardoni, Tiffany Axelrod <br>Zoe Feinstein, Angelina Dellibovi <br>Bunny Doyne, or what's her name' <br>Mo Cristofaro <br>And Ellie Mazie Rosenthal's really well built <br>When Heather Levin stares at me <br>Why do I wilt? <br>I like when Julie Johnson <br>Does splits in her kilt <br><br>Of these girls <br>Which should I invite to my bar mitzvah? <br>I've a problem to flaunt: <br>I don't want the girls I should want <br><br>I want girls for whom I lust <br>Girls who wear a lot of makeup <br>Girls who smoke and show their bust <br>Girls with whom I always wake up- <br><br>Would they come though <br>If they were invited? <br>And not laugh <br>At my hebrew <br>And not laugh <br>At my father and his friends? <br><br>Excluding them, I find exciting <br>And I'm left with them, I'll be inviting <br>Selecting girls for one's bar mitzvah <br>God, that's the miracle of Judaism <br>That'd be the miracle of Judaism]]></content><category term="Anthony Rosenthal" label="Anthony Rosenthal"/><category term="Miracle Of Judaism" label="Miracle Of Judaism"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anthony_Rosenthal/Year_Of_The_Child/</id><title>Anthony Rosenthal - Year Of The Child - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anthony_Rosenthal/Year_Of_The_Child/" title="Anthony Rosenthal - Year Of The Child - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[JASON] <br>Baruch, baruch atah <br>Baruch atah Adonai <br>Baruch atah Adonai eloheinu <br>Melech haolam <br>Asher kidshanu, asher kidshanu <br>V'tzivanu l'hitateif batzitzit <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Jason dear, hello <br>Are you packed and waiting? <br>But before we go <br>Let me talk with father alone <br><br>Now as the bar mitzvah nears- <br>Jason, put your Walkerman on and hum <br>Since this is the last loving thing <br>We'll probably ever do together <br>Let's act adult and not go crazy <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Have you chosen yet who'll cater? <br><br>[TRINA] <br>What about it? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I know a person who can cater <br><br>[TRINA] <br>It's a personal opinion who should cater <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Can we consider who's gonna cater? <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Shh! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Please? <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Shh! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Please? <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Shh! <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Stop! This is so much crap <br>Throw a simple party! <br>Religion's just a trap <br>That ensnares the weak and the dumb <br>Stop with the prayers <br><br>[TRINA] <br>How can you stop with the prayers at a bar mitzvah? <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>The whole thing's voodoo <br>And I know more than you do! <br><br>[MARVIN AND TRINA] <br>This is the year of Jason's bar mitzvah! <br>We're more excited than we should be <br>This is the year of the child <br>When he spreads out his wings! <br>There's music in his heart! <br>His life's about to start! <br>His body's going wild! <br>My child <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>My child <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Our child <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Children, please <br>Throw the kid a celebration and relax <br>I'll bring women from the wrong side of the tracks <br>We'll have a ball! <br>I guess I'll have to raise this Jason myself <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Isn't he an asshole? <br><br>[TRINA]------------------------[MENDEL] <br>Yes, he is.--------------------My own bar mitzvah was <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Isn't he too much?----------A miserable occasion <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Yeah, but so are you--------The cause for such <br>Really, kiddo, so are you----Abrasion in my family <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Jesus, what an asshole!----It still gives me hives <br>Jason, where's my hug? <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Where's my hug? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Where's my hug? <br><br>[MARVIN, TRINA, AND MENDEL] <br>This is the year for Jason's bar mitzvah <br>This is the year for Jason's bar mitzvah! <br><br>(doorbell rings) <br><br>[CHARLOTTE] <br>Look, look, look, look, look <br>It's a lesbian from next door! <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>Followed by her lover <br>Who's a lesbian from next door too! <br>And I've got food for you <br>Delicious food for you! <br>Nouvelle bar mitzvah cuisine! <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Ah... <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>Here's dietetic knishes, gefilte fishes <br>Food that's from the heart! <br>So take a bite and see <br>If all your friends agree <br>It's good! <br><br>[MARVIN, TRINA, MENDEL, CHARLOTTE, AND CORDELIA] <br>Yummy yummy <br>Yummy yummy <br>Yummy yummy <br>Yummy yummy <br>Yummy yummy yummy yummy yum! <br><br>We'll have one perfect time! <br>We'll spend billions of dollars! <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>Conga! <br><br>[MARVIN, TRINA, MENDEL, CHARLOTTE, AND CORDELIA] <br>We'll have flowers galore (Whoo!) <br>And the band will sound fine! (Whoo!) <br>There'll be chandeliers set round the room <br>With the men in tuxedos! <br><br>There'll be food, like food never before! <br>What a day to remember! <br>This is the year of Jason's bar mitzvah! <br><br>[JASON] <br>They're more excited than they should be <br><br>[MARVIN, TRINA, MENDEL, CHARLOTTE, AND CORDELIA] <br>This is the year of the child <br>When he spreads out his wings! <br>There's music in his heart! <br>His life's about to start! <br>His body's going wild! <br>My <br>Child!]]></content><category term="Anthony Rosenthal" label="Anthony Rosenthal"/><category term="Year Of The Child" label="Year Of The Child"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Falsettos_2016_Broadway_Company/Falsettoland___About_Time/</id><title>`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company - Falsettoland / About Time - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Falsettos_2016_Broadway_Company/Falsettoland___About_Time/" title="`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company - Falsettoland / About Time - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[MENDEL] <br>Homosexuals <br>Women with children <br>Short insomniacs <br>And a teeny tiny band <br><br>Come, back in <br>The welcome mat is on the floor <br>Let's, begin <br>This story needs an ending <br><br>Homosexual <br>Father with children <br>One bar mitzfah that <br>Is scrupulously planned <br><br>[ALL] <br>Lover's come and lover's go <br>Lover's fight and sing fortissimo <br>Give these handsome boys a hand <br>Welcome to Falsettoland <br><br>[TRINA AND WHIZZER] <br>Nancy Reagan <br>Meanest and thinnest of the first Ladies <br>Moves into the White House <br><br>[MARVIN, JASON, MENDEL, CHARLOTTE, CORDELIA] <br>Ya-bah-dah-bah <br><br>[WHIZZER AND TRINA] <br>It's the '80s <br><br>[MARVIN, JASON, MENDEL, CHARLOTTE, CORDELIA] <br>Ya-bah-dah-bah <br><br>[WHIZZER AND TRINA] <br>Ooh, the '80s <br><br>[MARVIN, JASON, MENDEL, CHARLOTTE, CORDELIA] <br>Ya-bah-dah-bah <br><br>[WHIZZER AND TRINA] <br>What a world we live <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, MENDEL, AND JASON] <br>March, march, march of the Falsettos <br>March of the Falsettos <br><br>[TRINA, CHARLOTTE, AND CORDELIA] <br>What a world we live in <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, MENDEL, AND JASON] <br>Who is man enough to march in <br>March of the Falsettos <br><br>[ALL] <br>Ya-bah-dah-bah <br><br>[CHARLOTTE AND CORDELIA] <br>Spiky lesbians <br><br>[DR. CHARLOTTE] <br>Women internists <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>Shiksa caterer <br><br>[TRINA, CORDELIA, AND CHARLOTTE] <br>Who is trying to expand <br><br>[ALL] <br>Everybody on your mark <br><br>[TRINA, CORDELIA, AND CHARLOTTE] <br>Congregate in Central Park <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, MENDEL, AND JASON] <br>Pretty boys are in demand <br><br>[ALL] <br>Welcome to Falsettoland <br>Whee! <br>Whoo! <br>What a world we live in! <br>Whee! <br>Whoo! <br>What a world we live in! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>It's about time, don't ya think? <br>It's about time to grow up, don't ya think? <br>It's about time to grow up and face the music <br>It's about time <br><br>Since we last spoke <br>Two years are waning <br>I'll try explaining <br>Just what you've missed <br>We called a truce <br>And fitfully we coexist <br>I'm still loose <br>She's still with the psychiatrist <br>So I don't have a psychiatrist <br>Except on the Jewish holidays <br>But I still have my son on the weekends <br>Just on the weekends <br>And some very good friends <br>But I don't have a lover anymore <br>Oh my God <br>When am I gonna get over this <br>When am I gonna get over this <br>When am I gonna get over this <br><br>[WHIZZER, CHARLOTTE, AND CORDELIA] <br>Homosexuals <br><br>[TRINA AND JASON] <br>Women with children <br><br>[ALL] <br>Ex-Ex Lovers <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>And a teeny tiny band <br><br>[ALL] <br>Welcome to Falsettoland <br><br>[CORDELIA] <br>Shiksa caterers <br><br>[CORDELIA AND MENDEL] <br>Short insomniacs <br><br>[CORDELIA, MENDEL, AND JASON] <br>Hypochondriacs <br><br>[ALL] <br>Yiddish Americans <br>Spiky families <br>Radiologists <br>Intellectuals <br>Nervous wrecks! <br>AH! <br>Welcome to Falsettoland <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>It's about time, don't ya think <br>It's about time to grow up, don't ya think <br>It's about time to grow up and face the music <br>It's about time <br>One day I'd like to be <br>As mature as my son, who Is twelve and a half <br>And this tall! <br>That's all I'd like to be <br>That's all! <br>It's about growing up, getting older, living on a lover's shoulder <br>Learning love is not a crime <br>It's about time <br>It's about time <br>It's about time <br>It's about-]]></content><category term="`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company" label="`Falsettos` 2016 Broadway Company"/><category term="Falsettoland / About Time" label="Falsettoland / About Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/Father_To_Son/</id><title>Christian Borle - Father To Son - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/Father_To_Son/" title="Christian Borle - Father To Son - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[JASON] <br>My father says that love <br>Is the most beautiful thing in the world <br>I think girls are <br>I think girls are the most <br>Beautiful thing <br>Not love <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Kid, be my son <br>What I've done to you is rotten <br>Say I was scared <br>I kept marching in one place <br>Marching in time <br>To a tune I'd forgotten <br><br>I loved you, I love you <br>I meant no disgrace <br>This here is love <br>When we're talking <br>Face to face <br><br>Father to son <br>I, for one, would take love slower <br>I've made my choice <br>But you can sing a different song <br>Watch as you sing <br>How your voice gets much lower <br><br>You'll be, kid, a man, kid <br>If nothing goes wrong <br>Sing for yourself <br>As you march <br>Along <br><br>A man, kid, you'll be, kid <br>Whatever your song <br>Sing for us all <br>As we march <br>Along]]></content><category term="Christian Borle" label="Christian Borle"/><category term="Father To Son" label="Father To Son"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stephanie_J_Block/I_Never_Wanted_To_Love_You/</id><title>Stephanie J. Block - I Never Wanted To Love You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stephanie_J_Block/I_Never_Wanted_To_Love_You/" title="Stephanie J. Block - I Never Wanted To Love You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[TRINA] <br>I never wanted to love you <br>I only wanted to love and not be blamed <br>Let me go, you should know <br>I'm not ashamed <br>To have loved you <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>I loved you more than I meant to <br>In my profession, one's love stays unexpressed <br>Here we stand, take my hand <br>God, I'm distressed <br>How I love you <br><br>[JASON] <br>I hate the world! <br><br>[TRINA] <br>He hates everything! <br><br>[JASON] <br>I love my dad! <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>He loves his father <br><br>[JASON] <br>I love the things I've never had <br><br>[TRINA AND MARVIN] <br>Love our family <br><br>[JASON] <br>Lord, hear our call! <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Help us all <br><br>[TRINA AND WHIZZER] <br>Help us all <br><br>[MARVIN AND JASON] <br>Helps us all <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Help us all <br><br>[TRINA AND MARVIN] <br>Help us all! <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>I never wanted to love you <br>I never wanted, 'till death do we two part.' <br>Condescend, stay my friend <br>How do I start <br>Not to love you? <br><br>[TRINA] <br>I'm everything he wanted <br>It's time I put it all together <br>Our hands were tied <br>My father cried <br>'You'll marry!' <br>We married! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I never wanted to love you <br><br>[TRINA AND JASON] <br>He's mine <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I only wanted to see my face in yours <br>Jason's wild, save this child <br><br>[TRINA AND JASON] <br>He's mine <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>How he adores, and hates me- <br><br>It really killed me when you took those vows <br>Don't misunderstand, I'm in demand! <br>And anyhow, we're through! <br>I never wanted <br>I wanted- <br>I never, never, never, never <br>Never, never wanted to love you! <br>I never wanted to love you! <br>I never wanted to love you! <br>I never wanted to love you! <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, TRINA, AND JASON] <br>Love you!]]></content><category term="Stephanie J. Block" label="Stephanie J. Block"/><category term="I Never Wanted To Love You" label="I Never Wanted To Love You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stephanie_J_Block/Marvin_Hits_Trina/</id><title>Stephanie J. Block - Marvin Hits Trina - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:11:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:11:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stephanie_J_Block/Marvin_Hits_Trina/" title="Stephanie J. Block - Marvin Hits Trina - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[MARVIN] <br>Hello, Trina, thank you for sending this <br>Goodness, Trina, I am relieved <br>Frankly, Trina, nice of you sending this <br>Thank you, Trina, I have received <br>Your new-sent wedding invitations! <br>They are <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, MENDEL, AND JASON] <br>Pseudo-romantic and sick! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>You say you'll <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, MENDEL, AND JASON] <br>Love him until you both die! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>You die on <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, MENDEL, AND JASON] <br>May 27th at eight! <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>He has lost his mind <br>Marvin is not so uncouth <br>Marvin is not so unkind <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Mendel plans to rub my back <br>Mendel's not a maniac <br>And he's sweet <br>And he's warm <br>And he loves me so <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Tell me, Trina, what was the impetus? <br>Sorry, Trina, look in my eyes <br>Really, Trina, this is ridiculous <br>Jesus, Trina, how I despise <br>Your need for stupid conversation! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>You are <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, MENDEL, AND JASON] <br>Trying to ruin my sleep! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I'm sure you <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, MENDEL, AND JASON] <br>Chose him to make me look bad! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>How could you <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, MENDEL, AND JASON] <br>Ever deny what we had? <br><br>[TRINA AND WHIZZER] <br>We had fights and games <br>Marvin called us funny names <br>Marvin always played the clown <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Marvin acts like he's untrained <br>Marvin, I am so ashamed <br><br>[TRINA AND WHIZZER] <br>And he's sweet <br>And he's mean <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Do I love him? <br>No <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I am so dumb <br><br>[WHIZZER, TRINA, MENDEL, AND JASON] <br>Dumb <br>Dumb <br>Dumb! <br>Dumb!]]></content><category term="Stephanie J. Block" label="Stephanie J. Block"/><category term="Marvin Hits Trina" label="Marvin Hits Trina"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Andrew_Rannells/The_Games_I_Play/</id><title>Andrew Rannells - The Games I Play - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:12:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:12:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Andrew_Rannells/The_Games_I_Play/" title="Andrew Rannells - The Games I Play - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[WHIZZER] <br>I don't look for trouble <br>I do not accept blame <br>I've a good and a bad side <br>But they're one and the same <br>Ask me to arouse you <br>I will rise and obey <br>These are the games I play <br><br>I screw every morning <br>Then bathe and drink tea <br>I been playing canasta <br>Disasta- <br>Rously <br>All my recreation seems to suit me okay <br>These are the games I play <br><br>It's tough with love <br>Love's tough to show <br>Let me face the music <br>It's a song that I was waiting to hear so long <br>So long ago <br><br>I bet on the horses <br>I die by degree <br>I am sure his divorce is <br>A tribute to me <br>Ask me if I love him <br>It depends on the day <br>These are the games I play <br><br>It's tough, my friend <br>Love's looking strong <br>Play again the music <br>It's a song that I been waiting to hear <br>For much to long <br>Years, years too long <br><br>It hurts not to love him <br>It hurts when love fades <br>It's hard when part of him <br>Is off playing family charades <br><br>Ask me if I need him <br>Get him out of my way <br>These are <br>These are the games <br>These are the games <br>These are the only games I play]]></content><category term="Andrew Rannells" label="Andrew Rannells"/><category term="The Games I Play" label="The Games I Play"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandon_Uranowitz/Making_A_Home/</id><title>Brandon Uranowitz - Making A Home - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:12:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:12:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandon_Uranowitz/Making_A_Home/" title="Brandon Uranowitz - Making A Home - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[MENDEL AND TRINA] <br>Welcome to our humble place <br>We're concerned with setting a tone <br>With filling the space <br>Making a home <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>She becomes a happy wife <br><br>[TRINA] <br>He decides the role to assume <br>Building a life <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Shaping a room <br><br>[MENDEL AND TRINA] <br>What it needs is people <br>Men and women talking <br>Men and women thinking out loud <br>How far to go? <br><br>Visit when you please <br>You are not required to phone <br>We'll buy the cheese <br>God bless our home <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Books abound <br>To show we read <br>The dog's been flea'd <br>And sent outside to play <br>I hope it runs away <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>So do I <br><br>[JASON] <br>So do I <br><br>[MENDEL AND TRINA] <br>Afternoons we make hors d'oeuvres <br>After afternoons, we receive <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>We deceive <br><br>[MENDEL AND TRINA] <br>This is the price <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>This is the price <br><br>[WHIZZER, MENDEL, AND TRINA] <br>Making believe <br><br>What it needs is people <br>Men and women laughing <br>Men and women thinking out loud <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Should he love me? <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Should she love me? <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Could he love me? <br><br>[MENDEL AND TRINA] <br>Yes, we love the bed <br>Yes, we love to fight the unknown <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Baking the bread <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Sharpening knives <br><br>[WHIZZER, MENDEL, AND TRINA] <br>Forging ahead <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Loving our- <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Liking our- <br><br>[WHIZZER AND JASON] <br>Hating our- <br><br>[WHIZZER, JASON, MENDEL, AND TRINA] <br>Lives <br><br>[WHIZZER, MENDEL, AND TRINA] <br>Making a home <br>Making a home <br><br>[MENDEL AND TRINA] <br>Making a home]]></content><category term="Brandon Uranowitz" label="Brandon Uranowitz"/><category term="Making A Home" label="Making A Home"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/The_Chess_Game/</id><title>Christian Borle - The Chess Game - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:12:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:12:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/The_Chess_Game/" title="Christian Borle - The Chess Game - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[MARVIN] <br>That's the king. Treat him nice <br>Use some brains; now protect him <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Yes, I know. Here I go <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Play the game <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Please, don't watch me <br>I can do it! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Have a little scotch <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Shit, I blew it <br>Maybe you could show me where <br>I fear <br>I've lost my head <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Do you want my help? <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>No, I don't <br>I can think it through myself <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Start again. We've seen the worst <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>I'll go first <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Move a pawn <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>No, sir <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Move <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Where? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>There <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Here? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Move a pawn <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Who? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Not the queen <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Who? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Jesus <br><br>[MARVIN AND WHIZZER] <br>Life's a sham and <br>Every move is wrong <br>We've examined <br>Every more as we move along <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Winning is everything to me <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Nothing is everything to me <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Winning is everything to me <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Nothing is everything to me <br>Except sex... <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Move the pawn <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>And money <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Good first move <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Quite alright <br>Take a turn <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Thank you kindly <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Move the pawn <br>Move the pawn <br>Take my hand <br>Play the game <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>God you're pretty <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Ah, more's the pity <br>Since you need a man... <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>What? <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Who's brainy... <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Or... <br><br>[MARVIN AND WHIZZER] <br>Witty <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Move <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>What should I do now? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Move <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Where? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>There <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>How should I behave myself? <br>Maybe we should call it quits <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>This game shits <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Let me win <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Yes, sir <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Please <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Yes <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Thanks <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Wait! <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Whizzer wins! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Wait! <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Whizzer wins! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Wait! <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Checkmate! <br><br>[MARVIN AND WHIZZER] <br>Life's a sham and every move is wrong <br>We've examined every move as we move along <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>What? <br>Marvin...! <br>Whizzer's supposed to make the dinner <br>Be a patsy, loose at chess <br>Always bravely acquiesce <br>Clip the coupons, make the dinner <br>And love him <br>This has got to come to a stop, Marvin <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>This had got to come to a stop, Whizzer <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>This has been a lousy but <br><br>[WHIZZER AND MARVIN] <br>Fabulous flop <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Anyone understand? <br>All I want's a kiss <br>Anyone understand? <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Don't start explaining <br>I'm sick of explaining <br><br>(MARVIN) AND [WHIZZER] <br>And this had better come to a stop <br>(Whizzer) [Marvin] <br>Now, (Whizzer) [Marvin] <br>Ciao, (Whizzer) [Marvin] <br>Bend <br>This had better come <br>This had better come to a <br>This, this, this, this <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>This had better come to an end <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>This had better come to an end <br><br>[MARVIN AND WHIZZER] <br>This had better come to an end]]></content><category term="Christian Borle" label="Christian Borle"/><category term="The Chess Game" label="The Chess Game"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stephanie_J_Block/Trinas_Song___March_Of_The_Falsettos___Trinas_Song/</id><title>Stephanie J. Block - Trina`s Song / March Of The Falsettos / Trina`s Song - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:12:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:12:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stephanie_J_Block/Trinas_Song___March_Of_The_Falsettos___Trinas_Song/" title="Stephanie J. Block - Trina`s Song / March Of The Falsettos / Trina`s Song - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[TRINA] <br>I'm tired of all the happy men who rule the world <br>They grow - of that I'm sure <br>They grow - but don't mature <br>I'd like the chance to hide in that world <br><br>I'm listening <br>As these men who aren't quite men yet, but aren't boys <br>Make noise, and throw their knives; <br>Their toys are people's lives <br>They fight too hard <br>And play too rough <br>They sometimes love, but not enough <br>My heart will beat at will, but still... <br><br>It's crazy how they're acting <br>It's crazy my response <br>It's stupid how I love them <br>So dumb, how I anticipate their wants <br>But, so long as they amuse me <br>That, alone is what's required <br><br>So I'll roar <br>Like I'm wired <br>I'll explore what I'm feeling <br>Except what I'm feeling <br>Is tired <br>I'm tired <br>So tired of all the happy men who rule the world <br>Happy, frightened men who rule the world <br>Stupid, charming men <br>Silly, childish jerks <br><br>That said, I'll be his wife <br>I'll wed and change my life <br>I'll laugh, I'll smile, I'll welcome cheer <br>The time is right, the men are near <br>Now happiness and love appear <br><br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, JASON, AND MENDEL] <br>March. March <br>March of the Falsettos <br>March of the Falsettos <br>Whee! <br>Who is <br>Man enough to march to <br>March of the Falsettos? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>C'mere <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, JASON, AND MENDEL] <br>One foot <br>Following the other <br>Teach it to your brother <br>Make him <br>March <br>March <br>March of the Falsettos <br>March of the Falsettos <br><br>March a little bit <br>March a little bit <br>March a little bit <br>On <br><br>Four men, swaying in <br>Phosphorescence <br>Keep replaying their <br>Adolescence <br><br>Four men marching <br>But never mincing <br>Four men marching <br>Is so convincing <br>It's a goddamn surety <br>We're lacking in maturity <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>March <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>March <br><br>[JASON] <br>March <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>March <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Marvin's always wary <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>March <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>March <br><br>[JASON] <br>March <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>March <br><br>[JASON] <br>Does this mean that I'm a fairy? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>March <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>March <br><br>[JASON] <br>March <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>March <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>What a stupid theory! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>March <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>March <br><br>[JASON] <br>March <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>March <br>Whizzer says it doesn't, dearie <br>Don't be scared <br>Don't get tight <br>Asses bared <br>My delight <br>Shared- <br><br>[JASON] <br>With <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Four <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Young <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Men <br><br>[MARVIN, WHIZZER, JASON, AND MENDEL] <br>Alone in the night <br>March. March <br>March of the Falsettos <br>March of the Falsettos <br>Who is <br>Man enough to march to <br>March of the Falsettos? <br>Hi <br>One foot <br>Following the other! <br>Practice it on one another <br>March. March <br>March of the Falsettos <br>March of the Falsettos <br>March of the Falsettos <br>Marching home! <br>Home <br><br><br>[TRINA] <br>Please forgive my former shpieling？ <br>It does not concern the man <br>As for doubts that I've been feeling <br>I'll ignore them when I can <br>And the things that I must do <br>I'll do to make this all succeed <br>I'll commit, that's agreed <br>And with wit and precision <br>I've made a decision <br>To get the things I need <br>God, I'll try, try, I'll cry <br><br>No, I'll laugh ？ and unafraid <br>I'll laugh ？ and hire a maid <br>I'll fight the gods. I'll fight my ex <br>I'll beat the odds. I'll have good sex <br>My future's now on trial <br>I smile]]></content><category term="Stephanie J. Block" label="Stephanie J. Block"/><category term="Trina`s Song / March Of The Falsettos / Trina`s Song" label="Trina`s Song / March Of The Falsettos / Trina`s Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandon_Uranowitz/A_Marriage_Proposal___A_Tight-Knit_Family/</id><title>Brandon Uranowitz - A Marriage Proposal / A Tight-Knit Family - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:12:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:12:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandon_Uranowitz/A_Marriage_Proposal___A_Tight-Knit_Family/" title="Brandon Uranowitz - A Marriage Proposal / A Tight-Knit Family - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[JASON] <br>This is how you make a marriage proposal <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>I love you dear <br>I think you're swell <br>You're never near me close enough to tell <br>If I'm delightful or not <br><br>I crave your wrist <br>I praise your thigh <br>There's not a guy <br>There's not a piece of paper <br>There's not a man in pants <br>Who could love you the same as I! <br><br>Oftentimes, lovers are crazy people <br>Sometimes they kill each other <br>Just like a biblical brother <br>Did to his biblical brother <br>Back in biblical times <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Biblical times? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Biblical times? <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Biblical times <br>Oh, those biblical times! <br><br>I love your eyes <br>I love your face <br>I want you by my side to take my place <br>If I get sick or detained <br><br>Don't touch your hair, you're perfect <br>Don't start to cry <br>There's not a guy <br>There's not a horse or zebra <br>There's not a giant man <br>Who could love you the same as I! <br><br>Forget that giant man <br>He can't love you the same as I! <br>I'm not a giant man <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Good <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>But I'll love you until <br>Love you until <br>I die! <br><br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Well, the situation's this; <br>I don't want to cause a stink <br>I divorced my wife <br>She dried her eyes <br>Then she ran off with my shrink <br><br>But I want a tight-knit family <br>I want a wife who knows what love is <br>Maybe she does, I'm too damn peeved <br>Too self-absorbed <br>Too self-deceived <br>Who knows? <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>I should worry what he says <br>Like his words could hurt me worse <br>Marvin acts bereft <br>My acts of theft <br>Are incredibly perverse <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>You said it <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>It's embarrassing <br>But I've got a nice, tight family <br>Son with a brain and nice, bright mother <br>Yes, I feel guilt. Yes, I'm annoyed <br>So was Jung, so was Freud! <br><br>But I, I know you'll come through it <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I...I can't believe she loves you <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>If so, you'll end looking rich <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Why, I'm sure she cannot love you! <br>But nothing's impossible! <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Look who's got power <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Ah, King of the Losers! <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>At eighty an hour! <br>He can bitch <br>I can stall <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I want <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>I've got <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I want <br><br>[BOTH] <br>It all! <br>I'm sure we're gonna come through it! <br>No doubt, the bastard prepares! <br>We're needy and wanting <br>We're greedy as swine! <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>I just got a family <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>The family was mine! <br><br>[BOTH] <br>But he dares <br>Dares to brawl? <br><br>[MENDEL] / [MARVIN] <br>I got it all! / I want it all! <br>I got it all! / I want it all! <br>I got it all! / I want it all!]]></content><category term="Brandon Uranowitz" label="Brandon Uranowitz"/><category term="A Marriage Proposal / A Tight-Knit Family" label="A Marriage Proposal / A Tight-Knit Family"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stephanie_J_Block/Im_Breaking_Down/</id><title>Stephanie J. Block - I`m Breaking Down - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:12:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:12:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stephanie_J_Block/Im_Breaking_Down/" title="Stephanie J. Block - I`m Breaking Down - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[TRINA] <br>I'd like to be a princess on a throne <br>To have a country I can call my own <br>And a king <br>Who's lusty and requires a fling <br>With a female thing <br><br>Great, men will be men <br>Let me turn on the gas <br>I caught them in the den with <br>Marvin grabbing Whizzer's ass <br><br>Oh sure, I'm sure, he's sure he did his best <br>I bet he meant to be what he was not <br>The things he was are things which I forgot <br>He's a queen <br>I'm a queen <br>Where is my crown? <br><br>I'm breaking down <br>I'm breaking down <br>My life is shitty <br>And my kid seems like an idiot to me <br>I mean that's sick <br>I mean he's great <br>It's me who is the matter <br>Talking madder <br>Than the maddest hatter <br><br>If I repeat one more word <br>I swear I'll lose my brain <br>Oh, what else should I explain? <br>Oh, yes it's true <br>I can cry on cue <br>But so can you <br><br>I'm breaking down <br>I'm breaking down <br>Down, down <br>You ask me "Is it fun to cry over nothing?" <br>It is, I'm breaking down <br><br>Now let's consider what I might do next <br>I hate admitting I've become perplexed <br>I'm bereaved <br>I've cried, I've shook, I've yelled, I've heaved <br>I have been deceived <br><br>As enemies go <br>Whizzer is not so bad <br>It's just he's so damn happy <br>That it makes me so damn mad <br><br>I want to hate him but I really can't <br>It's like a nightmare how this all proceeds <br>I hope that Whizzer don't fulfill his needs <br>Don't is wrong <br>Sing along <br>What was the noun? <br><br>I'm breaking down <br>I'm breaking down <br>I'll soon redecorate these stalls <br>I want some padding on the wall <br>And also pills <br>I wanna sleep <br>Sure thing'll probably worsen <br>But it's not like I'm some healthy person <br><br>I've rethought my talks with Marv <br>And one fact does emerge <br>I think I like his shrink <br>So that is why I might turn to drink <br>I'm on the brink <br><br>Of breaking down <br>I'm breaking down <br>Down, down <br>I only want to love a man who can love me.... <br>Or like me... <br>Or help me... <br>Help me! <br><br>Marvin was never mine <br>He took his meetings in the boy's latrine <br>I used to cry <br>He'd make a scene <br>I'd rather die <br>Than dry-clean <br>Marvin's wedding gown <br><br>I'm breaking down <br>I'm breaking down <br>It's so upsetting how I found <br>That what's rectangular is round <br>I mean it stinks <br>I mean he's queer <br>And me, I'm just a freak <br>Who needs it maybe every other week <br><br>I've rethought the fun we've had <br>And one fact to emerge: <br>I've played the foolish clown <br>The almost virgin <br>Who sing this dirge <br>Is on the verge <br><br>Of breaking down <br>I'm breaking down <br>Down, down <br>The only thing that's breaking up is my family <br>The only thing that's breaking up is my family <br>But me, I'm breaking down]]></content><category term="Stephanie J. Block" label="Stephanie J. Block"/><category term="I`m Breaking Down" label="I`m Breaking Down"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/This_Had_Better_Come_To_A_Stop/</id><title>Christian Borle - This Had Better Come To A Stop - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:12:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:12:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/This_Had_Better_Come_To_A_Stop/" title="Christian Borle - This Had Better Come To A Stop - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[WHIZZER] <br>Late for dinner, late again <br><br>[WHIZZER AND TRINA] <br>Late for dinner, late again <br><br>[WHIZZER, MARVIN, AND TRINA] <br>Late for dinner, late again <br>Late for dinner, late, late, late, late <br>Late for dinner, late again <br>Late for dinner, late again <br>Late for dinner, late again <br>Late for dinner, late, late, late, late <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Whizzer's supposed to always be here <br>Making dinner, set to screw <br>That's what pretty boys should do <br>Check their hairlines, make the dinner <br>And love me <br><br>This is going nowhere and fast, Whizzer <br>This little thing that we have will not last <br>Don't feel responsible <br>After all, it's through <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>I'm not responsible <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Life can be wonderful <br>Isn't this wonderful? <br>And this had better come to a stop, Whizzer <br>Now, Whizzer <br>Ciao, Whizzer <br>Bend <br>This had better come to an end <br><br>[TRINA] <br>I was supposed to make the dinner <br>Make it pretty on his plate <br>Every wife should pull her weight <br>Have it ready, make it tasty <br>And love him <br><br>This had better come to a stop, doctor <br>This has been a tragic and horrible flop <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Don't feel responsible <br>After all, it's through <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Who is responsible? <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Don't ask me questions! <br>I'm frightened of questions <br>But grateful that it's <br>Come to a stop, Trina <br>Smile, Trina <br>I'll help you mend <br><br>[WHIZZER AND TRINA] <br>I met this man today <br>He wasn't very smart <br>But he was rich, Marvin <br>Which, Marvin <br>Do you prefer I lust for- <br>Brains or money? <br><br>[MARVIN] / [WHIZZER &amp; TRINA] <br>Brains <br>I'm not so rich / Brains or money? <br>But, hell, I'm smart <br>Love me <br><br>[WHIZZER AND TRINA, spoken] <br>No <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Love me, please <br>Or break my heart <br><br>[WHIZZER &amp; TRINA] / [MARVIN] <br>This is all very neat <br>/ This is all very neat <br>This is all very smart / This is all very neat <br>/ This is all very smart <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>This had better come to a stop, Mendel <br>Don't touch me <br>Don't condescend <br>This had better come- <br>This had better come to a- <br>This, this, this, this <br>This had better come to an end <br>This had better come to an end <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Chop chop chop chop chop <br>I chopped it <br>And served his food <br>The asshole forced me <br><br>[WHIZZER, MENDEL, AND JASON] <br>Chop chop chop chop <br>Chop chop chop chop <br><br>[TRINA] <br>And still the bastard divorced me <br><br>[TRINA] / [MARVIN] / [OTHERS] <br>/ / Chop chop chop chop <br>/ / Chop chop chop chop <br>/ Late for dinner, late again / Chop chop chop chop <br>It isn't like he says / Late for dinner, late again / Chop chop chop chop <br>You probably hurt his pride / Late for dinner, late again / Chop chop chop chop <br>He's got to have it all / Late for dinner, late again / Chop chop chop chop <br>He's like a baby who's denied / Late for dinner, late- / Chop chop chop chop <br><br>[WHIZZER, MENDEL, AND JASON] <br>This had better come to a stop, Marvin <br><br>[WHIZZER, TRINA, MENDEL, AND JASON] <br>This has been a lousy but fabulous flop <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Why is it always ourselves who have to change? <br><br>[MARVIN, spoken] <br>This is incredibly boring! <br><br>[WHIZZER, TRINA, MENDEL, AND JASON] <br>You've got a temper that redefines temper <br>And this had better come to a stop, Marvin <br>Why, Marvin <br>Try, Marvin <br>Bend <br><br>This had better come- <br>This had better come to a- <br>This this this this <br>This had better come to an end <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>This had better come to an end <br><br>[ALL] <br>This had better come to an end <br>]]></content><category term="Christian Borle" label="Christian Borle"/><category term="This Had Better Come To A Stop" label="This Had Better Come To A Stop"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anthony_Rosenthal/My_Fathers_A_Homo___Everyone_Tells_Jason_To_See_A_Psychiatrist/</id><title>Anthony Rosenthal - My Father`s A Homo / Everyone Tells Jason To See A Psychiatrist - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:12:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:12:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anthony_Rosenthal/My_Fathers_A_Homo___Everyone_Tells_Jason_To_See_A_Psychiatrist/" title="Anthony Rosenthal - My Father`s A Homo / Everyone Tells Jason To See A Psychiatrist - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[JASON] <br>My father's a homo <br>My mother's not thrilled at all <br>Father homo: <br>What about chromosomes? <br>Do they carry? <br>Will they carry? <br>Who's the homo now? <br>My father said that one day I'll grow to be president <br>And that idea's not so wild <br>I don't live the life of a normal child <br>'Cause I'm too smart for my own good <br>And I'm too good for my sorry little life <br>My mother's no wife <br>And my fathers no man <br>No man at all! <br><br>[TRINA, spoken] <br>Honey, why don't you go out and play? <br><br>[JASON, spoken] <br>No <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Sweetheart I worry <br>Sweetheart I do <br>I worry a lot <br>I worry a lot <br>I worry a lot <br><br>I could take you to the Jewish center? <br><br>[TRINA] <br>I think you like playing chess alone <br>That's not normal <br><br>[JASON] <br>What is normal? <br><br>[TRINA, spoken] <br>I wouldn't know <br><br>Why don't you speak on the telephone <br>With anyone, just get a friend- <br>Anyone <br><br>Darling, please a psychiatrist <br>He's quite a guy <br>And I admire how he acts <br>No one is saying you're a sick neurotic <br>But you could find some help <br>Hear me out, please <br>Yes, you could find some help <br>He could help you realize <br><br>How confused you are! <br>Yes, it's very clear: <br>Daddy's sincere <br>But a schmo! <br>You and I must trust our emotions <br>Make no commotions <br>Will you go? <br><br>[JASON, spoken] <br>No! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Jason, please see a psychiatrist <br>He's just a psychiatrist <br>I'll pay the bill <br>Until <br>You're old <br><br>[MARVIN] / [TRINA] / [JASON] <br>Jason / Darling please listen <br>Please see / To your father here / No <br>A psychiatrist / He's not a genius type Lord knows, but he / I won't go <br>He's just / Knows whats true / I will not go <br>A psychiatrist / He chose a man who I <br>I'll pay the / Think knows the answers <br>Bill / To all your problems / Never never <br>Until / Mendel understands / Never never <br>You're old / What's bothering you / Never <br><br>[JASON, spoken] <br>Forget it <br><br>[ALL] <br>What a mess this is <br>This family! <br>Experts can see <br>This is so! <br><br>Photographs can't <br>Capture our magic <br>We're simply tragic! <br><br>[MARVIN AND TRINA] <br>Will you go? <br><br>[JASON, spoken] <br>No <br><br>[MARVIN AND TRINA] <br>Jason, please see a psychiatrist! <br>He's not- <br><br>[JASON] <br>I won't say boo! <br><br>[MARVIN AND TRINA] <br>-exorbitant <br>And he's very smart! <br><br>[JASON] <br>If intelligence were the only criterion <br>Then I wouldn't really need a psychiatrist, would I? <br><br>[TRINA, spoken] <br>No <br><br>[JASON] <br>Would I? <br><br>[MARVIN, spoken] <br>No <br><br>[JASON] <br>Just because you failed as parents... <br><br>[TRINA] <br>...Get thee to a psychiatrist! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Hey, kid, listen- <br><br>[JASON] <br>I don't need- <br><br>[TRINA AND MARVIN] <br>He needs a psychiatrist! <br><br>[JASON] <br>I want- <br><br>[TRINA AND MARVIN] <br>A psychiatrist! <br><br>[JASON] <br>I wanna speak with Whizzer! <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Speak with whom? <br><br>[JASON] <br>With Whizzer <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>With Whizzer? <br><br>[TRINA] <br>With Whizzer <br><br>[JASON] <br>With Whizzer <br><br>[MARVIN, spoken] <br>Oh my god <br><br>[TRINA, MARVIN, AND JASON] <br>Whizzer! <br>Whizzer! <br>Whizzer! <br>Whizzer! <br><br>[JASON] <br>Whizzer, do you think I should see a psychiatrist? <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>I'm not sure, Jason <br>Jason, maybe so <br>Absolutely, Jason <br><br>[JASON] <br>...OK, I'll go <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>He'll go <br><br>[JASON] <br>I'll go <br><br>[TRINA] <br>He'll go! <br><br>[JASON] <br>If he comes here <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>If he comes here? <br><br>[TRINA] <br>He might come here <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>They don't make house calls <br><br>[WHIZZER, spoken] <br>Oh!]]></content><category term="Anthony Rosenthal" label="Anthony Rosenthal"/><category term="My Father`s A Homo / Everyone Tells Jason To See A Psychiatrist" label="My Father`s A Homo / Everyone Tells Jason To See A Psychiatrist"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anthony_Rosenthal/Marvin_At_The_Psychiatrist_A_Three-Part_Mini-Opera/</id><title>Anthony Rosenthal - Marvin At The Psychiatrist (A Three-Part Mini-Opera) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:12:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:12:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anthony_Rosenthal/Marvin_At_The_Psychiatrist_A_Three-Part_Mini-Opera/" title="Anthony Rosenthal - Marvin At The Psychiatrist (A Three-Part Mini-Opera) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My father says that love <br>Is the most beautiful thing in the world <br>I think games are <br>I think chess is the most <br>Beautiful thing <br>Not love <br><br>Marvin at the Psychiatrist, a three-part mini opera <br>Part One <br><br>Do you love him? <br>Sorta kinda <br>Do you need him? <br><br>Sorta kinda <br>He makes me smile a lot <br>Especially at mealtime <br>It makes me feel I'm sort of smart <br><br>Mm-hmm <br>Is he special? <br><br>He's delightful <br>And romantic? <br><br>Yes, and spiteful <br>And yet it seems that so am I <br><br>Just enjoy what you can <br>Love the boy, not the man <br><br>Man' <br>Sorta stylish <br><br>Kinda very <br>Mmm, very very sorta <br>And kind of hard to describe...? <br>Yes, yes, you know, that's very true <br>When he's naked- <br>Yes? <br>Does he thrill you? <br>Yes! <br>Is he vicious? <br>Yes! <br>Would he kill you? <br><br>(thinks) Yes <br>I think he's sorta kinda mean <br>But I love him, and I need it <br>If he loved me, I'd concede it <br><br>Don't despise what you feel <br>Love the friend, not the heel <br><br>Heel <br>He's sometimes worthless <br>Sometimes evil <br>Sometimes smarmy <br>Part Two <br><br>Explore, Mr. Marvin <br>Your core, Mr. Marvin <br>Note how your wife, your ex-wife’s subtle glories <br>Coupled with her tragic stories <br>Move me in unreported ways <br><br>At our very first session <br>She made quite the impression <br>Do you mind that <br>She was here to speak of Jason <br>And I find that <br>I hope Jason acts out more <br>Cause there’s a few more things we need explored <br><br>Good <br>You said she was withholding - <br>Right <br>Well that’s not quite true <br>No? <br>Perhaps she held back love from you <br>Did she really? <br><br>I just know what I’m told <br>Cause when I met your wife, she was anything but cold <br>It was not precise to say that she was ice <br>When I met your wife, she was very nice <br>Very, very, very <br>Was she faithful? Be objective <br><br>Yes <br>She was faithful <br>Yes <br>And you wanted to… <br>Impress her <br><br>Yes sir, yes sir <br>But impress her I did not <br><br>Did she sweat a lot? <br>What? <br>Was she ruthless? <br>Huh? <br><br>Narcissistic? <br>Let me vary the mood <br><br>Yes, please <br>Does she sleep in the nude? <br>Nope <br><br>No, does not sleep nude <br>Okay, going on <br>I have questions <br>That should probably go unanswered <br>But there're questions <br>Other questions <br>Like, does she wear a neglige <br>Could you blow and it would blow away? <br><br>Since the session’s nearly through <br>Tell me, what is going on with you? <br><br>So, now you’re interested in me? <br>Of course <br>Part Three <br>My son's distressing <br>My father's snide <br>I'm convalescing <br>He's morbid and dissatisfied <br>What should I do now? <br>He loves another <br>I agree <br>I love my mother <br>Why not me? <br>We go to ball games <br><br>The ball is tossed <br>The pitcher's handsome <br>Yeah, and our team lost <br><br>Is that my fault, though? <br>Should I be blamed for that? <br><br>Explore museums <br>Admire art <br>We stand together <br><br>But we stand there looking miles apart <br>How do I reach him? <br>What words of wisdom? <br>What should I do now? <br><br>My father says that love <br>Is the most beautiful thing in the world <br>I think games are <br>I think chess is the most <br>Beautiful thing <br>Not love <br><br>Marvin at the Psychiatrist, a three-part mini opera <br>The End]]></content><category term="Anthony Rosenthal" label="Anthony Rosenthal"/><category term="Marvin At The Psychiatrist (A Three-Part Mini-Opera)" label="Marvin At The Psychiatrist (A Three-Part Mini-Opera)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/The_Thrill_Of_First_Love/</id><title>Christian Borle - The Thrill Of First Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:12:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:12:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/The_Thrill_Of_First_Love/" title="Christian Borle - The Thrill Of First Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[WHIZZER] <br>Hang up all your clothes <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Whizzer begs <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Whizzer knows <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Shave your legs <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Make me sick <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>You're a prick <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>God you're impossible <br>We've been together for nine months <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Ten months <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Nine Months <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Ten Months <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Nine months <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Ten months <br>We are the salt of the bourgeoisie <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>While I put the steak in <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I bring home the bacon <br><br>[BOTH] <br>And we're proud to say we love it how we <br><br>[MARVIN/ WHIZZER] <br>Don't/ Won't <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Don't <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Won't <br><br>[MARVIN AND WHIZZER] <br>Agree <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Everything he owns is vile <br>Marvin doesn't care <br>A whit <br>Marvin doesn't share <br>My devotion to <br>Style <br>Men from France can cancel a debt <br>Men in cufflinks make me forget my name <br>I intend to upset <br>This regrettable game <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Whizzer takes me by the neck <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>What is that, wash and wear? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Whizzer has unlimited knowledge of <br>Dreck <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Send me flowers <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Mention is made <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Make them roses <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Attention is paid <br>In full <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>See how quickly he sours <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>When he pushes, I pull <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Pick up your clothes, Marvin <br>Breeding shows Marvin <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I was rich <br>He was horny <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>We fit like a glove <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Close your eyes, Whizzer <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Passion dies <br>But I'd kill for that thrill of first <br>Love <br><br>[BOTH] <br>We ask for passion at all times <br>We stand for passion and drink this toast <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Still it's awfully trying <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>And we're not denying <br><br>[BOTH] <br>That of all the lesser passions <br>We like fighting most <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Eh... <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Whizzer screws too much to see <br>What a joy's monogamy <br>What a joy is saving his joys <br>For one man <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Leave me <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Love me <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Don't be a fool <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Want me <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Feed me <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>No one's so cruel <br>And cheap <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>What I love I devour <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>What you love you devour <br>What I covet I keep <br><br>Isn't that right, Whizzer? <br>Let's both fight, Whizzer! <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>I was trained in karate <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I'm best when I cheat <br>So I'll cheat, Whizzer, and I'll shove <br>And I'll kill for that thrill of first <br>Love <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>We've been together for nine months- <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Ten months <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Nine months <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>We've been together for ten months <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>What, it's been nine months <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Ten months <br><br>[MARVIN AND WHIZZER] <br>In fact we've almost survived a year <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>True, but <br><br>[BOTH] <br>Who is counting? <br>We're too busy mounting <br>A display of our affection <br>That is so sincere <br><br>(30 measure interlude) <br><br>[BOTH] <br>Passion dies <br>Passion dies <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>I would kill for that thrill of first love <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I would kill for that thrill of first love- <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>I would kill for that thrill of first love- <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I would kill for that thrill <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>I would kill for that thrill of first <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I would kill for that thrill of first <br><br>[BOTH] <br>Love <br>Love <br>Lo-ve!]]></content><category term="Christian Borle" label="Christian Borle"/><category term="The Thrill Of First Love" label="The Thrill Of First Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/A_Tight-Knit_Family___Love_Is_Blind/</id><title>Christian Borle - A Tight-Knit Family / Love Is Blind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:12:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:12:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christian_Borle/A_Tight-Knit_Family___Love_Is_Blind/" title="Christian Borle - A Tight-Knit Family / Love Is Blind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, the situation's this <br>I do not wish to offend <br>I divorced my wife <br>I left my child <br>And I ran off with a friend <br><br>But I want a tight-knit family <br>I want a group that harmonizes <br>I want my wife and kid and friend <br>To pretend <br>Time will mend <br>Our pain <br><br>So it's nineteen seventy-nine <br>So we don't go by the book <br>We all eat as one- <br>Wife, friend, and son- <br>And I sing out as I cook <br><br>I love my tight-knit family <br>I love the way they cook linguine <br>Isn't it great? We're all so swell <br>Such a dear clientele <br><br>I swear we're gonna come through it <br>I fear we'll probably fight <br>But nothing's impossible <br>Live by your wit- <br>Kid, wife, and lover will have to admit <br>I was right <br>I cushioned the fall <br>I want it all <br>I want it all <br>I want it <br><br>Sit down, my dear <br>I hear you have a problem <br>I'm sure you're not disgusting or indiscreet <br>Take a load off your feet <br><br>Thank you <br>Happy or sad? <br>Well, I -- <br><br>That's a question with no answer <br>Let's not discuss the weather, let's face the facts <br>Marvin's wife must relax <br><br>Love isn't sex <br>That's a thing my husband once told me <br>Marvin, my ex- <br>You've seen him for years- <br>Told me over the phone to tell you my fears <br>Do you only treat queers? <br><br>Breathe deep, my dear <br>You'll find me understanding <br>Your pain is a priori <br>Unfold you untold story <br>Now to break bread <br>Loosen your glands <br>Put your head in my hands <br><br>I'm everything he wanted <br>It's time I put it all together <br>The date was set <br>My father let me marry <br>I married. I... <br>Then Marvin came from work <br>Sat me down on the bed <br>He told me how he loved me <br>How needed and/or valued me <br>I have <br><br>What? <br>Syphilis <br>He said <br>Good <br>I have <br>Yes? <br>Syphilis <br>It's true <br>Good <br><br>I had something rotten <br>Which appears though now it's well forgotten <br><br>Maybe, darling, so do you <br>Maybe, darling, so do you <br>I am probably diseased <br>You're a lovely girl <br>And so easily appeased <br>What a lovely girl, though she's probably diseased <br><br>He took pains to not excite us <br>He explains I've <br><br>Hepatitis <br>Too <br>Hepa hepa hepatitis hepatitis hepatitis <br><br>Love is blind <br>Love can tell a million stories <br>Love's unkind <br>Spiteful in a million ways <br><br>Then I stayed home from work <br>Took good care of my men <br>They faked despair, they wet their bed <br>They combed their hair, they acted dead <br>One said <br><br>Yes? <br>Daddy is a prick <br>What? <br>He said <br>Yes? <br>Daddy isn't mine <br>Good <br><br>He filled my coats <br>With candies and notes <br>With "Will you be my valentine?" <br><br>Will you be my valentine? <br>This gets harder to believe <br>You're a damaged girl <br>I've a scalpel up my sleeve <br>What a damaged girl <br>Do not ever slit your wrists <br><br>I've missed him; he's still missing <br>Don't make noise, but daddy's kissing <br>Boys <br><br>Petty, petty, petty, petty <br><br>Love is blind <br>Love can tell a million stories <br>Love's unkind <br>Spiteful in a million ways <br><br>Love is blind <br>Love can tell a million stories <br>Love's unkind <br>Spiteful in a million ways <br><br>Love is crazy <br>Love is often boring <br>Love stinks <br>Love is pretty often debris <br>When you find <br>What you find. Then <br>Never, never, never, never, never <br>Do it over again <br><br>Love reads like a bad biography <br>All the names are changed <br>To protect the innocent Love <br><br>Love is blind <br><br>My name is Mendel <br>I treat her husband <br>I think she's very insecure <br>But so am I <br>I've never married <br>Work, work is my passion <br>Or perhaps that's an alibi <br><br>Yeah, perhaps it is <br>Yeah, I don't care to discuss it <br><br>I think she's charming <br>I think she's needy <br>In just five sessions on my couch <br>She'll be like new <br><br>His name is Mendel <br>Ah-ah <br><br>Return next Friday <br>I admit I admire you]]></content><category term="Christian Borle" label="Christian Borle"/><category term="A Tight-Knit Family / Love Is Blind" label="A Tight-Knit Family / Love Is Blind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Andrew_Rannells/Four_Jews_In_A_Room_Bitching/</id><title>Andrew Rannells - Four Jews In A Room Bitching - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:12:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:12:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Andrew_Rannells/Four_Jews_In_A_Room_Bitching/" title="Andrew Rannells - Four Jews In A Room Bitching - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[FOUR MEN] <br>Four Jews in a room bitching <br>Four Jews in a room plot a crime <br><br>I'm bitching. He's bitching <br>They're bitching. We're bitching <br>Bitch bitch bitch bitch <br>Funny funny funny funny <br>Bitch bitch bitch bitch bitch bitch <br>All the time <br><br>[MENDEL (MARVIN, WHIZZER, JASON)] <br>Whadda they do for love? (Oooo) <br><br>[MENDEL (MARVIN, WHIZZER, JASON)] <br>Whadda they do for love? (Oooo) <br><br>[FOUR MEN] <br>Four Jews in a room <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>Bitching <br><br>[JASON] <br>Bitching <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Bitching <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Bitching <br><br>[FOUR MEN] <br>Four Jews in a room stoop <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>They stoop? <br><br>[FOUR MEN] <br>To pray <br><br>[JASON] <br>I'm Jewish <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I'm Jewish <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>I'm Jewish <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Half Jewish <br><br>[FOUR MEN] <br>Bitch bitch bitch bitch <br>Funny funny funny funny <br>Bitch bitch bitch bitch bitch bitch <br>Night and day <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Slavery, slavery <br><br>[FOUR MEN] <br>We crossed the desert <br>Running for our lives <br>Fleeing from the Pharaoh <br>Who was up to no good <br><br>Now we’re at the Red Sea <br>Pharaoh is behind us <br>Wanting us extincted <br><br>[JASON] <br>What we need’s a miracle! <br><br>[FOUR MEN] <br>And then the Red Sea <br>Split before us <br>No more tsouris <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>We got our miracle <br><br>[JASON] <br>We got our miracle <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>We got our miracle <br><br>[FOUR MEN] <br>Four Jews itching for answers <br>Four Jews bitching their whole life long <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>I'm Whizzer <br><br>[JASON] <br>I'm Jason <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>I'm Mendel <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I'm Marvin <br><br>[FOUR MEN] <br>Bitch bitch bitch bitch <br>Funny funny funny funny <br>Bitch bitch bitch bitch bitch bitch <br>Right or wrong <br><br>[JASON] <br>In case of smoke please call our mothers on the phone <br>And say their sons are all on fire <br><br>[MARVIN AND WHIZZER] <br>We are manipulating people and we need to know <br>Our worst sides aren't ignored <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>The guilt invested will in time pay wisely <br><br>[WHIZZER AND JASON] <br>We do not tippy toe <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>We charge ahead to show <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>We're good in bed <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>Excel in bed <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>We smell in bed <br><br>[JASON] <br>Where is the bed? <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>I love the bed <br><br>[JASON] <br>Who has the bed? <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>I want the bed! <br><br>[JASON] <br>Who stole the bed? <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>Who stole the bed? <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>I lost it twice <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>The bed is mine <br><br>[JASON] <br>The bed is nice <br><br>[FOUR MEN] <br>The bed is <br>Four Jews in a room bitching <br>Four Jews talking like Jew-ish men <br>I'm neurotic, he's neurotic <br>They're neurotic, we're neurotic <br>Bitch bitch bitch bitch <br>Funny funny funny funny <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>I'm nauseous <br><br>[WHIZZER] <br>I'm nauseous <br><br>[JASON] <br>I'm simple <br><br>[MENDEL] <br>I'm Jewish <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Slavery, slavery <br><br>[FOUR MEN] <br>Bitch bitch bitch bitch <br>Funny funny funny funny <br><br>[MARVIN, JASON WHIZZER MENDEL] <br>I'm Jewish I'm neurotic Bitch bitch <br>He's Jewish He's neurotic Bitch bitch <br>They're Jewish they're neurotic Funny funny <br>We're Jewish We're neurotic Funny funny <br>Bitch bitch Four Jews I'm Jewish <br>Bitch bitch In a room bitching He's Jewish <br>Funny funny Bitch bitch They're Jewish <br>Funny funny Bitch bitch We're Jewish <br><br>[FOUR MEN] <br>Four Jews in a room bitching <br><br>[MARVIN] <br>In a room bitching <br><br>[FOUR MEN] <br>Bitch bitch <br>Bitch bitch bitch bitch <br>Now and then <br>Can't lose <br>Loose screws <br>Four <br>One, two, three, four <br><br>[TRINA] <br>Five <br><br>[FOUR MEN] <br>Five Jews]]></content><category term="Andrew Rannells" label="Andrew Rannells"/><category term="Four Jews In A Room Bitching" label="Four Jews In A Room Bitching"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/모야밴드/샤랄라/</id><title>모야밴드 - 샤랄라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:12:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:12:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AA%A8%EC%95%BC%EB%B0%B4%EB%93%9C/%EC%83%A4%EB%9E%84%EB%9D%BC/" title="모야밴드 - 샤랄라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[엄지손가락이 보이지 않게 <br>빠른 타자로 썼다 <br>누구한테 보내는 문자인지 <br>나는 알고 있는 걸 <br>I know I know <br>금방 울리는 휴대폰 진동 <br>네가 저질러 놓은 <br>내 맘의 진동 <br>샤랄라 내 맘은 샤랄라 <br>너와 함께면 <br>언제든지 좋은 날들이 <br>내 맘은 샤랄라 <br>새끼손가락을 내 손에 걸고 <br>소중한 약속을 했다 <br>비밀이라 말하면 안 되지만 <br>우린 알고 있는 걸 <br>I know You know <br>금방 울리는 너의 벨 소리 <br>내가 불러주는 이 노랫소리 <br>샤랄라 내 맘은 샤랄라 <br>너와 함께면 <br>언제든지 좋은 날들이 <br>내 맘은 샤랄라 <br>널 볼 때 내게 떠오르는 하나 <br>다른 표현 없는 이 마음 <br>부르는 한 가지 <br>이렇게 말할 수 있을까 <br>샤랄라 내 맘은 샤랄라 <br>너와 함께면 <br>언제든지 좋은 날들이 <br>내 맘은 샤랄라 <br>샤랄라 내 맘은 샤랄라 <br>우리들의 사랑 이야긴 <br>언제나 샤랄라 <br>]]></content><category term="모야밴드" label="모야밴드"/><category term="샤랄라" label="샤랄라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lang狼Kim/세상을_몰라/</id><title>Lang狼Kim - 세상을 몰라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:13:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:13:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lang%E7%8B%BCKim/%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81%EC%9D%84_%EB%AA%B0%EB%9D%BC/" title="Lang狼Kim - 세상을 몰라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그래 나는 아직 <br>세상을 몰라 <br>정말 아무것도 <br>알 수가 없어 <br>모두가 정해진 <br>그 시간 속으로 <br>가야만 하는게 <br>옳은걸까 <br>누구나 그렇듯 <br>나도 미래를 꿈꿔 <br>그토록 원하던 <br>멋진 자동차를 타고 <br>부족함이 없는 <br>그런 세상속에서 <br>멋지게 사는 <br>나를 그리곤해 <br>조금은 다르다고 <br>그게 틀린거라 <br>생각 하지마 <br>모두가 같은 얼굴 <br>내가 네가 될순 없잖아 <br>그래 나는 세상을 몰라 <br>안다 해도 인정할순 없어 <br>세상과는 조금 다르다 해줘 <br>내가 모두와 같을순 없어 <br>그래 나는 아직 <br>세상을 몰라 <br>정말 아무것도 <br>알 수가 없어 <br>모두가 정해진 <br>그런 시간속에서 <br>살아야 하는게 <br>옳은걸까 <br>조금은 다르다고 <br>그런 눈빛으로 <br>나를 보지마 <br>모두가 같은 얼굴 <br>내가 네가 될 순 없잖아 <br>그래 나는 세상을 몰라 <br>안다 해도 인정할 순 없어 <br>세상과는 조금 다르다 해줘 <br>내가 모두와 같을 순 없어 <br>그래 나는 세상을 몰라 <br>안다 해도 인정할 순 없어 <br>이런채 눈 감는다해도 <br>더 끝까지 가보려해 <br>내길을 가보려해 한걸음 <br>]]></content><category term="Lang狼Kim" label="Lang狼Kim"/><category term="세상을 몰라" label="세상을 몰라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lang狼Kim/미련한_사랑/</id><title>Lang狼Kim - 미련한 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:13:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:13:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lang%E7%8B%BCKim/%EB%AF%B8%EB%A0%A8%ED%95%9C_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="Lang狼Kim - 미련한 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그 어떤 말로도 <br>그대의 발걸음 <br>돌릴수가 없네여 <br>그대의 뒷모습 <br>홀로 바라보는건 <br>익숙하지 않아요 <br>그 무슨 말로도 <br>그대의 마음을 <br>채울 수는 없지만 <br>단한번이라도 <br>돌아봐요 가지마요 <br>사랑해요 <br>입가에 맴돌아 <br>미련한 사랑아 <br>이못난 사람아 <br>놓아줘 가슴아 <br>두볼에 뜨거운 눈물 <br>멀어져만 가는 <br>그대의 모습에 <br>눈을 뗄수 없어요 <br>점점 더 작아져 <br>그대 한점이 되도 <br>움직일수 없어요 <br>단 한번이라도 <br>그대 돌아오길 <br>간절히 바래요 <br>단 한번이라도 <br>돌아봐요 가지마요 <br>사랑해요 <br>혼자서 외친다 <br>그대 그렇게 <br>날 두고 떠나면 <br>남겨진 나는 <br>난 어떡하라고 <br>그대 그렇게 <br>날 버리고 가면 <br>미안하단 말도 오 <br>미련한 사랑아 <br>미련한 사랑아 <br>이못난 사람아 <br>놓아줘 가슴아 <br>두볼에 뜨거운 눈물 <br>미련한 사랑아 <br>놓아줘 가슴아 <br>두볼에 뜨거운 <br>아직도 뜨거운 눈물 <br>]]></content><category term="Lang狼Kim" label="Lang狼Kim"/><category term="미련한 사랑" label="미련한 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/팬시_FANCY/Stupid_In_Love_Prod_By_Nior/</id><title>팬시 (FANCY) - Stupid In Love (Prod. By Nior) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:15:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:15:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8C%AC%EC%8B%9C_FANCY/Stupid_In_Love_Prod_By_Nior/" title="팬시 (FANCY) - Stupid In Love (Prod. By Nior) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Last night <br>I couldn't get out of there <br>It was a grey <br>freezing cold rainy day <br>We fought again <br>The way you treated me <br>really burns me up <br>Yeah I'm crying <br>But I couldn't leave <br>I still stood there <br>Stupid in love Stupid in love <br>When you see me <br>at that time your face eyes <br>I've never seen before <br>When you see me <br>at that time your face eyes <br>I've never seen before <br>Oh luv No hate Oh luv No hate <br>No luv I don't wanna see you again <br>Oh hate I'm still in a lot of pain <br>No luv I don't wanna suffer again <br>Oh hate I'm still in a lot of pain <br>I tried to figure it out for us <br>Why are you hiding in the forest <br>Is it a worth Is it a love <br>I'm worried about this quarrel <br>I think is a total waste of time <br>I know your selfish how can I do <br>this <br>I wanna finish it <br>Stupid in love Stupid in love <br>When you see me <br>at that time your face eyes <br>I've never seen before <br>When you see me <br>at that time your face eyes <br>I've never seen before <br>Oh luv No hate Oh luv No hate <br>No luv I don't wanna see you again <br>Oh hate I'm still in a lot of pain <br>No luv I don't wanna suffer again <br>Oh hate I'm still in a lot of pain <br>You said it yourself <br>Please have a good night baby <br>But that was nightmare <br>Love is all pain <br>I do not won't stand <br>I just want it to end <br>Damn You'll never love me <br>like i can <br>You know I used to be in hell <br>but try to repeat myself <br>you already know <br>Stupid love Crazy love <br>Stupid in love Stupid in love <br>When you see me <br>at that time your face eyes <br>I've never seen before <br>When you see me <br>at that time your face eyes <br>I've never seen before <br>you eyes you lips <br>I've never seen before <br>]]></content><category term="팬시 (FANCY)" label="팬시 (FANCY)"/><category term="Stupid In Love (Prod. By Nior)" label="Stupid In Love (Prod. By Nior)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조관우/겨울이야기_Part2/</id><title>조관우 - 겨울이야기 Part.2 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:15:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:15:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EA%B4%80%EC%9A%B0/%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC%EA%B8%B0_Part2/" title="조관우 - 겨울이야기 Part.2 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[들렸었나요 <br>그 때 그 겨울 노래 <br>두 손 차던 계절에 <br>흰 눈 오던 날 <br>그대 흔적 꺼내며 <br>다시 내게 돌아오라던 <br>하얗게 하얗게 내리면 <br>어느새 흐른 뜨거운 눈물로 <br>부르고 부르면 볼 수 있다고 <br>매 겨울마다 그대를 부르네요 <br>아름답네요 <br>추억속의 그대는 <br>그 미소 참 따뜻하네요 <br>많이 변했겠죠 <br>그대와 나 모두가 <br>하지만 가슴은 아는지 <br>하얗게 하얗게 내리면 <br>어느새 흐른 뜨거운 눈물로 <br>부르고 부르면 볼 수 있다며 <br>기다리는 나 이렇게 <br>이 겨울지나 또 봄이 오면 <br>모두 다 녹아버릴까 <br>얼어붙게 만들었죠 눈물로 <br>하얗게 하얗게 내리면 <br>그리워 그리워 찾겠죠 <br>다시 찾겠죠 <br>눈물로 바꾼 그대와의 기억 <br>부르고 불러도 볼 순 없나요 <br>눈빛 마주칠 한 순간 만이라도 <br>]]></content><category term="조관우" label="조관우"/><category term="겨울이야기 Part.2" label="겨울이야기 Part.2"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/알케이/따뜻한_겨울이야_Feat_무아_종엽_혜주_지현_여령_홍은_민성/</id><title>알케이 - 따뜻한 겨울이야 (Feat. 무아, 종엽, 혜주, 지현, 여령, 홍은, 민성) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:15:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:15:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%8C%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4/%EB%94%B0%EB%9C%BB%ED%95%9C_%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC_Feat_%EB%AC%B4%EC%95%84_%EC%A2%85%EC%97%BD_%ED%98%9C%EC%A3%BC_%EC%A7%80%ED%98%84_%EC%97%AC%EB%A0%B9_%ED%99%8D%EC%9D%80_%EB%AF%BC%EC%84%B1/" title="알케이 - 따뜻한 겨울이야 (Feat. 무아, 종엽, 혜주, 지현, 여령, 홍은, 민성) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 일기예보는 <br>영하까지 떨어진대요 <br>날씨가 추워서 그런지 <br>따뜻함은 어디에 <br>날씨의 따뜻함이 아니라 <br>마음의 따뜻함을 <br>내가 먼저 나눠 줄게요 <br>사람과 사랑이 모여 <br>하나 둘씩 건네는 말이 <br>추운 겨울 마음만은 <br>따뜻하게 해 <br>세상 모든 곳에 행복함이 <br>가득할 때까지 <br>하얀 눈송이와 하나 되어 <br>웃을 때까지 <br>쉽게 눈물짓진 말아요 <br>내 옆으로 와서 푹 쉬세요 <br>내 사람들이 내 사랑들이 <br>행복할 때 까지 <br>아픈 기억들 <br>아픈 기억들 <br>나쁜 생각들 <br>나쁜 생각들 <br>다 떨쳐버리고 <br>행복한 일들과 <br>기쁜 일들만 미소 지으며 <br>생각하도록 <br>행복이라는 말은 <br>마음의 달콤한 이야기 <br>하얗게 내리는 눈처럼 <br>다가와 줄래 <br>사람과 사랑이 모여 <br>하나 둘씩 건네는 말이 <br>추운 겨울 마음만은 <br>따뜻하게 해 <br>세상 모든 곳에 행복함이 <br>가득할 때까지 <br>하얀 눈송이와 하나 되어 <br>웃을 때까지 <br>쉽게 눈물짓진 말아요 <br>내 옆으로 와서 푹 쉬세요 <br>내 사랑들이 행복할 때까지 <br>눈이 소복하게 쌓인 <br>길거리를 봐 <br>커플들도 솔로들도 <br>행복하나 봐 <br>세상이 하얗게 <br>물들어 내 맘도 <br>행복으로 물들었나 봐 <br>너와 함께 했던 <br>행복한 기억도 <br>내리는 눈과 함께 <br>Oh yeah <br>Oh yeah <br>세상 모든 곳에 행복함이 <br>가득할 때까지 <br>하얀 눈송이와 하나 되어 <br>웃을 때까지 <br>쉽게 눈물짓진 말아요 <br>내 옆으로 와서 푹 쉬세요 <br>내 사랑들이 행복할 때 까지 <br>사랑하는 사람과 <br>보고 싶은 사람들 <br>함께하는 게 <br>얼마나 행복 한 건지 <br>남녀노소 우리 모두 <br>웃음꽃 피는 그날은 정말 <br>따뜻한 겨울일 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="알케이" label="알케이"/><category term="따뜻한 겨울이야 (Feat. 무아, 종엽, 혜주, 지현, 여령, 홍은, 민성)" label="따뜻한 겨울이야 (Feat. 무아, 종엽, 혜주, 지현, 여령, 홍은, 민성)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/어쿠스윗/눈이_녹을때쯤/</id><title>어쿠스윗 - 눈이 녹을때쯤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:16:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:16:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%B4%EC%BF%A0%EC%8A%A4%EC%9C%97/%EB%88%88%EC%9D%B4_%EB%85%B9%EC%9D%84%EB%95%8C%EC%AF%A4/" title="어쿠스윗 - 눈이 녹을때쯤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람이 멎는다 <br>겨울이 나린다 <br>소리 없이 천천히 <br>너의 기억이 <br>흩뿌려진다 <br>눈물이 흐른다 <br>너를 비워낸다 난 <br>차가워진 내 마음에 <br>따스했던 니 손이 <br>오늘은 더 그립다 <br>이 눈이 다 녹을 때쯤 <br>봄 이려나 <br>내 눈물 다 마를 때쯤 <br>널 잊으려나 <br>이내 더 쌓여 <br>두발에 밟힌 <br>사랑 이려나 눈처럼 <br>추억이 흩날려 <br>내 가슴에 소복이 <br>온통 내 맘을 <br>하얗게 덮는다 <br>눈이 다 녹을 때쯤 <br>내 눈물 마르려나 <br>시간이 멈춘 듯 <br>바람이 머문다 <br>소리 없는 기억이 <br>너와의 추억이 <br>흩뿌려진다 <br>거리를 거닐다 <br>눈물을 떨군다 또 <br>어제와 다 같은데 <br>우리 추억은 <br>멈춰 서 있다 <br>이 눈이 다 녹을 때쯤 <br>봄 이려나 <br>내 눈물 다 마를 때쯤 <br>널 잊으려나 <br>이내 더 쌓여 <br>두발에 밟힌 <br>사랑 이려나 눈처럼 <br>추억이 흩날려 <br>내 가슴에 소복이 <br>온통 내 맘을 <br>하얗게 덮는다 <br>눈이 다 녹을 때쯤 <br>내 눈물 마르려나 <br>바람이 멎는다 <br>겨울이 나린다 <br>소리 없이 천천히 <br>너의 기억이 흩뿌려진다 <br>]]></content><category term="어쿠스윗" label="어쿠스윗"/><category term="눈이 녹을때쯤" label="눈이 녹을때쯤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나영환/예수를_따라/</id><title>나영환 - 예수를 따라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:16:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:16:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EC%98%81%ED%99%98/%EC%98%88%EC%88%98%EB%A5%BC_%EB%94%B0%EB%9D%BC/" title="나영환 - 예수를 따라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[예수를 따라 예수를 따라 <br>예수를 따라 살아가려네 <br>나를 버리고 더 낮아져서 <br>조건 없이 사랑을 주리 <br>내 삶을 주리 <br>나를 죽이고 남을 살리는 <br>그 길을 걸어가리 빛을 비추리 <br>예수를 따라 예수를 따라 <br>예수를 따라 살아가려네 <br>인술은 다른 게 아닙니다 <br>자기 눈앞에 나타난 <br>불쌍하게 여길 것들을 <br>불쌍하게 여기는 사람이 <br>인술을 할 사람이에요 <br>그건 사람이면 누구나 <br>다 가지고 있는 거예요 <br>다만 하는가 안 하는가 그 차이지 <br>인술을 하는 마음은 <br>다 가지고 있습니다 <br>나를 버리고 더 낮아져서 <br>조건 없이 사랑을 주리 <br>내 삶을 주리 <br>나를 죽이고 남을 살리는 <br>그 길을 걸어가리 빛을 비추리 <br>예수를 따라 예수를 따라 <br>예수를 따라 살아 가려네 <br>그 길을 따라 걸어 가려네 <br>]]></content><category term="나영환" label="나영환"/><category term="예수를 따라" label="예수를 따라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제비_더_블루/뜨는머리/</id><title>제비, 더 블루 - 뜨는머리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:16:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:16:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EB%B9%84_%EB%8D%94_%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8/%EB%9C%A8%EB%8A%94%EB%A8%B8%EB%A6%AC/" title="제비, 더 블루 - 뜨는머리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어릴 때부터 내 머리는 뜨는 머리 <br>누르고 눌러도 안 눌러져 <br>나는 말야 <br>다른 사람들이랑 달라 <br>멋이라곤 도통 부리기 힘든 <br>지랄 같은 머리카락 <br>뜨는 머리 <br>내 머리는 뜨는 머리 <br>Die Hard Die Hard Die Hard Die Hard <br>Old Habits <br>Die Hard Die Hard Die Hard Die Hard <br>Old Habits <br>남들이 웃을 때 내 표정은 억지미소 <br>맞춰야 하는 게 힘들어 <br>요즘에는 제법 익수해진 것 같아 <br>어딜 가든 대충 묻어는 가는듯한 <br>이런 나는 사실 <br>뜨는 머리 <br>내 머리는 뜨는 머리 <br>Die Hard Die Hard Die Hard Die Hard <br>Old Habits <br>Die Hard Die Hard Die Hard Die Hard <br>Old Habits <br>젠장 이곳은 <br>아무리 봐도 <br>나 있을 곳 아냐 Baby <br>I don't belong here <br>I don't belong here <br>but i'm livin' in here <br>뜨는 머리 <br>내 머리는 뜨는 머리 <br>뜨는 머리 <br>내 머리는 뜨는 머리 <br>Die Hard Die Hard Die Hard Die Hard <br>Old Habits <br>Die Hard Die Hard Die Hard Die Hard <br>Old Habits]]></content><category term="제비, 더 블루" label="제비, 더 블루"/><category term="뜨는머리" label="뜨는머리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이샘/미우나_고우나/</id><title>이샘 - 미우나 고우나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:17:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:17:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%98/%EB%AF%B8%EC%9A%B0%EB%82%98_%EA%B3%A0%EC%9A%B0%EB%82%98/" title="이샘 - 미우나 고우나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[옷깃만 스쳐도 인연이라 <br>내 가슴을 애태우더니 <br>어짜피 피고 진 사랑이라면 <br>내 맘을 왜 꺾고 갔나 <br>미우나 고우나 당신 생각뿐인데 <br>떠나간 내 님은 언제쯤 오시려나 <br>아 잊지 못할 남자야 <br>아 그땐 그땐 너무 했지 <br>미우나 고우나 <br>나를 떠나간 그 남자 사랑했더라 <br>옷깃만 스쳐도 인연이라 <br>내 가슴을 애태우더니 <br>어짜피 피고 진 사랑이라면 <br>내 맘을 왜 꺾고 갔나 <br>미우나 고우나 당신 생각뿐인데 <br>떠나간 내 님은 언제쯤 오시려나 <br>아 잊지 못할 남자야 <br>아 그땐 그땐 너무 했지 <br>미우나 고우나 <br>나를 떠나간 그 남자 사랑했더라 <br>미우나 고우나 <br>나를 떠나간 그 남자 사랑했더라 <br>]]></content><category term="이샘" label="이샘"/><category term="미우나 고우나" label="미우나 고우나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/권혁민/당신이_좋아_Solo_Ver/</id><title>권혁민 - 당신이 좋아 (Solo Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:17:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:17:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B6%8C%ED%98%81%EB%AF%BC/%EB%8B%B9%EC%8B%A0%EC%9D%B4_%EC%A2%8B%EC%95%84_Solo_Ver/" title="권혁민 - 당신이 좋아 (Solo Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1.그대는 내 사랑 당신도 내 사랑 <br>이 세상의 그 무엇도 쨉이 안되지 <br><br>원앙이 따로 있나 우리가 원앙이지 <br>환상의 해피한 원앙이지 <br><br>아~ 꿀맛 같은 그대 사랑에~ 내 인생을 걸었잖아~~ <br><br>비가 와도 좋아 눈이 와도 좋아 바람 불어도 좋아 <br>좋아 좋아 당신이 좋아~ <br><br>2.그대는 내 운명 당신도 내 운명 <br>하늘 아래 누가 와도 쨉이 안되지 <br><br>그대는 꽃 중에 꽃~ 당신은 벌 나비~ <br>환상의 해피한 꽃과 나비지 <br><br>아~ 꿀맛 같은 그대 사랑에~ 내 인생을 걸었잖아~~ <br><br>비가 와도 좋아 눈이 와도 좋아 바람 불어도 좋아 <br>좋아 좋아 당신이 좋아~ <br><br>아~ 꿀맛 같은 그대 사랑에~ 내 인생을 걸었잖아~~ <br><br>비가 와도 좋아 눈이 와도 좋아 바람 불어도 좋아 <br>좋아 좋아 당신이 좋아~ <br>좋아 좋아 당신이 좋아~ <br>]]></content><category term="권혁민" label="권혁민"/><category term="당신이 좋아 (Solo Ver.)" label="당신이 좋아 (Solo Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/권혁민/초혼/</id><title>권혁민 - 초혼 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:17:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:17:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B6%8C%ED%98%81%EB%AF%BC/%EC%B4%88%ED%98%BC/" title="권혁민 - 초혼 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 살아서는 갖지 못하는 그런 이름 하나 때문에 <br>그리운 맘 눈물 속에~ 난 띄워 보낼 뿐이죠. <br><br>스치듯 보낼 사람이 어쩌다 내게 들어와 <br>장미의 가시로 남아서 날 아프게 지켜 보내요 <br><br>따라가면 만날 수 있나 멀고 먼 세상 끝까지 <br>그대라면 어디라도 난 그저 행복할 테니.. <br><br>2. 살아서는 갖지 못하는 그런 이름 하나 때문에 <br>그리운 맘 눈물 속에~ 난 띄워 보낼 뿐이죠. <br><br>스치듯 보낼 사람이 어쩌다 내게 들어와 <br>장미의 가시로 남아서 날 아프게 지켜 보내요 <br><br>따라가면 만날 수 있나 멀고 먼 세상 끝까지 <br>그대라면 어디라도 난 그저 행복할 테니.. <br>난 너무 행복할 테니.. <br>]]></content><category term="권혁민" label="권혁민"/><category term="초혼" label="초혼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/권혁민/사는_동안/</id><title>권혁민 - 사는 동안 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:17:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:17:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B6%8C%ED%98%81%EB%AF%BC/%EC%82%AC%EB%8A%94_%EB%8F%99%EC%95%88/" title="권혁민 - 사는 동안 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1.있으면 있는 대로 없으면 없는 대로 <br>내 몫 만큼 살았습니다~ <br><br>바람 불면 흔들리고 비가 오면 젖은채로~ <br>이별 없고 눈물 없는 그런 세상 없겠지만은~ <br><br>그래도 사랑하고 웃으며 살고 싶은 <br>고지식한 내 인생 상도 벌도 주지 마오~~ <br><br><br>2.기쁘면 기쁜 대로 슬프면 슬픈 대로 <br>뿌린 만큼 살으렵니다~ <br><br>가진 만큼 아는 만큼 배운 대로 들은 대로~ <br>가난 없고 그늘 없는 그런 세상 없겠지만은~ <br><br>그래도 사랑하고 웃으며 살고 싶은 <br>고지식한 내 인생 상도 벌도 주지 마오~ <br><br>그래도 사랑하고 웃으며 살고 싶은 <br>고지식한 내 인생 상도 벌도 주지 마오~ <br>]]></content><category term="권혁민" label="권혁민"/><category term="사는 동안" label="사는 동안"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/권혁민/수은등/</id><title>권혁민 - 수은등 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:17:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:17:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B6%8C%ED%98%81%EB%AF%BC/%EC%88%98%EC%9D%80%EB%93%B1/" title="권혁민 - 수은등 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1.어스름 저녁 길에 하나 둘 수은등 꽃이 피면은~ <br>그대와 단 둘이서 거닐던 이 길을 서성입니다~ <br>수은등 은은한 빛 변함 없어도~ <br>당신은 변했구려 보이질 않네 <br>아~~~ 수은등 불빛 아래 이 발길은 떠날 줄 몰라~~ <br><br>2.어두운 밤 거리에 하나 둘 오색불 깜빡거리면~ <br>그대의 웃음소리 들려 올 듯 내 가슴은 설레이네~ <br>바람 부는 이 거리는 변함이 없건만~ <br>당신은 변했구려 보이질 않네 <br>아~~~ 오색 불 깜빡이는 이 거리를 잊으셨구려~~ <br>]]></content><category term="권혁민" label="권혁민"/><category term="수은등" label="수은등"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/권혁민/줄리엣/</id><title>권혁민 - 줄리엣 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:17:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:17:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B6%8C%ED%98%81%EB%AF%BC/%EC%A4%84%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%A3/" title="권혁민 - 줄리엣 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 오오오 줄리엣 오오 줄리엣 운명처럼 다가온 그 사랑 <br>오오오 줄리엣 오오 줄리엣 로미오의 사랑을 받아 주 <br><br>처음 본 순간 느꼈어 넌 내 여자라는 걸 <br>긴 머리 검은 두 눈동자 내 맘을 사로잡았네~ <br><br>영화 속 주인공처럼 널 위해 살고 싶어 <br>죽어도 너와 함께라면 그 무엇도 두렵지 않아 <br><br>아~ 누가 우릴 막아도 아~ 우릴 갈라놓아도 <br>넌 영원한 나의 사랑 헤어질 수 없는 거야~ 워~~ <br><br>오오오 줄리엣 오오 줄리엣 운명처럼 다가온 그 사랑 <br>오오오 줄리엣 오오 줄리엣 로미오의 사랑을 받아 주 <br><br>2. 아~ 누가 우릴 막아도 아~ 우릴 갈라놓아도 <br>넌 영원한 나의 사랑 헤어질 수 없는 거야~ 워~~ <br><br>오오오 줄리엣 오오 줄리엣 운명처럼 다가온 그 사랑 <br>오오오 줄리엣 오오 줄리엣 로미오의 사랑을 받아 주 <br><br>오오오 줄리엣 오오 줄리엣 운명처럼 다가온 그 사랑 <br>오오오 줄리엣 오오 줄리엣 로미오의 사랑을 받아 주 <br>로미오의 사랑을 받아 주 <br>]]></content><category term="권혁민" label="권혁민"/><category term="줄리엣" label="줄리엣"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/권혁민/내_스타일이야/</id><title>권혁민 - 내 스타일이야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:17:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:17:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B6%8C%ED%98%81%EB%AF%BC/%EB%82%B4_%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80%EC%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC/" title="권혁민 - 내 스타일이야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1.첫눈에 반했어~ 너에게 반했어~ <br>너는 너는 너는~ 내 스타일이야~ <br>너는 너는 너는 내 사랑이야 내 스타일이야~ <br>머리에서 발끝까지~ 내 스타일이야~ <br>너는 너는 내 모든 것이야~~ <br><br>속눈썹이 너무 너무 길어 촉촉한 너의 눈 <br>들여다 보면 내 마음이 쏙 빠져~ <br>살랑 살랑 살랑 걸어 올 때마다~ <br>내 마음이 두근 두근거려~~ <br><br>미소도 예쁘고~ 웃을 때 덧니도 예쁘고~ <br>목소리까지 예쁜 내 사랑~ <br>아무리 봐도 내 스타일이야~ <br>내 스타일이 바로 바로 너야~ <br><br>2.첫눈에 반했어~ 너에게 반했어~ <br>너는 너는 너는~ 내 스타일이야~ <br>너는 너는 너는 내 사랑이야 내 스타일이야~ <br>머리에서 발끝까지~ 내 스타일이야~ <br>너는 너는 내 모든 것이야~~ <br><br>속눈썹이 너무 너무 길어 촉촉한 너의 눈 <br>들여다 보면 내 마음이 쏙 빠져~ <br>살랑 살랑 살랑 걸어 올 때마다~ <br>내 마음이 두근 두근거려~~ <br><br>미소도 예쁘고~ 웃을 때 덧니도 예쁘고~ <br>목소리까지 예쁜 내 사랑~ <br>아무리 봐도 내 스타일이야~ <br>내 스타일이 바로 바로 너야~ <br><br>내 스타일이 바로 바로 너야~ <br>]]></content><category term="권혁민" label="권혁민"/><category term="내 스타일이야" label="내 스타일이야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/권혁민/진한_커피/</id><title>권혁민 - 진한 커피 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:17:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:17:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B6%8C%ED%98%81%EB%AF%BC/%EC%A7%84%ED%95%9C_%EC%BB%A4%ED%94%BC/" title="권혁민 - 진한 커피 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1.진한 커피 향 그윽한~ 카페에 앉아~ <br>희미한 불 빛 속에서~ 난 널~ 그려 본다~ <br><br>우리가 앉아 있던 그 자리~ 너의 모습 보이지 않고~ <br>찻 잔 속에 떨어지는~ 너의 얼굴~ <br>시린 가슴 달래어 본다~ <br><br>뜨거웠던 우리 사랑~ 그 날의 추억들이~~ <br>식어 버린 찻 잔 속에~ 그리움으로 녹아 있네~ <br><br>스쳐가는 사람 틈에~ 너의 모습 찾아 본다~ <br>진한 커피 한 잔 속에~ 너의 얼굴 그려 본다 <br><br>2.뜨거웠던 우리 사랑~그 날의 추억들이~~ <br>식어버린 찻 잔 속에~ 그리움으로 녹아 있네~ <br><br>스쳐가는 사람 틈에~ 너의 모습 찾아 본다~ <br>진한 커피 한 잔 속에~ 너의 얼굴 그려 본다 <br><br>진한 커피 한 잔 속에~ 너의 얼굴 그려 본다 <br>너의 얼굴 그려 본다~~ <br>]]></content><category term="권혁민" label="권혁민"/><category term="진한 커피" label="진한 커피"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/권혁민/사랑보다_깊은_상처_Duet_With_초루/</id><title>권혁민 - 사랑보다 깊은 상처 (Duet With 초루) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:17:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:17:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B6%8C%ED%98%81%EB%AF%BC/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EB%B3%B4%EB%8B%A4_%EA%B9%8A%EC%9D%80_%EC%83%81%EC%B2%98_Duet_With_%EC%B4%88%EB%A3%A8/" title="권혁민 - 사랑보다 깊은 상처 (Duet With 초루) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 오랫동안 기다려 왔어 내가 원한 너였기에 <br>슬픔을 감추며 널 보내 줬었지 <br>날 속여 가면서 잡고 싶었는지 몰라 <br><br>너의 눈물 속의 내 모습 아직까지 남아 있어 <br>추억을 버리긴 너무나 아쉬워 <br>난 너를 기억해 이젠 말할게 내 오랜 기다림 <br><br>너 떠나고 너의 미소 볼 수 없지만 <br>항상 기억할게 너의 그 모든 걸 <br>사랑보다 깊은 상처만 준 난 <br>이젠 깨달았어 후회하고 있다는 걸 <br><br>2.이젠 모두 떠나갔지만 나에게 넌 남아 있어 <br>추억에 갇힌 채 넌 울고 있었어 <br>난 이제 너에게 아무런 말도 할 수 없어 <br><br>그런 넌 용서할지 몰라 부족했던 내 모습을 <br>넌 나를 지키며 항상 위로했었지 <br>난 그런 너에게 이젠 이렇게 아픔만 남겼어 <br><br>너 떠나고 너의 미소 볼 수 없지만 <br>항상 기억할게 너의 그 모든 걸 <br>사랑보다 깊은 상처만 준 난 <br>이젠 깨달았어 후회하고 있다는 걸 <br><br>나는 상상했었지 나의 곁에 있는 널 <br>이젠 모든 나의 꿈들을 너에게 줄게~ <br><br>너 떠나고 너의 미소 볼 수 없지만 <br>항상 기억할게 너의 그 모든 걸 <br>사랑보다 깊은 상처만 준 난 <br>이젠 깨달았어 후회하고 있다는 걸 <br>]]></content><category term="권혁민" label="권혁민"/><category term="사랑보다 깊은 상처 (Duet With 초루)" label="사랑보다 깊은 상처 (Duet With 초루)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/권혁민/산다는_건_Cheer_Up/</id><title>권혁민 - 산다는 건 (Cheer Up) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T20:17:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T20:17:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B6%8C%ED%98%81%EB%AF%BC/%EC%82%B0%EB%8B%A4%EB%8A%94_%EA%B1%B4_Cheer_Up/" title="권혁민 - 산다는 건 (Cheer Up) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1.산다는 건 다 그런 거래요~ 힘들고 아픈 날도 많지만~ <br>산다는 건 참 좋은 거래요~ 오늘도 수고 많으셨어요 ~ <br><br>어떻게 지내셨나요 오늘도 한잔 걸치셨나요~ <br>뜻대로 되는 일 없어~ 한숨이 나도 슬퍼 마세요~ <br><br>어느 구름 속에 비가~ 들었는지 누가 알아~ <br>살다 보면 나에게도~ 좋은 날이 온답니다~ <br><br>산다는 건 다 그런 거래요~ 힘들고 아픈 날도 많지만~ <br>산다는 건 참 좋은 거래요~ 오늘도 수고 많으셨어요~ <br><br>2.옆 집이 부러운가요~ 친구가 요즘 잘 나가나요~ <br>남들은 다 좋아 보여~ 속상해져도 슬퍼 마세요~ <br><br>사람 마다 알고 보면~ 말 못할 사연도 많아~ <br>인생이 별거 있나요~ 거기서 거기인 거지~ <br><br>산다는 건 다 그런 거래요~ 힘들고 아픈 날도 많지만~ <br>산다는 건 참 좋은 거래요~ 오늘도 수고 많으셨어요~ <br><br>산다는 건 다 그런 거래요~ 세상일이란 알 수 없지만~ <br>산다는 건 참 멋진 거래요~ 모두가 내일도 힘내세요~ <br><br>오늘도 수고 많으셨어요~ <br>]]></content><category term="권혁민" label="권혁민"/><category term="산다는 건 (Cheer Up)" label="산다는 건 (Cheer Up)"/></entry></feed>