<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:44+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/꽃가람/뭘_하는지/</id><title>꽃가람 - 뭘 하는지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:27:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:27:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%BD%83%EA%B0%80%EB%9E%8C/%EB%AD%98_%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94%EC%A7%80/" title="꽃가람 - 뭘 하는지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[무슨 말을 어떻게 하나 <br>생각해 본다 <br>이런 얘기 이렇게 하며 <br>노래해 본다 <br>생각 없는 생각도 <br>생각하면서 한다 <br>아무 생각 없는 척하며 <br>노래를 한다 <br>언제나 하고 싶은 생각들과 <br>순간의 기억들 <br>언제나 생각한다 이런 생각 <br>무엇을 할까 <br>걱정마 시간은 많아 <br>천천히 생각해라 <br>걱정은 모두 버리고 <br>앞을 바라봐 잘하고 있어 <br>무슨 말을 어떻게 할지 <br>생각을 했다 <br>이런 얘기 이렇게 하며 <br>노래를 한다 <br>생각 없는 척을 하면서 <br>노랠 부른다 <br>노래는 끝이 났지만 <br>절반이 남았다 <br>걱정마 시간은 많아 <br>천천히 생각해라 <br>걱정은 모두 버리고 <br>앞을 바라봐 잘하고 있어 <br>무슨 말을 어떻게 하나 <br>생각해 본다 <br>이런 얘기 이렇게 하며 <br>노래해 본다 <br>생각 없는 생각도 <br>생각하면서 한다 <br>아무 생각 없는 척하며 <br>노래를 한다 <br>]]></content><category term="꽃가람" label="꽃가람"/><category term="뭘 하는지" label="뭘 하는지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김용진/알고있나요/</id><title>김용진 - 알고있나요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:29:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:29:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9A%A9%EC%A7%84/%EC%95%8C%EA%B3%A0%EC%9E%88%EB%82%98%EC%9A%94/" title="김용진 - 알고있나요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 욕심내지 않아요 <br>오늘 그대 곁에 <br>잠시라도 머물 수 있다면 <br>나는 바랄게 없어요 이 기다림도 <br>그저 행복이니까 <br>난 모르는 게 없어요 <br>그대 일이라면 <br>눈을 보면 다 알 수가 있죠 <br>혹시라도 그대에게 짐이 될까봐 <br>오늘도 이렇게 마음을 숨기며 <br>그 사람 때문에 내 가슴 다 헤져도 <br>눈물 때문에 앞을 볼 수가 없대도 <br>빛이 바라지 않는 사랑해 한마디 <br>결국 너의 곁에 닿지 않아도 <br>그대는 알고 있나요 <br>내 삶보다 값진 <br>그댈 바라보다가 내 숨이 다해도 <br>이사랑은 후회하지 않아요 <br>세상 어디 있어도 먼 길이라 해도 <br>어디 있든 찾아낼 수 있죠 <br>어느 샌가 다 커버린 나의 사랑은 <br>아무리 감춰도 숨기지 못해요 <br>그 사람 때문에 내 가슴 다 헤져도 <br>눈물 때문에 앞을 볼 수가 없대도 <br>빛이 바라지 않는 사랑해 한마디 <br>결국 너의 곁에 닿지 않아도 <br>그대는 알고 있나요 <br>내 삶보다 값진 <br>그댈 바라보다가 내 숨이 다해도 <br>이사랑은 후회하지 않아요 <br>나를 잊진 말아요 <br>나를 잊진 말아요 <br>가슴에 꼭 숨겨두고서 널 기다려 <br>끝내 바라지 못한 미안해 한마디 <br>결국 너의 곁에 가지 못해도 <br>널 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="김용진" label="김용진"/><category term="알고있나요" label="알고있나요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ralph_Cieli/Wild_Life_Feat_Aimi/</id><title>Ralph_Cieli - Wild Life (Feat. Aimi) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:31:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:31:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ralph_Cieli/Wild_Life_Feat_Aimi/" title="Ralph_Cieli - Wild Life (Feat. Aimi) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I will be your wild and free and fly away <br>fly away <br>I will be your wild and free <br>and fly away fly away <br>I will be your wild and free and fly away <br>fly away <br>I will be your wild and free and fly away <br>fly away <br>way <br>way <br>way <br>I will be your wild and free and fly away <br>fly away <br>I will be your wild and free and fly away <br>fly away <br>I will be your wild and free and fly away <br>fly away <br>I will be your wild and free and fly away <br>fly away <br>way <br>way <br>awu <br>fly away]]></content><category term="Ralph Cieli" label="Ralph Cieli"/><category term="Wild Life (Feat. Aimi)" label="Wild Life (Feat. Aimi)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/듀엣_코리아/New강/</id><title>듀엣_코리아 - New...강 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:31:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:31:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%93%80%EC%97%A3_%EC%BD%94%EB%A6%AC%EC%95%84/New%EA%B0%95/" title="듀엣_코리아 - New...강 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나의 희망으로 새벽을 내달린다 반드시 만나리라 영광의 그 바다여 뽀얀 안개속을 쉽없이 흘러간다 고단한 사연들은 그렇게 묻어주고 긁히우고 부딪혀도 멉추지 않으리 그곳 <br><br>까지 닿기전엔 돌아서지 않으리라 허허한 마음으로 강물은 흐르는데 갈숲을 지나가는 사르르 바람소리 <br><br><br><br>빨간 하늘아래 파란 땅 사이로 역사를 굽이치며 오늘을 살아간다 푸른 산을 안고 남빛하늘 담아 네게 바치오리 대한국민이여 작열하는 태양아래 더욱 빛나라 지혜롭게 낮추이는 <br><br>위대한 생명이여 너와 내가 간다 지금 이 순간을 창창한 그 바다여 우리 조국이여 창창한 <br><br>그 바다여 대한민국이여]]></content><category term="듀엣 코리아" label="듀엣 코리아"/><category term="New...강" label="New...강"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤지훈/말이야/</id><title>윤지훈 - 말이야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:33:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:33:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A7%80%ED%9B%88/%EB%A7%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC/" title="윤지훈 - 말이야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가슴이 뛰네 계속 웃음이 나네 <br>종일 그대 생각에 <br>자꾸만 전화를 쳐다봐요 <br>그대가 누른 좋아요 그 알림에 <br>나는 하늘을 날죠 <br>자꾸 신경 쓰이고 <br>계속 생각이 나고 <br>사랑인 걸까 왜 자꾸만 맴돌아 <br>그대는 알까 혹시 나와 같을까 <br>오늘은 내 맘 보여줄래 <br>내게는 너밖에 없단 그 말야 <br>내 눈엔 너만 보인단 그 말야 <br>Baby I'm in love <br>너무 예뻐보여 <br>그대 내 맘을 받아줘요 <br>내게는 너밖에 없단 그 말야 <br>내 눈엔 너만 보인단 그 말야 <br>널 사랑해 <br>Oh l'm in love for you <br>우리 사랑 시작해요 둘이서 <br>자꾸 신경 쓰이고 <br>계속 생각이 나고 <br>사랑인 걸까 왜 자꾸만 맴돌아 <br>그대는 알까 혹시 나와 같을까 <br>오늘은 내 맘 보여줄래 <br>내게는 너밖에 없단 그 말야 <br>내 눈엔 너만 보인단 그 말야 <br>Baby I'm in love <br>너무 예뻐보여 <br>그대 내 맘을 받아줘요 <br>내게는 너밖에 없단 그 말야 <br>내 눈엔 너만 보인단 그 말야 <br>널 사랑해 <br>Oh l'm in love for you <br>우리 사랑 시작해요 둘이서 <br>보잘것없던 날이 특별해져 갔죠 <br>그대 와요 내게로 와요 <br>사랑을 시작해요 <br>내 눈엔 너만 보인단 그 말야 <br>Baby I'm in love <br>너무 예뻐보여 <br>그대 내 맘을 받아줘요 <br>내게는 너밖에 없단 그 말야 <br>내 눈엔 너만 보인단 그 말야 <br>널 사랑해 <br>Oh l'm in love for you <br>우리 사랑 시작해요 둘이서 <br>]]></content><category term="윤지훈" label="윤지훈"/><category term="말이야" label="말이야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조형래/부족한_사랑/</id><title>조형래 - 부족한 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:35:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:35:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%ED%98%95%EB%9E%98/%EB%B6%80%EC%A1%B1%ED%95%9C_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="조형래 - 부족한 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[늘 드려도 더 채워주시는 <br>주 사랑엔 끝이 없어서 <br>나의 가진 모든 것 <br>전부를 드려도 <br>언제나 늘 부족합니다 <br>더 드릴 것이 없어서 <br>나의 맘 드립니다 <br>오직 주께서만 <br>받아 주소서 <br>나의 평생의 주를 <br>위한 한 가지 <br>내 생명 오직 <br>주님 사랑뿐 <br>더 가까이 주께로 가까이 <br>채우시는 그 사랑 곁으로 <br>모든 것을 잃어도 <br>주님만 있으면 <br>내 삶은 완전합니다 <br>더 드릴 것이 없어서 <br>나의 맘 드립니다 <br>오직 주께서만 <br>받아 주소서 <br>나의 평생의 주를 <br>위한 한 가지 <br>내 생명 오직 <br>주님 사랑뿐 <br>더 드릴 것이 없어서 <br>나의 맘 드립니다 <br>오직 주께서만 <br>받아 주소서 <br>나의 평생의 주를 <br>위한 한 가지 <br>내 생명 오직 <br>주님 사랑뿐 <br>모든 것 주께 드립니다 <br>]]></content><category term="조형래" label="조형래"/><category term="부족한 사랑" label="부족한 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더필름/하나_Inst/</id><title>더필름 - 하나 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:36:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:36:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%ED%95%84%EB%A6%84/%ED%95%98%EB%82%98_Inst/" title="더필름 - 하나 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나 너에게 <br>원하는 게 있어 <br>오래 전에 <br>지나간 일이지만 <br>함께했던 처음이 <br>믿어지지 않았듯이 <br>이제 마지막 <br>얘기를 하고 싶어 <br>잘 지내렴 <br>내 인연이 아니라면 <br>잘 지내렴 <br>부디 행복하게 살아 <br>혹시라도 한 밤에 <br>아프지는 말아 <br>그리고 나보다 훨씬 더 <br>어울리는 사람 <br>꼭 만나야 해 <br>하나 <br>너에게 부탁할게 있어 <br>내가 행여라도 <br>큰 짐이라면 <br>그래 남은 보잘 것 없는 <br>기억마저 지워 <br>네가 편하게 <br>지낼 수만 있다면 <br>잘 지내렴 <br>내 인연이 아니라면 <br>잘 지내렴 <br>부디 행복하게 살아 <br>혹시라도 한 밤에 <br>아프지는 말아 <br>그리고 나보다 훨씬 더 <br>어울리는 사람 <br>꼭 만나야 해 <br>꼭 잘 지내 행복하게 살아 <br>좋은 사람 곁에서 <br>너도 꼭 웃어줘 <br>이제 짧은 기억이나마 <br>다 지우려고 해 <br>그래도 할 말이 남았다면 <br>떠나지마 <br>이 노랠 듣고 있다면 <br>떠나지마 <br>다시 내게로 돌아와 <br>하나야 난 <br>한 번도 잊은 적이 없어 <br>너도 많이 힘이 들잖아 <br>너도 많이 마음이 아프잖아 <br>돌아와줘 <br>이 노래를 듣고 있다면 <br>이 노래를 네가 듣고 있다면 <br>]]></content><category term="더필름" label="더필름"/><category term="하나 (Inst.)" label="하나 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더필름/이_노래를_네가_듣고_있다면_1st_Demo_하나/</id><title>더필름 - 이 노래를 네가 듣고 있다면 (1st Demo `하나`) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:36:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:36:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%ED%95%84%EB%A6%84/%EC%9D%B4_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98%EB%A5%BC_%EB%84%A4%EA%B0%80_%EB%93%A3%EA%B3%A0_%EC%9E%88%EB%8B%A4%EB%A9%B4_1st_Demo_%ED%95%98%EB%82%98/" title="더필름 - 이 노래를 네가 듣고 있다면 (1st Demo `하나`) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나 너에게 원하는 게 있어 <br>오래 전에 지나간 일이지만 <br>함께했던 처음이 <br>믿어지지 않았듯이 <br>이제 마지막 얘기를 <br>하고 싶어 <br>하나 너에게 바라는 게 있어 <br>오래 전에 스쳐간 나이기에 <br>내가 이런 말을 꺼내기 <br>참 어색하지만 <br>네게 마지막 <br>인사를 하고 싶어 <br>잘 지내렴 <br>내 인연이 아니라면 <br>잘 지내렴 <br>부디 행복하게 살아 <br>혹시라도 한 밤에 <br>아프지는 말아 <br>그리고 나보다 훨씬 더 <br>어울리는 사람 <br>꼭 만나야 해 <br>하나 <br>너에게 부탁할게 있어 <br>내가 행여라도 큰 짐이라면 <br>그래 남은 보잘 것 없는 <br>기억마저 지워 <br>네가 편하게 <br>지낼 수만 있다면 <br>잘 지내렴 <br>내 인연이 아니라면 <br>잘 지내렴 <br>부디 행복하게 살아 <br>혹시라도 한 밤에 <br>아프지는 말아 <br>그리고 나보다 훨씬 더 <br>어울리는 사람 <br>꼭 만나야 해 <br>시간을 돌릴 수 없어 <br>어제로 데려다 <br>줄 자전거도 없지 <br>이제 짧은 기억이나마 <br>다 지우려고 해 <br>그래도 할 말이 남았다면 <br>떠나지마 <br>이 노랠 듣고 있다면 <br>떠나지마 <br>다시 내게로 돌아와 <br>하나야 난 <br>한 번도 잊은 적이 없어 <br>너도 많이 힘이 들잖아 <br>너도 많이 마음이 아프잖아 <br>돌아와줘 <br>이 노래를 듣고 있다면 <br>이 노래를 네가 듣고 있다면 <br>]]></content><category term="더필름" label="더필름"/><category term="이 노래를 네가 듣고 있다면 (1st Demo `하나`)" label="이 노래를 네가 듣고 있다면 (1st Demo `하나`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더필름/하나_Vocal_By_안녕/</id><title>더필름 - 하나 (Vocal By 안녕) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:36:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:36:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%ED%95%84%EB%A6%84/%ED%95%98%EB%82%98_Vocal_By_%EC%95%88%EB%85%95/" title="더필름 - 하나 (Vocal By 안녕) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나 너에게 <br>원하는 게 있어 <br>오래 전에 <br>지나간 일이지만 <br>함께했던 처음이 <br>믿어지지 않았듯이 <br>이제 마지막 <br>얘기를 하고 싶어 <br>잘 지내렴 <br>내 인연이 아니라면 <br>잘 지내렴 <br>부디 행복하게 살아 <br>혹시라도 한 밤에 <br>아프지는 말아 <br>그리고 나보다 훨씬 더 <br>어울리는 사람 <br>꼭 만나야 해 <br>하나 <br>너에게 부탁할게 있어 <br>내가 행여라도 <br>큰 짐이라면 <br>그래 남은 보잘 것 없는 <br>기억마저 지워 <br>네가 편하게 <br>지낼 수만 있다면 <br>잘 지내렴 <br>내 인연이 아니라면 <br>잘 지내렴 <br>부디 행복하게 살아 <br>혹시라도 한 밤에 <br>아프지는 말아 <br>그리고 나보다 훨씬 더 <br>어울리는 사람 <br>꼭 만나야 해 <br>꼭 잘 지내 행복하게 살아 <br>좋은 사람 곁에서 <br>너도 꼭 웃어줘 <br>이제 짧은 기억이나마 <br>다 지우려고 해 <br>그래도 할 말이 남았다면 <br>떠나지마 <br>이 노랠 듣고 있다면 <br>떠나지마 <br>다시 내게로 돌아와 <br>하나야 난 <br>한 번도 잊은 적이 없어 <br>너도 많이 힘이 들잖아 <br>너도 많이 마음이 아프잖아 <br>돌아와줘 <br>이 노래를 듣고 있다면 <br>이 노래를 네가 듣고 있다면 <br>]]></content><category term="더필름" label="더필름"/><category term="하나 (Vocal By 안녕)" label="하나 (Vocal By 안녕)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/미스김/60대_미스김/</id><title>미스김 - 60대 미스김 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:36:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:36:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AF%B8%EC%8A%A4%EA%B9%80/60%EB%8C%80_%EB%AF%B8%EC%8A%A4%EA%B9%80/" title="미스김 - 60대 미스김 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[할머니라고 부르지 마라 <br>나는야 60대 미스김 <br>짧은 치마에 화장을 하고 <br>오늘도 길을 나선다 <br>할머니라고 부르지 마라 <br>나는야 60대 미스김 <br>아직은 남은 인생 창창하단다 <br>나는야 아가씨란다 <br>이제는 희생하라 강요치마라 <br>여지껏 할 만큼 했다 <br>나도 이젠 살아가련다 <br>나만의 나의 인생을 <br>나만의 나의 인생을 <br>애 봐달라고 찾지 좀 마라 <br>나는야 60대 미스김 <br>짧은 치마에 화장을 하고 <br>오늘도 길을 나선다 <br>밥 차리라고 찾지 좀 마라 <br>나는야 60대 미스김 <br>아직도 남은 인생 창창하단다 <br>나는야 아가씨란다 <br>이제는 희생하라 강요치마라 <br>여지껏 할 만큼 했다 <br>나도 이젠 살아가련다 <br>나만의 나의 인생을 <br>이제는 희생하라 강요치마라 <br>여지껏 할 만큼 했다 <br>나도 이젠 살아가련다 <br>나만의 나의 인생을 <br>나만의 나의 인생을 <br>나만의 나의 인생을 <br>]]></content><category term="미스김" label="미스김"/><category term="60대 미스김" label="60대 미스김"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Say_Something_Loving/</id><title>The_XX - Say Something Loving - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:36:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:36:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Say_Something_Loving/" title="The_XX - Say Something Loving - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Before it slips away <br><br>Say something loving <br>I just don't remember the thrill of affection <br>I just don't remember <br>Say something loving <br>I need a reminder, the feeling's escaped me <br><br>I went looking for it <br>Could have been anyone's kiss <br>Throwing my arms at no one <br>When I gave up, I found love <br><br>The thought flows through my mind <br>And it's growing all the time <br>I do myself a disservice <br>To feel this weak, to be this nervous <br><br>You say something loving <br>It's so overwhelming, the thrill of affection <br>Feels so unfamiliar <br>You say something loving <br>Without hesitation it hits me, hits me <br>It feels so unfamiliar <br><br>Before it slips away <br><br>Your touch stays on my skin <br>I feel it start sinking in <br>Here come my insecurities <br>I almost expect you to leave <br><br>Were you really looking for me? <br>Try your best to reassure me <br>I wasn't patient to meet you <br>Am I too needy, am I too eager? <br><br>I don't know, I don't know, I don't know <br>I don't know what this is, but it doesn't feel wrong <br>I don't know, I don't know, I don't know <br>I don't know what this is, but it doesn't feel wrong <br><br>Did you hear me say it? <br>Say it <br>Did you hear me say? <br><br>I say something loving <br>I can't hold it inside, the thrill of affection <br>Is only getting stronger <br>I say something loving <br>All my hesitations are fading, fading <br>I feel it taking over <br><br>Before it slips away <br>Don't let it slip away <br>Before it slips away <br>Don't let it slip awa]]></content><category term="The XX" label="The XX"/><category term="Say Something Loving" label="Say Something Loving"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이고_Ego/Overdrink_Feat_NAKED/</id><title>이고_Ego - Overdrink (Feat. NAKED) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:36:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:36:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EA%B3%A0_Ego/Overdrink_Feat_NAKED/" title="이고_Ego - Overdrink (Feat. NAKED) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What's the matter <br>니가 흘러내려 보여 <br>too expensive <br>파란 잔에 핀 입술도 <br>잔을 따뤄 둔채 <br>I wanna talkin' about you <br>늘어지게 더 취해 <br>여기 한잔만 더 채워줄래 <br>뻔한 대화 oh no no <br>또 오겠지만 hangover <br>Right now <br>모두 흘러내린 faces <br>Don't worry <br>오늘 밤은 like pay day <br>Oh yeah i'm feel <br>so good tonight <br>trippin' i'm down <br>and down and down <br>so trippin' drink flexin' <br>so trippin' drink flexin' <br>so trippin' drink flexin' <br>so trippin' drink flexin' <br>So overdrink <br>So overdrink <br>So overdrink <br>just drink it up pour up <br>pour up <br>하늘위로 떨어지게 밀어줘 <br>Just like parachute <br>이 밤을 환하게 <br>우린 더 비춰줘 <br>So kissin on cup <br>흘러내리는 body <br>We gonna speak body language <br>on the water <br>밤새 잔을 채우고 <br>계속 더 들이부어 <br>철없게들 굴어 <br>아무도 안보듯이 <br>흘러내린 채 더 drink <br>기분은 떠 구름 위 swim <br>I'm drunken now feeling <br>so high <br>더 무너져 내려 <br>we're down <br>Oh yeah i'm feel <br>so good tonight <br>trippin' i'm down <br>and down and down <br>so trippin' drink flexin' <br>so trippin' drink flexin' <br>so trippin' drink flexin' <br>so trippin' drink flexin' <br>so overdrink <br>so overdrink <br>so overdrink <br>just drink it up pour up <br>pour up <br>다 비슷하게 보여 <br>beat up down <br>there woo wait up boi <br>down and down <br>더 취해 다른 날 묻기에 <br>wait up call me boi <br>다 내겐 빛나 보여 <br>다 내겐 빛나 보여 <br>A young firefly <br>넌 자꾸 내게 <br>다른걸 묻고 원해 girl <br>i slay when im ballin <br>i slay when im ballin 계속해 <br>i wanna talk about you <br>i wanna talk about <br>how you turned out <br>조금만 더 네게 <br>focus on <br>조금만 더 내게 <br>focus on <br>right now 취해 <br>머릴 비운 채로 <br>조금씩 더 내게 focus on <br>]]></content><category term="이고 (Ego)" label="이고 (Ego)"/><category term="Overdrink (Feat. NAKED)" label="Overdrink (Feat. NAKED)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루아민/Bystander_방관자/</id><title>루아민 - Bystander (방관자) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:36:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:36:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%EC%95%84%EB%AF%BC/Bystander_%EB%B0%A9%EA%B4%80%EC%9E%90/" title="루아민 - Bystander (방관자) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쿵 쾅 <br>머리를 울리는 <br>지겨운 소리 <br>좁고 좁은 공간 <br>사이엔 없네 예의 <br>사실 그보다 더 먼저인 <br>두려움과 매정함만 <br>선뜻 나서지 <br>못하는 모습은 <br>언제부터였을까 <br>모른척 입 다물고 <br>숨 쉬는 것이 <br>내가 살아갈 길 <br>괜히 정의롭다싶게 <br>나선다면 <br>그거야 말로 저승길 <br>변해버린 세상과 <br>굳혀진 현실보다 <br>더 무서워진건 <br>암묵적으로 동의하는 <br>내 표정 <br>가만히 못 들을 척 <br>이대로 이불을 덮고 <br>오늘이 지나면 내일이 <br>아무렇지 않게 될거야 <br>얘야 괜히 나서다가 <br>큰일 당하지마라 <br>오늘따라 괜히 더 <br>어머니의 말씀이 <br>씁쓸해지네 <br>모른척 입 다물고 <br>숨 쉬는 것이 <br>내가 살아갈 길 <br>괜히 정의롭다싶게 <br>나선다면 <br>그거야 말로 저승길 <br>변해버린 세상과 <br>굳혀진 현실보다 <br>더 무서워진건 <br>암묵적으로 동의하는 <br>내 표정 <br>가만히 못 들을 척 <br>이대로 이불을 덮고 <br>오늘이 지나면 내일이 <br>아무렇지 않게 될거야 <br>얘야 괜히 나서다가 <br>큰일 당하지마라 <br>오늘따라 괜히 더 <br>어머니의 말씀이 <br>씁쓸해지네 <br>가만히 못 들을 척 <br>이대로 이불을 덮고 <br>오늘이 지나면 내일이 <br>아무렇지 않게 될거야 <br>얘야 괜히 나서다가 <br>큰일 당하지마라 <br>오늘따라 괜히 더 <br>어머니의 말씀이 <br>씁쓸해지네 <br>]]></content><category term="루아민" label="루아민"/><category term="Bystander (방관자)" label="Bystander (방관자)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루아민/Tic_Toc/</id><title>루아민 - Tic Toc - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:36:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:36:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%EC%95%84%EB%AF%BC/Tic_Toc/" title="루아민 - Tic Toc - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무 말도 하고 <br>싶지가 않아 <br>너도 알고 있잖아 <br>쏟아지듯 뱉어낸 <br>그 말들을 <br>다 듣고 있는 나를 <br>언제까지 이럴 거냐는 <br>니 말에 <br>난 더는 할 말이 없어 <br>그저 멍하니 너의 <br>얼굴을 바라보기만 <br>먼저 일어날게 <br>조심히 들어가 <br>지금 너에게 해줄 수 <br>있는 건 이게 전부야 <br>이제 그만할래 <br>더는 할 말이 없어 <br>그만 멈출래 <br>더 이상은 흐르지 않도록 <br>그만할래 어색한 <br>이 공간에 <br>시계바늘 소리만 <br>가득 차네 <br>I don't wanna fall <br>in love again <br>모든 게 다 어지럽기만 <br>할 뿐인 나인데 <br>아무렇지 않은 것처럼 <br>이 공간에서 난 널 보네 <br>평소와 다른 <br>어떤 하루에 <br>니가 사라져서 <br>난 낯선데도 <br>여전히 난 지금이 <br>더 나은 것 같애 <br>조금씩 다 잊혀질 쯤엔 <br>시간이 흘러가 <br>그 모든 게 <br>제자리로 제자리로 <br>돌아가네 <br>이제 그만할래 <br>더는 할 말이 없어 <br>그만 멈출래 <br>더 이상은 흐르지 않도록 <br>그만 할래 어색한 <br>이 공간에 <br>시계바늘 소리만 <br>가득 차네 <br>I don't wanna fall <br>in love again <br>I don't wanna fall <br>in love again <br>I don't wanna fall <br>in love again <br>don't wanna fall <br>in love <br>이제 그만할래 <br>더는 할 말이 없어 <br>그만 멈출래 <br>더 이상은 흐르지 않도록 <br>그만 할래 어색한 <br>이 공간에 <br>시계바늘 소리만 <br>가득 차네 <br>]]></content><category term="루아민" label="루아민"/><category term="Tic Toc" label="Tic Toc"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/애월/Rain_Feat_Lua/</id><title>애월 - Rain (Feat, Lua) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:36:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:36:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%A0%EC%9B%94/Rain_Feat_Lua/" title="애월 - Rain (Feat, Lua) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이렇게 날이 저무는 가봐 <br>노을 빛 하늘에 물들다 <br>조금씩 색을 잃어 가잖아 <br>나는 이 사랑 멈출 수 없는데 <br>못 다한 사랑 붉게 나누는 <br>서녘 하늘이 말해주잖아 <br>너무도 사랑해 당장에 이별은 <br>감당하지 못할 일이라는 걸 <br>흘러 네 모습이 <br>흘러 비가 되어 <br>흘러 가슴에 내리면 <br>아팠던 날에 시간들 보다 <br>서로 사랑했던 날들만 남아 <br>흘러 기억들이 <br>흘러 바람 되어 <br>흘러 나의 가슴속에 <br>이별의 긴 밤을 지나면 <br>그 끝엔 사랑이 있을까요 <br>좋은 계절도 다 가는 가봐 <br>주홍빛 거리로 물들다 <br>조금씩 색을 잃어 가잖아 <br>나는 이사랑 멈출 수 없는데 <br>흘러 네 모습이 <br>흘러 비가 되어 <br>흘러 가슴에 내리면 <br>아팠던 날에 시간들 보다 <br>서로 사랑했던 날들만 남아 <br>흘러 기억들이 <br>흘러 바람 되어 <br>흘러 나의 가슴속에 <br>이별의 긴 밤을 지나면 <br>그 끝엔 사랑이 있을까요 <br>모르는 척 사랑 할래요 <br>잊혀지는 시간도 사랑이니깐 <br>너를 사랑했던 <br>순간 잊지 못해 <br>자꾸 생각이 나도 <br>지나온 이별의 시간들 <br>그 끝엔 사랑이 있겠죠 <br>]]></content><category term="애월" label="애월"/><category term="Rain (Feat, Lua)" label="Rain (Feat, Lua)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/브로콜리너마저/잊어버리고_싶어요_Radio_Edit/</id><title>브로콜리너마저 - 잊어버리고 싶어요 (Radio Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:37:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:37:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A1%9C%EC%BD%9C%EB%A6%AC%EB%84%88%EB%A7%88%EC%A0%80/%EC%9E%8A%EC%96%B4%EB%B2%84%EB%A6%AC%EA%B3%A0_%EC%8B%B6%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94_Radio_Edit/" title="브로콜리너마저 - 잊어버리고 싶어요 (Radio Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잊혀지지 않았으면 <br>하는 것들이 <br>바보 같은 일상에 <br>밀려가는 날 <br>마음속에 뽑히지 않는 <br>가시 같은 말에 <br>아끼는 스웨터의 <br>올이 나가 버린 날 <br>무릎에 앉은 딱지를 <br>자꾸 긁게 되는 밤 <br>손댈수록 뿌옇게 되는 <br>수채화 속 하늘 <br>할 수 있는 일보다 <br>언제나 앞선 마음에 <br>슬퍼하는 일은 언제나 <br>뒤늦은 나의 몫 <br>좋았었던 일들부터 <br>먼저 잊어주세요 <br>차라리 그러면 견디는 <br>일이 조금은 쉬울까 <br>행복했던 기억 하나로만 <br>버텨왔던 날은 <br>쉽게도 무너지네요 <br>잊어버리고 싶어요 <br>그 좋았었던 날들이 <br>왜 지금 나를 자꾸만 <br>무너지게 하나요 <br>지워버리고 싶어요 <br>그 좋았었던 사람이 <br>왜 지금 나를 자꾸만 <br>힘이 들게 하나요 <br>좋았었던 일들부터 <br>먼저 잊어주세요 <br>차라리 그러면 견디는 <br>일이 조금은 쉬울까 <br>행복했던 기억 하나로만 <br>버텨왔던 날은 <br>쉽게도 무너지네요 <br>잊어버리고 싶어요 <br>그 좋았었던 날들이 <br>왜 지금 나를 자꾸만 <br>무너지게 하나요 <br>지워버리고 싶어요 <br>그 좋았었던 사람이 <br>왜 지금 나를 자꾸만 <br>힘이 들게 하나요 <br>잊어버리고 싶어요 <br>]]></content><category term="브로콜리너마저" label="브로콜리너마저"/><category term="잊어버리고 싶어요 (Radio Edit)" label="잊어버리고 싶어요 (Radio Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/브로콜리너마저/잊어버리고_싶어요_Inst/</id><title>브로콜리너마저 - 잊어버리고 싶어요 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:37:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:37:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A1%9C%EC%BD%9C%EB%A6%AC%EB%84%88%EB%A7%88%EC%A0%80/%EC%9E%8A%EC%96%B4%EB%B2%84%EB%A6%AC%EA%B3%A0_%EC%8B%B6%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94_Inst/" title="브로콜리너마저 - 잊어버리고 싶어요 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잊혀지지 않았으면 <br>하는 것들이 <br>바보 같은 일상에 <br>밀려가는 날 <br>마음속에 뽑히지 않는 <br>가시 같은 말에 <br>아끼는 스웨터의 <br>올이 나가 버린 날 <br>무릎에 앉은 딱지를 <br>자꾸 긁게 되는 밤 <br>손댈수록 뿌옇게 되는 <br>수채화 속 하늘 <br>할 수 있는 일보다 <br>언제나 앞선 마음에 <br>슬퍼하는 일은 언제나 <br>뒤늦은 나의 몫 <br>좋았었던 일들부터 <br>먼저 잊어주세요 <br>차라리 그러면 견디는 <br>일이 조금은 쉬울까 <br>행복했던 기억 하나로만 <br>버텨왔던 날은 <br>쉽게도 무너지네요 <br>잊어버리고 싶어요 <br>그 좋았었던 날들이 <br>왜 지금 나를 자꾸만 <br>무너지게 하나요 <br>지워버리고 싶어요 <br>그 좋았었던 사람이 <br>왜 지금 나를 자꾸만 <br>힘이 들게 하나요 <br>좋았었던 일들부터 <br>먼저 잊어주세요 <br>차라리 그러면 견디는 <br>일이 조금은 쉬울까 <br>행복했던 기억 하나로만 <br>버텨왔던 날은 <br>쉽게도 무너지네요 <br>잊어버리고 싶어요 <br>그 좋았었던 날들이 <br>왜 지금 나를 자꾸만 <br>무너지게 하나요 <br>지워버리고 싶어요 <br>그 좋았었던 사람이 <br>왜 지금 나를 자꾸만 <br>힘이 들게 하나요 <br>잊어버리고 싶어요 <br>]]></content><category term="브로콜리너마저" label="브로콜리너마저"/><category term="잊어버리고 싶어요 (Inst.)" label="잊어버리고 싶어요 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/브로콜리너마저/잊어버리고_싶어요/</id><title>브로콜리너마저 - 잊어버리고 싶어요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:37:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:37:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A1%9C%EC%BD%9C%EB%A6%AC%EB%84%88%EB%A7%88%EC%A0%80/%EC%9E%8A%EC%96%B4%EB%B2%84%EB%A6%AC%EA%B3%A0_%EC%8B%B6%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="브로콜리너마저 - 잊어버리고 싶어요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잊혀지지 않았으면 <br>하는 것들이 <br>바보 같은 일상에 <br>밀려가는 날 <br>마음속에 뽑히지 않는 <br>가시 같은 말에 <br>아끼는 스웨터의 <br>올이 나가 버린 날 <br>무릎에 앉은 딱지를 <br>자꾸 긁게 되는 밤 <br>손댈수록 뿌옇게 되는 <br>수채화 속 하늘 <br>할 수 있는 일보다 <br>언제나 앞선 마음에 <br>슬퍼하는 일은 언제나 <br>뒤늦은 나의 몫 <br>좋았었던 일들부터 <br>먼저 잊어주세요 <br>차라리 그러면 견디는 <br>일이 조금은 쉬울까 <br>행복했던 기억 하나로만 <br>버텨왔던 날은 <br>쉽게도 무너지네요 <br>잊어버리고 싶어요 <br>그 좋았었던 날들이 <br>왜 지금 나를 자꾸만 <br>무너지게 하나요 <br>지워버리고 싶어요 <br>그 좋았었던 사람이 <br>왜 지금 나를 자꾸만 <br>힘이 들게 하나요 <br>좋았었던 일들부터 <br>먼저 잊어주세요 <br>차라리 그러면 견디는 <br>일이 조금은 쉬울까 <br>행복했던 기억 하나로만 <br>버텨왔던 날은 <br>쉽게도 무너지네요 <br>잊어버리고 싶어요 <br>그 좋았었던 날들이 <br>왜 지금 나를 자꾸만 <br>무너지게 하나요 <br>지워버리고 싶어요 <br>그 좋았었던 사람이 <br>왜 지금 나를 자꾸만 <br>힘이 들게 하나요 <br>잊어버리고 싶어요 <br>]]></content><category term="브로콜리너마저" label="브로콜리너마저"/><category term="잊어버리고 싶어요" label="잊어버리고 싶어요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/심인섭/널_지켜줄거야/</id><title>심인섭 - 널 지켜줄거야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:37:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:37:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%AC%EC%9D%B8%EC%84%AD/%EB%84%90_%EC%A7%80%EC%BC%9C%EC%A4%84%EA%B1%B0%EC%95%BC/" title="심인섭 - 널 지켜줄거야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그댈 만난 순간부터 <br>나의 마지막 <br>사랑이길 바랬지 <br>그 후로 많은 <br>시간들을 보내며 <br>함께할 날을 원했어 <br>이제야 하나 되는 거야 <br>그토록 바래왔던 순간을 <br>영원히 함께해 <br>앞으로의 날들 <br>이제 시작인 거야 우리 <br>그댈 사랑합니다 <br>내 전부인 사람 <br>힘이 들고 지칠 때 <br>네 손 잡아줄 거야 <br>너무 소중한 <br>하나뿐인 단 한 사람 <br>널 지켜줄 거야 <br>영원히 <br>천천히 그려보는 거야 <br>우리의 행복할 시간들을 <br>새롭게 시작해 <br>먼 훗날의 미래까지 <br>함께인 거야 우리 <br>하나뿐인 내 사랑 <br>약속 하나 할게 <br>험한 거친 세상 속 <br>널 놓진 않을 거야 <br>너를 위해서 <br>내 모든 걸 다 걸어서 <br>널 지켜줄 거야 <br>그댈 사랑합니다 <br>내 전부인 사람 <br>힘이 들고 지칠 때 <br>네 손 잡아줄거야 <br>너무 소중한 <br>하나뿐인 단 한 사람 <br>널 지켜줄 거야 <br>영원히 <br>]]></content><category term="심인섭" label="심인섭"/><category term="널 지켜줄거야" label="널 지켜줄거야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신기원/슬로우다운_Slow_Down/</id><title>신기원 - 슬로우다운 (Slow Down) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:38:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:38:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EA%B8%B0%EC%9B%90/%EC%8A%AC%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B0%EB%8B%A4%EC%9A%B4_Slow_Down/" title="신기원 - 슬로우다운 (Slow Down) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니가 없어 난 항상 울었어 <br>보고 싶어 널 찾아 다녔어 <br>내 맘속에 너의 모습도 <br>흐릿해 졌어 지워 지나봐 <br>울었어 또 울었어 <br>미칠 것만 같아서 <br>꿈을 꾸고 있었으면 좋겠어 <br>다시 내게 돌아와 <br>Slow Down Slow Down <br>이별의 준비 안됐어 <br>나에겐 시간이 필요한데 <br>난 아직 니가 그대로인데 <br>Slow Down Slow Down <br>나에겐 니가 필요해 <br>사랑이라고 말해줘 <br>니가 없어 난 항상 울었어 <br>보고 싶어 널 찾아 다녔어 <br>내 맘속에 너의 모습도 <br>흐릿해 졌어 지워 지나봐 <br>울었어 또 울었어 <br>미칠 것만 같아서 <br>꿈을 꾸고 있었으면 좋겠어 <br>다시 내게 돌아와 <br>Slow Down Slow Down <br>이별의 준비 안됐어 <br>나에겐 시간이 필요한데 <br>난 아직 니가 그대로인데 <br>Slow Down Slow Down <br>나에겐 니가 필요해 <br>사랑이라고 말해줘 <br>울었어 또 울었어 <br>미칠 것만 같아서 <br>꿈을 꾸고 있었으면 좋겠어 <br>다시 내게 돌아와 <br>Slow Down Slow Down <br>이별의 준비 안됐어 <br>나에겐 시간이 필요한데 <br>난 아직 니가 그대로인데 <br>Slow Down Slow Down <br>나에겐 니가 필요해 <br>사랑이라고 말해줘 <br>]]></content><category term="신기원" label="신기원"/><category term="슬로우다운 (Slow Down)" label="슬로우다운 (Slow Down)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/장희영/다시는_사랑할_수_없을_것_같아_Inst/</id><title>장희영 - 다시는 사랑할 수 없을 것 같아 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:38:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:38:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%ED%9D%AC%EC%98%81/%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C%EB%8A%94_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%A0_%EC%88%98_%EC%97%86%EC%9D%84_%EA%B2%83_%EA%B0%99%EC%95%84_Inst/" title="장희영 - 다시는 사랑할 수 없을 것 같아 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생각하지도 말자 <br>불러도 절대 안돼 <br>다짐해도 이렇게 <br>무너지네요 <br>달라질게 없는 걸 <br>나는 알고 있는데 <br>돌아갈 수 없어 <br>머리는 알고 있지만 <br>마음이 외면 하나 봐 <br>지치지도 않아 <br>너와 시작해 내 하루는 <br>다시는 사랑할 수 <br>없을 것 같아 <br>아프고 아파 그때 <br>그 시간 속 살고 있는데 <br>두 번은 없을 사랑이기에 <br>자꾸만 뒤를 돌아보게 돼요 <br>잠도 오지 않는데 <br>내게 가혹한 이 밤 <br>지독한 그리움 <br>머리는 알고 있지만 <br>마음이 외면 하나 봐 <br>지치지도 않아 <br>너와 시작해 내 하루는 <br>다시는 사랑할 수 <br>없을 것 같아 <br>아프고 아파 그때 <br>그 시간 속 살고 있는데 <br>두 번은 없을 사랑이기에 <br>자꾸만 뒤를 돌아보게 돼요 <br>참 후회가 되는걸요 <br>지난 시간들 <br>그대와 나 생각이 나서 <br>다시는 사랑할 수 <br>없을 것 같아 <br>아프고 아파 그때 <br>그 시간 속 살고 있는데 <br>두 번은 없을 사랑이기에 <br>자꾸만 뒤를 돌아보게 돼요 <br>다시는 사랑은 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="장희영" label="장희영"/><category term="다시는 사랑할 수 없을 것 같아 (Inst.)" label="다시는 사랑할 수 없을 것 같아 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/장희영/다시는_사랑할_수_없을_것_같아/</id><title>장희영 - 다시는 사랑할 수 없을 것 같아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:38:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:38:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%ED%9D%AC%EC%98%81/%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C%EB%8A%94_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%A0_%EC%88%98_%EC%97%86%EC%9D%84_%EA%B2%83_%EA%B0%99%EC%95%84/" title="장희영 - 다시는 사랑할 수 없을 것 같아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생각하지도 말자 <br>불러도 절대 안돼 <br>다짐해도 이렇게 <br>무너지네요 <br>달라질게 없는 걸 <br>나는 알고 있는데 <br>돌아갈 수 없어 <br>머리는 알고 있지만 <br>마음이 외면 하나 봐 <br>지치지도 않아 <br>너와 시작해 내 하루는 <br>다시는 사랑할 수 <br>없을 것 같아 <br>아프고 아파 그때 <br>그 시간 속 살고 있는데 <br>두 번은 없을 사랑이기에 <br>자꾸만 뒤를 돌아보게 돼요 <br>잠도 오지 않는데 <br>내게 가혹한 이 밤 <br>지독한 그리움 <br>머리는 알고 있지만 <br>마음이 외면 하나 봐 <br>지치지도 않아 <br>너와 시작해 내 하루는 <br>다시는 사랑할 수 <br>없을 것 같아 <br>아프고 아파 그때 <br>그 시간 속 살고 있는데 <br>두 번은 없을 사랑이기에 <br>자꾸만 뒤를 돌아보게 돼요 <br>참 후회가 되는걸요 <br>지난 시간들 <br>그대와 나 생각이 나서 <br>다시는 사랑할 수 <br>없을 것 같아 <br>아프고 아파 그때 <br>그 시간 속 살고 있는데 <br>두 번은 없을 사랑이기에 <br>자꾸만 뒤를 돌아보게 돼요 <br>다시는 사랑은 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="장희영" label="장희영"/><category term="다시는 사랑할 수 없을 것 같아" label="다시는 사랑할 수 없을 것 같아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HongHye/6월에서_5월까지/</id><title>HongHye - 6월에서 5월까지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:38:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:38:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HongHye/6%EC%9B%94%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C_5%EC%9B%94%EA%B9%8C%EC%A7%80/" title="HongHye - 6월에서 5월까지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[6월에 무더운 여름날 <br>우리는 처음 만났죠 <br>그대는 너무 <br>아름다웠고 빛이 났죠 <br>하나뿐인 매력적인 눈웃음 <br>누구도 손대지 <br>못할 순수함 <br>천사가 있다면 <br>울엄마라고 말할 수 있어 <br>어린시절 잡아주던 <br>다정했던 엄마의 손 <br>햇살 좋은 날 손잡고 <br>자주가던 푸른바다 산책길 <br>난 항상 엄마를 <br>보며 행복했어 <br>난 항상 엄마가 <br>행복하길 바랬지 <br>엄마가 슬피 울때면 <br>내맘도 슬퍼 <br>매일을 행복하기만 바랬어 <br>포근하게 안아주던 <br>하나뿐인 엄마의 품 <br>안겨있을때 들리던 <br>쿵쾅대는 편안한 심장소리 <br>따뜻한 눈으로 <br>나를 바라보며 <br>따뜻한 웃음을 <br>항상 지어주던 <br>엄마의 웃는 <br>모습을 바라보면서 <br>나도 같이 웃곤했지 <br>내곁에서 멀어지던 <br>그 뒷모습 <br>괜찮다며 눈물 흘리던 <br>엄마의 슬픈얼굴 <br>마지막 이별이 <br>될 줄 모르고 <br>말썽만 피우며 <br>힘들게 했던 지난날들 <br>하나씩 머릿속을 스쳐가 <br>내게 남은 후회들만 <br>5월의 마지막이던 <br>그날 많은 눈물을 흘렸죠 <br>그대는 웃는게 <br>가장 예뻐요 울지 말아요 <br>하나뿐인 매력적인 눈웃음 <br>누구도 손대지 <br>못할 순수함 <br>천사가 있다면 <br>울엄마라고 말할 수 있어 <br>]]></content><category term="HongHye" label="HongHye"/><category term="6월에서 5월까지" label="6월에서 5월까지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Project_SH/환경오염_절대_안돼_From_오늘도_조별과제/</id><title>Project_SH - 환경오염 절대 안돼 (From `오늘도 조별과제`) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:39:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:39:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Project_SH/%ED%99%98%EA%B2%BD%EC%98%A4%EC%97%BC_%EC%A0%88%EB%8C%80_%EC%95%88%EB%8F%BC_From_%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98%EB%8F%84_%EC%A1%B0%EB%B3%84%EA%B3%BC%EC%A0%9C/" title="Project_SH - 환경오염 절대 안돼 (From `오늘도 조별과제`) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 심각해요 환경오염 <br>미세먼지와 지구온난화 <br>앗 뜨거워 <br>빙하가 녹아 <br>세상이 잠기면 <br>네 친구랑 나중에 <br>누굴 구할래 <br>지구가 아프면 <br>내 맘도 아픈걸 <br>지금도 전세계 <br>도시인구 80% 이상이 <br>대기오염속에 살고 있어 <br>환경오염 절대 안돼 <br>환경오염 절대 안돼 <br>벌금으로 패가망신 <br>온난화 예방으로 <br>세상은 시원하게 <br>너와 나는 뜨겁게 <br>너와 나는 뜨겁게 <br>]]></content><category term="Project SH" label="Project SH"/><category term="환경오염 절대 안돼 (From `오늘도 조별과제`)" label="환경오염 절대 안돼 (From `오늘도 조별과제`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Project_SH/우리는_유튜버_From_우리는_유튜버/</id><title>Project_SH - 우리는 유튜버 (From `우리는 유튜버`) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:39:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:39:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Project_SH/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_%EC%9C%A0%ED%8A%9C%EB%B2%84_From_%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_%EC%9C%A0%ED%8A%9C%EB%B2%84/" title="Project_SH - 우리는 유튜버 (From `우리는 유튜버`) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어제도 밤새고 <br>오늘도 밤새고 <br>내일도 똑같이 <br>이렇게 밤새겠지 <br>이번 영상도 <br>잘 넘어갔지만 <br>다음엔 또 뭘 <br>찍어야 하나 <br>방이 더러워도 <br>찍을 땐 있어보이게 <br>피부관리도 빠질 수 없지 <br>아 흰머리가 <br>매일 남몰래 고생하는 <br>우린 유튜버 <br>음악 촬영 편집 <br>일손이 부족할 땐 <br>전부 혼자 해야돼 <br>이번에 올린 건 <br>좀 부끄러워도 <br>또 댓글 보려고 <br>새로고침 <br>밤새 알바해도 <br>촬영 땐 멀쩡해야 돼 <br>사실 조금 더 <br>고생하는 우린 <br>그래도 어쩔 수 없지 <br>왜냐면 우리는 <br>]]></content><category term="Project SH" label="Project SH"/><category term="우리는 유튜버 (From `우리는 유튜버`)" label="우리는 유튜버 (From `우리는 유튜버`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Project_SH/중계중_From_중계중/</id><title>Project_SH - 중계중 (From `중계중`) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:39:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:39:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Project_SH/%EC%A4%91%EA%B3%84%EC%A4%91_From_%EC%A4%91%EA%B3%84%EC%A4%91/" title="Project_SH - 중계중 (From `중계중`) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자 후반전 <br>지금 막 시작되었습니다 <br>수비수 왼쪽 측면으로 <br>길게 연결합니다 <br>수비수 두명 제치고 <br>먼 거리에서 슈팅 <br>굴하지 않고 <br>달려갑니다 <br>자 슛 <br>자 경기를 뒤집을 <br>마지막 기회 <br>떨리는 순간입니다 <br>네 수비수 상대 편으로 <br>공을 날리면서 <br>나이스 패스 <br>오늘 기가 막히는데요 <br>미드필더 수비 뚫고 <br>달리면서 패스 <br>자 드디어 공격수 <br>골대로 돌격 <br>이제 마지막 순간 <br>골키퍼와 일대일 상황 <br>빠르게 달려가 <br>골대를 향해 <br>강하게 슛 골 <br>]]></content><category term="Project SH" label="Project SH"/><category term="중계중 (From `중계중`)" label="중계중 (From `중계중`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정민아/떡국/</id><title>정민아 - 떡국 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:39:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:39:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EB%AF%BC%EC%95%84/%EB%96%A1%EA%B5%AD/" title="정민아 - 떡국 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[떡국 한 그릇 먹었네 <br>나이도 먹었네 <br>엄마한테 욕도 먹었네 <br>내 귀도 먹었네 <br>티비에선 높은 분들이 <br>많이도 해먹었네 <br>공부해도 매일 일해도 <br>나는 물먹었네 <br>올해도 새해다짐은 <br>금연 저축 다이어트 연애 <br>내년에도 새해다짐은 <br>금연 저축 다이어트 연애 <br>연애 연애 연애 <br>떡국 한 그릇 늘었네 <br>나이도 늘었네 <br>세상살이도 늘었네 <br>인생은 늘어가네 <br>아까운 이 내 청춘 <br>무정한 세월아 <br>굴하지 않고 오늘도 난 <br>떡국을 먹는다 <br>나이를 먹는다 <br>]]></content><category term="정민아" label="정민아"/><category term="떡국" label="떡국"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신기현/당신만이/</id><title>신기현 - 당신만이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:40:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:40:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EA%B8%B0%ED%98%84/%EB%8B%B9%EC%8B%A0%EB%A7%8C%EC%9D%B4/" title="신기현 - 당신만이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[부끄러워하지 않기 <br>나를 위해 흘리신 보혈 <br>당당하게 말하기 <br>죽기까지 날 사랑한 당신 <br>겁쟁이처럼 숨지 않겠네 <br>이제 내 눈을 들어 <br>주님만 바라네 <br>당신만이 내 삶의 노래 <br>당신만이 나의 이야기 <br>당신만이 완전한 사랑 <br>이 시간 고백합니다 <br>당신만이 나의 모든 것 <br>당신만이 내 유일한 고백 <br>오직 주님만이 <br>겁쟁이처럼 숨지 않겠네 <br>이제 내 눈을 들어 <br>주님만 바라네 <br>당신만이 내 삶의 노래 <br>당신만이 나의 이야기 <br>당신만이 완전한 사랑 <br>이 시간 고백합니다 <br>당신만이 나의 모든 것 <br>당신만이 내 유일한 고백 <br>오직 주님만이 <br>그대만 바라보기에 <br>그대만 의지하기에 <br>또다시 넘어지지만 <br>다시 일어날 수가 있죠 <br>나의 모든 것 되신 <br>그분 인해 <br>주님만이 내 삶의 노래 <br>주님만이 나의 이야기 <br>주님만이 완전한 사랑 <br>이 시간 고백합니다 <br>주님만이 나의 모든 것 <br>주님만이 내 유일한 고백 <br>오직 주님만이 <br>]]></content><category term="신기현" label="신기현"/><category term="당신만이" label="당신만이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김명식/새_아침이_올_꺼야/</id><title>김명식 - 새 아침이 올 꺼야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:40:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:40:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%AA%85%EC%8B%9D/%EC%83%88_%EC%95%84%EC%B9%A8%EC%9D%B4_%EC%98%AC_%EA%BA%BC%EC%95%BC/" title="김명식 - 새 아침이 올 꺼야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새 아침이 올 꺼야 <br>어둔 밤 지나면 <br>작은 촛불 모여 소망의 꽃 피워 <br>찬란한 태양 될 테니 <br>새 아침의 하늘로 <br>작은 새 날개짓하고 <br>들판의 꽃들도 사방에 피어나 <br>노래하는 세상 될 테니 <br>깊은 밤 지나서 <br>아침이 오면 <br>어둠은 사라져 <br>어둠에 가려진 <br>아름다운 세상 <br>곧 보게 될 거야 <br>새 아침의 나라 <br>봄이 오듯이 펼쳐질 거야 <br>가슴 속 흐르던 눈물 <br>봄눈 녹듯이 사라질 거야 <br>새 아침의 나라 <br>소망의 날개 달고 날아오르리 <br>두려움 모두 이기고 <br>꿈에 그리던 저 하늘로 <br>깊은 밤 지나서 아침이 오면 <br>아픔은 사라져 <br>부둥켜 울었던 착한 사람들 <br>다 춤추게 되리 <br>새 아침의 나라 <br>봄이 오듯이 펼쳐질 거야 <br>가슴 속 흐르던 눈물 <br>봄눈 녹듯이 사라질 거야 <br>새 아침의 나라 <br>소망의 날개 달고 날아오르리 <br>두려움 모두 이기고 <br>꿈에 그리던 저 하늘로 <br>아무도 간 적 없었고 <br>누구도 본 적 없었지 <br>하지만 우리 손 모아 <br>기도하는 <br>새 아침의 나라 <br>새 아침의 나라 <br>봄이 오듯이 펼쳐질 거야 <br>가슴 속 흐르던 눈물 <br>봄눈 녹듯이 사라질 거야 <br>새 아침의 나라 <br>소망의 날개 달고 날아오르리 <br>두려움 모두 이기고 <br>꿈에 그리던 저 하늘로 <br>새 아침이 올 꺼야 <br>]]></content><category term="김명식" label="김명식"/><category term="새 아침이 올 꺼야" label="새 아침이 올 꺼야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/타임브릿지/하얀고백_Vocal_손효규/</id><title>타임브릿지 - 하얀고백 (Vocal 손효규) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:40:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:40:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%80%EC%9E%84%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80/%ED%95%98%EC%96%80%EA%B3%A0%EB%B0%B1_Vocal_%EC%86%90%ED%9A%A8%EA%B7%9C/" title="타임브릿지 - 하얀고백 (Vocal 손효규) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[저기 저 멀리 보이는 그대 <br>너무나 눈이 부셔 <br>점점 그대가 내게 <br>꿈처럼 다가와 <br>수줍게 웃는 그대 <br>아무 말도 필요 없잖아 <br>눈빛만 봐도 알 수 있어 <br>난 이미 너 아님 안 되는걸 <br>약속할게 언제나 <br>너의 편이 될게 <br>영원히 그댈 사랑할게 <br>아무리 힘들고 지쳐도 <br>그 오랜 시간이 지나도 <br>평생 그대 손 놓지 않을게 <br>우리 함께 걸어갈 이 길이 <br>너무나 설레는걸 <br>그대 심장소리가 <br>내게도 느껴져 <br>떨리는 그대 두 손 <br>아무 말도 필요 없잖아 <br>눈빛만 봐도 알 수 있어 <br>난 이미 너 아님 안 되는걸 <br>약속할게 언제나 <br>너의 편이 될게 <br>영원히 그댈 사랑할게 <br>아무리 힘들고 지쳐도 <br>그 오랜 시간이 지나도 <br>평생 그대 손 놓지 않을게 <br>그대 정말 고마워 <br>아무것도 없는 <br>지금의 나를 <br>믿고 사랑해줘서 <br>고백할게 <br>이렇게 너의 <br>두 손을 잡은 지금 <br>이 순간만을 기다렸다고 <br>처음 그댈 본 순간에도 <br>난 항상 같은 맘였다고 <br>평생 그대만을 사랑할게 <br>평생 그댈 웃게 해줄게 <br>]]></content><category term="타임브릿지" label="타임브릿지"/><category term="하얀고백 (Vocal 손효규)" label="하얀고백 (Vocal 손효규)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/타임브릿지/아닌걸_알면서도/</id><title>타임브릿지 - 아닌걸 알면서도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:40:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:40:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%80%EC%9E%84%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80/%EC%95%84%EB%8B%8C%EA%B1%B8_%EC%95%8C%EB%A9%B4%EC%84%9C%EB%8F%84/" title="타임브릿지 - 아닌걸 알면서도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[두 눈을 감고 <br>내 귀를 막고 <br>널 보지 않으려 해도 <br>널 듣지 않으려 해도 <br>어느새 난 또 <br>온통 너로 가득 차 <br>다시 또 아파와 <br>이미 닳아 버린 맘인데 <br>꽃들이 필 때면 <br>네 맘도 열릴까 <br>흰 눈이 내리면 <br>네가 내게 올까 <br>아닌걸 알면서도 <br>왜 난 또 널 그렇게 찾는지 <br>아플 걸 알면서도 <br>널 보며 왜 난 웃고 있는지 <br>아닌걸 알면서도 <br>왜 난 또 널 향해 가는건지 <br>아플 걸 알면서도 <br>놓을 수가 없잖아 <br>결국 난 너인가봐 <br>왜 난 멈추지 못하는지 <br>꽃잎이 질때면 <br>내 맘도 닫힐까 <br>흰 눈이 녹으면 <br>내 맘도 사라질까 <br>아닌걸 알면서도 <br>왜 난 또 널 그렇게 찾는지 <br>아플 걸 알면서도 <br>널 보며 왜 난 웃고 있는지 <br>아닌걸 알면서도 <br>왜 난 또 널 향해 가는건지 <br>아플 걸 알면서도 <br>놓을 수가 없잖아 <br>결국 난 너인가봐 <br>왜 난 멈추지 못하는지 <br>사랑은 왜 내게만 온 건지 <br>얼마나 더 기다려야 <br>네가 내게 올까 <br>넌 아마 모를 거야 <br>가슴 속 깊이 감춰둔 내 맘 <br>혹시 멀어질까봐 <br>전하지도 못하는 나인데 <br>어떤 날엔 화가나 <br>또 어떤 날엔 너무 그리워 <br>단 한번만이라도 <br>내게 와줄 순 없니 <br>결국 난 너인가봐 <br>널 사랑하고 나 아플래 <br>]]></content><category term="타임브릿지" label="타임브릿지"/><category term="아닌걸 알면서도" label="아닌걸 알면서도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/타임브릿지/여전하구나_Vocal_오윤혜/</id><title>타임브릿지 - 여전하구나 (Vocal 오윤혜) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:40:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:40:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%80%EC%9E%84%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80/%EC%97%AC%EC%A0%84%ED%95%98%EA%B5%AC%EB%82%98_Vocal_%EC%98%A4%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C/" title="타임브릿지 - 여전하구나 (Vocal 오윤혜) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잘 지냈냐는 너의 그 말에 <br>숨겨온 추억이 스쳐가 <br>편하게 웃으며 보고 싶던 너인데 <br>웃으려 할수록 <br>가슴이 자꾸 메어와 <br>무슨 말부터 해야 좋을지 <br>묻고 싶은 게 참 많은데 <br>차마 하지 못해 그때의 나처럼 <br>그저 그렇게 널 바라보고만 있어 <br>여전하구나 <br>참 지독히도 사랑했던 넌 <br>아이 같은 그 미소도 <br>여리고 슬픈 그 두 눈도 <br>여전하구나 <br>너란 꿈을 꿨던 내 맘이 <br>이렇게 아프단 것도 <br>이젠 꿈 꿀 수도 없는 너라서 <br>너로 빛나던 나의 시간들이 <br>거짓말처럼 사라질까 <br>차마 잊지 못해 그때의 나처럼 <br>그저 그렇게 널 바라보고만 있어 <br>여전하구나 <br>참 지독히도 사랑했던 넌 <br>아이 같은 그 미소도 <br>여리고 슬픈 그 두 눈도 <br>여전하구나 <br>다시는 널 볼 수 없어도 <br>내 안에 가득한 너라 <br>한 걸음도 뗄 수 없는 나라서 <br>그 흔한 이별이 <br>이토록 너에겐 어려운지 <br>애쓰는 내 맘이 더 미워 <br>보내지 말걸 <br>운명이라는 그 변명 속에 <br>이토록 죽을 만큼 <br>사랑해본 적 없다고 <br>여전하구나 <br>널 비우고 또 비워도 <br>내 안에 가득한 너라 <br>아무도 모르게 <br>난 널 <br>]]></content><category term="타임브릿지" label="타임브릿지"/><category term="여전하구나 (Vocal 오윤혜)" label="여전하구나 (Vocal 오윤혜)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/타임브릿지/멈춘시계_Vocal_주보라/</id><title>타임브릿지 - 멈춘시계 (Vocal 주보라) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:40:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:40:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%80%EC%9E%84%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80/%EB%A9%88%EC%B6%98%EC%8B%9C%EA%B3%84_Vocal_%EC%A3%BC%EB%B3%B4%EB%9D%BC/" title="타임브릿지 - 멈춘시계 (Vocal 주보라) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비겁한 변명이라도 <br>할 걸 그랬나봐 <br>지독히도 깊은 내 맘은 <br>저물지를 않아 <br>너라는 빛을 잃고 <br>비틀거리는 나 <br>아득한 시간에 갇혀 <br>한 걸음도 뗄 수 없어 <br>그 누구도 그 무엇도 <br>너 없이는 아무 의미 없잖아 <br>네가 있던 그 계절에 <br>네가 있던 그 공간에 <br>모든 것이 멈춘 채 <br>점점 더 또렷해져가 <br>고장난 내 마음은 <br>멈춘 시곗바늘처럼 <br>제 자리에 서있어 <br>널 잃게 된 그날부터 <br>초라한 내 눈물이 가슴에 번져도 <br>수북히 쌓인 널 뒤로 한 채 <br>한 걸음도 뗄 수 없어 <br>그 누구도 그 무엇도 <br>너 없이는 아무 의미 없잖아 <br>네가 있던 그 계절에 <br>네가 있던 그 공간에 <br>모든 것이 멈춘 채 <br>점점 더 또렷해져가 <br>고장난 내 마음은 <br>멈춘 시곗바늘처럼 <br>제자리에 서있어 <br>널 잃게 된 그날부터 <br>갇힌 바람처럼 <br>더는 갈 곳이 없잖아 <br>엉켜진 추억을 다 버리고 <br>떠날 자신이 없어 <br>아직 남은 너의 향기 <br>깊게 새긴 너의 흔적 <br>모든 것이 다 선명해 <br>도저히 지울 수 없어 <br>네가 떠난 이 자리에 <br>하염없이 기다릴게 <br>언제라도 올 수 있게 <br>어서 내 손을 잡아줘 <br>넌 내게 숨이었잖아 <br>제발 돌아와 줘 <br>너만이 깨울 수 있어 <br>내 멈춰진 시간 <br>]]></content><category term="타임브릿지" label="타임브릿지"/><category term="멈춘시계 (Vocal 주보라)" label="멈춘시계 (Vocal 주보라)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/타임브릿지/이별감기_Vocal_폴림/</id><title>타임브릿지 - 이별감기 (Vocal 폴림) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:40:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:40:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%80%EC%9E%84%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84%EA%B0%90%EA%B8%B0_Vocal_%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%BC/" title="타임브릿지 - 이별감기 (Vocal 폴림) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[참 낫질 않아 <br>그대라는 열병은 <br>한동안 괜찮다가도 <br>다시 또 아픔이 되어 찾아와 <br>또 눈물이 나고 <br>또 가슴이 아파 <br>내 맘 속 빈틈없이 사랑한 너잖아 <br>사랑이 사랑인줄 모르고 <br>이별이 이별인줄 몰랐던 <br>조금은 위태롭고 불안했던 날들 <br>그때의 우리 <br>널 더 이해했더라면 <br>너라는 따뜻한 온길 잃고 <br>맘이 무너질 듯 아파 <br>하룰 울어도 이틀을 앓아도 <br>나을 것 같지 않아 <br>날 밀어내던 차가운 네 손 끝에 <br>몸이 부서질 듯 아파 <br>며칠 아파도 아무리 앓아도 <br>끝날 것 같질 않아 <br>사랑이 사랑인줄 모르고 <br>이별이 이별인줄 몰랐던 <br>조금은 위태롭고 불안했던 날들 <br>그때의 우리 <br>널 더 이해했더라면 <br>너라는 따뜻한 온길 잃고 <br>맘이 무너질 듯 아파 <br>하룰 울어도 이틀을 앓아도 <br>나을 것 같질 않아 <br>날 밀어내던 차가운 네 손 끝에 <br>몸이 부서질 듯 아파 <br>며칠 아파도 아무리 앓아도 <br>끝날 것 같지 않아 <br>나에겐 너였고 <br>너에겐 내가 전부였던 <br>그날이 다시 올 것만 같아 <br>내 전부였던 너란 사람을 잃고 <br>죽을 만큼 너무 아파 <br>끝이 없나 봐 <br>난 아직도 네가 다시 올 것만 같아 <br>날 안아주던 따스한 네 온기가 <br>아직 내 가슴에 남아 <br>며칠 앓아도 아무리 아파도 <br>끝날 것 같지 않아 <br>]]></content><category term="타임브릿지" label="타임브릿지"/><category term="이별감기 (Vocal 폴림)" label="이별감기 (Vocal 폴림)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/타임브릿지/헤매이다_Vocal_채하/</id><title>타임브릿지 - 헤매이다 (Vocal 채하) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:40:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:40:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%80%EC%9E%84%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80/%ED%97%A4%EB%A7%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%A4_Vocal_%EC%B1%84%ED%95%98/" title="타임브릿지 - 헤매이다 (Vocal 채하) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[심장이 멎는 줄 알았어 <br>갑작스러운 너의 연락에 <br>잘 지냈냐는 그 말 한마디에 <br>다 무너지잖아 난 또 아프잖아 <br>아무 말 없이 너의 손을 <br>잡고 걷던 길모퉁이에서 <br>너와 나눴던 그 속삭임들 <br>다시 떠오르잖아 <br>지워지지가 않아 <br>우리 같이 걸었던 <br>시간을 혼자서 헤매다가 <br>그 꿈의 끝에서 주저앉아 울었어 <br>이제 오지 않을 널 <br>다 알면서도 계속 난 기다리잖아 <br>혹시 네가 올 까봐 <br>서랍 속 깊숙이 넣어둔 <br>너와의 사진과 손 편지들 <br>겨우 가둬두었던 그 흔적들 <br>다시 떠오르잖아 <br>지워지지가 않아 <br>우리 같이 걸었던 <br>시간을 혼자서 헤매다가 <br>그 꿈의 끝에서 주저앉아 울었어 <br>이제 오지 않을 널 <br>다 알면서도 계속 난 <br>기다리잖아 혹시 네가 올 까봐 <br>닫혀버린 저 문을 열면 <br>예전처럼 네가 닿을 것만 같아 <br>네가 너무 보고 싶어 <br>서투른 내 마음에 <br>널 아프게 했던 그 시간이 <br>온 세상이 그대였던 <br>그날들이 차올라 <br>아무리 비워내도 <br>하염없이 쌓이는 너라서 <br>두 눈을 감아도 아무리 비워도 <br>난 널 <br>]]></content><category term="타임브릿지" label="타임브릿지"/><category term="헤매이다 (Vocal 채하)" label="헤매이다 (Vocal 채하)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/타임브릿지/기억의_숲_Vocal_미키드/</id><title>타임브릿지 - 기억의 숲 (Vocal 미키드) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:40:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:40:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%80%EC%9E%84%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80/%EA%B8%B0%EC%96%B5%EC%9D%98_%EC%88%B2_Vocal_%EB%AF%B8%ED%82%A4%EB%93%9C/" title="타임브릿지 - 기억의 숲 (Vocal 미키드) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뒤엉켜진 생각 속을 <br>하염없이 걷다 <br>수없이 썼다 구겼던 <br>내 맘 한 켠에 적힌 <br>마음속에 맺혀있던 <br>그대를 꺼내죠 <br>아픈 기억조차 <br>무뎌지나 봐 <br>아직도 내 손 끝에 남은 <br>그대의 온기가 <br>바람결에 흩어질까 <br>난 두려워 <br>눈을 감으면 그대가 <br>내게 불어와 <br>그대라는 향기가 <br>내 맘의 창을 열고서 <br>하늘빛 담은 그대가 <br>내게 불어와 <br>그대라는 사람을 온전히 <br>느낄 수 있어 <br>끝없이 그대라는 바람이 <br>내게 분다 <br>그대 <br>아물지 않는 기억의 숲에 <br>그대가 서있죠 <br>내 맘 깊숙이 피어나는 그대 <br>눈을 감으면 그대가 <br>내게 불어와 <br>그대라는 향기가 <br>내 맘의 창을 열고서 <br>하늘빛 담은 그대가 <br>내게 불어와 <br>그대라는 사람을 온전히 <br>느낄 수 있어 <br>끝없이 그대라는 바람이 <br>내게 분다 <br>그대 <br>두 손을 내밀면 그대가 <br>닿을 것 같아 <br>차마 담지 못했던 그대가 <br>아련한 꿈처럼 그대가 <br>내게 다가와 <br>차오른 달빛에 머문 <br>그대를 느낄 수 있어 <br>그댈 가득 담은 바람이 <br>내게 불어와 <br>그대라는 사람을 온전히 <br>느낄 수 있어 <br>끝없이 그대라는 바람이 <br>내게 분다 <br>그대 <br>]]></content><category term="타임브릿지" label="타임브릿지"/><category term="기억의 숲 (Vocal 미키드)" label="기억의 숲 (Vocal 미키드)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Ill_String_Along_With_You/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - I`ll String Along With You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:40:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:40:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Ill_String_Along_With_You/" title="Louis_Armstrong - I`ll String Along With You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll string along, string along <br>String along with you, dear <br>I'll string along, string along <br>String along with you, dear <br><br>You may not be an angel <br>'Cause angels are so few <br>But until the day that one comes along <br>I'll string along with you <br><br>I'm looking for an angel <br>To sing my love song to <br>And until the day that one comes along <br>I'll sing my song to you <br><br>For every little fault that you have <br>Say I've got three or four <br>The human little faults you do have <br>Just make me love you more <br><br>You may not be an angel <br>But still I'm sure you'll do <br>So until the day that one comes along <br>I'll string along with you <br><br>You may not be an angel <br>'Cause angels are so few <br>But until the day that one comes along <br>I'll string along with you, say <br><br>I'm looking for an angel <br>To sing my love song to <br>And until the day that one comes along <br>Yes, I'll string along with you <br><br>For every little fault that she has <br>Say I've got three or four, maybe more <br>The little human faults she does have <br>Just make me love you more <br><br>You may not be an angel <br>But still I'm sure you'll do, oh yeah, yes <br>So until the day that one comes along <br>Yes, I'll string along with you <br><br>Until he finds an angel <br>I'll string, string along with you <br>String along]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="I`ll String Along With You" label="I`ll String Along With You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/On_My_Way_Feat_Sy_Oliver_Choir__The_All_Stars/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - On My Way (Feat. Sy Oliver Choir &amp; The All Stars) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:40:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:40:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/On_My_Way_Feat_Sy_Oliver_Choir__The_All_Stars/" title="Louis_Armstrong - On My Way (Feat. Sy Oliver Choir &amp; The All Stars) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[On my way now, got on my travelling shoes <br><br>On my way now, got on my travelling shoes <br>Well, I'm on my way now got on my travelling shoes <br>Them shoes now got on my travelling shoes <br>Oh, way child got on my travelling shoes <br><br>Well, I went to the church, I walked right in <br>The saints began to pray and the Lord came in <br>I went to the alter, didn't find a fault <br>The saints began to pray and the fires did halt <br><br>On my way now, got on my travelling shoes <br>Well, I'm on my way now got on my travelling shoes <br>Them shoes now got on my travelling shoes <br>Oh, way child got on my travelling shoes <br><br>Well, I went to the valley, didn't go to stay <br>My soul got empty and I stayed all day <br>I went to the river and walked right in <br>The saints were all saying, wash away your sins <br><br>On my way now, got on my travelling shoes <br>Well, I'm on my way now got on my travelling shoes <br>Them shoes now got on my travelling shoes <br>Oh, way child got on my travelling shoes <br><br>I'm on my way now got on my travelling shoes <br>on my way <br>Yes, I'm about to leave you on my way <br>I'm wearing my travelling shoes on my way <br><br>Yes, I'm going home where things are always good]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="On My Way (Feat. Sy Oliver Choir &amp; The All Stars)" label="On My Way (Feat. Sy Oliver Choir &amp; The All Stars)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/I_Love_Jazz/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - I Love Jazz - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:40:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:40:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/I_Love_Jazz/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - I Love Jazz - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A little jazz is just a bit of this and that <br>Sometimes we sing, sometimes we play, sometimes we scat <br>But most of all it's how you feel about the groove <br>And when it's groovin', how the groove makes you move <br><br>Jazz music sprouted rock and roll <br>It was the very first music that we call soul <br>Jazz is hot, it's cool, it's good, it's bad <br>And it can change your mood to happy from sad <br><br>Jazz is hip, it's groovy, it's fresh, it's jive <br>And when you play it, it makes your soul come alive <br>You know it's the upbeat rhythm that makes it bop <br>And once you get it started, well, it sure is hard to stop <br><br>No other music can compare <br>When the bass starts walkin', it fills the air <br>You know that the sass of brass has made it last <br>And it's the groove of blues from present to past <br><br>Hey, what about some of those great legends of jazz <br>Yeah, like Jazz Royalty <br>Oh, you mean Duke Ellington and Count Bassie <br>What about the great horn players <br>Louis Armstrong, yeah, and Miles and Dizzy too <br>Don't forget Snookie <br>What about Yarnburn <br>What, don't you mean Charlie Parker <br>Yeah, this cool named Freddy Hubert <br><br>A little jazz is just a little bit of this and that <br>Sometimes we sing, sometimes we play, sometimes we scat <br>But most of all it's how you feel about the groove <br>And when it's grovin', how the groove makes you move]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars"/><category term="I Love Jazz" label="I Love Jazz"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/When_Youre_Smiling_The_Whole_World_Smiles_With_You/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - When You`re Smiling (The Whole World Smiles With You) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:40:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:40:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/When_Youre_Smiling_The_Whole_World_Smiles_With_You/" title="Louis_Armstrong - When You`re Smiling (The Whole World Smiles With You) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh when you smilin', when you smilin' <br>The whole world smiles with you <br>Yes when you laughin', when you laughin' <br>Yes the sun come shinin' through <br><br>But when you cryin' you bring on the rain <br>So stop your sighin' baby and be happy again <br>Yes and keep on smilin, keep on smilin' <br>And the whole world smiles with you]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="When You`re Smiling (The Whole World Smiles With You)" label="When You`re Smiling (The Whole World Smiles With You)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/Nobody_Knows_The_Trouble_Ive_Seen_Feat_Sy_Oliver_Choir/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - Nobody Knows The Trouble I`ve Seen (Feat. Sy Oliver Choir) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:40:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:40:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/Nobody_Knows_The_Trouble_Ive_Seen_Feat_Sy_Oliver_Choir/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - Nobody Knows The Trouble I`ve Seen (Feat. Sy Oliver Choir) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody knows the trouble I've seen <br>Nobody knows but Jesus <br>Nobody knows the trouble I've seen <br>Glory Hallelujah <br><br>Sometimes I'm up and sometimes I'm down <br>Yes lord, you know sometimes I'm almost to the ground <br>O yes, Lord, still <br><br>Nobody knows the trouble I've seen <br>Nobody knows but Jesus <br>Nobody knows the trouble I've seen <br>Glory Hallelujah <br><br>You got here before I do <br>O yes Lord, don't forget to tell all my friends I'm coming too <br><br>O yes Lord, still <br><br>Nobody knows the trouble I've seen <br>Nobody knows but Jesus <br>Nobody knows the trouble I've seen <br>Glory Hallelujah]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars"/><category term="Nobody Knows The Trouble I`ve Seen (Feat. Sy Oliver Choir)" label="Nobody Knows The Trouble I`ve Seen (Feat. Sy Oliver Choir)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Youre_A_Heavenly_Thing/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - You`re A Heavenly Thing - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:40:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:40:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Youre_A_Heavenly_Thing/" title="Louis_Armstrong - You`re A Heavenly Thing - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Told me, darling, that you had to go <br>Done take your money, I don't care no more <br>I know you're happy, try to get along <br><br>Money won't change you <br>Money won't change you <br>Money won't change you <br>But time will take you on <br>Lookie here <br><br>If everybody had once been hurt <br>Then you know how it mean to be treated like dirt <br>Go ahead, baby, tell the world <br>That you're my woman and my only girl <br><br>Money won't change you <br>Money won't change you <br>I said, Money won't change you <br>But time will take you on <br><br>I you're happy <br>know you're happy <br>And now you're gone <br><br>Money won't change you <br>Money won't change you, mama <br>Money won't change you <br>I said, Money won't change you <br>But time will take you on <br><br>Lookie here, lookie here <br>Look here <br><br>I said, One time, one time <br>Oh, yeah, hold out, hold out <br>Hold out, hold it, slow it down, hold on <br><br>Get it, get it, get it, get it <br>Get it, get it, get it, get it <br>Get it, get it, get it, get it <br>Get it, get it <br><br>Get on up, get on up <br>Get on up, get on up <br>Come on, baby <br>Come on, baby <br><br>Everybody stand up <br>Everybody stand up <br>Raise your hands <br>Raise your hands]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="You`re A Heavenly Thing" label="You`re A Heavenly Thing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/Them_There_Eyes_1983_Satchmo_Ver/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - Them There Eyes (1983 Satchmo Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/Them_There_Eyes_1983_Satchmo_Ver/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - Them There Eyes (1983 Satchmo Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was just minding my business <br>Life was a beautiful song <br>Didn't have a care nor worry <br>Then you had to come along <br>I fell in love with you first time <br>I looked into them there eyes <br>You've got a certain lil' cute way of flirtin' <br>With them there eyes <br>They make me feel happy, they make me blue <br>No stallin' <br>I'm fallin' <br>Going in a big way for sweet little you <br>My heart is jumpin' <br>You sure started somethin' <br>With them there eyes <br>You'd better watch them if you're wise <br>They sparkle, they bubble <br>They're gonna get you in a whole lot of trouble <br>You're overworkin' 'em <br>There's danger lurkin' in <br>Them there eyes <br>Maybe you think I'm just flirtin' <br>Maybe you think I'm all lies <br>Just because I get romantic when I gaze in <br>Them there eyes <br>I fell in love with you first time <br>I looked into them there eyes <br>You've got a certain lil' cute way of flirtin' <br>With them there eyes <br>They make me feel happy, they make me blue <br>No stallin' <br>I'm fallin' <br>Going in a big way for sweet little you <br>My heart is jumpin' <br>You sure started somethin' <br>With them there eyes <br>You'd better watch them if you're wise <br>They sparkle <br>They bubble <br>They're gonna get you in a whole lot of trouble <br>You're overworkin' 'em <br>There's danger lurkin' in <br>Them there eyes]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra"/><category term="Them There Eyes (1983 Satchmo Ver.)" label="Them There Eyes (1983 Satchmo Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/If_I_Could_Be_With_You_One_Hour_Tonight_1983_Satchmo_Ver/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - If I Could Be With You (One Hour Tonight) (1983 Satchmo Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/If_I_Could_Be_With_You_One_Hour_Tonight_1983_Satchmo_Ver/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - If I Could Be With You (One Hour Tonight) (1983 Satchmo Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby, baby <br>I wanna be with you tonight <br><br>If I could be with you, I'd love you strong <br>If I could be with you, I'd love you long <br>I want you to know that I wouldn't go <br>Until I told you honey why I love you so <br><br>If I could be with you, one hour tonight <br>If I was free to do the things I might, things I might <br>I'm telling you true, I'd be anything but blue <br>If I could be with you, hmm babe <br>If I could be with you]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra"/><category term="If I Could Be With You (One Hour Tonight) (1983 Satchmo Ver.)" label="If I Could Be With You (One Hour Tonight) (1983 Satchmo Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/On_The_Sunny_Side_Of_The_Street/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - On The Sunny Side Of The Street - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/On_The_Sunny_Side_Of_The_Street/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - On The Sunny Side Of The Street - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Grab your coat and grab your hat baby <br>Leave your worries on the doorstep <br>Just direct your feet <br>On the sunny side of the street <br><br>Can't you hear that pitter pat there <br>That happy tune is yours now <br>Life can be so sweet <br>On the sunny side of the street <br><br>I used to walk in the shade <br>With those blues on parade <br>But I'm not afraid baby <br>My rover, crossed over <br><br>If I never have a cent <br>I'll be rich as Rockefeller <br>With gold dust at my feet <br>On the sunny side of the street]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra"/><category term="On The Sunny Side Of The Street" label="On The Sunny Side Of The Street"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/I_Cant_Give_You_Anything_But_Love/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - I Can`t Give You Anything But Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/I_Cant_Give_You_Anything_But_Love/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - I Can`t Give You Anything But Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can't give you anything but love, baby <br>That's the only thing I'm plenty of, baby <br>Dream a while, scheme a while, baby <br>You're sure to find happiness and I guess <br>All those things that you've pined for <br><br>Gee, I'd like to see you lookin' swell, baby <br>Diamond bracelets, woolworths doesn't sell, baby <br>Till that lucky day, lucky day you know darn well, baby <br>I can't give you anything but love]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra"/><category term="I Can`t Give You Anything But Love" label="I Can`t Give You Anything But Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Lazy_Bones/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Lazy Bones - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Lazy_Bones/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Lazy Bones - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lazybones, sleepin' in the sun <br>How you 'spect to get your day's work done <br>You can't get your day's work done <br>Sleepin' in the noon day sun <br><br>Lazybones, layin' in the shade <br>How you gonna get your cornmeal made <br>You can't get no cornmeal made <br>Sleepin' in that evening shade <br><br>When taters need sprayin' <br>I bet you keep prayin' <br>The bugs'll fall off of the vine <br><br>And when you go fishin' <br>I bet you keep wishin' <br>Them fish don't grab your line <br><br>Lazybones, loafin' all the day <br>How you 'spect to make a dime that way <br>You won't make no dime that way <br>Loafin' in the shade all day]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Lazy Bones" label="Lazy Bones"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Christmas_Night_In_Harlem/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Christmas Night In Harlem - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Christmas_Night_In_Harlem/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Christmas Night In Harlem - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hallelujah, Hallelujah, glory, Halle <br>What's all that noise <br>Hallelujah <br>Don't give up with that now <br><br>Glory, Halle <br>Who's that over in the corner <br>Hallelujah <br>I believe that's Mr Teagarden <br><br>Hey what you doin' up there, man <br>Last time I saw you <br>You were sayin' fare thee well to Harlem <br>I done bin wise g'wine <br>An' I ain't g'wine there n'more <br><br>You sho' come back the right time <br>It's Christmas up here <br>What d'ya mean up here <br>It's Christmas ev'rywhere <br><br>Yeah, but it ain't all Christmas <br>Like it's Christmas in Harlem <br>No <br><br>Ev'ry gal struttin' with her beau <br>Through the streets covered white with snow <br>Happy smiles er'ywhere you go <br>Christmas night in Harlem <br><br>Black and tans feelin' mighty good <br>In that old colored neighborhood <br>Here and now be it understood <br>Christmas night in Harlem <br><br>Ev'ryone is gonna sit up <br>Until after three <br>Ev'ryone will be all lit up <br>Like a Christmas tree <br><br>Come on now ev'ry coal black Joe <br>You just lead me t'the mistletoe <br>With a kiss and a hi de ho <br>Christmas night in Harlem <br><br>Hee, man, dog <br>What'd Santa Claus leave in your stockin' <br>Let me see, there's an orange, a jar <br>And, man, look at this slide trombone <br>Yeah, but it might not sound so pretty <br>Let me hear you tune it <br><br>Mr Mercer, I'm glad to be back in this festivity <br>Ah, you said it Mr T <br>It's Christmas night in Harlem <br>Well it's Christmas night in Harlem <br>Man, you drew the]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Christmas Night In Harlem" label="Christmas Night In Harlem"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Christmas_In_New_Orleans/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Christmas In New Orleans - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Christmas_In_New_Orleans/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Christmas In New Orleans - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Magnolia trees at night <br>Sparkling bright <br>Fields of cotton look wintery white <br>When it's Christmas time <br>In New Orleans <br><br>A barefoot choir in prayer <br>Fills the air <br>Mississippi folks <br>Are gathering there <br>When it's Christmas time <br>In New Orleans <br><br>You'll see a dixieland Santa Claus <br>Leading the band <br>To a good old Creole beat <br>And golly what a spirit <br>You can only hear it <br>Down on Basin Street <br>Your cares will disappear <br>When you hear <br>Hallelujah St Nicholas is here <br>When it's Christmas time <br>In New Orleans <br><br>You'll see <br>A dixieland Santa Claus <br>Leading the band <br>To a good old Creole beat <br>And golly what a spirit <br>You can only hear it <br>Down on Basin Street <br>Your cares will disappear <br>When you hear <br>Hallelujah old St Nicholas is here <br>When it's Christmas time <br>In New Orleans <br><br>When it's Christmas time in <br>It's Christmas time in in New Orleans]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Christmas In New Orleans" label="Christmas In New Orleans"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Moments_To_Remember/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Moments To Remember - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Moments_To_Remember/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Moments To Remember - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[January to December we'll have moments to remember <br><br>The New Year's Eve we did the town <br>The day we tore the goal post down <br>We'll have these moments to remember <br><br>The quiet walks the noisy fun <br>The ballroom prize we almost won <br>We will have these moments to remember <br><br>Though summer turns to winter <br>And the present disappears <br>The laughter we were glad to share <br>Will echo through the years <br><br>When other nights and other days <br>May find us gone our separate ways <br>We will have these moments to remember <br><br>The drive in movie where we'd go <br>And somehow never watched the show <br>We will have these moments to remember <br><br>When other nights and other days <br>May find us gone our separate ways <br>We will have these moments to remember <br><br>The drive in movie where we'd go <br>And somehow never watched the show <br>We will have these moments to remember]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Moments To Remember" label="Moments To Remember"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Only_You/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Only You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Only_You/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Only You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Only you <br>Can make this world seem right <br>Only you <br>Can make the darkness bright <br>Only you and you alone <br>Can thrill me like you do <br>And fill my heart with love for only you <br><br>Baby only you <br>Can make this change in me <br>For its true <br>You're my destiny <br>And when you hold my hand I understand <br>The magic that you do <br>You're my dream come true <br>My one and only you <br><br>Ohhh only you <br>Can make this change in meeeeee <br>Baby, its so true <br>You are my destiny <br>When you hold my hand, I understand <br>The magic that you do <br>Baby you my dream come true and my one and only youuuu]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Only You" label="Only You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Sincerely/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Sincerely - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Sincerely/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Sincerely - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sincerely, oh yes, sincerely <br>'Cause I love you so dearly, please, say you'll be mine <br>Sincerely, oh, you know how I love you <br>I'll do anything for you please, say you'll be mine <br><br>Oh, Lord, won't you tell me why <br>I love that fella so <br>He doesn't want me <br>But I'll never, never, never, never let him go <br><br>Sincerely, oh, you know how I love you <br>I'll do anything for you please, say you'll be mine <br><br>Oh, Lord, won't you tell me why <br>I love that fella so <br>He doesn't want me <br>But I'll never, never, never, never let him go <br><br>Sincerely, oh, you know how I love you <br>I'll do anything for you please, say you'll be mine <br>Please, say you'll be mine]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Sincerely" label="Sincerely"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Ko_Ko_Mo_I_Love_You_So/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Ko Ko Mo (I Love You So) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Ko_Ko_Mo_I_Love_You_So/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Ko Ko Mo (I Love You So) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ko Ko Mo Ko Ko Mo Ko Ko Mo <br><br>Talk to me baby, whisper in my ear <br>a come a little closer, don't you have no fear <br><br>Don't you know I love you so <br>Don't you know I love you so <br>When I holler Hey Ko Ko Mo <br><br>Heard what you told me, heard what you said <br>Heard what you told me, heard what you said <br>Don't you worry my purdy, I don't lose my head <br><br>There's dimples on my elbows, dimples on her knees <br>dimples on my elbows, dimples on her knees <br>she thrills an' thrills me, just a little squeeze <br><br>Ko, Ko, Ko Ko Mo Ko, Ko, Ko Ko Mo <br>Ko, Ko, Ko Ko Mo <br><br>Don't you know Ko Ko Mo that I love you so <br>Oh talk to me baby talk, talk whisper in my ear talk, talk, talk <br>Oh talk to me baby talk, talk whisper in my ear talk, talk, talk <br>Tell it to me come a little closer, don't you have no fear <br><br>Ah Don't you know I love you so <br>Don't you know ~ I love you so <br>When I holler Hey Hey Ko Ko Mo <br><br>Ko Ko Mo Ko Ko Mo Ko Ko Mo <br><br>Don't you know <br>I love you Ko Ko Mo <br><br>Ko Ko Mo]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Ko Ko Mo (I Love You So)" label="Ko Ko Mo (I Love You So)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Trees/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Trees - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Trees/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Trees - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I think that I shall never see <br>A poem as lovely as a tree <br>A tree whose hungry mouth is pressed <br>Against the earth's sweet flowing breast <br><br>O, a tree that looks at God all day <br>And lifts her leafy arms to pray <br>A tree that may in summer wear <br>Yeah, a nest of robins in her hair <br><br>Upon whose bosom snow has lain <br>Who intimately lives with rain <br>Poems are made by fools like me <br>But only God can make a tree]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Trees" label="Trees"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/Muskrat_Ramble/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - Muskrat Ramble - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/Muskrat_Ramble/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - Muskrat Ramble - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I look at them shuffle and the shuffle come down <br>Ramblin' and scramblin' and a headin' for town <br>Hoppin' and boppin' and a buzzin' around <br>Happily awaitin' at the station <br>I look at that train number 709 <br>Hoppin' and boppin' and arrivin' on time <br>Who do you think is about to arrive <br>The band they call the Dixieland Five <br><br>They're gonna play that muskrat ramble tune <br>Like the way you never heard it played <br>Get ready for the big parade <br>All together now one and two <br>Join that happy crowd <br>Tellin' me that ramblin' scramblin' muskrat song <br>Come on, ramble along <br>Yeah]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars"/><category term="Muskrat Ramble" label="Muskrat Ramble"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Someday_Youll_Be_Sorry_Single_Ver/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Someday (You`ll Be Sorry) (Single Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Someday_Youll_Be_Sorry_Single_Ver/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Someday (You`ll Be Sorry) (Single Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Someday you'll be sorry <br>The way you treated me was wrong <br>I was the one who taught you all you know <br>Your friends have told you to make me sing another song <br><br>So good luck may be with you <br>And for the future have no fears <br>There won't be another to treat you like a brother <br>Someday you'll be sorry dear]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Someday (You`ll Be Sorry) (Single Ver.)" label="Someday (You`ll Be Sorry) (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/The_Whiffenpoof_Song/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - The Whiffenpoof Song - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/The_Whiffenpoof_Song/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - The Whiffenpoof Song - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[To the tables down at Mory's, to the place where Louie dwells <br>To the dear old Temple bar we love so well <br>Sing the Whiffenpoofs assembled, with their glasses raised on high <br>And the magic of their singing casts its spell <br><br>Yes, the magic of their singing, of the songs we love so well <br>Shall I Wasting and Mavourneen and the rest <br><br>We will serenade our Louie while life and voice shall last <br><br>Then we'll pass and be forgotten with the rest <br><br>We're poor little lambs who have lost our way <br>Baa, baa, baa <br><br>We're little black sheep who have gone astray <br>Baa, baa, baa <br><br>Gentleman songsters off on a spree <br>Doomed from here to eternity <br>Lord have mercy on such as we <br>Baa, baa, baa <br><br>Gentleman songsters off on a spree <br>Doomed from here to eternity <br><br>Lord have mercy on such as we <br>Baa, baa, baa]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars"/><category term="The Whiffenpoof Song" label="The Whiffenpoof Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Bye_And_Bye/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Bye And Bye - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Bye_And_Bye/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Bye And Bye - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bye bye blues bye bye blues <br>Bells ring birds sing <br>Sun is shin in' no more pin in' <br><br>Just we two smil in' through <br>Don't sigh don't cry <br>Bye bye blues <br><br>Bye bye blues i'm sayin' bye bye blues <br>Bells will ring and birds all sing <br>Stop your mope in', keep on hope in' <br><br>You and me can't you see <br>Now don't you sigh and don't you cry <br>Bye bye blues]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Bye And Bye" label="Bye And Bye"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/The_Gypsy_Single_Ver/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - The Gypsy (Single Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:41:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:41:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/The_Gypsy_Single_Ver/" title="Louis_Armstrong - The Gypsy (Single Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In a quaint caravan <br>There's a lady, they call The Gypsy, yes <br>She can look in the future <br>And drive away all your fears, yes, yes, yes <br><br>Everything will come right <br>If you only believe The Gypsy, yeah <br>She can tell at a glance <br>That your heart's full of tears <br><br>Yes, she looked in my hand and told me <br>My lover was always true <br>But even my heart, I know dear <br>Somebody else is kissing you, yes <br><br>But I'll go there again <br>'Cause I want to believe The Gypsy <br>Although I know she is lying <br>That my lover is true <br>And will come back to me some day]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="The Gypsy (Single Ver.)" label="The Gypsy (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Cool_Yule_Feat_The_Commanders/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Cool Yule (Feat. The Commanders) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Cool_Yule_Feat_The_Commanders/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Cool Yule (Feat. The Commanders) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[From Coney Island to The Sunset Strip <br>Somebody's gonna make a happy trip <br>Tonight, while the moon is bright <br><br>He's gonna have a bag of crazy toys <br>To give the groanies of the girls and boys <br>So dig, Santa comes on big <br><br>He'll come a callin' when the snow's the most <br>When all you cats are sleepin' warm as toast <br>And you gonna flip when Old Saint Nick <br>a lick on the peppermint stick <br><br>He'll come a flyin' from a higher place <br>And fill the stocking by the fireplace <br>So you'll have a yule that's cool <br><br>Yeah, from Coney Island to The Sunset Strip <br>Somebody's gonna make a happy trip <br>Tonight, while the moon is bright <br><br>He's gonna have a bag of crazy toys <br>To give the groanies of the girls and boys <br>So dig, Santa comes on big <br><br>Come a callin' when the snow's the most <br>Cats are sleepin' warm as toast <br>And you gonna flip when the Old Saint Nick <br>a lick on the peppermint stick <br><br>He'll come a flyin' from the higher place <br>Fill the stockings by the fireplace <br>So you'll have a yule that's cool <br><br>Have a yule that's cool <br>Yeah, cool yule]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Cool Yule (Feat. The Commanders)" label="Cool Yule (Feat. The Commanders)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Zat_You_Santa_Claus__Single_Ver/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - `Zat You, Santa Claus? (Single Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Zat_You_Santa_Claus__Single_Ver/" title="Louis_Armstrong - `Zat You, Santa Claus? (Single Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Zat You, Santa Claus <br>Gifts I'm preparing for some Christmas sharing <br>But I pause because <br>Hanging my stocking I can hear a knocking <br>'Zat you, Santa Claus <br>Sure is dark out, ain't the slightest spark out <br>'Pon my slackened jaw <br>Who's there Who is it stopping for a visit <br>'Zat you, Santa Claus <br>Are you bringing a present for me <br>Something pleasantly pleasant for me <br>Then it's just what I've been waiting for <br>Would you mind slipping it under the door <br>Cold winds are howling, or could that be growling <br>My legs feel like straws <br>My my oh me my, kindly would you reply <br><br>'Zat you, Santa Claus <br>Hanging the stocking, I can hear a knocking <br>'Zat you, Santa Claus <br>I say, who's there, who is it Are you stopping for a visit <br>'Zat you, Santa Claus <br>Oh there, Santa, you gave me a scare <br>Now stop teasing cause I know you're there <br>We don't believe in no goblins today <br>But I can't explain why I'm shaking that way <br>Bet I can see ole Santa in the keyhole <br>I'll get to the cause <br>One peek and I'll try there oh oh, there's an eye there <br>'Zat you, Santa Claus <br>Please, please, pity my knees <br>Say that's you, Santa Claus]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="`Zat You, Santa Claus? (Single Ver.)" label="`Zat You, Santa Claus? (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/The_Dummy_Song_Single_Ver/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - The Dummy Song (Single Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/The_Dummy_Song_Single_Ver/" title="Louis_Armstrong - The Dummy Song (Single Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll take the legs from some old table <br>I'll take the arms from some old chair <br>I'll take the neck from some old bottle <br>And from a horse I'll take the hair <br><br>I'll take the hands and face from some old clock <br>And baby, when I'm through <br>I'll get more loving from the dum, dum, dummy <br>Than I ever got from you <br><br>Get me some legs, get me a chair <br>And a bottle, too <br>Give me a horse, give me some time <br>And baby, when I'm through <br><br>I'll take the legs from some old table <br>I'll take the arms from some old chair <br>I'll take the neck from some old bottle <br>And from a horse I'll take the hair <br><br>I'll take the hands and face from some old clock <br>And baby, when I'm through <br>I'll get more loving from the dum, dum, dummy <br>Than I ever got from you <br><br>I get more loving <br>From that dum, dum, dummy <br>Than I've ever gotten from you <br>Yeah, mama, get more loving <br>From a dummy than I get from you]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="The Dummy Song (Single Ver.)" label="The Dummy Song (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Sittin_In_The_Sun_Single_Ver/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Sittin` In The Sun (Single Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Sittin_In_The_Sun_Single_Ver/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Sittin` In The Sun (Single Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sittin' in the sun, countin' my money <br>Fanned by a summer breeze <br>Sweeter than the honey is countin' my money <br>Those greenbacks on the trees <br>Comes a summer shower, drops o' rain falling <br>Sweeter than Christmas chimes <br>Hearing those jingles upon the roof shingles <br>Like pennies, nickels and dimes <br>Tho' it's known that what I own is not a large amount <br>Fields of gold that I behold are in my bank account <br>Yeah, sittin' in the sun, countin' my money <br>Happy as I can be <br>And to top it all <br>When shadows fall <br><br>I look to heaven and I see <br>There's a silver dollar in the sky <br>Shining down on me <br>Yeah, sittin' in the sun, countin' my money <br>Happy as I can be, yes <br>And to top it all <br>When shadows fall <br>I look to heaven and I see <br>There's a silver dollar in the sky <br>It's shining, shining, shining down on me]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Sittin` In The Sun (Single Ver.)" label="Sittin` In The Sun (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/Ramona/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - Ramona - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/Ramona/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - Ramona - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wander out yonder o'er the hills <br>Where the mountains high <br>Seem to kiss the sky <br>Someone is out yonder, o'er the hills <br>Waiting patiently, Waiting just for me <br><br>Ramona, I hear the mission bells above <br>Ramona, they're ringing out our song of love <br>I press you, caress you, and bless the day you taught me to care <br>To always remember the rambling rose you wear in your hair <br>Ramona, when day is done you'll hear my call <br>Ramona, we'll meet beside the water fall <br>I dread the dawn when I awake to find you gone <br>Ramona I need you my own <br><br>Let's wander out yonder o'er the hills <br>By a babbling brook <br>Where we'll find a nook <br>To build our own love nest, o'er the hills <br>Darling of my heart, Never more to part <br><br>Ramona, I hear the mission bells above <br>Ramona, they're ringing out our song of love <br>I press you, caress you, and bless the day you taught me to care <br>To always remember the rambling rose you wear in your hair <br>Ramona, when day is done you'll hear my call <br>Ramona, we'll meet beside the water fall <br>I dread the dawn when I awake to find you gone <br>Ramona I need you my own]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra"/><category term="Ramona" label="Ramona"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/April_In_Portugal/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - April In Portugal - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/April_In_Portugal/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - April In Portugal - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[April in Paris, chestnuts in blossom <br>Holiday tables under the trees <br>April in Paris, this is a feeling <br>No one can ever reprieve <br>I never knew the charm of spring <br>Never met it face to face <br>I never knew my heart could sing <br>Never missed a warm embrace <br>'Til April in Paris whom can I run to <br>What have you done to my heart <br>I never knew the charm of spring <br>Never met it face to face <br>I never knew my heart could sing <br>Never missed a warm embrace <br>'Til April in Paris whom can I run to <br>What have you done to my heart]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra"/><category term="April In Portugal" label="April In Portugal"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Congratulations_To_Someone/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Congratulations To Someone - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Congratulations_To_Someone/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Congratulations To Someone - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to someone <br>Someone who's happy with you <br>I guess he did the right things <br>I was wise enough to do <br><br>Yes, congratulations to someone <br>Someone who's holding you now <br>You know I'll always love you <br>But I'll get along somehow <br><br>Now, didn't I kiss you often enough <br>Didn't I hold you tight <br>Why did you leave here by myself <br>Cryin' alone in the night, babe <br><br>I thought you'd love me forever <br>Somehow it just couldn't be <br>Congratulations to someone <br>But I wish that someone was me <br><br>I thought you'd love me forever <br>Somehow it just couldn't be <br>Congratulations to someone <br>Oh, I wish that someone was me <br>Yes, I wish that someone was me]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Congratulations To Someone" label="Congratulations To Someone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Your_Cheatin_Heart_Single_Ver/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Your Cheatin` Heart (Single Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Your_Cheatin_Heart_Single_Ver/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Your Cheatin` Heart (Single Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Your cheating heart will make you weep <br>You'll cry and cry and try to sleep <br>But sleep won't come the whole night through <br>Your cheating heart will tell on you <br><br>When tears come down like falling rain <br>You'll toss around and call my name <br>You'll walk the floor, yes, the way I do <br>Your cheating heart will tell on you <br><br>When tears come down like falling rain <br>You'll toss around and call my name <br>You'll walk the floor, yes, the way I do <br>Your cheating heart will tell on you <br>Yes, your cheating heart will tell on you]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Your Cheatin` Heart (Single Ver.)" label="Your Cheatin` Heart (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Who_Walks_In_When_I_Walk_Out_/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Who Walks In When I Walk Out? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Who_Walks_In_When_I_Walk_Out_/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Who Walks In When I Walk Out? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Who walks in when I walk out <br>And who gives you that, Hi, baby <br>Who's it who got me jealous of you <br><br>Who walks in when I walk out <br>Now, don't you know you're my baby <br>Who's it who got me worrying too <br><br>Now when we kiss, I kinda miss <br>Something that used to be <br>Everyday while I'm away <br>I got a feeling that you're fooling me <br><br>Oh, who walks in when I walk out <br>Who gives you that, Hi, baby <br>Who's it who got me jealous of you <br><br>When we kiss, I kinda miss <br>Something that used to be <br>Everyday while I'm away <br>I get that feeling you're fooling me <br><br>Who walks in when I walk out <br>Who gives you that, Hi, baby <br>Who's it who got me jealous of you <br>Got me jealous of you]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Who Walks In When I Walk Out?" label="Who Walks In When I Walk Out?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Would_You_Like_To_Take_A_Walk_/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Would You Like To Take A Walk? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Would_You_Like_To_Take_A_Walk_/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Would You Like To Take A Walk? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I saw you strolling by your solitary <br>Am I nosy Very, very <br>I'd like to be a juicy huckleberry <br>What you're after is a gal <br>We're both in luck, for introductions <br>Are not necessary <br><br>Mmm, would you like to take walk <br>Mmm, do you think it's gonna rain <br>Mmm, how about a sarsaparilla <br>Gee, the moon is yeller <br>Sump'n good'll come from that <br><br>Mmm, have you heard the latest song <br>Mmm, it's a very pretty strain <br>Mmm, don't you feel a little thrilly <br>Gee, it's getting chilly <br>Sump'n good'll come from that <br><br>When you're strolling though the wheresies <br>You need a whosies to lean upon <br>But when you have no whosies <br>To hug and whatsies, gosh, darn <br><br>Mmm, would you like to take walk <br>Mmm, do you think it's gonna rain <br>Mmm, ain't you tired of the talkies <br>I prefer the walkies <br>Sump'n good'll come from that <br><br>My little heart is full of palpitation <br>What I need is consolation <br>I'd like to stage a little celebration <br>In the moonlight, right away <br>I'll feel all pepped if you'll accept <br>My friendly invitation <br><br>Mmm, would you like to take walk <br>Mmm, do you think it's gonna rain <br>Mmm, how about a sarsaparilla <br>Gee, the moon is yeller <br>Sump'n good'll come from that <br><br>Mmm, have you heard the latest song <br>Mmm, it's a very pretty strain <br>Mmm, don't you feel a little thrilly <br>Gee, it's getting chilly <br>Sump'n good'll come from that <br><br>When you're strolling though the wheresies <br>You need a whosies to lean upon <br>But when you have no whosies <br>To hug and whatsies, gosh, darn <br><br>Mmm, would you like to take walk <br>Mmm, do you think it's gonna rain <br>Mmm, ain't you tired of the talkies <br>I prefer the walkies <br>Sump'n good'll come from that]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Would You Like To Take A Walk?" label="Would You Like To Take A Walk?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Chloe_Song_Of_The_Swamp_Single_Ver/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Chloe (Song Of The Swamp) (Single Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Chloe_Song_Of_The_Swamp_Single_Ver/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Chloe (Song Of The Swamp) (Single Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Chloe Chloe <br>Someone's calling, no reply <br>Nightshade's falling , hear him sigh <br>Chloe Chloe <br>Empty spaces meet his eyes <br>Empty arms outstretched , he's crying <br><br>Through the black of night <br>I've got to go where you are <br>If it's wrong or right <br>I've got to go where you are <br><br>I'll roll through the dismal swamplands <br>Searching for you <br>'Cause if you are there <br>Let me be there too <br><br>Through the smoke and flame <br>I've got to go where you are <br>For no place could be too far <br>Where you are <br><br>Ain't no chains can bind you <br>If you live, I'll find you <br>Love is calling me <br>I've got to go where you are <br><br>What's that Somebody called my name <br>I believe that I hear love calling me <br>I've got to go where you are]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Chloe (Song Of The Swamp) (Single Ver.)" label="Chloe (Song Of The Swamp) (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Winter_Wonderland_Single_Ver/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Winter Wonderland (Single Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Winter_Wonderland_Single_Ver/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Winter Wonderland (Single Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sleigh bells ring are you listening <br>In the lane snow is glistening <br>A beautiful sight oh, we're happy tonight <br>Walking in a winter wonderland <br><br>Gone away is the bluebird <br>Here to stay is a new bird <br>He's singing a song as we go along <br>Walking in a winter wonderland <br><br>Well, in the meadow we can build a snowman <br>And pretend that he is Parson Brown <br>He'll say, are you married We'll say no man <br>But you can do the job when you're in town <br><br>Later on we'll conspire <br>As we dream by the fire <br>To face unafraid of the plans that we made <br>Walking in a winter wonderland <br><br>In the meadow we can build a snowman <br>And pretend he's a circus clown <br>We'll have lots of fun with Mr Snowman <br>Until the other kiddies knock him down <br><br>Oh, when it snows, ain't it filling <br>Though your nose gets a chilling <br>We'll frolic and play the Eskimo way <br>Walking in a winter wonderland <br>Wonderland wonderland]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Winter Wonderland (Single Ver.)" label="Winter Wonderland (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/White_Christmas_Single_Ver/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - White Christmas (Single Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/White_Christmas_Single_Ver/" title="Louis_Armstrong - White Christmas (Single Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm dreaming of a white Christmas <br>Just like the ones I used to know <br>Where the treetops glisten and children listen <br>To hear sleigh bells in the snow <br><br>I'm dreaming of a white Christmas <br>With every Christmas card I write <br>And may your days be merry and bright <br>And may all your Christmases be white <br><br>May your days be merry and bright <br>And may all your Christmases be white]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="White Christmas (Single Ver.)" label="White Christmas (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/It_Takes_Two_To_Tango_Single_Ver/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - It Takes Two To Tango (Single Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/It_Takes_Two_To_Tango_Single_Ver/" title="Louis_Armstrong - It Takes Two To Tango (Single Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, baby, how about this dance <br>Why 'Cause it takes two to do this dance <br><br>Takes two to tango, two to tango <br>Two to really get the feeling of romance <br>Let's do the tango, do the tango <br>Do the dance of love <br><br>You can sail on a ship by yourself <br>Take a nap or a nip by yourself <br>You can get into debt on your own <br>There's a lot of things that you can do alone <br><br>But <br><br>Takes two to tango, two to tango <br>Two to really get the feeling of romance <br>Let's do the tango, do the tango <br>Do the dance of love <br><br>You can stare at the moon by yourself <br>Take a laugh like a loon by yourself <br>Spend a lot, go to pot on your own <br>There's a lot of things that you can do alone <br><br>But, listen here <br><br>Takes two to tango, two to tango <br>Two to really get the feeling of romance <br>Let's do the tango, do the tango <br>Do the dance of love <br><br>Oh, see]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="It Takes Two To Tango (Single Ver.)" label="It Takes Two To Tango (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/Thats_My_Desire/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - That`s My Desire - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/Thats_My_Desire/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - That`s My Desire - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[To spend one night with you <br>In our old rendezvous <br>And reminisce with you <br>That's my desire <br><br>To be where gypsies play <br>Down in that ole cafe <br>We'll dance till break of day <br>That's my desire <br><br>We'll sip a little glass of wine <br>I'll gaze into your eyes divine <br>I'll feel the touch of your lips <br>Pressing on mine <br><br>To hear you whisper low <br>Just when it's time to go <br>Darling, I love you, so <br>That's my desire <br><br>To hear you whisper low <br>Doggone you know it's time to go <br>Darling, I love you so <br>You're my desire <br><br>Though you found someone new <br>I'll always love you <br>That's my desire]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars"/><category term="That`s My Desire" label="That`s My Desire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Baby_Its_Cold_Outside/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Baby It`s Cold Outside - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Baby_Its_Cold_Outside/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Baby It`s Cold Outside - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I really can't stay <br>But baby, it's cold outside <br>I've got to go away <br>But baby, it's cold outside <br><br>This evening has been <br>Been hoping that you'd drop in <br>So very nice <br>I'll hold your hands, they're just like ice <br><br>My mother will start to worry <br>Beautiful, what's your hurry <br>My father will be pacing the floor <br>Listen to the fireplace roar <br><br>So really I'd better scurry <br>Beautiful, please don't hurry <br>But maybe just a half a drink more <br>Put some records on while I pour <br><br>The neighbors might think <br>Baby, it's bad out there <br>Say, what's in this drink <br>No cabs to be had out there <br><br>I wish I knew how <br>Your eyes are like starlight <br>To break this spell <br>I'll take your hat, your hair looks swell <br><br>I ought to say no, no, no, sir <br>Mind if I move in closer <br>At least I'm gonna say that I tried <br>What's the sense in hurting my pride <br><br>I really can't stay <br>Baby, don't hold out <br>Oh, but it's cold outside <br><br>I simply must go <br>But baby, it's cold outside <br>The answer is no <br>But baby, it's cold outside <br><br>This welcome has been <br>How lucky that you dropped in <br>So nice and warm <br>Look out the window at that storm <br><br>My sister will be suspicious <br>Gosh, your lips look delicious <br>My brother will be there at the door <br>Waves upon a tropical shore <br><br>My maiden aunt's mind is vicious <br>Ooh, your lips are delicious <br>But maybe just a cigarette more <br>Never such a blizzard before <br><br>I've got to get home <br>But baby, you'll freeze out there <br>Say, lend me your coat <br>It's up to your knees out there <br><br>You've really been grand <br>I thrill when you touch my hand <br>But don't you see <br>How can you do this thing to me <br><br>There's bound to be talk tomorrow <br>Think of my life long sorrow <br>At least there will be plenty implied <br>If you caught pneumonia and died <br><br>I really can't stay <br>Get over that hold out <br>Oh, but it's cold outside]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Baby It`s Cold Outside" label="Baby It`s Cold Outside"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/Kiss_Of_Fire/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - Kiss Of Fire - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/Kiss_Of_Fire/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - Kiss Of Fire - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I touch your lips and all at once the sparks go flying <br>Those devil lips that know so well the art of lying <br>And though I see the danger, still the flame grows higher <br>I know I must surrender to your kiss of fire <br><br>Just like a torch, you set the soul within me burning <br>I must go on, I'm on this road of no returning <br>And though it burns me and it turns me into ashes <br>My whole world crashes without your kiss of fire <br><br>I can't resist you, what good is there in trying <br>What good is there denying you're all that I desire <br>Since first I kissed you my heart was yours completely <br>If I'm a slave, then it's a slave I want to be <br>Don't pity me, don't pity me <br><br>Give me your lips, the lips you only let me borrow <br>Love me tonight and let the devil take tomorrow <br>I know that I must have your kiss although it dooms me <br>Though it consumes me, your kiss of fire <br><br>I can't resist you, what good is there in trying <br>What good is there denying you're all that I desire <br>Since first I kissed you my heart was yours completely <br>If I'm a slave, then it's a slave I want to be <br>Don't pity me, don't pity me <br><br>Give me your lips, the lips you only let me borrow <br>Love me tonight and let the devil take tomorrow <br>I know that I must have your kiss although it dooms me <br>Though it consumes me the kiss of fire <br><br>Aaah Burn me]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra"/><category term="Kiss Of Fire" label="Kiss Of Fire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Ill_Walk_Alone_Feat_Gordon_Jenkins__His_Orchestra/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - I`ll Walk Alone (Feat. Gordon Jenkins &amp; His Orchestra) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Ill_Walk_Alone_Feat_Gordon_Jenkins__His_Orchestra/" title="Louis_Armstrong - I`ll Walk Alone (Feat. Gordon Jenkins &amp; His Orchestra) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll walk alone <br>But to tell you the truth, I'll be lonely <br>I don't mind being lonely <br>When my heart tells me you are lonely, too <br><br>I'll walk alone <br>They'll ask me why and I'll tell them I'd rather <br>There are dreams I must gather <br>Dreams we fashioned the night you held me tight <br><br>I'll always be near you wherever you are each night <br>In every prayer <br>If you call I'll hear you, no matter how far <br>Just close your eyes and I'll be there <br><br>Please walk alone <br>And send your love and your kisses to guide me <br>Till you're walking beside me <br>I'll walk alone <br><br>I'll always be near you wherever you are each night <br>In every prayer <br>If you call I'll hear you, no matter how far <br>Just close your eyes and I'll be there <br><br>Please walk alone <br>And send your love and your kisses to guide me <br>Till you're walking beside me, I'll walk alone <br>I'll walk alone]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="I`ll Walk Alone (Feat. Gordon Jenkins &amp; His Orchestra)" label="I`ll Walk Alone (Feat. Gordon Jenkins &amp; His Orchestra)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Indian_Love_Call/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Indian Love Call - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Indian_Love_Call/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Indian Love Call - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I'm calling you <br>Will you answer too <br><br>That means I offer my love to you to be my own <br>If you refuse me I will be blue and waiting all alone <br>But if when you hear my love call ringing clear <br>And I hear your answering echo so clear <br><br>Babe, then I will know our love will come true <br>You belong to me, I belong to you <br>You belong to me, I belong to you]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Indian Love Call" label="Indian Love Call"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Jeannine_I_Dream_Of_Lilac_Time/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Jeannine (I Dream Of Lilac Time) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Jeannine_I_Dream_Of_Lilac_Time/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Jeannine (I Dream Of Lilac Time) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jeannine, I dream of lilac time <br>Your eyes, they beam in the lilac time <br>Your winning smile <br>And cheeks blushing like the rose <br>Yet all the while, you sigh when nobody knows <br>Jeannine, my queen of lilac times <br>When I return, I'll make you mine <br>For you and I, our love dream can never die]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Jeannine (I Dream Of Lilac Time)" label="Jeannine (I Dream Of Lilac Time)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/Youre_The_Apple_Of_My_Eye/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - You`re The Apple Of My Eye - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/Youre_The_Apple_Of_My_Eye/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - You`re The Apple Of My Eye - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're the apple of my eye <br>You're luscious and you're sweet <br>You're the apple of my eye <br>You're sweet enough to eat <br><br>Now since we met <br>I always get that certain feeling <br>And furthermore I love you <br>For you're so appealing <br><br>You're the apple of my eye <br>Your kisses are delish <br>They're tastier, yeah, than homemade apple pie <br><br>I'll hang around your orchid <br>Till I win your heart <br>'Cause you're the only apple <br>In my apple cart <br><br>I'm gonna shake your tree <br>Until you fall for me <br>'Cause you're the apple of my eye <br><br>Now look here Velma <br>You know, you're the apple of my eye too, baby <br>You're luscious and you're sweet <br>You're the apple of my eye <br>You're sweet enough to eat <br><br>Now since we met <br>I always get that certain feelin' <br>Me too <br>And furthermore I love you <br>For you're so appealing <br>Sure <br><br>You're the apple of my eye <br>You're kisses are delish <br>They're tastier than a homemade apple pie <br><br>Now dig this Velma <br>Now speakin' of your history or so they say <br>If I ate an apple <br>That'd keep that old doctor away <br>You bad man <br><br>Gonna shake your tree <br>Until you fall for me <br>'Cause you're the apple of my eye <br>Hey pops, dig this <br><br>You're the apple of my eye <br>Apple of my eye <br><br>When Adam ate that apple <br>Darlin', I believe <br>That this is just exactly <br>What he said to Eve <br><br>Well dig this, pops, I'm gonna shake your tree <br>Yeah baby <br>Gal, look like you're tryin' to fall for me <br>'Cause you're apple of my eye]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars"/><category term="You`re The Apple Of My Eye" label="You`re The Apple Of My Eye"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Big_Butter_And_Eggman/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Big Butter And Eggman - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Big_Butter_And_Eggman/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Big Butter And Eggman - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Now she wants a butter and egg man <br>From way out in the West <br>She wants somebody who's workin' all day <br>So she's got money when she wants to play <br><br>Now pretty clothes, they'll never be mine <br>But what she told me the other day <br>I hope she don't change her mind <br><br>Now she wants a butter and egg man <br>A great big butter and egg man <br>From way down South]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Big Butter And Eggman" label="Big Butter And Eggman"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Necessary_Evil/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Necessary Evil - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Necessary_Evil/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Necessary Evil - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So I tried hard to be good <br>And do the things I should <br>I give up everything that I enjoyed <br>But if u slip abit <br>And ur heart says this is it <br>Thats a necessary evil my boy <br>All my friends say I'm a fool <br>And I won't break any rules <br>Why all the saintly virtues I employ <br>But if the slightest fling <br>Makes your soul begin to sing <br>That's a necessary evil, my boy <br>Well, a man sometime has to sip a drink <br>And cast his eyes on a lovely shape <br>Then, sometimes, a wager desires <br>If a man says he don't <br>He's not a man, he's a liar <br>So don't let yourself be sad <br>If what looks good is bad <br>Reach out accept the things that bring you joy <br>And so you feel inclined <br>It will help to keep in mind <br>Baby, that's a necessary evil <br>For a man sometime has to sip of the grape <br>Or cast his eye on a lovely shape <br>And then, sometimes, a wager desire <br>If a man says he don't <br>He's not a man, he's a liar <br>So dont let yourself be sad <br>If what looks good is bad <br>Reach out accept the things that bring you joy <br>A man has got to live <br>Even stealers make you give <br>That's a necessary evil <br>Absoultely necessary <br>A necessary evil my boy]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Necessary Evil" label="Necessary Evil"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/When_Its_Sleepy_Time_Down_South/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - When It`s Sleepy Time Down South - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:42:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:42:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/When_Its_Sleepy_Time_Down_South/" title="Louis_Armstrong - When It`s Sleepy Time Down South - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ah, the pale moon's shining the fields below <br>Dark is crooning songs soft and low <br>You needn't tell me, boy, because I know <br>It's sleepy time down south <br><br>And soft winds blowing through the pinewood trees <br>Folks down there live a life of ease <br>When old mammy falls upon her knees <br>It's sleepy time down south <br><br>Oh, steamboats on the river a coming, a going <br>Splashing the night away <br>You hear those banjos ringing, the dark is singing <br>They dance till the break of day <br><br>Dear old southland with his dreamy songs <br>Takes me back to the gallent John <br>Oh, how I'd love to hold her in my arms <br>When it's sleepy time way down, down south]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="When It`s Sleepy Time Down South" label="When It`s Sleepy Time Down South"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Its_All_In_The_Game_Feat_Gordon_Jenkins__His_Orchestra/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - It`s All In The Game (Feat. Gordon Jenkins &amp; His Orchestra) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Its_All_In_The_Game_Feat_Gordon_Jenkins__His_Orchestra/" title="Louis_Armstrong - It`s All In The Game (Feat. Gordon Jenkins &amp; His Orchestra) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Many a tear has to fall, but it's all in the game <br>All in the wonderful game that we know as love <br>You have words with him and your future's looking dim <br>But these things your hearts can rise above <br><br>Once in a while he won't call, but it's all in the game <br>Soon he'll be there at your side with a sweet bouquet <br>And he'll kiss your lips and caress your waiting fingertips <br>And your heart will fly away <br><br>Soon he'll be there at your side with a sweet bouquet <br>Then he'll kiss your lips and caress your waiting fingertips <br>And your heart will fly away]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="It`s All In The Game (Feat. Gordon Jenkins &amp; His Orchestra)" label="It`s All In The Game (Feat. Gordon Jenkins &amp; His Orchestra)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/Because_Of_You/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - Because Of You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/Because_Of_You/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - Because Of You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Because of you there's a song in my heart <br>Because of you my romance had its start <br>Because of you the sun will shine <br>The moon and stars will say you're mine <br>Forever and never to part <br><br>I only live for your love and your kiss <br>It's paradise to be near you like this <br>Because of you my life is now worthwhile <br>And I can smile <br>Because of you <br><br>I only live for your love and your kiss <br>It's paradise to be near you like this <br>Because of you my life is now worthwhile <br>And I can smile <br>Because of you]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra"/><category term="Because Of You" label="Because Of You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Cold_Cold_Heart/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Cold Cold Heart - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Cold_Cold_Heart/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Cold Cold Heart - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, yes, man, I tried so hard, my dear, to show that you're my every dream <br>Yet you're afraid each thing I do is just some evil scheme <br>A memory from your lonesome past keeps us so far apart <br>Why can't I free your doubtful mind and melt your cold, cold heart <br><br>Another love before my time made your heart sad and blue <br>And so my heart is paying now for things I didn't do, yes <br>In anger, unkind words are said that make the teardrops start <br>Why can't I free your doubtful mind and melt your cold, cold heart]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Cold Cold Heart" label="Cold Cold Heart"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/When_We_Are_Dancin_I_Get_Ideas/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - (When We Are Dancin`) I Get Ideas - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/When_We_Are_Dancin_I_Get_Ideas/" title="Louis_Armstrong - (When We Are Dancin`) I Get Ideas - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When we are dancing and you're dangerously near me <br>I get ideas, I get ideas <br>I want to hold you so much closer than I dare to <br>I want to scold you 'cause I care more than I care to <br><br>And when you touch me and there's fire in every finger <br>I get ideas, yes, I get ideas <br>And after we have kissed goodnight and still you linger <br>I kinda think you get ideas too <br><br>Your eyes are always saying the things you're never saying <br>I only hope they're saying that you could love me too <br>For that's the whole idea it's true <br>Lovely idea that I'm falling in love with you <br><br>And after we have kissed goodnight and still you linger <br>Babe, I kinda think you get ideas too]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="(When We Are Dancin`) I Get Ideas" label="(When We Are Dancin`) I Get Ideas"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/A_Kiss_To_Build_A_Dream_On/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - A Kiss To Build A Dream On - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/A_Kiss_To_Build_A_Dream_On/" title="Louis_Armstrong - A Kiss To Build A Dream On - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Give me a kiss to build a dream on <br>And my imagination will thrive upon that kiss <br>Sweetheart, I ask no more than this <br>A kiss to build a dream on <br><br>Give me a kiss before you leave me <br>And my imagination will feed my hungry heart <br>Leave me one thing before we part <br>A kiss to build a dream on <br><br>When I'm alone with my fancies, I'll be with you <br>Weaving romances, making believe they're true <br><br>Give me your lips for just a moment <br>And my imagination will make that moment live <br>Give me what you alone can give <br>A kiss to build a dream on]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="A Kiss To Build A Dream On" label="A Kiss To Build A Dream On"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Gone_Fishin/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Gone Fishin` - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Gone_Fishin/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Gone Fishin` - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll tell you why I can't find you <br>Every time I go out to your place <br><br>You gone fishin' well how you know <br>Well there's a sign upon your door uh huh <br>Gone fishin' I'm real gone man <br>You ain't workin' anymore could be <br>There's your hoe out in the sun <br>Where you left a row half done <br>You claim that hoein' ain't no fun well I can prove it <br>You ain't got no ambition <br><br>Gone fishin' by a shady wady pool shangrila, really la <br>I'm wishin' I could be that kind of fool should I twist your arm <br>I'd say no more work for mine welcome to the club <br>On my door I'd hang a sign <br>Gone fishin' instead of just a wishin' <br><br>Papa bing yeah louis <br>I stopped by your place a time or two lately <br>And you aren't home either <br>Well, I'm a busy man louis I got a lotta deals cookin' <br>I was probably tied up at the studio <br><br>You weren't tied up you dog <br>You was just plain old <br><br>Gone fishin' bah boo bah boo bah boo bah boo bah <br>There's a sign upon your door pops, don't blab it around, will you <br>Gone fishin' keep it shady, I got me a big one staked out <br>Mmm, you ain't workin' anymore I don't have to work, I got me a piece of gary <br>Cows need milkin' in the barn I have the twins on that detail, they each take a side <br>But you just don't give a darn give 'em four bits a cow and hand lotion <br>You just never seem to learn man, you taught me <br>You ain't got no ambition you're convincin' me <br><br>Gone fishin' bah boo dah do dah do dah do <br>Got your hound dog by your side that's old cindy lou goin' with me <br>Gone fishin' mmm hmm hmm hmm hmm <br>Fleas are bitin' at his hide get away from me boy, you bother me <br><br>Mmm, folks won't find us now because <br>Mister satch and mister cros <br>We gone fishin' instead of just a wishin' <br>Bah boo baby bah boo bah bay mmm bo bay <br>Oh yeah]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Gone Fishin`" label="Gone Fishin`"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Youre_Just_In_Love/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - You`re Just In Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Youre_Just_In_Love/" title="Louis_Armstrong - You`re Just In Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I hear singing and there's no one there <br>I smell blossoms and the trees are bare <br>All day long I seem to walk on air <br>I wonder why, I wonder why <br><br>Now, I keep tossing in my sleep at night <br>And what's more, I've lost my appetite <br>Stars that used to twinkle in the skies <br>Are twinkling in my eyes, I wonder why <br><br>Pops, you don't need no analyzin' , man <br>No <br>It is not so surprising <br>That you feel very strange but nice <br><br>Your heart goes pitter patter <br>Pops, I know what's the matter <br>Because I've been there once or twice <br><br>Put your head on my shoulder <br>You need someone who's older <br>A rubdown with a velvet glove <br><br>There is nothing you can take <br>To relieve that pleasant ache <br>You're not sick, man, you're in love <br><br>I hear singing and there's no one there <br>You don't need analyzin', it is not so surprising <br>I smell blossoms and the trees are bare <br>That you feel very strange but nice <br><br>All day long, I seem to walk on air <br>Your heart goes pitter patter, pops, I know what's the matter <br>I wonder why, I wonder why <br>Because I've been there once or twice <br><br>I keep tossing in my sleep at night <br>Keep your head on my shoulder, you need some chick who's older <br>A rubdown with a velvet glove <br>And what's more I've lost my appetite <br><br>Stars that used to twinkle in the skies <br>There is nothin' you can take to relieve that groovy ache <br>Are twinkling in my eyes, I wonder why <br>You're not sick, pops, you're in love <br><br>Whatcha mean I'm in love, honey <br>Dig yourself, dig yourself down <br>You heard me, you're not sick, man, you're in love <br>I'm in love]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="You`re Just In Love" label="You`re Just In Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Sit_Down_Youre_Rocking_The_Boat/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Sit Down, You`re Rocking The Boat - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Sit_Down_Youre_Rocking_The_Boat/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Sit Down, You`re Rocking The Boat - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Now look here don't be singin' that pretty music for me <br>I've learned my lesson and I ain't ready to go yet <br>Let me tell you all about it <br><br>I dreamed last night I got on the boat to Heaven <br>And by some chance I had brought my dice along <br>And there I stood, and I hollered, Someone fade me <br>But the passengers they knew right from wrong <br><br>For the people all said <br>Sit down, sit down you're rockin' the boat <br>And the people all said <br>Sit down, sit down you're rockin' the boat <br><br>And the devil will drag you under <br>By the sharp lapel of your checkered coat <br>Sit down, sit down <br>Sit down you're rocking the boat <br><br>Now I sailed away on that little boat to Heaven <br>And by some chance found a bottle in my fist <br>And there I stood nicely passin' out the whiskey <br>But the passengers were bound to resist <br><br>For the people all said <br>Beware, you are on a heavenly trip <br>People all said <br>Beware, beware you'll scuttle the ship <br><br>And the devil will drag you under <br>By the fancy tie 'round your wicked throat <br>Sit down, sit down <br>Sit down you're rockin' the boat <br><br>Now as I laughed at those passengers to Heaven <br>A great big wave came and washed me overboard <br>And as I sank, and I hollered, Someone save me <br>That's the moment I woke up, thank the Lord <br><br>And I said to myself <br>Sit down, sit down you're rockin' the boat <br>I said to myself <br>Sit down, sit down you're rockin' the boat <br><br>And the devil will drag you under <br>With a soul so heavy you'd never float <br>Sit down, sit down <br>Sit down you're rockin' the boat <br>Sit down you're rockin' the boat <br><br>Sit down you're rockin' the boat <br>And I ain't gonna rock it no more]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Sit Down, You`re Rocking The Boat" label="Sit Down, You`re Rocking The Boat"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/You_Rascal_You_Ill_Be_Glad_When_Youre_Dead/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - You Rascal You (I`ll Be Glad When You`re Dead) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/You_Rascal_You_Ill_Be_Glad_When_Youre_Dead/" title="Louis_Armstrong - You Rascal You (I`ll Be Glad When You`re Dead) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Now I'll be glad when you're dead, you rascal you, uh huh <br>I'll be glad when you're dead, you rascal you, oh yeah <br>Well I let into my home, you gonna leave my woman alone <br>I'll be glad when you're dead, you rascal you <br><br>Now I'll be glad when you die, you rascal you, uh huh <br>I'll be glad, oh I'll be tickled to death when you leave this earth it's true, oh yeah <br>When you're lyin' down six feet deep, no more fried chicken will you eat <br>I'll be glad when you're dead, you rascal you, oh yeah <br><br>Ah, you just ain't no good oh, you dog <br><br>Now listen here, I'll be glad when you're dead, you rascal you, uh huh <br>I'll be glad when you're dead, you rascal you, oh yeah <br>I'll be standin' on the corner high, when they drag your body by <br>I'll be glad when you're dead, you know I'm gonna be so happy when you're gone you dog <br>I'll be glad when you're dead, you rascal you]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="You Rascal You (I`ll Be Glad When You`re Dead)" label="You Rascal You (I`ll Be Glad When You`re Dead)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Can_Anyone_Explain_/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Can Anyone Explain? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Can_Anyone_Explain_/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Can Anyone Explain? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Can anyone explain the thrill of a kiss <br>No No No <br>But when two eager lips are pressed against yours <br>You'll know, yes, you'll know <br><br>Can anyone explain the glow of romance <br>No No No <br>But when you hear the phrase It's you I adore <br>You'll know, yes, you'll know <br><br>And you will find, to give love a start <br>Don't think with your mind just feel with your heart <br><br>Can anyone explain the wonder of love <br>No No No <br>But now that you and I are sharing a sigh <br>We know, yes, we know <br><br>And you will find, to give love a start <br>Don't think with your mind just feel with your heart <br><br>Can anyone explain the wonder of love <br>No No No <br>But now that you and I are sharing a sigh <br>We know, yes, we know]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Can Anyone Explain?" label="Can Anyone Explain?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Dream_A_Little_Dream_Of_Me/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - Dream A Little Dream Of Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Dream_A_Little_Dream_Of_Me/" title="Louis_Armstrong - Dream A Little Dream Of Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stars shining bright above you <br>Night breezes seem to whisper I love you <br>Birds singing in the sycamore tree <br>Dream a little dream of me <br><br>Say Nighty night and kiss me <br>Just hold me tight and tell me you'll miss me <br>While I'm alone and blue as can be <br>Dream a little dream of me <br><br>Stars fading but I linger on dear <br>Oh how you linger on <br>Still craving your kiss <br>How you crave my kiss <br><br>Now I'm longin' to linger till dawn dear <br>Just saying this <br><br>Give me a little kiss <br><br>Sweet dreams till sunbeams find you <br>Sweet dreams that leave all worries behind you <br>But in your dreams, whatever they be <br>Dream a little dream of me <br><br>Stars fading but I linger on dear <br>Still craving your kiss <br>Yeah, I'm longing to linger till dawn dear <br>Just saying this, yes <br><br>Sweet dreams <br>Dreamin' <br><br>Till sunbeams find you <br>Keep dreaming <br><br>Gotta keep dreamin' <br><br>Leave your worries far behind you <br>But in your dreams, whatever they be <br><br>You gotta make me a promise <br>Promise to me you'll dream <br>Dream a little dream of me]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Dream A Little Dream Of Me" label="Dream A Little Dream Of Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Cest_Si_Bon_Its_So_Good/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong - C`est Si Bon (It`s So Good) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Cest_Si_Bon_Its_So_Good/" title="Louis_Armstrong - C`est Si Bon (It`s So Good) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[C'est si bon it's so good <br><br>De <br>Com <br><br>C'est si bon <br>Lovers say that in france <br>When they thrill to romance <br>It means that it's so good <br>C'est si bon <br>So I say to you <br>Like the french people do <br><br>Because it's oh so good <br>Every word, every sigh, every kiss, dear <br>Leads to only one thought <br>And the thought is this, dear <br>C'est si bon <br>Nothing else can replace <br>Just your slyest embrace <br>And if you only would <br>Be my own for the rest of my days <br>I will whisper this phrase <br>My darling, my darling <br>C'est si bon]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="C`est Si Bon (It`s So Good)" label="C`est Si Bon (It`s So Good)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/La_Vie_En_Rose/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - La Vie En Rose - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra/La_Vie_En_Rose/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_Orchestra - La Vie En Rose - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hold me close and hold me fast <br>The magic spell you cast <br>This is la vie en rose <br>When you kiss me heaven sighs <br>And though I close my eyes <br>I see la vie en rose <br>When you press me to your heart <br>I'm in a world apart <br>A world where roses bloom <br>And when you speak <br>Angels sing from above <br>Everyday words seems <br>To turn into love song <br>Give your heart and soul to me <br>And life will always be la vie en rose]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His Orchestra"/><category term="La Vie En Rose" label="La Vie En Rose"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/My_Buckets_Got_A_Hole_In_It/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - My Bucket`s Got A Hole In It - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/My_Buckets_Got_A_Hole_In_It/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - My Bucket`s Got A Hole In It - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, the bucket's got a hole in it <br>Hmm, the bucket's got a hole in it <br>The bucket's got a hole in it <br>And we can't buy no more beer <br><br>I said the bucket's got a hole in it <br>It's too bad, the bucket's got a hole in it <br>Yeah, man, the bucket's got a hole in it <br>Somebody better run <br><br>It's after hours and you can't get in <br>It's after hours and you can't get in <br>We close at nine and now it's half past ten <br>Oh honey would you]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars"/><category term="My Bucket`s Got A Hole In It" label="My Bucket`s Got A Hole In It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/Fine_And_Dandy/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - Fine And Dandy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/Fine_And_Dandy/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - Fine And Dandy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Please forgive this platitude <br>But I like your attitude <br>You are just the kind I've had in mind <br>Never could find <br><br>Honey, I'm so keen on you <br>I could come to lean on you <br>On a random bay, give you your way <br>Do what you say <br><br>Gee, it's all fine and dandy <br>Sugar candy, when I've got you <br><br>Then I only see the sunny side <br>Even trouble has it's funny side <br>When you're gone, my sugar candy <br>I get so lonesome, I get blue <br><br>But when you're handy <br>It's fine and dandy <br>But when you're gone <br>What can I do]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars"/><category term="Fine And Dandy" label="Fine And Dandy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/Baby_Wont_You_Please_Come_Home/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - Baby, Won`t You Please Come Home - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/Baby_Wont_You_Please_Come_Home/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - Baby, Won`t You Please Come Home - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've got the blues, I feel so lonely <br>I'd give the world if I could only <br>Make you understand <br>It truly would be grand <br>I'm gonna telephone my baby <br>Ask him won't you please come home <br>Oh, when you gone <br>I'm worried all day long <br>Baby, won't you please come home <br>Baby, won't you please come home <br>I have tried in vain <br>Nevermore to call your name <br>When you left you broke my heart <br>That will never make us part <br>Every hour in the day <br>You will hear me say <br>Baby, won't you please come home <br>I mean, baby, won't you please come home <br>Baby, won't you please come home <br>'Cause your mama's all alone <br>I have tried in vain <br>Nevermore to call your name <br>When you left you broke my heart <br>That will never make us part <br>Landlord's gettin' worse <br>I gotta move May the first <br>Baby, won't you please come home <br>I need money <br>Baby, won't you please come home]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars"/><category term="Baby, Won`t You Please Come Home" label="Baby, Won`t You Please Come Home"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/Russian_Lullaby/</id><title>Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - Russian Lullaby - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T14:43:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T14:43:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars/Russian_Lullaby/" title="Louis_Armstrong__His_All-Stars - Russian Lullaby - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Where the dreamy Volga flows <br>There's a lonely Russian rose <br>Gazing tenderly <br>Down upon her knee <br>Where a baby's brown eyes glisten <br>Listen <br><br>Every night you'll hear her croon <br>A Russian lullaby <br>Just a little plaintive tune <br>When baby starts to cry <br><br>Rock a bye, my baby <br>Somewhere there may be <br>A land that's free for you and me <br>And a Russian lullaby]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars" label="Louis Armstrong &amp; His All-Stars"/><category term="Russian Lullaby" label="Russian Lullaby"/></entry></feed>