<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:32:47+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trevor_트레버/Good_Hood_Feat_장현지/</id><title>Trevor_트레버 - Good Hood (Feat. 장현지) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:52:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:52:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trevor_%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EB%B2%84/Good_Hood_Feat_%EC%9E%A5%ED%98%84%EC%A7%80/" title="Trevor_트레버 - Good Hood (Feat. 장현지) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지하철을 탈까나 <br>버스를 탈까나 <br>무엇이던 what ever ok <br>its a good hood there <br>나른한 오후 1시 <br>작은 카페에서 <br>한잔하는 아이스티는 <br>유난히 달아 <br>So sweet <br>니 목소리처럼 달아서 <br>심장이 반응하잖아 <br>이건 확실한 타이밍 <br>바로 전화를 꺼내 <br>너에게 calling <br>오늘은 특별한 <br>날이 될거야 ma babe <br>난 보여주고 싶어 new world <br>그 중심엔 니가 있어 <br>ill tell you somethin cool <br>Righ good girl good girl <br>내 머리 속은 <br>전부 너뿐이란 걸 <br>기분이 좋아져 <br>웃음이 나오네 <br>바라만 봐도 <br>세상 다가진 것 같은데 <br>yeah Just you and me <br>우리 단둘이 <br>어디든 가보자고 <br>멀리 보이는 view <br>손을 잡고 슝 <br>잊을 수 없어 never ever <br>햇살에 비친 너의 눈빛이 <br>내게 말해 <br>난 너만 있으면 해 <br>boy only you <br>너와 함께라면 <br>그곳은 파라다이스 <br>I can say it too now <br>want you now <br>곁에 있어줘 <br>닫혀있던 문을 열고서 <br>move it now <br>저 거리 옆에 <br>나무와 빌딩들 사이 <br>행복이라는 공간 <br>만들어가자고 <br>같이 돌아보면 어때 <br>돈으로 매길 순 없어 <br>girl 아님 잠시만 <br>눈을 감아봐 그 앞에 <br>모든 것이 나타나 <br>멀리 보이는 view <br>손을 잡고 슝 <br>구름 뒤에서 <br>떠오르는 무지개 ha <br>paris oasis 보다도 완벽해 <br>we call it here a good hood <br>햇살에 비친 너의 눈빛이 <br>내게 말해 <br>난 너만 있으면 해 <br>boy only you <br>너와 함께라면 <br>그곳은 파라다이스 <br>I can say it too now <br>바람에 몸을 맡겨 <br>천천히 걸어 <br>발자국을 남겨 <br>파란 하늘 <br>별들 아래서 <br>간직할게 memories 영원히 <br>la la la la la <br>never ever <br>la la la la la <br>never ever <br>la la la la la <br>Good Hood 여긴 마치 천국 <br>미소 짓고 있는 너와나 <br>yeah just you and me <br>우리 단둘이 <br>어디든 가보자고 <br>멀리 보이는 view <br>손을 잡고 슝 <br>잊을 수 없어 never ever <br>yeah 멀리 보이는 <br>view 손을 잡고 슝 <br>구름 뒤에서 <br>떠오르는 무지개 ha <br>paris oasis <br>보다도 완벽해 <br>we call it here a good hood <br>햇살에 비친 너의 눈빛이 <br>내게 말해 <br>난 너만 있으면 해 <br>boy only you <br>너와 함께라면 <br>그곳은 파라다이스 <br>]]></content><category term="Trevor (트레버)" label="Trevor (트레버)"/><category term="Good Hood (Feat. 장현지)" label="Good Hood (Feat. 장현지)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조한민/두번째_나의_삶/</id><title>조한민 - 두번째 나의 삶 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:54:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:54:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%ED%95%9C%EB%AF%BC/%EB%91%90%EB%B2%88%EC%A7%B8_%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%82%B6/" title="조한민 - 두번째 나의 삶 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다시 태어난걸요 <br>당신의 사랑으로 <br>난 새 삶을 얻었죠 <br>이미 죽어있던 나에게 <br>생명의 기쁨과 <br>소망을 주었죠 <br>처음 나를 만나 주었던 <br>그 날을 기억해 <br>뜨거웠던 눈물 <br>따스한 손길 <br>포기 않고 바라보신 <br>그 사랑 때문에 <br>다시 찾은 <br>두번 째 나의 삶 <br>내게 희망없던 삶인데 <br>변함없이 찾아와 <br>내 맘을 위로해 <br>이젠 떠나지 않을께요 <br>주만 의지하면서 <br>주님 곁에서 <br>처음 나를 만나 주었던 <br>그 날을 기억해 <br>뜨거웠던 눈물 <br>따스한 손길 <br>포기 않고 바라보신 <br>그 사랑 때문에 <br>다시 찾은 <br>두번 째 나의 삶 <br>처음 나를 만나 주었던 <br>그 날을 기억해 <br>뜨거웠던 눈물 <br>따스한 손길 <br>포기 않고 바라보신 <br>그 사랑 때문에 <br>다시 찾은 <br>두번 째 나의 삶 <br>이것이 바로 <br>주님 주신 내 삶 <br>]]></content><category term="조한민" label="조한민"/><category term="두번째 나의 삶" label="두번째 나의 삶"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이현주/그랬잖아/</id><title>이현주 - 그랬잖아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:54:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:54:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%98%84%EC%A3%BC/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%AC%EC%9E%96%EC%95%84/" title="이현주 - 그랬잖아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그냥 가지그랬니 <br>아무말도 하지말고 <br>웃으면서 인사하는 <br>니 모습에 <br>괜히 니가 미웠어 <br>태연한척 너를 <br>보려해봐도 안돼 <br>자꾸만 눈물이 <br>날 것 같아서 <br>아무렇지 않은척 <br>뒤돌아 가려해봐도 <br>니가 없는 내일이 <br>아직 자신이 없어 <br>사랑한다고 <br>내게 말했잖아 <br>나 아니면 안된다고 <br>보고싶다 말했잖아 <br>미안하다는 그런말은 <br>안해도되니까 <br>다시 돌아와 기다리는 <br>나를 안아줘 <br>그냥 아프다말할걸 <br>그랬어 괜히 <br>솔직히 말할걸 <br>보고싶었다고 <br>아무렇지 않은척 <br>뒤돌아 가려해봐도 <br>니가 없는 오늘을 <br>버틸 자신이없어 <br>사랑한다고 <br>내게 말했잖아 <br>나 아니면 안된다고 <br>보고싶다 말했잖아 <br>미안하다는 그런말은 <br>안해도되니까 <br>다시 돌아와 기다리는 <br>나를 안아줘 <br>해도 안되는게 있나봐 <br>널 잊는게 안돼 <br>기다리면 <br>니가 올것만 같은데 <br>사랑한다고 <br>아직 아니라고 <br>너 아니면 안된다고 <br>보고싶다 말해봐도 <br>대답없는널 부르고 <br>또 다시 불러본다 <br>제발 돌아와 기다리는 <br>나를 안아줘 <br>]]></content><category term="이현주" label="이현주"/><category term="그랬잖아" label="그랬잖아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/라엘_RaL/기억을_지워줘요/</id><title>라엘_RaL - 기억을 지워줘요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:54:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:54:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9D%BC%EC%97%98_RaL/%EA%B8%B0%EC%96%B5%EC%9D%84_%EC%A7%80%EC%9B%8C%EC%A4%98%EC%9A%94/" title="라엘_RaL - 기억을 지워줘요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아침이 오면 무거운 눈꺼풀 <br>쉽게 잘 떠지지가 않어 <br>하루 온종일 아른거리는 너 <br>So baby i be movin' on <br>i gotta go 네가 없는 곳으로 <br>누가 좀 지워줘요 <br>아프게 새겨진 우리 추억을 <br>i wanna run 도망치고 싶어 <br>기억을 지워줘요 <br>아무일 없었던 것처럼 <br>Runaway Runaway Runaway <br>아무생각없이 달리면 <br>괜찮아질거야 <br>Runaway Runaway Runaway <br>자꾸 떠올라 <br>잘 해주지 못해서 이제야 <br>미안함이 남아 <br>조각나버린 유리조각처럼 <br>다시는 붙을 수 없어 <br>i gotta go <br>네가 없는 곳으로 <br>누가 좀 지워줘요 <br>아프게 새겨진 우리 추억을 <br>i wanna run <br>도망치고 싶어 <br>기억을 지워줘요 <br>아무일 없었던 것처럼 <br>Runaway Runaway Runaway <br>아무생각없이 달리면 <br>괜찮아질거야 <br>Runaway Runaway Runaway <br>Yeah Yeah yeah <br>i gotta go <br>네가 없는 곳으로 <br>누가 좀 지워줘요 <br>아프게 새겨진 우리 추억을 <br>i wanna run <br>도망치고 싶어 <br>기억을 지워줘요 <br>아무일 없었던 것처럼 <br>Runaway Runaway Runaway <br>아무생각없이 달리면 <br>괜찮아질거야 <br>Runaway Runaway Runaway <br>Yeah Yeah yeah <br>Runaway <br>Runaway <br>Yeah Yeah yeah <br>]]></content><category term="라엘 (Ra.L)" label="라엘 (Ra.L)"/><category term="기억을 지워줘요" label="기억을 지워줘요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/삼부자_The_Three_Rich/</id><title>Odee - 삼부자 (The Three Rich) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/%EC%82%BC%EB%B6%80%EC%9E%90_The_Three_Rich/" title="Odee - 삼부자 (The Three Rich) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘의 점심값 해결하는 돈 <br>낡아빠진 신발의 밑창을 가는 돈 <br>벌기 위해 작업실로 가는 지하철 <br>타는 차빌 충전하기 <br>위해서 버는 돈 <br>친구들과의 술자리에서 한 번쯤 <br>가오 상하지 않게 <br>한턱 낼 수 있는 돈 <br>신용카드 저번 달에 <br>얼마를 썼는지 <br>계산할 필요 없이 <br>긁어댈 수 있는 돈 <br>들어오면 통장에 냄새만 묻혀 <br>맛까지 보기 위해 벌어야 해 큰 돈 <br>아침에 나가 중고차 <br>파시는 아버지 <br>들어올 땐 외제차 타게 하는 큰 돈 <br>우리 삼부잔 돼야 해 three rich <br>집세 걱정 없이 정착할 수 있는 돈 <br>그 전에 얹혀 살고 있는 나부터 <br>버기 형의 집 벗어날 <br>보증금이 먼저 <br>뭉칫돈 혹은 수표 지갑에 <br>명함 대신 꽉 차게 넣고 <br>뭉칫돈 혹은 수표 지갑에 <br>명함 대신 꽉 차게 넣고 <br>내 뒷주머니에다 꽂아 넣기 <br>내 뒷주머니에다 꽂아 넣기 <br>내 뒷주머니에다 꽂아 넣기 <br>내 뒷주머니에다 꽂아 넣기 <br>힘들 만큼 벌어 <br>제주도에 별장을 하나 세워 줘 <br>Porsche 차 키를 손에 쥐어 줘 <br>아버지와 형이 가끔 하는 농담 <br>이뤄야 될 목록에 <br>지나치지 않고 적어둬 <br>내가 휴학 면담을 할 때 <br>대학교순 말해 <br>그거 해서 얼마 벌게 <br>똑같이 반응하던 나의 친구새낀 <br>이제 밥 사라며 <br>학생이라 돈이 없대 <br>ay 난 그들 앞에선 더 여유부리고 <br>택시에선 미터기 <br>대신 창밖에 눈을 둬 <br>수입으로 날 견적 내는 시선 <br>이미 고른 치아에 <br>교정기를 끼고 보여줘 <br>있게 태어난 놈들 안 부럽게 <br>종로에 가서 맞춰볼 거야 <br>금수저 세트 <br>돈 없을 때 걱정하는 말들 <br>내 머리 위에서 못하게 <br>나대로 get money <br>뭉칫돈 혹은 수표 지갑에 <br>명함 대신 꽉 차게 넣고 <br>뭉칫돈 혹은 수표 지갑에 <br>명함 대신 꽉 차게 넣고 <br>내 뒷주머니에다 꽂아 넣기 <br>내 뒷주머니에다 꽂아 넣기 <br>내 뒷주머니에다 꽂아 넣기 <br>내 뒷주머니에다 꽂아 넣기 <br>힘들 만큼 벌어 <br>]]></content><category term="Odee" label="Odee"/><category term="삼부자 (The Three Rich)" label="삼부자 (The Three Rich)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/Deja_Vu/</id><title>Odee - Deja Vu - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/Deja_Vu/" title="Odee - Deja Vu - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[익숙한 이 장면 Deja vu ay ay ay <br>머리를 잠시 스쳐갈 뿐 ay ay ay <br>언제 그랬냐는 듯 반복 ay ay ay <br>내일은 오늘의 Deja vu ay ay ay <br>히야시가 된 소주 <br>Marlboro white menthol <br>한잔에 다음 챕턴 <br>한 모금에 다음 행동 <br>저기 여자에겐 헬로 <br>재도전할 확률 백프로 <br>저번에도 계산 쨌던 사람들 <br>항상 똑같은 패턴 <br>클럽 안엔 올 때마다 봤던 애 <br>쟤도 나와 똑같은 반응이지 <br>DJ는 익숙함을 거들지 <br>데낄라에 레몬 얹듯이 <br>늘 서있던 곳에 자리하고 <br>새로운 상황에 얼굴을 찾어 <br>누군가 주는 한 잔을 받고 <br>또 기억의 편집점 다시 잡어 <br>집에서 눈떠 끊겨있던 <br>film을 트는 이유 <br>여자친구의 부재중 기록 <br>이따 걸게 술이 좀 더 깬 뒤로 <br>이번엔 다를 줄 알았지 <br>란 기대감에 반비례하지 <br>이걸 되풀이 할 시간에 <br>차라리 작업이나 하러 가지 <br>익숙한 이 장면 Deja vu ay ay ay <br>머리를 잠시 스쳐갈 뿐 ay ay ay <br>언제 그랬냐는 듯 반복 ay ay ay <br>내일은 오늘의 Deja vu ay ay ay <br>익숙한 이 장면 Deja vu ay ay ay <br>머리를 잠시 스쳐갈 뿐 ay ay ay <br>언제 그랬냐는 듯 반복 ay ay ay <br>내일은 오늘의 Deja vu ay ay ay <br>해 떨어졌어 난 어김없이 <br>습관처럼 나왔지 작업실 <br>가족은 매일 보는 거지 <br>형들과는 어떤 감정 없이 <br>인사하고 방에 불을 켜 <br>각자의 매뉴얼이 도는 거지 <br>오늘의 신보는 뭐가 <br>나왔는질 확인해 <br>영감의 창구는 반복된 <br>삶에서 아주 좁기에 <br>쥐어짰었던 머릴 적시지 <br>내 어제 쓰던 가사를 엎지 <br>다시 몇 마디 뭔가 적지 <br>마른 순간 다시 머릴 쥐었지 <br>필요해 난 brainwave <br>밖에 나감 얻겠지 쉽게 <br>기대돼 새로운 게 <br>이번 주말엔 뭔가 있겠지 ay <br>익숙한 이 장면 Deja vu ay ay ay <br>머리를 잠시 스쳐갈 뿐 ay ay ay <br>언제 그랬냐는 듯 반복 ay ay ay <br>내일은 오늘의 Deja vu ay ay ay <br>익숙한 이 장면 Deja vu ay ay ay <br>머리를 잠시 스쳐갈 뿐 ay ay ay <br>언제 그랬냐는 듯 반복 ay ay ay <br>내일은 오늘의 Deja vu ay ay ay <br>]]></content><category term="Odee" label="Odee"/><category term="Deja Vu" label="Deja Vu"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/John_Doe/</id><title>Odee - John Doe - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/John_Doe/" title="Odee - John Doe - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[전활 걸어 받지 않겠지 <br>엄마의 번호 <br>난 잘하고 있는가를 <br>묻기엔 어려워 <br>내 맘대로 하는 <br>행동에 대한 내 변호 <br>참견 말어 나의 <br>가족이 아니라면 <br>몇 년 전엔 노가다로 <br>벌고 받았던 pay <br>그걸로 며칠을 어떻게 <br>버틸지만 생각해 <br>그때 내 친군 말해 <br>쉽게 쓰고 쉽게 버는 게 <br>답인걸 알게 해줬고 <br>변했지 모든 게 <br>yeah 그래서 남김 없는 장산 안 해 <br>yeah 그래서 형들과 내게 투잘 해 <br>yeah 그래서 나잇값을 <br>지불하지 못하게 된 <br>네 삶의 반대로 내가 남게 <br>내가 살 인생에 repost는 안 받어 <br>현실의 feed 주인공인 날 빨어 <br>난 허비한 3년 동안에 <br>널 올려놨으니 <br>내 버린 시간을 먹고 <br>큰 대가릴 박어 <br>코 묻은 돈 삥 뜯을 음악 안 만들어 <br>끈적한 손 건네 악수하는 <br>넌 참 낯뜨거 <br>목 디스크 걸릴 정도의 <br>gold chain을 걸 때에 <br>내 무게감 가볍담 입을 다물어 <br>자기만족은 걸렀어 <br>그 감각은 나의 한계를 긋는 결론 <br>남들은 제자린데 <br>난 조바심 느껴서 <br>근거 없이 내게 채찍질을 즐겨 <br>결국 술잔엔 비싼 <br>성공 따를 거야 차고 넘쳐 <br>항상 취해있을 만큼 입에 털어 <br>대신 난 너희들이 늘 빠는 <br>좆같은 hustler는 안 될 거야 <br>잔만 채우려거든 술잔을 엎어 <br>Fuck you 넌 내 열등감이 못돼 <br>너의 자극은 발을 <br>지압하는데 보태 <br>경쟁은 방송을 <br>나가느냐를 전제해 <br>좆 까 넌 나보다 못하던데 <br>꿀 빠네 motherfuckers <br>내가 죽으면 저기 <br>Youtube에다 묻어줘 <br>곱게 남게 될 걸 아마도 <br>나는 곧 죽어도 관에 <br>날개를 달은 채로 <br>I'm on flying coffin <br>요샌 본능이 존나 꼴린 대로 한 척 <br>다 뒤에선 계산기를 뒀지 <br>ayo motherfuckers <br>의심병이 돌지만 <br>어차피 솔직한 놈은 없지 <br>나에게만큼 확신을 가져 <br>앞날이 어둡게 와도 <br>누구 조명을 받아서 <br>반짝하긴 싫다고 <br>내가 밤새 하는 작업 <br>매일 피곤함에 속아서 <br>아무것도 못 하고 가도 <br>매번 다시 나오지 <br>go hard 쉴 때 빠는 니코틴 <br>작업이 끝나고 먹는 <br>술을 또 넘기지 <br>여기다 쓴 맛을 보는 걸 <br>끝내놓기 위해서 일하지 <br>거창하게 난 행복을 좇지 <br>내 볼일은 많아 <br>올린 지펄 다시 내려 <br>앨범과 집안일 <br>머리가 복잡한 새벽 <br>얼마나 좋은 음악 <br>누가 만들어 냈건 <br>신경 쓰자니 해야 되지 내 걸 <br>어떻게든 되겠지 뭐 난 잘못이 <br>붙기 이전에 알았지 제대로 난 놈 <br>내가 원하는 결과는 <br>저기 영화 같은 삶보다 <br>삶이 영화가 되는 그 장면 <br>]]></content><category term="Odee" label="Odee"/><category term="John Doe" label="John Doe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/Drop_Feat_넉살/</id><title>Odee - Drop (Feat. 넉살) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/Drop_Feat_%EB%84%89%EC%82%B4/" title="Odee - Drop (Feat. 넉살) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주변의 관심 알겠어 <br>잠시 쉬게 좀 끊어봐 <br>ay drop <br>그만 내 바짓가랑일 <br>잡지 손떼 떨어져봐 <br>ay drop <br>주변의 관심 알겠어 <br>잠시 쉬게 좀 끊어봐 <br>ay drop <br>그만 내 바짓가랑일 <br>잡지 손떼 떨어져봐 <br>ay drop <br>스무 살에 Newera는 <br>갖다 던졌어 <br>내게 맞는 분수란 건 <br>따로 없어 <br>장래희망 놈팽이가 <br>나의 목표 <br>내 방 침대는 Ace <br>누워 두 발 뻗고 <br>그래 무대는 <br>내 침대 나도 Ace <br>관객들 벌써 <br>날 닮은 애 있어 <br>난 깔끔하게 하고 <br>가니까 죽지 않아 <br>Eazy-E 눈을 감아도 <br>선명한 이미지 <br>선명한 일이지 <br>싫은 일 편식해도 <br>균형 잃을 일은 없는 게 <br>니가 써놓은 버킷리스트 <br>아무 일도 일어나지 않을 <br>양동일 난 뒤집을게 <br>저기 뒷짐지고 걷는 꼰대들 <br>다 꽁해있어 돈벌이는 no <br>오동통 살찐 오동호 <br>내게 귀띔해 줬지 <br>쟤네 다 좆 됐어 형 <br>쟤네만 보면 한숨 <br>날 의심했어 공황장애 <br>지금 나의 건강이 <br>안 좋지 니들 덕에 <br>화병이 도졌지 <br>풀어야지 음악에 <br>내 통장을 차게 <br>만들어 탈이 나게 <br>미안 우리 덕에 너흰 <br>배알이 진정해 워워 <br>불안해 보이는 <br>네 친구는 배 탔지 <br>잘 살길 빌어 묵념 drop <br>주변의 관심 알겠어 <br>잠시 쉬게 좀 끊어봐 <br>ay drop <br>그만 내 바짓가랑일 <br>잡지 손떼 떨어져봐 <br>ay drop <br>주변의 관심 알겠어 <br>잠시 쉬게 좀 끊어봐 <br>ay drop <br>그만 내 바짓가랑일 <br>잡지 손떼 떨어져봐 <br>ay drop <br>쉬고 올라가게 쉬고 <br>올라가게 쉬고 올라가게 <br>ay drop <br>쉬고 올라가게 쉬고 <br>올라가게 쉬고 올라가게 <br>ay drop <br>쉬고 올라가게 쉬고 <br>올라가게 쉬고 올라가게 <br>ay drop <br>쉬고 올라가게 쉬고 <br>올라가게 쉬고 올라가게 <br>ay drop <br>profit profit 우린 <br>돈을 벌어야 해 <br>오디는 당차게 <br>술값을 카운터에 drop it <br>우리 팀에도 이제 <br>결혼할 사람 있어 <br>불가리로 가는 <br>신혼카는 역시 Bugatti <br>hey 매일 해 매일 일내 <br>끝까지 떨어졌다 튕김 <br>다시 올라와 매진해 <br>공연 매진돼 <br>SLY는 앨범이름 <br>성공은 닉네임 <br>나의 대가린 더 커가지 <br>누가됐건 대들 수 <br>있게끔 준빌 하지 <br>여든까진 못고칠 내 습관 <br>남의 떡까지 도벽 <br>다 내 걸로 봐야지 <br>덜 떨어진 새끼들 <br>제대로 떨궈 <br>잡고 있는 동아줄을 썩히고 <br>내 몫을 해 one coin clear <br>한몫하고 싶다면 줄 서 <br>차롈 지켜 내 뒤로 <br>질투와 시기는 <br>우리에게 uh <br>우린 몸에 해로운 걸 <br>많이 잡숴 <br>그것보다 안 좋은 건 <br>네가 rapper <br>왜 rapper 집에 가라 <br>써줄게 롤링페이퍼 <br>Paper workin <br>거기에서 멈춘 애들은 <br>대기실을 집에 drop it <br>hot shit 공연은 식은 죽 먹기 <br>죽이 맞는 형제와 같이 <br>주변의 관심 알겠어 <br>잠시 쉬게 좀 끊어봐 <br>ay drop <br>그만 내 바짓가랑일 <br>잡지 손떼 떨어져봐 <br>ay drop <br>주변의 관심 알겠어 <br>잠시 쉬게 좀 끊어봐 <br>ay drop <br>그만 내 바짓가랑일 <br>잡지 손떼 떨어져봐 <br>ay drop <br>쉬고 올라가게 쉬고 <br>올라가게 쉬고 올라가게 <br>ay drop <br>쉬고 올라가게 쉬고 <br>올라가게 쉬고 올라가게 <br>ay drop <br>쉬고 올라가게 쉬고 <br>올라가게 쉬고 올라가게 <br>ay drop <br>쉬고 올라가게 쉬고 <br>올라가게 쉬고 올라가게 <br>ay drop <br>]]></content><category term="Odee" label="Odee"/><category term="Drop (Feat. 넉살)" label="Drop (Feat. 넉살)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/SLY_Still_Look_Young_Feat_화지/</id><title>Odee - S.L.Y. (Still Look Young) (Feat. 화지) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/SLY_Still_Look_Young_Feat_%ED%99%94%EC%A7%80/" title="Odee - S.L.Y. (Still Look Young) (Feat. 화지) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[머리가 큰 만큼 <br>꽉 찬 걱정 <br>빠개지기 전 내 상태 <br>ay 다 내 알 바 아니지 <br>난 이젠 매일이 <br>파티여야 해 <br>어떤 것이 더 무겁고 <br>중요한 일인지 <br>저울질하며 살던 <br>난 어렸고 지금도 어려 <br>스물다섯이란 나이 <br>진지 빨긴 아직 가벼워 <br>복잡한 정신은 <br>클럽 보관함에 <br>취하고 살아야지 <br>일 아닌 한라산에 <br>가사 대신 써야지 <br>몸뚱일 하루 종일 <br>쥐어야지 내 손에 <br>여자들의 엉덩일 <br>한량이란 단어에 <br>젊음을 씌웠네 <br>지금 이거야 <br>내가 쌓고 싶은 경험치 <br>원하는 삶 속에 <br>나는 어떨지 <br>안정감이 없는 <br>모험에 늘 겁먹지만 <br>This is the way <br>how I wanna live <br>따지고 사는 <br>내게서 멀리 떨어진 <br>난 이렇게 사는 <br>내 모습을 담아 <br>얼마 안 남은 <br>내 젊음은 짧아 <br>돈 보다는 돈으로 <br>펼 수 있는 모든 환상 <br>난 안 가려 <br>이 몸 성할 때 <br>노는 게 좌우명 <br>너도 같다면 반가워 <br>yo let's get it <br>yo let's get it <br>yo let's get it <br>yo let's get it <br>yo let's get it 수단 안 가려 <br>정승처럼 벌어 <br>개처럼 쓰는 우리 같은 <br>너네 yo 반가워 <br>짊어질 건 많고 <br>계속 들기엔 버거워 <br>뇌의 주름을 펴 <br>골 아픈 생각 비웠어 <br>뭔갈 안 하고 <br>논다는 불안함도 <br>꼬신 여자와 잘 수 <br>있을까에다 돌렸어 <br>내 꿈이 무슨 위인도 아니고 <br>뭐 대단한 일 있냐 <br>걱정은 비워 <br>이도 저도 아니던 <br>내 모습보다 <br>한심한 놈이 가만있는 <br>것보단 차라리 나아 <br>위치에 따라서 <br>차등분배 되는 여유로움 <br>1등석에 앉는 <br>순간은 가까워져도 <br>앞일에 시선을 놓자니 <br>내겐 오늘이 보이지 않네 <br>씨발 그럼 다 뭔 소용이지 <br>내 나이 앞에 유통기한 <br>기분 상하지 않게 <br>걍 지나치진 마 <br>지루한 일상처럼 <br>돌던 보일러도 껐어 <br>좆대로 하기 <br>딱 좋은 날씨니까 <br>everyday must be be <br>party for me <br>everyday must be be <br>party for me <br>everyday must be be <br>party for me <br>나중 일은 지금 없으니까 <br>everyday must be be <br>party for me <br>everyday must be be <br>party for me <br>everyday must be be <br>party for me <br>될 놈은 알아서 될 테니까 <br>돈 보다는 돈으로 <br>펼 수 있는 모든 환상 <br>난 안 가려 <br>이 몸 성할 때 <br>노는 게 좌우명 <br>너도 같다면 반가워 <br>yo let's get it <br>yo let's get it <br>yo let's get it <br>yo let's get it <br>yo let's get it 수단 안 가려 <br>정승처럼 벌어 <br>개처럼 쓰는 우리 같은 <br>너네 yo 반가워 <br>]]></content><category term="Odee" label="Odee"/><category term="S.L.Y. (Still Look Young) (Feat. 화지)" label="S.L.Y. (Still Look Young) (Feat. 화지)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/Fleek_Feat_MBA_ek/</id><title>Odee - Fleek (Feat. MBA ek) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/Fleek_Feat_MBA_ek/" title="Odee - Fleek (Feat. MBA ek) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너의 의심의 알리바이 <br>ma rap on fleek <br>shout to ma father <br>왜냐 ma voice on fleek <br>나의 등뒤엔 VMC <br>ma team on fleek <br>질투와 시길 사 <br>계산해 cause I'm <br>on fleek <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>너의 되고 싶은 놈 <br>되게끔 I'm on fleek <br>큰 그림 그려둬 <br>내 사진 위로 덧칠 <br>동경 어린 눈 <br>난 거울이 필요 없지 <br>우월감에 젖은 속옷 <br>전부 발가벗기지 <br>매일 내 입에 <br>양주를 들이부어 <br>니 무슨 신념은 좆 까 <br>내가 좋을 삶을 좇지 <br>넌 피땀 흘리도록 <br>노력해 제자리걸음 <br>상처 받았다면 발러 <br>빨리 낫게 포비돈 <br>난 어디 있든 간 <br>기분 날아가지 <br>너희들의 두 다리 위 <br>날 얹어 이륙하지 <br>사촌이 땅 사면 <br>복통이 오는 병신들에겐 <br>내가 될 거야 <br>그 일가친척이 <br>사람들의 입엔 <br>하게 될 내 PPL <br>받게 될 동경엔 없애지 oppa <br>내 과거를 누군가의 <br>밟고 싶은 길로 <br>만들어 넌 내 발자국만 <br>따라 발 딛어 <br>너의 의심의 알리바이 <br>ma rap on fleek <br>shout to ma father <br>왜냐 ma voice on fleek <br>나의 등뒤엔 VMC <br>ma team on fleek <br>질투와 시길 사 <br>계산해 cause I'm <br>on fleek <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>난 유명하지도 <br>않은 채로 치고 올라올 <br>목표달성 뒤 모습은 <br>rap Obama <br>on fleek so I deep sleep <br>앞엔 main dish <br>멋이 베어있지 <br>굳이 왜 해 설명 <br>bpm 리듬 타고 <br>오디 곡을 조져 <br>그래 killin track <br>이미지에 비대해진 <br>래펀 기대에 비대칭 <br>미래의 씬 짊어질 <br>내 이름 새겨 <br>most bad Asian 미리 vip <br>I’m the mofuckin <br>boss 자수성가형 <br>멋이 수식어 <br>그래 하던 거 말고 <br>명찰 뒤로 쭉 <br>늘어나는 공 불어 <br>요술봉 염두에 둬 <br>넌 나의 가능성 <br>MVMCA 동갑내기 <br>래퍼 둘 이름 <br>오디 ek 밑에 깔릴 <br>래퍼들과 지폐 um <br>이거 뒤엔 늦어 새끼야 <br>네가 뭘 하던 I get it get it <br>see you again <br>거역해도 기억 <br>cause I’m on fleek <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>가만히 나와 니 <br>낮은 어깨를 나란히 <br>견주어보길 바라니 <br>가망 없어 니 야망이 <br>내 뒤엔 VM 옆에 <br>ek는 MBA <br>yeah we don't land <br>우린 비행 중이야 everyday <br>네 성공엔 존재하지도 <br>않잖아 지니 <br>눌려버린 머리 같은 <br>놈 위에 난 마치 비니 <br>니 랩은 니네들 갈라서게 <br>될 확실한 빌미 <br>그 사이 우린 오르지 <br>너 빼고 다 아는 비밀 <br>너의 의심의 알리바이 <br>ma rap on fleek <br>shout to ma father <br>왜냐 ma voice on fleek <br>나의 등뒤엔 VMC <br>ma team on fleek <br>질투와 시길 사 <br>계산해 cause I'm <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>on fleek on fleek <br>너 말고 내가 <br>]]></content><category term="Odee" label="Odee"/><category term="Fleek (Feat. MBA ek)" label="Fleek (Feat. MBA ek)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/Underdog_Feat_Don_Mills__우탄/</id><title>Odee - Underdog (Feat. Don Mills &amp; 우탄) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/Underdog_Feat_Don_Mills__%EC%9A%B0%ED%83%84/" title="Odee - Underdog (Feat. Don Mills &amp; 우탄) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내려다 봄을 즐겨 <br>하늘 위에서 구경 <br>애써봐 모두 <br>good luck <br>너흴 난 이렇게 불러 <br>I say underdog I say underdog <br>I say underdog I say underdog <br>I say underdog I say underdog <br>I say underdog I say underdog <br>잘하는 애들 많지 <br>단지 그게 랩부터가 아니고 <br>걔넨 필요한 게 마이킹 <br>bitches 한 일없이 <br>대가만을 가지려 해 <br>그 꼴은 못 봐 난 체하지 손 따 <br>피 보는 싸움에 난 먼저 올라 <br>내 승리를 못 박지 <br>이미 너희가 넘나들지 못할 <br>벽엔 자국들이 존나 있지 <br>내려가 있는 건 바지뿐이야 <br>잠시도 올라가는 모습에 <br>나를 저버린 적 없어 <br>정점을 찍어 내 가사에 <br>마침표 축밸 들 손에 <br>관절은 나가기 직전 <br>난 작품을 위해서 팔 생각들 <br>넌 상품을 만들어 팔 생각뿐 <br>죽이는 걸 내면 애들이 목매 <br>좆 된다의 뜻이 난 너완 다르지 <br>같은 데서 넌 서지 못해 <br>너가 노려볼 건 <br>underdog effect <br>다른 전술은 없어 <br>그건 지휘하지 못할 병법 <br>너는 팔 게 없지 한 개도 <br>사서 하는 걱정만 늘어나 계속 <br>새로운 관계도 그려보든지 <br>너가 잘 되든 또 안 되든 <br>안 보여 넌 내 앞에서 <br>내려다 봄을 즐겨 <br>하늘 위에서 구경 <br>애써봐 모두 <br>good luck <br>너흴 난 이렇게 불러 <br>I say underdog I say underdog <br>I say underdog I say underdog <br>I say underdog I say underdog <br>I say underdog I say underdog <br>잘하는 애들은 많지 <br>말만 늘어놓은 애들은 널렸잖아 <br>니가 알다시피 난 내 맘대로 <br>하는데 좋다고 날리잖아 <br>그만 좀 나를 귀찮게 좀 해 <br>나는 병신같이 굴어대는데도 <br>나를 보고 멋있다네 <br>멋 부리려 개 고생해 너넨 <br>우리편이야 우리편이야 <br>우리편이 아니라면 <br>여기 발도 디디지마 <br>oh yeah 소리질렀지 <br>공연페이 다 들어왔지 <br>잘 들어 내 발꼬락에 <br>지문도 닿지 않는 <br>대가리만 큰 새끼들아 <br>넌 한 방을 노려 나는 <br>목적을 달성하는 내 모습을 <br>노려 매일같이 노력해 <br>yeah 이 놈들 이제 날 빨아대 <br>yeah <br>앨범 나오니까 태도에 <br>변화가 생겼어 너네 <br>유행하는 것만 빨아대지 너네 <br>유일한 행보는 쇼미더머니 <br>다음 시즌 팀 선택이겠지 너네 다 <br>I say underdog I say underdog <br>I say underdog I say underdog <br>내 손잡아 어서 여긴 <br>공기가 죽여줘 <br>손오공 산신령 하나도 안 부러워 <br>꼭대기에 우린 엉덩이 걸쳐 <br>이건 Dreezy의 View motherfucker <br>오디와 난 같이 다리나 떨어 <br>너흰 발 냄새도 못 맡지 <br>여긴 너무 멀어 <br>유통기한 짧은 래퍼들은 <br>냉동 비비고 화끈하게 <br>달궈진 프라이팬은 TV show <br>제대로 익히지도 못해 <br>급히 데우려다 새까맣게 <br>타버렸지 싹 다 뒤집어 <br>대부분이 한철 짜리 과일 <br>우린 던밀스의 <br>쌀 사계절 먹히는 거 <br>우린 더욱 더욱 더욱 더욱 <br>노력했으니까 올핸 얻어가지 <br>더욱 더욱 더욱 더욱 <br>우린 모두 강백호처럼 <br>더욱 그냥 해버리지 리지 yeah <br>너흰 under 나는 top topdog <br>죽이지 느낌이 낌이 yeah <br>난 내 허리춤 쥐어 잡고 <br>난 그 아래 것들은 <br>상대 안 해 안 해 안 해 <br>그 아래서 니들이 흥분을 해서 <br>힘줘봐도 내겐 걍 좆 같은 거 <br>아가리도 안 닿네 <br>]]></content><category term="Odee" label="Odee"/><category term="Underdog (Feat. Don Mills &amp; 우탄)" label="Underdog (Feat. Don Mills &amp; 우탄)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/Open_Ending/</id><title>Odee - Open Ending - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Odee/Open_Ending/" title="Odee - Open Ending - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모든 결정 내 확신의 결과 <br>받아야지 나에 대한 꼴값 <br>내 이름이 두 개가 되는 것까지 <br>뭐가 어떻게 될는지 내 결말 <br>몰라도 터뜨렸지 샴페인 <br>몰라도 터뜨렸지 샴페인 <br>몰라도 터뜨렸지 샴페인 <br>몰라도 터뜨렸지 샴페인 <br>대학굔 때려 쳤지 <br>나의 학점도 2 점 몇 <br>600 얼마 등록금 지랄엔 <br>헛돈만 날렸어 <br>내가 열심힌줄 알던 <br>아버지의 안댈 벗겼고 <br>이젠 음악할거라 던진 말에 <br>걱정을 쥐셨어 <br>매일 매일 난 그 손을 <br>펼 때까지 go hard <br>누가 날 보며 삶에 대한 <br>지 안도감 느끼지 못하게 <br>다시 꺼내보면 또 엉킨 <br>이어폰과 내 결정에 <br>푸는 결과가 더 이상 <br>꼬이지 않길 바라 누구보다 <br>부모님의 탓도 커 <br>내 재능에 대해서 <br>썩힐 수가 없는 거 <br>어쩜 신내림 같은 것 <br>헛물켠 날의 번복 <br>발엔 air 1을 신고 <br>땅을 밟어 가는 길엔 <br>이젠 벗겨질 일 없어 <br>모든 결정 내 확신의 결과 <br>받아야지 나에 대한 꼴값 <br>내 이름이 두 개가 되는 것까지 <br>뭐가 어떻게 될는지 내 결말 <br>몰라도 터뜨렸지 샴페인 <br>몰라도 터뜨렸지 샴페인 <br>몰라도 터뜨렸지 샴페인 <br>몰라도 터뜨렸지 샴페인 <br>까만 하늘 보면서 <br>들 수 없는 단잠 <br>나는 예술가인 척할 <br>가장 따윈 안 하지 <br>내 두 눈에 적신혼 <br>나에 대한 green light <br>네가 보기엔 어떨 거 <br>같냐 내 팔자 <br>최고가 될 거 아님 말라고 <br>배웠기에 내가 할라고 <br>될 것 같은 기분 하나론 <br>안 돼 내가 가진 야마론 <br>죽여준다 내게 말하면 <br>난 더 협박 받길 바라고 <br>성공을 위한 그림 가졌지 <br>내 가사는 나의 달마도 <br>풀지 못할 단추를 잠갔어 <br>내 꿈과 좁히는 각도 <br>숫자에나 목을 매달려 <br>시작했담 여긴 무간도 <br>밤새워 작업하지 내가 <br>볼 일은 아직도 많아 <br>열린 결말에 결정해 <br>난 방문을 또다시 닫어 <br>모든 결정 내 확신의 결과 <br>받아야지 나에 대한 꼴값 <br>내 이름이 두 개가 되는 것까지 <br>뭐가 어떻게 될는지 내 결말 <br>몰라도 터뜨렸지 샴페인 <br>몰라도 터뜨렸지 샴페인 <br>몰라도 터뜨렸지 샴페인 <br>몰라도 터뜨렸지 샴페인 <br>모든 결정 내 확신의 결과 <br>받아야지 나에 대한 꼴값 <br>터뜨렸지 샴페인 <br>]]></content><category term="Odee" label="Odee"/><category term="Open Ending" label="Open Ending"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sam_Ock/Save/</id><title>Sam_Ock - Save - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sam_Ock/Save/" title="Sam_Ock - Save - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[He was born in a stable on that day <br>Where the animals fed is where he laid <br>Oh the infinite king in helpless babe <br>What a glorious way He came to save <br>How can we know humility <br>see how He laid upon the tree <br>Oh what gentleness and peace <br>Christ in full humanity <br><br>Matchless and might yet patient come <br>Saving the world by his desire <br>Beautiful the mystery <br>Why the Lord would come to me <br><br>He was born in a stable on that day <br>where the animals fed in where He laid <br>Oh the infinite King in helpless babe <br>What a glorious way He came to save <br><br>Worship with gratitude and soul <br>Worship the Immanuel <br>Worship the everlasting King <br>Come to Israel <br><br>Worship with tidings and with joy <br>Worship incarnate son <br>Worship the trinity as one <br>World as flesh bare for us <br><br>He was born <br>He was born <br><br>He was born in a stable on that day <br>where the animals fed is where He laid <br>Oh the infinite King in helpless babe <br>What a glorious way He came to save <br><br>You were born in a stable on that day <br>Where the animals fed is where You laid <br>Oh the infinite king in helpless babe <br>What a glorious way You came to save <br><br>What a glorious way You came to save]]></content><category term="Sam Ock" label="Sam Ock"/><category term="Save" label="Save"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sam_Ock/Tidings__Joy/</id><title>Sam_Ock - Tidings &amp; Joy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sam_Ock/Tidings__Joy/" title="Sam_Ock - Tidings &amp; Joy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I would like to wish you a very merry Christmas <br>and I wanna tell you that you are not alone <br>for He has come to overcome with love bringing the tidings and great joy <br><br>Oh what have I done to get such never-ending grace <br>I am forgiven and You call me as your own <br>for who would come from heaven site for someone like me <br>I am beloved and I’m free <br><br>so I’d like to wish you a very merry Christmas <br>and i wanna tell you that you are not alone <br>for He has come to overcome with love bringing the tidings and great joy <br><br>Lord what have I done to get Your never-ending grace <br>I am forgiven and You call me as your own <br>that you would come from heaven site for someone like me <br>I am beloved and I’m free <br><br>I would like to wish you a very merry Christmas <br>and I wanna tell you that you are not alone <br>for He has come to overcome with love bringing the tidings and great joy <br><br>You are never-ending joy <br><br>So do you a very merry Christmas <br>and I wanna tell you that you are not alone <br>For He has come to overcome with love bringing tidings and great joy]]></content><category term="Sam Ock" label="Sam Ock"/><category term="Tidings &amp; Joy" label="Tidings &amp; Joy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sam_Ock/Who_Wouldve_Thought_Feat_Hanbyul/</id><title>Sam_Ock - Who Would`ve Thought (Feat. Hanbyul) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sam_Ock/Who_Wouldve_Thought_Feat_Hanbyul/" title="Sam_Ock - Who Would`ve Thought (Feat. Hanbyul) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Who would’ve thought that You’ve came here for me <br>Born into the world to let the blind man see <br>Oh what a wonderful King You are <br>Came into the world under a shining star <br>All of His story it points to Your glory <br>And the Words You came to say <br><br>You are the reason for this very season <br>I celebrate my Lord in every way <br>Who would’ve thought that You came here for me <br>Born into the world to let the blind man see <br><br>Oh what a wonderful King You are <br>A Son of God You’ve set me free <br><br><br>Who would’ve thought that You’ve came here for me <br>Born into the world to let the blind man see <br>Oh what a wonderful King You are <br>Came into the world under a shining star <br>All of His story it points to Your glory <br>And the ones You came to say <br><br>You are the reason for this very season <br>I celebrate You Lord in every way <br>Who would’ve thought that You come down for me <br>Born into the world to let this blind man see <br><br>Oh what a glorious King You are <br>A Son of God You’ve set me free <br>]]></content><category term="Sam Ock" label="Sam Ock"/><category term="Who Would`ve Thought (Feat. Hanbyul)" label="Who Would`ve Thought (Feat. Hanbyul)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/뮤즈그레인_MuzGrain/비밀_폴더/</id><title>뮤즈그레인_MuzGrain - 비밀 폴더 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AE%A4%EC%A6%88%EA%B7%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8_MuzGrain/%EB%B9%84%EB%B0%80_%ED%8F%B4%EB%8D%94/" title="뮤즈그레인_MuzGrain - 비밀 폴더 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오랜만이라서 놀랐어 <br>짧은 인사도 잘 못했지 <br>오늘 입고 나온 옷은 <br>왜 하필 이런 옷인거야 <br>멀리서 니 모습 봤다면 <br>그냥 모른 척 했을텐데 <br>니가 날 아는 척 할진 몰랐어 <br>가난한 연인들의 <br>흔한 사랑 이야기 <br>못난 자존심 세우다 <br>너를 울려버린 기억 <br>왜 그랬나 싶어 <br>얼굴이 화끈거리네 <br>모두 잊고 싶어 이불을 걷어차네 <br>보고 싶었단 말을 미안했단 말을 <br>니 주위를 어슬렁대다 <br>차마 못하고 말았어 <br>이제는 돌아갈 수 없는 <br>내 어린 시절을 떠올리며 <br>못난 놈아 너는 덜 컸다 <br>미니홈피 속 비밀 폴던 <br>아직 그대로 <br>오랜만에 열어보니 <br>너와 나는 웃고 있네 <br>그대로네 너는 아직도 좋아 보여 <br>오늘 밤에는 또 옛 추억을 마시네 <br>보고 싶었단 말을 미안했단 말을 <br>니 주위를 어슬렁대다 <br>차마 못하고 말았어 <br>이제는 돌아갈 수 없는 <br>내 어린 시절을 떠올리며 <br>너는 어떤지 <br>모두 기억하긴 하는지 <br>나는 어떤 남자인지 <br>그냥 웃긴 놈인건지 <br>너의 머릿속을 뒤져 <br>못난 기억 지우고 싶어 <br>좋았던 기억만 남았으면 좋겠어 <br>보고 싶었단 말을 고마웠단 말을 <br>이제 와서 뭘 어쩌겠어 <br>입 속에 넣고 말았어 <br>다시 돌아가고 싶어라 <br>내 어린 시절을 떠올리며 <br>잘 지내라 너 그 때 그 마음들도 <br>못난 놈아 너는 좀 더 크거라 <br>]]></content><category term="뮤즈그레인 (MuzGrain)" label="뮤즈그레인 (MuzGrain)"/><category term="비밀 폴더" label="비밀 폴더"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조동진/강의_노래/</id><title>조동진 - 강의 노래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EB%8F%99%EC%A7%84/%EA%B0%95%EC%9D%98_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="조동진 - 강의 노래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밤새 불어난 강물 <br>물에 잠겨버린 너의 날들 <br>밤새 달려온 강물 <br>물에 쓸려가는 너의 아픔 <br>불어오는 바람의 위로 <br>물에 비친 구름 빈 하늘 <br>잃어버린 시간의 흔적 <br>저 산 그림자 <br>이름 이름 모를 숲 <br>저문 들판을 지나 <br>우리 떠나왔던 곳 <br>다시 돌아서 가는 <br>시작도 끝도 없는 여행 <br>밤새 들려온 강물 <br>물에 흘려보낸 너의 노래 <br>고여드는 마음의 강물 <br>우리 이제 다시 흐르니 <br>돌아오는 새들의 행렬 <br>저 먼 종소리 <br>이름 이름 모를 숲 <br>저문 들판을 지나 <br>우리 떠나왔던 곳 <br>다시 돌아서 가는 <br>시작도 끝도 없는 여행 <br>]]></content><category term="조동진" label="조동진"/><category term="강의 노래" label="강의 노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조동진/그날은_별들이_Farewell/</id><title>조동진 - 그날은 별들이 (Farewell) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EB%8F%99%EC%A7%84/%EA%B7%B8%EB%82%A0%EC%9D%80_%EB%B3%84%EB%93%A4%EC%9D%B4_Farewell/" title="조동진 - 그날은 별들이 (Farewell) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그날은 아픔도 멎어 버린 <br>바람마저 잠든 오후 <br>연기처럼 사라져간 <br>그대 잔잔한 숨결 <br>그날은 시간도 멈춰 버린 <br>가슴 속에 지는 불꽃 <br>얼어붙은 순간들은 <br>흘리지 못했던 눈물 <br>그날은 별들이 쏟아질 듯 <br>머리 위에 닿은 하늘 <br>깊고 푸른 내 슬픔은 <br>물빛 고요한 강물 <br>]]></content><category term="조동진" label="조동진"/><category term="그날은 별들이 (Farewell)" label="그날은 별들이 (Farewell)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조동진/이날이_가기_전에/</id><title>조동진 - 이날이 가기 전에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EB%8F%99%EC%A7%84/%EC%9D%B4%EB%82%A0%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B0%80%EA%B8%B0_%EC%A0%84%EC%97%90/" title="조동진 - 이날이 가기 전에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이날이 가기 전에 <br>내가 그리던 세상 <br>보여줬으면 좋았을 텐데 <br>이 밤이 가기 전에 <br>내가 부르던 노래 <br>들려줬으면 좋았을 텐데 <br>달려 가는 불빛들 <br>많지 않은 시간들 <br>무슨 말을 해야 할지 몰라 <br>무슨 생각 해야 할지 몰라 <br>비 젖은 저녁을 지나서 온 당신 <br>당신과 그리고 나 <br>달려 가는 불빛들 <br>많지 않은 시간들 <br>무슨 말을 해야 할지 몰라 <br>무슨 생각 해야 할지 몰라 <br>비 젖은 저녁을 지나서 온 당신 <br>당신과 그리고 나 <br>]]></content><category term="조동진" label="조동진"/><category term="이날이 가기 전에" label="이날이 가기 전에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조동진/천사/</id><title>조동진 - 천사 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EB%8F%99%EC%A7%84/%EC%B2%9C%EC%82%AC/" title="조동진 - 천사 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그댄 어쩌면 <br>천사였을지도 <br>비 오는 저녁 <br>고인 빗물로 내려와 <br>그댄 어쩌면 <br>천사였을지도 <br>기다란 방을 지나 <br>빈 가슴으로 다가와 <br>창 너머 어두운 풍경 <br>아직 끝나지 않은 하루 <br>멀리 불을 켜는 바다 <br>그 눈부신 그대의 <br>어둠 어둠 <br>창 너머 어두운 풍경 <br>아직 끝나지 않은 하루 <br>멀리 불을 켜는 바다 <br>그 눈부신 그대의 <br>어둠 어둠 <br>눈 앞에 펼쳐진 <br>어지러운 세상 <br>그 속에 다시 설 때 까지 <br>날 지켜준 <br>천사 <br>]]></content><category term="조동진" label="조동진"/><category term="천사" label="천사"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조동진/향기/</id><title>조동진 - 향기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EB%8F%99%EC%A7%84/%ED%96%A5%EA%B8%B0/" title="조동진 - 향기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밤은 깊었어도 <br>길을 잃은 게 아니듯 <br>날은 밝았어도 <br>빛을 잃은 게 아니듯 <br>봄은 다시 와도 <br>모두 시작은 아니듯 <br>너는 떠났어도 <br>모두 끝난 게 아니듯 <br>여기 떠도는 향기 <br>꽃잎 흔드는 바람 <br>그 뜨거움조차 <br>꿈이라고 해야 할지 <br>이 그리움조차 <br>아니라고 해야 할지 <br>여기 떠도는 향기 <br>꽃잎 흔드는 바람 <br>그 뜨거움조차 <br>꿈이라고 해야 할지 <br>이 그리움조차 <br>아니라고 해야 할지 <br>]]></content><category term="조동진" label="조동진"/><category term="향기" label="향기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조동진/하얀_벽/</id><title>조동진 - 하얀 벽 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:55:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:55:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EB%8F%99%EC%A7%84/%ED%95%98%EC%96%80_%EB%B2%BD/" title="조동진 - 하얀 벽 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 자꾸만 잠이 드는 건지 <br>이 눈부신 날에 <br>왜 자꾸만 꿈을 꾸는 건지 <br>이 공허한 밤에 <br>하얀 벽 위에 춤추는 그림자 <br>소리 없이 흐르는 시간들 <br>여기 쓰러져 내려앉은 꿈 <br>또 다른 시련일 뿐 인데 <br>거기 외진 곳 <br>너의 잠든 모습 <br>또 다른 하루의 <br>외로운 밤일 뿐 인데 <br>하얀 벽 위에 춤추는 그림자 <br>소리 없이 흐르는 시간들 <br>여기 쓰러져 내려앉은 꿈 <br>또 다른 시련일 뿐 인데 <br>거기 외진 곳 <br>너의 잠든 모습 <br>또 다른 하루의 <br>외로운 밤일 뿐 인데 <br>왜 자꾸만 잠이 드는 건지 <br>이 눈부신 날에 <br>왜 자꾸만 꿈을 꾸는 건지 <br>이 공허한 밤에 <br>]]></content><category term="조동진" label="조동진"/><category term="하얀 벽" label="하얀 벽"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조동진/1970/</id><title>조동진 - 1970 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:56:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:56:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EB%8F%99%EC%A7%84/1970/" title="조동진 - 1970 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람 불어 대는 비탈길에 <br>해는 떠올라도 <br>우리 푸르던 날 하늘빛에 <br>더 서글퍼 보였었네 <br>저문 거리 마다 네온 불빛 <br>밤을 밝혔어도 <br>우리 고단한 꿈 어깨 위에 <br>더 쓸쓸해보였었네 <br>허기진 가슴들을 <br>노래 불러 달래며 <br>눈뜨면 어디로든 <br>걷고 또 걸어야 했던 <br>그래 그때 <br>그때 우리는 떠도는 바람 이었고 <br>그래 그때 <br>그땐 누구나 구르는 돌 이었네 <br>다시 쏟아지는 새벽 비를 <br>피할 곳은 없어도 <br>그대 흩날리는 긴 머리에 <br>내 젊음을 걸었었네 <br>허기진 가슴들을 <br>노래 불러 달래며 <br>눈뜨면 어디로든 <br>걷고 또 걸어야 했던 <br>그래 그때 <br>그때 우리는 떠도는 바람 이었고 <br>그래 그때 <br>그땐 누구나 구르는 돌 이었네 <br>그래 그때 <br>그때 우리는 떠도는 바람 이었고 <br>그래 그때 <br>그땐 누구나 구르는 돌 이었네 <br>]]></content><category term="조동진" label="조동진"/><category term="1970" label="1970"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조동진/섬_안의_섬/</id><title>조동진 - 섬 안의 섬 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:56:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:56:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EB%8F%99%EC%A7%84/%EC%84%AC_%EC%95%88%EC%9D%98_%EC%84%AC/" title="조동진 - 섬 안의 섬 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[거기 누가 있을지 <br>거기 아직 누가 <br>거기 누가 잠들지 <br>거기 아직 그대 <br>섬 안의 섬 <br>섬 안의 섬 <br>섬 안의 섬 <br>섬 안의 섬 <br>저 검은 물결 너머 <br>내 절망의 거품들 <br>저 거친 바람 속에 <br>내 침묵의 시간들 <br>거기 누가 있을지 <br>구름 걸린 언덕 <br>거기 누가 오를지 <br>거기 아직 그대 <br>꿈 속의 꿈 <br>꿈 속의 꿈 <br>꿈 속의 꿈 <br>꿈 속의 꿈 <br>이 공허의 방을 지나 <br>꿈의 창가로 <br>이 버려진 시간 따라 <br>밤의 향기로 <br>꿈 속의 꿈 <br>꿈 속의 꿈 <br>꿈 속의 꿈 <br>꿈 속의 꿈 <br>푸른 빛 속을 지나 <br>어둠의 바다를 지나 <br>우리 처음 만나기 이전으로 <br>다시 돌아가는 길 <br>이 공허의 방을 지나 <br>꿈의 창가로 <br>이 버려진 시간 따라 <br>밤의 향기로 <br>섬 안에 섬 <br>섬 안에 섬 <br>섬 안에 섬 <br>섬 안에 섬 <br>섬 안에 섬 <br>섬 안의 섬 <br>]]></content><category term="조동진" label="조동진"/><category term="섬 안의 섬" label="섬 안의 섬"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조동진/나무가_되어/</id><title>조동진 - 나무가 되어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:56:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:56:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EB%8F%99%EC%A7%84/%EB%82%98%EB%AC%B4%EA%B0%80_%EB%90%98%EC%96%B4/" title="조동진 - 나무가 되어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 거기 다가갈 수 없으니 <br>그대 너무 멀리 있지 않기를 <br>나는 별빛 내린 나무가 되어 <br>이전 처럼 움직일 수가 없어 <br>나는 다시 돌이킬 수 없으니 <br>그대 너무 외면하지 않기를 <br>나는 하늘 가린 나무가 되어 <br>예전 처럼 노래 할 수도 없어 <br>나무가 되어 <br>나무가 되어 <br>끝이 없는 그리움도 <br>흙 속으로 <br>나는 이제 따라갈 수 없으니 <br>그대 홀로 떠나 갈 수 있기를 <br>나는 비에 젖은 나무가 되어 <br>예전 처럼 외로움조차 없어 <br>나무가 되어 <br>나무가 되어 <br>끝이 없는 그리움도 <br>흙 속으로 <br>]]></content><category term="조동진" label="조동진"/><category term="나무가 되어" label="나무가 되어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조동진/그렇게_10년/</id><title>조동진 - 그렇게 10년 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:56:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:56:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EB%8F%99%EC%A7%84/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A0%87%EA%B2%8C_10%EB%85%84/" title="조동진 - 그렇게 10년 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어느 바람찬 봄날 갑자기 <br>숨차게 부르던 노래 소리 그치고 <br>어느 낯 설은 길목 지나서 <br>말없이 그렇게 십년을 <br>다시 흘려 보냈네 <br>표정 없는 기다란 하루 <br>길이 없는 숲의 날들 <br>시간 아닌 시간 속을 지나는 바람 <br>표정 없는 기다란 하루 <br>길이 없는 숲의 날들 <br>시간 아닌 시간 속을 지나는 바람 <br>어느 바닷가 젖은 모래 위 <br>하얗게 떠도는 거품처럼 <br>그렇게 십년을 다시 흘려 보냈네 <br>]]></content><category term="조동진" label="조동진"/><category term="그렇게 10년" label="그렇게 10년"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로즈베리_Rosevary/나요나요/</id><title>로즈베리_Rosevary - 나요나요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:56:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:56:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EC%A6%88%EB%B2%A0%EB%A6%AC_Rosevary/%EB%82%98%EC%9A%94%EB%82%98%EC%9A%94/" title="로즈베리_Rosevary - 나요나요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You 슬쩍 봐요 <br>너와 마주칠까 힐끔 해요 <br>널 향한 저 수많은 시선들 어머 <br>어쩜 좋아요 <br>휴 너와 마주치면 <br>아무 생각 없이 <br>너만 바라봐 나 예예 <br>너 정말 사람 맞나 <br>믿을 수 없는 걸요 <br>오 이런 나요 나요 너 때문에 나 <br>오 I know I know 너 때문에 난 <br>싫은 척 하는 내 맘 잘 알잖아요 <br>두근대는 내 맘 <br>이젠 나를 바라봐요 <br>왜 손만 보지 <br>너를 두고 이런 반응 oh no <br>속만 타요 아무도 모를 걸 어머 <br>어쩜 좋아요 <br>휴 너와 마주치면 <br>아무 생각 없이 <br>너만 바라봐 나 예예 <br>너 정말 사람 맞나 <br>믿을 수 없는 걸요 <br>오 이런 나요 나요 너 때문에 나 <br>오 I know I know 너 때문에 난 <br>싫은 척 하는 내 맘 잘 알잖아요 <br>두근대는 내 맘 <br>이젠 나를 바라봐요 <br>그렇게 하지말아요 <br>너에게 말해 something love <br>아직도 네게 말을 못해 I say love <br>오 이런 나요 나요 너 때문에 나 <br>오 I know I know 너 때문에 난 <br>싫은 척 하는 내 맘 잘 알잖아요 <br>두근대는 내 맘 <br>이젠 나를 바라봐요 <br>]]></content><category term="로즈베리 (Rosevary)" label="로즈베리 (Rosevary)"/><category term="나요나요" label="나요나요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/달콤상큼짜릿/숨은_너_찾기_Feat_FEELGOOD/</id><title>달콤상큼짜릿 - 숨은 너 찾기 (Feat. FEELGOOD) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:56:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:56:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%AC%EC%BD%A4%EC%83%81%ED%81%BC%EC%A7%9C%EB%A6%BF/%EC%88%A8%EC%9D%80_%EB%84%88_%EC%B0%BE%EA%B8%B0_Feat_FEELGOOD/" title="달콤상큼짜릿 - 숨은 너 찾기 (Feat. FEELGOOD) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[더 이상 오지 마 <br>그대로 거기 멈춰 <br>왜 자꾸 따라와 <br>너 참 별로다 <br>떠나가지마 사라지지마 <br>흔들리게 한 건 <br>너야 내가 아냐 <br>나 정말 답답해 <br>숨지 말고 나와봐 <br>보일듯 말 듯 <br>잡힐듯 말 듯 <br>헷갈리게 너 왜 그러니 <br>진짜 미치겠다 <br>제발 나타나줘 <br>그만 이제 싫어 그만 둬 <br>Ah 나도 못 참아 <br>찾지 않을거야 <br>이대로 끝내 <br>더 이상 하지 마 <br>그대로 거기 멈춰 <br>나 혼자 뭐 했니 <br>너 참 별로다 <br>그동안 얼마나 <br>널 찾아 헤맸는데 <br>어떻게 나한테 이래 <br>가 가버려 <br>우린 안 돼 Oh 왜 안 돼 <br>뒤죽박죽 <br>몰라 <br>어디에 숨어 있니 <br>너 <br>아 너무 힘들어서 그래 <br>지쳐버리겠지 <br>도대체 뭐가 맞을까 <br>보일듯 말 듯 <br>잡힐듯 말 듯 <br>헷갈리게 너 왜 그러니 <br>진짜 미치겠다 <br>제발 나타나줘 <br>그만 이제 싫어 그만 둬 <br>Ah 나도 못 참아 <br>찾지 않을거야 <br>이대로 끝내 <br>결국엔 똑같아 <br>비겁해 도망쳤어 <br>이렇게 쓸쓸히 <br>나만 남았어 <br>]]></content><category term="달콤상큼짜릿" label="달콤상큼짜릿"/><category term="숨은 너 찾기 (Feat. FEELGOOD)" label="숨은 너 찾기 (Feat. FEELGOOD)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동요유치원/뭐가_될거니/</id><title>동요유치원 - 뭐가 될거니 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:56:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:56:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%9C%A0%EC%B9%98%EC%9B%90/%EB%AD%90%EA%B0%80_%EB%90%A0%EA%B1%B0%EB%8B%88/" title="동요유치원 - 뭐가 될거니 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너는 너는 자라서 뭐가 될거니 <br>나는 나는 의사가 되고 싶어요 <br>아픈사람 고쳐주는 <br>훌륭한 의사가 되고 싶어요 <br><br>너는 너는 자라서 뭐가 될거니 <br>나는 나는 선생님 되고 싶어요 <br>어린이와 공부하는 <br>훌륭한 선생님 되고 싶어요 <br><br>너는 너는 자라서 뭐가 될거니 <br>나는 나는 가수가 되고 싶어요 <br>무대에서 노래하는 <br>멋있는 가수가 되고 싶어요]]></content><category term="동요유치원" label="동요유치원"/><category term="뭐가 될거니" label="뭐가 될거니"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/팻두/사람을_죽여드립니다/</id><title>팻두 - 사람을 죽여드립니다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:56:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:56:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8C%BB%EB%91%90/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C%EC%9D%84_%EC%A3%BD%EC%97%AC%EB%93%9C%EB%A6%BD%EB%8B%88%EB%8B%A4/" title="팻두 - 사람을 죽여드립니다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이제야 찾았다 <br>사람을 죽여드립니다 <br>여보세요 저기여 <br>네 선금이여 네 <br>내가 암에 걸렸데 <br>7번의 수술을 해도 <br>살아 날 확율은 5 프로 <br>온 몸에 싹 다 퍼졌데 <br>그놈의 암세포가 <br>평소 병원을 멀리했던 <br>내 고집의 최후 <br>지금 난 너무 멀쩡한데 <br>팔 다리 맘대로 <br>움직일 수 있고 어제도 <br>홍대에서 밤샜어 <br>이렇게 젊고 멀쩡한데 <br>암 말기라니 <br>이제야 자리 잡았는데 <br>무덤으로 돌아가라니 <br>집 전세 빼고 통장 <br>긁으면 1억5천 <br>확율 5 프로 에 이 돈을 <br>배팅 안해 못 고쳐 <br>그냥 내 영혼이 편히 <br>성불할 수 있게 <br>피땀 흘려 번 전재산 <br>복수에 올인 할래 <br>동업하자며 돈 갖고 튄 <br>10년 친구 영진이 <br>내 약혼녀하고 잤던 철수 <br>그리고 그 잔 개년 <br>그리고 아빠한테 <br>보증 서게 해서 <br>우리 부모님 자살하게 <br>만든 개새끼까지 <br>그 쓰레기들은 지금 너무나 <br>행복하게 잘 사는데 <br>왜 나는 두려움에 떨며 <br>죽음을 맞이하는데 <br>인정할 수 없어 <br>그래서 돈을 입금했어 <br>나는 계속 살아갈래 <br>죽지 않고 날아갈래 <br>불멸의 삶을 살아갈래 <br>죽을바엔 너도 죽일래 <br>어제 철수 오빠 죽었데 <br>오늘 새벽 스물네살 김모양이 <br>불에 타죽은 채 발견되었습니다 <br>자살의 흔적은 없었고 <br>너 뒷통수 쳤던 영진이 있잖아 <br>어제 교통사고로 죽었데 <br>하늘이 뻥 뚫리고 <br>빛이 들어옴을 느껴 <br>너무 통쾌해 먹구름은 <br>갔어 비는 그쳐 <br>꼭 범죄자들 사기꾼들이 <br>오래 살더라 <br>돈으로 안되는 거 없지 <br>이번엔 내 차례다 <br>근데 제일 중요한 새끼의 <br>소식이 들려오질 않아 <br>여보세요 나머지 한명은 <br>잔금이요 그건 일 다 끝나고 <br>드리기로 아 네 내일이요 <br>알겠습니다 내일 봽죠 <br>갑자기 잔금을 처리해 <br>달래서 갔어 <br>네 여기 돈 가져왔어여 <br>이쪽으로 오이소 <br>여기 나머지 잔금 <br>아이구 거 미안하게 됐습니다 <br>사람을 죽이러 가 <br>돈을 10배로 준다하지 <br>않겠습니까 <br>어설프게 있는 <br>사람으로는 요런데 <br>오면 안됩니더 <br>1억5천이면 그 사람들한테는 <br>껌값이니께는 아이지 껌값도 <br>아니되지 뭐 암튼 <br>미안하게 됐습니다 <br>나는 계속 살아갈래 <br>죽지 않고 날아갈래 <br>불멸의 삶을 살아갈래 <br>죽을바엔 너도 죽일래 <br>죽는다는 게 너무 두려웠어 <br>영원히 잠을 자야 된다는 게 <br>믿기질 않았어 <br>친구들도 다시는 못 보고 <br>이 세상에서 완전히 <br>사라진다는 게 믿어지질 않았어 <br>사람들은 종교를 믿고 <br>후생을 믿어 <br>하지만 나는 그러질 못했어 <br>그 두려움을 어딘가에 <br>표출해야만 했고 <br>내가 암에 걸리게 만든 <br>원인이라 생각했어 <br>죽기 싫어 난 <br>죽기 싫어 <br>정말 죽기 싫어 <br>]]></content><category term="팻두" label="팻두"/><category term="사람을 죽여드립니다" label="사람을 죽여드립니다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임세준/그래도_사랑_Inst/</id><title>임세준 - 그래도 사랑 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:59:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:59:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%84%B8%EC%A4%80/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%98%EB%8F%84_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_Inst/" title="임세준 - 그래도 사랑 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[있잖아 그럴 때가 있잖아 <br>보고 싶어서 미칠 것만 같고 <br>당장 달려가고 싶을 때 <br>못 잊어 따뜻했던 널 못 잊어 <br>그게 너라서 너라서 못 잊어 <br>너무 포근했던 그 냄새를 <br>가끔 말야 너 힘들거나 지치거나 <br>기댈 곳이 필요해지면 날 써 <br>네가 부르면 어디든지 <br>세상 끝까지라도 꼭 갈게 <br>사랑 못난 내 사랑 <br>그래도 사랑 사랑 <br>울잖아 너 없이 나 울잖아 <br>사랑이란게 그리움이란게 <br>내 마음처럼 안 되는거잖아 <br>가끔 말야 너 힘들거나 지치거나 <br>기댈 곳이 필요해지면 날 써 <br>네가 부르면 어디든지 <br>세상 끝까지라도 꼭 갈게 <br>사랑 못난 내 사랑 <br>그래도 사랑 그래도 사랑 <br>사랑 못난 내 사랑 사랑 <br>나는 말야 너 결국엔 난 너 <br>내 모든 걸 다 걸 수 있고 <br>줄 수 있는 오직 한 사람 너 <br>사랑 아픈 내 사랑 <br>소중한 사랑 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="임세준" label="임세준"/><category term="그래도 사랑 (Inst.)" label="그래도 사랑 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정기고/소소하게_조금씩_Inst/</id><title>정기고 - 소소하게 조금씩 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:59:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:59:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B8%B0%EA%B3%A0/%EC%86%8C%EC%86%8C%ED%95%98%EA%B2%8C_%EC%A1%B0%EA%B8%88%EC%94%A9_Inst/" title="정기고 - 소소하게 조금씩 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[소소하게 조금씩 love you <br>한걸음 다가갈게 love you <br>더 가까이 <br>한 번도 생각한 적 없던 <br>너와 나 우리 우리 둘 사이 hmm <br>너와 단 둘이 영원히 둘이 <br>여기 살고 싶다는 <br>조그만 소원 하나 <br>너를 모르지 아직 모르지 <br>그런 겁 없는 상상 말도 안돼 <br>한번쯤 내 맘을 부디 내 맘을 <br>심장 꺼낼 수 있다면 <br>사랑해 사랑해 그땐 내 맘 알까 <br>내 눈을 나의 두 눈을 <br>바라보면 다 알텐데 이렇게 <br>우리 멋진 더 멋진 oh 훨씬 더 멋진 <br>사랑 한번 만들어봐 <br>내겐 너 내겐 너뿐 <br>멋진 더 멋진 oh 훨씬 더 멋진 <br>천천히 와 서두르지마 <br>소소하게 조금씩 <br>뭘 해도 보고싶고 <br>왜 때문에 생각나 <br>어떡하지 내 내 내 맘을 <br>이제는 조금 알 것 같아 <br>나도 가끔은 설레이는데 hmm <br>너와 단 둘이 영원히 둘이 <br>여기 살고 싶다는 <br>조그만 소원 하나 <br>너를 모르지 아직 모르지 <br>그런 겁 없는 상상 말도 안돼 <br>한번쯤 내 맘을 부디 내 맘을 <br>심장 꺼낼 수 있다면 <br>사랑해 사랑해 그땐 내 맘 알까 <br>내 눈을 나의 두 눈을 <br>바라보면 다 알텐데 이렇게 <br>I love you I need you I want you <br>어떤 말도 표현이 안돼 <br>멀지 않았어 더 보여줄래 <br>내가 너를 믿을 수 있게 <br>내일은 꿈처럼 매일 꿈처럼 <br>나도 들을 수 있다면 <br>사랑해 사랑해 좀 더 기다릴게 <br>사랑은 나의 사랑은 <br>다 알아도 넌 모르게 이렇게 <br>너무 멋진 더 멋진 oh 훨씬 더 멋진 <br>사랑 한번 만들어봐 <br>내겐 너 내겐 너뿐 <br>멋진 더 멋진 oh 훨씬 더 멋진 <br>나도 갈게 서두르지마 <br>소소하게 조금씩 <br>]]></content><category term="정기고" label="정기고"/><category term="소소하게 조금씩 (Inst.)" label="소소하게 조금씩 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임세준/그래도_사랑/</id><title>임세준 - 그래도 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:59:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:59:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%84%B8%EC%A4%80/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%98%EB%8F%84_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="임세준 - 그래도 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[있잖아 그럴 때가 있잖아 <br>보고 싶어서 미칠 것만 같고 <br>당장 달려가고 싶을 때 <br>못 잊어 따뜻했던 널 못 잊어 <br>그게 너라서 너라서 못 잊어 <br>너무 포근했던 그 냄새를 <br>가끔 말야 너 힘들거나 지치거나 <br>기댈 곳이 필요해지면 날 써 <br>네가 부르면 어디든지 <br>세상 끝까지라도 꼭 갈게 <br>사랑 못난 내 사랑 <br>그래도 사랑 사랑 <br>울잖아 너 없이 나 울잖아 <br>사랑이란게 그리움이란게 <br>내 마음처럼 안 되는거잖아 <br>가끔 말야 너 힘들거나 지치거나 <br>기댈 곳이 필요해지면 날 써 <br>네가 부르면 어디든지 <br>세상 끝까지라도 꼭 갈게 <br>사랑 못난 내 사랑 <br>그래도 사랑 그래도 사랑 <br>사랑 못난 내 사랑 사랑 <br>나는 말야 너 결국엔 난 너 <br>내 모든 걸 다 걸 수 있고 <br>줄 수 있는 오직 한 사람 너 <br>사랑 아픈 내 사랑 <br>소중한 사랑 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="임세준" label="임세준"/><category term="그래도 사랑" label="그래도 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정기고/소소하게_조금씩/</id><title>정기고 - 소소하게 조금씩 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T22:59:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T22:59:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B8%B0%EA%B3%A0/%EC%86%8C%EC%86%8C%ED%95%98%EA%B2%8C_%EC%A1%B0%EA%B8%88%EC%94%A9/" title="정기고 - 소소하게 조금씩 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[소소하게 조금씩 love you <br>한걸음 다가갈게 love you <br>더 가까이 <br>한 번도 생각한 적 없던 <br>너와 나 우리 우리 둘 사이 hmm <br>너와 단 둘이 영원히 둘이 <br>여기 살고 싶다는 <br>조그만 소원 하나 <br>너를 모르지 아직 모르지 <br>그런 겁 없는 상상 말도 안돼 <br>한번쯤 내 맘을 부디 내 맘을 <br>심장 꺼낼 수 있다면 <br>사랑해 사랑해 그땐 내 맘 알까 <br>내 눈을 나의 두 눈을 <br>바라보면 다 알텐데 이렇게 <br>우리 멋진 더 멋진 oh 훨씬 더 멋진 <br>사랑 한번 만들어봐 <br>내겐 너 내겐 너뿐 <br>멋진 더 멋진 oh 훨씬 더 멋진 <br>천천히 와 서두르지마 <br>소소하게 조금씩 <br>뭘 해도 보고싶고 <br>왜 때문에 생각나 <br>어떡하지 내 내 내 맘을 <br>이제는 조금 알 것 같아 <br>나도 가끔은 설레이는데 hmm <br>너와 단 둘이 영원히 둘이 <br>여기 살고 싶다는 <br>조그만 소원 하나 <br>너를 모르지 아직 모르지 <br>그런 겁 없는 상상 말도 안돼 <br>한번쯤 내 맘을 부디 내 맘을 <br>심장 꺼낼 수 있다면 <br>사랑해 사랑해 그땐 내 맘 알까 <br>내 눈을 나의 두 눈을 <br>바라보면 다 알텐데 이렇게 <br>I love you I need you I want you <br>어떤 말도 표현이 안돼 <br>멀지 않았어 더 보여줄래 <br>내가 너를 믿을 수 있게 <br>내일은 꿈처럼 매일 꿈처럼 <br>나도 들을 수 있다면 <br>사랑해 사랑해 좀 더 기다릴게 <br>사랑은 나의 사랑은 <br>다 알아도 넌 모르게 이렇게 <br>너무 멋진 더 멋진 oh 훨씬 더 멋진 <br>사랑 한번 만들어봐 <br>내겐 너 내겐 너뿐 <br>멋진 더 멋진 oh 훨씬 더 멋진 <br>나도 갈게 서두르지마 <br>소소하게 조금씩 <br>]]></content><category term="정기고" label="정기고"/><category term="소소하게 조금씩" label="소소하게 조금씩"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/플로우식_Flowsik/시작하기_좋은_날/</id><title>플로우식_Flowsik - 시작하기 좋은 날 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:03:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:03:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%8C%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B0%EC%8B%9D_Flowsik/%EC%8B%9C%EC%9E%91%ED%95%98%EA%B8%B0_%EC%A2%8B%EC%9D%80_%EB%82%A0/" title="플로우식_Flowsik - 시작하기 좋은 날 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그래 우린 달라 달라 <br>아니 어쩌면 우린 같아 <br>하루하루가 힘들어 <br>고개를 숙였어 <br>다시 시작하기 좋은 날 <br>꿈을 현실로 Today <br>I'll be on my way <br>on my way on my way <br>꿈을 간직하길 바랄게 <br>동무들과 신나게 <br>축구 시합했어 <br>연락하라 고함치며 <br>신호 보냈어 <br>나한테 공을 <br>왜 안주는 건데 <br>연락이 아니라 <br>패쓰 패쓰 패쓰 <br>교통카드도 몰랐고 <br>잔돈도 없었어 <br>택시 탈까 망설이다 <br>돈 아끼자 했지 <br>버스 타고 5만원 <br>돈 통에 넣었어 <br>기사님이 놀라서 <br>내가 더 놀랐어 <br>국어 시간에는 <br>머리 몽롱해져 <br>다른 과목도 <br>마찬가지야 Yeah <br>교집합이 뭔지 <br>미적분이 뭔지 <br>수업시간 자체가 <br>외계어 시간 Yeah <br>누난 싫어해도 <br>나는 수학이 좋아 <br>공식대로 풀어보면 <br>모든 문제 풀려 <br>주변 돌아보면 <br>모르는 거 천지 <br>내 고민 풀어줄 <br>공식 찾고 싶어 <br>발음 고치려고 <br>매일 뉴스를 봤지 <br>입에 볼펜 물고 <br>발음 연습했지 <br>아야어여오요 <br>오요우요으이 <br>발음 안 되고 <br>침만 흘러내렸어 UH <br>친구들이 M.T 가서 <br>실컷 놀자 했지 <br>M.T가 어디야 <br>눈치만 봤어 <br>외국은 아니겠지 <br>한국 안이겠지 <br>지도를 찾아봐도 <br>그런 곳은 없어 <br>컴퓨터 고장 나서 <br>수리점을 갔어 <br>눈앞에 보이는 건 <br>컴퓨터크리닝 <br>당당하게 문 열고 <br>안으로 갔지 <br>세탁하던 아저씨와 <br>눈이 마주쳤어 <br>와 뭐가 이리 <br>어려운 게 많아 <br>뭐가 뭔지 모르겠고 <br>말하기도 두려워 <br>우리를 쳐다보는 <br>시선도 무서워 <br>별거 아닌 일에도 <br>한없이 작아져 <br>STOP 얘들아 <br>내 말 들어봐 <br>미국에서 자란 한국인인지 <br>한국에서 사는 미국인인지 <br>많은 고난을 <br>견뎌내 찾은 행복 <br>이 순간을 그대로 멈춰 <br>그 시간 속에 허우적 <br>뿌연 안개를 뚫고 <br>앞으로 왔지 <br>가까스로 싸우며 <br>지금까지 왔지 <br>시간은 왔어 자 봐 <br>Now watch me shine forever <br>이제 용기를 가져 <br>편견 따윈 날려버려 <br>플로우식 고마워 <br>큰 용기가 됐어 <br>우리 함께 멋진 <br>꿈을 향해 달려가 <br>화려한 무대 <br>신나는 노래 <br>다 따라 불러봐 <br>우리들의 노래 <br>더 넓은 세상 향해 <br>날아가고 싶어 <br>하늘을 나는 <br>승무원이 꿈이야 <br>행복을 주는 <br>요리사가 되고 싶어 <br>외래어가 힘들지만 <br>난 꿈을 이 룰 거야 <br>간호사가 되길 <br>엄마는 바라지 <br>하지만 나는 <br>내 꿈으로 향하지 <br>춤 잘 추는 <br>내 꿈은 영화배우야 <br>이 정도 외모도 훌륭하잖아 <br>예전엔 나도 축구선수였지 <br>지금의 내 꿈은 <br>스포츠 트레이너 <br>Own it you got it <br>혼자 고민할 바엔 옆에 타 <br>음악 크게 틀고 <br>걱정 날려 버려 <br>용기 가득 채웠다 <br>어디든지 끝까지 같이 가 <br>나도 알아 <br>Once upon a time <br>똑같지 않은 게 <br>힘들게 느껴져 <br>모두가 말할 때 <br>난 고개를 숙였지만 <br>I’m look up to the sky <br>별이 되고 싶은걸 <br>어두운 밤 빛이 돼 <br>용기를 가득 채워 <br>그래 우린 달라 달라 <br>아니 어쩌면 우린 같아 <br>하루하루가 힘들어 <br>고개를 숙였어 <br>다시 시작하기 좋은 날 <br>꿈을 현실로 Today <br>I'll be on my way <br>on my way on my way <br>꿈을 간직하길 바랄게 <br>고개 들고 어깨 펴고 <br>용기 내서 세상 끝까지 <br>고개 들고 어깨 펴고 <br>용기 내서 세상 끝까지 <br>]]></content><category term="플로우식 (Flowsik)" label="플로우식 (Flowsik)"/><category term="시작하기 좋은 날" label="시작하기 좋은 날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/빅베이비드라이버트리오/Untitled_온스테이지_Ver/</id><title>빅베이비드라이버트리오 - Untitled (온스테이지 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:03:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:03:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%85%EB%B2%A0%EC%9D%B4%EB%B9%84%EB%93%9C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EB%B2%84%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%98%A4/Untitled_%EC%98%A8%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80_Ver/" title="빅베이비드라이버트리오 - Untitled (온스테이지 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Where is your light <br>I know who you are <br>I know who you are <br>So don’t be alarmed <br>I know who you are <br>I know who you are <br>]]></content><category term="빅베이비드라이버트리오" label="빅베이비드라이버트리오"/><category term="Untitled (온스테이지 Ver.)" label="Untitled (온스테이지 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/빅베이비드라이버트리오/A_Line_In_The_Sky_온스테이지_Ver/</id><title>빅베이비드라이버트리오 - A Line In The Sky (온스테이지 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:03:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:03:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%85%EB%B2%A0%EC%9D%B4%EB%B9%84%EB%93%9C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EB%B2%84%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%98%A4/A_Line_In_The_Sky_%EC%98%A8%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80_Ver/" title="빅베이비드라이버트리오 - A Line In The Sky (온스테이지 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Once you draw a line in the sky <br>You ought to stay with me <br>You ought to stay with me <br>Then you'll know wha’s up in the sky <br>you ought to stay with me <br>you ought to stay with me <br>Once you know wha’s up in the sky <br>You ought to stay with me <br>You ought to stay with me <br>Then you’ll know <br>wha’s up in your mind <br>You ought to stay with me <br>You ought to stay with me <br>Cause you know <br>Once know what’s up in your mind <br>You ought to stay with me <br>You ought to stay with me <br>Then you will draw a line in the sky <br>You ought to stay with me <br>You ought to stay with me <br>Cause you know <br>]]></content><category term="빅베이비드라이버트리오" label="빅베이비드라이버트리오"/><category term="A Line In The Sky (온스테이지 Ver.)" label="A Line In The Sky (온스테이지 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Azier/Talk_To_Me/</id><title>Thomas_Azier - Talk To Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:08:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:08:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Azier/Talk_To_Me/" title="Thomas_Azier - Talk To Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My father wants the best for me <br>But I'm feeling super low <br>I wonder what's the best for me <br>I don't know which way to go <br><br>He tells me I will be alright <br>I just need a little time <br>I'm trying but my tears are dry <br>I have wasted them online <br><br>Talk to me <br>Talk to me <br>Tell me how you really feel <br>Talk to me <br>Talk to me <br>Tell me what is fake and what is real <br><br>I want to find escape tonight <br>Wake me up when this summer comes <br>Painkillers for my brain tonight <br>I want to fade until I'm gone <br><br>It burns when it caresses me <br>Like a medusa in the sand <br>It hurts but it possesses me <br>But I can feel myself again <br><br>Talk to me <br>Talk to me <br>Tell me how you really feel <br>Talk to me <br>Talk to me <br>Tell me what is fake and what is real]]></content><category term="Thomas Azier" label="Thomas Azier"/><category term="Talk To Me" label="Talk To Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SUPA/숨바꼭질/</id><title>SUPA - 숨바꼭질 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:10:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:10:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SUPA/%EC%88%A8%EB%B0%94%EA%BC%AD%EC%A7%88/" title="SUPA - 숨바꼭질 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꼭꼭 숨어라 <br>얜 그냥 친한 친구라는 <br>그 말 <br>넌 항상 그녀에게 <br>everyday <br>단 둘이 있을때완 <br>너무 다른 너 <br>뭘 그리 어색하게 <br>쳐다보니 <br>애매한 시선 <br>처리 어떡할래 <br>아닌 척 관심 <br>없는 척 하지만 난 <br>I don’t think so <br>더 이상 숨기려고 하지마 <br>난 이미 눈치채고 있는걸 <br>그래도 아니라면 no <br>꼭꼭 숨어라 <br>머리카락 보일라 <br>꼭꼭 숨겨라 <br>니 마음 다 보인다 <br>꼭꼭 숨어라 <br>머리카락 보일라 <br>꼭꼭 숨겨라 <br>뭘 그리 어색하게 <br>쳐다보니 <br>애매한 시선 처리 <br>어떡할래 <br>아닌 척 관심 <br>없는 척 하지만 난 <br>I don’t think so <br>더 이상 숨기려고 하지마 <br>난 이미 눈치채고 있는걸 <br>그래도 아니라면 no <br>꼭꼭 숨겨라 거 니 맘 <br>눈치 채던 말던 <br>그건 그냥 내 맘 <br>알잖아 너도 지금 <br>이미 늦어버린걸 <br>나도 그냥 모른 척 <br>넘어갈지도 몰라 <br>열까지 센다 <br>갈 수 있는데 까지 <br>더 멀리 Far away <br>어디 숨었던 <br>난 너를 찾으려 해 <br>나를 외면 하지 말아요 <br>왜 나를 두고 <br>딴 곳만 보나요 <br>나를 혼자 두지 말아요 <br>그대 맘 난 다 알아요 <br>I don’t think so <br>더 이상 숨기려고 하지마 <br>난 이미 눈치채고 있는걸 <br>그래도 아니라면 no <br>I don’t think so <br>더 이상 숨기려고 하지마 <br>난 이미 눈치채고 있는걸 <br>그래도 아니라면 no <br>꼭꼭 숨어라 <br>머리카락 보일라 <br>꼭꼭 숨겨라 <br>니 마음 다 보인다 <br>꼭꼭 숨어라 <br>머리카락 보일라 <br>꼭꼭 숨겨라 꼭 <br>]]></content><category term="SUPA" label="SUPA"/><category term="숨바꼭질" label="숨바꼭질"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SUPA/Sweet_Girl/</id><title>SUPA - Sweet Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:10:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:10:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SUPA/Sweet_Girl/" title="SUPA - Sweet Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey listen <br>난 널 생각해 <br>But I’m <br>너에게 말할 수 없는 <br>사소한 비밀은 숨겨야 해 <br>그건 <br>Never tell you <br>Even if you know <br>Cause I don’t know what <br>니 주위에 많은 <br>유혹들이 있단 걸 알지만 <br>니가 나를 택한 그 순간에 넌 <br>다시 되돌릴 수도 없는 <br>What you know fantasy <br>Sweet Girl <br>잠깐만 나를 바라봐 <br>니가 무슨 생각 하든 <br>널 가질 수 있어 <br>Sweet Girl <br>이젠 내 손을 잡아봐 <br>그렇게 내게로 <br>다가와 지금부터 <br>Would you be my boy <br>I gonna make you <br>feel so everything <br>잠시 시간을 잃어버려도 돼 <br>화려한 조명 속에 나를 봐 <br>그래 <br>Doing all this I prepared for you <br>Cause I don’t know what <br>니 주위에 많은 <br>유혹들이 있단 걸 알지만 <br>니가 나를 택한 그 순간에 넌 <br>다시 되돌릴 수도 없는 <br>What you know fantasy <br>Sweet Girl <br>잠깐만 나를 바라봐 <br>니가 무슨 생각 하든 <br>널 가질 수 있어 <br>Sweet Girl <br>이젠 내 손을 잡아봐 <br>그렇게 내게로 <br>다가와 지금부터 <br>Would you be my boy <br>뒤돌아 서지마 <br>난 널 위해 여기서 <br>모든 걸 보여 주려 해 <br>다신 너를 감추려도 마 <br>Find a fire <br>in your mind right now <br>이제 너를 데려갈게 <br>Sweet Girl <br>잠깐만 나를 바라봐 <br>니가 무슨 생각 하든 <br>널 가질 수 있어 <br>Sweet Girl <br>이젠 내 손을 잡아봐 <br>그렇게 내게로 <br>다가와 지금부터 <br>Would you be my boy <br>Sweet Girl <br>잠깐만 나를 바라봐 <br>니가 무슨 생각 하든 <br>널 가질 수 있어 <br>Sweet Girl <br>이젠 내 손을 잡아봐 <br>그렇게 내게로 <br>다가와 지금부터 <br>Would you be my boy <br>지금부터 <br>Would you be my boy <br>]]></content><category term="SUPA" label="SUPA"/><category term="Sweet Girl" label="Sweet Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/Daydreams/</id><title>Im_Glad_Its_You - Daydreams - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:10:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:10:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/Daydreams/" title="Im_Glad_Its_You - Daydreams - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Daydreams that you never want to leave <br>Only your own thoughts to keep you company <br>Like a room of strangers staring quietly <br>Playing make believe to keep you in between <br>Selfish and alone <br>Where did you go <br>Never find you in a memory <br>Never see you when my eyes are closed <br>Never present, my head's never full of you <br>Full of you <br><br>Blank stares and trying hard to be concerned <br>Filling in the blanks of lessons never learned <br>Point your eyes the wrong way just to feel secure <br>I feel your apathy <br>To me it all feels the same <br>I want to know how to think the way you think <br>About anyone but me <br>But you're never sure <br>Never present, I want to fill my head with you]]></content><category term="I`m Glad It`s You" label="I`m Glad It`s You"/><category term="Daydreams" label="Daydreams"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/Time_Capsule/</id><title>Im_Glad_Its_You - Time Capsule - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:11:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:11:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/Time_Capsule/" title="Im_Glad_Its_You - Time Capsule - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Behind closed eyes I was watching my mind wander <br>It's amazing all of the things you miss <br>When fear has kept you in <br>I was led past my trouble and last hopes of self preservation <br>And I watched as it all disappeared as though it had never been <br>Then I found you in the last place that I left you <br>In a diner, drinking coffee all alone <br>I can see your whole life pass by right in front of me <br>Yeah, I saw something I had never seen <br>And now I can't tell which foot is in the past <br>Spent whole days trying to move forward <br>But go back to my best dreams <br>Where I can see everything <br><br>Someday I'll be buried in your backyard <br>And I'll escape the twenty first century <br>And I'll always be a time capsule for you and me <br>And everything that we'd bring <br>And I'll see everything]]></content><category term="I`m Glad It`s You" label="I`m Glad It`s You"/><category term="Time Capsule" label="Time Capsule"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/Communion/</id><title>Im_Glad_Its_You - Communion - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:11:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:11:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/Communion/" title="Im_Glad_Its_You - Communion - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I put tin cans on string <br>And made a telephone from you to me <br>But every time you call, it seems I'm deaf to you <br>And numb to the touch <br><br>And on the other side of the wire <br>You stay out of sight, out of touch, and always on my mind <br>You're a language so foreign to me <br>That you always leave me questioning why there's nothing <br>It's just noise <br>And it's nothing at all like the sound of your voice <br>From the window, I swear I can see the telephone <br>Tangled up in the tree <br><br>And I don't know if you're still there <br>But I can't hear anything anymore <br>And I don't know if you're still there <br>But I can't hear anything anymore <br>And that's why we don't talk much anymore <br>That's why we don't talk much anymore <br>That's why we don't talk much anymore <br>We don't talk much <br>We don't talk much <br>We don't talk much <br>I wish we talked the way we used to]]></content><category term="I`m Glad It`s You" label="I`m Glad It`s You"/><category term="Communion" label="Communion"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/Small_Talk/</id><title>Im_Glad_Its_You - Small Talk - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:11:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:11:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/Small_Talk/" title="Im_Glad_Its_You - Small Talk - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Still talk in present tense <br>But I'm not with you when you're with me <br>I wish I could see through all the changes <br>But we both know that you're not with me when I'm with you <br><br>And listening's not easy when you've heard it all before <br>And heavy repetition gets so easy to ignore <br>So we can call this talking if that's what you need to hear <br>Just don't call it easy <br>'Cause it's just not easy <br><br>'Cause it's just not easy for me <br>When you're only a time and place <br>No, it's just not easy for me <br>'Cause you were more than a time and place]]></content><category term="I`m Glad It`s You" label="I`m Glad It`s You"/><category term="Small Talk" label="Small Talk"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/Curbside/</id><title>Im_Glad_Its_You - Curbside - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:11:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:11:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/Curbside/" title="Im_Glad_Its_You - Curbside - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Take a long last look at everything <br>That means anything to you me <br>There's not a thing left to say <br>Just watch it all fade away <br>And there's a funny thing <br>The way it all still runs through me <br>And if it's all you leave me with, I don't even mind <br>Just a long last look at everything we were before <br><br>Most days and most nights <br>You spend your time trying to hide <br>In the last breaths of your past <br>Pretending to be anything that'll distract you <br>From the life that you let go <br>But I know that it's hard <br>When everything reminds you that you're always falling behind <br>Everything reminds you that you're probably wasting your time <br>Everything reminds you that you can't ever be what you were <br>But at least you can say <br><br>If you didn't stand by me, I'd be alone <br>If you didn't stand by me, I'd still be alone <br>It was a life that I stole from late nights on curbsides <br>And I can't seem to ever get it back <br>You were my only peace of mind <br>It left when you left <br>And I can't seem to ever get it back]]></content><category term="I`m Glad It`s You" label="I`m Glad It`s You"/><category term="Curbside" label="Curbside"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/Keepsake/</id><title>Im_Glad_Its_You - Keepsake - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:11:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:11:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/Keepsake/" title="Im_Glad_Its_You - Keepsake - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stare at your old favorite photographs just to come back to life <br>Or picture some new friends <br>Who do things that people like me never see <br>Been hiding the feeling behind the lines of a sarcastic smile <br>Still waiting to hear you say <br>Yeah, I guess I still feel pretty small <br>When you find dead birds on your walk home <br>Do you feel like nothing, the way I do <br><br>Well, I would love to just sit this one out <br>Because I already the know the way that these things go <br>Running it over and over again <br>And you're still trying to find a way out <br><br>And I've got better things to do than stay inside all day <br>While everybody leaves <br>Sinking in sweeter memories 'cause they're all you get to keep <br>A slow decay in some clean, well lighted place <br>And I don't want to stay here anymore <br>'Cause I'm not afraid to die <br>I'm not afraid to die <br>I just want to be something for you to leave behind]]></content><category term="I`m Glad It`s You" label="I`m Glad It`s You"/><category term="Keepsake" label="Keepsake"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/The_Things_I_Never_Say/</id><title>Im_Glad_Its_You - The Things I Never Say - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:11:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:11:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/The_Things_I_Never_Say/" title="Im_Glad_Its_You - The Things I Never Say - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Never told you how the ending was my favorite part <br>But you mean more to me than anything <br>Never speak up from the spirit that I feel behind my eyes <br>I just stay up late with all those things that make you wonder <br>What's left when I'm dead <br>Or the time left between now and then <br><br>Give me all the things you never say anymore <br>All your adolescent eagerness <br>All the bitter thoughts get buried in the floor <br>Your empty words just fail to make you feel <br>Something close to something real <br>Like most people, always living in the dark <br>Like the things I never say <br>I don't want this anymore]]></content><category term="I`m Glad It`s You" label="I`m Glad It`s You"/><category term="The Things I Never Say" label="The Things I Never Say"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/The_Things_We_Lose/</id><title>Im_Glad_Its_You - The Things We Lose - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:11:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:11:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Im_Glad_Its_You/The_Things_We_Lose/" title="Im_Glad_Its_You - The Things We Lose - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So this is progress <br>This is the way that the we get <br>From swimming oceans in my head <br>It's good to know in times like these <br>There's a counterfeit for everything we lose along the way <br><br>But I want to see everything with clarity <br>I want to feel a real sense of beauty <br>I want to fight <br>Show me what it takes to feel alive]]></content><category term="I`m Glad It`s You" label="I`m Glad It`s You"/><category term="The Things We Lose" label="The Things We Lose"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Omighty/Holy_내가_부르고_싶어서_부르는_노래/</id><title>Denzel_Omighty - Holy (내가 부르고 싶어서 부르는 노래) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:12:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:12:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Omighty/Holy_%EB%82%B4%EA%B0%80_%EB%B6%80%EB%A5%B4%EA%B3%A0_%EC%8B%B6%EC%96%B4%EC%84%9C_%EB%B6%80%EB%A5%B4%EB%8A%94_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="Denzel_Omighty - Holy (내가 부르고 싶어서 부르는 노래) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I just wanna know <br>we holy night <br>I just wanna hold you tight <br>Always ride fuck my life <br>내 뻔한 말을 왜 몰라 <br>i'll go whatever route <br>ever route ever route <br>And you sayin <br>now we broke up <br>now we broke up <br>now we broke up <br>지금 이 순간 <br>I've been here all day <br>너와 함께한 <br>순간이고 시간이고 <br>내 사랑도 다 burnin’ <br>oh 아무런 덫 없는 <br>것들 이더라고 <br>Can't hear them <br>난 너와 못해 <br>저 저기 끝까지로 <br>우리 달려가지도 <br>You can't break the law <br>with me <br>아무 맛이 없던 니 의미 <br>그래 여기까지네 <br>이미 이젠 끝이네 <br>dayout <br>The sun is going down <br>너의 감정이 다르잖아 <br>why not oh no yeah <br>motherfuckin 잊지마 <br>그 밤의 너의 show <br>단 하루도 뜨질 않아 <br>너의 몸과 손 <br>입술과 허리를 <br>안은 손을 봐 <br>oh no oh no <br>dayout <br>1번출구와 2번출구 사이 <br>내 그림자는 <br>어디로 가야 할지 <br>나 많이 망설였어 <br>회기역에 <br>남은 건 혼자여서 <br>니가 없는 <br>내가 익숙해질까봐 <br>혼자 겁내 고개를 돌려도 <br>방한켠엔 니가 있어 <br>니가 있어야만 하는데 <br>나 혼자였어 <br>그래 정신을 차려보니 <br>거짓일까 너의 눈웃음도 <br>다 꿈일까 <br>가만있지 못한 밤 <br>과거로 돌아가 <br>우린 쉴새 없었던 <br>너의 품에서 다시 <br>새벽을 잃고 싶어 <br>The sun is going down <br>너의 감정이 다르잖아 <br>why not oh no yeah <br>motherfuckin 잊지마 <br>그 밤의 너의 show <br>단 하루도 뜨질 않아 <br>너의 몸과 손 <br>입술과 허리를 <br>안은 손을 봐 <br>oh no oh no <br>dayout <br>I just wanna know we <br>holy night <br>I just wanna hold you tight <br>I just wanna know we <br>holy night <br>I just wanna hold you tight <br>]]></content><category term="Denzel O`mighty" label="Denzel O`mighty"/><category term="Holy (내가 부르고 싶어서 부르는 노래)" label="Holy (내가 부르고 싶어서 부르는 노래)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Omighty/Xo/</id><title>Denzel_Omighty - Xo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:12:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:12:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Omighty/Xo/" title="Denzel_Omighty - Xo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[no solution 공식 없어 <br>어떤 값을 대입 해도 <br>우리 둘의 관계는 error <br>그러니 미지수는 빼줘 <br>그저 생각한 대로 <br>it's okay 머리 속에 <br>뉴런이 전달하는 <br>방식이 다르지 all day <br>i know that you know that <br>여기와 저기 <br>넌 보기만 할거니 <br>가까이 붙어보니 <br>니 생각보다 어렵지 <br>it's alright <br>you're just recognize <br>it's alright <br>you're just recognize <br>just XO <br>해쳐가려 하지마 <br>아무도 믿지마 <br>다 거짓말 <br>just XO XO <br>XO XO XO XO <br>Just XO <br>벗어나려 하지마 <br>아침과 함께 가 <br>right all in night <br>just XO XO <br>XO XO XO XO <br>니가 어떤 문제인지 yeah <br>니가 어떤 여자인지 yeah yeah <br>내가 어떤 문제인지 yeah <br>don't know bitches <br>Just because i love you yeah <br>I gotta admit it <br>Give me a little bit <br>What am I afraid fo <br>I gotta admit it <br>니가 어떤 인연인지 yea yeah <br>니가 자꾸 내 머릴 <br>아프게 더 해 <br>그게 끝이네 <br>it's alright <br>you're just recognize <br>it's alright <br>you're just recognize <br>just XO <br>해쳐가려 하지마 <br>아무도 믿지마 <br>다 거짓말 <br>just XO XO <br>XO XO XO XO <br>Just XO <br>벗어나려 하지마 <br>아침과 함께 가 <br>right all in night <br>just XO XO <br>XO XO XO XO <br>I need it I'm a mess now <br>Let it crash down on me now <br>I need it I'm a mess now <br>Let it crash down on me now <br>I need it I'm a mess now <br>Let it crash down on me now <br>I need it I'm a mess now <br>Let it crash down on me now <br>just XO <br>해쳐가려 하지마 <br>아무도 믿지마 <br>다 거짓말 <br>just XO XO <br>XO XO XO XO <br>Just XO <br>벗어나려 하지마 <br>아침과 함께 가 <br>right all in night <br>just XO XO <br>XO XO XO XO <br>]]></content><category term="Denzel O`mighty" label="Denzel O`mighty"/><category term="Xo" label="Xo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Omighty/Doin_Bish/</id><title>Denzel_Omighty - Doin` Bish - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:12:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:12:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Omighty/Doin_Bish/" title="Denzel_Omighty - Doin` Bish - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[연연해 마 니가 잘 알잖아 <br>다 바라지마 다르게 생각하자 <br>잘해보잔 그런 말은 하지마 <br>그저 기쁜 것만 <br>서로 공유하며 웃자 <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>i'm so good so good so good <br>oh no no no <br>i'm so good so good so good <br>oh no no no <br>슬프고 우울한 건 <br>니 남자친구한테 맡길게 <br>걔한텐 비밀인데 <br>오늘 하루 종일 좀 빌릴게 <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>i'm so good so good so good <br>oh no no no <br>i'm so good so good so good <br>oh no no no <br>내가 매일 매일 <br>매일같이 손을 들고서 계속 <br>니가 슬픈 느낌 <br>다 지워 줄 수 있어 <br>I can't rewind <br>I'm giving you my eyes <br>가져가 도로 니 맘 <br>i get it in <br>그런 방식 <br>It always hurt <br>또 그래 다시 <br>So you pray to get it back <br>널 잃어가네 이 밤에 <br>쓰고 나면 버릴 까봐 yeah <br>아무 말하지 마 <br>내가 다 하잖아 <br>좀 더 바라지마 <br>우린 서로 맞아 <br>그래 서야 서로 안 보인단 말 <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>just doin' bish <br>i'm so good so good so good <br>i'm so good so good so good <br>]]></content><category term="Denzel O`mighty" label="Denzel O`mighty"/><category term="Doin` Bish" label="Doin` Bish"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Omighty/Me_And_You/</id><title>Denzel_Omighty - Me And You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:12:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:12:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Omighty/Me_And_You/" title="Denzel_Omighty - Me And You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[i just me and me and you <br>just me and me and you <br>It's going down for sure <br>꽤 겁 많은 애처럼 감아줘 <br>i just me and me and you <br>just me and me and you <br>니 머릿결을 뒤로 젖혀둬 <br>yea just me and me and you <br>네 머릴 뒤로 <br>i don't worry <br>니가 양손으로 그려 원 <br>bitches <br>love the way it tastes <br>know it 이곳엔 one menu <br>아무렴 이젠 <br>one last night fuckin show <br>네 인생에 최고로 <br>느낄거야 slow <br>이제서 느껴 fuckin <br>니 one love <br>눈빛에 문제를 읽어내 <br>oh no <br>신경 꺼둬 <br>위를 눌러 round me <br>안보여도 알어 <br>너의 아래 위 <br>입을 맞춰 동선에는 <br>문제 없어 <br>gonna make you feel <br>니가 변하는걸 보고 <br>내가 널 더 눌러 <br>그런 다음 이 세계는 <br>더 색달라 가득히 <br>i don't need a fuck yo second <br>마음이 널 더 원해 <br>어느새 밝음이 <br>i just me and me and you <br>just me and me and you <br>It's going down for sure <br>꽤 겁많은 애처럼 감아줘 <br>i just me and me and you <br>just me and me and you <br>니 머릿결을 뒤로 젖혀둬 <br>yea just me and me and you <br>우린 오늘부터 먼가 정의하기 <br>애매한 그런 관계가 될 텐데 <br>어때 난 좋아 동의하니 <br>내일 모르겠단 입고리 짓지마 <br>이미 알고 있겠지만 <br>언제든 지금 일 때를 <br>기다려 말해줘 <br>나도 준비할게 우리 사이 <br>점이 찍힐지 안 찍힐지 <br>계속 모아둘게 <br>up and up up and up <br>위로 더 올라만 가야 돼 <br>전부 몰아주겠어 <br>전부 몰아주겠어 <br>누가 뭐라든 됐어 <br>미로 갖히게 됐어 <br>my rule에 적용 <br>i just me and me and you <br>just me and me and you <br>It's going down for sure <br>꽤 겁많은 애처럼 감아줘 <br>i just me and me and you <br>just me and me and you <br>니 머릿결을 뒤로 젖혀둬 <br>yea just me and me and you <br>]]></content><category term="Denzel O`mighty" label="Denzel O`mighty"/><category term="Me And You" label="Me And You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Omighty/Continue/</id><title>Denzel_Omighty - Continue - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:12:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:12:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Omighty/Continue/" title="Denzel_Omighty - Continue - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[설레임이 무뎌지는 그 순간 <br>우린 더 깊은 곳을 향해 가 <br>oh nah I'll give you <br>my everything <br>oh nah I'll give you <br>my everything <br>여기까지 왔어 <br>잘 참고 힘들게 왔어 <br>우리 이제 쉴새 없이 계속 <br>하고 싶은 말은 그냥 뱉어 <br>baby 우린 둘 다 비슷해 <br>style ego intelli thinkin' <br>너와 같은 배에 탈게 <br>all day <br>알잖아 노는 내가 저을게 <br>시간을 멈추고 싶어 <br>너와 같은 공간에 서서 <br>말해 원하는 건 모두 <br>매일 오늘 같이 놀아 재껴 <br>내일 일이 있다면 미뤄 <br>너도 나와 복사 붙여 <br>mirror <br>이때가 아니면 <br>놓칠 수 밖에 없는걸 <br>나는 이미 알고 있어 <br>I'll give you <br>my everything tonight <br>I'll give you <br>my everything tonight <br>I'll give you <br>my everything tonight <br>I'll give you <br>my everything tonight <br>I'll give you <br>my everything tonight <br>I'll give you <br>my everything tonight <br>I'll give you <br>my everything tonight <br>I'll give you <br>my everything tonight <br>This is how it is <br>this is how we live huh <br>This is how it is <br>this is how we live huh <br>This is how it is <br>this is how we live huh <br>니 허리부터 <br>tension <br>미쳐가네 누워있어 계속 <br>내가 전부 먼저 다 하겠어 <br>그래 여긴 쟤완 다른 행성 <br>니가 더 날 잡아줘야 해 내 손 <br>벌써 흔들리네 허리하고 <br>oh <br>I'll give you <br>my everything tonight oh <br>I'll give you <br>my everything tonight oh <br>I'll give you <br>my everything tonight oh <br>I'll give you <br>my everything tonight oh <br>]]></content><category term="Denzel O`mighty" label="Denzel O`mighty"/><category term="Continue" label="Continue"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Omighty/Save_Me/</id><title>Denzel_Omighty - Save Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:12:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:12:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Omighty/Save_Me/" title="Denzel_Omighty - Save Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh get ma eyes <br>save me now save me now <br>Oh get ma eyes <br>save me now save me now <br>니가 날 구해줄래 <br>그래 더 이상 기횐 없어 <br>쓸데 없는 이런 저런 <br>니 머리 속 비워버려 <br>니가 날 구해줄래 <br>다시 돌아 갈수 있어 <br>우리 조금 더 달아도 돼 <br>그래 그 맛이 조금 비었어 <br>니가 날 구해줄래 <br>알아 바로 닿을 수 있어 <br>미끄러워 보여도 넘어지지 않아 <br>너무 깊이 박혀 있어 <br>save me 당장 save me babe <br>save me 당장 save me babe <br>날 구해줄래 니가 <br>날 구해줄래 니가 <br>날 구해줄래 니가 날 구해줄래 <br>Oh get ma eyes <br>save me now save me now <br>oh save me save me save save me <br>save me save me save save me <br>anytime oh no anytime <br>can you save me love me <br>I think I need that back <br>다시 돌아갈 수 있을 땐 <br>이러지는 말아 너 <br>난 널 몰랐어도 돼 <br>알고 싶지 않아 널 말야 <br>난 꼭 그랬어야 해 <br>Can't do it like that <br>니가 나를 원할 때 <br>여태 넌 뭘 마셨는진 몰라도 <br>내 물에 마른 너의 가뭄 차도 <br>나의 맘에 물은 빠져 <br>옮겨가지 네게 <br>I know I know it's late I know I know it <br>너와 걔는 비슷해 <br>I don't know ya I don't <br>I know I know it's late I know I know it <br>나와 걔는 아닌데 <br>I don't know I don't <br>날 구해줄래 <br>니가 울지 않을 수 있게 <br>이젠 거긴 가지 않을게 <br>니가 날 안을 수 있게 <br>Oh get ma eyes <br>save me now save me now <br>oh save me save me save save me <br>save me save me save save me <br>anytime oh no anytime <br>]]></content><category term="Denzel O`mighty" label="Denzel O`mighty"/><category term="Save Me" label="Save Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Omighty/탈피/</id><title>Denzel_Omighty - 탈피 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:12:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:12:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Omighty/%ED%83%88%ED%94%BC/" title="Denzel_Omighty - 탈피 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[oh 난 네게 할말 많아 <br>너만 마른 하늘 같아 <br>꽤 길었지 아마 우리 만난 시간 <br>사실 아직 좋아도 생각이 많아 <br>너만 바라본 날들이 시려워 <br>또 난 네게 썼던 모든 돈 <br>그리고 시간 아깝지 않아 <br>다만 그 반만 알수 있을까 넌 <br>oh 난 네게 할말 많아 <br>너만 마른 하늘 같아 <br>니 영혼에서 탈피해 <br>살아볼게 날 위해 <br>널 미워하는 날 이해해 <br>날 이해해 날 이해해 <br>니 영혼에서 탈피해 <br>살아볼게 날 위해 <br>널 증오하는 날 위해 <br>날 이해해 날 이해해 <br>oh 난 그래도 난 너에게 <br>아무 말도 안해 <br>그건 멋없는 거라 배웠거든 oh 난 <br>난 니 술잔위에 오른 술들이 아냐 <br>니 말에 흘린 눈물이 아냐 <br>어쩌다 보니 여기로 왔지만 <br>괜찮아 너 땜에 힘든게 아냐 <br>I’ll fight you till the end <br>Cause we couldn't let it fuckin end <br>you know 우린 벌써 져있네 <br>근데 내 두발은 서있네 <br>너만을 보고 살았던 <br>이 시간을 지우고 말았지 <br>깨끗히 닦았지 bish <br>그 누날 닮았던 앨 보면 <br>이렇게 살아선 안된다 생각해 bish <br>나 혼자 울었지 몰래 <br>너 없이 살았지 원래 <br>다 필요없지 나 원래 너의a ay <br>너만 바라본 날들이 시려워 <br>또 난 네게 썼던 모든 돈 <br>그리고 시간 아깝지 않아 <br>다만 그 반만 알 수 있을까 넌 <br>oh 난 네게 할말 많아 <br>너만 마른 하늘 같아 <br>니 영혼에서 탈피해 <br>살아볼게 날 위해 <br>널 미워하는 날 이해해 <br>날 이해해 날 이해해 <br>니 영혼에서 탈피해 <br>살아볼게 날 위해 <br>널 증오하는 날 위해 <br>날 이해해 날 이해해 <br>oh 난 그래도 난 너에게 <br>아무 말도 안해 <br>그건 멋없는 거라 배웠거든 oh 난 <br>]]></content><category term="Denzel O`mighty" label="Denzel O`mighty"/><category term="탈피" label="탈피"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SiMs/Spinning_Away/</id><title>SiMs - Spinning Away - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:17:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:17:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SiMs/Spinning_Away/" title="SiMs - Spinning Away - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You were in a shouting match with god on the fire escape of the sound gallery and I thought <br>What a waste <br>What a waste <br>Of perfectly good cocaine <br><br>Small change got rained on with his own 38 <br>And he couldn't find a saint to blame <br>What to Say <br>Emptied every cupboard, covered every cave, undid every buckle <br>Nothing but the plate gave <br>Nothing was the same <br>What to say <br><br>A boy on a plane broke through the clouds for the first time <br>And I didn't see a single solitary grandparent <br>Or a dead dog <br>And my head cocked staring through the plexiglass <br>Can you picture that <br>Was the picture looking back <br>And several curtains close and lift <br>And I sat stiff, supposing this was it <br>That moment was a monument <br>Did not intend to get to so morbid <br>But I never felt more <br>Out here in orbit <br><br>Are you out here spinning too <br>Are you out here spinning too <br><br>Space bending around me <br>Pounding boundary <br>Found me echolocating <br>Everything sounding <br>Everything in it <br>Are you spinning <br>Are you here <br>Everything in it, everything spinning <br>Are you here <br>Are you spinning <br>Are you here spinning too]]></content><category term="SiMs" label="SiMs"/><category term="Spinning Away" label="Spinning Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SiMs/Flash_Paper/</id><title>SiMs - Flash Paper - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:17:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:17:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SiMs/Flash_Paper/" title="SiMs - Flash Paper - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Too corrupt <br>I was giving up <br>On this ball of clay <br>What would you say <br>Turning til we turned away <br>I was too tuned in <br>Couldn't tune out <br>And it gets so loud <br>And I'm feeling I'm got a feeling I'm bound <br><br>Vibrate like a tuning fork <br>Like New York <br>Like a sub bass taking deep breaths when I'm back on the concourse <br>And my laugh <br>My laugh is like the bottom of the ocean <br>Feet flap like wind up birds <br>The gears and the cranks loop feedback <br>And what I find absurd is you still comehow can't find your words <br>I put my seat back <br>Oh my, how the tides <br>Somehwere between the desire and the spasm it happens <br>Right before fire hits vacuum <br>The cannon that's found in the wave of the sine <br>The divine dividing the atom <br>For thine is the wow <br>Haven't you had enough now <br>Stand at the ground <br>Intend to ascend from the plow <br>Stand at the bow <br>Into the heart of somewhere, somehow <br>Insert the order destiny <br>Disarm you from your weaponry <br>Sequence all the entropy <br>What's heavenly is drawn from your quarter <br>The gesture doesn't measure me <br>You worry about your legacy to carry you forward <br>From the hollow men to farther <br>Well, I don't bother <br>I don't bother <br>I don't bother <br>I don't bother <br>I don't bother <br><br>I'm flash paper <br>Flash paper x5 <br><br>And that may be <br>And the radius burns <br>Uranium <br>And the gradient is greying <br>And it radiates a feeling like I'm peeling off the floor <br>Or I'm peeling out the door <br>Aching for the way that it were <br>And the wipers don't work <br>Blurred <br>And the viper's at lurch <br>And the sniper is perched somewhere along that berm <br>Somewhere along my wherewithal exhausted <br>The noxious air of the logic <br>The emperor's new cotton <br>The lockpicks left in pockets <br>And the ladies and germs in the stadium cheer <br>And I think of cicadas <br>Flash bang, disappear <br>That doesn't fill me with straw, nor does it gnaw at the core <br>It doesn't make me feel hollow <br>But it doesn't put me on board <br><br>Too corrupt <br>On this ball of clay <br><br>Flash paper x12]]></content><category term="SiMs" label="SiMs"/><category term="Flash Paper" label="Flash Paper"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SiMs/Onehundred/</id><title>SiMs - Onehundred - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:17:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:17:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SiMs/Onehundred/" title="SiMs - Onehundred - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been living in a fish bowl <br>Everybody looking, everybody looking, yeah <br>Looking at the kid go <br>Doing what they wouldn't <br>Doing what they couldn't <br><br>Beats up, hanging out the window <br>Everybody juking, everybody juking, yeah <br>Getting up then we get low <br>Everybody pushing, everybody pushing, yeah <br><br>Uh, it's the one they thumb they nose at <br>Low class, brutal dance, looking like some road rash <br>No hands, go fast, wrote 'em off, no chance <br>No control, now look at him go <br>If I want it I get it <br>I just lassoed a comet <br>Just to know that I did it <br>You said blah blah blah blah blah like I invited the comments <br>I need to see all the bodies <br>Before the toe tag <br>Cro mags, we gotta know <br><br>I've been living in a fish bowl <br>Everybody looking, everybody looking, yeah <br>Looking at the kid go <br>Doing what they wouldn't <br>Doing what they couldn't <br><br>Beats up, hanging out the window <br>Everybody juking, everybody juking, yeah <br>Getting up then we get low <br>Everybody pushing, everybody pushing, yeah <br><br>I stopped tripping about the powers that be <br>Started thinking with the powers of ten <br>Give you a sense of the lens <br>Follow my lead as I cut through the breeze <br>Every step GPSed, CC TVed <br>Every breath squeezed through some SJW's tweet <br>You're so off beat and so PC <br>They take the sweet right out the cantelope <br>Damn, they take the beats right out the animal <br>Can I live <br>Well ain't that a bucket of dicks <br>I was just having fun running from the abyss <br>Now you coming in hot <br>And telling me what the shit is or what it is not <br>And what's cut from a rib <br>Script never fit, pink mist <br>Ever since me and my brother were kids <br>Newports flip tricks on a grip <br>Tell the world which dick he can kiss <br>Killer big, leave the rest for the buzzards to pick <br>Uh, a real son of a bitch <br>From the hip <br>For the whole clique to split <br>Nothing but a flick of the wrist <br><br>I've been living in a fish bowl <br>Everybody looking, everybody looking, yeah <br>Looking at the kid go <br>Doing what they wouldn't <br>Doing what they couldn't <br><br>Beats up, hanging out the window <br>Everybody juking, everybody juking, yeah <br>Getting up then we get low <br>Everybody pushing, everybody pushing, yeah <br><br>When I dip they dip <br>When I jump they jump <br>I just talk my shit <br>Have my fun <br>Make it buck <br><br>Me and my boss chick making boss moves <br>Driving you crazy in your lazy costume <br>Huh, you want to fake it till you make it shit <br>I'm on some etheridge, fuck it, break this shit <br>Hey, I don't know what you say <br>I don't think it's a game <br>So I care who wins <br>I was scared sick, used to disassociate <br>Now look at all these hairpins I negotiate <br>Pssh, styling on em <br>Wild as a motherfucker <br>Higher than you buying it <br>Blame my environment <br>There's something in my wiring <br>I don't know, maybe they're too microscope <br>Maybe I'm too macro with the tackles on the microphone <br>Oh I think they like it though <br>Trying to keep it lighter but it's darker out <br>Pull the marker out <br>Make a map about the moment <br>Go ahead, go in, I'm zoning, I'm coping <br>I'm hoping I'm rolling, I wrote it <br>I made it for you <br>True <br>Just trying to step around the dog doo doo <br><br>I've been living in a fish bowl <br>Everybody looking, everybody looking, yeah <br>Looking at the kid go <br>Doing what they wouldn't <br>Doing what they couldn't <br><br>Beats up, hanging out the window <br>Everybody juking, everybody juking, yeah <br>Getting up then we get low <br>Everybody pushing, everybody pushing, yeah]]></content><category term="SiMs" label="SiMs"/><category term="Onehundred" label="Onehundred"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SiMs/Brutal_Dance/</id><title>SiMs - Brutal Dance - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:17:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:17:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SiMs/Brutal_Dance/" title="SiMs - Brutal Dance - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[SLIDING THROUGH THE BELLY <br>I DO THE BRUTAL DANCE <br>RIDE AROUND LIKE I STOLE IT <br>MY TRUE ROMANCE <br>ALL DAY <br>LET GO THE EFFORT <br>CAN'T BE SO PRECIOUS <br>MORE THAN EVER <br>GETTING BY <br>SO IT GOES <br>BEEN LOW, BEEN HIGH <br>CHIPPING DOWN TO WHAT I REALLY LOVE <br>BAPTIZED IN A MUDSLIDE <br>HANG TEN AH YEAH <br>SURF THE EPHEMERA <br>THE WORLD BEEN CRAZY <br>POCKET FULL OF SAND, WHERE YOU AT <br>WHERE YOU AT <br>BLADE IN MY HAND, CUT THE FAT, CUT THE FAT <br>HERE COMES THE SHOVEL <br>COME TO TUCK YOU UNDER <br>DON'T YOU LOVE TO HUNT FOR TROUBLE <br>BEFORE I RIP I RUMBLE, RUMBLE <br><br>FINDING LOVE <br>DYING YOUNG <br>SOMETHING INSIDE OF US CLIMBING OUT, LIGHTING UP SOMETHING REMINDING US <br>WHERE YOU AT WHERE YOU AT <br>GET RELENTLESS WITH IT <br>WHERE YOU AT WHERE YOU AT <br>LET'S GET RECKLESS WITH IT <br>WHERE YOU AT <br>HOW I LOVE IT, LIVE IT, ATTACK IT <br>I KEEP COMING AND I GET IT <br>RIGHT NOW MORE THAN EVER <br>NOW MORE THAN EVER <br><br>MY MIND IS RACING WHILE I SIT IN TRAFFIC <br>DON'T WANT TO GET TOO BACKED UP <br>DON'T WANT TO GET TOO DRAMATIC <br>BUT THE MAGNET TO THE MADNESS THAT PUTS MY FRIENDS IN THEIR CASKETS IS WEIGHING HEAVY ON ME <br>I AIN'T MADE ENOUGH <br>NO WAITING UP <br>I FEEL LIKE I FEEL LIFE TOO MUCH <br>I FEEL HIGH, I FEEL LOW, I FEEL BOTH, I FEEL FUCKED <br>I'VE BEEN THINKING ON MY SINS FOR THE LAST FOUR BLOCKS <br>THAT'S TWO HAIL MARYS AND A HALF COURT SHOT <br>SOMETHING TOUGH ON MYSELF <br>DRAG MY BODY THROUGH THE VELDT <br>AND VOW TO DO THE MOST <br>LEAVE NONE FOR LATER <br>PRAY FOR MY HATERS]]></content><category term="SiMs" label="SiMs"/><category term="Brutal Dance" label="Brutal Dance"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SiMs/Icarus/</id><title>SiMs - Icarus - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:17:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:17:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SiMs/Icarus/" title="SiMs - Icarus - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I heard they prey on weak <br>I heard they play for keeps <br>I feel 'em grabbing at my feet <br>I heard them say don't speak <br>I just hit another level <br>Watch 'em try to pull me down <br>With the petty, with the heavy <br>Put the devil in the crown <br>What can I say to you <br>I'm too right brain for you <br>Twain my communique <br>You, you are what's in <br>Supreme <br>Fuckboy starter pack <br>I'm Huck Finn, huck shit, hassoi <br>Living art in fact <br>I see deceit, I see 'em back stab <br>I've got no need for that <br>I'm sliding off like the goddamn pizza rat <br>I'm out, I'm out, with that free that I just found <br>My sound and it bumps <br>Look at what amounts from the jump <br>And I'm never coming down <br><br>I an living lawless thinking I won't come down, come down <br>I am flying high now thinking I won't come down, come down <br><br>All the doubters <br>They can shout out from the towers <br>I just laugh, I just stay up <br>What a way to waste your hours <br>I'm not wastin', I'm not wastin' <br>Boy I'm racing, got no patience <br>I ain't stressing, count my blessings <br>I go right into it <br>Burn the brightest 'til it's done <br>Right into the sun <br>More cognitive than dissonance <br>They call me Icarus <br>I'm stretching my whole frame out <br>They're readying their takedowns from the safe ground <br>Pulling all their blades out <br>Cut me up, cut me up, fuck me up, what are they really gonna take <br>Cuff me to the truth of failure <br>Ay that's okay <br>While you're living like a stowaway, I go my own <br>Far from perfect <br>Let no person put a verdict on that, no way <br>Cannot touch me, cannot touch me <br>I am beauty, I am ugly <br>I am living art <br>A ok play your part <br><br>I an living lawless thinking I won't come down, come down <br>I am flying high now thinking I won't come down, come down]]></content><category term="SiMs" label="SiMs"/><category term="Icarus" label="Icarus"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SiMs/A_Bad_Flying_Bird/</id><title>SiMs - A Bad Flying Bird - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:17:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:17:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SiMs/A_Bad_Flying_Bird/" title="SiMs - A Bad Flying Bird - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been a real proper bit chomper <br>Leaning on my locker looking for the glitch <br>Since forever, never fit <br>Heavy steeper, filter through the blades for scales <br>Moccasins are swimming too <br>Forbidden fruit, they're kidding you <br>Just killing all the kid in you <br>I get into the wildest <br>Style is off the stylus <br>Never listened to the mild guiding all these blind pilots <br>That's fifty shades of beige <br>Fifty shades of pumpkin spice <br>Fifty ways of throwing shade on something bright <br>I was different <br>I was surfing on the rain where it's purple <br>Only corners cut, making squares into circles <br>The whole idea was so neutered <br>Commuter in a stupor suit <br>OK Computer, stupid future <br>Well, they're so removed <br>Straight out of the catalog <br>Middle of the mall shit <br>I came from the battle fog <br>Analog snake bit <br>Just might be the light to impress upon your insight <br>This is what happens when you feed him after midnight <br><br>I want you to say something different for me <br>Wake up, all you do is play dumb <br>I want you to say something different for me <br>Play dumb, but I want you to wake up <br><br>I was always too weird for the cool ones <br>Too smart for the dope ones <br>Cut bait found woke ones <br>We made our own, something out the box <br>Something we could rock <br>Found some ply, found some parts <br>No comply, grinding, coping 'til it sparks <br>Then I used the watts, flipped the future shock to something useful <br>Before the shoe could drop <br>Before the coup de grace <br>Been around since the beta <br>Made some layups, missed some easy shots <br>But without the fatal ones <br>It wouldn't be the same <br>Spin cycle spinning bum outs, can't blame the malaise <br>But it's that same lazy blase that gets 'em hit with the strays <br>What to say <br>What to say <br>They're not thinking anyway <br>I'm on the case though, separate the flavor from the mayo <br>Felt like they were on the payroll <br>Felt like I was getting KO'd <br>Lights Out Paris that's my word <br>I'm a bad flying bird <br>I've flown into some windows, put the air back in the windpipe <br>This what happens when a bad one goes up in flight <br><br>I want you to say something different for me <br>Wake up, all you do is play dumb <br>I want you to say something different for me <br>Play dumb, but I want you to wake up <br><br>I put that on my last dying words on this beautiful earth <br>I'm a bad flying bird <br>Making it work]]></content><category term="SiMs" label="SiMs"/><category term="A Bad Flying Bird" label="A Bad Flying Bird"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mackenzie_Nicole/Deleted/</id><title>Mackenzie_Nicole - Deleted - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:18:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:18:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mackenzie_Nicole/Deleted/" title="Mackenzie_Nicole - Deleted - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah yeah <br><br>Say what you gotta say, yeah <br>Turn around and run the other way other way, yeah <br>Read it, read it, yeah you said it <br>That's the price I gotta pay <br>So keep doin' what you're doin' if it feels right <br>Is that really what it takes to make you sleep at night Alright <br>You didn't have to look me up <br>Now I'm looking down to try <br><br>You don't like what you see Deleted <br>I don't know what you want me to be Deleted <br>And I came here to do me Deleted <br>And so if you don't agree <br>Deleted <br><br>I could just keep it inside, you could ignore what I said <br>No, I got nothing to hide, plus you don't know where I stand <br>It's not about you, it's about me <br>You Actin' Like you Know, so you can go <br><br>Tear me down, tear me down, tear me down <br>Let me down, let me down <br><br>Can you say it to my face <br>Kinda hurts me, but it fades <br>I'm feeling kinda like What'ev <br>Keep on throwing shade <br>So keep doin' what you're doin' if it feels right <br>Is that really what it takes to make you sleep at night Alright <br>See I love it, love it, love it <br>The city'll see, watch me rise above it <br><br>You don't like what you see Deleted <br>I don't know what you want me to be Deleted <br>And I came here to do me Deleted <br>And so if you don't agree <br>Deleted <br><br>I could just keep it inside, you could ignore what I said <br>No, I got nothing to hide, plus you don't know where I stand <br>It's not about you, it's about me <br>You Actin' Like you Know, so you can go <br><br>Tear me down, tear me down, tear me down <br>Let me down, let me down easy <br>Tear me down, tear me down, tear me down <br>Let me down, let me down <br><br>You don't like what you see Deleted <br>I don't know what you want me to be Deleted <br>And I came here to do me Deleted <br>And so if you don't agree <br>Deleted <br><br>I could just keep it inside, you could ignore what I said <br>No, I got nothing to hide, plus you don't know where I stand <br>It's not about you, it's about me <br>You Actin' Like you Know, so you can go]]></content><category term="Mackenzie Nicole" label="Mackenzie Nicole"/><category term="Deleted" label="Deleted"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Danny_Howard/Dont_Wanna_Stop/</id><title>Danny_Howard - Don`t Wanna Stop - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:18:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:18:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Danny_Howard/Dont_Wanna_Stop/" title="Danny_Howard - Don`t Wanna Stop - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[punchica pum <br>punchica pum <br>punchica pum <br><br>punchica pum <br>chica pum chica pum chica pum <br>beat box <br>cuando tu me miras yo te quiero conmigo <br>estamos en la calle aun asi somo amigo <br>dime si tu me quiereeee <br>no importa np aksjuq <br>dime si tu me quiereeeee eh eh <br>cuando comienza la obia <br>esuqe yo te quiero mami y tu mr quieres no ay que hacer que nada rompa con nuestro amor tan sincrro y verdadero del bueno <br>esque tu me quiereee ehe eh <br>y yo te quirro oh oh <br>pero solo cuando me miras <br>me miras <br>amor del bueno]]></content><category term="Danny Howard" label="Danny Howard"/><category term="Don`t Wanna Stop" label="Don`t Wanna Stop"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이상은/꿈을_따라가_Inst/</id><title>이상은 - 꿈을 따라가 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:20:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:20:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%81%EC%9D%80/%EA%BF%88%EC%9D%84_%EB%94%B0%EB%9D%BC%EA%B0%80_Inst/" title="이상은 - 꿈을 따라가 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꿈을 따라가 반짝이는 <br>가슴 속 불빛을 따라서 <br>무거워지는 어둠 속 <br>사막 위엔 검은 모래뿐 <br>이곳이 세상이란 걸 <br>깨달은 순간 얼어붙었지 <br>두려움에 <br>꿈을 따라가 반짝이는 <br>투명한 강을 찾아서 <br>하늘하늘 눈물이 떨어진 <br>모래 위 피어난 풀잎 <br>그래 사막 어딘가 <br>있는 문을 열면 <br>반짝반짝 투명한 강이 <br>꿈을 따라가 반짝이는 <br>가슴 속 불빛을 따라서 <br>꺼진 줄 알았던 불빛 <br>이젠 꺼트리면 안돼 <br>길을 밝혀 줄 테니 <br>꿈을 따라가 반짝이는 <br>가슴 속 불빛을 따라서 <br>꿈을 따라가 <br>꿈을 따라가 반짝이는 <br>투명한 강을 찾아서 <br>꿈을 따라가 <br>그래 사막 어딘가 <br>있는 문을 열면 <br>]]></content><category term="이상은" label="이상은"/><category term="꿈을 따라가 (Inst.)" label="꿈을 따라가 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이상은/꿈을_따라가/</id><title>이상은 - 꿈을 따라가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:20:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:20:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%81%EC%9D%80/%EA%BF%88%EC%9D%84_%EB%94%B0%EB%9D%BC%EA%B0%80/" title="이상은 - 꿈을 따라가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꿈을 따라가 반짝이는 <br>가슴 속 불빛을 따라서 <br>무거워지는 어둠 속 <br>사막 위엔 검은 모래뿐 <br>이곳이 세상이란 걸 <br>깨달은 순간 얼어붙었지 <br>두려움에 <br>꿈을 따라가 반짝이는 <br>투명한 강을 찾아서 <br>하늘하늘 눈물이 떨어진 <br>모래 위 피어난 풀잎 <br>그래 사막 어딘가 <br>있는 문을 열면 <br>반짝반짝 투명한 강이 <br>꿈을 따라가 반짝이는 <br>가슴 속 불빛을 따라서 <br>꺼진 줄 알았던 불빛 <br>이젠 꺼트리면 안돼 <br>길을 밝혀 줄 테니 <br>꿈을 따라가 반짝이는 <br>가슴 속 불빛을 따라서 <br>꿈을 따라가 <br>꿈을 따라가 반짝이는 <br>투명한 강을 찾아서 <br>꿈을 따라가 <br>그래 사막 어딘가 <br>있는 문을 열면 <br>]]></content><category term="이상은" label="이상은"/><category term="꿈을 따라가" label="꿈을 따라가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/UNUSED/Drink_Feat_ENORMOUS_TAD/</id><title>UNUSED - Drink (Feat. ENORMOUS, TAD) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:23:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:23:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/UNUSED/Drink_Feat_ENORMOUS_TAD/" title="UNUSED - Drink (Feat. ENORMOUS, TAD) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby girl <br>이 안에선 너만 보여 <br>너의 앞에 있는 <br>잔을 들어 올려 <br>너무 아름다워서 <br>Baby <br>조금 더 뜨거워지면 넌 불러 <br>너의 위에서 아래까지 <br>다른 점이 없게 해 <br>너를 감싸면 느껴지지 <br>너의 예쁜 몸매 <br>너의 볼에 있는 <br>작은 점이 보일 때면 <br>girl <br>우리 둘 사이에 <br>빈틈이 없어지게 돼 <br>오늘 밤이 가면 <br>넌 내 옆에만 있게 돼 <br>나의 손이 닿는 곳에 <br>너가 있으면 돼 <br>Baby I wanna make u mine girl <br>You and I <br>너와 눈이 마주 칠 때면 <br>Drink tonight Drink all-night <br>Drink tonight Drink all-night <br>Drink tonight Drink all-night <br>Drink tonight Drink all-night <br>Drink tonight <br>계속 그렇게 마셔 <br>계속 헝클어진 <br>머리를 넘기고 <br>날 보며 입맛을 다셔 <br>Oh yeah <br>잔을 넘기는 너의 목선 <br>자꾸 내 시선을 가져가 <br>이러면 안되는데 <br>나쁜 목적을 만들게 돼 <br>Sorry but <br>이건 내 잘못이 아냐 <br>됐고 <br>give you one some more <br>지금 너에게 난 <br>뭐가 될지 알아 <br>혹시 오늘 밤에 <br>내가 너에게 독이 된다면 <br>사과 할게 <br>baby you trust me Whoo <br>기대가 되는 만큼 <br>나한테 기대 <br>너무 마시지마 <br>조금 걱정 돼 <br>속이 아프다면 <br>고쳐줄걸 약속해 <br>내 손은 약 손이 거든 <br>yeah <br>오늘 밤이 가면 <br>넌 내 옆에만 있게 돼 <br>나의 손이 닿는 곳에 <br>너가 있으면 돼 <br>baby I wanna make u mine girl <br>You and I <br>너와 눈이 마주 칠 때면 <br>Drink tonight Drink all-night <br>Drink tonight Drink all-night <br>Drink tonight Drink all-night <br>Drink tonight Drink all-night <br>]]></content><category term="UNUSED" label="UNUSED"/><category term="Drink (Feat. ENORMOUS, TAD)" label="Drink (Feat. ENORMOUS, TAD)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노상현/밤은_너무_위험해_Guitar_양희범/</id><title>노상현 - 밤은 너무 위험해 (Guitar. 양희범) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:24:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:24:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EC%83%81%ED%98%84/%EB%B0%A4%EC%9D%80_%EB%84%88%EB%AC%B4_%EC%9C%84%ED%97%98%ED%95%B4_Guitar_%EC%96%91%ED%9D%AC%EB%B2%94/" title="노상현 - 밤은 너무 위험해 (Guitar. 양희범) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아름다운 너에게 <br>밤은 너무 위험해 <br>밖은 너무 위험해 <br>이런 말하기 <br>참 쑥스럽지만 <br>오늘도 참 예쁘다 <br>이런 말하기 <br>참 부끄럽지만 <br>오늘따라 더 곱다 <br>1분만 더 안아줘 <br>1분만 더 안아주면 <br>정말 갈게 <br>아름다운 너에게 <br>밤은 너무 위험해 <br>밖은 너무 위험해 <br>아리따운 너에게 <br>밤은 너무 위험해 <br>이불 밖은 위험해 <br>한번 더 입 맞춰줘 <br>한번 더 입 맞춰주면 <br>정말 갈게 <br>아름다운 너에게 <br>밤은 너무 위험해 <br>밖은 너무 위험해 <br>아리따운 너에게 <br>밤은 너무 위험해 <br>이불 밖은 위험해 <br>아름다운 너에게 <br>밤은 너무 위험해 <br>밖은 너무 위험해 <br>아리따운 너에겐 <br>밤은 너무 위험해 <br>이불 밖은 위험해 <br>이불 밖은 위험해 <br>]]></content><category term="노상현" label="노상현"/><category term="밤은 너무 위험해 (Guitar. 양희범)" label="밤은 너무 위험해 (Guitar. 양희범)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/란_RAN/안녕_다시는_볼_수_없겠지/</id><title>란_RAN - 안녕 다시는 볼 수 없겠지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:24:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:24:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9E%80_RAN/%EC%95%88%EB%85%95_%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C%EB%8A%94_%EB%B3%BC_%EC%88%98_%EC%97%86%EA%B2%A0%EC%A7%80/" title="란_RAN - 안녕 다시는 볼 수 없겠지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[둘이서 손잡고서 거닐었던 거리 <br>그 곳 걸어가요 <br>마음이 같았으니 <br>이런 날이 올 줄은 몰랐는데 <br>친구들 헤어져 우는걸 <br>이해못한 나였는데 <br>내가 그렇게 울고서 아파하네요 <br>안녕 다시는 볼 수 없겠지 <br>내 마음 그대로인데 <br>헤어지자 말하면 끝나는거니 <br>안녕 모두 다 잊진 말아줘 <br>그러지마 그게 더 아파와 <br>처음엔 덤덤했어 <br>이게 이별이라 그냥 그랬는데 <br>시간이 지날수록 깊어지는 <br>그리움 다가오죠 <br>차갑던 그 눈빛 <br>냉정한 그 말투가 생각이나 <br>사랑에 웃고 행복한 그 시간들을 <br>안녕 다시는 볼 수 없겠지 <br>내 마음 그대로인데 <br>헤어지자 말하면 끝나는거니 <br>안녕 모두 다 잊진 말아줘 <br>그러지마 그게 더 아파와 <br>자신이 없는걸요 <br>혼자서 모든걸 해야하는 <br>나의 모습 어쩌죠 <br>안녕 다시는 볼 수 없겠지 <br>내 마음 그대로인데 <br>헤어지자 말하면 끝나는거니 <br>안녕 모두 다 잊진 말아줘 <br>그러지마 그게 더 아파와 <br>]]></content><category term="란 (RAN)" label="란 (RAN)"/><category term="안녕 다시는 볼 수 없겠지" label="안녕 다시는 볼 수 없겠지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Free_Wrestlers_Remix/</id><title>Body_Language - Free (Wrestlers Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:24:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:24:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Free_Wrestlers_Remix/" title="Body_Language - Free (Wrestlers Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Just tell me what you want from me <br>Is it lust, is it love <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me, are you really free <br>Do you trust, do you care <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br><br>Tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me <br>Tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me <br>Tell me, tell me what, tell me what you, tell me what <br>Tell me what you, tell me what, just tell me what you want from me <br><br>Just tell me what you want from me <br>Is it lust, is it love <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me, are you really free <br>Do you trust, do you care <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br><br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free]]></content><category term="Body Language" label="Body Language"/><category term="Free (Wrestlers Remix)" label="Free (Wrestlers Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Addicted_Memoryy_Remix/</id><title>Body_Language - Addicted (Memoryy Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:24:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:24:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Addicted_Memoryy_Remix/" title="Body_Language - Addicted (Memoryy Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You told me, you told me <br>You told me, you told me <br>You told me, you told me <br>You told me <br><br>You told me you've been goin' your way <br>We seen eachother other days <br>Since this, my head's a constant mess <br>So, sue me, I'd just like you to stay <br><br>But you had me from the start <br>With arrow through the heart <br>I'm waitin' by the telephone <br>'Cause you and me, we breathe <br>You ain't gotta tease <br>Don't leave me in a trench alone <br><br>But I can't get you off my mind <br>No, I can't get you off my mind <br>I just might be addicted <br>Know this feeling's hard to fight <br>Know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I just might be afflicted <br>Know this feeling's hard to fight <br>Know this feeling's hard to fight <br><br>There's no such thing as bein' too free <br>And I know you want me, at least that's how it seems <br>Your love is all I need <br>I'm not beggin', but I'm down on my knees <br><br>But you had me from the start <br>With arrow through the heart <br>I'm waitin' by the telephone <br>'Cause you and me, we breathe <br>You ain't gotta tease <br>Don't leave me in a trench alone <br><br>But you had me from the start <br>With arrow through the heart <br>I'm waitin' by the telephone <br>'Cause you and me, we breathe <br>You ain't gotta tease <br>Don't leave me in a trench alone <br><br>But I can't get you off my mind <br>No, I can't get you off my mind <br>I just might be addicted <br>Know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I just might be afflicted <br>Know this feeling's hard to fight <br><br>I just might be addicted <br>I know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I just might be addicted <br>I know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I just might be addicted <br>I know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I just might be addicted <br>I know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I just might be afflicted]]></content><category term="Body Language" label="Body Language"/><category term="Addicted (Memoryy Remix)" label="Addicted (Memoryy Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Cant_Hang_On_Shiny_Objects_Remix/</id><title>Body_Language - Can`t Hang On (Shiny Objects Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:24:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:24:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Cant_Hang_On_Shiny_Objects_Remix/" title="Body_Language - Can`t Hang On (Shiny Objects Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You say to me you want a lift <br>But you're stuck in line <br>I want it all for you and me <br>But we're wastin' time <br>You never want, you never called <br>You never get away <br>I'm at a loss, where do we cross <br>Do you really wanna stay <br><br>I think the walls are high enough <br>I think the world is wide enough <br>If you really wanted that <br>You'll know, you'll know, you'll know <br>I think the walls are high enough <br><br>I can't hang on <br>Can't lift you up <br>I can't hang on <br>I'd love you, but I can not move <br>Can't lift you up <br>You can not play me for the fool <br><br>Play me, play me for the fool <br>Play me, play me for the fool <br><br>You came to me as plain as day <br>The feeling came around <br>I hold you up, I wanna stay <br>But I know I'll drown <br>You are my one, you are my drum <br>You'll never fade away <br>The roots are deep but never dull <br>I know that I can say <br><br>But I can't hang on <br>Can't lift you up <br>We fall in farther than we knew <br>I can't hang on <br>I'd love you, but I can not move <br>Can't lift you up <br>You can not play me for the fool <br><br>Play me, play me for the fool <br>You can not play me for the fool <br>But I can't hang on <br>I'd love you, but I can not move <br>But I can't hang on <br>But I can't hang on <br><br>But I can't hang on <br>Can't lift you up <br>We fall in farther than we knew <br>I can't hang on <br>Can't lift you up <br>You can not play me for the fool]]></content><category term="Body Language" label="Body Language"/><category term="Can`t Hang On (Shiny Objects Remix)" label="Can`t Hang On (Shiny Objects Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Cold_Shoulder/</id><title>Body_Language - Cold Shoulder - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:24:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:24:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Cold_Shoulder/" title="Body_Language - Cold Shoulder - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a thousand miles on my way to Heaven <br>I'm a thousand miles on my way to Heaven <br>Take your time, just get in bow, yeah <br>I'm no longer wiser as I'm gettin' older <br>To your cold shoulder, 'cause it still ain't walkin' our <br><br>Thousand miles, I fuck on my way to Heaven <br>If I told you it was real, would you fondle me there <br>Take your time, just get in bow, yeah <br>You're heavy as water, so carry me over <br>On your cold shoulder <br><br>'Cause it still ain't walkin' our way <br>Way, way, way, way, way, way <br>Way, way, way, way, way, way <br>'Cause it still ain't walkin' our way <br><br>Came a thousand miles on my way to Heaven <br>I came a thousand miles on my way to Heaven <br>Take your time, so volatile, yeah <br>I feel so much farther 'cause I'm gettin' closer <br>To your cold shoulder <br><br>'Cause it still ain't walkin' our way <br>Way, way, way, way, way, way <br>Way, way, way, way, way, way <br>'Cause it still ain't walkin' our way <br>Way, way, way, way, way, way, way <br>Way, way, way, way, way, way, way <br><br>If you come to me, my baby <br>I won't ask for much <br>Just a massive love <br>And if you come to me, my baby <br>I won't ask for much <br>Just a massive love <br><br>It still ain't walkin' our way <br>Way, way, way, way, way, way <br>Way, way, way, way, way, way <br>'Cause it still ain't walkin' our way <br>Way, way, way, way, way, way, way <br>And I still ain't <br>Way, way, way, way, way, way, way <br>And I still won't, and I, and I]]></content><category term="Body Language" label="Body Language"/><category term="Cold Shoulder" label="Cold Shoulder"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Be_Mine/</id><title>Body_Language - Be Mine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:25:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:25:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Be_Mine/" title="Body_Language - Be Mine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Face to face, I wonder what you're doin' here <br>Where you're from, so I asked you <br>What's your name No wastin' time <br>His momma's fall, oh, wait, it's plain to see <br>Pleasantries in the canopy <br>Under watch, you see me <br><br>As the night goes on, gods surround you <br>But you wouldn't have my love too soon <br><br>If you want me, my goodness, in time <br>Between now and then, you'll be on my mind <br>In time, in time, you'll be mine <br>In time, in time, you'll be mine <br><br>Eye to eye, the sight is over <br>Went to compare it with the glow <br>Does it flow in deeper fields <br>If what you say is true, don't worry 'bout me <br>I will wait if trusted <br>Come with me, don't be afraid <br><br>As the night goes on, gods surround you <br>But you wouldn't have my love too soon <br><br>If you want me, my goodness, in time <br>Between now and then, you'll be on my mind <br>In time, in time, you'll be mine <br><br>If you want me, my goodness, in time <br>Between now and then, you'll be on my mind <br>In time, in time, you'll be mine <br>In time, in time, you'll be mine <br><br>You'll be on my mind <br>You'll be on my mind <br>You'll be on my mind <br>You'll be on my mind]]></content><category term="Body Language" label="Body Language"/><category term="Be Mine" label="Be Mine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Martyr/</id><title>Body_Language - Martyr - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:25:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:25:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Martyr/" title="Body_Language - Martyr - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been trying to reach you but I can not find the simple way <br>Tried to reach you but I can not find the way <br>And I've been trying to reach you but I can not find the simple way <br>Tried to reach you but I wasn't never able <br><br>Ooh, are we waiting for a martyr <br>No, 'cause I ain't waitin' no longer <br>True, things that always how we walked down <br>So, I'll take the reins from a soldier <br><br>Listen to your voice, trust the white noise <br>Trust the white noise, in tune <br>We don't have no freedom, we don't have no freedom <br>We don't have no freedom to do whatever we want <br><br>Are we waiting for a martyr <br>No, 'cause I ain't waiting no longer <br>True, things that always how we walked down <br>So, I'll take the reins from a soldier <br><br>I've been trying to reach you but I can not find the simple way <br>Tried to meet you but I can not find the way <br>And I've been trying to reach you but I can not find the simple way <br>Tried to reach you but I wasn't ever able <br><br>Ooh, are we waiting for a martyr <br>No, 'cause I ain't waitin' no longer <br>True, things that always how we walked down <br>So, I'll take the reins from a soldier]]></content><category term="Body Language" label="Body Language"/><category term="Martyr" label="Martyr"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Chasing_Tides/</id><title>Body_Language - Chasing Tides - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:25:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:25:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Chasing_Tides/" title="Body_Language - Chasing Tides - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm after the races, running by, losing time <br>If change is faceless, affection is priceless, keep in mind <br>Here I go again, chasing tides, with bones of glass <br>Losing control with hands that don't help, who wants to pass <br><br>Yeah, I'm chasing, chasing, chasing tides <br>Moving, moving, slow as ice <br>Chasing, chasing, chasing tides <br>Moving, moving slow as ice <br><br>Scared it will rise is lying, I'm bound to hold you close <br>If change is tireless, I'm off to fight, need the most <br>Here I go again, feathers of wax, into the Sun <br>I'm out to sea, who's at the helm, who wants to come <br><br>Yeah, I'm chasing, chasing, chasing tides <br>Moving, moving, slow as ice <br>Chasing, chasing, chasing tides <br>Moving, moving slow as ice <br>Slow as ice]]></content><category term="Body Language" label="Body Language"/><category term="Chasing Tides" label="Chasing Tides"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Free/</id><title>Body_Language - Free - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:25:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:25:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Free/" title="Body_Language - Free - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Just tell me what you want from me <br>Is it lust, is it love <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me, are you really free <br>Do you trust, do you care <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br><br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br><br>Just tell me what you want from me <br>Is it lust, is it love <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me, are you really free <br>Do you trust, do you care <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br>Tell me what you really wanna be <br><br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free <br>Let it be, let it be, let it be, set yourself free]]></content><category term="Body Language" label="Body Language"/><category term="Free" label="Free"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Cant_Hang_On/</id><title>Body_Language - Can`t Hang On - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:25:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:25:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Cant_Hang_On/" title="Body_Language - Can`t Hang On - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You say to me you want a lift <br>But you're stuck in line <br>I want it all for you and me <br>But we're wastin' time <br>You never want, you never called <br>You never get away <br>I'm at a loss, where do we cross <br>Do you really wanna stay <br><br>I think the walls are high enough <br>I think the world is wide enough <br>If you really wanted that <br>You'll know, you'll know, you'll know <br><br>But I can't hang on <br>We're drifting farther from the truth <br>Can't lift you up <br>We fall in father than we knew <br>I can't hang on <br>I'd love you, but I can not move <br>Can't lift you up <br>You can not play me for the fool <br><br>You came to me as plain as day <br>The feeling came around <br>I hold you up, I wanna stay <br>But I know I'll drown <br>You are my one, you are my drum <br>You'll never fade away <br>The roots are deep but never dull <br>I know that I can say <br><br>But I can't hang on <br>We're drifting farther from the truth <br>Can't lift you up <br>We fall in farther than we knew <br>I can't hang on <br>I'd love you, but I can not move <br>Can't lift you up <br>You can not play me for the fool <br><br>You can not play me for the fool <br>But I can't hang on <br>I'd love you, but I can not move <br>But I can't hang on <br>But I can't hang on <br><br>But I can't hang on <br>We're drifting farther from the truth <br>Can't lift you up <br>We fall in farther than we knew <br>I can't hang on <br>I'd love you, but I can not move <br>Can't lift you up <br>You can not play me for the fool]]></content><category term="Body Language" label="Body Language"/><category term="Can`t Hang On" label="Can`t Hang On"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Addicted/</id><title>Body_Language - Addicted - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:25:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:25:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Body_Language/Addicted/" title="Body_Language - Addicted - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You told me you've been goin' your way <br>We seen eachother other days <br>Since this, my head's a constant mess <br>So, sue me, I'd just like you to stay <br><br>But you had me from the start <br>With arrow through the heart <br>I'm waitin' by the telephone <br>'Cause you and me, we breathe <br>You ain't gotta tease <br>Don't leave me in a trench alone <br><br>But I can't get you off my mind <br>No, I can't get you off my mind <br>I just might be addicted <br>Know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I just might be afflicted <br>Know this feeling's hard to fight <br><br>There's no such thing as bein' too free <br>And I know you want me, at least that's how it seems <br>Your love is all I need <br>I'm not beggin', but I'm down on my knees <br><br>But I can't get you off my mind <br>No, I can't get you off my mind <br>I just might be addicted <br>Know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I just might be afflicted <br>Know this feeling's hard to fight <br><br>Know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I can't get you off my mind <br>I can't get you off my mind <br><br>But I can't get you off my mind <br>I just can't get you off my mind <br>No, I can't get you off my mind <br>I just can't get you off my mind <br>I just might be addicted <br>Know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I know, I know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I just might be afflicted <br>Know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I know, I know this feeling's hard to fight <br><br>I know, I know, I know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I know, I know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I know this feeling's hard to fight <br>I know, I know, I know this feeling's hard to fight]]></content><category term="Body Language" label="Body Language"/><category term="Addicted" label="Addicted"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유니즌/Love_Is_So_Hard/</id><title>유니즌 - Love Is So Hard - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:25:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:25:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EB%8B%88%EC%A6%8C/Love_Is_So_Hard/" title="유니즌 - Love Is So Hard - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It is all about you <br>leave 그날 모든게 다 <br>끝난 영화처럼 <br>아무 것도 남겨 진것 없이 <br>It is all about you <br>here 이곳에 너하나만 <br>빠져버린건데 왠지 낯설게 <br>멍하니 하늘을 바라보다 <br>생각났어 니가 <br>나쁘기만 했던 <br>울리기만 했던 너였는데 <br>잘생기지 않고 <br>달달함도 없던 너였는데 <br>Why Love's so Hard <br>Why Love's so hard <br>Why Love's so Hard <br>Why Love's so hard <br>It is all about you <br>look 내눈에 너는 정말 <br>별로였었는데 왜 좋아 졌지 <br>어디서 뭘하든 신경안써 <br>그리고 찾아 instagram <br>나쁘기만 했던 <br>울리기만 했던 너였는데 <br>잘생기지 않고 <br>달달함도 없던 너였는데 <br>Why Love's so Hard <br>Why Love's so hard <br>Why Love's so Hard <br>Why Love's so hard <br>아무렇지 않게 잘지내 <br>연락이나 해볼까 <br>아니 잠이나 자자 <br>꿈에서 너를 볼수있나 <br>나쁘기만 했던 <br>울리기만 했던 너였는데 <br>잘생기지 않고 <br>달달함도 없던 너였는데 <br>Why Love's so Hard <br>Why Love's so hard <br>Why Love's so Hard <br>Why Love's so hard <br>]]></content><category term="유니즌" label="유니즌"/><category term="Love Is So Hard" label="Love Is So Hard"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alpines/Stay/</id><title>Alpines - Stay - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:26:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:26:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alpines/Stay/" title="Alpines - Stay - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Its heaven <br>you want this <br>I need you <br><br>I promise <br>Celestial <br>When you hold me <br>Its perfectly <br>Unfolding <br>Coz' nobody makes me feel the way you make me feel <br>Coz' nobody makes me heal the way you make me heal <br>Stay <br>Stay <br>I'm searching <br>So restless <br>Surround me <br>I'm boundless <br>Transcending <br>In the space <br>Longing for <br>Your embrace <br>Coz' nobody makes me feel the way you make me feel <br>Coz' nobody makes me heal the way you make me heal <br>Stay <br>Stay <br>So way you do <br>the things you do <br>So way i fall <br>right into you <br>So way you say <br>the things you say <br>So you'r making <br>making me stay <br>Coz' nobody makes me feel the way you make me feel <br>Coz' nobody makes me heal the way you make me heal <br>Coz' nobody makes me feel the way you make me feel <br>Coz' nobody makes me heal the way you make me heal <br>Coz' nobody makes me feel the way you do <br>Coz' nobody makes me heal the way you do <br>Stay There's nobody else that makes me feel this way <br>Stay There's nobody else that makes me feel this way]]></content><category term="Alpines" label="Alpines"/><category term="Stay" label="Stay"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alpines/Completely/</id><title>Alpines - Completely - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:26:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:26:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alpines/Completely/" title="Alpines - Completely - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Why'd you always come around <br>When there's nothing left to say <br>When the silence seems so loud <br>You've taken every breath away <br><br>Oh boy, you're breaking me down every step by step <br>I don't say what I know you're feeling <br>Oh boy, you're breaking me down every step by step <br>I don't say what I know you're feeling <br><br>You make it seem so easy <br>The way you have me completely <br>You make it seem so easy <br>The way you have me completely <br>Completely, completely, completely <br><br>Completely, completely, completely <br>Completely, completely, completely <br><br>Why is so much left unsaid <br>This silence is deafening <br>I need to know now where you stand <br>My heart is in the palm of your hands <br><br>Oh boy, you're breaking me down every step by step <br>I don't say what I know you're feeling <br>Oh boy, you're breaking me down every step by step <br>I don't say what I know you're feeling <br>You make it seem so easy <br>The way you have me completely <br>You make it seem so easy <br>The way you have me completely <br>Completely, completely, completely <br><br>Completely, completely, completely <br>Completely, completely, completely <br>Completely, completely, completely <br><br>Completely in touch <br>Completely in love <br>Completely in love <br>Completely in touch <br>Completely in touch <br>Completely in love <br>Completely in love <br>Completely in touch]]></content><category term="Alpines" label="Alpines"/><category term="Completely" label="Completely"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/In_Common/</id><title>Alicia_Keys - In Common - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:26:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:26:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/In_Common/" title="Alicia_Keys - In Common - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Said I'd be gone by five <br>But it's sunrise and <br>I'm still in your bed <br>Goodnight usually means goodbye <br>Me replaying memories in my head <br>Look at you look at you <br>Look what you made me do <br>How do you <br>how do you think know <br>my every move <br>Who are you Who are you <br>You look so familiar <br>I know you I know you <br>baby I know the truth <br>We got way too much in common <br>If I'm being honest with you <br>We got way too much in common <br>Since I'm being honest with you <br>Who wants to love somebody like me <br>You wanna love somebody like me <br>If you could love somebody like me <br>You must be messed up too <br>Who wants to love somebody like me <br>You wanna love somebody like me <br>If you could love somebody like me <br>You must be messed up too <br>We used to talk 'til midnight <br>All those days that you <br>stayed at my house <br>We were just passing the time <br>When we were young and <br>we ain't had no vows <br>Now now now maybe later on <br>I'll text you and maybe you'll reply <br>We both know <br>we had no patience together <br>day and night <br>Getting high on our supply <br>yeah we ain't satisfied <br>I could love you all occasions <br>We got way too much in common <br>If I'm being honest with you <br>We got way too much in common <br>Since I'm being honest with you <br>Who wants to love somebody like me <br>You wanna love somebody like me <br>If you could love somebody like me <br>You must be mystical too <br>Who wants to love somebody like me <br>You wanna love somebody like me <br>If you could love somebody like me <br>You must be messed up too <br>Messed up too messed up too <br>Just like you just like you <br>Messed up too messed up too <br>Just like you just like you <br>We got way too much in common <br>If I'm being honest with you <br>We got way too much in common <br>Since I'm being honest with you <br>Who wants to love somebody like me <br>You wanna love somebody like me <br>If you could love somebody like me <br>You must be messed up too <br>Who wants to love somebody like me <br>You wanna love somebody like me <br>If you could love somebody like me <br>You must be messed up too <br>]]></content><category term="Alicia Keys" label="Alicia Keys"/><category term="In Common" label="In Common"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/Hallelujah/</id><title>Alicia_Keys - Hallelujah - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:26:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:26:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/Hallelujah/" title="Alicia_Keys - Hallelujah - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a hole in my heart <br>I've been hiding <br>I've been strong for so long <br>that I'm blind <br>Is there a place I can go <br>where the lonely river flows <br>Where fear ends and faith begins <br>Hallelujah hallelujah <br>let me in <br>I've been praying <br>but I'm paying for my sins <br>Won't you give me a sign <br>before I lose my mind <br>Woah hallelujah let me in <br>Every step makes me think <br>that I'm closer <br>But somehow <br>I just never arrived <br>When our hope disappears <br>please protect me from my tears <br>I need you right by my side <br>Hallelujah hallelujah <br>let me in <br>I've been praying <br>but I'm paying for my sins <br>Won't you give me a sign <br>before I lose my mind <br>Woah hallelujah let me in <br>Woah woah hallelujah <br>Woah woah hallelujah <br>All the places I've been <br>Please forgive me for my sins <br>Woah hallelujah let me in <br>Woah woah let me in <br>Woah woah let me in <br>Woah woah <br>Please forgive me for my sins <br>Woah hallelujah let me in <br>]]></content><category term="Alicia Keys" label="Alicia Keys"/><category term="Hallelujah" label="Hallelujah"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/Work_On_It/</id><title>Alicia_Keys - Work On It - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:26:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:26:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/Work_On_It/" title="Alicia_Keys - Work On It - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Work on it, work on it <br>Work on it, baby <br><br>Oh baby, some may think that we moved too fast <br>But I know you and you know me <br>Baby, that's what makes it last <br>Darling, so many lies were spread about us <br>Oh, that's the heartache, that's the heartache <br>That makes us build all the trust <br><br>I know some people like to say <br>That the easiest way is to fake it <br>We gonna make it if we try <br>Gotta promise not to abuse it <br>If you use it, don't lose it or break it <br>'Cause we gonna make it <br>You and I <br><br>When they see us coming they'll say <br>Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh <br>When they see us coming they'll say <br>Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh <br><br>Some days are hard <br>There ain't no easy way <br>No matter how we try <br>Nobody is perfect <br>But if we just love each other through it all <br>Baby, now that, that makes it worth it <br><br>I know some people try to say <br>That he easiest way is to fake it <br>We gonna make it if we try <br>Gotta promise not to abuse it <br>If you use it, don't lose it or break it <br>We gonna make it <br>You and I <br><br>When they hear us coming they'll say <br>Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh <br>When they hear us coming they'll say <br>Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh <br><br>When they feel us coming they'll say <br>Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh <br>When they feel us coming they'll say <br>Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh <br><br>Oh, we gonna work on it, baby <br>Me and you, we gonna work on it, baby]]></content><category term="Alicia Keys" label="Alicia Keys"/><category term="Work On It" label="Work On It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/She_Dont_Really_Care_1_Luv/</id><title>Alicia_Keys - She Don`t Really Care_1 Luv - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:26:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:26:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/She_Dont_Really_Care_1_Luv/" title="Alicia_Keys - She Don`t Really Care_1 Luv - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She grew up in Brooklyn <br>She grew up in Harlem <br>She grew up in Bronx <br>She know she was a queen <br>She lived in Queens <br>Oh yeah oh yeah <br>But she don't really care <br>She don't really care <br>She want them diamonds in her ear <br>Diamonds in the air <br>Oh yeah oh yeah <br>She lived in Somalia <br>Her parents from Egypt <br>She was a queen in Cairo <br>Oh yeah oh yeah <br>But she don't really care <br>She don't really care <br>She want them diamonds in her ear <br>Diamonds in the air <br>Oh yeah oh yeah <br>She picking all the wrong ones <br>And she's looking for the right one <br>in the wrong place <br>You remember her face <br>The prettiest face prettiest face <br>Oh yeah oh yeah <br>She looking for fulfillment <br>You would think <br>she was looking for love <br>searching for love <br>She just looking to be taken care of <br>Oh yeah oh yeah <br>You can find her in Harlem <br>or Brooklyn <br>You can find her Brixton <br>or Kingston <br>She's a queen know what I mean <br>Oh yeah oh yeah <br>She think she want a baby <br>and she do it with the wrong one <br>Cause she's looking for something <br>but he don't really care <br>He don't really care <br>And life just isn't fair <br>She grew up in Brooklyn Uh-huh <br>She grew up in Harlem Harlem <br>She grew up in Bronx <br>She know she was a queen A queen <br>She lived in Queens Uh-huh <br>Oh yeah oh yeah <br>She don't really care <br>She don't really care <br>She throw them diamonds in her air <br>Diamonds in the air yeah <br>Oh yeah oh yeah <br>She lived in Somalia talk about it <br>Her parents from Egypt Egypt <br>She was a queen in Cairo <br>She's a queen yeah <br>Oh yeah oh yeah <br>But she don't really care <br>She don't really care <br>She want them diamonds in her ear <br>Diamonds in the air <br>Oh yeah oh yeah <br>Brooklyn yeah <br>You think she loves you But she don't <br>Oh yeah oh yeah <br>You got to wake up open your eyes <br>See the way it really is <br>Oh yeah oh yeah <br>Brooklyn New York <br>The Bronx Harlem baby <br>New York Brooklyn baby <br>You think she loves you <br>She'll take you for everything <br>you've got <br>You gotta remember that <br>The Big Apple <br>New York City <br>Brooklyn Harlem <br>the Bronx Brooklyn baby <br>wake up brother <br>Wake up wake up wake up <br>Open up your eyes <br>And realize the truth <br>Watch your step brother <br>Watch your step brother <br>Move it to the left <br>move it to the right <br>Now that's exciting <br>Better go home New York City <br>It's the truth it's the dead truth <br>Live truth <br>It's the live truth yeah <br>It's where the life yeah <br>All along I've ignored <br>what I've always known <br>That the chair <br>I've been sitting on is a throne <br>Affection kneels <br>at the seat of my soul <br>Tell the truth it can't get no better <br>Swear to life it <br>can't get no better oh no <br>By the way <br>I've been meaning to thank ya <br>By the way <br>I've been meaning to thank ya <br>all along <br>One love one love one love one love <br>One love one love one love one love <br>One love one love one love one love <br>One love one love one love one love <br>All along <br>I was hoping understanding <br>would be born <br>I was looking for knowledge <br>to sing my song <br>But now I know that <br>I am wisdom on my own <br>Tell the truth it can't get no better <br>Swear to life it can't get no better <br>Oh no <br>By the way <br>I've been meaning to thank ya <br>By the way <br>I've been meaning to thank ya <br>all along <br>One love one love one love one love <br>One love one love one love one love <br>One love one love one love one love <br>One love one love one love one love <br>]]></content><category term="Alicia Keys" label="Alicia Keys"/><category term="She Don`t Really Care_1 Luv" label="She Don`t Really Care_1 Luv"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/Pawn_It_All/</id><title>Alicia_Keys - Pawn It All - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:26:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:26:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/Pawn_It_All/" title="Alicia_Keys - Pawn It All - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah ah <br>Yeah ah <br>Yeah ah <br>Yeah ah <br>I will pawn you my watch <br>I will pawn you my chain <br>I will pawn you this gold <br>and diamond ring <br>'Cause I need it so bad <br>I would give you everything <br>Just so I could start <br>my life over again <br>Sometimes you gotta let it go <br>Just to make it possible <br>Sometimes you gotta do it <br>Be willing to lose it <br>Freedom has no price you know <br>Thinking how we gonna make it now <br>How we gonna feed the babies now <br>We gonna make it through it <br>God gonna see to it <br>Just get up and do it now <br>I will pawn you my watch <br>I will pawn you my chain <br>I will pawn you this gold <br>and diamond ring <br>'Cause I need it so bad <br>I would give you everything <br>Just so I could start <br>my life over again <br>Get on up hey <br>Get on up hey <br>Get on up hey <br>Get on up hey <br>Get on up <br>See I learned the hard way <br>Now I'm doing it my way <br>'Cause life is too short to <br>fall in New York <br>Can't get up and get away <br>So I gotta let it all go <br>Start back from zero <br>'Cause I've give it up <br>I don't give a fuck <br>As long is my hero <br>I will pawn you my watch <br>I will pawn you my chain <br>I will pawn you this gold <br>and diamond ring <br>'Cause I need it so bad <br>I would give you everything <br>Just so I could start <br>my life over again <br>I will pawn you my watch <br>I will pawn you my chain <br>I will pawn you this gold <br>and diamond ring <br>'Cause I need it so bad <br>I would give you everything <br>Just so I could start <br>my life over again <br>Get on up hey <br>Get on up hey <br>Get on up hey <br>Get on up hey <br>Get on up <br>]]></content><category term="Alicia Keys" label="Alicia Keys"/><category term="Pawn It All" label="Pawn It All"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/The_Gospel/</id><title>Alicia_Keys - The Gospel - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:26:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:26:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/The_Gospel/" title="Alicia_Keys - The Gospel - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So we all got children <br>products of the ghetto <br>Momma cooked us soup <br>daddy did the yelling <br>Uncle was a drunk cousin was a felon <br>When he got pitched <br>he told them he wasn't tellin' <br>Auntie was a cook <br>her husband was a crook <br>Cause every job he had they be <br>payin' him off the books <br>Ghetto university <br>knowledge is all it took <br>In a tenement <br>I was listenin' to the hook <br>Change gon' come <br>the spirit of Sam Cook <br>When the feds comin' <br>everybody get shook <br>Now we doin' life <br>like Eddie Murphy and Martin <br>On the chain gang <br>I was singing into the coffin <br>The roaches and the rats <br>heroin and the cracks <br>Couldn't blame me <br>I'm just giving the facts <br>Tryna hit the top the bottom <br>ain't where it's at <br>Everybody got a past <br>but you can never go back <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>Sing yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Sing yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Sing yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Sing yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Tellin' you like it is <br>how we ever gon' live <br>If we ain't gettin' money <br>how we feedin' the kids <br>It's a revolving door <br>where brothers be doin' bids <br>I know it sound wrong <br>but the door will be what it is <br>Survival of the fittest <br>this poor girl the illest <br>Broke parents and black cats <br>give me heebie-geebies <br>Life seems hard <br>but nothin' ever comes easy <br>Whatever's in the dark <br>can always become the light <br>If you ain't in a battle <br>how you gon' win the fight <br>Gotta speak the truth <br>when I'm up in the booth <br>The streets be flyin' birds <br>but they don't be on the roof <br>Poverty is a pain <br>like you pullin' a tooth <br>Told the streets don't let me go <br>like I'm Bishop in Juice <br>The roaches and the rats <br>heroin and the cracks <br>Couldn't blame me <br>I'm just giving the facts <br>Tryna hit the top the bottom <br>ain't where it's at <br>Everybody got a past <br>but you can never go back <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>Sing yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Sing yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>You gotta sing <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>She's a king <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>And they sing New York City <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>]]></content><category term="Alicia Keys" label="Alicia Keys"/><category term="The Gospel" label="The Gospel"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/The_Beginning_Interlude/</id><title>Alicia_Keys - The Beginning (Interlude) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:26:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:26:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/The_Beginning_Interlude/" title="Alicia_Keys - The Beginning (Interlude) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like history on the turntables <br>Old school to new school <br>Like nothing ever been realer <br>On the history of the turntables <br>I'm the mystery of what's inside the speaker cables <br>I'm Nina Simone in the park and Harlem in the dark <br>I'm the musical to the project fables <br>I'm the words scratched out on the record label <br>I'm the wind when the record spins <br>I'm the dramatic static before the song begins <br>I'm the erratic energy that gets in your skin <br>And if you don't let me in <br>I'm the shot in the air when the party ends]]></content><category term="Alicia Keys" label="Alicia Keys"/><category term="The Beginning (Interlude)" label="The Beginning (Interlude)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Desi_Valentine/Fate_Dont_Know_You/</id><title>Desi_Valentine - Fate Don`t Know You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:28:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:28:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Desi_Valentine/Fate_Dont_Know_You/" title="Desi_Valentine - Fate Don`t Know You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I put my palms before her eyes <br>And she told me my truth <br>Laid the road for me <br>A rich man's destiny <br>But she saw it without you <br><br>She's a liar <br>She has no clue <br>You're the one thing I will not lose <br><br>I'll turn the tide <br>Pull down the moon <br>Run rivers dry <br>Battle fate for you <br>Let's burn the pages <br>We'll start anew <br>Right through the ages, to prove <br>Fate don't know you like I do <br>Like I do <br><br>I'm gonna make you feel my love <br>Leave you no room for doubt <br>No other hope for me <br>You're my destiny <br>Won't go nowhere without you <br><br>You're my fire <br>That much is true <br>You're the one thing I will not lose <br><br>I'll turn the tide <br>Pull down the moon <br>Run rivers dry <br>Battle fate for you <br>Let's burn the pages <br>We'll start anew <br>Right through the ages, to prove <br>Fate don't know you like I do oh <br>Like I do <br>Like I do <br><br>You're my fire <br>They have no clue <br>You're the one thing I will not lose <br>I will not lose <br><br>I'll turn the tide <br>Pull down the moon <br>Run rivers dry <br>Battle fate for you <br>Let's burn the pages <br>We'll start anew <br>Right through the ages <br>Fate don't know you like I do oh <br>Know you like I do <br>Fate don't know you like I do]]></content><category term="Desi Valentine" label="Desi Valentine"/><category term="Fate Don`t Know You" label="Fate Don`t Know You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Guard/Die_Online/</id><title>Guard - Die Online - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:28:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:28:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Guard/Die_Online/" title="Guard - Die Online - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I swear I'm gonna die online <br>And no one has to know <br>I've already backed up my soul <br>I've got no real eyes, I only see codes <br>I only see why it's in the null <br><br>Take a hit <br>Have a sip <br>Been a memory chip <br>Come on a seven day trip <br>Nothing but ghosts <br>Soldiers for show, I don't even like you <br><br>I swear I'm gonna die online <br>And no one has to know <br>I've already backed up my soul <br>I've got no real eyes, I only see codes <br>I only see why it's in the null <br>I swear I'm gonna die online <br>And no one has to know <br>I've already backed up my soul <br>I've got no real eyes, I only see codes <br>I only see why it's in the null <br><br>We gotta disconnect <br>To reconnect <br>Hooked on your ethernet <br>My cigarette <br>I let you into me into me, into me <br>I know you're killing me killing me, killing me <br>We gotta disconnect <br>To reconnect <br>Hooked on your ethernet <br>My cigarette <br>I let you into me into me, into me <br>I know you're killing me killing me, killing me <br><br>I swear I'm gonna die online <br>And no one has to know <br>I've already backed up my soul <br>I've got no real eyes, I only see codes <br>I only see why it's in the null]]></content><category term="Guard" label="Guard"/><category term="Die Online" label="Die Online"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ness_네스/대한미국인_Korean-American/</id><title>ness_네스 - 대한미국인 (Korean-American) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:30:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:30:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ness_%EB%84%A4%EC%8A%A4/%EB%8C%80%ED%95%9C%EB%AF%B8%EA%B5%AD%EC%9D%B8_Korean-American/" title="ness_네스 - 대한미국인 (Korean-American) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[대한민국 나는 대한미국인 <br>대한민국 나는 대한미국인 <br>대한민국 나는 대한미국인 <br>대한민국 나는 대한미국인 <br>내 의지로 된건 아니지만 <br>나는 대한미국인 <br>국적은 미국이지만 <br>심장에 박힌 태극기 <br>타지에서도 늘 자랑스러웠어 <br>대한민국이 <br>한번도 느껴보지 못한 <br>미국에 대한 애국심 <br>나도 한때는 있었지 <br>대한민국의 여권이 <br>하지만 나를 유학 보낼려고 <br>결심했던 부모님 <br>내 교육을 위해 <br>날 거의 혼자 키우신 어머니 <br>미국에서 아빠 엄마 역할을 <br>둘다 채우신 어머니 <br>가족을 위해 한몸 다 바치면서 <br>일하신 아버지 <br>아이들을 위해 <br>자진해서 됐지 기러기 <br>항상 내 뒷바라지를 해주신 <br>사랑스러운 우리 할머니 <br>내가 미국에 있는 동안 <br>자전거에 치여서 <br>다리 다치신 우리 할머니 <br>내가 크는걸 옆에서 지켜보다 <br>하늘로 떠난 콩이 <br>아직도 그 생각하면 <br>폭포처럼 흐르는 눈물이 <br>그래도 미국은 내 인생에서 blessing <br>꼬마아이의 귀를 열어줬던건 slim shady <br>대한민국 나는 대한미국인 <br>대한민국 나는 대한미국인 <br>대한민국 나는 대한미국인 <br>대한민국 나는 대한미국인 <br>무한도전이랑 <br>만화책으로 배운 한국어 <br>영어가 더 편하지만 <br>나한테는 제1외국어 <br>오랜 해외생활속에서도 <br>한번도 잊어버린적 없던 모국어 <br>외국인 친구는 많아도 <br>항상 느꼈던 벽 <br>못느껴봤다면 <br>거짓말이겠지 인종차별 <br>티는 안냈지만 언제나 <br>조금씩 마음에 상처 <br>한국에선 친구들이랑 <br>영어로 대화하면 <br>차갑게 느껴졌던 따가운 시선 <br>대한미국인들의 여전한 <br>아지트 압구정 로데오 <br>아직 한국인들이 보기엔 <br>난 속이 하얀 노란 오레오 <br>내 정체성의 혼란 <br>내 가르마처럼 5 대 5 <br>거짓말 뿐인 세상 <br>허나 코 안커지는 피노키오 <br>그래 나는 자랑스러운 <br>대한미국인 aka 교포 <br>허나 나도 자부심 갖고 <br>불러 우리땅 독도 <br>동해물 백두산과 <br>자유의 여신상이 낳은 <br>대한미국 국보 thats me <br>대한민국 나는 대한미국인 <br>대한민국 나는 대한미국인 <br>대한민국 나는 대한미국인 <br>대한민국 나는 대한미국인 <br>]]></content><category term="ness (네스)" label="ness (네스)"/><category term="대한미국인 (Korean-American)" label="대한미국인 (Korean-American)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Min_G/사랑이_깊어서/</id><title>Min_G - 사랑이 깊어서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:30:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:30:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Min_G/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B9%8A%EC%96%B4%EC%84%9C/" title="Min_G - 사랑이 깊어서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 힘이들어요 <br>그댄 나없이 괜찮나요 <br>몰랐었는데 너무 내 생각만했죠 <br>참 미안했어요 <br>참 좋았었는데 <br>괜한 생각에 또 우네요 <br>투정부리고 떠난 뒷모습에 우는 <br>난 나쁜 여잔 가봐요 <br>하루 또 하루 괜찮아지겠죠 <br>근데 어쩌죠 내맘은 힘든데 <br>내 사랑이 깊어서 <br>그댈 많이 힘들게 했나봐요 <br>못해준게 많아서 <br>내맘이 그댈 놓지 못해요 <br>할말이 많아도 이젠 참아볼게요 <br>그 사랑 때문에 나 이렇게 울어요 <br>손에 닿을듯 그리워 지네요 <br>맘이 말해요 그댈 잊으라고 <br>내 사랑이 깊어서 <br>그댈 많이 힘들게 했나봐요 <br>못해준게 많아서 <br>내맘이 그댈 놓지 못해요 <br>할말이 많아도 이젠 참아볼게요 <br>그 사랑 때문에 나 이렇게 울어요 <br>참 미안했어요 그땐 몰랐죠 <br>흐르는 그대 눈물이 <br>이별이었단 걸 <br>나 잊지 않을게요 <br>행복한 날에 웃던 그 기억도 <br>함께했던 추억만 <br>꼭 간직하며 살아갈게요 <br>참 고마웠어요 미안한게 많아도 <br>그 사람때문에 나 이렇게 살아요 <br>]]></content><category term="Min G" label="Min G"/><category term="사랑이 깊어서" label="사랑이 깊어서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강유진/어디서_오셨습니까/</id><title>강유진 - 어디서 오셨습니까 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:30:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:30:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%9C%A0%EC%A7%84/%EC%96%B4%EB%94%94%EC%84%9C_%EC%98%A4%EC%85%A8%EC%8A%B5%EB%8B%88%EA%B9%8C/" title="강유진 - 어디서 오셨습니까 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어디서 오셨습니까 <br>어디서 오셨습니까 <br>참 잘오셨습니다 <br>악수 라도 한번 합시다 <br>언제다시 만나리라는 <br>날짜도 없이 <br>기약도 없이 <br>떠나면 그만 <br>안오면 그만 <br>떠돌이 구름 같은 <br>인생이지만 <br>다시 만납시다 그때우리 <br>술이라도 한잔 합시다 <br>어디서 오셨습니까 <br>어디서 오셨습니까 <br>만난 것도 인연인데 <br>헤어지기 아쉽습니다 <br>언제다시 만나리라는 <br>날짜도 없이 <br>기약도 없이 <br>떠나면 그만 <br>안오면 그만 <br>떠돌이 구름 같은 <br>인생이지만 <br>다시 만납시다 그때우리 <br>술이라도 한잔 합시다 <br>어디서 오셨습니까 <br>어디서 오셨습니까 <br>참 잘오셨습니다 <br>악수 라도 한번 합시다 <br>언제다시 만나리라는 <br>날짜도 없이 <br>기약도 없이 <br>떠나면 그만 <br>안오면 그만 <br>떠돌이 구름 같은 <br>인생이지만 <br>다시 만납시다 그때우리 <br>술이라도 한잔 합시다 <br>]]></content><category term="강유진" label="강유진"/><category term="어디서 오셨습니까" label="어디서 오셨습니까"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강유진/꽁무니/</id><title>강유진 - 꽁무니 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:30:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:30:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%9C%A0%EC%A7%84/%EA%BD%81%EB%AC%B4%EB%8B%88/" title="강유진 - 꽁무니 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꽁무니를 졸졸졸 <br>따라오던 당신을 <br>당신만을 사랑했는데 <br>뒤돌아보니 어느새 벌써 <br>꽁무니 빼고 멀어져가네 <br>이슬 같은 눈동자에 <br>센스 있는 당신이 <br>내마음을 모르시다니 <br>내 사랑을 받아주세요 <br>실망일랑 주지 말아요 <br>꽁무니 빼고 가지 말아요 <br>당신만을 사랑하니까 <br>꽁무니를 졸졸졸 <br>따라오던 당신을 <br>당신만을 사랑했는데 <br>뒤돌아보니 어느새 벌써 <br>꽁무니 빼고 멀어져가네 <br>이슬 같은 눈동자에 <br>센스 있는 당신이 <br>내마음을 모르시다니 <br>내 사랑을 받아주세요 <br>실망일랑 주지 말아요 <br>꽁무니 빼고 가지 말아요 <br>당신만을 사랑하니까 <br>당신만을 사랑하니까 <br>]]></content><category term="강유진" label="강유진"/><category term="꽁무니" label="꽁무니"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/본_보야지_Bon_Voyaze/Nouveau_Voyage_Au_Revoir/</id><title>본_보야지_Bon_Voyaze - Nouveau Voyage (Au Revoir) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:31:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:31:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B3%B8_%EB%B3%B4%EC%95%BC%EC%A7%80_Bon_Voyaze/Nouveau_Voyage_Au_Revoir/" title="본_보야지_Bon_Voyaze - Nouveau Voyage (Au Revoir) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[it’s Beautiful Day <br>it’s Beautiful Day <br>아름다웠네 아름다우길 <br>그 자체가 아름다움이지 <br>I love myself <br>Nouveau Voyage 그 첫번째 chapter <br>어린 시절엔 순수하고 무식해 <br>애기 생기는 법을 <br>알게 된게 중 1때 <br>믿지 않겠지만 <br>생각보다 많이 무지해 <br>머리를 쓰기보단 몸을 쓰는 일 <br>일이라기보단 그저 노는 것이지 <br>전혀 보지 않던 남들의 눈치 <br>그런 내가 든 펜으로 쓴 <br>가사들의 이미지 <br>그 안엔 뭐가 담겨있는지 <br>이제와 보게 되면 웃게 돼 피식 <br>여자친구 얘기 또는 친구 얘기 <br>또 있지도 않은 것들 꺼내선 <br>자랑하곤 했지 <br>그런 순수했던 때가 있었지 <br>너무 너무 그리운 <br>내 기억속에 갇힌 <br>이 Verse안의 드리운 나 과거속의 나 <br>그랬던 나도 그래 그랬던 나도 <br>Nouveau Voyage Nouveau Voyage <br>Nouveau Voyage Nouveau Voyage <br>mayday mayday <br>난 절대 안 그럴거라던 때에 <br>내게 얘기해봐야해 <br>너 또한 똑같다고 <br>내가 욕했던 이들과 <br>똑같은 행동을 해 <br>그 행동들을 한 뒤 <br>내 자신에게 두려움이 <br>생겼네 나도 이렇게 <br>되는구나 싶어서 <br>조심해야겠단 생각이 <br>문득 들었어 <br>나도 저들처럼 되는건 아닐까 <br>무조건 욕구 해소한다고 <br>행복한건 아니야 <br>앞으로 어찌 될지 난 몰라 <br>펼쳐질 Chapter 3 속의 숨은 나 <br>의 모습은 어떤 모습일까 <br>나에게 물어 <br>잘모르겠다는 듯 <br>미래 쪽으로 몸을 기울여 <br>Nouveau Voyage Nouveau Voyage <br>Nouveau Voyage Nouveau Voyage <br>넘실거리는 파도 뒤 <br>뭐가 있는지 몰라도 <br>뭉툭히 뜬 태양 뒤 <br>어떤 달이 뜰지 몰라도 잘 몰라도 <br>내가 어찌 변할지 몰라도 <br>곧 겪을 여행 끝에 변화된 <br>나를 사랑해야지 Nouveau Voyage <br>Nouveau Voyage Nouveau Voyage <br>Nouveau Voyage Nouveau Voyage <br>]]></content><category term="본 보야지 (Bon Voyaze)" label="본 보야지 (Bon Voyaze)"/><category term="Nouveau Voyage (Au Revoir)" label="Nouveau Voyage (Au Revoir)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안향연/울지마라_가야금/</id><title>안향연 - 울지마라 가야금 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:32:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:32:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%ED%96%A5%EC%97%B0/%EC%9A%B8%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88%EB%9D%BC_%EA%B0%80%EC%95%BC%EA%B8%88/" title="안향연 - 울지마라 가야금 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[울어 울어 우는구나 <br>가야금 열두줄이 <br>한줄을 퉁겨보니 <br>님의 모습 떠오르고 <br>두줄을 퉁겨보니 <br>님의 소식 그립구나 <br>울지마라 가야금아 <br>너마저 날 울리면 <br>애끓는 이 내 간장 <br>구비구비 눈물진다 <br><br>꿈아 꿈아 깨지 마라 <br>푸른 꿈 나의 꿈아 <br>세줄을 퉁겨보니 <br>님의 입술 새로웁고 <br>열두줄 퉁겨보니 <br>설움만이 북받치네 <br>울지마라 가야금아 <br>너마저 날 울리면 <br>설마설마 기다리는 <br>내 청춘이 서글프다]]></content><category term="안향연" label="안향연"/><category term="울지마라 가야금" label="울지마라 가야금"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안향연/까투리_사냥/</id><title>안향연 - 까투리 사냥 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:32:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:32:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%ED%96%A5%EC%97%B0/%EA%B9%8C%ED%88%AC%EB%A6%AC_%EC%82%AC%EB%83%A5/" title="안향연 - 까투리 사냥 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[까투리 까투리 까투리 까투리 <br>까투리 사냥을 나간다 우여 <br>전라도라 지리산으로 <br>꿩사냥을 나간다 <br>지리산을 넘어 무등산을 지나 <br>나주 금성산을 당도허니 <br>까투리 한 마리 부두둥 허니 매방울이 떨렁 <br>우여우여 허허 까투리 사냥을 나간다 우여 <br><br>까투리 까투리 까투리 까투리 <br>까투리 사냥을 나간다 우여 <br>충청도라 계룡산으로 <br>꿩사냥을 나간다 <br>충청도를 올라 계룡산을 지나 <br>경산도 가야산 당도허니 <br>까투리 한 마리 부두둥 허니 매방울이 떨렁 <br>우여우여 허허 까투리 사냥을 나간다 우여 <br>경기도라 삼각산으로 <br>꿩사냥을 나간다 <br>경기도를 올라 삼각산을 지나 <br>광주산성을 당도허니]]></content><category term="안향연" label="안향연"/><category term="까투리 사냥" label="까투리 사냥"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안향연/야월삼경/</id><title>안향연 - 야월삼경 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:32:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:32:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%ED%96%A5%EC%97%B0/%EC%95%BC%EC%9B%94%EC%82%BC%EA%B2%BD/" title="안향연 - 야월삼경 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[야월삼경 달 밝은 밤 <br>온다온다 말만하고 <br>밤은 점차 다 새는데 <br>님의 소식 돈절하네 <br>에루화 성화로구나 음~ 성화로구나 <br>님없는 이 한밤이 큰 성화로다. <br><br>촛불같이 타는 가슴 <br>혼자서만 눈물 짓네 <br>한양낭군 기다리다 <br>뜬눈으로 밤새웠네 <br>에루화 성화로구나 음~ 성화로구나 <br>한깊은 이 한밤이 큰 성화로다]]></content><category term="안향연" label="안향연"/><category term="야월삼경" label="야월삼경"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안향연/경사났네/</id><title>안향연 - 경사났네 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:32:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:32:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%ED%96%A5%EC%97%B0/%EA%B2%BD%EC%82%AC%EB%82%AC%EB%84%A4/" title="안향연 - 경사났네 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 에헤~ 금수강산에 풍년이 왔네 <br>호남평야 넓은들에 <br>참새는 짹짹 까치는 깍깍 <br>하늘 높고 황소는 잔다 <br>황금 나락에 메뚜기 날고 <br>징 장고 소리에 꽹과리 칭칭 <br>구성지게 들려오는 피리소리 <br>흥겹구나 비비 배배~ 비비 배배~ <br>얼씨구 좋다 절시구나 좋아 <br>지화자 좋구나 어깨춤이 난다 <br>시화연풍 우리농가 <br>방방곡곡 경사로구나 <br><br>2. 에헤~ 동산 마루에 반달이 떴네 <br>강산 풍월 둥실둥실 <br>놋줄은 출렁 잉어는 펄떡 <br>하늘 높고 황소는 잔다 <br>화륜선위에 노적을 싣고 <br>나루터마다 깃발이나니 <br>은은하게 들려오는 피리소리 <br>흥겹구나 비비 배배~ 비비 배배~ <br>얼씨구 좋다 절시구나 좋아 <br>지화자 좋구나 어깨춤이 난다 <br>해해 연년 우리농가 <br>방방곡곡 경사로구나]]></content><category term="안향연" label="안향연"/><category term="경사났네" label="경사났네"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한세일/모정의_세월/</id><title>한세일 - 모정의 세월 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T23:32:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T23:32:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EC%84%B8%EC%9D%BC/%EB%AA%A8%EC%A0%95%EC%9D%98_%EC%84%B8%EC%9B%94/" title="한세일 - 모정의 세월 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[동지섯달 긴긴밤이 짧기만한것은 <br>근심으로 지세우는 어머님 마음 <br>힌머리 잔주름이 늘어만 가시는데 <br>한없이 이어지는 모정의 세월 <br>아 가지많은 나무에 바람이일듯 <br>어머님 가슴에는 물결만 높네 <br>길고긴 여름날이 짧기만한 것은 <br>언제나 분주한 어머님 마음 <br>정성으로 기른자식 <br>모두들 가버려도 <br>근심으로 얼룩지는 모정의 세월 <br>아 가지많은 나무에 바람이 일듯 <br>어머님 가슴에는 물결만 높네]]></content><category term="한세일" label="한세일"/><category term="모정의 세월" label="모정의 세월"/></entry></feed>