<feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:09:31+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mystery_Skulls/One_of_Us/</id><title>Mystery Skulls - One of Us - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:09:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:09:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mystery_Skulls/One_of_Us/" title="Mystery Skulls - One of Us - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Even if I told you <br>Even if you told me, you would only do <br>Darkness is my signal <br><br>What do you to me, what do me to you? <br><br>Are you one of us? <br>Are you one of us? <br>Tell me, are you one of us? <br>Are you one of us? <br><br>I know that this sounds crazy <br>Waitin' for this moment <br>Can you see me? <br>Cuz I know that you're out there <br>This darkness is my signal <br>Come and find me <br><br>Are you one of us? <br>Are you one of us? <br>Tell me, are you one of us? <br>Are you one of us? <br><br>Are you one of us? <br>Are you one of us? <br>Are you one of us? <br>Are you one of us? <br><br>Are you one of us? <br>Are you one of us? <br>Tell me, are you one of us? <br>Are you one of us? <br><br>Are you one of us? <br>Are you one of us? <br>Are you one of us? <br>Are you one of us?]]></content><category term="Mystery Skulls" label="Mystery Skulls"/><category term="One of Us" label="One of Us"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daley/The_Only_One/</id><title>Daley - The Only One - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:09:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:09:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daley/The_Only_One/" title="Daley - The Only One - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Had your heart broken <br>You lost it all <br>Now you're afraid to climb down from the shelf <br>'Cause you're scared you'll fall again <br>How long can you live that way? <br>You're holding back, it's driving me away <br><br>It's fair to say some give and take is what we need <br>We both have stress in our lives and I'm dealing with mine <br>Well I'm trying, so don't take it out on me <br><br>'Cause you're not the only one, the only one <br>The only one with shh... on your mind <br>The street runs both ways, we've all had those days <br>And if you don't see my side, then I don't feel to try <br>'Cause you're not the only one, the only one <br>The only one who struggles sometimes <br>You're so full of yourself, but you won't get no help <br>'Til you realise, you're not the only one <br><br>You make it hard, so hard, difficult to the end <br>Why should I break my back? <br>When you refuse to bend your rules <br>I wanna make one from two again <br>But it's just so hard to do it, yeah <br>When you're not playing fair <br><br>So it's fair to say some give and take is what we need <br>We're all messed up in our ways, but I'm trying to change <br>Can you say the same? <br>Well don't take it out on me <br><br>'Cause you're not the only one, the only one <br>The only one with shh... on your mind <br>The street runs both ways, we've all had those days <br>And if you don't see my side, then I don't feel to try <br>'Cause you're not the only one, the only (one) <br>The only one who struggles sometimes <br>You're so full of yourself, but you won't get no help <br>'Til you realise, that you're not the only one <br><br>Oh no, so don't take it out on me <br>On me <br>The only one with shit on your mind <br>You're so full of yourself, but you won't get no help <br>'Til you realise, you're not the only one]]></content><category term="Daley" label="Daley"/><category term="The Only One" label="The Only One"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강유경/미시령_옛길/</id><title>강유경 - 미시령 옛길 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:10:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:10:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%9C%A0%EA%B2%BD/%EB%AF%B8%EC%8B%9C%EB%A0%B9_%EC%98%9B%EA%B8%B8/" title="강유경 - 미시령 옛길 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[구비 구비 돌고 돌아 <br>다시 한 번 옛길을 넘는다 <br>바람 부는 계곡마다 <br>그리움만 가득 하네 <br>인제 가면 언제 오나 <br>원통해서 못 넘겠네 <br>사연도 많아 추억도 많아 <br>그 옛날이 서글퍼라 <br>인생 같은 미시령 옛길 <br>구비 구비 돌고 돌아 <br>다시 한 번 옛길을 넘는다 <br>꽃이 피는 가지마다 <br>그 시절만 생각 나네 <br>인제 가면 언제 오나 <br>원통해서 못 넘겠네 <br>미련도 많아 아쉬움 많아 <br>그 사람이 보고 파라 <br>인생 같은 미시령 옛길 <br>인제 가면 언제 오나 <br>원통해서 못 넘겠네 <br>미련도 많아 아쉬움 많아 <br>그 사람이 보고 파라 <br>인생 같은 미시령 옛길 <br>]]></content><category term="강유경" label="강유경"/><category term="미시령 옛길" label="미시령 옛길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KElephant_Fresh_켈리펀트_프레쉬/Run_Away_Feat_zsu/</id><title>KElephant Fresh (켈리펀트 프레쉬) - Run Away (Feat. z.su) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:11:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:11:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KElephant_Fresh_%EC%BC%88%EB%A6%AC%ED%8E%80%ED%8A%B8_%ED%94%84%EB%A0%88%EC%89%AC/Run_Away_Feat_zsu/" title="KElephant Fresh (켈리펀트 프레쉬) - Run Away (Feat. z.su) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[시간이 많이 지나고 <br>나도 나이를 먹었지 <br>지난 지긋지긋 지루한 듯 <br>지루처럼 감흥 없는 <br>추억에 희끗희끗한 머리는 <br>어른이 맞나 봐 <br>내 안에 아메리카노 안의 향기처럼 <br>깊이가 생겼어 <br>내면 속 깃든 쓴맛도 보았네 <br>내 꽃들은 나비가 되어 <br>아이가 생겼지 <br>이젠 눈이 핑 돌아버릴 <br>클럽의 언니보단 <br>자연의 엠보싱 캠핑이 취미네 <br>캄캄한 바닥으로 가라앉기 싫어 <br>한발 더 발 뻗기 바빴지 <br>물수제비처럼 <br>검은 바닥에서 악어가 물지 않을까 <br>아래만 보고 뛰어다녔지 <br>소금쟁이처럼 <br>지난날 매미처럼 부르던 <br>행복한 노래는 <br>꿈같은 시간 속에 말라 <br>박제가 되었네 <br>두 손에 못 박고 말라버렸으니 <br>사흘만 더 꿈을 꿔볼까 <br>다시 태어날지 <br>I can`t run away from the past <br>그래도 나에게는 <br>You can`t run away from the past <br>그래도 너에게는 <br>다람쥐 쳇바퀴 돌듯 살았다는 <br>말은 하고 싶지 않아 탔어 삐딱선 <br>열심히 살았다는 말을 구걸하진 않아 <br>근데 주변의 시선들이 <br>신경 쓰일 나이 <br>어지간한 이슈는 한번 짜리 티슈 <br>만도 못해 그저 살기 위한 race에 <br>마침표를 찍기 위해 누군갈 찍어내 <br>마치 우표를 찍어낸 듯 <br>모두 같은 face <br>월요병은 또 빚쟁이 마냥 찾아와 <br>전날 밤 뜬눈은 감길 줄을 몰라 <br>불면증에 시달리는 <br>겁쟁이가 되어 기대어보는 <br>소주 몇 잔이 <br>또 아쉬워서 불러본다 <br>이슬 같은 너를 <br>비 오던 어느 새벽 <br>나를 적신 그날의 냄새 <br>가끔은 그리워지는 <br>소박했던 어릴 적 꿈이 <br>모든 게 내 것이 <br>아닌 것만 같은 지금 <br>이곳이 과연 내 길인지 <br>I can`t run away from the past <br>그래도 나에게는 <br>You can`t run away from the past <br>그래도 너에게는 <br>어차피 인생살이 <br>한 번뿐인 거 다 알아 <br>발버둥 쳐봤자 <br>도망치지 못할 것도 알아 <br>결국 세월 속에 묻힐 <br>먼지 같은 존재기에 <br>미련 없이 enjoy life 난 뭐든지 해 <br>내가 남긴 시간에 서성거릴 때 <br>다시 한번 sik 꿈을 꿀 수 있게 <br>I can`t run away from the past <br>I don`t run away that easy <br>]]></content><category term="KElephant Fresh (켈리펀트 프레쉬)" label="KElephant Fresh (켈리펀트 프레쉬)"/><category term="Run Away (Feat. z.su)" label="Run Away (Feat. z.su)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/WIJ/나_주님_보기_원합니다/</id><title>WIJ - 나 주님 보기 원합니다 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:11:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:11:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/WIJ/%EB%82%98_%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98_%EB%B3%B4%EA%B8%B0_%EC%9B%90%ED%95%A9%EB%8B%88%EB%8B%A4/" title="WIJ - 나 주님 보기 원합니다 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 주님 보기 원합니다 <br>나 주님 보기 원합니다 <br>아름다우신 주님의 얼굴 <br>나 영원히 보기 원합니다 <br>나 주님 알기 원합니다 <br>나 주님 알기 원합니다 <br>아름다우신 주님의 얼굴 <br>나 영원히 알기 원합니다 <br>오 성령님 임하소서 <br>내 눈을 열어 주 보게 하소서 <br>주의 영광을 내게 보이소서 <br>수건을 벗은 얼굴로 <br>주 보게 하소서 <br>오 주님 오 주님 <br>내 눈을 열어 주 보게 하소서 <br>오 주님 오 주님 <br>내 눈을 열어 주 보게 하소서 <br>오 주님 <br>나 주님 닮기 원합니다 <br>나 주님 닮기 원합니다 <br>아름다우신 주님의 얼굴 <br>나 영원히 닮기 원합니다 <br>아름다우신 주님의 얼굴 <br>나 영원히 닮기 원합니다 <br>나 주님 보기 원합니다 <br>나 주님 보기 원합니다 <br>아름다우신 주님의 얼굴 <br>나 영원히 보기 원합니다 <br>나 주님 알기 원합니다 <br>나 주님 알기 원합니다 <br>아름다우신 주님의 얼굴 <br>나 영원히 알기 원합니다 <br>오 성령님 임하소서 <br>내 눈을 열어 주 보게 하소서 <br>주의 영광을 내게 보이소서 <br>수건을 벗은 얼굴로 <br>주 보게 하소서 <br>오 주님 오 주님 <br>내 눈을 열어 주 보게 하소서 <br>오 주님 오 주님 <br>내 눈을 열어 주 보게 하소서 <br>오 주님 <br>나 주님 닮기 원합니다 <br>나 주님 닮기 원합니다 <br>아름다우신 주님의 얼굴 <br>나 영원히 닮기 원합니다 <br>아름다우신 주님의 얼굴 <br>나 영원히 닮기 원합니다 <br>]]></content><category term="WIJ" label="WIJ"/><category term="나 주님 보기 원합니다" label="나 주님 보기 원합니다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오재호/너에게로_가는_길_Feat_HUB_효선/</id><title>오재호 - 너에게로 가는 길 (Feat. H.U.B 효선) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:11:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:11:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EC%9E%AC%ED%98%B8/%EB%84%88%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C%EB%A1%9C_%EA%B0%80%EB%8A%94_%EA%B8%B8_Feat_HUB_%ED%9A%A8%EC%84%A0/" title="오재호 - 너에게로 가는 길 (Feat. H.U.B 효선) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어느새 봄이 다가와 <br>따스한 햇살 비춘 날 그대 <br>난 처음 보았죠 <br>유난히 맑은 두 눈에 <br>사랑스런 그 미소가 나를 <br>더욱 설레게 해 <br>이제 더 이상은 <br>내 맘 감출 수 없죠 <br>그댈 위해 준비한 <br>이 노랠 시작할게요 <br>너에게로 다가가는 길 <br>참 쉽지만 않은 길 <br>괜찮겠니 잠시 쉬었다가도 <br>그대 내게 천천히 와도 돼 <br>행복한 설렘이 가득해 <br>환한 미소를 띠고 <br>네 심장소리를 듣고 <br>쿵쾅 뛰고 있는 게 <br>다 나 때문인 거 같애 <br>콩닥 숨길 수 없는 <br>내 마음이 대답해 <br>깜찍한 네 목소리에 <br>달콤하던 네 향기가 나를 <br>두근거리게 해 <br>이제 더 이상은 <br>내 맘 감출 수 없죠 <br>그댈 위해 준비한 <br>이 노랠 시작할게요 <br>너에게로 다가가는 길 <br>참 쉽지만 않은 길 <br>괜찮겠니 잠시 쉬었다가도 <br>오래도록 기다린 만큼 <br>너를 마주한 이 순간 <br>네 눈을 보며 고백할 거야 <br>너를 사랑한다고 <br>이제 너와 함께 걷는 길 <br>나 너에게 약속해 <br>영원히 너만을 사랑한다고 <br>]]></content><category term="오재호" label="오재호"/><category term="너에게로 가는 길 (Feat. H.U.B 효선)" label="너에게로 가는 길 (Feat. H.U.B 효선)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오재호/한참을_그렇게/</id><title>오재호 - 한참을 그렇게 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:11:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:11:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EC%9E%AC%ED%98%B8/%ED%95%9C%EC%B0%B8%EC%9D%84_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A0%87%EA%B2%8C/" title="오재호 - 한참을 그렇게 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[할 말이 참 많았는데 <br>멍하니 그렇게 너를 <br>바라만 보다가 아무 말 못하고 <br>너의 뒷모습만 너의 뒷모습만 <br>언제부터 였었는지 <br>나만 몰랐던 거니 <br>거리의 사람들 이 모든 사람들 <br>날보고 비웃는 것만 같아 <br>눈물도 말라 버렸다 <br>한숨도 얼어 붙었다 <br>한참을 그렇게 <br>네 뒤에 그렇게 <br>목놓아서 울었다 <br>할 말을 다 잊었는지 <br>내가 바보가 된 건지 <br>말을 잇지 못하고 <br>너를 잡지 못하고 <br>너의 뒷모습만 너의 뒷모습만 <br>눈물도 말라 버렸다 <br>한숨도 얼어 붙었다 <br>한참을 그렇게 <br>네 뒤에 그렇게 <br>목놓아서 울었다 <br>이 순간 너의 모든 게 <br>달콤했던 꿈처럼 <br>영원히 그렇게 <br>나에게서 그렇게 <br>멀어지고 말았다 <br>눈물도 말라 버렸다 <br>한숨도 얼어 붙었다 <br>한참을 그렇게 <br>한참을 그렇게 <br>목놓아서 울었다 <br>]]></content><category term="오재호" label="오재호"/><category term="한참을 그렇게" label="한참을 그렇게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/미리내/살아가는_법/</id><title>미리내 - 살아가는 법 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:12:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:12:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AF%B8%EB%A6%AC%EB%82%B4/%EC%82%B4%EC%95%84%EA%B0%80%EB%8A%94_%EB%B2%95/" title="미리내 - 살아가는 법 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[힘들었던 하루 지쳐버린 내 몸 <br>이렇게 또 내일이 반복되는 일이 <br>힘든 감정 속상한 기분 <br>울고픈 마음 모조리 <br>숨겨야 하는 현실인 것을 느낀다 <br>내 마음처럼 비가 오는 오늘은 <br>더욱 힘없이 내 몸도 무거워 지네 <br>행복했던 날들 즐거웠던 날들 <br>항상 생각나지 오늘도 생각해 <br>그리워서 너무 그리워서 <br>자꾸 생각이 나나 봐 <br>내 눈물이 온몸을 다 적셔 내린다 <br>내 마음처럼 비가 오는 오늘은 <br>더욱 힘없이 내 몸도 무거워 지네 <br>살아가다 보면 <br>이런 날들도 익숙해지겠지 <br>돌이켜보면 별거 아닌 것들 <br>내 마음처럼 비가 오는 오늘은 <br>더욱 힘없이 내 몸도 무거워 지네 <br>이 모든 말들이 살아가는 법 <br>]]></content><category term="미리내" label="미리내"/><category term="살아가는 법" label="살아가는 법"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지코_ZICO/FANXY_CHILD_Feat_FANXY_CHILD/</id><title>지코 (ZICO) - FANXY CHILD (Feat. FANXY CHILD) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:13:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:13:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EC%BD%94_ZICO/FANXY_CHILD_Feat_FANXY_CHILD/" title="지코 (ZICO) - FANXY CHILD (Feat. FANXY CHILD) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Life is what you make of it <br>남보다 한 페이지 일찍 넘겨 <br>고등래퍼 땐 이미 작업한 뒤 <br>with swings and verbal <br>나의 잠재력 눈치 까고 <br>서둘러 죽이려던 놈들 <br>간곡한 부탁 다 거절 놓고 <br>다음 광고 콘티를 훑고 있어 <br>흥미 없어요 집 공개는 yeah <br>내가 날 가졌기 때문 yeah <br>네 정서를 배려하는 차원에서 <br>수입에 대한 건 노코멘트 yeah <br>Go back to 2014 <br>아무도 몰랐지 편견은 <br>반전 줄 때 효과 있지 <br>I was 24 at show me 4 <br>And I be 26 at season 6 <br>미디어와 내 안목을 합치면 <br>it will be big benefit <br>껄끄러운 인간관계는 <br>정리할게 여지없이 <br>왜냐 빛이 강한 곳 주변엔 <br>늘 벌레들이 득실이니 <br>You get it Fanxy <br>U CAN'T HANDLE FANXY CHILD <br>U CAN'T HANDLE FANXY CHILD <br>I DON'T LIKE YOUR FASHION STYLE <br>다 뒤처지느라 고생이 많다 <br>길거리를 거닐 때에 <br>데시벨은 에버랜드 yeah <br>1 2년 새에 이제 더는 없는 vacation <br>Oh yeah gentleman <br>네 여친은 떨어 내 이름에 <br>질투는 건강에 해롭기에 get away <br>내 피처링은 danger <br>Hmm 많은 래퍼를 죽였어 트랙에서 <br>We make make 팬케이크 yeah <br>네 콧대는 눌리게 돼 있어 <br>Different R&amp;B R&amp;B <br>I don't care 메인 스트림 or 인디신 <br>어떤 시스템에 들어가기엔 <br>덩치가 커진 원숭이띠들 Fanxy <br>U CAN'T HANDLE FANXY CHILD <br>U CAN'T HANDLE FANXY CHILD <br>I DON'T LIKE YOUR FASHION STYLE <br>다 뒤처지느라 고생이 많다 <br>Imma rip it up like a monster 내 DNA <br>우리 92는 제일 맛있어 <br>Yummy yummy <br>듣고 판단해 디자이너 <br>Now wait wait wait wait wait <br>방금 위험해 <br>아 참 이건 표절곡 <br>잘못했다간 욕먹어 <br>댓글 적어 Khalifa 형 오졌고 <br>떼창할 땐 가사는 몰라도 돼 맞죠 <br>최고는 싫고 <br>Supreme preme preme은 멋져 <br>So we slay we slay we slay <br>Whippin whippin whippin <br>손오공이 된 기분 비행기는 근두운 <br>세계를 누빌 잔나비띠들 Fanxy <br>U CAN'T HANDLE FANXY CHILD <br>U CAN'T HANDLE FANXY CHILD <br>I DON'T LIKE YOUR FASHION STYLE <br>다 뒤처지느라 고생이 많다 <br>Get in my 2411 <br>GTS는 초록색 버스 <br>맨 뒷자리에서부터 <br>내일 나 이사해 통유리 <br>한강이 다 보이네 <br>No more minor 이 melody처럼 <br>now I'm fuckin major <br>벌레 같은 게 나풀대 <br>나부끼네 나부끼네 나부끼네 <br>누운 자리 이부자리를 개 <br>자리를 개 자리를 개 자리를 개 <br>똥이 차 있네 차 있기에 <br>네 아가리에 잘 관리해 <br>이 새끼 Fanxy you 잘 들어봐 봐 <br>안에 매미 소리 녹음돼 있어 <br>Sippin bottles of champagne <br>병을 따자 아무도 날 못 건드려 <br>내 친구들이 방패 <br>티키타카 티키타카 너넬 갖고 놀아 <br>내 친구들은 너넬 붙였다 뗐다 <br>스티커 티커 존나 쉬워 <br>우린 한치 두치 세치 네치 <br>뿌꾸뿌꾸빠만 불러도 야 <br>1위를 찍어 Fanxy <br>U CAN'T HANDLE FANXY CHILD <br>U CAN'T HANDLE FANXY CHILD <br>I DON'T LIKE YOUR FASHION STYLE <br>다 뒤처지느라 고생이 많다 <br>]]></content><category term="지코 (ZICO)" label="지코 (ZICO)"/><category term="FANXY CHILD (Feat. FANXY CHILD)" label="FANXY CHILD (Feat. FANXY CHILD)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지코_ZICO/ANTI_Feat_GSoul/</id><title>지코 (ZICO) - ANTI (Feat. G.Soul) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:13:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:13:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EC%BD%94_ZICO/ANTI_Feat_GSoul/" title="지코 (ZICO) - ANTI (Feat. G.Soul) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[속이지 못해 난 <br>화면 밖의 네 표정을 본 적이 있어 <br>분칠을 벗겨 내고 <br>전부 시늉이었단 걸 알릴 거야 <br>Why do I hate <br>I don't understand <br>널 주목하는 시선들이 <br>I don't understand <br>그 나이에 거머쥔 것들이 <br>열광 중인 팬 널 출연시킨 <br>TV 프로들이 <br>너의 주위를 구성하는 <br>뮤지션들이 yo <br>자세한 동기는 없지 벽치는데 <br>이유 없지 <br>집단에 파묻히면 양심은 <br>가려지는 법이지 <br>뭔 노력을 펼쳤고 어떤 수모를 겪었던 <br>출세는 너가 다시 욕먹을 자격을 줬어 <br>네 교만함의 뿌릴 뽑아 <br>인생을 휘청이게 할 거야 <br>이런 교양 없는 양아치를 <br>그녀는 왜 만난 걸까 <br>연예인은 조명에 눈멀고 환호에 <br>귀가 먹어서 <br>보고 듣고도 손 못 써 <br>속이지 못해 난 <br>화면 밖의 네 표정을 본 적이 있어 <br>분칠을 벗겨 내고 <br>전부 시늉이었단 걸 알릴 거야 <br>Why do I hate you <br>누리는 만큼 <br>더 큰 대가를 치러 <br>That's all I wanna tell you about <br>I'm not you anti anti anti baby <br>I don't understand <br>히트친 네 음악들이 <br>매년 수여받는 상들이 <br>호사스러운 근황들이 <br>너가 버는 수익 내겐 그저 불이익 <br>이쯤에서 딱 물의 일으키면 <br>나이스 타이밍 <br>폭언이 준비된 입을 달싹이지 <br>Our needs are simple <br>한 문장 삐끗하면 돼 <br>해석은 내 몫이고 사상 또한 내가 정해 <br>백 번의 선행은 모래 위 <br>한 번의 과오는 바위에 다 새길 거야 <br>적 되면 누가 손해게 직접 봐 <br>카메라 렌즈는 불시에 총구로 변해 <br>you should know eh <br>네게 아무리 엿 같은 장단이 <br>주어져도 깍듯이 춤춰 <br>If u agree say yes <br>I'm not an anti its fan mail <br>점점 선플이 달릴 때 <br>이미 넌 한물가 있겠지 <br>속이지 못해 난 <br>화면 밖의 네 표정을 본 적이 있어 <br>분칠을 벗겨 내고 <br>전부 시늉이었단 걸 알릴 거야 <br>Why do I hate you <br>누리는 만큼 <br>더 큰 대가를 치러 <br>That's all I wanna tell you about <br>I'm not you anti anti anti baby <br>명심해 예명을 지은 순간 널 죽여야 돼 <br>선택은 너의 자유야 <br>먹히려면 우선 씹혀 도마 위에 올라가 <br>프로는 항상 입꼬리 찢어 <br>인기 얻기 위해 심판 받아 <br>상품에 프라이버시가 어디 있냐고 <br>여긴 왕이야 소비자가 <br>격조 갖춰 표정 감춰 <br>평소에 모자 마스크 쓰는 이유잖아 huh <br>증오도 관심이야 <br>언제까지 대우받을 것 같아 bro <br>So 나에게도 감사해 <br>I'll make you loose your way <br>오래 봤으면 좋겠다 이만 마칠게 <br>속이지 못해 난 <br>화면 밖의 네 표정을 본 적이 있어 <br>분칠을 벗겨 내고 <br>전부 시늉이었단 걸 알릴 거야 <br>Why do I hate you <br>누리는 만큼 <br>더 큰 대가를 치러 <br>That's all I wanna tell you about <br>I'm not you anti anti anti baby <br>]]></content><category term="지코 (ZICO)" label="지코 (ZICO)"/><category term="ANTI (Feat. G.Soul)" label="ANTI (Feat. G.Soul)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지코_ZICO/Artist/</id><title>지코 (ZICO) - Artist - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:13:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:13:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EC%BD%94_ZICO/Artist/" title="지코 (ZICO) - Artist - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We are we are we artist baby <br>We are we are we artist ZICO <br>뭔가 예감 좋아 번뜩 악상이 떠올라 <br>금토일도 월요일같이 사는 내게 <br>상 줄 거야 Alright <br>올해도 스케줄 꽉 찼고 <br>길 가면 다 알아보고 <br>Fanxy child 겁나 핫하고 <br>그런데도 나 외로워 <br>What should I do <br>지루해 죽기 직전인 사람 <br>절대 양반은 못 되는 사람 <br>굳이 긁어 부스럼 만드는 사람 <br>아주 박살을 내버릴 사람들 Oh yes <br>언제까지 머릿속만 시끄러울래 <br>예술에 조예가 깊다면 <br>Let’s draw something <br>From now on <br>모든 것을 백지로 되돌려 놓고 <br>생각 말고 저질러 <br>붓은 너가 쥐고 있어 <br>제일 감각 있잖아 <br>자기 집 거울 앞에선 yeah <br>Life is short Art is long <br>너나 나나 쟤나 I make’em say <br>Ah We are we artist baby <br>We are we are we artist baby <br>We are we are we artist baby <br>Hey Life is short Art is long <br>너나 나나 쟤나 I make’em say <br>Let me think about it 도대체 뭘 <br>얻고자 온종일 노랠 만들었을까 <br>일하고 품위 유진 언제 해 <br>막히면 저 반대 길로 역주행 해 <br>모자 눌러 써 신발 구겨 신어 <br>바깥 공기 마시며 세상 구경 좀 해 <br>남이 재단할 수 없어 <br>내 인생은 내가 디자인해 Get up <br>시선 빼 그러다 목에 담 와 <br>손에 잡히지 않는 건 다 놔 <br>구색 따윈 갖추지 말자 <br>흥얼대 혼자 샤워할 때처럼 <br>Like whoo yes <br>난 나이를 먹지 않고 도로 뱉을 건데 <br>내 말이 설득력 있다면 <br>Make some noise <br>From now on <br>모든 것을 백지로 되돌려 놓고 <br>생각 말고 저질러 <br>붓은 너가 쥐고 있어 <br>제일 감각 있잖아 <br>자기 집 거울 앞에선 yeah <br>Life is short Art is long <br>너나 나나 쟤나 I make’em say <br>Ah We are we artist baby <br>We are we are we artist baby <br>We are we are we artist baby <br>Hey Life is short Art is long <br>너나 나나 쟤나 I make’em say <br>미루지 마 즐거움을 <br>그건 저축이 불가능 <br>Somebody say 이 다음에 커서 <br>그 커서가 바로 지금 <br>내일 지구가 멸망하면 <br>Answer me what you gon do <br>행복의 언저리에서 고민은 금물 <br>Now on <br>모든 것을 백지로 되돌려 놓고 <br>생각 말고 저질러 <br>붓은 너가 쥐고 있어 <br>제일 감각 있잖아 <br>자기 집 거울 앞에선 yeah <br>Life is short Art is long <br>너나 나나 쟤나 I make’em say <br>Are are are are artist baby <br>We are are are are artist baby <br>Are are are are artist baby <br>One more time <br>Life is short Art is long <br>너나 나나 쟤나 I make’em say <br>]]></content><category term="지코 (ZICO)" label="지코 (ZICO)"/><category term="Artist" label="Artist"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지코_ZICO/천재_Behind_the_scene/</id><title>지코 (ZICO) - 천재 (Behind the scene) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:13:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:13:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EC%BD%94_ZICO/%EC%B2%9C%EC%9E%AC_Behind_the_scene/" title="지코 (ZICO) - 천재 (Behind the scene) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Give me the bass line <br>있어 보여 멋있어 보여 <br>What's going on guys Hello <br>있어 보여 멋있어 보여 <br>I put it all in the music <br>있어 보여 멋있어 보여 <br>More time to get it right <br>있어 보여 멋있어 보여 <br>Fanxy Television <br>Sorry my bro 밥 살게 진짜 <br>약속 또 펑크 내고 작업실로 기어가 <br>The orange lights 두 겹의 컵에 <br>탄산수 가득 채우고 <br>Let's do it something Aight <br>개쩔거나 개졸작이거나 <br>퇴근길 내 입모양으로 알 수 있지 <br>오늘 컨디션 별로라 뭐라도 걸려라는 <br>심정으로 던져 영감의 미끼 <br>From movies books music <br>문화를 변태처럼 더듬어 <br>거들먹대는 내 모든 작품들 <br>저 너머엔 <br>특출난 척 용쓰는 멍청이가 <br>건조해진 머리를 쥐어짜고 있네 <br>Uhm 수고스러운 평론을 <br>준비 중이라면 <br>넣어둬 이 새꺄 <br>Uhm 난 작업 당시에 충분히 <br>내가 병신임을 체험해 이 새꺄 <br>있어 보여 멋있어 보여 <br>Well I don't think so you fools <br>너희처럼 I’m also normal <br>That's right 음악은 어려워 <br>있어 보여 멋있어 보여 <br>Well I don't think so you fools <br>There’s a lot of trouble behind <br>추측하지 마 이건 자기 비하 <br>구상만 하다 하루를 통째로 날려 <br>스트레스 받을 틈도 없어 <br>한숨은 하품할 때 몰아쉬어 <br>G major도 못 집던 놈의 <br>과감한 터치는 없고 <br>요령만 잔뜩 터득한 걸 <br>화가와 작가 연기자와 음악가 <br>다 빚쟁이 처지 작품을 독촉 받아 <br>자뻑을 언제 했는지 기억조차 안 나 <br>무지한 게 때론 창조적인 거 알아 <br>우아한 백조의 발은 악착같이 <br>물을 저어 현재 내 모습 같아 <br>독특한 발상 그래 creative ideas <br>고통 속에 피우는 예술 감각 <br>나 자체를 장르화 <br>시키는 게 빠르겠어 <br>앨범 단위로 mixtape <br>막 찍어내던 때로 <br>이 또한 음악인의 자세 <br>고 김광석께 경례 <br>Still inspired by 김성재 <br>있어 보여 멋있어 보여 <br>Well I don't think so you fools <br>너희처럼 I’m also normal <br>That's right 음악은 어려워 <br>있어 보여 멋있어 보여 <br>Well I don't think so you fools <br>There’s a lot of trouble behind <br>추측하지 마 이건 자기 비하 <br>I’m not a genius is no difference <br>I’m not a genius is no difference <br>That's for sure <br>]]></content><category term="지코 (ZICO)" label="지코 (ZICO)"/><category term="천재 (Behind the scene)" label="천재 (Behind the scene)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/금채안/오빠가_좋아/</id><title>금채안 - 오빠가 좋아 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:13:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:13:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%88%EC%B1%84%EC%95%88/%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%A0%EA%B0%80_%EC%A2%8B%EC%95%84/" title="금채안 - 오빠가 좋아 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오빠가 너무 좋아 첫눈에 반했어요 <br>오빠가 너무 좋아 오빠가 좋아좋아 <br>나는 행복해요 그대 여자라서 <br>나만 바라봐요 내 사랑 다 줄께요 <br>하늘에 별이라도 따다 준다는 사람 <br>내가 원하는 건 뭐든지 다 줄 사람 <br>오빠가 너무 좋아 나를 안아줘요 <br>오빠가 너무 좋아 오빠 사랑해요 <br>오빠가 너무 좋아 첫눈에 반했어요 <br>오빠가 너무 좋아 오빠가 좋아좋아 <br>나는 행복해요 그대 여자라서 <br>나만 바라봐요 내 사랑 다 줄께요 <br>내 눈에 콩깍지가 씌였다 말하지만 <br>옆에만 있어줘도 마음 설레는 사람 <br>오빠가 너무 좋아 나를 안아줘요 <br>오빠가 너무 좋아 오빠 사랑해요 <br>오빠가 너무 좋아 오빠 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="금채안" label="금채안"/><category term="오빠가 좋아" label="오빠가 좋아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤일/WAVE/</id><title>헤일 - WAVE - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:14:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:14:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%BC/WAVE/" title="헤일 - WAVE - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wave <br>파도소리따라 <br>Wave <br>몸이 가는대로 <br>Wave <br>리듬에 맞춰서 <br>이번 여름에는 헤일과 함께 춤을 <br>맴맴맴 매미 왔다 여름곡 써야지 <br>통기타 뚬바뚬바 쳐보고있는데 <br>자꾸만 생각나네 우리보고 뭐 뭐 <br>우리노래가 거기서 거기래 <br>내 가사도 얘 멜로디도 <br>틀에 박혔다나 <br>틀이 뭔데 뭐 창틀이야 <br>빵틀이야 뭐야 <br>이노랠 완성시키면 <br>땅을 치고 후회할거다 <br>범생이 헤일과 춤이나 춰 <br>Wave <br>파도소리따라 <br>Wave <br>몸이 가는대로 <br>Wave <br>리듬에 맞춰서 <br>이번 여름에는 헤일과 함께 춤을 <br>Wave wave <br>Wave wave <br>Wave wave <br>Wave <br>Wave <br>헤일과 함께 춤을 <br>이래도 말할텐가 틀에박혔다고 <br>방금 꿀렁꿀렁 춤춘거 다 봤는데 <br>아직도 꼼짝않네 따라해봐 yo yo <br>이거까진 안할랬는데 <br>huh drop the beat <br>It's time to boogie with me <br>아직도 가만히 있니 <br>이건 swag feel my swag <br>범생이들의 swag <br>봄바람은 이미 휘날렸고 <br>씨스타도 이제 못보잖아 <br>이제부터 여름엔 뭐 헤일과 함께 춤을 <br>Wave <br>파도소리따라 <br>Wave <br>몸이 가는대로 <br>Wave <br>리듬에 맞춰서 <br>이번 여름에는 헤일과 함께 춤을 <br>Wave wave <br>Wave wave <br>Wave wave <br>Wave <br>Wave <br>헤일과 함께 춤을 <br>헤일과 함께 춤을 <br>Wave <br>파도소리따라 <br>Wave <br>몸이 가는대로 <br>Wave <br>리듬에 맞춰서 <br>이번 여름에는 헤일과 함께 춤을 <br>Wave wave <br>Wave wave <br>Wave wave <br>Wave <br>Wave <br>헤일과 함께 춤을 <br>]]></content><category term="헤일" label="헤일"/><category term="WAVE" label="WAVE"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김영은/고백하는_날/</id><title>김영은 - 고백하는 날 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:14:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:14:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%98%81%EC%9D%80/%EA%B3%A0%EB%B0%B1%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%82%A0/" title="김영은 - 고백하는 날 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[포근한 햇살이 내리쬐는 날 <br>눈부시게 밝은 하늘 <br>달콤한 꽃향기도 가득 <br>어느새 봄이 왔나봐 <br>살랑살랑 불어오는 봄바람에 <br>따스한 네 미소가 생각 나 <br>어느새 내 마음은 너로 <br>네가 보고싶어져 <br>너에게 가까이 더 가까이 <br>다가가고 싶은데 <br>난 여전히 용기가 없어 <br>오늘도 난 네 생각만 <br>쿵쾅쿵쾅 떨려오는 심장소리 <br>솜사탕같은 너의 목소리 <br>봄이 다 가기 전에 <br>너와 이 길을 걷고 싶어 <br>오늘도 혼자서 상상해 <br>너에게 고백하는 나 <br>상상만으로도 볼이 발그레해지는 걸 <br>너에게 가까이 더 가까이 <br>다가가고 싶은데 <br>난 여전히 용기가 없어 <br>오늘도 난 네 생각만 <br>아무것도 할 수 없어 <br>나에겐 온통 너의 생각뿐 <br>너는 알고 있을까 이런 나의 마음을 <br>생각만 해도 좋아 <br>가까이 더 가까이 다가가고 싶은데 <br>나 여전히 자신이 없어 <br>너에게로 가는 길 <br>더 천천히 더 천천히 <br>다가갈게 너에게 <br>나 이제야 용기를 낼게 <br>오늘은 고백하는 날 <br>]]></content><category term="김영은" label="김영은"/><category term="고백하는 날" label="고백하는 날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/허영생/바라보기_Inst/</id><title>허영생 - 바라보기 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:14:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:14:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%88%EC%98%81%EC%83%9D/%EB%B0%94%EB%9D%BC%EB%B3%B4%EA%B8%B0_Inst/" title="허영생 - 바라보기 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[또 하루가 가죠 <br>아픔 속에 잠이 들죠 <br>언젠가 그대 품에 <br>잠이 드는 꿈을 꾸죠 <br>또 멀어질까 봐 <br>혼자서만 간직하는 <br>이런 사랑 아나요 <br>마음 아나요 <br>맴도는 아픈 사랑을 <br>바라보기 바라보기 <br>그대만 바라보네요 <br>기다리기 기다리기 <br>가슴이 아려와도 <br>사랑하기 사랑하기 <br>그대를 잃을 수 없는 가슴을 <br>알고 있나요 그대 <br>또 멀어질까 봐 <br>혼자서만 간직하는 <br>이런 사랑 아나요 <br>마음 아나요 <br>맴도는 아픈 사랑을 <br>바라보기 바라보기 <br>그대만 바라보네요 <br>기다리기 기다리기 <br>가슴이 아려와도 <br>사랑하기 사랑하기 <br>그대를 잃을 수 없는 가슴을 <br>알고 있나요 그대 <br>바라보다 바라보다 <br>혹시나 지쳐버리면 <br>어떡하죠 어떡하죠 <br>문득 겁이 나네요 <br>사랑하기 사랑하기 <br>그대를 잃을 수 없는 가슴을 <br>알고 있나요 그대 <br>사랑합니다 그대 <br>]]></content><category term="허영생" label="허영생"/><category term="바라보기 (Inst.)" label="바라보기 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/허영생/바라보기/</id><title>허영생 - 바라보기 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:14:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:14:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%88%EC%98%81%EC%83%9D/%EB%B0%94%EB%9D%BC%EB%B3%B4%EA%B8%B0/" title="허영생 - 바라보기 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[또 하루가 가죠 <br>아픔 속에 잠이 들죠 <br>언젠가 그대 품에 <br>잠이 드는 꿈을 꾸죠 <br>또 멀어질까 봐 <br>혼자서만 간직하는 <br>이런 사랑 아나요 <br>마음 아나요 <br>맴도는 아픈 사랑을 <br>바라보기 바라보기 <br>그대만 바라보네요 <br>기다리기 기다리기 <br>가슴이 아려와도 <br>사랑하기 사랑하기 <br>그대를 잃을 수 없는 가슴을 <br>알고 있나요 그대 <br>또 멀어질까 봐 <br>혼자서만 간직하는 <br>이런 사랑 아나요 <br>마음 아나요 <br>맴도는 아픈 사랑을 <br>바라보기 바라보기 <br>그대만 바라보네요 <br>기다리기 기다리기 <br>가슴이 아려와도 <br>사랑하기 사랑하기 <br>그대를 잃을 수 없는 가슴을 <br>알고 있나요 그대 <br>바라보다 바라보다 <br>혹시나 지쳐버리면 <br>어떡하죠 어떡하죠 <br>문득 겁이 나네요 <br>사랑하기 사랑하기 <br>그대를 잃을 수 없는 가슴을 <br>알고 있나요 그대 <br>사랑합니다 그대 <br>]]></content><category term="허영생" label="허영생"/><category term="바라보기" label="바라보기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김보름/술에_취한_밤/</id><title>김보름 - 술에 취한 밤 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:14:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:14:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%B3%B4%EB%A6%84/%EC%88%A0%EC%97%90_%EC%B7%A8%ED%95%9C_%EB%B0%A4/" title="김보름 - 술에 취한 밤 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지친 몸을 이끌고 <br>집에 들어가기 전에 <br>쓸쓸한 거리에 혼자 <br>술잔을 기울인다 <br>이제 겨우 아홉 시 <br>사람들과 섞여 앉아 <br>조금씩 마시다 보니 <br>어느새 새벽 두 시 <br>반짝이는 불빛아래 <br>화려한 이 세상 속에 <br>나만 혼자 남겨진 기분 <br>반복된 일상에 지쳐 <br>맘 기댈 곳 하나 없는데 <br>지금은 행복한 시간 <br>맘의 짐을 덜 수 있는 시간 <br>아무런 생각하지 않아도 되는 이 밤 <br>한잔 술에 어제를 잊고 <br>두잔 술에 널 지우고 <br>힘든 하루 술잔에 담네 <br>흔들리는 내 맘 속에 <br>기대 쉴 곳 하나 없는데 <br>지금은 행복한 시간 <br>맘의 짐을 덜 수 있는 시간 <br>아무런 생각하지 않아도 되는 이 밤 <br>한잔 두잔 세잔 네 잔 <br>점점 날이 밝아오고 <br>술에 취한 내 모습이 <br>초라해 보이는데 <br>지금은 행복한 시간 <br>맘의 짐을 덜 수 있는 시간 <br>아무런 생각하지 않아도 되는 이 밤 <br>지금은 특별한 시간 <br>슬픔을 잊을 수 있는 시간 <br>지루했던 일상을 지워버리는 이 밤 <br>]]></content><category term="김보름" label="김보름"/><category term="술에 취한 밤" label="술에 취한 밤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Yes/</id><title>Sfb - Yes! - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:16:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:16:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Yes/" title="Sfb - Yes! - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ohyeah <br>Kijk hoe ik flex in m'n nest <br>Kijk hoe ik money invest <br>Of je ziet mij met een turk <br>Kijk hoe ik murda, we doen nu ons best <br>Of je ziet mij in BE <br>Ik gooi wat diamonds op me chest <br>En jullie niggas zeiden Nee <br>Nu zeggen modellen me Yes <br><br>Diamonds net als Kim K <br>Focus net als Kanye West <br>Die mannen spelen supergaande <br>Maar ik ben liever super blessed <br>Jullie niggas zeiden Nee <br>Nu zeggen de labels me Yes <br>En jullie bitches zeiden Nee <br>Nu zeggen modellen me Yes <br><br>Ik zeg het je straight <br>Ik neem die groupies niet met me op dates <br>Champs elysees <br>Ik boss een check op mezelf, niet gay <br>Party agenda, ik kom op de feest <br>Pak m'n agenda, wanneer zie ik Kees <br>Ik zet nu een streep <br> toen die hebben geraced <br>Ik weet het, niemand of my sort is <br>Het werken doet pof, net een koortslip <br>Je kan niet fucken met een wasteman <br>Jullie zijn een mislukte abortus <br><br>Die niggas haten van de start <br>Maar wie eindigt dan op de Forbes list <br>Die niggas haten me allang <br>Omdat de money veels te kort is <br>Taz een Blackberry Curve <br>Meer een iPhone 7 Plus <br>Ik post een picca met je zus <br>Voordat ik pull up en ik boss in d'r kut <br>Voor ik slaap tel ik een rug <br>Dan komt een nigga pas tot rust <br>Die mannen zijn alleen op hype <br>Maar wat ga je doen als die hype is gesust ya <br><br>Kijk hoe ik flex in m'n nest <br>Kijk hoe ik money invest <br>Of je ziet mij met een turk <br>Kijk hoe ik murda, we doen nu ons best <br>Of je ziet mij in BE <br>Ik gooi wat diamonds op me chest <br>En jullie niggas zeiden Nee <br>Nu zeggen modellen me Yes <br><br>Diamonds net als Kim K <br>Focus net als Kanye West <br>Die mannen spelen supergaande <br>Maar ik ben liever super blessed <br>Jullie niggas zeiden Nee <br>Nu zeggen de labels me Yes <br>En jullie bitches zeiden Nee <br>Nu zeggen modellen me Yes <br><br>De realest boys zonder twijfel <br>Proper songen, we gaan veilig <br>Of ik pullup in die Merrie skrr <br>Met die klasse die niet spijbelt <br>Nu wil je springen op me eikel <br>Maar sorry schat je bent op cijfers <br>Ik zet m'n handen op de bijbel <br>Dat ik never ever lack <br>Dit is money boven kechs <br>Jij moet weten dat ik rem <br>Dit is bleeden voor de fam <br>En dat is eenmaal wie ik ben <br>Ik wil m'n Rolley presidential <br>Geen verkiezing, maak gebruik van de stem <br>Ik zag m'n cel als een Tweede Kamer toen ik door de po' werd geklemd <br><br>They don't wanna see the rave <br>They don't wanna see me blessed <br>Gooi die diamonds om me nek <br>En dan stap ik in een jet <br>Ben met Barry en Promes <br>Ik hoor ze zeggen Je bent next <br>Gooi die blessings op me chest <br>En haat de haters van me weg <br>Er wordt never nooit gelackt <br>En dat zweer ik op me stacks <br>Ik doe die shit voor m'n moeder <br>En voor m'n niggers in de trap <br><br>Louboutin die is echt leer <br>Check in het veld hoe ik presteer <br><br>Kijk hoe ik flex in m'n nest <br>Kijk hoe ik money invest <br>Of je ziet mij met een turk <br>Kijk hoe ik murda, we doen ons best <br>Of je ziet mij in BE <br>Ik gooi wat diamonds op me chest <br>En jullie niggas zeiden Nee <br>ja <br><br>Diamonds net als Kim K <br>Focus net als Kanye West <br>Die mannen spelen supergaande <br>Maar ik ben liever super blessed <br>Jullie niggas zeiden Nee <br>Nu zeggen de labels me Yes <br>En jullie bitches zeiden Nee <br>Nu zeggen modellen me Yes <br><br>Ja, je hebt ups and downs maar <br>The only way is up, you get me <br>Nu zeggen modellen me Yes <br>By the way, fuck alle ops <br>Ben blij met al die niggas die down met me zijn, you get me <br>Nu zeggen modellen me Yes]]></content><category term="Sfb" label="Sfb"/><category term="Yes!" label="Yes!"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Lovely_Body_Feat_Ronnie_Flex/</id><title>Sfb - Lovely Body (Feat. Ronnie Flex) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:16:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:16:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Lovely_Body_Feat_Ronnie_Flex/" title="Sfb - Lovely Body (Feat. Ronnie Flex) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ben je mami wata, schat, of ben je dat niet <br>Ik wil dat je waka met je lovely body <br>Ik wil dat je danst, yeah yeah, dans it for me <br>Ik wil dat je waka met je lovely body ey, ey, ey <br><br>Ik kan je brengen naar de wild wild west <br>Maar luister goed naar wat je mama zegt <br>Want ik heb hier die badman flex <br>En je weet ik heb die badman sex, en <br><br>Je weet ik heb die badman sauce <br>No lie, ik houd het echt met jou <br>Je weet dat ik vecht met jou <br>That way, ik ga weg met jou <br><br>I'm looking for a bad gyal to dansi for me <br>I'm looking for a bad gyal to dansi for me <br>I'm looking for a bad gyal to dansi for me <br>I'm looking for a bad gyal to dansi for me <br><br>Ben je mami wata, schat, of ben je dat niet <br>Ik wil dat je waka met je lovely body <br>Ik wil dat je danst, yeah yeah, dans it for me <br>Ik wil dat je waka met je lovely body ey, ey, ey <br><br>Bad gyal o be dada mi <br>Ik wil niet dat je aan me zit aan me zit <br>Maar ik wil dat je met me danst yeah, yeah <br>Come again, want ik grijp mijn kans <br>Pull up selecta <br>Club shutdown like Skepta <br>Matta op de bank, Manchester <br>Ik was al lit voor ik rapte <br><br>Oh je kijkt me zolang aan <br>Kan je die dingen ook langzaam <br>Ja ik weet een manier wooh, wooh <br>Manier hoe het kan gaan <br>Baby, ik wil niet meer blijven hangen aan de zijkant <br>Jij bent veel mooier aan mijn hand <br>Wat is het niet, wat is het wel, wat gaat het zijn dan <br>Ik wil niet meer in wachten in de rij, want <br><br>Ben je mami wata, schat, of ben je dat niet <br>Ik wil dat je waka met je lovely body <br>Ik wil dat je danst, yeah yeah, dans it for me <br>Ik wil dat je waka met je lovely body ey, ey, ey <br><br>Nobody haffi know, say we're gon' fuck ey <br>Heb die pussy on lock <br>Fine China, you wanna glow up <br>Ik bel Kleine, you wanna turn up <br>Tell me wan fi di whine pon me <br>All the night, till the next morning <br>Je ziet de ice, wanna be darling <br>Je ziet de ice, wanna be darling <br><br>Ben je mami wata, schat, of ben je dat niet <br>Ik wil dat je waka met je lovely body <br>Ik wil dat je danst, yeah yeah, dans it for me <br>Ik wil dat je waka met je lovely body ey, ey, ey <br><br>Ben je mami wata, schat, of ben je dat niet <br>Ik wil dat je waka met je lovely body <br>Ik wil dat je danst, yeah yeah, dans it for me <br>Ik wil dat je waka met je lovely body ey, ey, ey]]></content><category term="Sfb" label="Sfb"/><category term="Lovely Body (Feat. Ronnie Flex)" label="Lovely Body (Feat. Ronnie Flex)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/25_To_Life_Feat_Jayh/</id><title>Sfb - 25 To Life (Feat. Jayh) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:17:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:17:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/25_To_Life_Feat_Jayh/" title="Sfb - 25 To Life (Feat. Jayh) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yah yah yah yah <br>Yah yah yah yah <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Tell 'em it's a <br><br>Ik ah fuck je lil' baby bitch, als ik je city hit skrr <br>Ben met Bariando, dat is dirty lit rrraaa <br>Main bitch out your league too, ah <br>Side bitch out of your league too, ah <br>Yah yah yah yah <br>Als iemand met je praat dan zet ik drama drama <br>Breng die shit terug net als karma, yeah <br>Ik ga je niet bevelen voor een Whine and Kotch <br>Want ik ben in love met jou back it up <br>En ik ben niet het type die met dingen rusht, maar ik weet niet anders zou <br>Moeten doen voor een girl als jou <br>Ben een real badman en ik ben real met jou <br>Kan niet kill met jou, ik zet die dame want ik speel never toneel met jou again yeah <br><br>Ya ya <br>Ik heb het over voor jou meisje <br>Ik wil die 25 to life <br>Ik ben je ride or die, oh I <br>Ik heb het over voor jou, yeah <br>Ik heb het over voor yeah yeah yeah <br>Ik heb het over voor jou <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Ik het over voor ik heb het over voor ik heb het over voor jou <br><br>Ik voel m'n baby als een diva, rwina <br>En we kunnen wel vecinas, als ze skeemen <br>Want m'n baby heeft een nina <br>Ik laat d'r moane net als Lisa, hey <br>We zijn hetzelfde <br>Schatje ik negeer je niet, ik zag niet dat je belde <br>Kom ik in die Merrie zet ik heel je dak op stelten skrr skrr skrrrr <br>Kijk voor jou is er geen drama <br>Ikke ben geen shooter maar voor jou boss ik die Bala's <br>Jij bent niet eens matta maar z'n chain wel Balenciaga <br>Geen masha rabi maar dan ben ik in Mufasa yeah, yeah <br><br>Ya ya <br>Ik heb het over voor jou meisje <br>Ik wil die 25 to life <br>Ik ben je ride or die, oh I <br>Ik heb het over voor jou, yeah <br>Ik heb het over voor yeah yeah yeah <br>Ik heb het over voor jou <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Ik het over voor ik heb het over voor ik heb het over voor jou <br><br>Ik voel m'n baby als een diva, rwina <br>En we kunnen wel vecinas, als ze skeemen <br>Want m'n baby heeft een nina <br>Ik laat d'r moane net als Lisa, hey]]></content><category term="Sfb" label="Sfb"/><category term="25 To Life (Feat. Jayh)" label="25 To Life (Feat. Jayh)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Heethoofd/</id><title>Sfb - Heethoofd - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:17:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:17:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Heethoofd/" title="Sfb - Heethoofd - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ah, ik ben een heethoofd <br>Touchdown in Holanda, richting Credo <br>Ik blow een reggae, blow een racket, same sane low <br>De social media verkneedt de waarheid als Play Doh <br>So so so don't play though <br>'Kheb m'n team dus we bangen, net Diego <br>Costa, kan me vinden net als Nemo <br>Ah, zeg me waarom doe je emo <br><br>Ik ben een heet hoofd <br>Zoek die millie maar je zet het in een doos <br>Ik ben een heet hoofd <br>Als die mannen willen zitten aan m'n dough <br>Ik ben een heethoofd <br>Jullie mannen willen ruzie met mij, nee <br>Heet hoofd <br>Real niggas leven tot de dood <br><br>Ik ben met Bali, in de jarie ay, in de jarie ay, in de jarie well <br>Ze vragen wie is je connect Ik zeg z'n naam niet, ik zeg z'n naam niet, ik zeg z'n naam niet <br>Want in detentie, hier is het niet fancy dom <br>Geen stroom, maar alsnog bellen we handsfree <br>Die assie bracht me naar een andere dimensie <br>In mijn defensie, ben ik net als Kensie <br>Dat is no face, no case, not a hansie <br>De recherche plus de rechter en een whamsie <br>Dat ze nada op me hebben en dat zie je <br>Want ik deed 77 nachten op m'n knieen <br>Dat is vragen om vergiffenis <br>Omdat het bikkel is <br>Boy dit is ridiculous <br>Hoe dit ontwikkelt is <br>En hoe de media veranderd in een circus is <br>Maar dat boeit me niet, zeg me hoe m'n nichtje is, want <br><br>Ik ben een heet hoofd <br>Zoek die millie maar je zet het in een doos <br>Ik ben een heet hoofd <br>Als die mannen willen zitten aan m'n dough <br>Ik ben een heethoofd <br>Jullie mannen willen ruzie met mij, nee <br>Heet hoofd <br>Real niggas leven tot de dood God, dom <br><br>Nigga was a rich man <br>Fully lobie, wil my money, would you love her who I am <br>See I just want all the money in the world and I spend it on my fam <br>En m'n whip <br>Ik was haar tinie aan het turnen daar in Boma <br>Zelfs in Suriname was een nigga aan het stunnen <br>Wie gaat voor je strijden broertje, wie gaat je iets gunnen <br>Money switchen als een knop bij het horen van die nullen, dom <br>Murda <br>Real niggas aan het stuurBeen through hell, maar nu ben ik terug met vuur <br>Chop chop man, tell a wasteman move <br>If a man's talk shit, come step in my sh <br><br>Ik ben een heet hoofd <br>Zoek die millie maar je zet het in een doos <br>Ik ben een heet hoofd <br>Als die mannen willen zitten aan m'n dough <br>Ik ben een heethoofd <br>Jullie mannen willen ruzie met mij, nee <br>Heethoofd <br>Real niggas leven tot de dood <br><br>Ben in de jarie, ik ben met whop whop <br>Ik heb nachtmerries dat ik nooit meer zit in drop top <br>Vandaag op m'n knieen, gister was ik nog van God los <br>Free al m'n niggas uit de jarie, hier gaat een bom los <br>Ben in de jarie, ik ben met whop whop <br>Ik heb nachtmerries dat ik nooit meer zit in drop top <br>Vandaag op m'n knieen, gister was ik nog van God los <br>Free al m'n niggas uit de jarie, hier gaat een bom los]]></content><category term="Sfb" label="Sfb"/><category term="Heethoofd" label="Heethoofd"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Badman_Flex_Feat_Jonna_Fraser/</id><title>Sfb - Badman Flex (Feat. Jonna Fraser) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:17:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:17:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Badman_Flex_Feat_Jonna_Fraser/" title="Sfb - Badman Flex (Feat. Jonna Fraser) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Badman <br>Uno, two, tres <br>What you sayyyy <br><br>Kijk goed naar die badman flex en <br>Ik laat je zien hoe een badman flext, ohyeah <br>Luister goed naar wat je mama zegt en <br>Zet het op slot en ga daarna weg <br>Zet die kilo's op m'n goddamn chest en <br>Daarom liep ze voor die badman seks ennuh <br>Ik kan het slaan, maar ga daarna weg, oh <br>'k Laat je zien hoe een badman flext <br><br>Ik kom binnen met een badman stack <br>Je kan het zien aan mijn badman dress <br>Ben nooit thuis, ik ben vaker weg <br>Ik ben vaak met Emms <br>Los van dat, we turnen op een donderdag <br>En we geven volle gas, precies wanneer je onderschat <br>Boekingen vier koppen strak, badman scotten dat <br>Toen ik aan het winnen was, wist ik dat het schokkend was <br>Mijn hele team is zakelijker dan stropdassen <br>Ik ga d'r op in wanneer je zegt dat ik moet oppassen <br>Badman ting yeah, money I am heat <br>Ik heb 'm in z'n sport, dat is high speed what you say <br><br>Kijk goed naar die badman flex en <br>Ik laat je zien hoe een badman flext, ohyeah <br>Luister goed naar wat je mama zegt en <br>Zet het op slot en ga daarna weg <br>Zet die kilo's op m'n goddamn chest en <br>Daarom liep ze voor die badman seks ennuh <br>Ik kan het slaan, maar ga daarna weg, ey <br>'k Laat je zien hoe een badman flext <br><br>Aye, and like honestly, why these pengs wanna talk to me <br>No liquor man, can't walk with me no, they can't walk with me <br>PTO, peng tings only, badman whip and a badman Roley <br>He know me, maar ik hou die shit lowkey <br>Badguy, laat me voelen net Tony <br>Yo G, why you wanna blow me <br>Why you wanna hate, you lonely <br>Ik was aan het shooten in the gym, net als Kobe <br>Die Roley is m'n trophy, vandaar dat ik show, dat is logisch <br>Zie me op the block, maar ik pose niet <br>Laat me je vertellen hoe een badman flext <br>Badman ting, money die springt <br>Dus ik gooi die gowtu op m'n goddman chest what you say <br><br>Kijk goed naar die badman flex en <br>Ik laat je zien hoe een badman flext, ohyeah <br>Luister goed naar wat je mama zegt en <br>Zet het op slot en ga daarna weg <br>Zet die kilo's op m'n goddamn chest en <br>Daarom liep ze voor die badman seks ennuh <br>Ik kan het slaan, maar ga daarna weg, oh <br>'k Laat je zien hoe een badman flext <br><br>Kijk goed naar die badman flex en <br>Ik laat je zien hoe een badman flext, yeah <br>Luister goed naar wat je mama zegt en <br>Zet het op slot en ga daarna weg <br>Zet die kilo's op m'n goddamn chest en <br>Daarom liep ze voor die badman seks ennuh <br>Ik kan het slaan, maar ga daarna weg <br>Ik laat je zien hoe een badman flext <br><br>Kijk, buyaka buyaka, dit is 619 <br>No little man, don't waste my time <br>No little man, can't block my shine <br>Yeah ya ya ya ya, put the ting on rewind <br>Kijk, buyaka buyaka, dit is 619 <br>No little man, don't waste my time <br>No little man, can't block my shine <br>Yeah ya ya ya ya, put the ting on rewind <br><br>I make the hits, not the public <br>I tell the DJ what to play <br>Understand]]></content><category term="Sfb" label="Sfb"/><category term="Badman Flex (Feat. Jonna Fraser)" label="Badman Flex (Feat. Jonna Fraser)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Dem_Say/</id><title>Sfb - Dem Say - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:17:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:17:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Dem_Say/" title="Sfb - Dem Say - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Aye <br><br>Ik neem m'n gang mee <br>Overal waar ik ga, neem ik m'n gang mee <br>Praten karaat, nou dan voel ik me een sensai <br>Ik ben een baas, never listen to what dem say <br>Nee, nee nee nee <br>Zetten herra op die MP <br>Kijk hoe ik sjaaf door de buurt net als MJ <br>I got the club goin' up on a Wednesday <br>Ik ben een baas, never listen to what dem say <br>Nee, nee nee nee <br><br>Ze zegt ze wil smooth criminal <br>Zij weet ik ben probleem <br>Smooth criminal <br>Ah yeah, yeah <br>Ze wil een smooth criminal <br>Criminal, yeah <br>Ze wil een smooth criminal <br>Zij weet ik ben probleem <br><br>Ik neem m'n gang mee <br>Overal waar ik ga neem ik m'n gang mee <br>Stacks in m'n billy jean, voel me MJ <br>Voorbij de rij ik wil niks weten van een entree <br>Nee nee nee nee <br>What a girl wants and needs <br>A rude boy like me <br>Shawty roll up my weed <br> boy ganji <br><br>Ik neem m'n gang mee <br>Overal waar ik ga, neem ik m'n gang mee <br>Praten karaat, nou dan voel ik me een sensai <br>Ik ben een baas, never listen to what dem say <br>Nee, nee nee nee <br>Zetten herra op die MP <br>Kijk hoe ik sjaaf door de buurt net als MJ <br>I got the club goin' up on a Wednesday <br>Ik ben een baas, never listen to what dem say <br>Nee, nee nee nee <br><br>Dem say ik geef je schande, maar dat is nog never waar <br>Dat ik op je verander zit niet in m'n DNA <br>Maar skippen voor een ander, nee dat vindt ze toch niet waard <br>Zeg me waar vind ze een guy nog zo goed, echt zo bad <br><br>Ze zegt ze wil een smooth criminal <br>Zij weet ik ben probleem <br>Smooth criminal <br>Ah yeah, yeah <br>Ze wil een smooth criminal <br>Criminal yeah <br>Ze wil een smooth criminal <br>Zij weet ik ben probleem <br><br>Dem say me a badman <br>Ik pull up in je club met m'n gunman <br>Bossen shots op je body, net als Popcaan <br>Laat d'r in een villa, zovan wagwhan <br>Ik ben een smooth criminal <br>Ik weet dat jij dat wil <br>Ben niet met die waka eh <br>Mannen willen proppen, maar ze proppen niks <br>Beter kan je stoppen, want m'n mannen ja die toppen niet <br><br>Badder than <br>I know she badder than bad <br>Badder than <br>I know she badder than bad <br>Badder than <br>I know she badder than bad <br>Badder than <br>I know she badder than bad <br><br>The block is hot hot <br>Summertime komen wij in die droptop <br>Money talks, zeg een wasteman shut up <br>Shawty alert, dus ik neem op op <br>Wagwhan shawty, you know my style <br>Balmain jeans en een beetje geld <br>Jouw ex boytje die faked Chanel <br>En ik buy alles wat je wil, my girl]]></content><category term="Sfb" label="Sfb"/><category term="Dem Say" label="Dem Say"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Switch_Sides_Feat_Jonna_Fraser/</id><title>Sfb - Switch Sides (Feat. Jonna Fraser) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:17:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:17:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Switch_Sides_Feat_Jonna_Fraser/" title="Sfb - Switch Sides (Feat. Jonna Fraser) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ik krijg nu juist zin <br>Shit wordt pas echt als je uitblinkt <br>Shinen, that, shine that, aye <br>Never switch on my friends <br>So why you wanna switch sides <br>Alleen real niggas here on this side <br>No lie, no lie, no lie, no lie <br>No plei, no plei, no plei, ayahh <br><br>Hou het altijd real, ik switch sowieso niet <br>Snitch on me verwacht ik sowieso niet <br>Delen en verdelen doen we sowieso wel <br>Is er iets wil ik dat je sowieso belt <br><br>So why you wanna switch <br>Gaat die cam aan, zeg me, why you wanna diss <br>En als ik reageer, nou dan maak ik niggas lit <br>Laatste keer dat die mannen me gebruiken als een lift <br>Nu zit ik in die Merrie en ik zet die bitch op sport, ay <br>Sta voor je deur en ik maak je chick, horse <br>We zien die gang weer rappen, net als mij, we moeten door <br>Ik zweer voor mijn positie doen die mannen daar een moord <br>Wist je nog dat ze claimden dat ik dood was <br>Of in Su toen Tamara niet beloofd was <br>Je switcht sides, jij dacht zeker dat ik boos was <br>Blij dat je liet zien wie echt m'n bro was <br><br>Ik krijg nu juist zin <br>Shit wordt pas echt als je uitblinkt <br>Shinen, that, shine that, aye <br>Never switch on my friends <br>So why you wanna switch sides <br>Alleen real niggas here on this side <br>No lie, no lie, no lie, no lie <br>No plei, no plei, no plei, ayahh <br><br>Hou het altijd real ik switch sowieso niet <br>Snitch on me verwacht ik sowieso niet <br>Delen en verdelen doe ik sowieso wel <br>Ligt er iets op je hart wil ik dat je mij belt <br><br>So why you wanna switch <br>Strijden voor je niggers dat is sowieso verplicht <br>Ik gaf je de keys van m'n auto en m'n crib <br>En behalve mijn bitch had je alles in bezit <br>Nu zit ik in die Range en ik zet die bitch op sport, aye <br>Blowen money dom, yeah we doen het voor de fun <br>M'n zakken die zijn bom, yeah ik kijk niet achterom <br>Weer een pokoe in de charts dus ik ga weer double up <br>Yes ik catch die bullet <br>Maar catch jij ook die bullet <br>We weten niet precies wat goed is <br>Maar ik heb love voor al m'n broeders, one love yay <br><br>Ik krijg nu juist zin <br>Shit wordt pas echt als je uitblinkt <br>Shinen, that, shine that, aye <br>Never switch on my friends <br>So why you wanna switch sides <br>Alleen real niggas here on this side <br>No lie, no lie, no lie, no lie <br>No plei, no plei, no plei, ayahh <br><br>So why you wanna switch <br>Strijden voor je niggers dat is sowieso verplicht <br>Pussy niggers switchen lanes sneller dan een bitch <br>Gooi m'n vingers in een 7, het verandert in een glitch <br>Nu zit ik in die Merrie, achterin ik word chauffeur <br>Money voor de Benz maar je wil niet dat ik scheur <br>Weer een pokoe in de charts dus ik ga weer double up <br>Ik zweer ik doe dit voor de gang <br>De rit is lang dus buckle up <br><br>Ik krijg nu juist zin <br>Shit wordt pas echt als je uitblinkt <br>Shinen, that, shine that, aye <br>Never switch on my friends <br>So why you wanna switch sides <br>Alleen real niggas here on this side <br>No lie, no lie, no lie, no lie <br>No plei, no plei, no plei, ayahh <br><br>Hou het altijd real, ik switch sowieso niet <br>Snitch on me verwacht ik sowieso niet <br>Delen en verdelen doen we sowieso wel <br>Is er iets wil ik dat je sowieso belt <br>Hou het altijd real ik switch sowieso niet <br>Snitch on me verwacht ik sowieso niet <br>Delen en verdelen doe ik sowieso wel <br>Ligt er iets op je hart wil ik dat je mij belt <br>Hou het altijd real, ik switch sowieso niet <br>Snitch on me verwacht ik sowieso niet <br>Delen en verdelen doen we sowieso wel <br>Is er iets wil ik dat je sowieso belt <br>Hou het altijd real ik switch sowieso niet <br>Snitch on me verwacht ik sowieso niet <br>Delen en verdelen doe ik sowieso wel <br>Ligt er iets op je hart wil ik dat je mij belt]]></content><category term="Sfb" label="Sfb"/><category term="Switch Sides (Feat. Jonna Fraser)" label="Switch Sides (Feat. Jonna Fraser)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/On_Lock/</id><title>Sfb - On Lock - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:17:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:17:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/On_Lock/" title="Sfb - On Lock - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah yeah ye yeah <br>Nobody haffi know <br>Yeah ai <br><br>Nobody haffi know, say we're gon' fuck <br>Ik heb die, ik heb die pussy on lock <br>Ik ga je niet controllen, ik ben niet op dat <br>Ik heb die, ik heb die pussy on lock <br>Als je met me bent, zet je tellie op lock <br>Ey, zet je tellie op lock <br>Als ik met je ben, nobody haffi know <br>Yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah <br><br>Laat me zien wat je waard ben <br>Diamonds op m'n Cartier ik kan niet slapen <br>Wat je wil je kan het krijgen, je moet vragen <br>En niet vergeten, je moet rennen tot je daar bent <br>Ik zie die mannen zijn on mijn thing <br>Ik neem, polshoogte maar geen Breitling <br>Ze doen never zo excited als ze mij zien <br>Kan het voelen aan je aura je bent Pricey <br><br>Oh baby whagwan <br>Kom je in m'n voorin zit je shotgun <br>Wat is die volgende stap net Jawson <br>Je nieuwe vriendje, nee hij is niet awesome, dus neem afstand <br>Why you wanna leave me <br>Big man diamonds vind je pretty <br>Plus ik ben blem, maar ik drink niet <br>Kom slow whine upon that thingy <br><br>Nobody haffi know, say we're gon' fuck <br>Ik heb die, ik heb die pussy on lock <br>Ik ga je niet controllen, ik ben niet op dat <br>Ik heb die, ik heb die pussy on lock <br>Als je met me bent, zet je tellie op lock <br>Ey, zet je tellie op lock <br>Als ik met je ben, nobody haffi know <br>Yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah <br><br>Ik heb die pussy on lock, net een kluis <br>Ik heb de sleutel van je, dat is m'n thuis <br>Ik weet niet als ik pull up in die foreign is het Duits <br>En stiekem wil je haten, al m'n niggers hebben buit <br>En mannen schreeuwen cheese, bij het flitsen van m'n ice <br>Je weet ik ben een dief, maar voor jou doe ik die grind <br>Sit down pon mi cocky en ik show je more life <br>De manier hoe je draait, zeg een nigga alright <br><br>Girl I need you <br>I need you to whine up on me <br>I need you to whine up on me <br>I need you to whine up on me <br>Girl I need you <br>I need you to whine up on me <br>I need you to whine up on me <br>I need you to whine up on me <br><br>Nobody haffi know, say we're gon' fuck <br>Ik heb die, ik heb die pussy on lock <br>Ik ga je niet controllen, ik ben niet op dat <br>Ik heb die, ik heb die pussy on lock <br>Als je met me bent, zet je tellie op lock <br>Ey, zet je tellie op lock <br>Als ik met je ben, nobody haffi know <br>Yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah]]></content><category term="Sfb" label="Sfb"/><category term="On Lock" label="On Lock"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Dont_You_Know/</id><title>Sfb - Don`t You Know - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:17:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:17:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Dont_You_Know/" title="Sfb - Don`t You Know - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ey, ey, yeah yeah <br>Don't you know <br>Don't you know <br>Don't you know <br><br>We badder than dey, oh don't you know <br>Dit is voor m'n magga's en ook voor de rovers <br>We badder than dey, oh don't you know <br>Rij een CLA, want ik ben een chauffeur <br>We better than they, oh don't you know <br>Ja ik sta klaar want ik ben een soldier <br>We badder than dey, oh don't you know <br>Oh yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah <br><br>Oh don't you know <br>We better than they, oh did you not <br>Her mommy is in love met a criminal <br>Rij een CLA, want ik ben een chauffeur <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Zeg me ben je klaar, want dan pull ik over <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah <br>En ik weet d'r is gevaar, maar ik ben een soldier <br>Ik hoor je bent nu klaar, is die shit al over <br>Overleefd in Santo Boma tussen alle cobras <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah <br><br>Oh, don't you know <br>Original ganja farmer, oh <br>Ik hoor je chick is magga, silly city oh <br>Zometeen dan ben ik daar, dan pull ik over <br>En dan gaan ze weer van hug me, hug me <br>Kiss me, squeeze me <br>''First they love me, now they wanna diss me'' <br>Ik kan niet focken met een wasteman <br>En free m'n focking nigga Jason <br><br>We badder than dey, oh don't you know <br>Dit is voor m'n magga's en ook voor de rovers <br>We badder than dey, oh don't you know <br>Rij een CLA, want ik ben een chauffeur <br>We badder than dey, oh don't you know <br>Ja ik sta klaar want ik ben een soldier <br>We badder than dey, oh don't you know <br>Oh yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah <br><br>Oh don't you know <br>Oh don't you know <br>Kijk naar m'n chains <br>Fully gold <br>Geef mij die bae <br>Ben niet meer broke <br>Of Vietnamees, nig' wanna know <br>Big man ja, ik ben een big man <br>Niet onderschatten als ik effe sliep want <br>Ik ga niet mengen, dus ik hou m'n distance <br>Ze willen leunen, maar ik ben geen kickstart <br><br>En als ik pull up in je endz <br>Dan ben ik met m'n huiswerk als ik pull up in die Benz <br>We better than them <br>Maar dat is allang bekend <br>Club shutdown and again and again Shutdown <br>Boss wan picca, show love aan een fan <br>Tatts op m'n arm, show love aan m'n gang <br>One man alone can't bleed for the fam What <br>One man alone can't bleed for the fam <br><br>We badder than dey, oh don't you know <br>Dit is voor m'n magga's en ook voor de rovers <br>We badder than dey, oh don't you know <br>Rij een CLA, want ik ben een chauffeur <br>We badder than dey, oh don't you know <br>Ja ik sta klaar want ik ben een soldier <br>We badder than dey, oh don't you know <br>Oh yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah]]></content><category term="Sfb" label="Sfb"/><category term="Don`t You Know" label="Don`t You Know"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Pon_Road_Feat_Sevn_Alias/</id><title>Sfb - Pon Road (Feat. Sevn Alias) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:17:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:17:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Pon_Road_Feat_Sevn_Alias/" title="Sfb - Pon Road (Feat. Sevn Alias) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Make money money, make money money money <br>Ik ga niet meer naar school <br>Another Badman tune, like yeah <br>Money money money like yeah, money money money yeah <br>Like yesss, God bless <br>Aye, aye, aye <br><br>You like, pon road <br>Ik pak weer een show <br>Ik ga niet meer naar school <br>Me make money pon road <br>Ze weten ik glow <br>Meer money meer blessings fo' sho' <br>Ik ga niet meer naar school <br>Me make money pon road <br><br>Me make money pon road, oh yeah <br>Ik heb die dingen op m'n schoot, yeah <br>Ik voelde me een lange tijd niet veilig <br>Al die chawa's met de ballen op schoot <br>En ik play anytime <br>We can get loose on a op, loose on a up <br>Run up get loose on a op <br>I don't like the way they be looking at us <br>24 7 aan het rennen voor die puntjes, stunten <br>Alias, Picasso ben een kunstenaar <br>Spitser dan Huntelaar <br>Op zoek naar die mil, hoop dat die wens ooit in vervulling gaat <br>Want ik ga niet meer naar school <br>Als het mij niet lukt met rap, ren ik in de trap <br>Met die packs en deal ik coke, yeah <br>Mijn waggie wil ik S splash <br>Money voor de stress, ik heb dingen aan m'n hoofd, yeah <br>Ben al dagen op die deck <br>M'n zorgen zijn nog niet weg <br>Dus vandaag kom ik niet home, yeah <br>Ik ben op de grind totdat ik dood ben, hey <br><br>You like, pon road <br>Ik pak weer een show <br>Ik ga niet meer naar school <br>Me make money pon road <br>Ze weten ik glow <br>Meer money meer blessings fo' sho' <br>Ik ga niet meer naar school <br>Me make money pon road <br><br>Je moet niet zitten aan me gun <br>wha pow chu chu <br>You gon' die <br>Eerste schot en het is raak <br>Laat het spugen net een draak <br>Zeg me doe je djoe djoe <br>White girls call it voodoo, ah aye <br>On road met m'n mensen, no more retention <br>Tell 'em, liquor boy stop <br>Zim zimma, who got the keys to the Bimma <br>Tell 'em like, who am I <br>Ik ben fly yeah, yeah, yeah <br>I make money 'pon road met hits, yeah <br>Ik heb een car om my wrist, yeah <br>Nigga, they don't make a starboy like this yeah <br>Diamonds on my wrist yeah <br>And never never try catch my fist <br><br>You like, pon road <br>Ik pak weer een show <br>Ik ga niet meer naar school <br>E make money pon road <br>Ze weet dat ik blow <br>Meer money meer blessings fo' sho' <br>Ik ga niet meer naar school <br>Me make money pon road, oh yeah <br><br>Make money, money <br>Make money, money <br>Ik ga niet meer naar school <br>Me want take money, money <br>Take money, money, money <br>Pon road <br>Make money, money <br>Make money, money <br>Ik ga niet meer naar school <br>Me want take money, money <br>Take money, money, money]]></content><category term="Sfb" label="Sfb"/><category term="Pon Road (Feat. Sevn Alias)" label="Pon Road (Feat. Sevn Alias)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Way_It_Goes/</id><title>Sfb - Way It Goes - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:17:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:17:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Way_It_Goes/" title="Sfb - Way It Goes - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Zie de een die doet drugs en die leeft <br>En de ander die rooft en die neemt <br>Zie de dagen gaan snel maar nog steeds <br>That's the way it goes <br>Uno, two, tres, four <br>Tche de de de <br>Tche de de de <br>Ta da da, ta ga da, da da da <br>Tche de de de <br>Tche de de de <br>Ta da da, ta ga da, da da da <br>Tche de de de <br>Tche de de de <br>Ta da da, ta ga da, da da da <br>That's the way it goes <br>Yeah <br><br>Je voelt je bom, bom, bom <br>Ik heb een bom, bom, bom, in m'n zak <br>If I do you like bom, bom, bom <br>Zie die mannen praten maar komen niet rond, rond, rond <br>Kan niet chillen, ben niet dom, dom, dom, ah <br>Al mijn niggas zijn aan <br>Ik kan je mannen niet verstaan <br>Tche de de de <br>Tche de de de <br>Ta da da da, ta da da da <br>Fully Nike no Adidas <br>Ik ben een boef jij mijn habiba <br>Late night dit is stamina <br>Zij lit, dit is la vida <br>Ga niet haten dit is mijn vida <br>Ik kan niet speaken voor een whine zina, nee <br>Tche de de de <br>Tche de de de <br>Ta da da, ta ga da, da da da <br><br>Zie de een die doet drugs en die leeft <br>En de ander die rooft en die neemt <br>Zie de dagen gaan snel maar nog steeds <br>That's the way it goes <br>Uno, two, tres, four <br>Tche de de de <br>Tche de de de <br>Ta da da, ta ga da, da da da <br>Tche de de de <br>Tche de de de <br>Ta da da, ta ga da, da da da <br>Tche de de de <br>Tche de de de <br>Ta da da, ta ga da, da da da <br>That's the way it goes <br>Yeah <br><br>Real nigga till I DIE <br>Popo wil me stoppen ik heb geen ID ID <br>Elke club is het VIP <br>Die bom die je trekt is een dynamiet boem <br>Call the shots and get it done <br>En al mijn niggas die zijn on <br>Tche de de de <br>Tche de de de <br>Ta ta da da, ta ta da da <br><br>Al die mannen kijken naar m'n wrist <br>Blijf daar, 'kheb het on my hip <br>Bad bitch en ze drived mijn whip <br>Never ever dat ze op mij switched <br>Mist Dit is gang business <br>You never ever met een boy like this <br>Tche de de de <br>Tche de de de <br>Ta da da, ta ga da, da da da <br><br>Zie de een die doet drugs en die leeft <br>En de ander die rooft en die neemt <br>Zie de dagen gaan snel maar nog steeds <br>That's the way it goes <br>Uno, two, tres, four <br>Tche de de de <br>Tche de de de <br>Ta da da, ta ga da, da da da <br>Tche de de de <br>Tche de de de <br>Ta da da, ta ga da, da da da <br>Tche de de de <br>Tche de de de <br>Ta da da, ta ga da, da da da <br>That's the way it goes <br>Yeah <br><br>Aba <br>Jaisah <br>Aba <br>Ke ke ke ke ke ke <br>Tche de de <br>Pa da da da, ta da da <br>That's the way it goes, baby <br>Pa pa pa pa rah]]></content><category term="Sfb" label="Sfb"/><category term="Way It Goes" label="Way It Goes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Santa_Boma/</id><title>Sfb - Santa Boma - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:17:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:17:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Santa_Boma/" title="Sfb - Santa Boma - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ha ha ha ha ha <br><br>Aye <br>Santa Boma, Santa Boma woelleh <br>Santa Boma, Santa Boma woelleh, aye <br>Ik hoor de boys zijn released, ah <br>Dat is the word on the streets, aye <br>Ik heb zoveel enemies, aye <br>Pop een balla of ik squeeze, aye <br>Santa Boma, Santa Boma woelleh <br>Santa Boma, Santa Boma woelleh, aye <br>Ik hoor de boys zijn released, ah <br>Dat is the word on the streets, aye <br>Ik heb zoveel enemies, aye <br>Beter doen die mannen iets, aye <br><br>Santa Boma, ik wilde alleen maar die komma's dom <br>Hayek, vonnis <br>Ik heb die ding overwonnen <br>Eerste weken in BE, en daarna dagje in Paris <br>Was op een focking shopping spree <br>Blow een rack, Givenchy dom <br>Ik zweer ze willen me stressen <br>Ik zweer ze willen me stressen <br>Maar dat is m'n accuratesse <br>M'n money zwart en geel net als Vitesse <br>Ik kan niet stressen om de media <br>Want al m'n mannen die bewegen ja <br>Was in die Rolls Royce, das een big toy, samen met m'n brada Elia <br><br>Santa Boma, Santa Boma woelleh <br>Santa Boma, Santa Boma woelleh, aye <br>Ik hoor de boys zijn released, ah <br>Dat is the word on the streets, aye <br>Ik heb zoveel enemies, aye <br>Pop een balla of ik squeeze, aye <br>Santa Boma, Santa Boma woelleh <br>Santa Boma, Santa Boma woelleh, aye <br>Ik hoor de boys zijn released, ah <br>Dat is the word on the streets, aye <br>Ik heb zoveel enemies, aye <br>Beter doen die mannen iets, aye <br><br>Young, Simba, maar nu ben ik als Mufasa <br>Ja nu ben ik als Matada <br>Zo noemt me Schuurman door die Katja <br>He, wow, laat me switchen van die flow dom <br>Laat me switchen van die lane dom <br>Schakel over naar die cope <br>Let me pull over the stick <br>Let it hit, let it hit <br>Schakel over naar m'n bitch <br>Zeg me keep it real and baby never switch <br>They just did it thick <br>Je bae just op me dick <br>Young Bull, baby <br>What it do, baby <br><br>Santa Boma, Santa Boma woelleh <br>Santa Boma, Santa Boma woelleh, aye <br>Ik hoor de boys zijn released, ah <br>Dat is the word on the streets, aye <br>Ik heb zoveel enemies, aye <br>Pop een balla of ik squeeze, aye <br>Santa Boma, Santa Boma woelleh <br>Santa Boma, Santa Boma woelleh, aye <br>Ik hoor de boys zijn released, ah <br>Dat is the word on the streets, aye <br>Ik heb zoveel enemies, aye <br>Beter doen die mannen iets, aye <br><br>Beter doen die mannen, uh <br>Beter doen de mannen iets, aye <br>Ik rij niet in een fucking lease, nee <br>Al m'n niggas zijn op cheese, aye <br>Ik draai me L in 7 <br>Ik ging door hell voor een zegen <br>Ik had niet voorspelt en dat weet je <br>Ik blow afoe daarom speel ik die hele, hele <br>Al m'n niggas zijn next, eh <br>Die domme jongens zijn back, eh <br>En als ik kom met die Lil Uzi, kra, why your friends are dead <br>Ik doe m'n goddamn best <br>Dit is die badman flex <br>Ik gooi die diamonds om m'n nek <br>Ik gooi die diamonds om m'n nek <br><br>Ha ha ha ha ha]]></content><category term="Sfb" label="Sfb"/><category term="Santa Boma" label="Santa Boma"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Hope__Pray_Feat_Lijpe__Boef/</id><title>Sfb - Hope & Pray (Feat. Lijpe & Boef) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:17:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:17:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sfb/Hope__Pray_Feat_Lijpe__Boef/" title="Sfb - Hope & Pray (Feat. Lijpe & Boef) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Aye hey hey yeahyeahyeahyeah, ay <br><br>Voor m'n mannetjes in HVB <br>Hope and pray, hope and pray <br>Ga op m'n knieen, zodat 'ie me vergeeft <br>Hope and pray, hope and pray <br>En ookal is het best zwaar, ik deed <br>Hope and pray, yeah <br>En mama straks ben ik daar, no lay <br>Hope and pray, hope and pray <br><br>Locked up <br>They won't let me out <br>Wazig <br>They won't let me out <br>Want ik wil niet met jou praten <br>They won't let me out <br>No, they won't let me out <br><br>Ay, m'n advocaat niet op bezoek geweest, vandaag heb ik een droeve geest <br>Ik ontwijk stress als ik m'n boeken lees <br>Ik ontwijk stress als ik 't inhaleer <br>En daar had ik die AK's maar had geen geweer <br>Want praat ik Santa Boma, ben ik wel geleerd <br>Lesgeld betaald vraag wat ik studeer, dom <br>Money niet compleet dan ga ik flink tekeer, fom <br>Loop niet met een niffi als ik opereer, long <br>Waggie voor de zomer wordt een open dak <br>Verhuis ik naar het Gooi, dan wordt het open gras <br>Zeg me wie zou me vervangen als het nodig was <br>Of als het nodig is maar dat zal never nodig zijn <br>Is er een muur dan help ik al mijn niggers overeind <br>Ik breng al m'n fucking brakka's naar de stomerij <br>Heb een collectie even duur als waar je nu in rijdt, brah <br><br>Voor m'n mannetjes in HVB <br>Voor m'n mannetjes in HVB <br>Hope and pray, hope and pray <br>Ga op m'n knieen, zodat 'ie me vergeeft <br>Hope and pray, hope and pray <br>En ookal is het best zwaar, ik deed <br>Hope and pray, yeah <br>En mama straks ben ik daar, no lay <br>Hope and pray, hope and pray <br><br>M'n boys in Duitsland zitten zo lang <br>M'n boy in Moro zit al zo lang <br>M'n boys in Duitsland zitten zo lang <br>M'n boy in Moro zit al zo lang <br>Maar op een dag ben je terug, ik hoop dan <br>Dat je niet meer terug hoeft, broertje leer d'r ook van <br>Want je moeder is bezorgd en ze heeft een hoop angst <br>Soms kijkt ze uit het raam en ze denkt je loopt langs <br>En tuurlijk ik begrijp je want je zoekt gewoon sjans <br>God heeft een groot plan, hou je effe groot dan komt <br>Alles goed, je kan geen kant op <br>Dus ben je blij met wat boeken en een hasj block <br>Loterij, heel dit leven is een kraslot <br>En er zijn slangen in je zaak, broertje pas op <br>Voor die anonieme tip zet je eigen kring <br>En ze gaan zehma omi vragen als je vast komt <br>En zeg ze nu ben je verstandig want je was dom <br>Al moet je morgen weer gaan jagen met een tas om <br>Werk slim en doe die flikkers maar de das om <br>Want je was anders als dit allemaal gepast kon <br>Zo zie je maar, je weet niet wat er op je pad komt <br>Zou deze avond met je chillen broer, als dat kon <br>Zou heel de avond op je spenden als een patron <br>Voor al m'n jongens daar in HVB <br><br>Voor m'n mannetjes in HVB <br>Hope and pray, hope and pray <br>Ga op m'n knieen, zodat 'ie me vergeeft <br>Hope and pray, hope and pray <br>En ookal is het best zwaar, ik deed <br>Hope and pray, yeah <br>En mama straks ben ik daar, no lay <br>Hope and pray, yeah <br><br>Ze zeggen doekoe praat, maar jij eet niet <br>Wanneer is Koevoet terug, man ik weet niet <br>Ik ben aan het strijden voor m'n lady <br>Jij bent op mij geswitch maar dat geeft niet <br>Want jij bleek een fuckboy, 'kheb je buitengesloten <br>Zit je in een luchtkooi, ben je buitengesloten <br>Ik had ook een Koevoet bij, maar was buiten met Moker <br>Zij zat niet aan de top, dus vraag huis voor die gozer <br>Je hebt gebruikers en kopers, de een is uit op een loper <br>Geld maakt d'r nat, verstop haar buit in de droger <br>Nu betaal je met cash, al maak zes duizendjes over <br>Al die baby's praten poep, moeten luiers verschonen, hah <br>Hou je sterk broer als je je verraden voelt <br>Ookal kom je voor het gerecht als tomatensoep <br>Ik word aangehouden, dat is wat m'n wagen doet <br>Hoe word ik miljonair is wat ik m'n vader vroeg <br>Ik had toen zwaar genoeg, hij zei me je moet slim wezen <br>Ik wou snel geld broer, dus ik ging inbreken <br>Van dat zwart geld broer wou die niks weten <br>Zei hem dat ik werkte, alleen zo kon ik m'n winst delen <br><br>Voor m'n mannetjes in HVB, ay, ay]]></content><category term="Sfb" label="Sfb"/><category term="Hope & Pray (Feat. Lijpe & Boef)" label="Hope & Pray (Feat. Lijpe & Boef)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jean_Deaux/Father_Time/</id><title>Jean Deaux - Father Time - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:18:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:18:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jean_Deaux/Father_Time/" title="Jean Deaux - Father Time - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know what you think about me <br>But I know that you probably don't see <br>How it feels when you're losing your mind <br>And you tell the world you're doing just fine <br>So you think that you really got it all <br>So you think that the world is too small <br>You pass the gates and it's all about the paper chase <br>Tell me why your feelings get involved <br><br>Uh huh, uh huh huh <br>I can feel it now <br>Uh huh, uh huh huh <br>Lift your spirits now <br>Before you hit the ground <br><br>You work my mind <br>With your heart beat just fine <br>You don't even know it yet <br>You ain't even living right <br>I've only met my father twice <br>I think his name is Father Time <br>I think his name is Father Time <br><br>I lost my emotions <br>They say that I'm potent, drinking the potions <br>I love this shit, need a lil more drugs with it <br>I'm back on the papers, inhaling the vapors <br>I'm feeling amazing, my body blazing <br>The fire is glazing, my empire's waiting <br><br>Don't get caught up in the moment <br>Cuz a nigga might push up on it <br>No time, no wait till the morning <br>You know right where you're zoning <br>Said he rolling off the bridge, he don't forget <br>I don't forgive <br>Don't get caught up in the moment <br>Cuz a nigga might push up on it <br>No say over what's important <br>You know right where you're zoning <br>By the time I'm off the bridge, he don't forget <br>I don't forgive <br>He don't forget, I don't forgive <br><br>You work my mind <br>With your heart beat just fine <br>You don't even know it yet <br>You ain't even living right <br>I've only met my father twice <br>I think his name is Father Time <br>I think his name is Father Time <br><br>I've only met my father twice <br>I think his name is Father Time <br>I think his name is Father Time]]></content><category term="Jean Deaux" label="Jean Deaux"/><category term="Father Time" label="Father Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sabrina_Carpenter/Why/</id><title>Sabrina Carpenter - Why - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:19:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:19:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sabrina_Carpenter/Why/" title="Sabrina Carpenter - Why - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You like New York City in the daytime <br>I like New York City in the nighttime <br>You say you like sleeping with the air off <br>I don't, I need it on <br>You like the light coming through the windows <br>I sleep late, so I just keep 'em all closed <br>You ignore the music on the radio <br>I don't, I sing a long <br><br>I don't ask for you to change, baby no no no <br>And you don't ask for me to change <br><br>Tell me how we're not alike <br>But we work so well and we don't even know why <br>Funny how the stars crossed right <br>'Cause we work so well and we don't even know why <br>You can call it fire and ice <br>But we work so well and we don't even know why <br>We don't even know why, no no <br>We don't even know why, no no no <br><br>No no no no <br>We like it in the daytime <br>We like it in the end of time <br>No no no no <br>We like it in the daytime <br>We like it in the end of time <br><br>Cold outside and you're just in a T shirt <br>I have cold blood even in a sweater <br>You start your night sippin' by the Kilo <br>I don't, I know you know <br><br>I don't ask for you to change, baby no no no <br>And you don't ask for me to change <br><br>Tell me how we're not alike <br>But we work so well and we don't even know why <br>Funny how the stars crossed right <br>'Cause we work so well and we don't even know why <br>You can call it fire and ice <br>But we work so well and we don't even know why <br>We don't even know why, no no no no no <br>We don't even know why, no no no <br><br>No no no no <br>We like it in the daytime we don't even know <br>We like it in the end of time we don't even know <br>No no no no <br>We like it in the daytime <br>We don't even know, know, know, know, know <br>We like it in the end of time <br><br>Somehow we end up on the same side <br>And you wouldn't think that we'd be alright <br>Even our eyes are different colors, but we see fine <br>Somehow we end up on the same side up on the same side <br>And you wouldn't think that we'd be alright <br>Think that we'd be alright <br>Even our eyes are different colors, but we see fine <br><br>Oh Tell me how we're not alike <br>But we work so well and we don't even know why <br>'Cause we work so well and we don't even know why, why <br>Funny how the stars crossed right <br>'Cause we work so well and we don't even know why <br>But we don't even know why <br>You can call it fire and ice <br>But we work so well and we don't even know why <br>'Cause we work so well and we don't even know why, why <br>We don't even know why, no no <br>We don't even know why, no no no <br><br>No no no no <br>We like it in the daytime oh <br>We like it in the end of time We don't even know why <br>No no no no <br>We like it in the daytime <br>We like it in the nighttime]]></content><category term="Sabrina Carpenter" label="Sabrina Carpenter"/><category term="Why" label="Why"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fullife/Thinking_About_You/</id><title>Fullife - Thinking About You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:20:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:20:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fullife/Thinking_About_You/" title="Fullife - Thinking About You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Girl you got me crazy <br>I wanna know your name <br>You read my mind like nobody else <br>I want to take you <br>To another place <br>'Cause I'm feeling something I can't explain <br><br>You let me hold you for a night <br>Don't be shy <br>I make you feel like the first time <br>Let me hold you for a night <br>I never let you go <br>I never let you go <br>I was thinking about you, you <br>I was thinking about you, you <br><br>I was thinking about you <br>I was thinking about you <br>I was thinking about you <br>I was thinking about you <br><br>Just want to feel alone <br>All night long <br>And I can see your eyes <br>And the wild you're looking for <br>Don't you wanna know <br><br>You let me hold you for a night <br>Don't be shy <br>I make you feel like the first time <br>Let me hold you for a night <br>I never let you go <br>I never let you go <br>I was thinking about you, you <br>I was thinking about you, you <br><br>I was thinking about you <br>I was thinking about you <br>I was thinking about you <br>I was thinking about you]]></content><category term="Fullife" label="Fullife"/><category term="Thinking About You" label="Thinking About You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dylan_Hyde/Clearly/</id><title>Dylan Hyde - Clearly - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:20:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:20:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dylan_Hyde/Clearly/" title="Dylan Hyde - Clearly - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I ain't asking for much <br>Keep just a little faith in me <br>It ain't easy I know <br>But don't give up on me, yeah <br>You can take this in two directions <br>With me or not <br>Together we're stronger <br>'Cause you're everything I'm not <br><br>I'm a simple man <br>Have simple needs, it's true <br>But you can be complicated <br>But nothing is promised, baby <br>So let me be honest, baby <br><br>I raise my voice <br>So everyone can hear me <br>I love you clearly <br>I love you clearly <br>I raise my hand <br>So everyone can see me <br>I love you clearly <br>I love you clearly <br><br>I will always be faithful <br>You won't be disrespected <br>The darkness can break you <br>But I would never let it <br>Never, never let it <br>No, never, never let it <br>But trust me, I'm ready <br>I'm ready, girl <br><br>I have a simple plan <br>A simple dream and you <br>Yes, you are a part of it <br>So I'll make a promise, baby <br>So we can get started, baby, yeah <br><br>I raise my voice <br>So everyone can hear me <br>So everyone can hear me <br>I love you clearly <br>'Cause I love, I love you <br>I love you clearly <br>'Cause I love, I love you <br>I raise my hand <br>So everyone can see me <br>So everyone can see me yeah <br>I love you clearly <br>'Cause I love, I love you <br>I love you clearly <br>'Cause I love, I love you <br><br>Every angle, every feature <br>In a dress or in a t shirt <br>You're perfect just the way you are <br>But these words don't even capture <br>How I feel or what I'm after <br>I promise, everywhere we are <br><br>I raise my voice <br>So everyone can hear me, oh <br>I love you clearly <br>I love you clearly <br>I love you clearly <br>I love you clearly <br>I raise my hand <br>So everyone can see me <br>So everyone can see me <br>I love you clearly 'cause I love, I love you <br>I love you clearly 'cause I love, I love you <br>Oh yeah]]></content><category term="Dylan Hyde" label="Dylan Hyde"/><category term="Clearly" label="Clearly"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/AC_DC/Shes_Got_The_Jack/</id><title>AC/DC - She`s Got The Jack - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:20:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:20:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/AC_DC/Shes_Got_The_Jack/" title="AC/DC - She`s Got The Jack - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She gave me the Queen <br>She gave me the King <br>She was wheelin' and dealin' <br>Just doin' her thing <br>She was holdin' a pair <br>But I had to try <br>Her Deuce was wild <br>But my Ace was high <br>But how was I to know <br>That she'd been dealt with before <br>Said she'd never had a Full House <br>But I should have known <br>From the tattoo on her left leg <br>And the garter on her right <br>She'd have the card to bring me down <br>If she played it right <br><br>She's got the jack, she's got the jack <br>She's got the jack, she's got the jack <br>She's got the jack, she's got the jack <br>She's got the jack, she's got the jack <br>She's got the jack, jack, jack, jack, jack, jack, jack <br>She's got the jack <br><br>Poker face was her name <br>Poker face was her nature <br>Poker straight was her game <br>If she knew she could get you <br>She played 'em fast <br>And she played 'em hard <br>She could close her eyes <br>And feel every card <br>But how was I to know <br>That she'd been shuffled before <br>Said she'd never had a Royal Flush <br>But I should have known <br>That all the cards were comin' <br>From the bottom of the pack <br>And if I'd known what she was dealin' out <br>I'd have dealt it back <br><br>She's got the jack, she's got the jack <br>She's got the jack, and who knows what else <br>She's got the jack, yeah, yeah <br>She's got the jack, she's got the jack <br>She's got the jack, she's got the jack <br>She's got the jack, jack, jack, jack, jack, jack, jack <br>She's got the jack <br><br>She's got the jack, she's got the jack <br>Ooh, It was a bad deal, Jack <br>She gave me the Jack, hey <br>She's got the Jack, she's got the Jack <br>She's got the Jack, ooh can't you tell <br>She's got the Jack, jack, jack, jack, jack, jack, jack, jack <br>She's got the jack, she's got the Jack <br>She's got the jack, she's got the Jack <br>She's got the jack, you never know <br>She's got the jack, she's got the jack <br>She's got the jack <br>She's got the jack, and it hurts <br>She's got the jack <br>She's got the jack, jack, jack, jack, jack, jack, jack <br>She's got the jack <br>Aaaaaah <br><br>Oooooh <br>Thank you, thank you, thank you people, thank you, thank you <br>I'm glad you like the show, yes, thank you very much folks <br>Goodnight and God bless]]></content><category term="AC/DC" label="AC/DC"/><category term="She`s Got The Jack" label="She`s Got The Jack"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Marianne/</id><title>Tori Amos - Marianne - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:20:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:20:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Marianne/" title="Tori Amos - Marianne - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tuna <br>Rubber <br>A little blubber in my igloo <br>And I knew you pigtails and all <br>Grils when they fall <br>And they said Marianne killed herself <br>And I said not a chance <br>Don't you love the girls ladies babes <br>Old bags who say she was so pretty why <br>Why why why did she crawl down in the old <br>Deep ravine <br><br>C'mon pigtails girls and all those sailors <br>Get your bags and hold down won't you just <br>Hold down cause Ed is watching my every sound <br>I said <br>They're watching my every sound <br><br>The weasel squeaks faster than a seven day week <br>I said Timmy and that purple Monkey <br>Are all down <br>At Bobby's house <br>Making themselves pesters and lesters and jesters an dmy <br>Traitors of kind <br>And I'm just having thoughts of Marianne <br>She could outrun the fastest slug <br>She could <br>Marianne <br>Quickest girl in the frying pan]]></content><category term="Tori Amos" label="Tori Amos"/><category term="Marianne" label="Marianne"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Little_Amsterdam/</id><title>Tori Amos - Little Amsterdam - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:20:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:20:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Little_Amsterdam/" title="Tori Amos - Little Amsterdam - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Little Amsterdam <br>In a southern town <br>Hominy get it on the plate girl <br>Momma keep your head down <br>Momma it wasn't my bullet <br><br>Don't take me back to the RAnge <br>I'm just comin out of the cell in my brain <br>Girl you got to know these days <br>Which side your on <br><br>Mamma got shit <br>She loved a brown man <br>Then she built a bridge in the Sheriff's bed <br>She'd do anyting to save her man <br>You see her olives are cold pressed <br>And her best friend is a sun dress <br>But Momma <br>It wasn't my bullet <br><br>Round and a round and a round I go <br>Round and a round this time for keeps <br>Father only you can save my sould <br>And playing that organ must count <br>For something <br>Girl you got to know these days <br>Which side your on <br>Little Amterdam <br>Shut down today <br>They buried her with a <br>Butter bean bouquet <br>And the Sheriff now can't ride away <br>And I won't say <br>He shouldna paid <br>But Momma <br>It wasn't my bullet]]></content><category term="Tori Amos" label="Tori Amos"/><category term="Little Amsterdam" label="Little Amsterdam"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/This_Old_Man/</id><title>Tori Amos - This Old Man - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:20:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:20:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/This_Old_Man/" title="Tori Amos - This Old Man - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This old man he played one <br>He played knick knack on my thumb <br>With a knick knack paddy whack, give your dog a bone <br>This old man came rolling home <br><br>This old man he played two <br>He played knick knack on my shoe <br>With a knick knack paddy whack, give your dog a bone <br><br>This old man he played three <br>He played knick knack on my knee <br>With a knick knack paddy whack <br>This old man <br><br>This old man he played four <br>He played knick knack on my door <br>With a knick knack paddy whack, give your dog a bone <br>This old man came rolling home <br><br>This old man he play ten <br>He played knick knack on my shin, on my shin <br>With a knick knack paddy whack, give your dog a bone]]></content><category term="Tori Amos" label="Tori Amos"/><category term="This Old Man" label="This Old Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Leather/</id><title>Tori Amos - Leather - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:20:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:20:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Leather/" title="Tori Amos - Leather - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look I'm standing naked before you <br>Don't you want more then my sex <br>I can scream as loud as your last one <br>But I can't claim innocence <br><br>Oh God <br>Could it be the weather <br>Oh God <br>Why am I here <br>If love Isn't forever <br>And it's not the weather <br>Hand me my leather <br><br>I could just pretend that you love me <br>The night would lose all sense of fear <br>But why do I need you to love me <br>When you can't Hold what I hold dear <br><br>Oh God <br>Could it be the weather <br>Oh God <br>Why am I here <br>If love Isn't forever <br>And it's not the weather <br>Hand me my leather <br><br>I almost ran over an angel <br>He had a nice big fat cigar <br>In a sense he said You're alone here <br>So if you jump you best jump far <br><br>Oh God <br>Could it be the weather <br>Oh God <br>Why am I here <br>If love Isn't forever <br>And it's not the weather <br>Hand me my leather]]></content><category term="Tori Amos" label="Tori Amos"/><category term="Leather" label="Leather"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Doughnut_Song/</id><title>Tori Amos - Doughnut Song - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:20:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:20:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Doughnut_Song/" title="Tori Amos - Doughnut Song - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Had me a trick and a kick and your message <br>Well you'll never gain weight from a doughnut hole <br>Then thought that I could decipher your message <br>There's no one here dear <br>No one at all <br><br>And if I'm wasting all your time <br>This time <br>Maybe you never learned to take <br>And if I'm hanging on to your shade <br>I guess I'm way beyond the pale <br><br>And souther men can grow gold <br>Can grow pretty <br>Blood can be pertty <br>Like a delicate man <br>Copper to steel to a hinge that is faltered <br>That let's you in let's you in let's you in <br>Somethings's just keeping you numb <br><br>You told me last night <br>You were a sun now with your very own <br><br>Devoted satellite <br>Happy for you <br>And I am sure that I hate you <br>Two sons too many too many able fires <br><br>And if I'm wasting all you time <br>This time <br>I think you never learned to take <br>And if I'm haning on to your shade <br>I guess I'm way beyond the pale]]></content><category term="Tori Amos" label="Tori Amos"/><category term="Doughnut Song" label="Doughnut Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Putting_The_Damage_On/</id><title>Tori Amos - Putting The Damage On - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:20:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:20:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Putting_The_Damage_On/" title="Tori Amos - Putting The Damage On - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Glue <br>Stuck to my shoes <br>Does anyone konw why you play with an orange rind <br>You say you packed my things <br>And divided what was mine you're off to the mountain top <br>I say her skinny legs could use sun <br>But now I'm wishing <br>For my best impression <br>Of my best Angie Dickinson <br>But now I've got to worry <br>Cause boy you still look pretty <br>When you're putt the damage on <br><br>Don't make me scratch on you door <br>I never left you <br>For a banjo <br>I only just turned around for a poodle <br>And a corvette <br>And my impression <br>of my best Angie Dickinson <br>But now I've got to worry <br>Cause boy you still look pretty <br>When you're putting the damage on <br><br>I'm trying not to move <br>It's just you ghost <br>Passing through <br>I said <br>I'm trying not to move <br>It's just your ghost passing through <br>It's just your ghost <br>Passing through <br>And now <br>I'm quite sure <br>There's a light in you platoon <br>I never seen a light move <br>LIke yours <br>Can do to Me <br>So now I'm wishing <br>For my best impression <br>of my best Angie Dickinson <br>But now I've got to worry <br>Cause boy you still look pretty <br>To me <br>But I've got a place to go <br>I've got a ticket to your late show <br>And now I'm worrying cause even still <br>You sure are pretty <br>When you're putting the damage on <br>Yes <br>When you're putting the damage on <br>You're just so pretty <br>When you're putting the damage on]]></content><category term="Tori Amos" label="Tori Amos"/><category term="Putting The Damage On" label="Putting The Damage On"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Caught_A_Lite_Sneeze/</id><title>Tori Amos - Caught A Lite Sneeze - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:20:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:20:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Caught_A_Lite_Sneeze/" title="Tori Amos - Caught A Lite Sneeze - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Caught a lite sneeze caught a lite breeze <br>Caught a lightweight lightingseed <br>Boys on my left side <br>Boys on my right side <br>Boys in th emiddle <br>And you're not here I need a big oan <br>From the girl zone <br><br>Building <br>tumbling down <br>Didn't know our love was so small <br>Coun't stand at all <br>Mr St John just bring you son <br><br>The spire is hot <br>And my cells can't feed <br>And you still got that Belle dragging your foots <br>I'm hiding it well Sister Ernestine <br>But I still got that Belle <br>Dragging my foots <br><br>Right on time you get closer <br>And closer <br>Called my name but there's no way in <br>Use that fame <br>Rent you wife and kids today <br>Maybe she will <br>Maybe she will caught a lite sneeze <br>Dreamed a little dream <br>Made my own pretty hate machine <br>Boys on my left side <br>Boys on my right side <br>Boys in the middle and you're not here <br>Boys in their dresses <br>And you're not here <br>I need a big loan from the girl zone]]></content><category term="Tori Amos" label="Tori Amos"/><category term="Caught A Lite Sneeze" label="Caught A Lite Sneeze"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Doughnut_Song/</id><title>Tori Amos - Doughnut Song - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:20:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:20:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Doughnut_Song/" title="Tori Amos - Doughnut Song - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Had me a trick and a kick and your message <br>Well you'll never gain weight from a doughnut hole <br>Then thought that I could decipher your message <br>There's no one here dear <br>No one at all <br><br>And if I'm wasting all your time <br>This time <br>Maybe you never learned to take <br>And if I'm hanging on to your shade <br>I guess I'm way beyond the pale <br><br>And souther men can grow gold <br>Can grow pretty <br>Blood can be pertty <br>Like a delicate man <br>Copper to steel to a hinge that is faltered <br>That let's you in let's you in let's you in <br>Somethings's just keeping you numb <br><br>You told me last night <br>You were a sun now with your very own <br><br>Devoted satellite <br>Happy for you <br>And I am sure that I hate you <br>Two sons too many too many able fires <br><br>And if I'm wasting all you time <br>This time <br>I think you never learned to take <br>And if I'm haning on to your shade <br>I guess I'm way beyond the pale]]></content><category term="Tori Amos" label="Tori Amos"/><category term="Doughnut Song" label="Doughnut Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Here_In_My_Head/</id><title>Tori Amos - Here. In My Head - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:20:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:20:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Here_In_My_Head/" title="Tori Amos - Here. In My Head - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In my head I found you there <br>And running around and following me <br>But you don't dare <br>But I find that I have now more than I ever wanted to <br><br>So maybe Thomas Jefferson wasn't born <br>In your backyard like you have said <br>And maybe I'm just the horizon you run to <br>When she has left you there <br><br>You are here in my head <br>And running around and calling me <br>Come back I'll show you the roses that brush off the snow <br>And open their petals again and again <br>And you know that apple green ice cream can melt in your hands <br>I can't so I held your hand at the fair <br>And even forgot what time it was <br><br>And even if Thomas Jefferson wasn't born <br>In your backyard like you have said <br>And maybe I'm just the horizon you run to <br>When she has left you and me here alone on the floor <br><br>You're counting my feathers as the bells toll <br>You see the bow and belt and the girl from the south <br>All favorites of mine, you know them all well <br><br>And spring brings fresh little puddles <br>That makes it all clear, makes it all <br>Do you know <br>Do you know what this is doing to me <br><br>Here <br>Here <br>Here <br>Here in my head]]></content><category term="Tori Amos" label="Tori Amos"/><category term="Here. In My Head" label="Here. In My Head"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Little_Amsterdam/</id><title>Tori Amos - Little Amsterdam - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:21:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:21:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Little_Amsterdam/" title="Tori Amos - Little Amsterdam - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Little Amsterdam <br>In a southern town <br>Hominy get it on the plate girl <br>Momma keep your head down <br>Momma it wasn't my bullet <br><br>Don't take me back to the RAnge <br>I'm just comin out of the cell in my brain <br>Girl you got to know these days <br>Which side your on <br><br>Mamma got shit <br>She loved a brown man <br>Then she built a bridge in the Sheriff's bed <br>She'd do anyting to save her man <br>You see her olives are cold pressed <br>And her best friend is a sun dress <br>But Momma <br>It wasn't my bullet <br><br>Round and a round and a round I go <br>Round and a round this time for keeps <br>Father only you can save my sould <br>And playing that organ must count <br>For something <br>Girl you got to know these days <br>Which side your on <br>Little Amterdam <br>Shut down today <br>They buried her with a <br>Butter bean bouquet <br>And the Sheriff now can't ride away <br>And I won't say <br>He shouldna paid <br>But Momma <br>It wasn't my bullet]]></content><category term="Tori Amos" label="Tori Amos"/><category term="Little Amsterdam" label="Little Amsterdam"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Blood_Roses/</id><title>Tori Amos - Blood Roses - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:21:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:21:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Blood_Roses/" title="Tori Amos - Blood Roses - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Blood roses <br>Blood roses <br>Back on the street now <br>Blood roses <br>Blood roses <br>Back on the street now <br>Can't forget the things you never said <br>On days like these starts me thinking <br>When chickens get a taste of your meat girl <br>Chickens get a taste of your meat yes <br><br>You gave him you blood <br>And your warm little diamond <br>He likes killing you after you're dead <br>You think I'm a queer <br>I think you're a queer <br>Said I think you're a queer <br>I think you're a queer <br>I shaved every place where you been boy <br>I said I shaved every place where you been yes <br><br>God knows I know <br>I've thrown away those graces <br>God knows I've thrown away <br>Those graces <br>God knows I know <br>I've thrown away those graces <br><br>The Belle of New Orleans tried to show me <br>Once how to tango <br>Wrapped around you feet <br>Wrapped around like good little roses <br><br>Blood Roses <br>Blood Roses <br>Back on the street now <br>Blood Roses <br>Blood Roses <br>Back on the street now <br>Now, Now <br>Now you've cut out the flute <br>From the throat of the loon <br>At least when you cry now <br>He can't even hear you <br>When chickens get a taste of your meat girl <br>Come on <br>Come on <br>Come on <br>Come on <br>Come on <br>Come on <br>Come on <br>Come on <br>Come on <br>When he sucks you deep <br>Sometimes you're nothing but meat]]></content><category term="Tori Amos" label="Tori Amos"/><category term="Blood Roses" label="Blood Roses"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Crucify/</id><title>Tori Amos - Crucify - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:21:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:21:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tori_Amos/Crucify/" title="Tori Amos - Crucify - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Every finger in the room <br>Is pointing at me <br>I wanna spit in their faces <br>Then I get afraid of what that could bring <br>I got a bowling ball in my stomach <br>I got a desert in my mouth <br>Figures that my courage would choose to sell out now <br><br>I've been looking for a savior in these dirty streets <br>Looking for a savior beneath these dirty sheets <br>I've been raising up my hands <br>Drive another nail in <br>Just what God needs <br>One more victim <br><br>Why do we <br>Crucify ourselves <br>Every day <br>I crucify myself <br>Nothing I do is good enough for you <br>Crucify myself <br>Every day <br>I crucify myself <br>My heart is sick of being, I said, my heart is sick of being in chains, oh, oh, chains <br><br>Got a kick for a dog <br>Beggin' for love <br>I gotta have my suffering <br>So that I can have my cross <br>I know a cat named Easter <br>He says, Will you ever learn <br>You're just an empty cage, girl <br>If you kill the bird <br><br>I've been looking for a savior in these dirty streets <br>Looking for a savior beneath these dirty sheets <br>I've been raising up my hands <br>Drive another nail in <br>Got enough guilt to start my own religion <br><br>Why do we <br>Crucify ourselves <br>Every day <br>I crucify myself <br>Nothing I do is good enough for you <br>Crucify myself <br>Every day <br>I crucify myself <br>My heart is sick of being, I said, my heart is sick of being in chains, oh, oh, chains <br><br>Please believe <br>Save me <br>I cry <br><br>I've been looking for a savior in these dirty streets <br>Looking for a savior beneath these dirty sheets <br>I've been raising up my hands <br>Drive another nail in <br>Where are those angels when you need them <br><br>Why do we crucify ourselves <br>Every day <br>I crucify myself <br>Nothing I do is good enough for you <br>Crucify myself <br>Every day <br>I crucify myself <br>My heart is sick of being, I said, my heart is sick of being in chains, oh, oh, chains <br><br>Why do we <br>Chains <br>Crucify myself <br><br>Never going back again to crucify myself again <br>You know never going back again to crucify myself everyday]]></content><category term="Tori Amos" label="Tori Amos"/><category term="Crucify" label="Crucify"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stray_Cats/Shes_Sex__17/</id><title>Stray Cats - (She`s) Sex + 17 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:21:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:21:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stray_Cats/Shes_Sex__17/" title="Stray Cats - (She`s) Sex + 17 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, man, I don't feel like goin' to school no more <br>Me neither, they can't make you go, no you daddy, oh yeah <br><br>I ain't goin' to school, it starts too early for me <br>Well, listen man, I ain't goin' to school no more <br>It starts much, much too early for me <br>I don't care about readin', writin', 'rithmetic or history <br><br>I'm gonna walk to the corner and meet my little Marie <br>I'm gonna walk to the corner and meet my little Marie <br>Well, she's the only girl in this whole world who understands me <br><br>Well, she's sexy and 17, my little rock n' roll queen <br>Acts a little bit obscene, gotta let off a little steam <br>Dig that sound, shake it around, you're mine, mine, mine <br><br>Johnny and Eddie and me and Jimmy and Jack <br>Are gonna do a little number on the teacher when she turns her back <br>We're gonna cut out of class, meet the girls by the railroad track <br><br>Well ev'ry Friday night, there's a band that you gotta hear <br>Just a dollar ticket in and twenty five cents a beer <br>They play rock n' roll music like it hasn't been rocked for years <br><br>Well, she's sexy and 17, my little rock n' roll queen <br>Acts a little bit obscene, gotta let off a little steam <br>Dig that sound and shake it around, you're mine, mine, mine, all mine <br><br>Oh c'mon, baby, yeah <br><br>Well, when I hear that rockin' beat, I can't sit still up out of my seat <br>Come on babe, let's jump around your feet <br>Can't learn nothin' in school, they don't teach you on the street <br><br>Wo oh, wo oh, baby, I like your style <br>Wo oh, oh, oh, oh, baby, I like your style <br>You don't care what the other kids say, you go real wild <br><br>Well, you're sexy and 17, my little rock n' roll queen <br>Acts a little bit obscene, gotta let off a little steam <br>Dig that sound and shake it around, you're mine, mine, mine, mine <br>Dig that sound and shake it around you're mine, mine, mine, mine <br>Dig that sound and shake it around you're mine, mine, mine]]></content><category term="Stray Cats" label="Stray Cats"/><category term="(She`s) Sex + 17" label="(She`s) Sex + 17"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stray_Cats/Gina/</id><title>Stray Cats - Gina - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:21:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:21:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stray_Cats/Gina/" title="Stray Cats - Gina - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well they say Gina don't you run with him <br>Because you know the trouble I've been in <br>Oh that was yesterday, don't listen when they say <br>Gina don't you run with him <br>Well they say Gina I'm a bad mistake <br>But that's the chance you know I have to take <br>Well I'm beggin' on my knees, baby darling please <br>Oh Gina don't you run with him <br><br>Well Gina you're a young girl <br>But I think you're old enough to decide <br>They think we're fooling, but I can see the love in your eyes <br>Oh Gina don't you run with him <br><br>Well Gina you're a young girl <br>But I think you're old enough to decide <br>They think we're fooling, but I can see the love in your eyes <br>No, no Don't listen when they say it baby <br><br>Gina don't you run with him <br>Because you know the trouble I've been in <br>Oh that was yesterday, don't listen when they say <br>Gina don't you run with him <br>Well they say Gina don't you run with him <br>Gina don't you run with him <br>Well they say Gina don't you run with him <br>Gina don't you run with him <br>Well they say Gina don't you run with him <br>Well they say Gina don't you run with him <br>No Gina don't you run with him <br>Well they say Gina don't you run with him <br>Gina don't you run with him]]></content><category term="Stray Cats" label="Stray Cats"/><category term="Gina" label="Gina"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stray_Cats/Nine_Lives/</id><title>Stray Cats - Nine Lives - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:21:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:21:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stray_Cats/Nine_Lives/" title="Stray Cats - Nine Lives - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well I got nine lives baby I just keep comin' back <br>I got nine lives baby I just keep comin' back oh yeah <br>I got nine lives and nearly lost them all <br>But each and every time I really had a ball <br>I got nine lives baby I just keep comin' back <br><br>First time that it happened well how was I to know <br>She loved me then she left me it was a long long time ago <br>Numbers eight and seven well they flew by like the wind <br>Don't stick around for me babe I'm coming back again <br><br>I got nine lives baby I just keep comin' back <br>I got nine lives baby I just keep comin' back <br>I got nine lives and nearly lost them all <br>But each and every time I really had a ball <br>I got nine lives baby I just keep comin' back <br><br>I had fun with number six But baby I got stuck on five <br>She took all of my money honey and she buried me alive <br>Four and three got better oh watch out for number two <br>That one almost killed me now don't you think it can't happen to you <br><br>I got just one live left I'm gonna live it all I'm gonna live it all <br>But just one last chance baby I gotta drive this last one home <br>No more whiskey, no more wine, no more women this time <br><br>There goes a kitten I'm smitten <br>I'm a fool again]]></content><category term="Stray Cats" label="Stray Cats"/><category term="Nine Lives" label="Nine Lives"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stray_Cats/Rockabilly_Rules/</id><title>Stray Cats - Rockabilly Rules - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:21:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:21:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stray_Cats/Rockabilly_Rules/" title="Stray Cats - Rockabilly Rules - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a crazy sound that sends my soul <br>It's part hillbilly part rock and roll <br>All you need is a guitar, bull bass and a big ol'drum <br>Well the cats and I get a kick from this song <br>Cause our feelings about it run deep and strong <br>We're naming this song rockabilly rules okay <br>Well rockabilly rules Okay <br>Rockabilly's cool Oh yeah <br>Rockabilly rocks Let's bop <br>Well rockabilly billy bop Let's bop <br>Well rockabilly rules Okay <br>Rockabilly's cool Oh yeah <br><br>Well it's a sound that's around to stay <br>I said rock rock rockabilly rules Okay <br>Well we packed our bags and we hit the trail <br>Now we're always on time just like the US mail <br>Through wind and through snow <br>We never ever miss a show <br>Well we rocked all around this great big world <br>And I'm telling you man we're gonna give it a whirl <br>Everybody knows that rockabilly rules okay <br>Well rockabilly rules Okay <br>Rockabilly's cool Oh yeah <br>Rockabilly rocks Let's bop <br>Well rockabilly billy bop Let's bop <br>Well rockabilly rules Okay <br>Rockabilly's cool Oh yeah <br>Well it's a sound that's around to stay <br>I said rock rock rockabilly rules Okay <br><br>Show you what I mean man <br>Well rockabilly rules Okay <br>Rockabilly's cool Oh yeah <br>Rockabilly rocks Let's bop <br>Well rockabilly billy bop Let's bop <br>Well rockabilly rules Okay <br>Rockabilly's cool Oh yeah <br>Well it's a sound that's around to stay <br>I said rock rock rockabilly rules Okay <br>Well rocka rocka rocka rockabilly rules <br>Rocka rocka rocka rockabilly rules <br>Rocka rocka rocka rockabilly rules <br>Rocka rocka rocka rockabilly rules <br>See my little baby coming down from the tracks <br>Even though she never never never wanna go back <br>Rocka rocka rocka rockabilly rules <br>Rocka rocka rocka rockabilly rules <br>Rocka rocka rocka rockabilly rules]]></content><category term="Stray Cats" label="Stray Cats"/><category term="Rockabilly Rules" label="Rockabilly Rules"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박용민/Scarlatti___Son_Tutta_Duolo_스카를라티___나는_괴로움에_찼네_이태리_가곡/</id><title>박용민 - Scarlatti : Son Tutta Duolo (스카를라티 : 나는 괴로움에 찼네) (이태리 가곡) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:22:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:22:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9A%A9%EB%AF%BC/Scarlatti___Son_Tutta_Duolo_%EC%8A%A4%EC%B9%B4%EB%A5%BC%EB%9D%BC%ED%8B%B0___%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EA%B4%B4%EB%A1%9C%EC%9B%80%EC%97%90_%EC%B0%BC%EB%84%A4_%EC%9D%B4%ED%83%9C%EB%A6%AC_%EA%B0%80%EA%B3%A1/" title="박용민 - Scarlatti : Son Tutta Duolo (스카를라티 : 나는 괴로움에 찼네) (이태리 가곡) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Son tutta duolo <br>non ho che affanni <br>E mi da morte pena crudel <br>pena crudel <br>E mi da morte pena crudel <br>pena crudel <br>E per me solo sono tiranni gli astri <br>La sorte i numi il ciel <br>E per me solo sono tiranni gli astri <br>La sorte i numi <br>i numi il ciel <br>i numi il ciel <br>Son tutta duolo <br>non ho che affanni <br>E mi da morte pena crudel <br>pena crudel <br>E mi da morte pena crudel <br>pena crudel <br>]]></content><category term="박용민" label="박용민"/><category term="Scarlatti : Son Tutta Duolo (스카를라티 : 나는 괴로움에 찼네) (이태리 가곡)" label="Scarlatti : Son Tutta Duolo (스카를라티 : 나는 괴로움에 찼네) (이태리 가곡)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월31일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월31일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9431%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월31일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 31일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 31일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 31일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월31일 생일축하노래" label="8월31일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월30일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월30일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9430%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월30일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 30일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 30일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 30일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월30일 생일축하노래" label="8월30일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월29일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월29일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9429%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월29일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 29일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 29일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 29일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월29일 생일축하노래" label="8월29일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월28일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월28일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9428%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월28일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 28일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 28일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 28일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월28일 생일축하노래" label="8월28일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월27일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월27일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9427%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월27일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 27일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 27일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 27일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월27일 생일축하노래" label="8월27일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월26일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월26일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9426%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월26일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 26일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 26일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 26일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월26일 생일축하노래" label="8월26일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월25일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월25일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9425%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월25일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 25일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 25일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 25일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월25일 생일축하노래" label="8월25일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월24일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월24일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9424%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월24일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 24일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 24일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 24일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월24일 생일축하노래" label="8월24일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월23일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월23일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9423%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월23일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 23일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 23일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 23일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월23일 생일축하노래" label="8월23일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월22일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월22일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9422%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월22일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 22일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 22일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 22일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월22일 생일축하노래" label="8월22일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월21일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월21일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9421%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월21일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 21일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 21일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 21일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월21일 생일축하노래" label="8월21일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월20일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월20일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9420%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월20일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 20일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 20일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 20일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월20일 생일축하노래" label="8월20일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월19일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월19일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9419%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월19일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 19일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 19일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 19일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월19일 생일축하노래" label="8월19일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월18일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월18일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9418%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월18일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 18일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 18일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 18일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월18일 생일축하노래" label="8월18일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월17일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월17일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9417%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월17일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 17일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 17일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 17일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월17일 생일축하노래" label="8월17일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월16일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월16일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9416%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월16일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 16일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 16일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 16일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월16일 생일축하노래" label="8월16일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월15일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월15일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9415%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월15일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 15일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 15일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 15일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월15일 생일축하노래" label="8월15일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월14일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월14일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9414%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월14일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 14일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 14일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 14일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월14일 생일축하노래" label="8월14일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월13일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월13일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:23:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:23:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9413%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월13일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 13일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 13일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 13일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월13일 생일축하노래" label="8월13일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월12일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월12일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:24:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:24:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9412%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월12일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 12일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 12일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 12일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월12일 생일축하노래" label="8월12일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월11일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월11일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:24:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:24:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9411%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월11일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 11일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 11일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 11일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월11일 생일축하노래" label="8월11일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월10일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월10일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:24:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:24:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%9410%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월10일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 10일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 10일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 10일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월10일 생일축하노래" label="8월10일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월9일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월9일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:24:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:24:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%949%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월9일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 9일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 9일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 9일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월9일 생일축하노래" label="8월9일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월8일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월8일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:24:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:24:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%948%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월8일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 8일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 8일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 8일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월8일 생일축하노래" label="8월8일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월7일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월7일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:24:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:24:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%947%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월7일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 7일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 7일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 7일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월7일 생일축하노래" label="8월7일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월6일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월6일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:24:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:24:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%946%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월6일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 6일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 6일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 6일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월6일 생일축하노래" label="8월6일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월5일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월5일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:24:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:24:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%945%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월5일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 5일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 5일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 5일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월5일 생일축하노래" label="8월5일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월4일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월4일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:24:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:24:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%944%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월4일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 4일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 4일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 4일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월4일 생일축하노래" label="8월4일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월3일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월3일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:24:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:24:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%943%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월3일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 3일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 3일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 3일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월3일 생일축하노래" label="8월3일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월2일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월2일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:24:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:24:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%942%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월2일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 2일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 2일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 2일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월2일 생일축하노래" label="8월2일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/8월1일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 8월1일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:24:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:24:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/8%EC%9B%941%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 8월1일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br>생일축하해요 생일축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>오늘은 8월 1일 당신이 태어난 날 <br>우리 함께 노래불러요 <br>생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>생일 케이크에 촛불을 켜요 <br>두눈 감고 소원 빌어봐요 <br>그소원 속에 내가 있을까 <br>즐거운 상상을 해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Birthday To You <br>Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>일년을 기다렸어요 8월 1일 <br>오늘을 기다렸어요 8월 1일 <br>지금부터 고백해요 내마음을 <br>당신을 사랑해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="8월1일 생일축하노래" label="8월1일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stevie_Nicks/Has_Anyone_Ever_Written_Anything_For_You/</id><title>Stevie Nicks - Has Anyone Ever Written Anything For You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:27:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:27:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stevie_Nicks/Has_Anyone_Ever_Written_Anything_For_You/" title="Stevie Nicks - Has Anyone Ever Written Anything For You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Has anyone ever written anything for you <br>In all your darkest hours <br>Have you ever heard me sing <br>Listen to me now <br>You know I'd rather be alone <br>Than be without you <br>Don't you know <br><br>Has anyone ever given anything to you <br>In your darkest hours <br>Did you ever give it back <br>Well, I have <br>I have given that to you <br>If it's all I ever do <br>This is your song <br><br>And the rain comes down <br>There's no pain and there's no doubt <br>It was easy to say <br>I believed in you everyday <br>If not for me <br>Then do it for the world <br><br>Has anyone ever written anything for you <br>In your darkest sorrow <br>Did you ever hear me sing <br>Listen to me now <br>You know I'd rather be alone <br>Than be without you <br>Don't you know <br><br>So, if not for me, then <br>Do it for yourself <br>If not for me then <br>Do it for the world <br>Poet priest of nothing <br>Poet priest of nothing]]></content><category term="Stevie Nicks" label="Stevie Nicks"/><category term="Has Anyone Ever Written Anything For You" label="Has Anyone Ever Written Anything For You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stevie_Nicks/No_Spoken_Word/</id><title>Stevie Nicks - No Spoken Word - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:27:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:27:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stevie_Nicks/No_Spoken_Word/" title="Stevie Nicks - No Spoken Word - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was just that old <br>That August dark, dark day <br>Swear that you never saw her face <br>Swear that you never heard her say <br><br>No spoken word <br>No small command <br>What was it she wanted <br>They say she had everything <br><br>No spoken word <br>No small command <br>What was it she wanted <br>They say she had everything <br><br>What shall I do <br>What shall I say <br>Should I say <br>Who all the things <br>That I'd like to say to you <br><br>No spoken word <br>No small command <br>What was it she wanted <br>They say she had everyting <br>Let's make a deal here <br><br>Ooh, for one night <br>Well baby, you fill the night with the <br>Wind and the rain and the water <br><br>Oh, for one night <br>Well, just for one night <br>You know that well that <br>Disasterous sound <br>Now it will make me wiser <br>He says, and it will make you look <br>She says, look out <br>I don't know how to learn <br>From the pages of a book <br><br>Well I either say too much, or I <br>I don't say enough <br>Well I play too hard <br>Still I'm not tough enough <br>What was it she wanted <br>They say she had everything <br><br>No spoken word <br>No small command <br>What was it she wanted <br>They said she had everything <br><br>Ooh come around tonight indecent <br>Well <br>Ah, ha come around <br>Tonight, indecent baby well <br>You fill the room <br>With the rain and the wind and the water <br><br>If you tell me <br>One more time <br>Oh baby, take it easy <br>Well, you won't see me ever again <br><br>Some people walk down that darkened street <br>With the faith of a child <br>And so go the faithless <br>But after awhile, she says <br><br>No spoken word <br>Let's make a deal here <br>No small command <br>What was it she wanted <br>They said she had everything <br>ooh, I don't want to know about it]]></content><category term="Stevie Nicks" label="Stevie Nicks"/><category term="No Spoken Word" label="No Spoken Word"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stevie_Nicks/Alice/</id><title>Stevie Nicks - Alice - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:27:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:27:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stevie_Nicks/Alice/" title="Stevie Nicks - Alice - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well I heard she flew down to the Mountain City <br>He said, That's not what I heard I hear she went higher <br>She depended on her friends to tell her when to stop it <br>To make a statement this is me talking to you <br><br>Like Alice through the Looking Glass <br>She used to know who she was <br>Call out my name call out my name <br>But I get no answer she prays <br><br>Better run for your life cried the Mad Hatter <br>Alright, said Alice I'm going back <br>To the other side of the mirror I'm going back <br>Oh no, you cannot tell a gypsy ooh, that she's no longer a member <br>Become a deadly weapon now along with everything else <br>Oh call my name <br><br>Like Alice through the Looking Glass <br>She used to know who she was <br>Call out my name like Alice through the Looking Glass <br>But I get no answer she used to know who she was <br>And she prays for the world that she comes from <br><br>Each had their own charm <br>Buried beneath a solid piece of armour or a steel plated vest <br>Some carry a stiletto in their garter along with everything else <br>That they carry Oh, call my name <br><br>Like Alice through the Looking Glass <br>She used to know who she was <br>Call out my name like Alice through the Looking Glass <br>But I get no answer she used to know who she was <br>And she prays for the world that she comes from <br>Alice call my name <br><br>Ooh run for your life said the Mad Hatter <br>Alright, said Alice I'm going back to the other side of the mirror <br>This is me talking to you well this is me talking to ya <br>Alice Alice]]></content><category term="Stevie Nicks" label="Stevie Nicks"/><category term="Alice" label="Alice"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucinda_Williams/Abandoned/</id><title>Lucinda Williams - Abandoned - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:28:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:28:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucinda_Williams/Abandoned/" title="Lucinda Williams - Abandoned - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All of my love has been taken for granted <br>I've been fair but you've been underhanded <br>I've been disgraced, but I can't bear to face it <br>Cause the truth is my heart has been abandoned <br><br>I was hoping for Heaven, but baby I ain't blind <br>This ain't the first time I've been undermined <br>Sad eyes and crooked smile that I remember well <br>Now it looks like all I got was time to kill <br><br>You can't fool me, I see it in your eyes <br>You can't fool me, I see it in your eyes <br>Everything I thought we had has all been cast aside <br>You can't fool me, I see it in your eyes <br><br>These boots are the same boots I was wearing then <br>And this beer I'm drinking is still the same old brand <br>But these blues are something new, they came around when I lost you <br>Now it looks like I got stuck with an empty hand <br><br>You can't fool me, I see it in your eyes <br>You can't fool me , I see it in your eyes <br>Everything I thought we had has all been cast aside <br>You can't fool me, I see it in your eyes <br><br>You can't fool me, I see it in your eyes]]></content><category term="Lucinda Williams" label="Lucinda Williams"/><category term="Abandoned" label="Abandoned"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucinda_Williams/Nothin_In_Ramblin/</id><title>Lucinda Williams - Nothin` In Ramblin` - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:28:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:28:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucinda_Williams/Nothin_In_Ramblin/" title="Lucinda Williams - Nothin` In Ramblin` - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was born in Louisiana, I was raised in Algiers <br>And everywhere I been, the peoples all say <br>Ain't nothing in rambling, either running around <br>Well, I believe I'll marry, oooo, wooo, Lord, and settle down <br><br>I was walking through the alley with my hand in my coat <br>The police start to shoot me, thought it was something I stole <br>You know it ain't nothing in rambling, either running around <br>Well, I believe I'll marry, oooo, wooo, Lord, and settle down <br><br>The peoples on the highway is walking and crying <br>Some is starving, some is dying <br>You know it ain't nothing in rambling, either running around <br>Well, I believe I'll marry, oooo, wooo, Lord, and settle down <br><br>You may go to Hollywood and try to get on the screen <br>But I'm gonna stay right here and eat these old charity beans <br>'Cause it ain't nothing in rambling, either running around <br>Well, I believe I'll marry, oooo, wooo, Lord, and settle down]]></content><category term="Lucinda Williams" label="Lucinda Williams"/><category term="Nothin` In Ramblin`" label="Nothin` In Ramblin`"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucinda_Williams/Ramblin_On_My_Mind/</id><title>Lucinda Williams - Ramblin` On My Mind - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:28:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:28:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucinda_Williams/Ramblin_On_My_Mind/" title="Lucinda Williams - Ramblin` On My Mind - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I got ramblin' <br>I got ramblin' on my mind <br>Little boy, little boy <br>I got ramblin' on my mind <br>I hate to leave you, baby <br>But you treat me so unkind <br><br>I got mean things <br>I got mean things on my mind <br>I got mean things <br>I got mean things on my mind <br>I hate to leave you, baby <br>But you treat me so unkind <br><br>I'ma pack up my bags <br>I'ma leave with the morning train <br>I'ma pack up my bags <br>I'ma leave with the morning train <br>I hate to hear it, baby <br>When you call me so and so name <br><br>I'm goin' down to the station <br>Get the fastest metal train I see <br>I'm goin' down to the station <br>Get the fastest metal train I see <br>I got the blues for Mister So And So <br>He got the blues about me <br><br>Well there's one thing, baby <br>Makes me begin to dream <br>The way you treat me, baby <br>Oh I begin to think <br>Ramblin' on my mind <br>I hate to leave you, baby <br>But you treat me so unkind <br><br>I got ramblin' <br>I got ramblin' on my mind <br>I got ramblin' <br>Ooh I got ramblin' on my mind <br>I hate to leave you, baby <br>But you treat me so unkind]]></content><category term="Lucinda Williams" label="Lucinda Williams"/><category term="Ramblin` On My Mind" label="Ramblin` On My Mind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucinda_Williams/Lafayette/</id><title>Lucinda Williams - Lafayette - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:28:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:28:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucinda_Williams/Lafayette/" title="Lucinda Williams - Lafayette - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, my sweet Lafayette, how I'm going to miss you <br>You feel so good, Lafayette, now I've come to greet you <br>Tell all my friends I've come back again <br>I couldn't stay away, I was gone only a day <br>But I'm comin' back to my sweet Lafayette <br><br>I'm goin' down to Lafayette, I don't care how long I'm gone <br>It's so hard to leave you, Lafayette, now I know where I belong <br>When that sweet fiddle sounds and Clifton gets down <br>That music sounds so good to me, I just might dance until three <br>And I gotta get back to my sweet Lafayette <br><br>Oh, those boys in Lafayette, smilin' so pretty <br>Those sweet boys in Lafayette, they sure do look good to me <br>We danced all night long to a sweet Cajun song <br>Drinkin' and jivin' 'til dawn, I could dance on and on <br>Doin' a two step in my sweet Lafayette <br>Take me back Lafayette, way down on the bayou <br>I'm your girl, Lafayette, I'm gonna hang around you <br>Eat that gumbo and rollin' and tumble <br>And do crazy things every night, soon I'll be feelin' alright <br>When I get back to my sweet Lafayette <br>When I get back to my sweet Lafayette]]></content><category term="Lucinda Williams" label="Lucinda Williams"/><category term="Lafayette" label="Lafayette"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucinda_Williams/Sharp_Cutting_Wings/</id><title>Lucinda Williams - Sharp Cutting Wings - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:28:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:28:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucinda_Williams/Sharp_Cutting_Wings/" title="Lucinda Williams - Sharp Cutting Wings - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're the one, you're my shinin' star <br>You're the one I've been waitin' for <br>Let's fly away <br>To some foreign country <br>Where nobody knows who we are <br><br>I wish I had a ship to sail the waters <br>I wish I had about a hundred dollars <br>But I just stand <br>With this glass in my hand <br>Feelin' like nothin' even matters <br><br>Your words run through me like the blood in my veins <br>I could swear I knew your love <br>Before I knew your name <br><br>Everyday I miss your smilin' face <br>No one here can ever take your place <br>The sun can shine down <br>Over my town <br>But it never shines in my days <br><br>I told all the stars above <br>I'm gonna shower you with my love <br>I won't demand you <br>I'll try to understand you <br>My love is as free as a dove <br><br>Your words run thru me like the blood in my veins <br>I could swear I knew your <br>Before I knew your name <br><br>You're the one, you're my shinin' star <br>You're the one I've been waitin' for <br>Let's fly away <br>To some foreign country <br>Where nobody knows who we are]]></content><category term="Lucinda Williams" label="Lucinda Williams"/><category term="Sharp Cutting Wings" label="Sharp Cutting Wings"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucinda_Williams/Happy_Woman_Blues/</id><title>Lucinda Williams - Happy Woman Blues - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:28:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:28:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucinda_Williams/Happy_Woman_Blues/" title="Lucinda Williams - Happy Woman Blues - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tryin' hard to be a happy woman <br><br>But sometimes life just overcomes me <br>Everyday I'm workin' just to pay my dues <br>Lay down at night, my mind is so confused <br>Goin' down south with the New York City blues <br><br>Gotta hit the road before I blow a fuse <br>I might buy me a Cadillac or a Chevrolet <br>I don't care what model as long as it takes me away <br><br>I've been hiding my heart in a trunk <br><br>Can you come see me when my ship has sunk <br>You can give me lovin, that I can't refuse <br>And love is the one thing that's sure to cure my blues <br>Goin' down the road with a heavy heart <br><br>Tryin' to find lightness in the dark <br>Tryin' to live my life, tryin' to get satisfied <br>My mind is in the city but my heart is in the countryside <br><br>Tryin' hard to be a happy woman <br><br>But sometimes life just overcomes me <br>Everyday I'm workin' just to pay my dues <br>Lay down at night, my mind is so confused <br>Lay down at night, my mind is so confused]]></content><category term="Lucinda Williams" label="Lucinda Williams"/><category term="Happy Woman Blues" label="Happy Woman Blues"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_La_Tengo/Here_Comes_My_Baby/</id><title>Yo La Tengo - Here Comes My Baby - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:30:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:30:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_La_Tengo/Here_Comes_My_Baby/" title="Yo La Tengo - Here Comes My Baby - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In the midnight moonlight I'll, be walkin a long and lonely mile <br>And every time I do, I keep seein this picture of you <br><br>Here comes my baby, here she comes now <br>And it can come as no surprise to me, with another guy <br>Here comes my baby, here she comes now <br>Walking with a love, with a love that's all so fine <br>Never could be mine, no matter how I try <br><br>You never walk alone, and you're forever talkin on the phone <br>I've tried to call you names, but every time it comes out the same <br><br>Here comes my baby, here she comes now <br>And it can come as no surprise to me, with another guy <br>Here comes my baby, here she comes now <br>Walking with a love, with a love that's all so fine <br>Never could be mine, no matter how I try <br><br>I'm still waitin for your heart, cause I'm sure that some day it's gonna start <br>You'll be mine to hold each day, but 'till then, this is all that I can say <br><br>Here comes my baby, here she comes now <br>And it can come as no surprise to me, with another guy <br>Here comes my baby, here she comes now <br>Walking with a love, with a love that's all so fine <br>Never could be mine, no matter how I try]]></content><category term="Yo La Tengo" label="Yo La Tengo"/><category term="Here Comes My Baby" label="Here Comes My Baby"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_La_Tengo/Tried_So_Hard/</id><title>Yo La Tengo - Tried So Hard - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:30:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:30:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_La_Tengo/Tried_So_Hard/" title="Yo La Tengo - Tried So Hard - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stopped awhile this morning on my way back home <br>I had to realize this time that I'd be all alone <br>Cause she is moving somewhere far away not slow <br>And though I tried so hard to please her <br>She said she really had to go <br>Even though this time it really hurts me bad <br>I've been through similarities it's not the first break I've had <br>And I just can't let it bring me down too low <br>And though I tried so hard to please her <br>There must be something more to know <br>Never thought that we would find our end this way <br>It seemed that everything was going fine <br>Still with all the things that I can do or say <br>It won't change the fate I know so well is mine <br>So I'll stop and look right past the pain <br>Cause I've been in love before and I can love again <br>While she's moving somewhere far away not slow <br>And though I tried so hard to please her <br>She said she really had to go]]></content><category term="Yo La Tengo" label="Yo La Tengo"/><category term="Tried So Hard" label="Tried So Hard"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_La_Tengo/The_One_To_Cry/</id><title>Yo La Tengo - The One To Cry - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:30:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:30:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_La_Tengo/The_One_To_Cry/" title="Yo La Tengo - The One To Cry - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I told you if I ever caught you fooling round again <br>That if you were untrue <br>That you and I are through <br>But now I've caught you and I know that this should be the end <br><br>Though I should tell you so <br>My heart keeps saying no <br>Oh if I say goodbye then I am gonna be the one to cry <br><br>Cry cry cry cry <br>Cry cry cry cry <br>Cry cry cry cry <br>Cry cry cry cry <br><br>Oh I can't bare to be the one to keep you from my side <br>How could you be so cruel <br>You played me for a fool <br>But if I change my mind then I would throw away my pride <br><br>So now what should I do <br>Oh how I wish I knew <br>Oh if I say goodbye then I am gonna be the one to cry <br><br>Cry cry cry cry <br>Cry cry cry cry <br><br>So now what should I do <br>Oh how I wish I knew <br>Oh if I say goodbye then I am gonna be the one to cry <br><br>Cry cry cry cry <br>Cry cry cry cry <br>Cry cry cry cry <br>Cry cry cry cry <br>Cry cry cry cry <br>Cry cry cry cry]]></content><category term="Yo La Tengo" label="Yo La Tengo"/><category term="The One To Cry" label="The One To Cry"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_La_Tengo/Emulsified/</id><title>Yo La Tengo - Emulsified - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:30:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:30:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_La_Tengo/Emulsified/" title="Yo La Tengo - Emulsified - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well oh yeah, do you know how to be emulsified now <br>No <br>I'm gonna tell you a little story about being emulsified <br>Now Yes please <br>It goes something like this <br><br>Alright Yeah <br>My baby's a real gone chick <br>Emulsified <br>When she calls me so quick <br>Emulsified <br>When my baby holds me tight <br>Don't you know I get emulsified <br><br>Oh yeah <br>Yes I do <br>Oh yeah <br>Yes, it's true <br>Emulsified <br>Wha' yeah <br>Emulsified <br>I'm going crazy 'cause I love my baby's soul <br><br>Emulsified <br>Never, never would I let her go <br>Emulsified <br>She squeezes me when she holds me tight <br>Don't you know I get emulsified <br><br>Oh yeah <br>Yes I do <br>Oh yeah <br>Yes, it's true <br>Emulsified <br>Yeah <br>I would go for you baby <br>And I would tell all the world that I do, ooooh <br>Please, please, please baby I don't want nobody but you <br><br>Emulsified <br>Come back baby give me one more chance <br>Emulsified <br>I want to make up a real romance <br>Emulsified <br>Squeeze me and hold me tight <br>Don't you know I get emulsified <br>And um um um um <br>Oh yeah <br>Everyday <br>Oh yeah <br>In the old way <br>Emulsified <br>I'm going crazy 'cause I love her so <br>Emulsified <br>Never, never, never would I let her go <br>Emulsified <br>Oh she squeezes me and she holds me tight <br>Don't you know I get emulsified <br><br>Oh yeah <br>Everyday <br>Oh yeah <br>In the old way <br>Emulsified <br>Oh yeah <br>On Monday <br>Emulsified <br>Emulsified on Tuesday <br>Emulsified <br>Emulsified <br>Emulsified]]></content><category term="Yo La Tengo" label="Yo La Tengo"/><category term="Emulsified" label="Emulsified"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_La_Tengo/Oklahoma_USA/</id><title>Yo La Tengo - Oklahoma U.S.A. - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:30:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:30:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_La_Tengo/Oklahoma_USA/" title="Yo La Tengo - Oklahoma U.S.A. - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All life we work, but work is a bore <br>If life's for livin', what's livin' for <br>She lives in a house that's near decay <br>Built for the industrial revolution <br>But in her dreams, she is far away, far away <br>In Oklahoma, USA <br><br>With Shirley Jones and Gordon McRea <br>As she buys her papers at the cornershop <br>She's walkin' on the surrey with the fringe on top <br>'Cause in her dreams, she is far away, far away <br>In Oklahoma, USA <br><br>She walks to work, but she's still in a daze <br>She's Rita Hayworth or Doris Day <br>And Errol Flynn wants to take her away <br>To Oklahoma, USA <br><br>All life we work, but work is a bore <br>If life's for livin', what's livin' for]]></content><category term="Yo La Tengo" label="Yo La Tengo"/><category term="Oklahoma U.S.A." label="Oklahoma U.S.A."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_La_Tengo/Yellow_Sarong/</id><title>Yo La Tengo - Yellow Sarong - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:30:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:30:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_La_Tengo/Yellow_Sarong/" title="Yo La Tengo - Yellow Sarong - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A man in the moon <br>Taps at the window <br>How will we know your silhouette <br>How will we reach you <br><br>Waving his hands <br>Shouting <br>Is there anymore to that yellow sarong <br>It's more than just a bit of grass <br>What a landscape <br>What a landscape <br><br>Yeah yeah yeah <br>Yeah yeah yeah <br>Yeah yeah yeah <br>A man in the moon <br>Taps at the window <br>How will we know your silhouette <br>How will we reach you <br>How will we reach you <br><br>Yeah yeah yeah <br>Yeah yeah yeah <br>Yeah yeah yeah]]></content><category term="Yo La Tengo" label="Yo La Tengo"/><category term="Yellow Sarong" label="Yellow Sarong"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_La_Tengo/Griselda/</id><title>Yo La Tengo - Griselda - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T17:30:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T17:30:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_La_Tengo/Griselda/" title="Yo La Tengo - Griselda - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come won't you walk with me Griselda <br>wearing the dress that moonlight shines through <br>I am a sad and lonely boy <br>since your mother said I couldn't see you <br><br>Slipping through the wood in the dark of the night <br>calling to the moon out yonder <br>O Lady Moon won't you shine a silver light, and lead me to my Griselda <br><br>Do you recall last night Griselda <br>Learning the lessons nature taught us <br>Watching the fish up the lake <br>it was lovely till your mother caught us <br><br>Slipping through the wood in the dark of the night <br>calling to the moon out yonder <br>O Lady Moon won't you shine a silver light, and lead me to my Griselda <br><br>Moonflower find upon the window <br>give me a foothold for my finding <br>I've got a row boat on the lake <br>Fishing around and all the sun was shining <br><br>Slipping through the wood in the dark of the night <br>calling to the moon out yonder <br>O Lady Moon won't you shine a silver light, and lead me to my Griselda <br><br>I've got a jug of wine Griselda <br>Why must you waste your time in sorrow <br>Hold out your hand have no fear <br>If we're caught, I'll marry you tomorrow <br><br>Slipping through the wood in the dark of the night <br>calling to the moon out yonder <br>O Lady Moon won't you shine a silver light, and lead me to my Griselda <br><br>Slipping through the wood in the dark of the night <br>calling to the moon out yonder <br>O Lady Moon won't you shine a silver light, and lead me to my Griselda]]></content><category term="Yo La Tengo" label="Yo La Tengo"/><category term="Griselda" label="Griselda"/></entry></feed>