<feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:05+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김보윤/인생사_별거더냐/</id><title>김보윤 - 인생사 별거더냐 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%B3%B4%EC%9C%A4/%EC%9D%B8%EC%83%9D%EC%82%AC_%EB%B3%84%EA%B1%B0%EB%8D%94%EB%83%90/" title="김보윤 - 인생사 별거더냐 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1절 <br>인생사 별거이더냐 <br>하루는 웃고 <br>하루는 울어도 <br>마음 편하게 <br>이내 몸 쉴곳 있다면은 <br>그렇게 사는게 <br>장땡 아니더냐 <br>술 한잔 나눌 친구가 있고 <br>당신이 곁에 있는데 <br>부귀 여화를 찾아서 <br>속고 또 속이는 <br>하루살이 인생보다 <br>후회 없이 사는 게 <br>최고가 아니더냐 <br>인생사 별거더냐 <br>후회 없이 사는게 <br>최고가 아니더냐 <br>인생사 별거더냐 (한번더) <br>1.2절 가사]]></content><category term="김보윤" label="김보윤"/><category term="인생사 별거더냐" label="인생사 별거더냐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Western_River_Sound/일가기싫어/</id><title>Western River Sound - 일가기싫어 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Western_River_Sound/%EC%9D%BC%EA%B0%80%EA%B8%B0%EC%8B%AB%EC%96%B4/" title="Western River Sound - 일가기싫어 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[일 가기 싫어 일 가기 싫어 <br>일 가기 싫어 일 가기 싫어 <br>6am <br>오늘도 새벽 알람 난 힘겹게 눈을 떠 <br>냉장고를 열고 마신 물은 <br>왜 이렇게 써 hork up <br>시체 같은 몸을 이끌고 <br>집을 나서보네 <br>만날 애인도 없는데 <br>온 정신은 퇴근길에 <br>창 밖의 벚꽃들은 펴가는데 <br>오늘도 나는 시들어 가겠지 <br>희망찬 내일도 없어 <br>매일 매일 갑갑한 <br>미세먼지 속에 지쳐가 <br>축 처진 어깨 뒤 <br>습관이 된 말 <br>일 가기 싫어 <br>일 가기 싫어 일 가기 싫어 <br>일 가기 싫어 일 가기 싫어 <br>따뜻한 바람이 부는 날은 <br>날 더 힘들게 해 <br>차라리 비라도 내려 메마른 <br>날 위로해 줬으면 싶어 <br>반복되는 무의미한 일상 속 <br>오래 전 꿈꿔 왔던 나의 이상은 <br>이젠 어디로 갔을까 오 난 <br>두려운 마음으로 <br>오늘도 출근길을 향해 <br>매일마다 피곤에 쩔은 <br>날 보니 내 속도 상해 <br>겉으론 의욕 넘치는 척 해봐도 <br>힐링이 필요해 <br>그래도 금요일 하나만 보고 살아가 <br>일 가기 싫어 <br>일 가기 싫어 <br>]]></content><category term="Western River Sound" label="Western River Sound"/><category term="일가기싫어" label="일가기싫어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박채림/조그마한달/</id><title>박채림 - 조그마한달 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%B1%84%EB%A6%BC/%EC%A1%B0%EA%B7%B8%EB%A7%88%ED%95%9C%EB%8B%AC/" title="박채림 - 조그마한달 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[조그마한 달 조그마한 달 <br>그대에게 전해줘 내 마음 <br>I uh uhm <br>저기 높이 뜬 저 달이 <br>그대를 비춰줬으면 <br>까마득히 먼 저 작은 달이 <br>그대를 닮았으면 좋겠다 <br>그대도 달을 보고 <br>내생각을 할까요 <br>달에게 물어 볼까요 <br>조그마한 달 조그마한 달 <br>그대에게 전해줘 내 마음 <br>I love you boy <br>조그마한 달 조그마한 달 <br>그대 목소리 들려줘 내게만 <br>only you and I <br>잠못드는 이 밤에 <br>높이 뜬 저 달에게 <br>내 맘을 고백 할께요 <br>조그마한 달 조그마한 달 <br>그대에게 전해줘 내 마음 <br>I love you boy <br>조그마한 달 조그마한 달 <br>그대 목소리 들려줘 내게만 <br>only you and I <br>나는 그대가 되고 <br>그대는 내가 되어서 <br>서로를 향한 이 마음을 속삭여봐요 <br>우린 영원히 함께 할 거라고 <br>조그마한 달 조그마한 달 <br>그대에게 전해줘 내 마음 <br>I love you boy <br>조그마한 달 조그마한 달 <br>그대 목소리 들려줘 내게만 <br>only you and I <br>조그마한 달 조그마한 달 <br>그대에게 전해줘 내 마음 <br>I love you boy <br>I'll love you boy <br>조그마한 달 조그마한 달 <br>그대 목소리 들려줘 내게만 <br>only you and I <br>]]></content><category term="박채림" label="박채림"/><category term="조그마한달" label="조그마한달"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LIZRO/얼음의_노래/</id><title>LIZRO - 얼음의 노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LIZRO/%EC%96%BC%EC%9D%8C%EC%9D%98_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="LIZRO - 얼음의 노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내일이면 저기 멀리 날아갈 새들을 봐 <br>아픔도 마찬가지 떠나갈 구름이야 <br>너와 걷던 길을 돌아 본다면 <br>꽃잎이 떨어져있다 <br>너는 끝나지 않을 것 같다 말했지만 <br>나는 널 찾아가 너의 맘 다 알아 난 <br>더 이상 널 아프게 하지 않아 <br>내일이면 녹아 내릴 얼음의 모습을 봐 <br>고통은 연기처럼 사라져 어디론가 <br>너와 걷다 고갤 들어 볼 때면 <br>달이 손 흔들고 있다 <br>너는 끝나지 않을 것 같다 말했지만 <br>나는 널 찾아가 너의 맘 다 알아 난 <br>더 이상 널 아프게 하지 않아 <br>I won't let you be alone <br>]]></content><category term="LIZRO" label="LIZRO"/><category term="얼음의 노래" label="얼음의 노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LIZRO/유람선/</id><title>LIZRO - 유람선 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LIZRO/%EC%9C%A0%EB%9E%8C%EC%84%A0/" title="LIZRO - 유람선 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 기다리고 있었어 <br>넌 나를 위해 빛났고 <br>난 기억되고 싶었어 <br>넌 눈부시게 빛났고 <br>난 말해야만 했었어 <br>하얀 그 옷을 입은 넌 <br>언제나 아름다웠어 <br>입술에 붉게 스며든 마음 <br>언제나 나에게 힘이 되 주네 <br>오늘 밤 유람선 뱃머리에 그대와 <br>달빛이 비치는 우주를 가르고 <br>널 위해 노래 부를 꺼야 <br>그대와 나만의 기억이란 빛으로 <br>조금씩 빨라지는 <br>이 유람선 곧 출발할거예요 <br>넌 내게 울고 있냐 물었지 <br>난 말해야만 했었고 <br>우린 전부 웃고 있어 <br>넌 눈부시게 빛났고 <br>난 사랑하고 있었어 <br>하얀 그 옷을 입은 넌 <br>언제나 아름다웠어 <br>입술에 붉게 스며든 마음 <br>언제나 나에게 힘이 되 주네 <br>오늘 밤 유람선 뱃머리에 그대와 <br>달빛이 비치는 우주를 가르고 <br>널 위해 노래 부를 꺼야 <br>그대와 나만의 기억이란 빛으로 <br>조금씩 빨라지는 <br>이 유람선 곧 출발할거예요 <br>]]></content><category term="LIZRO" label="LIZRO"/><category term="유람선" label="유람선"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LIZRO/One_Way_Ticket/</id><title>LIZRO - One Way Ticket - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LIZRO/One_Way_Ticket/" title="LIZRO - One Way Ticket - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ho ho <br>너의 맘 속으로 가는 법 <br>경유역 없는 편도로 끊었지 <br>돌아갈 맘도 없었고 <br>다시 돌아갈 차도 없었는걸 <br>say ho <br>널 갖고 싶었던 시간들 <br>모두 다 all right <br>one way ticket <br>I need your weekend <br>날 가두던 모든 것 다 버리고 <br>오늘 밤만은 내가 널 지켜줄게요 <br>one way ticket <br>I need your weekend <br>날 가두던 모든 것 다 버리고 <br>오늘 밤만은 내가 널 지켜줄게요 <br>ho ho <br>ho ho <br>ho ho <br>트레일로 달리던 기차 속 <br>차창 밖으로 시작을 보았지 <br>달리던 시간은 어디로 <br>마주한 곳엔 네가 서있었어 <br>say ho <br>널 갖고 싶었던 시간들 <br>모두 다 all right <br>one way ticket <br>I need your weekend <br>날 가두던 모든 것 다 버리고 <br>오늘 밤만은 내가 널 지켜줄게요 <br>one way ticket <br>I need your weekend <br>날 가두던 모든 것 다 버리고 <br>오늘 밤만은 내가 널 지켜줄게요 <br>ho ho <br>one way ticket <br>I need your weekend <br>날 가두던 모든 것 다 버리고 <br>오늘 밤만은 내가 널 지켜줄게요 <br>one way ticket <br>I need your weekend <br>날 가두던 모든 것 다 버리고 <br>오늘 밤만은 내가 널 지켜줄게요 <br>Yeah <br>ho ho <br>ho ho <br>ho ho <br>]]></content><category term="LIZRO" label="LIZRO"/><category term="One Way Ticket" label="One Way Ticket"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LIZRO/두빛나래/</id><title>LIZRO - 두빛나래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LIZRO/%EB%91%90%EB%B9%9B%EB%82%98%EB%9E%98/" title="LIZRO - 두빛나래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밤이 지나 찾아온 건 <br>때늦은 새벽공기처럼 <br>환해지던 너의 표정 <br>해가 뜨자 시작된 오전 <br>You will say Ah O <br>We will say Ah O <br>하늘 위로 날아간 건 <br>틀을 깬 imagination <br>얼어붙은 공식처럼 <br>깨져버린 limitation <br>You will say Ah O <br>We will say Ah O <br>돌아보지 말고 가 <br>내게 등을 내며 <br>스치는 사람들의 <br>닫혀버린 마음 <br>사랑하지 않았던 <br>나의 길이 아닌 <br>꿈에 피어나는 <br>찬란하게 빛나는 나의 <br>하늘을 나는 두빛나래 <br>아직 많이 남아있어 <br>누구도 가지 않았던 <br>나의 길을 보는 <br>눈가의 짙은 안개처럼 <br>You will say Ah O <br>We will say Ah O <br>돌아보지 말고 가 <br>내게 등을 내며 <br>스치는 사람들의 <br>닫혀버린 마음 <br>사랑하지 않았던 <br>나의 길이 아닌 <br>꿈에 피어나는 <br>찬란하게 빛나는 나의 <br>하늘을 나는 두빛나래 <br>돌아보지 말고 가 <br>내게 등을 내며 <br>스치는 사람들의 <br>닫혀버린 마음 <br>사랑하지 않았던 <br>나의 길이 아닌 <br>꿈에 피어나는 <br>찬란하게 빛나는 나의 <br>하늘을 나는 두빛나래 <br>]]></content><category term="LIZRO" label="LIZRO"/><category term="두빛나래" label="두빛나래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LIZRO/Show_Me_Your_Light/</id><title>LIZRO - Show Me Your Light - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LIZRO/Show_Me_Your_Light/" title="LIZRO - Show Me Your Light - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve got to show me your light <br>You’ve got to show me your light <br>show me your light <br>show me your light <br>You are the lighthouse on my way <br>You are the best friend on my way <br>You are the lighthouse on my way <br>You are a flash behind my back <br>You’ve got to show me your light <br>You’ve got to show me your light <br>show me your light <br>show me your light <br>]]></content><category term="LIZRO" label="LIZRO"/><category term="Show Me Your Light" label="Show Me Your Light"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LIZRO/Maybe/</id><title>LIZRO - Maybe - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LIZRO/Maybe/" title="LIZRO - Maybe - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아직 남아 있을까 <br>우리가 이루었던 많은 <br>시작과 그 마음 그 이전과 그 다음 <br>어디서부터였을까 <br>내 맘 속 깊은 어딘가 <br>일어나던 파란 짙은 모래바람 <br>어제와 다른 바람이 불면 <br>저 별은 떠오르네 <br>눈부신 볕에 고개를 들 때 <br>우리는 노래하네 <br>When it's time that you <br>and me here <br>You and me made this everland <br>When it's gone <br>in front of your eyes <br>It will be in your mind <br>forever maybe <br>멀어진 길을 따라 걸어갔다면 얼마나 <br>덜 힘들었을까 돌아보던 내가 <br>처음 만났던 너와 나 <br>별이 빛나던 그날 밤 <br>시작했던 그 마음 <br>그 처음과 그 다음 <br>어제와 다른 바람이 불면 <br>저 별은 떠오르네 <br>눈부신 볕에 고개를 들 때 <br>우리는 노래하네 <br>When it's time that you <br>and me here <br>You and me made this everland <br>When it's gone <br>in front of your eyes <br>It will be in your mind <br>forever maybe <br>When it's time that you <br>and me here <br>You and me made this everland <br>When it's gone <br>in front of your eyes <br>It will be in your mind <br>forever maybe <br>]]></content><category term="LIZRO" label="LIZRO"/><category term="Maybe" label="Maybe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박하이_Park_Hi/밀랍천사/</id><title>박하이 (Park Hi) - 밀랍천사 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4_Park_Hi/%EB%B0%80%EB%9E%8D%EC%B2%9C%EC%82%AC/" title="박하이 (Park Hi) - 밀랍천사 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[차가운 너는 나만의 천사 나만의 것 <br>숨쉬지 않아도 좋아 예예 <br>싸늘한 너는 나만의 연인 나만의 것 <br>말하지 않아도 좋아 예예예예 <br>오늘밤 너는 너무 근사해 보여 <br>너무 행복해 보여 너무 <br>오늘밤 너를 그냥 둔다면 <br>너를 그냥 둔다면 말도 안돼 아우 <br>내 빨간 입술에 입맞출 거야 <br>오늘 말해 줄 거야 오늘 <br>다시는 보내지 않을 거야 <br>너를 보내지 않을 거야 너를 <br>차가운 너는 나만의 천사 나만의 것 <br>숨쉬지 않아도 좋아 예예 <br>싸늘한 너는 나만의 연인 나만의 것 <br>말하지 않아도 좋아 예예예예 <br>오늘밤 너는 너무 완벽해 보여 <br>너무 행복해 보여 너무 <br>오늘밤 내게 안겨 웃어봐 <br>내게 안겨 춤춰봐 내게 안겨 아우 <br>차가운 내 피부 너를 만지고 싶어 <br>만지고 싶어 <br>싸늘한 눈동자 너를 가지고 싶어 <br>가지고 싶어 <br>차가운 너는 나만의 천사 나만의 것 <br>숨쉬지 않아도 좋아 예예 <br>싸늘한 너는 나만의 연인 나만의 것 <br>말하지 않아도 좋아 예예예예 <br>차가운 너는 나만의 천사 나만의 것 <br>숨쉬지 않아도 좋아 예예 <br>싸늘한 너는 나만의 연인 나만의 것 <br>말하지 않아도 좋아 예예예예 <br>오늘밤 너는 너무 근사해 보여 <br>너무 행복해 보여 너무 <br>오늘밤 너를 그냥 둔다면 <br>너를 그냥 둔다면 말도 안돼 아우 <br>]]></content><category term="박하이 (Park Hi)" label="박하이 (Park Hi)"/><category term="밀랍천사" label="밀랍천사"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박하이_Park_Hi/Scene/</id><title>박하이 (Park Hi) - Scene - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4_Park_Hi/Scene/" title="박하이 (Park Hi) - Scene - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[갑자기 떠난다니 <br>웃음이 터져나와 <br>어제도 늘 그랬듯 <br>툭툭치며 용서해줬잖아 <br>술이 좀 덜 깬거니 <br>알아 넌 달라졌어 <br>화를 내도 욕을 해도 예전처럼 <br>넌 미안치않아 <br>할 말이 없겠니 <br>뭐 불만없는 사랑 어딨어 <br>내 마음 나도 모를 때 많아 <br>훌쩍 떠나고파 <br>그럴때면 나 억지라도 달래왔는데 <br>사랑이란 거 <br>내일 일도 알 수 없지만 <br>우리는 아직 이별은 아냐 <br>제발 후회 말고 내 말 좀 들어 <br>너 가지 말라고 <br>너 밖에 안 봤는데 <br>그래서 더 화냈어 <br>좋은사람 얼마든지 많았는데 <br>좀 고마우라고 <br>할 말이 없겠니 <br>뭐 불만없는 사랑 어딨어 <br>내 마음 나도 모를 때 많아 <br>훌쩍 떠나고파 <br>그럴때면 나 억지라도 달래왔는데 <br>사랑이란 거 <br>내일 일도 알 수 없지만 <br>우리는 아직 이별은 아냐 <br>제발 후회 말고 내 말 좀 들어 <br>너 가지 말라고 <br>참 오랜만에 친구들을 만났어 <br>또 한번 쏠로된 걸 축하한대 <br>얼마든 좋은 남자 <br>다시 내가 만날거래 <br>나도 모르겠어 <br>널 미워해도 모자랄 내가 <br>왜 미안하고 고마운건지 <br>다시 너를 닮은 사랑이 <br>거울처럼 찾아온다면 <br>그땐 나도 니가 되어 사랑 해볼께 <br>나 그제서야 알게 되겠지 <br>내게 주려 했던 너의 그 한마디 <br>날 사랑했다고 <br>]]></content><category term="박하이 (Park Hi)" label="박하이 (Park Hi)"/><category term="Scene" label="Scene"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박하이_Park_Hi/Higher/</id><title>박하이 (Park Hi) - Higher - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4_Park_Hi/Higher/" title="박하이 (Park Hi) - Higher - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 또 왜 이래 <br>다시 사랑에 빠졌어 <br>취한만큼 아플 사랑 또 사랑 <br>이번엔 좀 달라 <br>아니 숨도 못 쉬겠어 <br>너와 모든 순간들이 <br>Stop the time <br>널 원해 원해 원해 원해 <br>많이 많이 <br>so afraid <br>Come on over and over and over <br>날 데려가 줘 yeah <br>날 휘감는 눈빛에 끌려 <br>You don't making me who i am <br>나 눈부신 빛으로 빠져 <br>You and i to become one <br>나 끝없이 하늘로 Higher <br>so sweet for me <br>so sweet for me <br>뚜루루 뚜루루 뚜루루 <br>Always love you <br>잠시라도 좋아 아니 오래 오래 <br>뚜루루 뚜루루 뚜루루 <br>너 하나로 난 충분해 <br>함께라면 나는 좋아 좋아 좋아 <br>뚜루루 뚜루루 뚜루루 <br>Higher with your love <br>어떻게 말해 사랑한다는 흔한 말 <br>그런 표현 따윈 내가 미안해 <br>차가운 말투로 나를 숨 못 쉬게 해도 <br>그게 너의 매력인걸 어떻게 <br>널 원해 원해 원해 원해 <br>많이 많이 <br>so afraid <br>Come on over and over and over <br>날 데려가 줘 yeah <br>날 휘감는 눈빛에 끌려 <br>You don't making me who i am <br>나 눈부신 빛으로 빠져 <br>You and i to become one <br>나 끝없이 하늘로 Higher <br>so sweet for me <br>so sweet for me <br>뚜루루 뚜루루 뚜루루 <br>Always love you <br>어떤 누구도 내 맘 가진 적 없었어 <br>모두 다 시시해 그랬어 뻔한 말들 <br>날 휘감는 눈빛에 끌려 <br>You don't making me who i am <br>나 눈부신 빛으로 빠져 <br>You and i to become one <br>나 끝없이 하늘로 Higher <br>so sweet for me <br>so sweet for me <br>뚜루루 뚜루루 뚜루루 <br>Always love you <br>잠시라도 좋아 아니 오래 오래 <br>뚜루루 뚜루루 뚜루루 <br>너 하나로 난 충분해 <br>함께라면 나는 좋아 좋아 좋아 <br>뚜루루 뚜루루 뚜루루 <br>Higher with your love <br>]]></content><category term="박하이 (Park Hi)" label="박하이 (Park Hi)"/><category term="Higher" label="Higher"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mike_Williams/Dont_Hurt_Feat_Brezy/</id><title>Mike Williams - Don`t Hurt (Feat. Brezy) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mike_Williams/Dont_Hurt_Feat_Brezy/" title="Mike Williams - Don`t Hurt (Feat. Brezy) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Did you cut your hair <br>'cause you look a little <br>different than I left ya <br>Why you always tryna hide <br>all that pain behind your eyes <br>I don't remember <br>I used to think <br>that I would always let you <br>get to me <br>That I would hear your voice <br>and hit my knees <br>And now I feel it all again again <br>But it don't hurt like it used to <br>No it don't burn like a coal still hot <br>And when I see you at the bar <br>with a honey on your arm <br>I feel nothing at all <br>'Cause it don't hurt <br>No it don't hurt like it used to <br>And when I see you at the bar <br>with a honey on your arm <br>I feel nothing at all <br>'Cause it don't hurt <br>'Cause it don't hurt <br>No it don't hurt like it used to <br>And when I see you at the bar <br>with a honey on your arm <br>I feel nothing at all <br>Did you cut your hair <br>'cause you look a little <br>different than I left ya <br>Why you always tryna hide <br>all that pain behind your eyes <br>I don't remember <br>I used to think <br>that I would always let you <br>get to me <br>That I would hear your voice <br>and hit my knees <br>And now I feel it all again again <br>But it don't hurt like it used to <br>No it don't burn like a coal still hot <br>And when I see you at the bar <br>with a honey on your arm <br>I feel nothing at all <br>'Cause it don't hurt <br>No it don't hurt like it used to <br>And when I see you at the bar <br>with a honey on your arm <br>I feel nothing at all <br>]]></content><category term="Mike Williams" label="Mike Williams"/><category term="Don`t Hurt (Feat. Brezy)" label="Don`t Hurt (Feat. Brezy)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엘리스_ELRIS/너와_나/</id><title>엘리스 (ELRIS) - 너와 나 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%98%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%A4_ELRIS/%EB%84%88%EC%99%80_%EB%82%98/" title="엘리스 (ELRIS) - 너와 나 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한 스푼 시럽처럼 살짝 <br>나른한 오후같이 스르르 <br>네게 기대 잠이 들면 좋겠다 <br>해가 바다 속에 잠기듯 <br>원래 그런 것처럼 당연하게 <br>네 맘속에 내가 물들고 싶어 <br>너와 나 사이 하나 둘 쌓인 <br>작은 감정들이 점점 <br>날 너에게 데려가 <br>어느새 이만큼 와 버렸어 <br>하루하루 사이 커지는 마음 <br>한 뼘 채 안될 만큼 <br>가까이 있고 싶어 <br>내 눈에 너만 보이게 <br>한 낮의 단잠처럼 달게 <br>주말의 끝처럼 벌써 이렇게 <br>내 맘 속은 어느새 너로 가득 <br>너와 나 사이 하나 둘 쌓인 <br>작은 감정들이 점점 <br>날 너에게 데려가 <br>어느새 이만큼 와 버렸어 <br>하루하루 사이 커지는 마음 <br>한 뼘 채 안될 만큼 <br>가까이 있고 싶어 <br>내 눈에 너만 보이게 <br>별이 쏟아지는 네 눈 속에 <br>풍덩 빠져도 될까나 <br>우리 둘 사이 더욱 가까이 <br>한 뼘 채 안될 만큼 <br>나를 꽉 안아줘 <br>네 눈은 나만을 <br>]]></content><category term="엘리스 (ELRIS)" label="엘리스 (ELRIS)"/><category term="너와 나" label="너와 나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엘리스_ELRIS/Miracle/</id><title>엘리스 (ELRIS) - Miracle - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%98%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%A4_ELRIS/Miracle/" title="엘리스 (ELRIS) - Miracle - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ELRIS Yeah ELRIS <br>있잖니 나 이상해 진건지 Serious <br>확실해 비정상인 게 딱 분명해 <br>궁금해 너의 온종일 <br>안절부절 못해 매일 설레어 <br>나 어쩌니 정신이 혼미 혼미해 <br>점점 부풀어 가 너란 풍선이 <br>아슬 아슬 터질 듯 말듯 위험 수위야 <br>이런 느낌 첨이야 Yaya <br>이 떨림 너무 좋아 <br>Good Good 좋아 <br>비어있니 네 옆자리 <br>어머나 어머나 뭐래 <br>빨주노초파남보 Colorful 무지개빛 <br>월화수목금토일 Everyday 가득 너야 <br>계속 맴 맴 맴돌아 <br>나 핑핑핑핑 도는 걸 <br>고장나버린 시계태엽 같아 <br>너란 기적으로 채워져 <br>내 눈에 담긴 세상이 Oh <br>반짝반짝 빛나는 하늘 <br>별빛보다 빛나요 반짝 <br>Oh my Miracle 기다렸어 Miracle <br>그댄 기적이에요 <br>You're my Miracle 그대라서 <br>Miracle My Miracle <br>좀 더 핫하게 Uh <br>예쁘게 예쁘게 워우 <br>이건 아냐 다른 옷을 추천해 What <br>어떤 Style 어떤 색 <br>에라 모르겠다 얼음 땡 <br>내 이름 불러 줄 때 <br>넌 어떤 심쿵 표정일지 <br>뭘까 너만의 향기는 <br>다른 별의 향기일지 <br>근데 왜 나만 늘어 고민거리 어쩜 <br>너도 혹시 조금은 나와 같을지 <br>이런 적은 첨이야 이 떨림 <br>너무 좋아 Good Good 좋아 <br>허락할게 내 옆자리 <br>어머나 어머나 몰라 <br>빨주노초파남보 Wonderful 무지개빛 <br>월화수목금토일 Everyday 오직 너야 <br>계속 맴 맴 맴돌아 <br>나 핑핑핑핑 도는 걸 <br>고장나버린 시계태엽 같아 <br>너란 기적으로 채워져 내 눈에 <br>담긴 세상이 Oh <br>반짝반짝 빛나는 하늘 <br>별빛보다 빛나요 반짝 <br>둘이 손 꼭 잡고 발 맞춰 걷는 상상 <br>살며시 내 두 눈 바라봐주는 상상 <br>조마조마해 간지러워 빨개져도 <br>나는 몰라 <br>어쩌면 좋아 이렇게 좋아 <br>멈출 수가 없는 걸 <br>어떤 말도 모자라 또 핑핑핑핑 <br>도는 걸 <br>이상한나라 속 주인공 같아 <br>너란 기적이 날 채워줘 1분1초 <br>매순간이 Oh <br>반짝반짝 빛나죠 하늘 <br>별빛보다 빛나요 반짝 <br>Oh my Miracle 기다렸어 Miracle <br>그댄 기적이에요 <br>You're my Miracle 그대라서 Miracle <br>Oh my Miracle 기다렸어 Miracle <br>그댄 기적이에요 <br>반짝반짝 빛나는 <br>너란 기적으로 채워줘 반짝 <br>]]></content><category term="엘리스 (ELRIS)" label="엘리스 (ELRIS)"/><category term="Miracle" label="Miracle"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엘리스_ELRIS/나의_별/</id><title>엘리스 (ELRIS) - 나의 별 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%98%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%A4_ELRIS/%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EB%B3%84/" title="엘리스 (ELRIS) - 나의 별 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're my star <br>그대는 나나나의 별 <br>어두운 밤하늘을 켜 <br>두려움뿐이던 내 가슴속에 <br>빛이 돼준 너 <br>꿈같은 시간 너와 함께 <br>소중한 기억일거야 <br>두근 두근 내 가슴이 자꾸 떨려와 <br>조금 조금 다가오는 너를 볼 때마다 <br>이런 느낌 어색해 모른 척 해봐도 <br>온통 네 생각뿐야 <br>내겐 너 뿐야란 말보다 Sweet하게 <br>나를 바라보던 그 눈빛 나 어떡해 <br>서로 감춰왔던 마음 들여다보며 <br>언제나 내 곁을 지켜줄래 <br>그대는 나나나의 별 <br>어두운 밤하늘을 켜 <br>두려움뿐이던 내 가슴속에 <br>빛이 돼준 너 <br>이제는 내 곁의 너와 함께 <br>소중한 기억들뿐야 <br>그대는 단하나의 별 <br>내 맘을 가진 Only one <br>포근한 너의 어깨에 <br>살며시 기대 잠들고 싶어 <br>꿈같은 시간 너와 함께 <br>소중한 기억일거야 <br>이런 기분 처음이라 <br>모른 척 해봐도 온통 네 생각뿐야 <br>넌 내 꺼야란 말보다 짜릿하게 <br>나를 감싸 안아주던 <br>네 품에 안겨 꼭 안겨 <br>서로 감춰왔던 마음 들여다보며 <br>언제나 내 곁을 지켜줄래 <br>그대는 나나나의 별 <br>어두운 밤하늘을 켜 <br>두려움뿐이던 내 가슴속에 <br>빛이 돼준 너 <br>이제는 내 곁의 너와 함께 <br>소중한 기억들뿐야 <br>널 닮아버린 나 <br>수줍어 못했던 말 <br>I can't stop falling in love <br>with u my love <br>언제까지나 내 맘 속 비춰주는 건 <br>오직 너 하나뿐야 <br>그대는 나나나의 별 <br>어두운 밤하늘을 켜 <br>두려움뿐이던 내 가슴속에 <br>빛이 돼준 너 <br>이제는 내 곁의 너와 함께 <br>소중한 기억들뿐야 <br>그대는 단 하나의 별 <br>내 맘을 가진 Only one <br>포근한 너의 어깨에 <br>살며시 기대 잠들고 싶어 <br>꿈같은 시간 너와 함께 <br>소중한 기억일거야 <br>You're my star <br>]]></content><category term="엘리스 (ELRIS)" label="엘리스 (ELRIS)"/><category term="나의 별" label="나의 별"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엘리스_ELRIS/우리_처음/</id><title>엘리스 (ELRIS) - 우리 처음 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%98%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%A4_ELRIS/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EC%B2%98%EC%9D%8C/" title="엘리스 (ELRIS) - 우리 처음 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 꿈 가까이 내 마음 더 깊이 <br>ELRIS Here I am <br>우리가 처음 만난 오늘을 난 <br>잊지 않을게 <br>이 바람 이 향기 우리 사이에 온도까지 <br>추운 날들을 딛고 이제 막 핀 꽃들처럼 <br>내 꿈과 내 맘을 <br>더 깊이깊이 그대와 피우고 싶어 <br>한 번도 느껴 본 적 없는 <br>이런 기분 뭐라고 하죠 <br>낯선 공기에 입술을 깨물어도 <br>나도 모르게 웃음이 나요 <br>한 순간 휙 이상한 <br>딴 세계로 빠진 것 같아 <br>우리가 처음 만난 오늘을 난 <br>잊지 않을게 <br>이 바람 이 향기 우리 사이에 온도까지 <br>추운 날들을 딛고 이제 막 핀 꽃들처럼 <br>내 꿈과 내 맘을 <br>더 깊이깊이 그대와 피우고 싶어 <br>세상에 많은 이야기가 <br>진짜 내 얘기 같기도 해 <br>숲 속 어딘가 깊이 잠들어 <br>그댈 기다린 것만 같아요 <br>혹시 깨면 꿈일까 익숙한 내 방일까 <br>아 그럼 무척 곤란해 <br>저 귀여운 토끼는 <br>따라가면 안 될 것 같아 <br>사실 난 처음이라 그래 조금 <br>두렵기도 해 <br>하나씩 하나씩 천천히 만들고 싶어 <br>마음은 벅차게 뛰고 <br>막 궁금한 게 많지만 <br>조금씩 조금씩 <br>지치지 않게 그대와 걷고 싶어 <br>뭐지 이 기분은 말이 안 되니까 <br>뭐라 답해야 할지도 잘 모르겠어 정말 <br>맘은 이미 Yes <br>내가 계속 웃잖아 Hey <br>ELRIS Here I am <br>우리들의 처음을 난 잊지 않을게 <br>이 바람 이 향기 우리 사이에 온도까지 <br>추운 날들을 딛고 이제 막 핀 꽃들처럼 <br>내 꿈과 내 맘을 <br>더 깊이깊이 그대와 피우고 싶어 <br>Yes Here we are 우린 <br>Yes Here we are <br>]]></content><category term="엘리스 (ELRIS)" label="엘리스 (ELRIS)"/><category term="우리 처음" label="우리 처음"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엘리스_ELRIS/Searching_for_ELRIS_Intro/</id><title>엘리스 (ELRIS) - Searching for ELRIS (Intro) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:54:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:54:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%98%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%A4_ELRIS/Searching_for_ELRIS_Intro/" title="엘리스 (ELRIS) - Searching for ELRIS (Intro) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ELRIS <br>햇살이 눈부시게 비추던 날 <br>나른한 기지개를 쭉 펴고 <br>소근소근 나누는 대화처럼 <br>부드러운 바람결을 따라 <br>하늘에 떠오르는 구름처럼 <br>피어나는 다섯 개 꽃송이 <br>알아요 반짝거리는 이 순간 <br>영원히 빛나게 할 거야 <br>나의 ELRIS를 찾아서 <br>Searching for ELRIS <br>]]></content><category term="엘리스 (ELRIS)" label="엘리스 (ELRIS)"/><category term="Searching for ELRIS (Intro)" label="Searching for ELRIS (Intro)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JBull/Call_Me_Just_Do_Eat/</id><title>J.Bull - Call Me (Just Do Eat) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:55:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:55:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JBull/Call_Me_Just_Do_Eat/" title="J.Bull - Call Me (Just Do Eat) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[just do eat 내 요리를 즐겨봐 <br>죽여줄테니 어서 내게 call me now <br>빨리 내게 전활 걸어 뭐가 고민이야 <br>시간 아까워 어서 어서 call me now <br>just do eat 눈치 보지말라고 <br>go call me call me call me <br>어서 내게 전활 걸어 뭐가 고민이야 <br>시간 아까워 어서 어서 call me now <br>oh yeah big hommies <br>오늘은 어디로 내 폰으로 지금 걸어 <br>돈없는 새끼도 뜨거운 <br>holliday 싹 다 불러 모아 <br>강남 이태원 홍대든 어디든지 간에 <br>call me now 내가 가는 곳이 노다지 <br>pepsi와는 완전히 다른 coca cola지 <br>유사품에 주의해 여전히 잘있지 난 <br>진짜는 세월이 변해도 fuck original <br>오늘따라 i'm so high 흘러넘쳐 <br>오해는 휴지통에 do not 대마초 <br>본질이 뭔지 느낀 다음에 <br>거품을 걷어내야돼 you know mean <br>이건 진짜배기야 westside <br>너도 모르게 원하게 되지 bulltime <br>이제 원하는 것들 다 거리를 좁혀가 <br>문제는 삼지않어 it's goin down <br>just do eat <br>내 요리를 즐겨봐 죽여줄테니 <br>어서 내게 call me now <br>빨리 내게 전활 걸어 뭐가 고민이야 <br>시간 아까워 어서 어서 call me now <br>just do eat 눈치 보지말라고 <br>go call me call me call me <br>어서 내게 전활 걸어 뭐가 고민이야 <br>시간 아까워 어서 어서 call me now <br>Today is a good day uh <br>친한척 해도 돼 곱게 yeah <br>난 부드러운 면도 있어 Like Pasta <br>내게 밀당은 하지마 끊어질테니까 <br>나이를 먹어도 내 감수성은 22 <br>시골서 눈 떴지만 이제는 마포구에 <br>창문 넘어로 한강이 보이진 않아도 <br>생각보다 좋은 곳에 있어 알아둬 <br>여기는 뜨거워 캘리는 아니지만 <br>자신감이 중요해 뱃살도 가리지마 <br>준비는 나에게 맡겨 <br>다 party with ma <br>Champange just dunkin 말리지마 <br>뻔한건 영어로 해도 no fun <br>변화를 즐겨 ay 고집불통 꼰대는 <br>재수없지 수시붙은 고딩 <br>겁없이 들이대 uh just ballin <br>just do eat 내 요리를 즐겨봐 <br>죽여줄테니 어서 내게 call me now <br>빨리 내게 전활 걸어 뭐가 고민이야 <br>시간 아까워 어서 어서 call me now <br>just do eat 눈치 보지말라고 <br>go call me call me call me <br>어서 내게 전활 걸어 뭐가 고민이야 <br>시간 아까워 어서 어서 call me now <br>내가 가는 곳이 노다지 <br>밤새도록 달리고 나면 좋은 아침 <br>어차피 자도 매일매일 피곤하지 <br>errday my birthday call me call me <br>내가 가는 곳이 노다지 <br>밤새도록 달리고 나면 좋은 아침 <br>어차피 자도 매일매일 피곤하지 <br>errday my birthday call me call me <br>just do eat 내 요리를 즐겨봐 <br>죽여줄테니 어서 내게 call me now <br>빨리 내게 전활 걸어 뭐가 고민이야 <br>시간 아까워 어서 어서 call me now <br>just do eat 눈치 보지말라고 <br>go call me call me call me <br>어서 내게 전활 걸어 뭐가 고민이야 <br>시간 아까워 어서 어서 call me now <br>]]></content><category term="J.Bull" label="J.Bull"/><category term="Call Me (Just Do Eat)" label="Call Me (Just Do Eat)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/려유/종이배/</id><title>려유 - 종이배 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:58:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:58:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%A4%EC%9C%A0/%EC%A2%85%EC%9D%B4%EB%B0%B0/" title="려유 - 종이배 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흐르는 시간에 내 종이배를 <br>그대에게 띄우리 <br>그 배 위에 내 마음 실어 <br>그대에게 보내리 <br>바람 타고 흘러가며 <br>아픈 기억 날려버리고 <br>밤하늘의 눈이 부신 <br>별과 같은 그대와 함께 <br>이렇게 그대와 저 바다 위로 <br>이 세상을 넘어 저 하늘 위로 <br>내 마음이 머무는 <br>저 작은 배 위에서 <br>Let’s just fall in love <br>이렇게 그대와 무지개 위로 <br>이 시간을 넘어 영원히 함께 <br>내 마음이 머무는 <br>저 작은 배 위에서 <br>Let’s just fall in love <br>바람 타고 흘러가며 <br>아픈 기억 날려버리고 <br>밤하늘의 눈이 부신 <br>별과 같은 그대와 함께 <br>이렇게 그대와 저 바다 위로 <br>이 세상을 넘어 저 하늘 위로 <br>내 마음이 머무는 <br>저 작은 배 위에서 <br>Let’s just fall in love <br>이렇게 그대와 무지개 위로 <br>이 시간을 넘어 영원히 함께 <br>내 마음이 머무는 <br>저 작은 배 위에서 <br>Let’s just fall in love <br>]]></content><category term="려유" label="려유"/><category term="종이배" label="종이배"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트리탑스/all4one/</id><title>트리탑스 - all4one - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:58:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:58:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AC%ED%83%91%EC%8A%A4/all4one/" title="트리탑스 - all4one - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[tonight i don't wanna be alone <br>and a thought just crossed my mind <br>that you might be the same with me <br>there's days <br>when we're falling down <br>and pressure is on our way <br>then baby who do you hold on to <br>so i made up my mind to give you <br>more than cheer up <br>let me let you know how I feel <br>remember <br>when you're down <br>and falling deep inside <br>when pain is all around <br>I will be the one to hold you <br>even when everyone <br>is trying to blame on you <br>and has no faith within you <br>maybe you're not alone <br>I will be there on your side <br>I could always make you smile <br>and I will ease your mind <br>I'll always be <br>your friend remember <br>even if there is no one <br>there to dry your tears <br>I will be the one to do for you <br>just rely and hold my hand <br>we can make it through the night <br>for you and I <br>tonight the stars <br>are shining bright <br>and the wind whisper to you <br>but you can't even feel they do <br>if I could do something for you <br>I will to do it all <br>but baby you're <br>just gonna say it's alright <br>so i made up my mind to give you <br>more than cheer up <br>let me let you know how I feel <br>when you're down <br>and falling deep inside <br>when pain is all around <br>I will be the one to hold you <br>even when everyone <br>is trying to blame on you <br>and has no faith within you <br>maybe you're not alone <br>I will be there on your side <br>I could always make you smile <br>and I will ease your mind <br>I'll always be <br>your friend remember <br>even if there is no one <br>there to dry your tears <br>I will be the one to do for you <br>just rely and hold my hand <br>we can make it through the night <br>for you and I <br>you might not understand <br>what I really mean <br>but there's nothing <br>that I wouldn't do <br>When hope has lost its senses <br>And fear is own your way <br>Take my hand and feel my heart <br>I'll always be there for you <br>When you cry <br>and need somebody's love <br>When you're left all alone <br>i'll be the one to hold you <br>even when everyone <br>is trying to blame on you <br>and has no faith within you <br>maybe you're not alone <br>I will be there on your side <br>I could always make you smile <br>and I will ease your mind <br>I'll always be <br>your friend remember <br>even if there is no one <br>there to dry your tears <br>I will be the one to do for you <br>just rely and hold my hand <br>we can make it through the night <br>for you and I <br>]]></content><category term="트리탑스" label="트리탑스"/><category term="all4one" label="all4one"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/허밍웨이/처음부터_다시_My_destiny_Feat_유화/</id><title>허밍웨이 - 처음부터 다시 (My destiny) (Feat. 유화) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:58:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:58:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%88%EB%B0%8D%EC%9B%A8%EC%9D%B4/%EC%B2%98%EC%9D%8C%EB%B6%80%ED%84%B0_%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C_My_destiny_Feat_%EC%9C%A0%ED%99%94/" title="허밍웨이 - 처음부터 다시 (My destiny) (Feat. 유화) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 잠들었던 그 자린 아직 <br>너의 온기와 <br>따스했던 네 토닥거림과 <br>웃어주던 네 미소까지 <br>모든 게 사라져 <br>믿을 수 없는 나의 현실과 <br>어색했던 전화목소리와 <br>웃어주려던 네 거짓까지 <br>되돌아 갈순 없겠지만 <br>단 한번 볼 수 있다면 <br>내 마음속엔 이미 너는 없다고 <br>괜한 얘기하며 괜찮다고 <br>그런 말조차 다시는 <br>하지 않았겠지 우 <br>익숙해져 버린 <br>믿을 수 없는 나의 일상에 <br>잊고 있었던 네 사진들과 <br>숨어 버렸던 내 마음까지 <br>되돌아 갈순 없겠지만 <br>단 한번 볼 수 있다면 <br>내 마음속엔 이미 너는 없다고 <br>괜한 얘기하며 괜찮다고 <br>그런 말조차 다시는 <br>하지 않았겠지 우 <br>되돌아 갈순 없겠지만 <br>단 한번 볼 수 있다면 <br>되돌아 갈순 없겠지만 <br>단 한번 볼 수 있다면 <br>내 마음속엔 이미 너는 없다고 <br>괜한 얘기하며 괜찮다고 <br>그런 말조차 다시는 <br>하지 않았겠지 예 <br>그런 말조차 않았겠지 <br>]]></content><category term="허밍웨이" label="허밍웨이"/><category term="처음부터 다시 (My destiny) (Feat. 유화)" label="처음부터 다시 (My destiny) (Feat. 유화)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/허밍웨이/처음부터_다시_My_destiny_Feat_재필/</id><title>허밍웨이 - 처음부터 다시 (My destiny) (Feat. 재필) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:58:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:58:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%88%EB%B0%8D%EC%9B%A8%EC%9D%B4/%EC%B2%98%EC%9D%8C%EB%B6%80%ED%84%B0_%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C_My_destiny_Feat_%EC%9E%AC%ED%95%84/" title="허밍웨이 - 처음부터 다시 (My destiny) (Feat. 재필) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 잠들었던 <br>그 자린 아직 너의 온기와 <br>따스했던 네 토닥거림과 <br>웃어주던 네 미소까지 <br>모든 게 사라져 <br>믿을 수 없는 나의 현실과 <br>어색했던 전화목소리와 <br>웃어주려던 네 거짓까지 <br>되돌아 갈 순 없겠지만 <br>단 한번 볼 수 있다면 <br>내 마음속엔 이미 너는 없다고 <br>괜한 얘기하며 괜찮다고 <br>그런 말조차 <br>다시는 하지 않았겠지 우 <br>익숙해져버린 <br>믿을 수 없는 나의 일상에 <br>잊고 있었던 네 사진들과 <br>숨어 버렸던 내 마음까지 <br>되돌아 갈 순 없겠지만 <br>단 한번 볼 수 있다면 <br>내 마음속엔 이미 너는 없다고 <br>괜한 얘기하며 괜찮다고 <br>그런 말조차 <br>다시는 하지 않았겠지 우 <br>되돌아 갈 순 없겠지만 <br>단 한번 볼 수 있다면 <br>되돌아 갈 순 없겠지만 <br>단 한번 볼 수 있다면 <br>내 마음속엔 이미 너는 없다고 <br>괜한 얘기하며 괜찮다고 <br>그런 말조차 <br>다시는 하지 않았겠지 우 <br>그런 말조차 않았겠지 <br>]]></content><category term="허밍웨이" label="허밍웨이"/><category term="처음부터 다시 (My destiny) (Feat. 재필)" label="처음부터 다시 (My destiny) (Feat. 재필)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스웨덴세탁소/그대는/</id><title>스웨덴세탁소 - 그대는 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:58:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:58:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%EC%9B%A8%EB%8D%B4%EC%84%B8%ED%83%81%EC%86%8C/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%8A%94/" title="스웨덴세탁소 - 그대는 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[He's like a wind <br>He's like a snowflake <br>닿기만 해도 사라지네 <br>He's like a moon <br>He's like a flower <br>바라만 봐도 벅차요 <br>그대는 말이 없어도 <br>그냥 아름다워요 <br>아마 어떤 말을 해도 <br>다 사랑스럽겠죠 <br>사랑은 이렇게 어지럽게 <br>향기로운가 봐요 <br>그대는 그대는 <br>새하얀 구름을 담은 <br>5월의 저 하늘 같아요 <br>모두의 사랑을 담은 <br>12월의 캐럴 같아요 <br>그대는 그대는 그대는 그대는 <br>여름밤 꿀처럼 불어오는 <br>바람 같아요 <br>가을밤 꿈처럼 들려오는 <br>노래 같아요 <br>그대는 그대는 그대는 그대는 <br>]]></content><category term="스웨덴세탁소" label="스웨덴세탁소"/><category term="그대는" label="그대는"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스웨덴세탁소/여름밤/</id><title>스웨덴세탁소 - 여름밤 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%EC%9B%A8%EB%8D%B4%EC%84%B8%ED%83%81%EC%86%8C/%EC%97%AC%EB%A6%84%EB%B0%A4/" title="스웨덴세탁소 - 여름밤 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh I wish I knew love like that <br>너는 가만히 누운 채 <br>잠꼬대처럼 조용히 <br>읊조리듯 말을 해 <br>사라지지 마 오늘만은 <br>맞닿은 손을 꼭 쥐고서 <br>쏟아질 것 같은 맘을 숨기지 못해 <br>눈을 감았던 여름밤 <br>소리도 없는 말들이 <br>가득 담겨진 두 눈을 <br>내게 내려줘 어디든 <br>곁에 있는 듯 감싸줘 <br>사라지지 마 오늘만은 <br>맞닿은 손을 꼭 쥐고서 <br>쏟아질 것 같은 맘을 숨기지 못해 <br>내게 안겨줘 오늘만은 <br>맞닿은 손을 꼭 쥐고서 <br>쏟아질 것 같은 맘을 숨기지 못해 <br>눈을 감았던 그 밤에 <br>Summer Bell <br>Summer Bell <br>Summer Bell <br>Summer Bell <br>]]></content><category term="스웨덴세탁소" label="스웨덴세탁소"/><category term="여름밤" label="여름밤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/AtoZ/Dark_Lady_Feat_YarrNoLzA/</id><title>AtoZ - Dark Lady (Feat. Yarr(NoLzA)) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/AtoZ/Dark_Lady_Feat_YarrNoLzA/" title="AtoZ - Dark Lady (Feat. Yarr(NoLzA)) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈이 마주친 지금 이순간 <br>나의 심장은 run away <br>너의 눈빛에 젖어드는 걸 <br>외로운밤 나 나 나 나를 비춰줘 <br>Electric Bounce bounce <br>널 위한 큐피트 <br>Bounce bounce 리듬에 Lay-back <br>눈이 부신 그녀는 가면을 쓴 채 <br>베일속에 가려진걸 <br>let me touch down <br>Elastic 리듬에 파고드는 빛 <br>Attention 처음 본 그 순간 <br>wake up wake up <br>Lalalala Look at me girls girls <br>빠져드는 이 순간 dream come true <br>I like a Treasure <br>Lalalala 강렬한 Touch <br>touch touch 최면에 걸린듯 <br>Loose control <br>중독되는 그 매력에 Lady <br>더 더 빠져드는 그댄 Lady <br>어둠속 화려한 이밤에 Baby <br>더 더 강렬한 리듬에 Lay-back <br>눈이 마주친 지금 이 순간 <br>나의 심장은 run away <br>매끈한 line 완벽한 balance <br>환상적인 rythem에 <br>단 하룻밤 꿈이라면 <br>i wanna feel inside your body <br>비처럼 쏟아지는 별 하얗게 불태워 <br>구름 사이로 달빛이 흘러 <br>i dream a beautiful girl <br>Lalalala Look at me girls girls <br>빠져드는 이 순간 dream come true <br>I like a Treasure <br>Lalalala 강렬한 Touch <br>touch touch 최면에 걸린듯 <br>Loose control <br>중독되는 그 매력에 Lady <br>더 더 빠져드는 그댄 Lady <br>어둠속 화려한 이밤에 Baby <br>더 더 강렬한 리듬에 Lay-back <br>가슴이 찌릿찌릿 아파오잖아 <br>터질 것 같은 heart break all way <br>날 깨워 Break up <br>너와의 Shake up 나를 비추는 걸 <br>Electric 들어와 내 품으로 <br>hot deep inside 이곳 <br>Bounce bounce you got me <br>falling you you got me fallihg <br>널 위한 큐피트 너와 나 그곳으로 <br>heven in the awesome door <br>Bounce bounce let me touch <br>down 리듬에 Lay-back <br>중독되는 그 매력에 Lady <br>더 더 빠져드는 그댄 Lady <br>어둠속 화려한 이밤에 Baby <br>더 더 강렬한 리듬에 Lay-back <br>]]></content><category term="AtoZ" label="AtoZ"/><category term="Dark Lady (Feat. Yarr(NoLzA))" label="Dark Lady (Feat. Yarr(NoLzA))"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Homemadesoul/Open/</id><title>Homemadesoul - Open - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Homemadesoul/Open/" title="Homemadesoul - Open - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This feeling that’s inside me girl <br>Let you know where u stand in my world <br>U got goin crazy <br>Girl I'd have all ur babies <br>You got me open <br>This life is doping, yeah <br><br>From that first night till this very day <br>You've intrigued me in every single way <br>It's shut up in my bones <br>I got to let it out <br>It makes me scream and shout, scream shout <br><br>I'm so open to you baby, <br>I'm gon let you walk right in walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk <br>I'm so open to you baby, <br>I'm gon let you walk right in walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk <br><br>There's no end to the things that I'm willing to do for you <br>Even though you got everything you need <br>My love is guaranteed <br>This love is real <br>You can bank on it <br>Pay your bills on it <br>Get your credit on it <br><br>I'm like your debit card <br>Just swipe me <br>Girl you funds run deep with me <br><br>I'm so open to you baby, <br>I'm gon let you walk right in walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk <br>I'm so open to you baby, <br>I'm gon let you walk right in walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk <br><br>Can you find this love <br>I can give you this love <br>Open up your love <br><br>I'm so open to you baby, <br>I'm gon let you walk right in walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk <br>I'm so open to you baby, <br>I'm gon let you walk right in walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk walk right in <br>walk walk <br>I'm so open to you baby <br>I'm so open to you baby]]></content><category term="Homemadesoul" label="Homemadesoul"/><category term="Open" label="Open"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Raquel_Rodriguez/Baby_Its_You/</id><title>Raquel Rodriguez - (Baby) It`s You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Raquel_Rodriguez/Baby_Its_You/" title="Raquel Rodriguez - (Baby) It`s You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can't give you up <br>So I'll take you down if you leave <br>Cause I can't get enough <br>You're the reason why I can breathe <br>So don't you dare tell me I'd <br>make better use of my time, <br>that's not your call it's mine. <br>So how could you walk out <br>and say that it's easy <br>I let down my guard <br>and gave you my heart <br>I need you to see that <br>I'm not that girl that always needs somebody. <br>I'm not that girl that always needs a hand <br>but if i do, oh if I do <br><br>then Baby, it's you. <br>then Baby, it's you. <br>I need you. <br>then Baby, it's you. <br><br>One more night with you <br>could be all I need <br>but I've got to show you <br>what you can't already, already see <br>Might be too young to know what's best <br>but sugar I will never rest until you're mine <br>always mine. <br>I was naive to <br>make you love too soon <br>I let down my guard <br>gave you my heart <br>I need you to see that <br>I'm not that girl that always needs somebody. <br>I'm not that girl that always needs a hand <br>but if i do, oh if I do <br><br>then Baby, it's you. <br>then Baby, it's you. <br>I need you. <br>then Baby, it's you. <br><br>I'm not that girl that always needs somebody. <br>I'm not that girl that always needs a hand <br>but if i do, oh if I do <br><br>then Baby, it's you. <br>then Baby, it's you. <br>I need you. <br>then Baby, it's you. <br>then Baby, it's you. <br>I need you. <br>then Baby, it's you.]]></content><category term="Raquel Rodriguez" label="Raquel Rodriguez"/><category term="(Baby) It`s You" label="(Baby) It`s You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matt_Boylan-Smith/Kissing_Games/</id><title>Matt Boylan-Smith - Kissing Games - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matt_Boylan-Smith/Kissing_Games/" title="Matt Boylan-Smith - Kissing Games - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here I go... <br>She said I don't know where to go but i'll meet your there, <br>Can I see you at the place we used to be and there I go.. <br>See my pretty haired girl walking down that hill <br>Watch her smile as she glances right over her shoulder, <br>See the thrill as I get, chased and away from the boys and the girls. <br><br>We play kissing Games, <br>Pretend to run away, <br>I let you catch me if you can and i'lll never be happier, <br>Catch me and you kiss me and i'll never be happier, ohhh <br>There I go <br><br>Her freckles speckled 'cross her face, just like they were raindrops I know, <br>She'd have grass stains on her feet runnin' to the place we'd I know-oh <br><br>We play kissing Games, <br>Pretend to run away, <br>I let you catch me if you can and i'lll never be happier, <br>Catch me and you kiss me and i'll never be happier, ohhh <br>There I go <br><br>I don't know how the bass drum goes but it's like my heartbeat <br>I don't know how the bass drum goes but it's like my heartbeat <br>I don't know how the bass drum goes but it's like my heartbeat <br>I don't know how the bass drum goes but it's like my heartbeat <br><br>We play kissing Games, <br>Pretend to run away, <br>I let you catch me if you can and i'lll never be happier, <br>Catch me and you kiss me and i'll never be happier, ohhh <br>There I go <br><br>We play kissing Games, <br>Pretend to run away, <br>I let you catch me if you can and i'lll never be happier, <br>Catch me and you kiss me and i'll never be happier, ohhh <br>There I go]]></content><category term="Matt Boylan-Smith" label="Matt Boylan-Smith"/><category term="Kissing Games" label="Kissing Games"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeff_Bernat/Heaven_Sent_Single_Ver/</id><title>Jeff Bernat - Heaven Sent (Single Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeff_Bernat/Heaven_Sent_Single_Ver/" title="Jeff Bernat - Heaven Sent (Single Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[see i know i could be busy <br>in the times i get distracted to <br>i forget the part i forget the job but <br>i promise i don't forget you <br><br>i know you have a past (i have one too) <br>scars and stuff beginning (all the stupid fellows) <br>play with your mind play with your soul <br>may lose your hope but love <br><br>god gave me your precious heart <br>and i'm far away from being perfect <br>but i'll heal all your battle scars and be your armor <br>cuz darling i swear that you worth it <br><br>god gave me your precious heart <br>and i'm far away from being perfect <br>but i'll heal all your battle scars and be your armor <br>cuz being your man is so worth it <br><br>see i know we still got time <br>and that time you have your a guard or two (please don't be scared) <br>but believe me girl i ain't the type of man of break your heart <br>like some other fools did ya <br><br>mama told me to respect the lady <br>cause of something that man should do <br>so i've always been a patient boy <br>and never been the type to pressure you <br><br>god gave me your precious heart <br>and i'm far away from being perfect <br>but i'll heal all your battle scars <br>and be your armor <br>cuz darling i swear that you worth it <br><br>i will protect her <br>and always hold her close to me <br>even though they try use them may light ahead <br>i will love her unconditionally <br><br>god gave me your precious heart <br>and i'm far away from being perfect <br>but i'll heal all your battle scars and be your armor <br>cuz darling i swear that you worth it <br><br>god gave me your precious heart <br>and i'm far away from being perfect <br>but i'll heal all your battle scars and be your armor <br>cuz being your man is so worth it <br><br>god gave me your precious heart <br>and i'm far away from being perfect <br>but i'll heal all your battle scars and be your armor <br>cuz darling i swear that you worth it]]></content><category term="Jeff Bernat" label="Jeff Bernat"/><category term="Heaven Sent (Single Ver.)" label="Heaven Sent (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CRSB/Romance/</id><title>CRSB - Romance - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CRSB/Romance/" title="CRSB - Romance - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ <br>Girl I could wait <br>a million years <br>for you to fall in love <br>And I would do <br>anything for you <br>without a reason just because <br><br>So listen baby <br>and listen clear to me <br>Cause I want you now <br>more than ever <br>and I need to have you near <br><br>So give it to me <br>Cause I can't breathe without you <br>Give it to me <br>Cause I can't live without you <br>Give it to me <br>Cause you're my baby you're my love you're my heart <br><br>So give it to me <br>Cause I can't breathe without you <br>Give it to me <br>Cause I can't live without you <br>Give it to me <br>Cause you're my baby you're my love you're my heart <br><br>I would cross the 7 seas <br>just for you to be with me <br>and I will take you past the point of endless love <br>girl don't give up <br>and I will love you more and more than yesterday oh baby <br><br>So listen baby <br>listen clear to me <br>Cause I want you now <br>More than ever <br>and I need to have you here <br><br>Give it to me <br>Cause I can't breathe without you <br>Give it to me <br>Cause I can't live without you <br>Give it to me <br>Cause you're my baby you're my love you're my heart <br><br>Give it to me <br>Cause I can't breathe without you <br>Give it to me <br>Cause I can't live without you <br>Give it to me <br>Cause you're my baby you're my heart]]></content><category term="CRSB" label="CRSB"/><category term="Romance" label="Romance"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tim_Atlas/Lyla/</id><title>Tim Atlas - Lyla - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tim_Atlas/Lyla/" title="Tim Atlas - Lyla - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a little crazy that <br>My heart starts beating twice as fast <br>Slow motion in my crazy head <br>Eventually speeds up again <br>The story as by until the end <br><br>You turn my pages over again <br>You stay until the very end <br>Can’t wait to see what happens next next <br>Lyla lyla lyla <br><br>It’s a little crazy that <br>All her passion outweighed sass <br>Who knew that you would be the key <br>To open doors that set her free <br><br>You turn my pages over again <br>You stay until the very end <br>Can’t wait to see what happens next next <br>Lyla lyla lyla <br><br>If love can make us move, <br>I’m runnin ‘cause of you <br><br>You turn my pages over again <br>You stay until the very end <br>Can’t wait to see what happens next next <br>Lyla lyla lyla]]></content><category term="Tim Atlas" label="Tim Atlas"/><category term="Lyla" label="Lyla"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Steptones/Eleanor_Album_Ver/</id><title>The Steptones - Eleanor (Album Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Steptones/Eleanor_Album_Ver/" title="The Steptones - Eleanor (Album Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So I kept those notes and letters you left in my bed <br>And I kept those photographs they’re safe inside my head <br>While you were here with me <br>You gave me everything, and you could set me free my eleanor <br><br>But once you took your leave yeah everything went grey <br>And I’m scared to go outside for fear of a new day <br>Oh once was not enough <br>I promise that above, I’ll give you all my love my Eleanor <br><br>Eleanor my dear, the words just aren’t so clear <br>Eleanor my dear, you take me back from here <br>Eleanor my dear, the words just aren’t so clear <br>Eleanor, Eleanor <br><br>So besides the things you said and you had me believe <br>When you came and took my hand it brought me to my knees <br>But you said we were friends <br>I’d do it all again, someday you’ll realise when i’m really gone <br><br>Eleanor my dear, the words just aren’t so clear <br>Eleanor my dear, you take me back from here <br>Eleanor my dear, the words just aren’t so clear <br>Eleanor, Eleanor <br><br>Eleanor my dear, the words just aren’t so clear <br>Eleanor my dear, you take me back from here <br>Eleanor my dear, the words just aren’t so clear <br>Eleanor, Eleanor <br><br>Eleanor my dear, the words just aren’t so clear <br>Eleanor my dear, you take me back from here <br>Eleanor my dear, the words just aren’t so clear <br>Eleanor, Eleanor]]></content><category term="The Steptones" label="The Steptones"/><category term="Eleanor (Album Ver.)" label="Eleanor (Album Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan_Mitchell_Grey/Inamorata/</id><title>Ryan Mitchell Grey - Inamorata - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan_Mitchell_Grey/Inamorata/" title="Ryan Mitchell Grey - Inamorata - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Holding onto hope <br>Five floors beneath the atmosphere <br>Seven hours til we land <br>Then all id have would be a souvenir <br>Of the sand we bottled up <br>On the other side of the pacific ocean <br><br>Speaking softly of our thoughts <br>Im seein you for who you really are <br>And if this isn't what you want <br>Id be a fool cause you have drawn me in <br>Now im drowning <br>Oo save me <br><br>Well I, can't find a thing wrong with your lovin <br>And I know, that we've got a long road down <br>My baby baby I promise my soul is set on you <br>A deep dive in a newfangled saga <br>Inamorata <br><br>Strollin up the streets <br>Of the city i grew up in <br>With you holding onto me <br>Your eyes reflect my happiness <br>And for a second all the skyscrapers surrounding <br>Fell under the clouds beneath our feet <br><br>Feeling right at home <br>In the nest you rest your head at <br>I could never feel alone <br>With you right here by my side <br>And though a few thousand <br>Miles away oo babe you have saved me <br><br>Well I, can't find a thing wrong with your lovin <br>And I know, that we've got a long road down <br>My baby baby I promise my soul is set on you <br>A deep dive in a newfangled saga <br>Inamorata <br><br>I swore into those eyes <br>Everything I felt at that instant baby <br>Oh I swore to you that I knew <br>I knew, I knew, I knew <br>Oh, baby <br><br>Well I, can't find a thing wrong with your lovin <br>And I know, that we've got a long road down <br>My baby baby I promise my soul is set on you <br>A deep dive in a newfangled saga <br>Inamorata <br><br>Holding onto hope <br>Five floors beneath the atmosphere]]></content><category term="Ryan Mitchell Grey" label="Ryan Mitchell Grey"/><category term="Inamorata" label="Inamorata"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesse_Barrera/Stay_With_Me_Feat_Melissa_Polinar/</id><title>Jesse Barrera - Stay With Me (Feat. Melissa Polinar) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesse_Barrera/Stay_With_Me_Feat_Melissa_Polinar/" title="Jesse Barrera - Stay With Me (Feat. Melissa Polinar) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I think everybody knows <br>When they've got something right <br>I think everybody feels it <br>When they don't even try <br><br>But I got lucky enough to find you <br>And so much of me to give <br><br>I can't ever find <br>The words to say <br>You changed my life <br>In ways that I can't explain <br>How lost I was <br>Don't need no one <br>But you <br><br>Can you stay, stay, stay with me? <br><br>I think that everybody hurts <br>A little bit everyday <br>I think that everybody needs somebody <br>To never ever turn away <br><br>But I got lucky enough to find you <br>And so much of me to give <br><br>I can't ever find <br>The words to say <br>You changed my life <br>In ways that I can't explain <br>How lost I was <br>Don't need no one <br>But you <br><br>Can you stay, stay, stay with me <br><br>And it's you <br>I never thought we'd <br>Find each other <br>You <br>Can you stay with me <br>I see life and love in technicolor <br>Never want to find another <br><br>I can't ever find <br>The words to say <br>You changed my life <br>In ways that I can't explain <br>How lost I was <br>Don't need no one <br>But you <br><br>Can you stay, stay, stay with me?]]></content><category term="Jesse Barrera" label="Jesse Barrera"/><category term="Stay With Me (Feat. Melissa Polinar)" label="Stay With Me (Feat. Melissa Polinar)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Damian_Yonge/Swing_Of_Your_Kiss/</id><title>Damian Yonge - Swing Of Your Kiss - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Damian_Yonge/Swing_Of_Your_Kiss/" title="Damian Yonge - Swing Of Your Kiss - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve got something so honest <br>In your eyes I can’t help but trust <br>A smile that makes me forget <br>About when and where delusion starts <br>And why the rhythm of my heart <br>Gets thrown off by the swing of your kiss <br>And I can’t help but feel so in love <br>When you pretend to walk away <br>And I’ll be right behind you <br>To call your bluff <br>I got the right moves to play your game <br><br>Just close your eyes and listen <br>To the beating of this daring heart <br><br>Let’s slow dance and see the sights <br>Midnight glow of the city lights <br>Let’s hold hands, crisscross our fingers <br>Lie on the street like crazy lovers <br>I’ve caught the swing of your kiss <br><br>Well there’s no better question <br>Than one with a yes or no <br>Answer in between the lines <br>No mixed message in your body language <br>When you’re fluent in the same as mine <br>And I can’t help but feel so in love <br>When you play hide and seek in my arms <br>And you can stay there <br>For as long as you’d like <br>There’s no cause for alarm <br><br>Let’s slow dance and see the sights <br>Midnight glow of the city lights <br>Let’s hold hands, crisscross our fingers <br>Lie on the street like crazy lovers <br>I’ve caught the swing of your… <br><br>…Kiss me now <br>Cuz I never thought I’d be the one <br>To count out every beat <br>But damn it girl you know how to have fun <br>You got me swinging with my two left feet <br>Yeah you do <br>Yeah you do <br>Yeah you do <br>Oh oh oh <br><br>Let’s slow dance and see the sights <br>Midnight glow of the city lights <br>Let’s hold hands, crisscross our fingers <br>Lie on the street like crazy lovers <br>I’ve caught the swing of your… <br>…kiss me now, cuz it’s now or never <br>And baby you’ve got me swinging <br>To your sweet, sweet kiss]]></content><category term="Damian Yonge" label="Damian Yonge"/><category term="Swing Of Your Kiss" label="Swing Of Your Kiss"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Hues/Meet_Me_at_Midnight/</id><title>The Hues - Meet Me at Midnight - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Hues/Meet_Me_at_Midnight/" title="The Hues - Meet Me at Midnight - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We meet every Tuesday <br>At the little place on Broadway <br>While you stir your coffee <br>I count the freckles on your cheek <br>You tell me about your weekend <br>Fighting with your boyfriend <br>Don’t know why you’re with him <br>He’ll never treat you right <br>I’m thinking if only you were mine, I’d say… <br><br>Meet me at midnight <br>We’ll catch some fireflies <br>And teach them how to write our names <br>Into the night sky <br>Under the bright lights <br>I’m gonna love you til’ the mornin’ comes <br>Meet me when the day is done <br>Meet me at midnight <br><br>Lately I’ve been dreaming <br>About you and I at eighteen <br>Dancing in the kitchen <br>We got drunk on your parents whiskey <br>I found that old picture <br>Taken after high school <br>That summer by the river <br>I should’ve kissed you, right <br>I’m thinking if only you were mine, I’d say… <br><br>Meet me at midnight <br>We’ll catch some fireflies <br>And teach them how to write our names <br>Into the night sky <br>Under the bright lights <br>I’m gonna love you til’ the mornin’ comes <br>Meet me when the day is done <br><br>Meet me where we drew the line <br>Somewhere between you and I <br>And if I asked you to be mine <br><br>Would you meet me at midnight <br>We’ll catch some fireflies <br>And teach them how to write our names <br>Into the night sky <br>Under the bright lights <br>I promise you there we morning sun <br>I’m gonna love you til’ the mornin’ comes <br>futures meet me at midnight <br>Meet me at midnight <br>Would you meet me at midnight]]></content><category term="The Hues" label="The Hues"/><category term="Meet Me at Midnight" label="Meet Me at Midnight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Noah_Bartfield/Real_Love/</id><title>Noah Bartfield - Real Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Noah_Bartfield/Real_Love/" title="Noah Bartfield - Real Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You tell me when I’m not myself <br>You’re there to catch me when I fall <br>We go up, come down <br>Lose ourselves to be found <br>More than a daydream <br>More than a red bouquet <br>Open and weightless <br>Past our thrill of the chase <br>Real Love isn’t just skin in the dark <br>Real Love isn’t just a skip of the heart <br>It’s a deeper thing <br>It’s deeper <br>Maybe time will tell it all <br>But love can’t run until crawls <br>We fall short, reach out <br>Bring our feet to the ground <br>Sometime’s I hurt you <br>Sometime’s I pull away <br>Fragile but callused <br>You’ll forgive my mistakes <br>Real Love isn’t just skin in the dark <br>Real Love isn’t just a skip of the heart <br>It’s a deeper thing <br>It’s deeper <br>If the fruit of this old tree <br>Grows bittersweet <br>With too many seasons <br>Not enough reasons left to stay <br>I wish you well, I wish you well <br>While my tired heart swells <br>Real Love isn’t just skin in the dark <br>Real Love isn’t just a skip of the heart <br>It’s a deeper thing <br>It’s deeper]]></content><category term="Noah Bartfield" label="Noah Bartfield"/><category term="Real Love" label="Real Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Liz_Lawrence/Bathroom_Spoons/</id><title>Liz Lawrence - Bathroom Spoons - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Liz_Lawrence/Bathroom_Spoons/" title="Liz Lawrence - Bathroom Spoons - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It would be nice to roll away down this hill, <br>I guess we’ll take it day by day, <br>And we’ll see it, <br>I hope that you will be ok my dear, <br>there’s always time for better days around here, <br><br>Ahh… <br><br>I think your mind has run away without you, <br>and you’re seeing faces upside down in coffee spoons <br>but i know that you will be ok my dear, <br>there’s always time for better days around here, <br><br>Ahh…]]></content><category term="Liz Lawrence" label="Liz Lawrence"/><category term="Bathroom Spoons" label="Bathroom Spoons"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Avalon_Young/Atmosphere_Acoustic/</id><title>Avalon Young - Atmosphere (Acoustic) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Avalon_Young/Atmosphere_Acoustic/" title="Avalon Young - Atmosphere (Acoustic) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[we can escape this place <br>and we can go anywhere you want to <br>want to <br>first <br>we can hit outer space <br>from the moon to the milky way i'll show you <br>baby i know you <br>really need somebody who can change your state of mind <br>who can take you to a different place and time <br>and maybe you don't know it yet but i promise i can show you that <br>ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh <br>not even gonna say a thing <br>just gonna show you what i mean <br>and i'll prove <br>there's not a thing that i won't do <br>baby i just want you <br>to come with me to another galaxy <br>broke out the atmosphere <br>didnt think we'd make it here but look around <br>tell me how you're feeling now <br>'cause i feel like <br>everything feels just right <br>i'll show you <br>baby i know you <br>could really use somebody who can change your state of mind <br>who can take you even higher than cloud nine <br>and maybe you don't know it yet but i promise i can show you that <br>ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh <br>not even gonna say a thing <br>just gonna show you what i mean <br>and i'll prove <br>there's not a thing that i won't do <br>baby i just want you <br>to come with me to another galaxy <br>there's no gravity <br>everytime you step into my space <br>and when you put your hands on me <br>my mind is gone without a trace <br>got front row tickets to this picture perfect place <br>so don't let it go to waste no don't let it go to waste <br>ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh <br>not even gonna say a thing <br>just gonna show you what i mean <br>and i'll prove <br>there's not a thing that i won't do <br>baby i just want you <br>to come with me to another galaxy <br>come with me to another galaxy]]></content><category term="Avalon Young" label="Avalon Young"/><category term="Atmosphere (Acoustic)" label="Atmosphere (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phe_Reds/Lonely_Together/</id><title>Phe Reds - Lonely Together - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phe_Reds/Lonely_Together/" title="Phe Reds - Lonely Together - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Our separation may not be ideal <br>Only Amy truly knows how you feel. <br>Had to go my own way to better myself <br>And you can’t imagine lovin’ somebody else. <br><br>Girl every time you cry, I die inside. <br>Console in the fact that it makes us feel better <br>We’re lonely Together. <br><br>We’re lonely together (Lonely Together). <br>Lonely Together (Lonely Together). <br>Lonely Together (Lonely Together). <br>Lonely Together. <br><br>You can get so dramatic when I leave you alone <br>And with only so much comfort I can give when I’m gone. <br>You’re worried I’m bound to find someone new. <br>But I can’t leave behind all we’ve been through. No. <br><br>Girl every time you cry, I die inside <br>Console in the fact that it makes us feel better <br>We’re lonely Together <br><br>We’re lonely together (Lonely Together). <br>Lonely Together (Lonely Together). <br>Lonely Together (Lonely Together). <br>Lonely Together. <br><br>And you keep sayin’, we won’t make it <br>Accusations, I deviated from the plans we had made. <br>But no replacements, you’re my lady. <br>All I’m askin’ is for some patience <br>For your man, aw babe. <br><br>Girl every time you cry, I die inside. <br>Console in the fact that it makes us feel better <br>We’re lonely Together. <br><br>We’re lonely together (Lonely Together) <br>Lonely Together (Lonely Together) <br>Lonely Together (Lonely Together) <br>Lonely Together]]></content><category term="Phe Reds" label="Phe Reds"/><category term="Lonely Together" label="Lonely Together"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alvin_Ordonez/How_Much_You_Mean_To_Me/</id><title>Alvin Ordonez - How Much You Mean To Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alvin_Ordonez/How_Much_You_Mean_To_Me/" title="Alvin Ordonez - How Much You Mean To Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It’s sometimes crazy when you wait away <br>Like there’s no hope and nothing matters today <br>The city’s burning I must find a way to live <br>‘Til I can learn to forgive <br>But I don’t know I don’t know I don’t know <br>I don’t know if I can dig so deep <br>Anticipating the next time we will meet <br>I fear to find just what tomorrow will bring <br>But I pray it’s a better version of yesterday <br><br>And oh I miss those times <br>We would fall asleep while we were still on the line <br>All those times when we would talk about <br>How happy we would be <br>I still wish it were you and me <br>Because you got me twisted oh girl <br>I’m down on my knees <br>I’m beggin you <br>Oh I’m beggin you please <br>Will you stand by me <br>And I will whisper softly how much you mean to me <br><br>Her laugh her smile are the things that light up my day <br>Memories of her in my head still not fading away <br>Wish she’d stay say okay please don’t go away <br>Please don’t go away because <br>I find myself smiling every time I think of you <br>There’s risks I have to take I said this is our fate <br>This time let’s make things go our way <br><br>And oh I miss those times <br>We would fall asleep while we were still on the line <br>All those times when we would talk about <br>How happy we would be <br>I still wish it were you and me <br>Because you got me twisted oh girl <br>I’m down on my knees <br>I’m beggin you <br>Oh I’m beggin you please <br>Will you stand by me <br>And I will whisper softly how much you mean to me <br><br>You and me <br>You amaze me <br>Me without you oh baby that’s crazy <br>Won’t you come over and save me <br><br>And oh I miss those times <br>We would fall asleep while we were still on the line <br>All those times when we would talk about <br>How happy we would be <br>I still wish it were you and me <br>Because you got me twisted oh girl <br>I’m down on my knees <br>I’m beggin you <br>Oh I’m beggin you please <br>Will you stand by me <br>And I will whisper softly how much you mean to me]]></content><category term="Alvin Ordonez" label="Alvin Ordonez"/><category term="How Much You Mean To Me" label="How Much You Mean To Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/AJ_Rafael/She_Was_Mine_Feat_Jesse_Barrera/</id><title>AJ Rafael - She Was Mine (Feat. Jesse Barrera) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/AJ_Rafael/She_Was_Mine_Feat_Jesse_Barrera/" title="AJ Rafael - She Was Mine (Feat. Jesse Barrera) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So I hopped on a train, <br>Three in the afternoon, <br>I don't know when I'm coming back, <br>But I hope that it's soon, <br>See I never thought, never thought, <br>that I'd have to leave your side, your side. <br><br>It's only physically, <br>But know that you will be on my mind, <br>Twenty four hours at a time, <br>'Cause in my eyes you were mine, you were mine. <br><br>No matter where you go, <br>I won't be very far, <br>'Cause in my head I'll be right there where you are, <br>'Cause love has no distance baby, <br>Love has no distance baby <br>No, not when it comes to you and me. <br><br>See she wrote me a letter, <br>Said the weather wasn't better, <br>But she said that she was doing fine, <br>I wanna see you face to face, <br>That's what she wrote to me that day, <br>And I knew that it was all a sign. <br><br>So I wrote back with this song, <br>Promise it won't be too long, <br>Wanna make up for all our lost time, <br>'Cause in my eyes you were mine, you were mine. <br><br>No matter where you go, <br>I won't be very far, <br>'Cause in my head I'll be right there where you are, <br>'Cause love has no distance baby, <br>Love has no distance baby <br>No, not when it comes to you and me. <br><br>So I'm going through these boxes. <br>My life's gone off track. <br>'Cause it's been three years. <br>She hasn't written back. <br>But in my eyes. <br>She's still mine. <br><br>And I know it sounds so stupid, <br>To be waiting this long, <br>But I'm still in love and I know I'm not wrong, <br>'Cause in my eyes, <br>She was mine. <br><br>No matter where you go, <br>I won't be very far, <br>'Cause in my head I'll be right there where you are, <br>'Cause love has no distance baby, <br>Love has no distance baby <br>No, not when it comes to you and <br><br>No matter where you go, <br>I won't be very far, <br>'Cause in my head I'll be right there where you are, <br>'Cause love has no distance baby, <br>Love has no distance baby <br>No, not when it comes to you and me.]]></content><category term="AJ Rafael" label="AJ Rafael"/><category term="She Was Mine (Feat. Jesse Barrera)" label="She Was Mine (Feat. Jesse Barrera)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeremy_Passion/Lemonade/</id><title>Jeremy Passion - Lemonade - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeremy_Passion/Lemonade/" title="Jeremy Passion - Lemonade - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She's my sunshine in the rain <br>My tylenol when I'm in pain, yeah <br>Let me tell you what she means to me <br>Like a tall glass of Lemonade <br>When it's burning hot on summer days <br>She's exactly what I need <br><br>She's soothing like <br>The ocean rushing on the sand <br>She takes care of me baby <br>And she helps me be a better man <br>She's so beautiful <br>Sometimes I stop to close my eyes <br>She's exactly what I need <br><br>She's my smile when I'm feeling blue <br>She's my good night sleep when the day is through <br>Let me tell you what she means to me <br>(She's kinda like this) <br>Kinda like the feeling after your first kiss <br>Except that everyday she makes me feel like this <br>She's exactly what I need <br><br>She's soothing like <br>The ocean rushing on the sand <br>She takes care of me baby <br>And she helps me be a better man <br>She's so beautiful <br>Sometimes I stop to close my eyes <br>She's exactly what I need <br><br>She's soothing like <br>The ocean rushing on the sand <br>She takes care of me baby <br>And she helps me be a better man <br>She's so beautiful <br>Sometimes I stop to close my eyes <br>She's exactly what I need <br>She's exactly what I need]]></content><category term="Jeremy Passion" label="Jeremy Passion"/><category term="Lemonade" label="Lemonade"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Carreon/The_Simple_Things/</id><title>Michael Carreon - The Simple Things - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Carreon/The_Simple_Things/" title="Michael Carreon - The Simple Things - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And it's the simple things you do <br>I just can't get enough of you <br>It's that perfume that you wear <br>And the way you do your hair <br>That I love so much <br>And it's the simple things you say <br>And how in bed we play <br>It's the way you kiss my cheek <br>When you think that I'm asleep <br>I love it so much <br>I love you words I never say <br>Friends make fun <br>but I tell you everyday <br>Anyway lately you've been <br>getting me home safely <br>Wake up love the coffee <br>that you make me <br>Asking me how my night was <br>I like us <br>It's so easy and <br>we don't ever fight cause <br>You don't blow up my phone <br>When you're home alone assuming <br>That I'm doin' what a guy does <br>Trust with just the <br>right amount of lust <br>Even loved by my family that's a must <br>And fun everything we do me and you <br>My song comes on <br>and you dance and sing too <br>With the windows down like geez <br>We don't care <br>who's around or who sees <br>And everyone is jealous of my ride <br>Because you're sitting <br>in the passengers side <br>And It's the simple things you do <br>I just can't get enough of you <br>It's that perfume that you wear <br>And the way you do your hair <br>That I love so much <br>And it's the simple things you say <br>And how in bed we play <br>It's the way you kiss my cheek <br>When you think that I'm asleep <br>I love it so much <br>Everyday scrubbin' it lovin' it <br>Crusin' freeways in our PJs <br>'Cause that's the fun of it unless <br>You wear that pretty black dress <br>oh yes <br>Catch me in a suit <br>so I can look as good as you <br>But I don't oh well <br>With that smile that you wear so well <br>And the way that you cry in movies <br>Pass you the ball <br>and pass it back to me <br>Beers with the guys <br>Ain't no thing <br>It's your eyes and the simple things <br>That make this work like it should <br>When you rock my shirt <br>Oh you look so good <br>So take my hand and stay <br>as long as you can with the man <br>That tells all the jokes <br>only you understand <br>And I promise to be honest <br>if you promise to accomplish love <br>And it's the simple things you do <br>I just can't get enough of you <br>It's that perfume that you wear <br>And the way you do your hair <br>That I love so much <br>And it's the simple things you say <br>And how in bed we play <br>It's the way you kiss my cheek <br>When you think that I'm asleep <br>I love it so much <br>]]></content><category term="Michael Carreon" label="Michael Carreon"/><category term="The Simple Things" label="The Simple Things"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Albert_Posis/Serendipity/</id><title>Albert Posis - Serendipity - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:59:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:59:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Albert_Posis/Serendipity/" title="Albert Posis - Serendipity - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You came out of nowhere <br>Caught my eye by surprise <br>And I think that you've been <br>heaven sent <br>Beauty is flarin' <br>rock what you're wearin' <br>So damn fine I keep on swearin' <br>You're the only one for me <br>Fell in love unexpectedly <br>We ain't gotta rush this is destiny <br>Every time I see you baby <br>it's so hard to speak <br>Girl this ain't no accident <br>Yeah I swear we're meant to be <br>What'cha doin' to me <br>What I'm feeling is so unreal <br>And baby you give me butterflies <br>Feels like I'm flyin' <br>song's never dyin' <br>So damn fine I keep on sighin' <br>You're the only one for me <br>Fell in love unexpectedly <br>We ain't gotta rush this is destiny <br>Every time I hold you baby <br>my knees get so weak <br>Girl this ain't no accident <br>Yeah I swear we're meant to be <br>There might be people <br>who just don't understand <br>How two could fall for each other <br>simply by chance <br>But it's God who put us here <br>'cause He had a plan <br>Don't gotta fuss just trust in us <br>and let me be your man <br>Fell in love unexpectedly <br>We ain't gotta rush this is destiny <br>Every time I kiss you baby <br>my heart skips a beat <br>Girl this ain't no accident <br>Yeah I swear we're meant to be <br>Said I swear we're meant to be <br>Damn I just wanna be with you <br>Girl this ain't no accident <br>Yeah it's serendipity <br>]]></content><category term="Albert Posis" label="Albert Posis"/><category term="Serendipity" label="Serendipity"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김대환/오마이달링프랜/</id><title>김대환 - 오마이달링프랜 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:00:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:00:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%8C%80%ED%99%98/%EC%98%A4%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%AC%EB%A7%81%ED%94%84%EB%9E%9C/" title="김대환 - 오마이달링프랜 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보고 싶은 친구 <br>멀리 떠나있어도 <br>함께했던 만남 <br>정든 즐거운 기억 <br>함께 있지 못해도 <br>마음만은 너에게 <br>우리 우정 이대로 <br>변치 말자 친구야 <br>오 마이 달링 프랜 <br>당신을 사랑해요 <br>우리 우정 이대로 <br>변치 말자 친구야 <br>보고 싶은 친구 <br>멀리 떠나있어도 <br>함께했던 만남 <br>정든 즐거운 기억 <br>함께 있지 못해도 <br>마음만은 너에게 <br>우리 우정 이대로 <br>변치 말자 친구야 <br>오 마이 달링 프랜 <br>당신을 사랑해요 <br>우리 우정 이대로 <br>변치 말자 친구야 <br>오 마이 달링 프랜 <br>당신을 사랑해요 <br>우리 우정 이대로 <br>변치 말자 친구야 <br>변치 말자 친구야 <br>]]></content><category term="김대환" label="김대환"/><category term="오마이달링프랜" label="오마이달링프랜"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Hopeless_Feat_Cashmere_Cat/</id><title>Halsey - Hopeless (Feat. Cashmere Cat) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:00:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:00:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Hopeless_Feat_Cashmere_Cat/" title="Halsey - Hopeless (Feat. Cashmere Cat) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Boy you make it <br>look so easy <br>Promise that I'm gonna call <br>you back in five <br>Sorry baby girl <br>but I can't tonight oh <br>Boy you make it <br>look so simple mm <br>Yeah <br>I've known that girl for <br>like my whole life <br>Back in my hotel and <br>I'm alone inside oh <br>'Cause you know the truth hurts <br>But secrets kill <br>Can't help thinkin' <br>that I love it still <br>Still here there must be <br>something real <br>'Cause you know the <br>good die young <br>But so did this <br>And so it must be better <br>than I think it is <br>Gimme those eyes <br>it's easy to forgive <br>Oh oh oh <br>Oh ooh <br>Oh oh oh <br>Oh ooh <br>Oh ooh <br>Oh ooh <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>Oh ooh <br>You and all your friends <br>all hate me oh <br>Thinkin' that you're better <br>when I'm not around <br>Hear me on the radio and <br>turn it down oh <br>I can't help the way <br>you made me <br>Hope that she believin' in <br>the truth you found <br>Thinkin' that you want us <br>'cause I can't find out oh <br>'Cause you know the truth hurts <br>But secrets kill <br>Can't help thinkin' <br>that I love it still <br>Still here there must <br>be something real <br>'Cause you know the <br>good die young <br>But so did this <br>And so it must be better than <br>I think it is <br>Gimme those eyes <br>it's easy to forgive <br>Oh oh oh <br>Oh ooh <br>Oh oh oh <br>I hope hopeless <br>Oh ooh <br>Changes over time <br>Oh ooh <br>I hope hopeless <br>Oh ooh <br>Changes over time <br>Oh ooh <br>I hope hopeless <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>Changes over time <br>Oh ooh]]></content><category term="Halsey" label="Halsey"/><category term="Hopeless (Feat. Cashmere Cat)" label="Hopeless (Feat. Cashmere Cat)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Devil_In_Me/</id><title>Halsey - Devil In Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:00:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:00:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Devil_In_Me/" title="Halsey - Devil In Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You said I would've <br>hit the ceiling <br>You said I <br>You said I should eat <br>my feelings <br>Head held high <br>I won't take anyone down <br>if I crawl tonight <br>But I still let everyone down <br>when I change in size <br>And I went tumbling down <br>tryna reach your high <br>But I scream too loud <br>if I speak my mind <br>I don't wanna wake it up <br>I don't wanna wake it up <br>I don't wanna wake it up <br>The devil in me <br>I don't wanna wake it up <br>I don't wanna wake it up <br>I don't wanna wake it up <br>The devil in me <br>Gotta wake up gotta wake up <br>Gotta wake up gotta wake up <br>Gotta wake up come back to life <br>Gotta wake up gotta wake up <br>Gotta wake up gotta wake up <br>Gotta wake up come back to life <br>You said I'm too much to handle <br>You said I <br>Shine too bright I burnt the candle <br>Flew too high <br>I won't take anyone down <br>if I crawl tonight <br>But I still let everyone down <br>when I change in size <br>And I went tumbling down <br>tryna reach your high <br>But I scream too loud <br>if I speak my mind <br>I don't wanna wake it up <br>I don't wanna wake it up <br>I don't wanna wake it up <br>The devil in me <br>I don't wanna wake it up <br>I don't wanna wake it up <br>I don't wanna wake it up <br>The devil in me <br>Gotta wake up gotta wake up <br>Gotta wake up gotta wake up <br>Gotta wake up come back to life <br>Gotta wake up gotta wake up <br>Gotta wake up gotta wake up <br>Gotta wake up come back to life <br>Now I gotta wake it up <br>Now I gotta wake it up <br>Now I gotta wake it up <br>The devil in me <br>Now I gotta wake it up <br>Now I gotta wake it up <br>Now I gotta wake it up <br>The devil in me <br>Gotta wake up gotta wake up <br>Gotta wake up gotta wake up <br>Gotta wake up come back to life <br>Gotta wake up gotta wake up <br>Gotta wake up gotta wake up <br>Gotta wake up come back to life]]></content><category term="Halsey" label="Halsey"/><category term="Devil In Me" label="Devil In Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Angel_On_Fire/</id><title>Halsey - Angel On Fire - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:00:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:00:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Angel_On_Fire/" title="Halsey - Angel On Fire - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I woke up to another <br>mess in the living room <br>Broken bottles all around my feet <br>They came again in the <br>night under crescent moon <br>Didn't wake me in my sleep <br>'Cause they talk and drink <br>and laugh 'bout things <br>And fall in love in my backyard <br>I hide and cower in the corner <br>Conversation's getting hard <br>'Cause nobody seems <br>to ask about me anymore <br>And nobody seems to care <br>'bout anything I think <br>And nobody seems to <br>recognize me in the crowd <br>In the background screaming <br>"Everybody look at me" <br>And I'm faded away you know <br>I used to be on fire <br>And I'm faded away you know <br>I used to be on fire <br>I'm standing in the ashes of <br>who I used to be <br>And I'm faded away you know <br>I used to be on fire <br>You know I used to be on fire <br>You know I used to be on fire fire <br>I used to be a darling starlet <br>like a centerpiece <br>Had the whole world wrapped <br>around my ring <br>I flew too closely to the sun <br>that's setting in the East <br>And now I'm melting from my wings <br>'Cause I laugh and drink and <br>talk 'bout things <br>And fall in love in my backyard <br>Now it´s my own anxiety <br>That makes the conversation hard <br>'Cause nobody seems to ask <br>about me anymore <br>And nobody ever cares <br>about anything I think <br>And nobody seems to <br>recognize me in the crowd <br>In the background screaming <br>"Everybody look at me" <br>And I'm faded away you know <br>I used to be on fire <br>And I'm faded away you know <br>I used to be on fire <br>I'm standing in the ashes of <br>who I used to be <br>And I'm faded away you know <br>I used to be on fire <br>You know I used to be on fire <br>You know I used to be on fire <br>Well I used to be on fire <br>You know I used to be on fire <br>You know I used to be on fire <br>You know I used to be on fire fire]]></content><category term="Halsey" label="Halsey"/><category term="Angel On Fire" label="Angel On Fire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Dont_Play/</id><title>Halsey - Don`t Play - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:00:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:00:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Dont_Play/" title="Halsey - Don`t Play - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Alone out in Saint Tropez <br>Lookin' as fine as a damn Monet <br>Tryna hydrate on Perrier <br>Everybody thirsty drinks on me <br>When I'm out clothes <br>on lay away <br>Tryna take back <br>what you say to me <br>I don't give a damn <br>what you say to me <br>There ain't no time <br>for games with me <br>I'm moving on <br>I'm getting paid <br>I'm on my own <br>I had some space <br>to deal with it <br>I'm moving on <br>it's getting late <br>Go and grab someone <br>and find a place to deal with it <br>Yeah don't even trap <br>Can't fuck with my vibe <br>Double cuppin' in my ride <br>Motherfucker don't play with me <br>Motherfucker don't play with me <br>Motherfucker don't play with me <br>Motherfucker don't play with me <br>Runnin' lines like a marathon <br>Got it all white like parmesan <br>I am not the type <br>to be out past dawn <br>Tomorrow got a flight <br>headed to Taiwan <br>Now you know <br>where the bottle gone <br>Drippin' so wet <br>with the Perignon <br>I am not the type to admit I'm on <br>How could I lie <br>when we sip so strong <br>I'm moving on I'm getting paid <br>I'm on my own <br>I had some space to deal with it <br>I'm moving on it's getting late <br>Go and grab someone <br>and find a place to deal with it <br>Yeah don't even trap <br>Can't fuck with my vibe <br>Double cuppin' in my ride <br>Motherfucker don't play with me <br>Motherfucker don't play with me <br>Motherfucker don't play with me <br>Motherfucker don't play with me <br>Hey play play play <br>Hey play play play <br>Hey play play play <br>Hey play play play <br>Hey play play play <br>Hey play play play <br>Hey play play play <br>Women don't play no games <br>Hey play play play <br>Women don't play no games <br>Hey play play play <br>Women don't play no games <br>Hey play play play <br>Women don't play no games <br>Hey play play play <br>Women]]></content><category term="Halsey" label="Halsey"/><category term="Don`t Play" label="Don`t Play"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Bad_At_Love/</id><title>Halsey - Bad At Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:01:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:01:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Bad_At_Love/" title="Halsey - Bad At Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Got a boy back home <br>in Michigan <br>And it tastes like Jack <br>when I'm kissing him <br>So I told him that <br>I never really liked his friends <br>Now he's gone and <br>he's calling me a bitch again <br>It's a guy that lives in <br>a garden state <br>And he told me we don't <br>make it 'til we graduate <br>So I told him the music <br>would be worth the wait <br>But he wants me in the <br>kitchen on a dinner plate <br>I believe I believe I believe I believe <br>That we're meant to be <br>But jealousy jealousy <br>jealousy jealousy <br>Gets the best of me <br>Look I don't mean to <br>frustrate but I <br>Always make the same <br>mistakes yeah <br>Always make the same <br>mistakes 'cause <br>I'm bad at love ooh ooh <br>But you can't blame me for tryin' <br>You know I'd be lyin' sayin' <br>You were the one ooh ooh <br>That could finally fix me <br>Lookin' at my history <br>I'm bad at love <br>Got a girl with California eyes <br>And I thought that <br>she could really be <br>the one this time <br>But I never got the chance <br>to make her mine <br>Because she fell in love <br>with little thin white lines <br>London girl with an attitude <br>We never told no one <br>but we look so cute <br>Both got way better things to do <br>But I always think about it <br>when I'm riding through <br>I believe I believe I believe I believe <br>That I'm in too deep <br>But jealousy jealousy <br>jealousy jealousy <br>Gets the best of me <br>Look I don't mean to frustrate but I <br>Always make the same <br>mistakes yeah <br>Always make the same <br>mistakes 'cause <br>I'm bad at love ooh ooh <br>But you can't blame me for tryin' <br>You know I'd be lyin' sayin' <br>You were the one ooh ooh <br>That could finally fix me <br>Lookin' at my history <br>I'm bad at love ooh ooh <br>Oh you know you know <br>you know you know <br>I'm bad at love ooh ooh <br>I'm bad at love ooh ooh <br>I know that you're afraid <br>I'm gonna walk away <br>Each time the feeling fades <br>Each time the feeling fades <br>I know that you're afraid <br>I'm gonna walk away <br>Each time the feeling fades <br>You know I'm bad at love ooh ooh <br>But you can't blame me for tryin' <br>You know I'd be lyin' sayin' <br>You were the one ooh ooh <br>That could finally fix me <br>Lookin' at my history <br>I'm bad at love ooh ooh <br>Oh you know you know <br>you know you know <br>I'm bad at love ooh ooh <br>Oh oh <br>]]></content><category term="Halsey" label="Halsey"/><category term="Bad At Love" label="Bad At Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오정태/갑질이야_Feat_김혜연/</id><title>오정태 - 갑질이야 (Feat. 김혜연) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:01:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:01:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EC%A0%95%ED%83%9C/%EA%B0%91%EC%A7%88%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC_Feat_%EA%B9%80%ED%98%9C%EC%97%B0/" title="오정태 - 갑질이야 (Feat. 김혜연) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[갑질이야 갑질이야 <br>뭐 그리 대단하다고 <br>갑질이야 갑질이야 <br>뭐 그리 특별하다고 <br>갑이 을이 되고 을이 갑이 되는 <br>우리 인생사다 <br>나누고 베풀고 살기도 짧은 우리 <br>갑갑하지 말자 <br>벼는 익을수록 고개를 숙이고 <br>갑은 뉴스에 나올 때만 <br>고개를 숙이네 <br>너나 나나 목욕탕에서 발가벗으면 <br>다 똑같은 사람이더라 <br>너나 나나 마누라가 제일 무섭잖아 <br>다 똑같은 사람이더라 갑질이야 <br>갑질이야 갑질이야 <br>뭐 그리 대단하다고 <br>갑질이야 갑질이야 <br>뭐 그리 특별하다고 <br>갑이 을이 되고 을이 갑이 되는 <br>우리 인생사다 <br>나누고 베풀고 살기도 짧은 우리 <br>갑갑하지 말자 <br>벼는 익을수록 고개를 숙이고 <br>갑은 뉴스에 나올 때만 <br>고개를 숙이네 <br>너나 나나 화장실 가서 힘 안주냐 <br>다 똑같은 사람이더라 <br>너나 나나 천년만년 살 것 같으냐 <br>다 똑같은 사람이더라 갑질이야 <br>갑질이야 갑질이야 <br>뭐 그리 대단하다고 <br>갑질이야 갑질이야 <br>뭐 그리 특별하다고 <br>갑이 을이 되고 을이 갑이 되는 <br>우리 인생사다 <br>나누고 베풀고 살기도 짧은 우리 <br>갑갑하지 말자 <br>갑질이야 갑질이야 <br>뭐 그리 대단하다고 <br>갑질이야 갑질이야 <br>뭐 그리 특별하다고 <br>갑이 을이 되고 을이 갑이 되는 <br>우리 인생사다 <br>나누고 베풀고 살기도 짧은 우리 <br>갑갑하지 말자 <br>갑갑하지 말자 갑질 <br>]]></content><category term="오정태" label="오정태"/><category term="갑질이야 (Feat. 김혜연)" label="갑질이야 (Feat. 김혜연)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Missy_Elliott/Im_Better_Feat_Eve_Lil_Kim__Trina/</id><title>Missy Elliott - I`m Better (Feat. Eve, Lil Kim & Trina) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:01:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:01:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Missy_Elliott/Im_Better_Feat_Eve_Lil_Kim__Trina/" title="Missy Elliott - I`m Better (Feat. Eve, Lil Kim & Trina) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Remix! <br><br>I'ma start it from the bottom <br>Show you how to flip a dollar <br>I got food in my dinin' room <br>I'm better, I'm better, I'm better <br>It's another day, another chance <br>I wake up, I wanna dance <br>So as long as I got my friends... <br>I'm better, I'm better, I'm better <br><br>Lil Kim! <br><br>And you can not be me, no never <br>Ain't got to explain why I'm better <br>Your man is a dog <br>He chase my kitty and he say my pussy is wetter <br>Hooooooool' up, remix! <br><br>I'ma start it from the bottom <br>Show you how to flip a dollar <br>I got food in my dinin' room <br>I'm better, I'm better, I'm better <br>It's another day, another chance <br>I wake up, I wanna dance (Woo!) <br>So as long as I got my friends... <br>I'm better, I'm better, I'm better <br><br>Lil Kim! <br><br>You can not be me, no never <br>Ain't got to explain why I'm better <br>Your man is a dog <br>He chase my kitty and he say my pussy is wetter <br>Me and Missy be high in them choppers <br>Landin' on hundred foot yachts <br>In Giuseppe heels, I kick in the door <br>Wavin' the 4 like I am Big Poppa <br>I'm better, I'm better, Balmain be the leather <br>My watch is so icy, if I walk outside in the summertime <br>I just might change the weather <br>I'm done with the Benz so I bought a Wraith <br>I don't trust the bank so I bought a safe <br>This fur on me like I fought a ape <br>I'm killin' 'em, yellow tape <br><br>I'ma start it from the bottom <br>Show you how to flip a dollar <br>I got food in my dinin' room (Hoooooool' up!) <br>I'm better, I'm better, I'm better <br>It's another day, another chance <br>I wake up, I wanna dance <br>So as long as I got my friends... <br>I'm better, I'm better, I'm better (Remix!) <br><br>I wake up, I wanna dance <br>I wake up, I wanna dance (dance) <br>I wake up, I wanna dance (dance) <br>Dance, d-d-dance <br>I wake up, I wanna dance <br>I wake up, I wanna dance (dance) <br>I wake up, I wanna dance (dance) <br>Dance, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better <br><br>Trina! <br><br>Yeah, I'm better, I'm better than them <br>And I get wetter than them <br>And fuck where you've been <br>Get too much cheddar for him <br>I set the bar and them bitches only settin' trends <br>I put the pressure on them <br>Still ain't turn into a diamond <br>I got the Midas, billionaire minded <br>Seat's on recline and I'm gettin' some head <br>Right in back of the pilot <br>Switchin' up pilots, damn and I'm shinin' <br>All my bitches with me, 305's finest <br>Don't come around us if you ain't 'bout commas <br>Commas, commas, commas, commas <br>Show you how to hit a lick <br>Collect the profit, watch it flip <br>(He watchin' my body like he watchin' Scandal <br>But I'm just yeah) Never front, so you spend <br><br>I'ma start it from the bottom <br>Show you how to flip a dollar <br>I got food in my dinin' room <br>I'm better, I'm better, I'm better <br>It's another day, another chance <br>I wake up, I wanna dance <br>So as long as I got my friends... <br>I'm better, I'm better, I'm better <br><br>Eve! <br><br>I've been away, I'm so anti <br>Winnin' in life by a landslide <br>I know you see me, you see me <br>Your chick wanna be me <br>But she can never be me, no <br>Man I'm too stuck in my ways <br>Countin' this money for days <br>Life is so good, it feel good <br>No worries with all of these foreigns up in my driveway <br>I ain't got no time for no dumb shit <br>A lot of y'all be on some bum shit <br>First I got my D's up, then I got my pounds up <br>What you been talkin' ain't addin' up <br>March to the beat of my own drum <br>Philly to London conundrum <br>I've been this way, baby since the first day <br>But they keep askin', "Where the fuck does she come from?" <br>I'm better <br><br>I'ma start it from the bottom <br>Show you how to flip a dollar <br>I got food in my dinin' room <br>I'm better, I'm better, I'm better <br>It's another day, another chance <br>I wake up, I wanna dance <br>So as long as I got my friends... <br>I'm better, I'm better, I'm better]]></content><category term="Missy Elliott" label="Missy Elliott"/><category term="I`m Better (Feat. Eve, Lil Kim & Trina)" label="I`m Better (Feat. Eve, Lil Kim & Trina)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Walls_Could_Talk/</id><title>Halsey - Walls Could Talk - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:01:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:01:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Walls_Could_Talk/" title="Halsey - Walls Could Talk - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Been about three days <br>and I'm comin' back <br>I'm about four minutes <br>from a heart attack <br>And I think you <br>make me a maniac <br>But you don't know oh <br>Two years and <br>we in between <br>But we both been here <br>since we seventeen <br>Here we go fist <br>fight in a limousine <br>But they don't know <br>And we both hope <br>there's something <br>But we bo both <br>keep fronting <br>And it's a closed discussion <br>And I'm thinking <br>"Damn if these walls could talk" <br>Oh oh oh <br>Well they'd be like <br>Oh oh oh <br>"Shit is crazy right" <br>Oh oh oh <br>I ain't your baby no more <br>Been about two weeks <br>since you went away <br>I'm about halfway <br>through a Cabernet <br>And I go <br>I'm wastin' a Saturday <br>Sittin' at ho home <br>Told my new roommate <br>not to let you in <br>But you're so damn good <br>with a bobby pin <br>Now you gon' play me <br>like a violin <br>Hittin' these no notes <br>And we both hope <br>there's something <br>But we bo both <br>keep fronting <br>And it's a closed discussion <br>And I'm thinking <br>"Damn if these walls could talk" <br>Oh oh oh <br>Well they'd be like <br>Oh oh oh <br>"Shit is crazy right" <br>Oh oh oh <br>I ain't your baby no more <br>Oh oh oh <br>Hey <br>Oh oh oh <br>No more <br>Oh oh oh <br>I ain't your baby no more <br>Oh oh oh]]></content><category term="Halsey" label="Halsey"/><category term="Walls Could Talk" label="Walls Could Talk"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Lie_Feat_Quavo/</id><title>Halsey - Lie (Feat. Quavo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:01:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:01:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Lie_Feat_Quavo/" title="Halsey - Lie (Feat. Quavo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh <br>Breakfast is cold <br>as cold as our bed oh <br>I'm watching you choke down <br>the words that you said <br>I watch you devour <br>mistake me for bread oh <br>Well boy is you fed <br>Or are you misled <br>I gave you the messiest head <br>You give me the messiest head <br>Oh you're turnin' red <br>'Cause I'm tryna give the impression <br>that I get the message you <br>wish I was dead <br>See you 'bouta break a sweat <br>I I I <br>I won't let us finish yet <br>I I I <br>Please don't take this as a threat <br>I I I <br>All I'm sayin' is if you don't love me <br>no more then why <br>Lie lie <br>Lie lie <br>I heard what you said <br>what she say <br>You talk about <br>your head game oh <br>I know that <br>it's fire flame fire <br>Your mouth make a <br>hurricane splash <br>You notice that <br>we in love love <br>That's something <br>we cannot change no <br>It's the plans <br>we should arrange plans <br>Treat her right and <br>she won't complain yeah <br>Bring back the title bring it back <br>She tall like the Eiffel yeah <br>Got no one to lie to no <br>There's no need to <br>lie no more ayy <br>Bring me a trial bring <br>Every move's vital ooh <br>What you gon' die for <br>When every day <br>you told lies alright <br>Lie lie <br>Lie lie <br>Lie lie <br>Lie lie]]></content><category term="Halsey" label="Halsey"/><category term="Lie (Feat. Quavo)" label="Lie (Feat. Quavo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Good_Mourning/</id><title>Halsey - Good Mourning - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:01:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:01:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Good_Mourning/" title="Halsey - Good Mourning - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They told me once <br>"There's a place <br>where love conquers all" <br>A city with the streets <br>full of milk and honey <br>I haven't found it yet <br>but I'm still searching <br>All I know is a hopeless <br>place that flows <br>with the blood of my kin <br>Perhaps hopeless isn't a place <br>Nothing but a state of mind <br>They told me once <br>"Don't trust the moon <br>she's always changing" <br>The shores bend <br>and break for her <br>And she begs to be loved <br>But nothing here is as it seems <br>Sun is coming up <br>oh why oh why oh why <br>Sun is coming up <br>oh why oh why oh why <br>Sun is coming up <br>oh why oh why oh why <br>Sun is coming up <br>oh why oh why oh why <br>Sun is coming up <br>oh why oh why oh why <br>Sun is coming up <br>oh why oh why oh why <br>Sun is coming up <br>oh why oh why oh why]]></content><category term="Halsey" label="Halsey"/><category term="Good Mourning" label="Good Mourning"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Sorry/</id><title>Halsey - Sorry - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:01:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:01:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Sorry/" title="Halsey - Sorry - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've missed your calls <br>for months it seems <br>Don't realize how <br>mean I can be <br>'Cause I can sometimes <br>treat the people <br>That I love like jewelry <br>'Cause I can change <br>my mind each day <br>I didn't mean to try you on <br>But I still know your birthday <br>And your mother's favorite song <br>So I'm sorry to my unknown lover <br>Sorry that I can't believe <br>That anybody ever really <br>Starts to fall in love with me <br>Sorry to my unknown lover <br>Sorry I could be so blind <br>Didn't mean to leave you <br>And all of the things <br>that we had behind <br>Ooh <br>Ooh <br>Ooh <br>I run away when <br>things are good <br>And never really understood <br>The way you laid <br>your eyes on me <br>In ways that no one ever could <br>And so it seems <br>I broke your heart <br>My ignorance has struck again <br>I failed to see it <br>from the start <br>And tore you <br>open 'til the end <br>So I'm sorry to <br>my unknown lover <br>Sorry that I can't believe <br>That anybody ever really <br>Starts to fall in love with me <br>Sorry to my unknown lover <br>Sorry I could be so blind <br>Didn't mean to leave you <br>And all of the things <br>that we had behind <br>And someone will love you <br>Someone will love you <br>Someone will love you <br>But someone isn't me <br>Someone will love you <br>Someone will love you <br>Someone will love you <br>But someone isn't me <br>Sorry to my unknown lover <br>Sorry that I can't believe <br>That anybody ever really <br>Starts to fall in love with me <br>Sorry to my unknown lover <br>Sorry I could be so blind <br>Didn't mean to leave you <br>And all of the things <br>that we had behind <br>And someone will love you <br>Someone will love you <br>Someone will love you <br>But someone isn't me <br>And someone will love you <br>Someone will love you <br>Someone will love you <br>But someone isn't me <br>]]></content><category term="Halsey" label="Halsey"/><category term="Sorry" label="Sorry"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Alone/</id><title>Halsey - Alone - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:01:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:01:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Alone/" title="Halsey - Alone - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If I <br>If I <br>Said he tried to phone me <br>but I never have time <br>He said that I never listen <br>but I don't even try <br>I got a new place in Cali <br>but I'm gone every night <br>So I fill it with strangers <br>so they keep on the lights <br>She said she told you <br>she knows me <br>But the face isn't right <br>She asked if I recognized her <br>And I told her I might <br>See everywhere I go <br>I got a million different <br>people tryna kick it <br>But I'm still alone in my mind yeah <br>I know you're dying to meet me <br>But I can just tell you this <br>Baby as soon as you meet me <br>You'll wish that you never did <br>you'll wish that you never did <br>I stayed a night out in Paris <br>where they don't know my name <br>And I got into some trouble <br>with that drink in my veins <br>I got a problem with parties <br>'cause it's loud in my brain <br>And I can never say sorry <br>'cause I won't take the blame <br>I know I always go missing <br>And you're lying awake <br>But if you ask why I'm distant <br>Oh I'm running away <br>You know that everywhere I go <br>I got a million different people <br>tryna kick it <br>But I'm still alone in my mind <br>I know you're dying to meet me <br>But I can just tell you this <br>Baby as soon as you meet me <br>You'll wish that you never did <br>You'll wish that you never did <br>I I know you wanna <br>I I know you wanna <br>I I know you wanna <br>Slip under my armor <br>I I know you wanna <br>I I know you wanna <br>I I know you wanna <br>Slip under my armor <br>See everywhere I go <br>I got a million different people <br>tryna hit it <br>But I'm still alone in my mind <br>I know you're dying to meet me <br>But I can just tell you this <br>Baby as soon as you meet me <br>You'll wish that you never did <br>You'll wish that you never did <br>Yeah <br>I know you wanna <br>I I know you wanna <br>You'll wish that you never did <br>I know you wanna <br>Slip under my armor <br>Oh <br>I know you wanna <br>I I know you wanna <br>You'll wish that you never did]]></content><category term="Halsey" label="Halsey"/><category term="Alone" label="Alone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Heaven_In_Hiding/</id><title>Halsey - Heaven In Hiding - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:01:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:01:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/Heaven_In_Hiding/" title="Halsey - Heaven In Hiding - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sittin' on the counter <br>in your kitchen <br>Can you hear <br>my heartbeat fucking kickin' <br>Your eyes light up <br>'cause you best believe <br>that I got something up my sleeve <br>I walk my talk no time <br>for wishful thinking <br>I push up on my toes you <br>call me "sweet thing" <br>And breathing down <br>your neck your body screaming <br>And you thought that you <br>were the boss tonight <br>but I can put up one good fight <br>I flip the script like I can take a beating <br>And when you start to <br>feel the rush <br>A crimson headache <br>aching blush <br>And you surrender to the <br>touch you'll know <br>I can put on a show <br>I can put on a show <br>Don't you see what <br>you're finding <br>This is Heaven in hiding oh <br>And when you start to <br>look at me a physical fatality <br>And you surrender to the <br>heat you'll know <br>I can put on a show <br>I can put on a show <br>Don't you see what you're finding <br>This is Heaven in hiding <br>This is Heaven in hiding oh <br>Sitting on the concrete <br>in your basement <br>But I don't have no time <br>for conversation <br>Said this ain't <br>what you usually do <br>and a girl like me is <br>new for you <br>And I can tell you mean it <br>'cause you're shaking <br>And when you start to <br>feel the rush <br>A crimson headache <br>aching blush <br>And you surrender <br>to the touch you'll know <br>I can put on a show <br>I can put on a show <br>Don't you see <br>what you're finding <br>This is Heaven in hiding oh <br>And when you start to <br>look at me a physical fatality <br>And you surrender <br>to the heat you'll know <br>I can put on a show <br>I can put on a show <br>Don't you see <br>what you're finding <br>This is Heaven in hiding <br>This is Heaven in hiding oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh ooh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>And when you start to <br>feel the rush <br>A crimson headache <br>aching blush <br>And you surrender <br>to the touch you'll know <br>I can put on a show <br>I can put on a show <br>Don't you see <br>what you're finding <br>This is Heaven in hiding oh <br>And when you start to <br>look at me a physical fatality <br>And you surrender <br>to the heat you'll know <br>I can put on a show <br>I can put on a show <br>Don't you see <br>what you're finding <br>This is Heaven in hiding <br>This is Heaven in hiding <br>This is Heaven in hiding oh <br>Oh this is Heaven in hiding <br>This is Heaven in hiding <br>'Cause I'm Heaven in hiding]]></content><category term="Halsey" label="Halsey"/><category term="Heaven In Hiding" label="Heaven In Hiding"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/100_Letters/</id><title>Halsey - 100 Letters - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:01:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:01:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/100_Letters/" title="Halsey - 100 Letters - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well King Midas put his <br>hands on me again <br>He said one day I'd realize why <br>I don't have any friends <br>I find myself alone at night <br>unless I'm having sex <br>But he can make me golden <br>if I just showed some respect <br>But I don't let him touch me anymore <br>I said I'm not something to butter up <br>and taste when you get bored <br>'Cause I have spent too many nights <br>on dirty bathroom floors <br>To find some peace and quiet <br>right behind a wooden door <br>He said Please don't go away <br>He said Please don't go away <br>I said It's too late <br>I said It's too late <br>He said Please don't go away <br>He said Please don't go away <br>I said It's too late <br>I said It's too late <br>And now I can't stop <br>thinking that I can't stop thinking <br>That I almost gave you everything <br>And now the whole thing's <br>finished and I can't stop wishing <br>That I never gave you anything <br>You wrote a hundred letters <br>just for me <br>And I find them in my closet <br>in the pockets of my jeans <br>Now I'm constantly reminded <br>of the time I was nineteen <br>Every single one's forgotten <br>in a laundromat machine <br>But I don't let him touch me anymore <br>I said I'm not something to butter up <br>and taste when you get bored <br>'Cause I have spent too many nights <br>on dirty bathroom floors <br>To find some peace and quiet <br>right behind a wooden door <br>He said Please don't go away <br>He said Please don't go away <br>I said It's too late <br>I said It's too late <br>He said Please don't go away <br>He said Please don't go away <br>I said It's too late <br>I said It's too late <br>And now I can't stop thinking <br>that I can't stop thinking <br>That I almost gave you everything <br>And now the whole thing's finished <br>and I can't stop wishing <br>That I never gave you anything <br>And I can't stop thinking <br>that I can't stop thinking <br>That I almost gave you everything <br>I said It's too late <br>And now the whole thing's finished <br>and I can't stop wishing <br>That I never gave you anything <br>He said Please don't go away <br>He said Please don't go away <br>I said It's too late <br>I said It's too late <br>He said Please don't go away <br>He said Please don't go away <br>I said It's too late <br>I said It's too late <br>]]></content><category term="Halsey" label="Halsey"/><category term="100 Letters" label="100 Letters"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/The_Prologue/</id><title>Halsey - The Prologue - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:01:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:01:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halsey/The_Prologue/" title="Halsey - The Prologue - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Two households both <br>alike in dignity <br>In fair Verona where <br>we lay our scene <br>From ancient grudge <br>break to new mutiny <br>Where civil blood makes <br>civil hands unclean <br>From forth the fatal <br>loins of these two foes <br>A pair of star-cross'd <br>lovers take their life; <br>Whose misadventured <br>piteous overthrows <br>Do with their death bury <br>their parents' strife <br>The fearful passage of <br>their death-mark'd love <br>And the continuance of <br>their parents' rage <br>Which but their children's end <br>nought could remove <br>Is now the two hours' <br>traffic of our stage <br>The which if you with <br>patient ears attend <br>What here shall miss our <br>toil shall strive to mend <br>I am a child of a <br>Money hungry prideful country <br>Grass is green and it's always sunny <br>Hands so bloody tastes like honey <br>I'm finding it hard to leave <br>I am a child of a <br>Money hungry prideful country <br>Grass is green and it's always sunny <br>Hands so bloody tastes like honey <br>I'm finding it hard to leave]]></content><category term="Halsey" label="Halsey"/><category term="The Prologue" label="The Prologue"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/효연_HYOYEON/Wannabe_Feat_San_E_Inst/</id><title>효연 (HYOYEON) - Wannabe (Feat. San E) (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:04:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:04:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9A%A8%EC%97%B0_HYOYEON/Wannabe_Feat_San_E_Inst/" title="효연 (HYOYEON) - Wannabe (Feat. San E) (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모두의 Wannabe <br>난 만인의 연인이지 <br>Loose한 큰 Box-T에도 <br>느껴지는 맵시 <br>날 보면 OMG <br>모두 감탄 내뱉지 <br>Hash Tag it girl <br>다 날 따라와 follow <br>근데 넌 자꾸 딴 생각 <br>Lipstick 누군데 <br>좋니 Honey <br>믿을 수 없어 Now talk it <br>이제 감 오니 <br>무슨 짓 한 건지 <br>품위 있게 말할 때 <br>자 거기서 멈춰 <br>잠깐 솔직하게 말해봐 <br>Sticker처럼 달라 붙지마 <br>거짓말이 넌 쉬워 쉬워 <br>넌 정말 답이 없는 바로 그런 Trouble <br>됐어 소용없어 그만해 <br>Because 달콤한 건 질렸어 <br>날카롭게 널 찔러 찔러 <br>넌 정말 답이 없는 바로 그런 Trouble <br>Awesome 다 갖춘 <br>흔히들 날 보면 Fortune <br>그 많은 Gossip도 <br>날 어쩔 순 없지 <br>잘 봐봐 모르겠어 <br>딴소리 할 때 아냐 <br>네 그 판단은 Miss <br>감추기는커녕 <br>오히려 더 뻔뻔해 <br>마침 딱 연습한 거니 <br>그냥 생각이 없어 So so so <br>속을 것 같니 <br>참을 수가 없어 <br>다시 한번 말할게 <br>자 거기서 멈춰 <br>잠깐 솔직하게 말해봐 <br>Sticker처럼 달라 붙지마 <br>거짓말이 넌 쉬워 쉬워 <br>넌 정말 답이 없는 바로 그런 Trouble <br>됐어 소용없어 그만해 <br>Because 달콤한 건 질렸어 <br>날카롭게 널 찔러 찔러 <br>넌 정말 답이 없는 바로 그런 Trouble <br>Pa pa pa pardon <br>잘못 들은 거 같아서 <br>I’m trouble <br>you said that’s right <br>잘못 들은 거 맞네 <br>존중해주는 남자 <br>you know I’m a feminist <br>못 믿겠단 그 표정 뭐야 <br>Actually it’s kinda cute oh <br>Woo that’s my baby <br>woo got this new bag uh <br>Woo just for ya <br>끈도 넣어뒀어 기분 풀래 hmm <br>한번 봐줘 뭐든 할게 <br>프사 배경화면 바꾸는 거 말곤 제발 <br>됐어 확실하게 해줄게 <br>이젠 아쉬울 게 없어 난 <br>두 번은 없어 지워 지워 <br>처음부터 알았어야 했던 너의 Trouble <br>Give up 힘들 것도 없어 난 <br>Because 별 게 아닌 너니까 <br>후회랄 건 딱 하나 하나 <br>처음부터 알았어야 했던 너의 Trouble <br>Happy Ending Another change <br>여기부터 다시 시작해 <br>좀 더 멋진 난 나로 충분해 <br>I don't need trouble oh <br>Hahaha <br>]]></content><category term="효연 (HYOYEON)" label="효연 (HYOYEON)"/><category term="Wannabe (Feat. San E) (Inst.)" label="Wannabe (Feat. San E) (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/효연_HYOYEON/Wannabe_Feat_San_E/</id><title>효연 (HYOYEON) - Wannabe (Feat. San E) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:04:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:04:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9A%A8%EC%97%B0_HYOYEON/Wannabe_Feat_San_E/" title="효연 (HYOYEON) - Wannabe (Feat. San E) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모두의 Wannabe <br>난 만인의 연인이지 <br>Loose한 큰 Box-T에도 <br>느껴지는 맵시 <br>날 보면 OMG <br>모두 감탄 내뱉지 <br>Hash Tag it girl <br>다 날 따라와 follow <br>근데 넌 자꾸 딴 생각 <br>Lipstick 누군데 <br>좋니 Honey <br>믿을 수 없어 Now talk it <br>이제 감 오니 <br>무슨 짓 한 건지 <br>품위 있게 말할 때 <br>자 거기서 멈춰 <br>잠깐 솔직하게 말해봐 <br>Sticker처럼 달라 붙지마 <br>거짓말이 넌 쉬워 쉬워 <br>넌 정말 답이 없는 바로 그런 Trouble <br>됐어 소용없어 그만해 <br>Because 달콤한 건 질렸어 <br>날카롭게 널 찔러 찔러 <br>넌 정말 답이 없는 바로 그런 Trouble <br>Awesome 다 갖춘 <br>흔히들 날 보면 Fortune <br>그 많은 Gossip도 <br>날 어쩔 순 없지 <br>잘 봐봐 모르겠어 <br>딴소리 할 때 아냐 <br>네 그 판단은 Miss <br>감추기는커녕 <br>오히려 더 뻔뻔해 <br>마침 딱 연습한 거니 <br>그냥 생각이 없어 So so so <br>속을 것 같니 <br>참을 수가 없어 <br>다시 한번 말할게 <br>자 거기서 멈춰 <br>잠깐 솔직하게 말해봐 <br>Sticker처럼 달라 붙지마 <br>거짓말이 넌 쉬워 쉬워 <br>넌 정말 답이 없는 바로 그런 Trouble <br>됐어 소용없어 그만해 <br>Because 달콤한 건 질렸어 <br>날카롭게 널 찔러 찔러 <br>넌 정말 답이 없는 바로 그런 Trouble <br>Pa pa pa pardon <br>잘못 들은 거 같아서 <br>I’m trouble <br>you said that’s right <br>잘못 들은 거 맞네 <br>존중해주는 남자 <br>you know I’m a feminist <br>못 믿겠단 그 표정 뭐야 <br>Actually it’s kinda cute oh <br>Woo that’s my baby <br>woo got this new bag uh <br>Woo just for ya <br>끈도 넣어뒀어 기분 풀래 hmm <br>한번 봐줘 뭐든 할게 <br>프사 배경화면 바꾸는 거 말곤 제발 <br>됐어 확실하게 해줄게 <br>이젠 아쉬울 게 없어 난 <br>두 번은 없어 지워 지워 <br>처음부터 알았어야 했던 너의 Trouble <br>Give up 힘들 것도 없어 난 <br>Because 별 게 아닌 너니까 <br>후회랄 건 딱 하나 하나 <br>처음부터 알았어야 했던 너의 Trouble <br>Happy Ending Another change <br>여기부터 다시 시작해 <br>좀 더 멋진 난 나로 충분해 <br>I don't need trouble oh <br>Hahaha <br>]]></content><category term="효연 (HYOYEON)" label="효연 (HYOYEON)"/><category term="Wannabe (Feat. San E)" label="Wannabe (Feat. San E)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/일레븐_Eleven/하아아/</id><title>일레븐 (Eleven) - 하아아 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:04:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:04:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%BC%EB%A0%88%EB%B8%90_Eleven/%ED%95%98%EC%95%84%EC%95%84/" title="일레븐 (Eleven) - 하아아 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>하아아 하아아 <br>]]></content><category term="일레븐 (Eleven)" label="일레븐 (Eleven)"/><category term="하아아" label="하아아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비하인더/Shower/</id><title>비하인더 - Shower - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:04:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:04:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B8%EB%8D%94/Shower/" title="비하인더 - Shower - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아쉽기만 하네 늘 <br>기약 없는 이별이 <br>끝은 아니겠지만 <br>다시 난 돌아 오겠지 <br>이 도시를 떠나면 <br>푸른 바다로 갈까 난 <br>끝은 아니겠지만 <br>다시 난 돌아 올 수 있을까 <br>Shower Shower <br>Shower Shower <br>푸른 바다로 가면 <br>너를 볼 수 있을까 <br>나를 숨 쉬게 하는 <br>날 위한 샤워가 내릴 꺼야 <br>이 도시를 떠나면 <br>너를 볼 수 있을까 <br>나를 숨 쉬게 하는 <br>날 위한 샤워가 내릴 꺼야 <br>Shower Shower <br>Shower Shower <br>]]></content><category term="비하인더" label="비하인더"/><category term="Shower" label="Shower"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비하인더/Soldier/</id><title>비하인더 - Soldier - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:04:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:04:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B8%EB%8D%94/Soldier/" title="비하인더 - Soldier - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사막에 해가 떨어지면 <br>또 다시 떠오르는 어둠들 <br>저 멀리 수많은 별들 속에 <br>아름다운 나의 고향 별 <br>나를 둘러싼 깊은 이 어둠 속 <br>나를 둘러싼 수많은 눈동자 <br>나는 무엇을 위해 여기에 <br>저 눈빛은 또 <br>무엇을 위해 여기에 <br>난 아무것도 두렵지 않아 <br>그저 밤하늘의 별을 <br>바라보고 싶을 뿐 <br>난 아무것도 두렵지 않아 <br>그댈 그리며 숨 쉬는 <br>이 밤이 소중할 뿐 <br>내 삶의 끝자락으로 <br>눈물을 훔치지 않기를 <br>두 손 모아 기도해요 <br>당신의 눈동자 속에 <br>얼굴을 묻고 웃으며 <br>그대 숨결 듣고 싶어 <br>]]></content><category term="비하인더" label="비하인더"/><category term="Soldier" label="Soldier"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비하인더/Robot_Song/</id><title>비하인더 - Robot Song - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:04:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:04:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B8%EB%8D%94/Robot_Song/" title="비하인더 - Robot Song - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[좋은 아침이죠 당신을 기다렸어요 <br>당신을 위해 노래를 만들었어요 <br>랄라라 랄랄라 오래된 피아노 소리 <br>당신의 지친 맘을 <br>편안하게 해 줄 꺼야 <br>랄라라 랄랄라 아날로그 신디 소리 <br>당신의 지친 맘을 <br>따뜻하게 해 줄 것 같아 <br>난 알 수 없죠 그 기분 <br>난 로봇이니까 <br>난 알 수 없죠 그 기분 <br>난 로봇이니까 <br>난 할 수 없죠 그 노래 <br>난 로봇이니까 <br>난 할 수 없죠 그 노래 <br>난 로봇이니까 <br>랄라라 랄랄라 오래된 피아노 소리 <br>당신의 지친 맘을 <br>편안하게 해 줄 꺼야 <br>랄라라 랄랄라 아날로그 신디 소리 <br>당신의 지친 맘을 <br>따뜻하게 해 줄 것 같아 <br>난 할 수 없죠 그 노래 <br>난 로봇이니까 <br>난 할 수 없죠 그 노래 <br>난 로봇이니까 <br>난 할 수 없죠 그 노래 <br>난 로봇이니까 <br>난 할 수 없죠 그 노래 <br>난 로봇이니까 <br>난 할 수 없죠 그 노래 <br>난 로봇이니까 <br>]]></content><category term="비하인더" label="비하인더"/><category term="Robot Song" label="Robot Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비하인더/OKStar/</id><title>비하인더 - O.K.Star - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:04:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:04:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B8%EB%8D%94/OKStar/" title="비하인더 - O.K.Star - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[고개를 흔들어 지울 필요는 없지 <br>Low Low Low <br>어차피 우리 둘 만의 기억 <br>High High High <br>아파도 미운 건 아닌 걸 너 너 너 <br>처음부터 끝을 알았는데 <br>Why Why Why <br>파란 우주선 위에 부푼 꿈을 싣고 <br>그대와 그대와 작은 별을 <br>달리던 그날 <br>하늘은 높고 푸르고 <br>내 마음도 그곳으로 <br>영원히 영원히 끝나지 않을 <br>꿈들을 꾸었네 <br>파란 우주선 위에 부푼 꿈을 싣고 <br>그대와 그대와 작은 별을 <br>달리던 그날 <br>하늘은 높고 푸르고 <br>내 마음도 그곳으로 <br>영원히 영원히 끝나지 않을 <br>꿈들을 꾸었네 <br>]]></content><category term="비하인더" label="비하인더"/><category term="O.K.Star" label="O.K.Star"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김맑음/미안해_Prod_서경교/</id><title>김맑음 - 미안해 (Prod. 서경교) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:04:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:04:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%A7%91%EC%9D%8C/%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%88%ED%95%B4_Prod_%EC%84%9C%EA%B2%BD%EA%B5%90/" title="김맑음 - 미안해 (Prod. 서경교) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[항상 내 곁에서 <br>아무것도 바라지 않고 <br>힘이 되어준 너에게 <br>해줄 수 있는 말 <br>미안해 미안해 <br>널 몰랐을 때로 <br>되돌아가고 싶어 사랑하지만 <br>나 같은 사람 <br>만나지 않았어야 하는데 너는 <br>점점 너도 지쳐가는 모습을 <br>옆에서 보고 <br>모른 척 널 바라만 보고 있네 <br>잊을 수 없니 <br>난 해줄 게 없네 정말 <br>날 버리고 가버려 이젠 <br>잊어주겠니 <br>날 떠나가버려 그대 <br>해줄 수 있는 게 <br>바라만 보고 미안해 너에게 <br>점점 너도 지쳐가는 모습을 <br>옆에서 보고 <br>모른 척 널 바라만 보고 있네 <br>잊을 수 없니 <br>난 해줄 게 없네 정말 <br>날 버리고 가버려 이젠 <br>잊어주겠니 <br>날 떠나가버려 그대 <br>해줄 수 있는 게 <br>바라만 보고 <br>널 보낼 수 없다는 걸 알면서 <br>그런 말이라도 해야 <br>내 맘이 좀 편해질 것 같아 <br>항상 내 곁에 <br>있어줘서 버티고 있어 <br>언젠가는 아침이 밝아 올 거야 <br>잊을 수 없니 <br>난 해줄 게 없네 정말 <br>날 버리고 가버려 이젠 <br>잊어주겠니 <br>날 떠나가버려 그대 <br>해줄 수 있는 게 <br>바라만 보고 미안해 너에게 <br>]]></content><category term="김맑음" label="김맑음"/><category term="미안해 (Prod. 서경교)" label="미안해 (Prod. 서경교)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김맑음/알것같아요_Prod_서경교/</id><title>김맑음 - 알것같아요 (Prod. 서경교) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:04:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:04:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%A7%91%EC%9D%8C/%EC%95%8C%EA%B2%83%EA%B0%99%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94_Prod_%EC%84%9C%EA%B2%BD%EA%B5%90/" title="김맑음 - 알것같아요 (Prod. 서경교) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나만 바라보고 있는 그대 <br>잘해도 걱정 못해도 걱정 <br>이젠 그대만을 위해 살 순 없나요 <br>내가 뭐가 그리 좋은가요 <br>난 그대를 위해 해준 게 없는데 <br>항상 그대를 <br>보면 눈물만 나 눈물만 나 <br>이젠 알 것 같아요 <br>나도 그대처럼 <br>사랑하는 사람이 있어요 <br>그대가 얼마나 날 사랑하는지 <br>이젠 알 것 같아요 <br>날 보며 행복해 했는지 미안해 <br>모든 걸 날 위해 다 주고 <br>그대 힘들고 외롭잖아요 <br>이젠 그대만을 위해 살 순 없나요 <br>내가 뭐가 그리 좋은가요 <br>난 그대를 위해 해준 게 없는데 <br>항상 그대를 <br>보면 눈물만 나 눈물만 나 <br>이젠 알 것 같아요 <br>내가 얼마나 그댈 힘들게 <br>힘들게 했는지 <br>이젠 그댈 위해 살 수 있을 것 같아 <br>이젠 알 것 같아요 <br>그댈 보면 행복하다는 걸 <br>그댈 위해 해줄 수 있는 게 <br>내 곁에 영원히 있어달라고 <br>언제까지나 사랑한다고 <br>이젠 알 것 같아요 <br>나도 그대처럼 <br>사랑하는 사람이 있어요 <br>그대가 얼마나 날 사랑하는지 <br>이젠 알 것 같아요 <br>날 보며 행복해 했는지 미안해 <br>]]></content><category term="김맑음" label="김맑음"/><category term="알것같아요 (Prod. 서경교)" label="알것같아요 (Prod. 서경교)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한영진/지금처럼_Feat_권선영/</id><title>한영진 - 지금처럼 (Feat. 권선영) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:04:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:04:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EC%98%81%EC%A7%84/%EC%A7%80%EA%B8%88%EC%B2%98%EB%9F%BC_Feat_%EA%B6%8C%EC%84%A0%EC%98%81/" title="한영진 - 지금처럼 (Feat. 권선영) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 향한 내 마음이 커질수록 <br>나는 왜 더 불안해질까 <br>손 잡고 걷고 싶고 <br>널 끌어 안고 싶고 <br>난 널 느끼고 싶어 <br>알아 너의 그 떨리는 손끝 <br>내 손을 잡고 <br>아무렇지 않은 척하는 너 <br>천천히 다가와줘 나의 곁으로 <br>있어줘요 언제나 내 곁에 <br>그대와 함께 갔던 그 카페 <br>그대와 함께 나눴던 대화들 <br>우리에겐 모든 것이 다 <br>소중한 추억 <br>어느 하나도 버릴 것이 없죠 <br>너와 처음 맞는 기념일에 <br>어떤 선물이 <br>좋을지 난 고민 고민해 <br>귀여워 고민하는 널 생각하면 <br>하루 종일 날 미소 짓게 해 <br>그대와 함께 갔던 그 카페 <br>그대와 함께 나눴던 대화들 <br>우리에겐 모든 것이 다 <br>소중한 추억 <br>어느 하나도 버릴 것이 없죠 <br>그대에게 나 많은 것을 <br>바라지 않아요 <br>지금처럼만 내 곁에서 <br>그대와 함께 갔던 그 카페 <br>그대와 함께 나눴던 대화들 <br>우리에겐 모든 것이 다 <br>소중한 추억 <br>어느 하나도 버릴 것이 없죠 <br>그대에게 수줍게 전한 내 입술 <br>내 눈을 바라보며 <br>그댄 내게 말했죠 <br>지금처럼 꽉 잡은 두 손 <br>놓지 말아요 <br>그대와 나 <br>forever love with you <br>]]></content><category term="한영진" label="한영진"/><category term="지금처럼 (Feat. 권선영)" label="지금처럼 (Feat. 권선영)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/무드살롱/캔디_크러쉬_Candy_Crush/</id><title>무드살롱 - 캔디 크러쉬 (Candy Crush) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:05:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:05:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B4%EB%93%9C%EC%82%B4%EB%A1%B1/%EC%BA%94%EB%94%94_%ED%81%AC%EB%9F%AC%EC%89%AC_Candy_Crush/" title="무드살롱 - 캔디 크러쉬 (Candy Crush) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love is candy too many taste <br>But it's one that favorite thing <br>Don't bite slowly slowly <br>chew chew <br>When its disappear <br>then I can't stop to cry <br>Before take a new <br>falling in loving you <br>Love is candy candy <br>Candy crush crush <br>Love is candy candy <br>Candy crush crush <br>Love is candy candy <br>Candy crush crush <br>Love is candy candy <br>Candy crush crush <br>Love is candy too many taste <br>But it's one that favorite thing <br>Don't bite slowly slowly <br>chew chew <br>When its disappear <br>then I can't stop to cry <br>Before take a new <br>falling in loving you <br>Love is candy candy <br>Candy crush crush <br>Love is candy candy <br>Candy crush crush <br>Love is candy candy <br>Candy crush crush <br>Love is candy candy <br>Candy crush crush <br>내 귀에 캔디에 베이비의 <br>재미의 모든 걸 거울 삼아 <br>자기의 사기 캐릭 같은 존재감 <br>내 눈에 모두 담아 <br>제일 먼저 안아줘 <br>Can't nobody <br>코흘리개 때와 같이 단순하게 <br>Look at me <br>걸어 단순한 멜로디 <br>여기에 털어 소중한 것들 <br>센치해 버렸던 <br>지난 것들에서 벗어 나 <br>무드무드 부드러운 구름 같은 너 <br>Love Candy Crush <br>Love is candy candy <br>Candy crush crush <br>Love is candy candy <br>Candy crush crush <br>Love is candy candy <br>Candy crush crush <br>Love is candy candy <br>Candy crush crush <br>Love is candy candy <br>Candy crush crush <br>Love is candy candy <br>Candy crush crush <br>]]></content><category term="무드살롱" label="무드살롱"/><category term="캔디 크러쉬 (Candy Crush)" label="캔디 크러쉬 (Candy Crush)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Im_Fine/</id><title>Chastity Belt - I`m Fine - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:05:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:05:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Im_Fine/" title="Chastity Belt - I`m Fine - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You came over to my house <br>You never asked for anything back <br>But I meant everything I said <br><br>And now I see the problem has always been me <br>But at least I'm happier <br>Now I'm fine <br><br>And we can both care <br>But not have to be there <br>You said I taught you some things <br>That I'm not even sure I believe <br><br>And now I see the problem has always been me <br>But at least I'm happier <br>Now I'm fine <br><br>Now that's no longer true <br>The problem is only you <br>But at least you're happier <br>Now you're fine]]></content><category term="Chastity Belt" label="Chastity Belt"/><category term="I`m Fine" label="I`m Fine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Bender/</id><title>Chastity Belt - Bender - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:05:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:05:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Bender/" title="Chastity Belt - Bender - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I haven't picked up in over two weeks <br>I'm living in the spaces in between <br>The less room I have to feel <br>What I really feel <br><br>I'm trying to let go <br>Of the things I used to think that you should know <br>'Cause I want to be free <br>From the hurt that I caused you to cause me <br><br>I am a liar and a freak <br>So what <br>I'm just like everybody else <br>I do fucked up things in my dreams <br>So what <br>I'm just like everybody else <br><br>I'm gonna bend until I break <br>And I'm gonna make a bunch of mistakes <br>'Cause I am doing whatever it takes <br>To get over you <br><br>I'm trying to let go <br>Of the things I used to think that you should know <br>'Cause I want to be free <br>From the hurt that I caused you to cause me <br><br>I'm a liar and a freak <br>So what <br>I'm just like everybody else <br>I do fucked up things in my dreams <br>So what <br>I'm just like everybody else <br><br>I will never be good enough <br>Good enough for you <br>But I'm already good enough for me <br>I will never be good enough for you <br>But I'm already good enough for me]]></content><category term="Chastity Belt" label="Chastity Belt"/><category term="Bender" label="Bender"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/5am/</id><title>Chastity Belt - 5am - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:05:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:05:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/5am/" title="Chastity Belt - 5am - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can't afford not to make a mistake <br>It's 5am and I'm full of hate <br>All the gauze, feel the waves in my brain <br>Saying things I shouldn't say <br><br>Immediate urge to get everything all straight <br>Need to express it, but it's not the time or place <br>Get strength from what you don't reveal <br>Communication's pretty hard <br>I've got some thoughts I cling to <br>What makes you bitter makes you old <br><br>A lot of time to sit and think <br>And the thoughts don't come naturally <br>Feeling out of touch with reality <br>But you've got the answers that I need <br><br>Immediate urge to get everything all straight <br>Need to express it, but it's not the time or place <br>Get strength from what you don't reveal <br>Communication's pretty hard <br>I've got some thoughts I cling to <br>What makes you bitter makes you old]]></content><category term="Chastity Belt" label="Chastity Belt"/><category term="5am" label="5am"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Used_to_Spend/</id><title>Chastity Belt - Used to Spend - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:05:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:05:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Used_to_Spend/" title="Chastity Belt - Used to Spend - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Talking trash <br>I like to have fun <br>Stop making sense <br>Start acting dumb <br><br>I wanna have some self control <br>I wanna be sincere <br>But nothing's ever really free when you're living in fear <br><br>Out of the fog and finally feeling fine <br>My doubts are all gone and I'm having a pretty good time <br>Feeling like a real champ, but for how long <br>I used to spend so much time alone <br><br>Higher than high <br>I wanna be bad <br>Compete with myself <br>See how much I can stand <br><br>I'd ask you to stay <br>But my pride is too strong <br>I would rather be alone than ask for what I want <br><br>Out of the fog and finally feeling fine <br>My doubts are all gone and I'm having a pretty good time <br>Feeling like a real champ, but for how long <br>I used to spend so much time alone]]></content><category term="Chastity Belt" label="Chastity Belt"/><category term="Used to Spend" label="Used to Spend"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Something_Else/</id><title>Chastity Belt - Something Else - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:05:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:05:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Something_Else/" title="Chastity Belt - Something Else - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I woke up when it was getting dark <br>That's not how life is supposed to work <br>But I got up on my own <br>And I looked at my phone <br>We're all talking about nothing <br>I wanna do something cool <br>And I wanna get paid <br>And wake up feeling great every day <br>Is that too much to ask <br>Is that too much to ask <br>Well maybe I'm an idiot <br><br>Thoughts drowned in <br>A sinking feeling <br>I'd rather be thinking about something else <br><br>Now the walls are caving in <br>I see and feel everything in waves <br>And the air is too thick <br>It's making me sick <br>I should get out and get over it <br><br>Thoughts drowned in <br>A sinking feeling <br>I'd rather be thinking about something else <br><br>A sinking feeling that I can't seem to place <br>I'd rather be thinking about something else]]></content><category term="Chastity Belt" label="Chastity Belt"/><category term="Something Else" label="Something Else"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/What_the_Hell/</id><title>Chastity Belt - What the Hell - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:05:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:05:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/What_the_Hell/" title="Chastity Belt - What the Hell - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I had a lot of thoughts today <br>I felt okay <br>I can convince myself of anything <br>So what the hell <br><br>But you tell me what I wanna hear <br>Yeah you tell me what I wanna hear <br>Sometimes I don't even know you at all <br>So what the hell <br><br>I look at my phone again, I just wanna die <br>Aside from that, I feel all right <br>I know myself when I'm by myself <br>But I'd rather be around you <br><br>Yeah you tell me what I wanna hear <br>Yeah you tell me what I wanna hear <br>Sometimes I don't even know you at all <br>So what the hell <br><br>What the hell]]></content><category term="Chastity Belt" label="Chastity Belt"/><category term="What the Hell" label="What the Hell"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Its_Obvious/</id><title>Chastity Belt - It`s Obvious - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:05:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:05:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Its_Obvious/" title="Chastity Belt - It`s Obvious - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A pretty man with a lot of hobbies <br>I can see right through you <br>I can hold your interest but only for a short time <br>And it feels freeing to lose <br><br>It's obvious <br>It's obvious <br>It's obvious <br>I'm stuck on it <br><br>Kill time in between the fake lies <br>Then gain a sense of self <br>Try to get to a place of stillness <br>Wonder what it feels like not to care <br><br>It's obvious <br>It's obvious <br>It's obvious <br>I'm stuck on it]]></content><category term="Chastity Belt" label="Chastity Belt"/><category term="It`s Obvious" label="It`s Obvious"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Complain/</id><title>Chastity Belt - Complain - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:05:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:05:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Complain/" title="Chastity Belt - Complain - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've had a drink and ate some stuff <br>Now I'm already bored <br>A couple of bros said some shit I'm choosing to ignore <br><br>I'm not okay <br>I'm not okay <br>I want to complain <br><br>I just fall on my face when I'm trying to have fun <br>Do you ever dream about what it's like to give up <br><br>I'm not okay <br>I'm not okay <br>I want to complain <br><br>I want to feel like nothing's wrong <br>Go to bed, sleep this off <br>I want to feel like nothing's wrong <br>Sleep it off, sleep it off, sleep it off <br><br>I should quit my job and get a life <br>Fuck Friday nights <br>But I want to be in the scene and there's comfort in routine <br><br>I'm not okay <br>I'm not okay <br>I want to complain]]></content><category term="Chastity Belt" label="Chastity Belt"/><category term="Complain" label="Complain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Stuck/</id><title>Chastity Belt - Stuck - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:05:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:05:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Stuck/" title="Chastity Belt - Stuck - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You feel that seeping through <br>It's calling back to you <br>An outline that you made <br>And nothing else feels quite right <br><br>You've been waiting around <br>For something to change <br>Leaving it up to fate <br>Is all the same <br><br>You're throwing the stones into water <br>And none of them make a splash <br>I'll find it something better <br>Or leaving behind what's best to lose <br><br>You've been waiting around <br>For something to change <br>Leaving it up to fate <br>Is all the same]]></content><category term="Chastity Belt" label="Chastity Belt"/><category term="Stuck" label="Stuck"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/This_Time_of_Night/</id><title>Chastity Belt - This Time of Night - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:05:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:05:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/This_Time_of_Night/" title="Chastity Belt - This Time of Night - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fucked up, anxious <br>Full of fear <br>How, how did I get here <br><br>Well I don't know <br>Pull the sheets over my eyes again <br>Unwind this time of night <br>It's wicked, but it's warm <br>And it doesn't feel right <br><br>Waiting for nothing <br>These feelings come and go <br>How, how do I get out of here <br><br>Well I don't know <br>Pull the sheets over my eyes again <br>Unwind this time of night <br>It's wicked, but it's warm <br>And it doesn't feel right <br><br>Pull the sheets over my eyes <br>Pull the sheets over my eyes <br>Pull the sheets over my eyes <br>Pull the sheets over my eyes]]></content><category term="Chastity Belt" label="Chastity Belt"/><category term="This Time of Night" label="This Time of Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Caught_in_a_Lie/</id><title>Chastity Belt - Caught in a Lie - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:05:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:05:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Caught_in_a_Lie/" title="Chastity Belt - Caught in a Lie - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're caught in a lie <br>Living someone else's dream <br>No one takes you that seriously <br>Well I can relate <br>The story's writing me <br>But the facts are false <br>What good does truth bring <br><br>Is this what you want <br>Is this who you want me to be <br>I'll take a shot of whatever you've got <br>But it's not going down that easily <br><br>You're caught in a lie <br>Living someone else's dream <br>Well I can relate <br>What good does truth bring <br><br>Is this what you want <br>Is this who you want me to be <br>I'll take a shot of whatever you've got <br>But it's not going down that easily]]></content><category term="Chastity Belt" label="Chastity Belt"/><category term="Caught in a Lie" label="Caught in a Lie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Different_Now/</id><title>Chastity Belt - Different Now - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:06:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:06:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chastity_Belt/Different_Now/" title="Chastity Belt - Different Now - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're hard on yourself <br>Well you can't always be right <br>All those little things that keep you up at night <br>You should take some time to figure out your life <br>But you're stuck indoors and thinking poorly <br><br>You'll find in time <br>All the answers that you seek <br>Have been sitting there just waiting to be seen <br>Take away your pride and take away your grief <br>And you'll finally be right where you need to be <br><br>Take all of it, take everything you're owed <br>'Til you finally feel okay being alone <br>Yeah it's different now <br>Yeah it's different now, you're old <br><br>And you try and you try and you try and you try]]></content><category term="Chastity Belt" label="Chastity Belt"/><category term="Different Now" label="Different Now"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소년은_소녀를/날_울리지마요/</id><title>소년은 소녀를 - 날 울리지마요 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:06:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:06:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84%EC%9D%80_%EC%86%8C%EB%85%80%EB%A5%BC/%EB%82%A0_%EC%9A%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88%EC%9A%94/" title="소년은 소녀를 - 날 울리지마요 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그댄 날 자꾸 울리지 마요 <br>아직 난 그대 맘 잘 모르겠어 <br>지금도 애타게 <br>너의 그 반응만 기다리는 <br>나를 바라봐줘 <br>이렇게 널 보고 있으면 <br>맘껏 미소 짓는데 <br>날 한번 더 <br>떨리게 하던 그 눈빛으로 <br>받아준다면 <br>어색한 분위기 이럼 안 되는데 <br>다른 널 보는 남자들 <br>다 나와 같은지 <br>가끔은 무관심 하게 <br>내가 널 밀어 내 볼까 <br>그럴 순 없어 <br>그댄 날 자꾸 울리지 마요 <br>아직 난 그대 맘 잘 모르겠어 <br>지금도 애타게 <br>너의 그 반응만 기다리는 <br>나를 바라봐줘 <br>이렇게 널 보고 있으면 <br>맘껏 미소 짓는데 <br>날 한번 더 <br>떨리게 하던 그 눈빛으로 <br>받아준다면 <br>어색한 분위기 이럼 안 되는데 <br>다른 널 보는 남자들 <br>다 나와 같은지 <br>가끔은 무관심 하게 <br>내가 널 밀어 내 볼까 <br>그럴 순 없어 <br>그댄 날 자꾸 울리지 마요 <br>아직 난 그대 맘 잘 모르겠어 <br>지금도 애타게 <br>너의 그 반응만 기다리는 <br>나를 바라봐줘 <br>지금 네 곁엔 그려지지 않아 <br>네 맘엔 채워지지 않아 <br>다시 날 울리게 될 시간에 <br>한번 더 내 곁에 다가와줄 네가 <br>내 맘에 채워지는 널 봐 <br>언젠가 이 품에 널 안을 수 있게 <br>그댄 날 자꾸 울리지 마요 <br>아직 난 그대 맘 잘 모르겠어 <br>지금도 애타게 <br>너의 그 반응만 기다리는 <br>나를 바라봐줘 <br>한번 더 날 헷갈리게 좀 마요 <br>내가 더 내게 솔직 할 수 있게 <br>싫대도 난 상관 안 해 <br>이미 난 그대뿐인걸 <br>사 사 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="소년은 소녀를" label="소년은 소녀를"/><category term="날 울리지마요" label="날 울리지마요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/달빛공작소/이게_아닌데_With_윤재/</id><title>달빛공작소 - 이게 아닌데 (With 윤재) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:06:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:06:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%AC%EB%B9%9B%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%91%EC%86%8C/%EC%9D%B4%EA%B2%8C_%EC%95%84%EB%8B%8C%EB%8D%B0_With_%EC%9C%A4%EC%9E%AC/" title="달빛공작소 - 이게 아닌데 (With 윤재) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[정신 차려보니 빠져들게 된 거야 <br>나도 모르게 널 기다리게 된 거야 <br>밝게 웃고 있는 귀여운 네 미소가 <br>머릿속에 남아 하루 종일 떠올라 <br>어떤 핑계로 단둘이 볼 수 있을까 <br>그냥 보고 싶다 만나자고 해볼까 <br>우연히 흘러나온 너와 듣던 노래가 <br>머릿속에 남아 하루 종일 떠올라 <br>너무 조용한 핸드폰이 괜히 불안해 <br>어디에 있니 뭘 하고 있는지 <br>이게 아닌데 <br>뭐가 이렇게 바보 같은지 <br>널 좋아한다 말도 못하고 <br>그저 맘으로 바라만 보는 <br>바라보고 있는 나를 <br>떨리는 맘으로 전화번호 누르고 <br>어떤 말을 하고 어떤 대화를 할지 <br>마침 들려오는 귀여운 네 목소리 <br>이상하게 점점 머릿속은 하얗게 <br>전화를 받고 안부를 물으니 <br>할 말이 없어 <br>심장은 뛰고 손에 땀은 나고 <br>이게 아닌데 <br>뭐가 이렇게 바보 같은지 <br>널 좋아한다 말도 못하고 <br>그저 맘으로 바라만 보는 <br>바라보고 있는 나를 <br>좋아하는데 널 좋아하는 내 마음을 <br>담아 보낼 순 없을까 <br>저기 아름다운 너 걸어온다 <br>참을 수가 없어 기다릴 수 없어 oh <br>뭐가 이렇게 바보 같은지 <br>널 좋아한다 말도 못하고 <br>그저 맘으로 바라만 보는 <br>바라보고 있는 나를 <br>뭐가 이렇게 떨리는 건지 <br>널 좋아한다 말을 하는 게 <br>내 말에 웃어주는 널 보며 <br>널 사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="달빛공작소" label="달빛공작소"/><category term="이게 아닌데 (With 윤재)" label="이게 아닌데 (With 윤재)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/허밍고트/너에게_Demo/</id><title>허밍고트 - 너에게 (Demo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:06:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:06:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%88%EB%B0%8D%EA%B3%A0%ED%8A%B8/%EB%84%88%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_Demo/" title="허밍고트 - 너에게 (Demo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[만약 네 맘을 볼 수 있다면 <br>제일 낡은 액자 속 사진부터 <br>빛 바랜 기억들을 꺼내 <br>내 눈 안에 담을 거야 <br>내 맘이 너로 인해 변하고 <br>내 세상이 환하게 비춰질 때 <br>내 눈 안에 담았던 기억들 <br>너에게 아낌없이 줄게 오 <br>이렇게 널 이해하고 싶어 <br>언제나 널 그려낼 수 있고 <br>너에게 꼭 해줄 말이 있어 <br>네 맘 힘들지 않았으면 참 좋겠어 <br>그땐 나도 너를 보며 밝게 웃고 싶어 <br>너에게 아낌없이 줄게 오 <br>이렇게 널 이해하고 싶어 <br>언제나 널 그려낼 수 있고 <br>너에게 꼭 해줄 말이 있어 <br>네 맘 힘들지 않았으면 참 좋겠어 <br>그땐 나도 너를 보며 밝게 웃고 싶어 <br>흘려야 할 눈물이 너무나 많아도 <br>우리가 셀 추억들이 더 값질 테니까 <br>]]></content><category term="허밍고트" label="허밍고트"/><category term="너에게 (Demo)" label="너에게 (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/허밍고트/너에게/</id><title>허밍고트 - 너에게 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:07:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:07:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%88%EB%B0%8D%EA%B3%A0%ED%8A%B8/%EB%84%88%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C/" title="허밍고트 - 너에게 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[만약 네 맘을 볼 수 있다면 <br>제일 낡은 액자 속 사진부터 <br>빛 바랜 기억들을 꺼내 <br>내 눈 안에 담을 거야 <br>내 맘이 너로 인해 변하고 <br>내 세상이 환하게 비춰질 때 <br>내 눈 안에 담았던 기억들 <br>너에게 아낌없이 줄게 오 <br>이렇게 널 이해하고 싶어 <br>언제나 널 그려낼 수 있고 <br>너에게 꼭 해줄 말이 있어 <br>네 맘 힘들지 않았으면 참 좋겠어 <br>그땐 나도 너를 보며 밝게 웃고 싶어 <br>너에게 아낌없이 줄게 오 <br>이렇게 널 이해하고 싶어 <br>언제나 널 그려낼 수 있고 <br>너에게 꼭 해줄 말이 있어 <br>네 맘 힘들지 않았으면 참 좋겠어 <br>그땐 나도 너를 보며 밝게 웃고 싶어 <br>흘려야 할 눈물이 너무나 많아도 <br>우리가 셀 추억들이 더 값질 테니까 <br>]]></content><category term="허밍고트" label="허밍고트"/><category term="너에게" label="너에게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이준형/우리끼리_2017_New_Ver/</id><title>이준형 - 우리끼리 (2017. New Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:07:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:07:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%A4%80%ED%98%95/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%81%BC%EB%A6%AC_2017_New_Ver/" title="이준형 - 우리끼리 (2017. New Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1절 <br><br>강 건너 산 넘어 <br><br>영화 같은 인생길 <br><br>사연도 참 많았다 <br><br>당신이 있어서 <br><br>아파도 참고 <br><br>슬퍼도 웃으며 <br><br>견디어 왔다 <br><br>아들은 더 이상 <br><br>내 자식이 아니야 <br><br>사돈의 사위 <br><br>며느리 남편 <br><br>딸도 더 이상 <br><br>내 자식이 아니야 <br><br>사돈의 며느리 <br><br>사위의 아내 <br><br>이제는 우리끼리 <br><br>사랑하며 살아요 <br><br>(여행도 다니면서) <br><br>(행복하게 살아요) <br><br>이제는 우리끼리 <br><br>의지하며 살아요 <br><br>(더 이상 자식에게) <br><br>(기대하지 말아요) <br><br>못다한 일을 하며 <br><br>우리끼리 살아요 <br><br>후렴: <br><br>아들은 더 이상 <br><br>내 자식이 아니야 <br><br>사돈의 사위 <br><br>며느리 남편 <br><br>딸도 더 이상 <br><br>내 자식이 아니야 <br><br>사돈의 며느리 <br><br>사위의 아내 <br><br>이제는 우리끼리 <br><br>사랑하며 살아요 <br><br>(여행도 다니면서) <br><br>(행복하게 살아요) <br><br>이제는 우리끼리 <br><br>의지하며 살아요 <br><br>(더 이상 자식에게) <br><br>(기대하지 말아요) <br><br>못다한 일을 하며 <br><br>우리끼리 살아요 <br><br>이제는 우리끼리 <br><br>사랑하며 살아요 <br><br>(여행도 다니면서) <br><br>(행복하게 살아요) <br><br>이제는 우리끼리 <br><br>의지하며 살아요 <br><br>(더이상 자식에게) <br><br>(기대하지 말아요) <br><br>못다한 일을 하며 <br><br>우리끼리 살아요 <br><br>못다한 일을 하며 <br><br>우리끼리 살아요 <br><br>1.2절 가사]]></content><category term="이준형" label="이준형"/><category term="우리끼리 (2017. New Ver.)" label="우리끼리 (2017. New Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ferry/Persian_Cat_Feat_SIJEL/</id><title>Ferry - Persian Cat (Feat. SIJEL) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:07:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:07:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ferry/Persian_Cat_Feat_SIJEL/" title="Ferry - Persian Cat (Feat. SIJEL) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[you are the one <br>make me feel so <br>crazy whole night <br>I love you tho' <br>you’re exciting me <br>by your kiss at the door <br>you’re exciting me <br>by your body on the floor <br>I never forgive <br>if you want to betray me <br>you promised me <br>always to stand by me <br>when the night is cold <br>or the day is so hot <br>stay with me <br>hold my hand <br>side to side <br>you are the one <br>make me feel so <br>crazy whole night <br>I love you tho' <br>you’re exciting me <br>by your kiss at the door <br>you’re exciting me <br>by your body on the floor <br>I never forgive <br>if you want to betray me <br>you promised me <br>always to stand by me <br>when the night is cold <br>or the day is so hot <br>stay with me <br>hold my hand <br>side to side <br>]]></content><category term="Ferry" label="Ferry"/><category term="Persian Cat (Feat. SIJEL)" label="Persian Cat (Feat. SIJEL)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김지원/아시나요/</id><title>김지원 - 아시나요 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:08:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:08:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%80%EC%9B%90/%EC%95%84%EC%8B%9C%EB%82%98%EC%9A%94/" title="김지원 - 아시나요 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1절 <br><br>아시나요 정말 알고 있나요 <br><br>누굴 위해 내가 웃고 있는지 <br><br>이슬비에 젖으며 살고 <br><br>지쳐 쓰러진대로 <br><br>당신 때문에 하루를 버팁니다 <br><br>고목처럼 나 하나만 바라보는 사람아 <br><br>지금처럼 내 곁에 있어줘요 <br><br>당신만 사랑합니다 <br><br>꿈꾸뜻 그리 살아요 <br><br>내가 던져준 사랑의 끈 <br><br>다시 단단히 메주세요 <br><br>당신 가슴에 영원히 영원히(한번더) <br><br>1.2절 가사]]></content><category term="김지원" label="김지원"/><category term="아시나요" label="아시나요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공유빈/브라보_창원/</id><title>공유빈 - 브라보 창원 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:08:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:08:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%EC%9C%A0%EB%B9%88/%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EB%B3%B4_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9B%90/" title="공유빈 - 브라보 창원 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꽃잎 따라 오솔길에 <br>살랑살랑 바람이 불면 <br>소곤소곤 창원의 밤 <br>불빛마다 아름다워라 <br>벚꽃 길 거닐던 내 사랑아 <br>행복 길 누비길 윙크하면서 <br>오색분수 로맨스에 <br>둘이 둘이 둘이 사랑을 하고 <br>거리거리마다 행복이 있네 <br>브라보 창원 내사랑 <br>파도 따라 마산항에 <br>찰랑찰랑 물결이치면 <br>두근두근 창동의 밤 <br>연인들이 아름다워라 <br>오동동 거닐던 내 사랑아 <br>무학산 둘레길 윙크하면서 <br>항구의 밤 로맨스에 <br>둘이 둘이 둘이 사랑을 하고 <br>거리거리마다 행복이 있네 <br>브라보 창원 내 사랑 <br>둘이 둘이 둘이 사랑을 하고 <br>거리거리마다 행복이 있네 <br>브라보 창원 내 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="공유빈" label="공유빈"/><category term="브라보 창원" label="브라보 창원"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공유빈/로망스_사랑/</id><title>공유빈 - 로망스 사랑 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:08:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:08:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%EC%9C%A0%EB%B9%88/%EB%A1%9C%EB%A7%9D%EC%8A%A4_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="공유빈 - 로망스 사랑 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[로망스 다리에서 만난 그 사람 <br>처음 본 순간부터 좋았던 사람 <br>꽃바람을 타고 꽃구름을 타고 <br>내게도 사랑이 찾아왔어요 <br>바람도 새들도 날 위해 <br>휘파람을 불고 <br>별들도 꽃들과 노래하네요 <br>이밤이 다가도록 사랑을 노래해요 <br>사랑스런 당신 아름다운 당신 <br>로망스 사랑 <br>진해루 벤치에서 정든그 사람 <br>처음 본 순간부터 좋았던 사람 <br>꽃바람을 타고 꽃구름을 타고 <br>내게도 사랑이 찾아왔어요 <br>바람도 새들도 날 위해 <br>휘파람을 불고 <br>별들도 꽃들과 노래하네요 <br>이밤이 다가도록 사랑을 노래해요 <br>사랑스런 당신 아름다운 당신 <br>로망스 사랑 <br>이밤이 다가도록 사랑을 노래해요 <br>사랑스런 당신 아름다운 당신 <br>로망스 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="공유빈" label="공유빈"/><category term="로망스 사랑" label="로망스 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공유빈/남편아닌_내편/</id><title>공유빈 - 남편아닌 내편 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:08:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:08:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%EC%9C%A0%EB%B9%88/%EB%82%A8%ED%8E%B8%EC%95%84%EB%8B%8C_%EB%82%B4%ED%8E%B8/" title="공유빈 - 남편아닌 내편 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 세상에 처음으로 사랑한 사람 <br>당신은 나만의 사랑 <br>난 별로 당신께 해준 게 없는데 <br>늘 곁에 있어준 사람 <br>바람만 불어도 고갤 돌리는 <br>너무도 야속한 세상이지만 <br>슬프지 않아 울지도 않아 <br>당신이 곁에 있으니 <br>언제나 남편 아닌 내편 <br>당신은 남편 아닌 내편 <br>언제나 남편 아닌 내편 <br>당신은 영원한 나만의 사랑 <br>바람만 불어도 고갤 돌리는 <br>너무도 야속한 세상이지만 <br>슬프지 않아 울지도 않아 <br>당신이 곁에 있으니 <br>언제나 남편 아닌 내편 <br>당신은 남편 아닌 내편 <br>언제나 남편 아닌 내편 <br>당신은 영원한 나만의 사랑 <br>언제나 남편 아닌 내편 <br>당신은 남편 아닌 내편 <br>언제나 남편 아닌 내편 <br>당신은 영원한 나만의 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="공유빈" label="공유빈"/><category term="남편아닌 내편" label="남편아닌 내편"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공유빈/어머니/</id><title>공유빈 - 어머니 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:08:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:08:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%EC%9C%A0%EB%B9%88/%EC%96%B4%EB%A8%B8%EB%8B%88/" title="공유빈 - 어머니 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[거친 이랑 일구어서 <br>새벽바람 기차 타고 <br>역전시장 노점한쪽 <br>굽은 손 울 어머니 <br>어머니 내 어머니 <br>내가 부모 되어보니 <br>지고지순 당신 사랑 <br>이제 겨우 알 것 같소 <br>새벽바다 항구 한쪽 <br>꼬막 조개 펼쳐놓고 <br>자나깨나 자식걱정 <br>굽은 손 울 어머니 <br>어머니 내 어머니 <br>내가 부모 되어보니 <br>지고지순 당신 사랑 <br>이제 겨우 알 것 같소 <br>어머니 내 어머니 <br>내가 부모 되어보니 <br>지고지순 당신 사랑 <br>이제 겨우 알 것 같소 <br>]]></content><category term="공유빈" label="공유빈"/><category term="어머니" label="어머니"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clint_Westwood_클린트_웨스트우드/관계_Feat_Horim/</id><title>Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드) - 관계 (Feat. Horim) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:10:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:10:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clint_Westwood_%ED%81%B4%EB%A6%B0%ED%8A%B8_%EC%9B%A8%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EC%9A%B0%EB%93%9C/%EA%B4%80%EA%B3%84_Feat_Horim/" title="Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드) - 관계 (Feat. Horim) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[a yo 낮과 밤 엄마가 깰까 봐 <br>매일 헤드폰 소리 줄이며 <br>데이트한 날들 <br>속에서 바뀐 계절에 색을 더해가 <br>한 우물 파느라 놓친 <br>인간관계엔 오해만 <br>남고 쌓여서 처지가 조금 가여워 <br>뻔한 사람들 속에 나누는 <br>말들은 많이 가벼워 <br>진한 우정을 나눴던 <br>친구들을 오랜만에 보고는 <br>세월엔 덧없어 <br>라고 말하는 내 자신과 <br>수긍하는 몇 몇 속에 <br>좋았던 분위기는 어느새 숙연해 <br>괜히 말했다 싶어 고갤 숙였네 <br>한잔해 한잔해 이 잔에 떨쳐내 <br>왔던 길 보다 갈 길이 <br>더 많이 남았기에 <br>한잔해 한잔해 딱 예전처럼 <br>좆도 없어도 웃고 지내던 <br>그날들처럼 let's go <br>밤이 나의 맘에다 물어봐 <br>Am I doing right <br>I'm doing right <br>저 하늘이 덧없이 말해주네 <br>Find your way uh oh <br>you got your day uh oh <br>쌓아놓은 말들을 내뱉지 않고 <br>꾹 삼키며 <br>겉도는 말들로 마냥 <br>웃으며 넘기는 상황 속에 <br>절레절레 젓는 고개 <br>어찌 보면 이게 더 익숙해 우린 <br>너무 멀리 와있어 <br>엄마가 말하던 다다익선 <br>많으면 많을수록 좋다던 <br>수많은 인간관계 속에 <br>나는 너무 잘게 잘려서 <br>흩뿌려져 있어 <br>누굴 탓하긴 어려운데 <br>항상 화살 끝은 남에게로 향해 있네 <br>좋은 척 하기 어려운데 <br>잡생각들로 머릿속은 하얘지네 <br>그럼 한잔해 한잔해 이 잔에 떨쳐내 <br>왔던 길 보다 갈 길이 <br>더 많이 남았기에 <br>한잔해 한잔해 딱 예전처럼 <br>좆도 없어도 웃고 지내던 <br>그날들처럼 let's go <br>밤이 나의 맘에다 물어봐 <br>Am I doing right <br>I'm doing right <br>저 하늘이 덧없이 말해주네 <br>Find your way uh oh <br>you got your day uh oh <br>같이 굵어진 머리와 <br>가늠할 수 없는 계산 속 <br>각자의 방식대로 다들 <br>생각하며 자랐어 <br>가끔 내 생각이 옳다는 <br>답에 닿아도 <br>침묵이 때로는 금이란 <br>생각에 눈 감았어 <br>아직 이 좁은 사람 <br>사이의 관계 안에서 <br>우린 수없이 헤매는데 <br>답이 정해져 있지 않다는 사실이 <br>나를 더욱 많이 괴롭히네 <br>괴롭히고 또 괴롭히네 <br>날이 갈 수록 외롭긴 해 <br>고치지 못한 나의 서툰 삶의 방식 <br>생각하고 또 생각해 <br>I feel it right away <br>이 길의 밤이 외로 <br>운 빛을 담아 에오 <br>난 내일의 나를 왜 <br>이리도 많이 괴로 <br>운 길을 가게 해 oh <br>]]></content><category term="Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드)" label="Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드)"/><category term="관계 (Feat. Horim)" label="관계 (Feat. Horim)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clint_Westwood_클린트_웨스트우드/Life/</id><title>Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드) - Life - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:10:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:10:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clint_Westwood_%ED%81%B4%EB%A6%B0%ED%8A%B8_%EC%9B%A8%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EC%9A%B0%EB%93%9C/Life/" title="Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드) - Life - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뭐든 할 수 있을 것 같았던 나의 청춘 <br>주변에선 나이의 숫자 따위로 <br>나를 겁주곤 <br>지금부터라도 열심히 살어 <br>what the fxxk <br>난 매일 매일 열심히 살어 <br>떠 있는 달이 내겐 익숙한 시간 <br>내 혼을 바친 결과물들을 믿지 난 <br>매일 버릇처럼 달고 다니는 <br>superstar <br>되지 않아도 좋아 <br>imma just be original <br>궁상맞은 사색이 짙어질 때쯤 <br>나오란 친구 놈의 전화 기울이는 맥주 <br>시시콜콜한 농담만 따먹다 <br>나오는 결론은 이번 생도 글렀다 <br>ay man 진정하구 진정하구 <br>위로 받고 싶은 사람은 나였다고 <br>네 놈은 안정적인 삶이라 말하던 찰나 <br>가만 보니까 네 인생도 참 가엽다고 <br>Life 다 똑같지 <br>다른 듯 보여도 다 똑같이 <br>허우적대네 허우적대네 <br>허우적대네 허우적대네 <br>뭐든 할 수 있을 것 같았던 너의 청춘 <br>이제 와서 뭐든 <br>시켜 주기만 하면 다 한다니 <br>세상이 원하는 인재상을 <br>요구사항에 따라 <br>딱 deadline에 맞춰 놨지 <br>상에 걸맞는 인재가 된 네 모습을 보며 <br>애들 다 모여 축하 파티를 한 지가 1년 <br>쯤 지났어 <br>이제 와서 하고 싶은 거 하며 살아가는 <br>이 모습이 정말 부럽다니 <br>ay 그건 상대적인 거라구 <br>나도 내 나름 가지고 있는 <br>고민들이 있다구 <br>나를 걱정하는 엄마와 아빠의 <br>따가운 시선 <br>이런 것들 내 뺨을 때려 이따금 <br>ay man 진정하구 진정하구 <br>위로 받을 사람이 나 말고 너였다니 <br>네 놈은 하고픈 대로 살아 <br>좋겠다 하던 찰나 <br>가만 보니 네 인생도 가엽다고 <br>Life 다 똑같지 <br>다른 듯 보여도 다 똑같이 <br>허우적대네 허우적대네 <br>허우적대네 허우적대네 <br>내일은 내일의 해가 뜬다는 말이 <br>가끔 어떨 땐 헛소리로 들려 <br>어느 위치건 아등바등 <br>쳇바퀴 굴러가듯 <br>똑같은 삶은 비눗방울 <br>닿았다 싶으면 사라지고 <br>더 힘차게 불어라 얼른 커지려면 <br>what you talkin bout <br>뭘 더 크게 하고 뭘 더 굴려야 해 <br>여태 배운 건 똑같은 <br>guideline 뿐인데 <br>]]></content><category term="Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드)" label="Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드)"/><category term="Life" label="Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clint_Westwood_클린트_웨스트우드/My_Ballad/</id><title>Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드) - My Ballad - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:10:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:10:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clint_Westwood_%ED%81%B4%EB%A6%B0%ED%8A%B8_%EC%9B%A8%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EC%9A%B0%EB%93%9C/My_Ballad/" title="Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드) - My Ballad - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[시작은 열일곱 <br>범물동 어느 목욕탕 <br>내 친구 종석이랑 <br>시시콜콜 떠들다 <br>전날 봤던 윤도현의 <br>love letter 얘기 <br>movement 나와서 move the <br>crowd하던 광경에 <br>존나게 뻑 갔지 <br>우리도 왼손을 들면 <br>사람들 오른손 들까 <br>반신반의 하며 <br>경북고 축제에 올라 <br>공연이 끝나고 반응 봐봐 holla <br>내 훤칠한 친구 <br>싸이월드 투데이는 <br>4-500을 찍고 <br>나도 그에 못지않게 <br>인기가 정점을 찍고 <br>자연스레 시험 답안지는 <br>문제도 안보고 찍고 <br>우린 세상 다 가진 듯 <br>취해서 주변 여고들을 <br>돌며 공연하기 시작해 <br>그땐 진짜 내가 세상에서 <br>젤 쩌는 놈인 줄만 알았네 <br>그런 줄 알았네 <br>임마 힙합 할려면 <br>외국 꺼 들어야 돼 <br>hip하게 보이려고 <br>처음 샀던 mos def <br>fairplay 옷가게서 <br>2xl 무지티도 샀네 <br>복장은 거의 gangster <br>big shit poppin <br>동네서 이렇게 하는 놈 없었지 <br>축제가 끝나면 <br>여고생들 기다리던 <br>교문을 연예인처럼 <br>얼굴을 가리며 <br>나와서 받은 페이로 먹은 <br>꽁꽁 얼은 고깃집 고기와 <br>꽁꽁 언 손 발 녹이며 <br>쑥스러운 듯 멀리서 지켜보던 <br>대구여고 가디건 <br>대구여고 가디건 <br>내가 짱인 줄 알았지 그땐 <br>뭣도 모르고 들었던 우탱 <br>덩치 큰 형들 멋에 흠뻑 취해 <br>미간 찌푸리며 험한 표정 짓네 <br>내가 짱인 줄 알았지 그땐 <br>뭣도 모르고 들었던 우탱 <br>덩치 큰 형들 멋에 흠뻑 취해 <br>미간 찌푸리며 험한 표정 짓네 <br>취한 듯 살다 얼마 안 가서 <br>존나 쩌는 형 하날 <br>소문으로 들었어 <br>나보다 한 학년 높은데 <br>자기 앨범까지 있네 <br>가사를 자기가 직접 써 <br>존나 충격 받았네 <br>uncut pure <br>수줍은 용기를 내뱉던 <br>그 사람 rap이 <br>울려 퍼지던 대명동 heavy <br>랩 하는 사람은 <br>정해져 있었구나 싶어 멘탈은 <br>집 밖을 나갔지 <br>그때부터 copy rapper에서 <br>그냥 열성 fan 됐어 <br>뒤 쫄쫄 따라다니며 <br>hova처럼 물고 있던 cigar <br>한대 펴보라며 주던 <br>존나 멋진 형의 기억 <br>그쯤부터 취미로 <br>끄적이던 가사엔 <br>내 수줍은 용기를 담아내 <br>첫 여자친구에게 쓴 노래와 기억 <br>재능 있다며 날 추켜 올려주던 <br>네 손 잡고 뛰어 <br>지금만 같았음 하던 <br>최고의 삶도 얼마 안가 지고 <br>꽁꽁 언 손 발 녹이며 <br>고향 앞으로 절하던 철원 <br>절하던 철원 <br>내가 짱인 줄 알았지 그땐 <br>뭣도 모르고 들었던 우탱 <br>덩치 큰 형들 멋에 흠뻑 취해 <br>미간 찌푸리며 험한 표정 짓네 <br>내가 짱인 줄 알았지 그땐 <br>뭣도 모르고 들었던 우탱 <br>덩치 큰 형들 멋에 흠뻑 취해 <br>미간 찌푸리며 험한 표정 짓네 <br>알맹이 없던 삶에 <br>계급만 다 채워서 제대 후에 <br>집밖을 나와 거리를 걸을 때 <br>엄청 잦은 빈도로 <br>들을 수 있는 drum base line <br>그 위에 내 목소리 <br>얹어놓는 상상을 해 <br>목욕탕에서 종석이랑 <br>얘기 나눌 때처럼 <br>무작정 철없이 덤벼들었던 <br>젊은 날의 내가 <br>나의 삶 전체를 <br>180도 바꿔 놨네 <br>나의 삶을 가꿔야 해 <br>누군간 섹스를 위해 <br>누군간 계몽을 위해 <br>누군간 철학을 위해 <br>누군간 예술을 위해 <br>다 좋지 난 그 모두를 위해 <br>내 삶 전체를 아우르는 <br>자신을 위해 <br>내 자신을 위해 <br>남들 따라 하기만 <br>바빴던 꼬맹이가 <br>삶의 온갖 풍파 <br>맞으면서 여물어가 <br>아직도 나의 어린 날의 <br>근거 없던 자신감이 <br>미약해도 여기까지 <br>끌고 온 원동력인 듯해 <br>꽁꽁 언 맘 이제는 녹일 때 <br>녹일 때 <br>내가 짱인 줄 알았지 그땐 <br>뭣도 모르고 들었던 우탱 <br>덩치 큰 형들 멋에 흠뻑 취해 <br>미간 찌푸리며 험한 표정 짓네 <br>내가 짱인 줄 알았지 그땐 <br>뭣도 모르고 들었던 우탱 <br>덩치 큰 형들 멋에 흠뻑 취해 <br>미간 찌푸리며 험한 표정 짓네 <br>]]></content><category term="Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드)" label="Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드)"/><category term="My Ballad" label="My Ballad"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clint_Westwood_클린트_웨스트우드/reLAxSEOUL/</id><title>Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드) - reLAxSEOUL - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T00:10:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T00:10:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clint_Westwood_%ED%81%B4%EB%A6%B0%ED%8A%B8_%EC%9B%A8%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EC%9A%B0%EB%93%9C/reLAxSEOUL/" title="Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드) - reLAxSEOUL - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[복잡한 서울시 <br>내 일 아닌 듯이 웃지 <br>내 친군 내 삶이 어리석다는 듯 <br>한숨 쉬며 날 비웃지 <br>마음대로 생각해 man <br>내키는 대로 살 건데 <br>내 주제는 내가 잘 알아서 <br>항상 규정 속돌 지켜내 <br>fresh 신발은 항상 나이키 <br>공기가 가득해서 <br>작아도 괜찮아 나의 키 <br>이미 손바닥은 저 하늘과 닿아 있지 <br>flash 가만히 있어도 <br>누군가 알아서 날 빛내줬음 하지 <br>천천히 가고 있어 <br>누군가 나를 빛내줬음 해 <br>천천히 가고 있어 <br>누군가 나를 빛내줬음 해 <br>아직 나는 너무 어려 <br>아직 나는 너무 어려 <br>내게 세상은 어려워 <br>내게 세상은 어려워 <br>서울은 복잡해서 <br>날 알아봐 줄 수가 없어 <br>난 지치지 않아서 계속 <br>뛰어 볼 거야 울 엄마 죄송 <br>답답한 도로에 내 발을 디디고 <br>자유로이 가고파 <br>강변북로 view도 좋지만 <br>악셀에 힘껏 발 올리고 파 <br>도착한 곳은 neverland <br>친구들은 벌써 헤벌레 <br>표정만 보고 있어도 나는 재밌네 <br>선진시민 우린 깨어 있네 <br>여기서 못 놀면 그걸로 죄인 돼 <br>relax 우리 뜻대로 하자고 <br>relax 너 꼴리는 대로 걍 하라고 <br>relax 우리 뜻대로 하자고 <br>relax 너 꼴리는 대로 걍 하라고 <br>걍 하라고 걍 하라고 <br>걍 하라고 걍 하라고 <br>relax relax relax <br>우리 뜻대로 하자고 <br>relax <br>너 꼴리는 대로 <br>걍 하라고 걍 하라고 <br>]]></content><category term="Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드)" label="Clint Westwood (클린트 웨스트우드)"/><category term="reLAxSEOUL" label="reLAxSEOUL"/></entry></feed>