<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:17+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루또_LUTTO/호미/</id><title>루또 (LUTTO) - 호미 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%EB%98%90_LUTTO/%ED%98%B8%EB%AF%B8/" title="루또 (LUTTO) - 호미 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[호걸이야 호미 <br>의심 마 호미 <br>굳이 말 하지 <br>않으려 했지만 굳이 말 하지 <br>호걸이야 호미 <br>의심 마 호미 <br>굳이 말 하지 <br>않으려 했지만 굳이 말 하지 <br>호걸이야 호미 <br>엄마는 조개 캐러 가는걸 좋아해 <br>요즘은 다들 바쁘니깐 <br>근 몇 년 간은 못 갔네 <br>속상해 그때마다 <br>호미는 꼭 챙겨가래 <br>엄마는 매번 내 것만큼은 <br>좋은 호미로 골랐대 <br>호미 호미 호미 <br>그래서 내 옆에 호미들은 <br>다 날이 섰어 <br>뭘 캘지는 모르겠지만 <br>그건 아마도 빛이 영롱해 <br>내 주변에 남은 호미는 <br>이제 몇 개 없어 <br>아무거나 쓰기엔 <br>내 호미들이 멋져 <br>다 같이 깊은 곳으로 <br>들어가다 보니 보물섬을 <br>봤어 우린 배를 띄우고 <br>이름을 붙여 빅부리호 <br>물이 계속 들어오고 <br>또 노 저어 또 노 저어 <br>든든하지 파머형도 올라탔고 <br>순항 중이야 진짜 <br>호걸이야 호미 <br>의심 마 호미 <br>굳이 말 하지 <br>않으려 했지만 굳이 말 하지 <br>호걸이야 호미 <br>의심 마 호미 <br>굳이 말 하지 <br>않으려 했지만 굳이 말 하지 <br>호걸이야 호미 <br>계속 노를 저어 꾸준히 <br>기나긴 항해 끝에 그 영광이 <br>내 건빵 주머니 속을 두둑히 <br>그 영광들로 더 멋지게 <br>음악을 만들어내고 <br>즐기면서 두둠칫 <br>아니 이건 그때 가서 <br>말하기로 하고 <br>우리 배는 충분히 <br>많이 넘어왔지 수천 번의 큰 파도 <br>이제 왠만한 건 두렵지도 않다고 <br>가만히 있으면 멈추는 게 아닌 <br>뒤로 가는 것도 이제 다 안다고 <br>우린 제대로 왔어 <br>이제 진짜로 말야 <br>그렸던 그림까지는 <br>얼마 안 남았어 <br>그래 진짜로 호걸이야 호미 <br>빛이 영롱한걸 캐 <br>날이 바짝 서있는 <br>내 호미들로 캐 <br>멋진 항해 끝에 <br>놓여져 있을 거야 케잌 <br>나도 창모처럼 <br>돈 캘 시간 돈 케잌 <br>호걸이야 호미 <br>의심 마 호미 <br>굳이 말 하지 <br>않으려 했지만 굳이 말 하지 <br>호걸이야 호미 <br>빛이 영롱한걸 캐 <br>날이 바짝 서있는 <br>내 호미들로 캐 <br>멋진 항해 끝에 <br>놓여져 있을 거야 케잌 <br>나도 창모처럼 <br>돈 캘 시간 돈 케잌 <br>호걸이야 호미 <br>의심 마 호미 <br>굳이 말 하지 <br>않으려 했지만 굳이 말 하지 <br>호걸이야 호미 <br>의심 마 호미 <br>굳이 말 하지 <br>않으려 했지만 굳이 말 하지 <br>호걸이야 호미 <br>]]></content><category term="루또 (LUTTO)" label="루또 (LUTTO)"/><category term="호미" label="호미"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루또_LUTTO/같은노래/</id><title>루또 (LUTTO) - 같은노래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%EB%98%90_LUTTO/%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="루또 (LUTTO) - 같은노래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[똑같은 노래 가사야 <br>전에 듣던 노래 같아 <br>내 맘이 가는 대로 할 거야 <br>내 발이 가는 대로 갈 거야 <br>똑같은 노래 똑같은 얘기야 <br>전에 했던 얘기 또 같은 얘기야 <br>맘이 가는 대로 막 하는 얘기 <br>맘이 발이 가는 대로 <br>또 가는 얘기야 <br>발이 가는 대로 가다 보니 <br>창문 활짝 열고 빵빵한 저 여자 <br>몸매 같은 음악소리 틀고 <br>달리는 좋은 차 <br>쟨 핸들을 휙휙 돌려 <br>난 걸으며 팔을 휘휘 저어 <br>뭐 어때 걸으면 어때 <br>덕분에 내 신발은 밑창이 없네 <br>깔창을 신고 다니는 기분 <br>그것 마저 없었다면 <br>난 거의 구석기 시대를 체험해 <br>그래도 난 아주 좋아 <br>행복한 게 맞을 거야 <br>아직 한 푼도 못 벌지만 <br>그 놈보다 행복한 게 맞을 거야 <br>행복한 척 계속 할 거고 <br>그건 음악으로 계속 만들 거고 <br>그 음악은 계속 비슷할 거고 <br>그 음악은 계속 존나 좋을 거야 <br>그 음악은 계속 존나 멋질 거야 <br>똑같은 노래 가사야 <br>전에 듣던 노래 같아 <br>내 맘이 가는 대로 할 거야 <br>내 발이 가는 대로 갈 거야 <br>똑같은 노래 똑같은 얘기야 <br>전에 했던 얘기 또 같은 얘기야 <br>맘이 가는 대로 막 하는 얘기 <br>맘이 발이 가는 대로 <br>또 가는 얘기야 <br>어제 일도 가사가 됐네 <br>가고 하는 대로 노래하니 <br>음악이 됐네 <br>비슷한 얘기 같은 얘기야 <br>근데 뭔가 많이 다르네 <br>내 노래 계속 체크 했다면 <br>나랑 친구된 기분이겠네 <br>내 주변엔 멋진 사람들만 있지 <br>물론 그건 내가 <br>멋진 사람이라는 뜻이 되고 <br>난 그들을 믿지 <br>여자얘기도 사랑얘기도 <br>난 아주 좋아 <br>술 마시는 것도 아주 좋아 <br>근데 주당은 아닌 거야 <br>내 얘기로만 가득할 거야 <br>돈이 없단 얘기 <br>그래도 좋단 얘기 <br>떳떳하단 얘기 괜찮다는 얘기 <br>이기적인 새끼들은 싫단 얘기 <br>계속할게 이 똑같은 얘기 <br>또 돈이 없단 얘기 <br>그래도 좋단 얘기 <br>떳떳하단 얘기 괜찮다는 얘기 <br>이기적인 새끼들은 싫단 얘기 <br>계속할게 똑같이 <br>똑같은 노래 가사야 <br>전에 듣던 노래 같아 <br>내 맘이 가는 대로 할 거야 <br>내 발이 가는 대로 갈 거야 <br>똑같은 노래 똑같은 얘기야 <br>전에 했던 얘기 또 같은 얘기야 <br>맘이 가는 대로 막 하는 얘기 <br>맘이 발이 가는 대로 <br>또 가는 얘기야 <br>]]></content><category term="루또 (LUTTO)" label="루또 (LUTTO)"/><category term="같은노래" label="같은노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루또_LUTTO/소박_Feat_Don_Mills/</id><title>루또 (LUTTO) - 소박 (Feat. Don Mills) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%EB%98%90_LUTTO/%EC%86%8C%EB%B0%95_Feat_Don_Mills/" title="루또 (LUTTO) - 소박 (Feat. Don Mills) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[즐겨 듣던 외국 힙합 음악 <br>가사가 궁금했어 엘이해석 <br>찾아 들어갔지 <br>와 이 신나는 곡 가사가 다 <br>돈 자랑 이었네 <br>그럼 나도 그런 노래 만들어봐 <br>귓속에 꽂은 이어폰 십 삼 만원 짜리 <br>슈루챌 나갔다가 이겨서 <br>신나게 받았지 <br>이어폰을 꽂은 핸드폰 삼 년째 똑같지 <br>너네 gx라는 핸드폰 <br>다들 들어는 봤니 호갱 <br>내 등에 덮인 아우터 알바비 받아서 <br>엥간치 큰 맘 먹고 어헤드 가서 샀어 <br>십만 원 정도라면 아우터 빼고 <br>자연 룩 멋쟁이 되기 완성 <br>귓볼을 뚫은 8천원짜리 은색 피어싱 <br>블링 블링 is 종현 보다 루또 <br>어때 멋있지 <br>현실적인 내 돈 자랑 <br>거짓 꾸밈 없이 자연스럽잖아 <br>소박이란 단어 그대로 살아 <br>소박이란 단어 그대로 살아 <br>야 내가 뭐 사치라도 하냐 <br>하는 짓도 딱 내 생긴 대로 잖아 <br>소박이란 단어 그대로 살아 <br>소박이란 단어 그대로야 <br>난 살아가지 부족한 삶도 아냐 <br>그러면 풍족한 삶도 아냐 <br>그러면 평범한 삶도 아냐 <br>그러면 소박한 삶이야 <br>I know u can’t do anythang without me <br>내가 없다면 너의 삶은 빙판길 <br>문제가 조금씩 해결되고 있다니까 <br>내 말은 무시하고 보내 일단 <br>돈 벌이 나아지고 있어 <br>이제 달라지고 있어 <br>곧 있으면 차도 하나 생겨 <br>물론 장기 렌트카 <br>지하철 안에서 날 알아보는 <br>사람에게 창피 안 해도 돼 <br>술을 마시는 날이 줄어 들겠지 아마 <br>그 돈 싹 다 모아가지고 <br>우리 동네로 돌아가야 해 <br>바로 go home <br>담배 펴 담배 펴 담배 펴 <br>오늘은 아무것도 없으니까 커텐을 쳐 <br>자연스럽게 길은 머리 <br>깔끔하게 바리깡으로 정리 <br>자연스럽게 흐르는 물결을 타 <br>이건 타의가 아닌 자의야 <br>자이 아파트 발코니에서 <br>담배 펴 담배 펴 담배 펴 <br>여긴 어린 나이 성공한 <br>내 친구 집이야 다 내 편 <br>나도 왠지 부러워 <br>이런 얘가 그때마다 <br>나의 삶에 집중하지 소박하게 <br>다시 손에 쥔 펜 <br>힘이 나지 내게 소리 지를 때 <br>어떤 일찍 이뤄낸 사람과 <br>어떤 부유하게 자란 사람과 날 비교 <br>하게 되면 끝도 없어 난 펜을 <br>잡을 때면 아니 메모장을 키면 <br>그런 게 어딨어 내가 <br>그 누구도 부러울 게 없어 여기서 내가 <br>제일 멋지고 당당하게 어깨 편 채로 <br>오늘도 가오가이거 하나가 가 작업실 <br>걸어가고 있어 수원에 갈 때는 <br>지하철 타고 가 날 알아 봐주는 이도 <br>하나도 없어 그저 내 이어폰에 <br>맡긴 채로 가사를 적고 옆 사람 이쁘네 <br>아니 흥에 겨워 신나게 춤을 <br>춘대도 절대로 <br>뭐라 할 사람은 없네 <br>그래 나답게 자연스럽게 <br>난 살아가지 부족한 삶도 아냐 <br>그러면 풍족한 삶도 아냐 <br>그러면 평범한 삶도 아냐 <br>그러면 소박한 삶이야 <br>]]></content><category term="루또 (LUTTO)" label="루또 (LUTTO)"/><category term="소박 (Feat. Don Mills)" label="소박 (Feat. Don Mills)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루또_LUTTO/산능선_Feat_Sickloo/</id><title>루또 (LUTTO) - 산능선 (Feat. Sickloo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%EB%98%90_LUTTO/%EC%82%B0%EB%8A%A5%EC%84%A0_Feat_Sickloo/" title="루또 (LUTTO) - 산능선 (Feat. Sickloo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈이 가 자꾸 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>눈이 가 자꾸 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>눈이 가 자꾸 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>눈이 가 자꾸 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>한곳에 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>딴 곳에 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>눈이 가 완벽한 작품 <br>한곳에 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>눈이 가 자꾸 한곳에 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>열심히 알바 중에도 내 본능이 자꾸 <br>엄청나게 자극적인 곳으로만 반응해 <br>내 눈은 분명히 없는 게 확실해 빠꾸 <br>바쁜 와중에도 눈치가 제로 <br>눈을 마주친 후 내려가 아래로 <br>분명히 손님과 대화 중인데 <br>내 입은 계속 흉부에게 말을 건네고 있어 <br>아냐 아냐 눈이 눈을 봐야 돼 <br>생각해도 야 이건 진짜 꼭 봐야 돼 <br>사람 몸에 이런 멋진 산 능선이 <br>춤을 추며 펼쳐져 있어 진풍경이 <br>진짜 존나게 자연을 사랑하는 놈 <br>저 산 능선 위에서 소리 치면 <br>메아리가 울릴까 생각 많이 해봤어 <br>아냐 아냐 다음 분 결제 도와드릴게요 <br>근데 계속 <br>눈이 가 자꾸 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>눈이 가 자꾸 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>눈이 가 자꾸 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>눈이 가 자꾸 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>한곳에 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>딴 곳에 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>눈이 가 완벽한 작품 <br>한곳에 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>야 한곳에 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>괜히 미끄러지는 바코드 <br>한국에도 이런 유망주가 <br>나오다니 숨이 차 딸꾹 <br>대놓고 단추 풀어서 까꿍 <br>쏟아질 것만 같아도 <br>너는 한술 더 떠 물어 <br>사이즈 C가 맞냐고 <br>싸다고 싸다고 바구니에 <br>하나 둘 셋 하나 둘 <br>바구니 바구니 바구니 바구니에 <br>민망한 모양만 한 가득에 <br>쿨하게 일시불 카드 <br>나 위험해 꽉 잠가 자크 <br>눈이 삐용 삐용 삐용해 <br>그쪽이 삐용 삐용 삐용해 <br>눈이 삐용 삐용 삐용해 <br>어디서 삐용 삐용 삐용해 <br>오우 나 정신이 혼미해져 <br>나도 모르게 머릿속에서 <br>산 능선이 아름답게 펼쳐져 있어 <br>다음 장면이 그려져 <br>이럼 안될 것만 같아 <br>근데도 계속 그려져 <br>한곳에 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>딴 곳에 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>한곳에 눈이 <br>눈이 가 자꾸 눈이 가 자꾸 <br>]]></content><category term="루또 (LUTTO)" label="루또 (LUTTO)"/><category term="산능선 (Feat. Sickloo)" label="산능선 (Feat. Sickloo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루또_LUTTO/마냥/</id><title>루또 (LUTTO) - 마냥 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%EB%98%90_LUTTO/%EB%A7%88%EB%83%A5/" title="루또 (LUTTO) - 마냥 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다들 재미 있자고 모여 <br>한탕 취할라고 모여 <br>웃고 즐기자고 말이야 <br>왜 그래 싸우지들 말아 <br>각자 견해 차이야 <br>우린 조금씩 달라 <br>난 누가 옆에 싸움 나면 <br>머리랑 등에 땀나 난 평화주의자야 <br>시국 얘길 하려 해 얜 <br>영화보다 더 심하던데 <br>여기선 그 얘기 별로네 <br>근데 근데 지금 나는 <br>마냥 웃고 즐기지 <br>마냥 웃고 즐기지 <br>마냥 웃고 즐기지 <br>마냥 웃고 즐기지 <br>앞에 술잔이 떡 하니 있는데 <br>심지어 그게 지금 비어있는데 <br>첫차까진 아직 시간이 있는데 <br>같이 마냥 웃고 즐기지 <br>야 왜 흘리고 그러냐 너 돈 좀 <br>버나보다 <br>신나게 놀더라도 흘리진 말라고 <br>야 아니 좀 너무했냐 <br>자린고비 flow가 <br>네 흥을 깨버렸냐 <br>나 요즘 분위기 너무 좋은데 <br>음악도 진짜 좋은데 <br>나랑 사진 찍어놓는 건 어때 <br>일년 뒤에도 쓸모가 없음 <br>지우는 거야 어때 <br>얘는 또 왜 삼십분째 <br>같은 얘기해 뭐라는 건데 <br>토종한국인이 왜 교포인척해 <br>근데 근데 지금 나는 <br>마냥 웃고 즐기지 <br>마냥 웃고 즐기지 <br>마냥 웃고 즐기지 <br>마냥 웃고 즐기지 <br>앞에 술잔이 떡하니 있는데 <br>심지어 그게 지금 비어있는데 <br>첫차까진 아직 시간이 있는데 <br>같이 마냥 웃고 즐기지 <br>우우우우 <br>노래는 내가 부를게 좀 취했으니 <br>우우우우 <br>아주 감미롭게 말이야 괜찮겠니 <br>sippin' drinkin' n smokin' <br>무슨 말이야 그냥 즐기지 난 <br>sippin' drinkin' n 그 뭐였지 <br>근데 근데 지금 나는 <br>마냥 웃고 즐기지 <br>마냥 웃고 즐기지 <br>마냥 웃고 즐기지 <br>마냥 웃고 즐기지 <br>앞에 술잔이 떡하니 있는데 <br>심지어 그게 지금 비어있는데 <br>첫차까진 아직 시간이 있는데 <br>같이 마냥 웃고 즐기지 <br>]]></content><category term="루또 (LUTTO)" label="루또 (LUTTO)"/><category term="마냥" label="마냥"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루또_LUTTO/저가항공/</id><title>루또 (LUTTO) - 저가항공 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%EB%98%90_LUTTO/%EC%A0%80%EA%B0%80%ED%95%AD%EA%B3%B5/" title="루또 (LUTTO) - 저가항공 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어디든 저 멀리 데려다 줘 <br>언제 세일하냐 저가항공 <br>가족 친구들 같이 가자고 <br>나중엔 타겠지 넓은 좌석 <br>이젠 부릉부릉 말고 윙윙 날아가 <br>어딜 가든 무릉 무릉도원 하고 <br>루또피아 <br>이젠 부릉부릉 말고 윙윙 날아가 <br>어딜 가든 무릉 무릉도원 하고 <br>루또피아 <br>보라카이 넉살형이 그랬어 <br>햇살이 부서질 거라고 우와 그랬어 <br>나도 상상해봤다고 해먹 위에서 <br>선글라스 끼고 자는 척 눈을 굴렸어 <br>야 왜 저 여자는 옷을 입다 만 거야 <br>눈을 어따 둬야 할 지 <br>모르겠잖아 고맙다 <br>아니아니 야 야 여긴 왜 <br>구름이 저기 떠있냐 <br>우린 같은 하늘이 아니였나봐 멋지다 <br>뭐야 벌써 숨는 거야 빨간 햇살아 <br>좀더 부숴줬으면 하거든 초록색바다 <br>몇 번 경포대 해운대 <br>바다 보며 맥주 마셨는데 <br>난 그것도 너무 좋았는데 말야 <br>여긴 차원이 다르다 애들아 <br>효도관광 보내주자 부모님께 말야 <br>그리고 다 같이 손잡고 와서 <br>신나게 제대로 즐겨보게 한 바탕 <br>우워 노래도 하고 막 춤도 추고 <br>막 음악도 만들고 <br>술도 마시고 막 짱 좋겠다 <br>어디든 저 멀리 데려다 줘 <br>언제 세일하냐 저가항공 <br>가족 친구들 같이 가자고 <br>나중엔 타겠지 넓은 좌석 <br>이젠 부릉부릉 말고 윙윙 날아가 <br>어딜 가든 무릉 무릉도원 하고 <br>루또피아 <br>이젠 부릉부릉 말고 윙윙 날아가 <br>어딜 가든 무릉 무릉도원 하고 <br>루또피아 <br>헤엄 헤엄 물고기들과 헤엄 <br>손엔 안 잡히는 게 내 미래 같네 <br>오 저건 인어공주인가 가까이 가보니 <br>다리가 두 개네 아 그냥 공주인 가봐 <br>아 야 넌 여기 사는 거야 <br>와 진짜 좋겠다 난 여기 살았음 아마 <br>한 달에 앨범 하나씩은 <br>나올 것만 같아 <br>분위기 진짜 좋다 경치도 진짜 좋다 <br>이야 망고쥬스로 한 곡 <br>야자수로도 한 곡 <br>눈에 보인 모든 것이 <br>영감이 되는 장소야 <br>근데 여기보다 좋은 곳이 <br>더 많다던데 <br>어디든 꼭 가볼래 내 사람들과 함께 <br>함께라면 더 좋겠네 <br>그때는 남은 돈 계산 안 해 <br>기념품 20kg 꽉 채워 갈게 <br>환율도 안보고 막 환전하고 막 <br>먹고 마시고 흥정도 안 하고 막 <br>짱 좋겠다 <br>어디든 저 멀리 데려다 줘 <br>언제 세일하냐 저가항공 <br>가족 친구들 같이 가자고 <br>나중엔 타겠지 넓은 좌석 <br>이젠 부릉부릉 말고 윙윙 날아가 <br>어딜 가든 무릉 무릉도원 하고 <br>루또피아 <br>이젠 부릉부릉 말고 윙윙 날아가 <br>어딜 가든 무릉 무릉도원 하고 <br>루또피아 <br>이젠 부릉부릉 말고 윙윙 날아가 <br>어딜 가든 무릉 무릉도원 하고 <br>루또피아 <br>이젠 부릉부릉 말고 윙윙 날아가 <br>어딜 가든 무릉 무릉도원 하고 <br>루또피아 <br>]]></content><category term="루또 (LUTTO)" label="루또 (LUTTO)"/><category term="저가항공" label="저가항공"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루또_LUTTO/라이트형제_Feat_진돗개/</id><title>루또 (LUTTO) - 라이트형제 (Feat. 진돗개) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%EB%98%90_LUTTO/%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%ED%8A%B8%ED%98%95%EC%A0%9C_Feat_%EC%A7%84%EB%8F%97%EA%B0%9C/" title="루또 (LUTTO) - 라이트형제 (Feat. 진돗개) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[진돗개형이랑 얘기 했어 <br>이번 년 계획에 대해서 <br>조금 더 빡세게 더 <br>해야한다고 난 동의했어 <br>우선 나부터 믿으라고 <br>믿는 대로 이뤄질 거라고 <br>저 무거운 비행기가 지금 어떻게 <br>날아서 다니겠냐고 나도 <br>안 될거야 아마도 라고 <br>단호하게 말할 거야 <br>게다가 주변에 나처럼 <br>이렇게 말한 건 <br>하나 둘이 아니었을 거고 <br>많은 사람들이 깠을 거야 근데 <br>다 족구 하라 했을 거고 <br>근데도 계속 믿었을 거야 그래서 <br>결국 하늘에 움직이는 별이 생겼고 <br>덕분에 나도 지금 만들 수 있었어 <br>저가항공 이라는 멋진 음악 말이야 <br>지금 형이랑 하는 이 곡도 말이야 <br>나도 내 음악에 자신감 있잖아 <br>돗개형도 알아봐준 거고 뿐만 아니라 <br>모두가 그럴거야 그렇게 믿을 거고 <br>꼭 그렇게 되도록 만들 거야 <br>믿어 나 자신을 뭐라도 된다는 듯이 <br>믿어 더 자신감 갖고 하면 돼 반드시 <br>믿어 나도 그렇게 날 수 있을 거라고 <br>믿어 되게 만들고 더 믿어 더 더 <br>your mind your mind your mind <br>your mind your mind <br>your eye your eye your eye <br>your eye your eyes <br>핑계 댈 시간조차 없게 <br>없애봐 시공간 <br>너를 믿어 <br>때는 내가 비행기를 탈 때 <br>문득 이런 생각이 났네 <br>대충 이론적으론 알지만 <br>어찌 이 큰 쇳덩이가 날지 <br>만약에 이 상태로 내가 <br>과거로 돌아간다면 <br>라이트형제한테 말했겠지 <br>안될 거라고 <br>야 어떻게 사람이 하늘을 나냐고 <br>그래 우리에게 중요한 건 <br>현실이 아닌 상상력 <br>이거 듣고 느끼는 새끼 <br>몇 명이나 있냐 <br>한번뿐인 인생 <br>하고픈 거 하며 살아 임마 <br>우린 어릴 때부터 <br>안 되는 걸 들어왔다지만 <br>삶이란 건 누가 대신 <br>살아 주는 것이 아니야 <br>믿어 너 자신을 <br>뭐라도 될 거라는 듯이 <br>믿어 간절하면 이뤄질 거야 반드시 <br>밀어 될 때까지 너흰 금방 <br>포기하는 게 습관이야 <br>그 작은 습관차이가 나눈 게 <br>하늘과 땅이야 <br>믿어 나 자신을 뭐라도 된다는 듯이 <br>믿어 더 자신감 갖고 하면 돼 반드시 <br>믿어 나도 그렇게 날 수 있을 거라고 <br>믿어 되게 만들고 더 믿어 더 더 <br>your mind your mind your mind <br>your mind your mind <br>your eye your eye your eye <br>your eye your eyes <br>your mind your mind your mind <br>your mind your mind <br>your eye your eye your eye <br>your eye your eyes <br>하고 싶은 대로 하고 <br>가고 싶은 대로 가 <br>너가 옳다 싶은 대로 가고 <br>믿는 대로 다 <br>이뤄질 거야 물론 <br>그만큼 움직인다면야 <br>비록 나도 아직 이룬 게 없어 <br>납득이 갈지는 모르겠지만 <br>]]></content><category term="루또 (LUTTO)" label="루또 (LUTTO)"/><category term="라이트형제 (Feat. 진돗개)" label="라이트형제 (Feat. 진돗개)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Enough_Of_The_Blues_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Enough Of The Blues (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Enough_Of_The_Blues_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Enough Of The Blues (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Somebody help me <br>Lord, I'm in misery <br>Somebody help me <br>Lord, I'm in misery <br>I had enough of the blues <br>But the blues ain't had enough of me <br><br>Had me a woman <br>Oh Lord, I done her wrong <br>Had me a woman <br>Oh Lord, I done her wrong <br>She got sick and tired of the cheatin' <br>And now she's up and gone <br><br>That's why she left me <br>Left me in misery <br>That's why she left me <br>Left me in misery <br>Yes, she did <br>I had enough of the blues <br>But the blues ain't had enough of me <br><br>Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br>Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br>Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br>Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br><br>Somebody help me <br>Lord, I'm in misery <br>Somebody help me <br>Lord, I'm in misery <br>Uh uh <br>Well, I had enough of the blues <br>But the blues ain't had enough of me <br>Oh, no <br><br>Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br>Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br>Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br>Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br><br>Somebody help me <br>Lord, I'm in misery <br>Somebody's gotta help me <br>Lord, I'm in misery <br>Yes, I am <br>I had enough of the blues <br>But the blues ain't had enough of me <br><br>I had enough of the blues <br>But the blues ain't had enough of me <br>Oh, no <br>I had enough of the blues <br>But the blues ain't had enough of me <br><br>Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br>Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br>Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br>Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br><br>Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br>Ah ah ah ah <br>Ah ah ah ah <br><br>Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br>Ah ah ah ah ah <br>Ah ah ah ah ah]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Enough Of The Blues (Live)" label="Enough Of The Blues (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Fire_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Fire (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Fire_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Fire (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You don't care about me <br>I don't care about that <br>Got a new fool <br>And I'd like to laugh at <br>I have only one burnin' desire <br>let me stand next to your fire <br><br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br><br>You say your mom ain't home <br>it ain't my turn <br>Just play with me <br>and you won't get burned <br>I have only one burnin' desire <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br><br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>I said let me stand next to your fire <br><br>Yeah <br>Ahh, move over, Rover <br>You try to give me your money <br>better save it, babe <br>Save it for your rainy day <br>I have only one itchin' desire <br>Let me stand next to your <br><br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br><br>Yeah]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Fire (Live)" label="Fire (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/How_Many_Lies_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - How Many Lies (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/How_Many_Lies_Live/" title="Gary Moore - How Many Lies (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How many more lies <br>You gonna have to tell <br>How many more lies <br>You gonna have to tell <br>Well, I've been watching what you're doin' <br>And I don't like what I see <br>You're makin' a fool out of me <br><br>How many more years <br>You gonna wreck my life <br>How many more years <br>You gonna wreck my life <br>Well, I've been checkin' on you baby <br>With your cheating and your lies <br>You're in for a big surprise <br>Yeah <br><br>How many more tears <br>Do I have to cry <br>How many more tears <br>Do I have to cry <br>When I'm old and I'm grey <br>I just gonna walk away <br>Try to make a fool out of me <br><br>How many more times <br>You gonna treat me like you do <br>How many more times <br>You gonna treat me like you do <br>I've been watching what you're doin' <br>And I don't like what I see <br>You're makin' a fool out of me <br>Yeah <br><br>How many more lies <br>You gonna have to tell <br>How many more lies <br>You gonna have to tell <br>Well, I've been checkin' on you baby <br>And I don't like what I see <br>All your lyin' and your cheatin' <br>Tryin' to make a fool of me <br>Had enough of all your prayin' <br>Gonna show you to the door <br>If I'm livin' when you're leavin' <br>I won't be a fool anymore <br>No <br><br>How many more lies <br>How many more times <br>How many more years <br>How many more tears <br><br>Hey hey hey <br>Hey hey hey <br>Hey hey hey <br>Hey hey hey]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="How Many Lies (Live)" label="How Many Lies (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Too_Tired_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Too Tired (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Too_Tired_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Too Tired (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>I laid down last night, too tired to wake <br>I had a chill this morning, too tired to shake <br>I got a good poker hand, too tired to win <br>I can hear my baby knockin', too tired to let her in <br><br>I'm tired <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm tired <br>Too tired, too tired for anything <br><br>I'm too tired to walk <br>Too tired to run <br>I can hear my baby callin' <br>Too tired, too tired <br>I'm tired <br>Yes, I'm tired <br>I'm tired <br>I'm too tired for anything <br><br>Take over Albert, I'm too tired for this <br><br>I'm tired of prospherity <br>I'm tired of luck <br>I'm sittin' on a pin <br>I'm too tired to get up <br><br>I'm tired <br>I declare I'm tired <br>I'm too tired <br>too tired for anything <br><br>Oh, Albert I'm tired <br>You better take over Albert <br>I'm too tired baby]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Too Tired (Live)" label="Too Tired (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Still_Got_The_Blues_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Still Got The Blues (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Still_Got_The_Blues_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Still Got The Blues (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Used to be so easy to give my heart away <br>But I found out the hard way <br>There's a price you have to pay <br>I found out that love was no friend of mine <br>I should have known time after time <br><br>So long, it was so long ago <br>But I've still got the blues for you <br><br>Used to be so easy to fall in love again <br>But I found out the hard way <br>It's a road that leads to pain <br>I found that love was more than just a game <br>You're playin' to win <br>But you lose just the same <br><br>So long, it was so long ago <br>But I've still got the blues for you <br><br>So many years since I've seen your face <br>Here in my heart, there's an empty space <br>Where you used to be <br><br>So long, it was so long ago <br>But I've still got the blues for you <br><br>Though the days come and go <br>There is one thing I know <br>I've still got the blues for you]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Still Got The Blues (Live)" label="Still Got The Blues (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/All_Your_Love_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - All Your Love (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/All_Your_Love_Live/" title="Gary Moore - All Your Love (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All your lovin' is lovin' <br>All your kissin' is kissin' <br>All your lovin' is lovin' <br>All your kissin' is kissin' <br>Before I met you baby <br>I never knew what I was missin' <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>When I say I love you baby <br>Gotta say you love me too <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>When I say I love you baby <br>You gotta say you love me too <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>Before I met you baby <br>I never knew what I was missin' <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>Before I met you baby <br>I never knew what I was missin']]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="All Your Love (Live)" label="All Your Love (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Oh_Pretty_Woman_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Oh Pretty Woman (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Oh_Pretty_Woman_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Oh Pretty Woman (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, pretty woman <br>Sure's the rising sun <br>Says all your cheap paint and powder <br>Ain't gonna help you none <br><br>'Cause she's a pretty woman <br>Right down to her bone <br>So you might as well <br>Leave your skin alone <br><br>Pretty woman <br>What's the matter with you <br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br><br>Oh, pretty woman <br>Whatcha gonna do <br>You kept on foolin' around <br>Till I got stuck on you <br><br>So you can drop your mess <br>And come down off your throne <br>Stop using my poor heart <br>As just a stepping stone <br><br>Pretty woman <br>What's the matter with you <br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br><br>Oh, pretty woman <br>That's all right for you <br>Now you just go on doing <br>What you wanna do <br><br>But someday when you think <br>That you've got it made <br>You're gettin' water deep enough <br>So you can't wade <br><br>Pretty woman <br>What's the matter with you <br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br><br>Oh, pretty woman <br>Oh, pretty woman <br>Oh, pretty woman <br>Oh, pretty woman <br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br>No <br><br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br>No <br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br><br>Oh, pretty woman <br>I just can't make you love me <br>Oh, no]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Oh Pretty Woman (Live)" label="Oh Pretty Woman (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Stormy_Monday_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Stormy Monday (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Stormy_Monday_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Stormy Monday (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Call it stormy Monday <br>But Tuesday's just as bad <br>Call it stormy Monday <br>Tuesday's just as bad <br>Wednesday is worse <br>And Thursday's all so sad <br><br>The eagle flies on Friday <br>Saturday I go out to play <br>Eagle flies on Friday <br>Saturday I go out to play <br>Sunday I go to church <br>I get down on my knees and pray <br><br>Lord have mercy <br>Lord have mercy, mercy on me <br>Lord have mercy <br>Lord have mercy, mercy on me <br>Oh, I'm crazy about my baby <br>Please send her home to me <br>Yeah, yeah <br><br>Lord have mercy <br>Lord have mercy, mercy on me <br>Yeah, Lord have mercy <br>Lord have mercy on me <br>Well, I'm crazy about my baby <br>Please, please send her home <br><br>Call it stormy Monday]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Stormy Monday (Live)" label="Stormy Monday (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Cold_Black_Night_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Cold Black Night (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Cold_Black_Night_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Cold Black Night (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It was a cold black night <br>And the rain was falling down <br>It was a cold black night <br>And the rain was falling down <br>It was a cold black night <br>The night that my baby left town <br><br>It was the darkest day <br>And the wind was howlin' through <br>It was the darkest day <br>And the wind came howlin' through <br>It was the darkest day <br>Day my baby said we're through <br><br>Oh, come back baby <br>Never did you no wrong <br>Come back baby <br>I never did you no wrong <br>I've been sleeping in the ground <br>Ever since your love been gone <br><br>It was a cold black night <br>And the rain was falling down <br>It was a cold black night <br>And the rain was falling down <br>It was a cold black night <br>The night my baby left town <br>Yeah <br><br>It was the darkest day <br>And the wind came howlin' through <br>It was the darkest day <br>And the wind came howlin' through <br>It was the darkest day <br>The day my baby said we're through <br><br>It was a cold black night <br>It was a cold black night <br>It was a cold black night <br>It was a cold black night <br><br>It was a cold black night <br>And the rain was falling down <br>It was a cold black night <br>And the rain was falling down <br>It was a cold black night <br>The night my baby left this town <br>Yes <br><br>It was a cold black night <br>It was a cold black night <br>It was a cold black night <br>It was a cold black night <br>It was a cold black night <br>The night my baby left town <br><br>It was a cold black night]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Cold Black Night (Live)" label="Cold Black Night (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/You_Upset_Me_Baby_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - You Upset Me Baby (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/You_Upset_Me_Baby_Live/" title="Gary Moore - You Upset Me Baby (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[That's right <br><br>Yes, she's 36 bust <br>28 in the waist <br>44 on the hip <br>She's got some crazy legs <br><br>It upsets me baby <br>Ooh, upsets me baby <br>Yeah, I'm tellin' you <br>She's so fine <br>Somethin' that you ought to see <br><br>Well, she's not too tall <br>Complexion is fair <br>It knocks me out <br>The way she wears her hair <br><br>You upsets me baby <br>You upsets me baby <br>Like beein' hit by a fallin' tree <br>Woman what you do to me <br><br>Well, I try to describe her <br>It's hard to stop <br>I better stop now <br>In case I got a weak heart <br><br>You upsets me baby <br>You upsets me baby <br>Like beein' hit by a fallin' tree <br>Woman what you do to me <br>Yeah <br><br>Yeah <br><br>Try to describe her <br>It's hard to stop <br>I better stop now <br>In case I got a weak heart <br><br>You upsets me baby <br>You upsets me baby <br>Like beein' hit by a fallin' tree <br>Woman what you do to me <br><br>It upsets me baby <br>It upsets me baby <br>It upsets me baby <br>It upsets me baby <br>Like beein' hit by a fallin' tree <br>Woman what you do to me <br>That's right <br><br>Hoh]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="You Upset Me Baby (Live)" label="You Upset Me Baby (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Parisienne_Walkways_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Parisienne Walkways (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:38:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:38:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Parisienne_Walkways_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Parisienne Walkways (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I remember Paris in '49 <br>The Champs Elysee, Saint Michel <br>And old Beaujolais wine <br>And I recall that you were mine <br>In those Parisienne days <br><br>Looking back at the photographs <br>Those summerdays spent outside corner cafes <br>Oh, I could write you paragraphs <br>About my old Parisienne days]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Parisienne Walkways (Live)" label="Parisienne Walkways (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Fire_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Fire (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Fire_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Fire (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You don't care about me <br>I don't care about that <br>Got a new fool <br>And I'd like to laugh at <br>I have only one burnin' desire <br>let me stand next to your fire <br><br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br><br>You say your mom ain't home <br>it ain't my turn <br>Just play with me <br>and you won't get burned <br>I have only one burnin' desire <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br><br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>I said let me stand next to your fire <br><br>Yeah <br>Ahh, move over, Rover <br>You try to give me your money <br>better save it, babe <br>Save it for your rainy day <br>I have only one itchin' desire <br>Let me stand next to your <br><br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br>let me stand <br>Let me stand next to your fire <br><br>Yeah]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Fire (Live)" label="Fire (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Further_On_Up_The_Road_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Further On Up The Road (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Further_On_Up_The_Road_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Further On Up The Road (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Further on up the road <br>Someone's gonna hurt you like you hurt me <br>Further on up the road <br>Someone's gonna hurt you like you hurt me <br>Further on up the road <br>Just you wait and see <br><br>Now you're laughing pretty baby <br>But one day you'll be cryin' <br>You're laughing pretty baby <br>But one day you'll be cryin' <br>Further on up the road <br>You'll see I wasn't lyin' <br><br>Further on up the road <br>Someone's gonna hurt you like you hurt me <br>Further on up the road <br>Someone's gonna hurt you like you hurt me <br>Further on up the road <br>Just you wait and see <br>Here we go <br><br>Now you're laughing pretty baby <br>But one day you'll be cryin' <br>You're laughing pretty baby <br>But one day you'll be cryin' <br>Further on up the road <br>You'll see I wasn't lyin' <br><br>Further on up the road <br>Someone's gonna hurt you like you hurt me <br>Further on up the road <br>Someone's gonna hurt you like you hurt me <br>Further on up the road <br>Just you wait and see, yeah <br><br>Now you're laughing pretty baby <br>But one day you'll be cryin' <br>You're laughing pretty baby <br>But one day you'll be cryin' <br>Further on up the road <br>You'll see I wasn't lyin' <br><br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road <br><br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road, yeah <br>Further on up the road <br>Someone's gonna hurt you]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Further On Up The Road (Live)" label="Further On Up The Road (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/The_Sky_Is_Crying_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - The Sky Is Crying (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/The_Sky_Is_Crying_Live/" title="Gary Moore - The Sky Is Crying (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The sky is cryin' <br>Look at the tears rollin' down the street <br>The sky is cryin' <br>Look at the tears rollin' down the street <br>I been lookin' for my baby <br>I wonder where she can be <br>That's right <br><br>I saw my baby one mornin' <br>And she was walkin' on down the street <br>I saw my baby one mornin' <br>And she was walkin' on down the street <br>Yes, she was <br>You know it hurt me so bad <br>It made my poor heart skip a beat <br>Here we go, play it for me <br><br>I've got a bad, bad feelin' <br>My baby don't love me no more <br>I've got a bad, bad feelin' <br>My baby don't love me no more, no <br>The sky is cryin' <br>Woh, look at the tears rolling down my nose <br><br>The sky is cryin' <br>Look at the tears rollin' down the street, yeah <br>The sky is cryin' <br>Look at the tears rollin' down the street <br>I been lookin' for my baby <br>I wonder where my baby can be]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="The Sky Is Crying (Live)" label="The Sky Is Crying (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Too_Tired_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Too Tired (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Too_Tired_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Too Tired (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>I laid down last night, too tired to wake <br>I had a chill this morning, too tired to shake <br>I got a good poker hand, too tired to win <br>I can hear my baby knockin', too tired to let her in <br><br>I'm tired <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm tired <br>Too tired, too tired for anything <br><br>I'm too tired to walk <br>Too tired to run <br>I can hear my baby callin' <br>Too tired, too tired <br>I'm tired <br>Yes, I'm tired <br>I'm tired <br>I'm too tired for anything <br><br>Take over Albert, I'm too tired for this <br><br>I'm tired of prospherity <br>I'm tired of luck <br>I'm sittin' on a pin <br>I'm too tired to get up <br><br>I'm tired <br>I declare I'm tired <br>I'm too tired <br>too tired for anything <br><br>Oh, Albert I'm tired <br>You better take over Albert <br>I'm too tired baby]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Too Tired (Live)" label="Too Tired (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Still_Got_The_Blues_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Still Got The Blues (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Still_Got_The_Blues_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Still Got The Blues (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Used to be so easy to give my heart away <br>But I found out the hard way <br>There's a price you have to pay <br>I found out that love was no friend of mine <br>I should have known time after time <br><br>So long, it was so long ago <br>But I've still got the blues for you <br><br>Used to be so easy to fall in love again <br>But I found out the hard way <br>It's a road that leads to pain <br>I found that love was more than just a game <br>You're playin' to win <br>But you lose just the same <br><br>So long, it was so long ago <br>But I've still got the blues for you <br><br>So many years since I've seen your face <br>Here in my heart, there's an empty space <br>Where you used to be <br><br>So long, it was so long ago <br>But I've still got the blues for you <br><br>Though the days come and go <br>There is one thing I know <br>I've still got the blues for you]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Still Got The Blues (Live)" label="Still Got The Blues (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/All_Your_Love_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - All Your Love (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/All_Your_Love_Live/" title="Gary Moore - All Your Love (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All your lovin' is lovin' <br>All your kissin' is kissin' <br>All your lovin' is lovin' <br>All your kissin' is kissin' <br>Before I met you baby <br>I never knew what I was missin' <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>When I say I love you baby <br>Gotta say you love me too <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>When I say I love you baby <br>You gotta say you love me too <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>Before I met you baby <br>I never knew what I was missin' <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>Before I met you baby <br>I never knew what I was missin']]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="All Your Love (Live)" label="All Your Love (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/You_Dont_Love_Me_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - You Don`t Love Me (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/You_Dont_Love_Me_Live/" title="Gary Moore - You Don`t Love Me (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You don't love me, woman <br>You don't love me, yes I know <br>You don't love me, woman <br>You don't love me, yes I know <br>Well I'm gonna tell everybody <br>Stay away of my back <br><br>Well I'm gonna talk to your mother <br>I'm gonna talk to your father too <br>Well I'm gonna talk to your mother <br>I'm gonna talk to your father too <br>Well I'm gonna tell everybody <br><br>What those young girls will do to you <br><br>Well I'm gonna talk to your mother <br>I'm gonna talk to your father too <br>Well I'm gonna talk to your mother <br>I'm gonna talk to your father too <br>Well I'm gonna tell everybody <br>What those young girls will do to you <br><br>You don't love me, woman <br>You don't love me, yes I know <br>You don't love me, woman <br>You don't love me, yes I know <br>Well I'm gonna tell everybody <br>Stay away of my back]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="You Don`t Love Me (Live)" label="You Don`t Love Me (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Tore_Down_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Tore Down (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Tore_Down_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Tore Down (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm tore down, I'm almost level with the ground <br>I'm tore down, I'm almost level with the ground <br>Well, I feel like this when my baby can't be found <br>I went to the river to jump in <br>My baby showed up and said, I will tell you when <br><br>Well, I'm tore down, I'm almost level with the ground <br>Well, I feel like this when my baby can't be found <br><br>I love you babe with all my heart and soul <br>Love like mine will never grow old <br>Love you in the morning and in the evening too <br>Every time you leave me I get mad with you <br>I love you baby with all my might <br>Love like mine is out of sight <br>I'll lie for you if you want me to <br>I really don't believe that your love is true <br><br>I'm tore down, I'm almost level with the ground <br>Well, I'm tore down, I'm almost level with the ground <br>Well, I feel like this when my baby can't be found]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Tore Down (Live)" label="Tore Down (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Need_Your_Love_So_Bad_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Need Your Love So Bad (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Need_Your_Love_So_Bad_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Need Your Love So Bad (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Need someone's hand <br>To lead me through the night <br>Need someone's arms <br>To hold and squeeze me tight <br>'Cause when the night begins <br>I'm at an end <br>Because I need your love so bad <br><br>Need some lips <br>To feel next to mine <br>Need someone to stand up <br>And tell me when I'm lyin' <br>When the lights are low <br>And it's time to go <br>That's when I need your love so bad <br><br>Why don't you give it up <br>Bring it on home to me <br>Or write it on a piece of paper, darlin' <br>So it can be read to me <br>Tell me that you love me <br>And stop driving me mad <br>Beacause I <br>I need your love so bad <br><br>Need your soft voice <br>Talk to me at night <br>Don't want you to worry baby <br>'Cause I know we can make everything allright <br>Listen to my plea baby <br>Bring it home to me <br>Because I need your love so bad]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Need Your Love So Bad (Live)" label="Need Your Love So Bad (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Since_I_Met_You_Baby_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Since I Met You Baby (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Since_I_Met_You_Baby_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Since I Met You Baby (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I used to wake up in the morning with an aching head <br>I couldn't remember anything I'd said <br>My friends told me I was getting out of line <br>If it wasn't for you baby, I'd be doing time <br><br>Since I met you baby <br>you've made a new man of me <br>Since I met you baby <br>I'm happy as a man could be <br>Yes, I am <br><br>I used to think I was better than the rest <br>Ain't no doubt about it, I was no second best <br>Didn't seem to matter what was right or what was wrong <br>I did some crazy things before you came along <br><br>Since I met you baby <br>you've made a new man of me <br>Since I met you baby <br>I'm happy as a man could be <br>Yes, I am <br><br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>I'm happy as a man could be <br>One more time <br><br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Well, since I met you baby <br>I'm happy as a man could be <br>Yes, I am <br><br>Happy as a man can be <br>You tell 'em Gary <br>Yeah]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Since I Met You Baby (Live)" label="Since I Met You Baby (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Walking_By_Myself_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Walking By Myself (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Walking_By_Myself_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Walking By Myself (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You know I love you <br>You know it's true <br>Give you all my love, babe <br>What more can I do <br><br>Walking by myself <br>I hope you'll understand <br>I just want to be your lovin' man <br><br>I love ya, yes I love you <br>With my heart and soul <br>I wouldn't mistreat you <br>For my weight in gold <br><br>You know I love you <br>You know it's true <br>Give you all my love, babe <br>What more can I do <br><br>Walking by myself <br>I hope you'll understand <br>I just want to be your lovin' man <br><br>Here we go <br>Keep on walkin' <br><br>You know I love you <br>You know it's true <br>I give you all my , babe <br>What more can I do <br><br>I'm walking by myself <br>I hope you'll understand <br>I just want to be your lovin' man <br><br>I said I'm walking by myself <br>I hope you'll understand <br>I just want to be your lovin' <br>I just want to be your lovin' <br>I just want to be your lovin' man <br>That's right]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Walking By Myself (Live)" label="Walking By Myself (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Parisienne_Walkways_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Parisienne Walkways (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Parisienne_Walkways_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Parisienne Walkways (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I remember Paris in '49 <br>The Champs Elysee, Saint Michel <br>And old Beaujolais wine <br>And I recall that you were mine <br>In those Parisienne days <br><br>Looking back at the photographs <br>Those summerdays spent outside corner cafes <br>Oh, I could write you paragraphs <br>About my old Parisienne days]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Parisienne Walkways (Live)" label="Parisienne Walkways (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Over_The_Hills_And_Far_Away_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Over The Hills And Far Away (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Over_The_Hills_And_Far_Away_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Over The Hills And Far Away (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They came for him one winter's night <br>Arrested, he was bound <br>They said there'd been a robbery <br>His pistol had been found <br><br>They marched him to the station house <br>He waited till the dawn <br>And as they led him to the dock <br>He knew that he'd been wronged <br>You stand accused of robbery <br>He heard the bailiff say <br>He knew without an alibi <br>Tomorrow's light would mourn his freedom <br><br>Over the hills and far away <br>For ten long years he'll count the days <br>Over the mountains and the seas <br>A prisoner's life for him there'll be <br><br>He knew that it would cost him deer <br>But yet he dare not say <br>Just where he had been that fateful night <br>A secret it must stay <br>He had to fight back tears of rage <br>His heart beat like a drum <br>For with the wife of his best friend <br>He'd spent his final night of freedom <br><br>Over the hills and far away <br>He swears he will return one day <br>Far from the mountains and the seas <br>Back in her arms again he'll be <br>Over the hills and far away <br><br>Each night within his prison cell <br>He looks out through the bars <br>He reads the letters that she wrote <br>One day he'll know the taste of freedom <br><br>Over the hills and far away <br>She prays he will return one day <br>As sure as the rivers reach the seas <br>Back in his arms again she'll be <br><br>Over the hills and far away <br>He swears he will return one day <br>As sure as the river reach the sea <br>Back in his arms is where she'll be <br><br>Over the hills and far away <br>She prays he will return one day <br>As sure as the rivers reach the seas <br>Back in her arms is where he'll be <br><br>Over the hills <br>Over the hills and far away <br><br>Over the hills <br>Over the hills and far away]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Over The Hills And Far Away (Live)" label="Over The Hills And Far Away (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Out_In_The_Fields_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Out In The Fields (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Out_In_The_Fields_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Out In The Fields (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It doesn't matter <br>If you're wrong or if you're right <br>It makes no difference <br>If you're black or if you're white <br><br>All men are equal <br>Till the victory is won <br>No colour or religion <br>Ever stopped the bullet from a gun <br><br>Out in the fields <br>The fighting has begun <br>Out on the streets <br>They're falling one by one <br>Out from the skies <br>A thousand more will die each day <br>Death is just a heartbeat away <br><br>It doesn't matter <br>If you're left or to the right <br>Don't try to hide behind the cause <br>They want to fight <br><br>There'll be no prisoners taken <br>When the day is done <br>No flag, no uniform <br>Ever stopped the bullet from a gun <br><br>Out in the fields <br>The fighting has begun <br>Out on the streets <br>They're falling one by one <br>Out from the skies <br>A thousand more will die each day <br>Death is just a heartbeat away <br><br>There's no communication <br>No one to take the blame <br>The cries of every nation <br>They're falling on deaf ears again <br><br>Out in the fields <br>Out in the fields <br>They're falling one by one <br>Out in the fields <br>No flag has ever stopped <br>The bullet from a gun <br><br>Death is just a heartbeat away <br>Out in the fields <br>A heartbeat away <br>Out in the fields <br>Death is just a heartbeat away <br>Out in the fields <br>A heartbeat away <br>Out in the fields <br><br>In the fields <br>The fighting has begun <br>Out on the streets <br>They're falling one by one <br>Out from the skies <br>A thousand more will die each day <br><br>OUT]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Out In The Fields (Live)" label="Out In The Fields (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Business_As_Usual_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Business As Usual (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Business_As_Usual_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Business As Usual (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The pink crucifix with the ivory Jesus I wanted <br>The man with the blood on his hands as I ran from the river <br>Kissing my cousin, before they took her to the graveyard <br>Trembling at night from the violence I heard from my bedroom <br><br>These are my memories <br>These are my memories, coming home <br><br>Called up at school 'cause my hand wasn't there to say present <br>Running the gauntlet outside the Club Rado at dawn <br>Rory and me without a spare string between us <br>Catching the last bus halfway through I'm so glad <br><br>These are my memories <br>These are my memories, coming home <br><br>Philip and me and the brush riding round in a transit <br>The Bailey, the Strangley's, the smoke and the speed and the acid <br>I lost my virginity to a Tipperary woman <br>A heart that was broken, but it wasn't the first or the last time <br><br>These are my memories <br>These are my memories, coming home <br><br>Under the wings of the man they called Green, I found freedom <br>Three children, one wife, a twist of the knife and a scandal <br>Divorce, separation, some kind of salvation came lately <br>So many have gone, but I know it's just business as usual <br><br>These are my memories <br>These are my memories <br>These are my memories <br>These are my memories <br>These are my memories <br>These are my memories, coming home <br><br>These memories keep coming back <br>These memories keep coming back <br>All those years ago <br>All those years ago]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Business As Usual (Live)" label="Business As Usual (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Walking_By_Myself_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Walking By Myself (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Walking_By_Myself_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Walking By Myself (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You know I love you <br>You know it's true <br>Give you all my love, babe <br>What more can I do <br><br>Walking by myself <br>I hope you'll understand <br>I just want to be your lovin' man <br><br>I love ya, yes I love you <br>With my heart and soul <br>I wouldn't mistreat you <br>For my weight in gold <br><br>You know I love you <br>You know it's true <br>Give you all my love, babe <br>What more can I do <br><br>Walking by myself <br>I hope you'll understand <br>I just want to be your lovin' man <br><br>Here we go <br>Keep on walkin' <br><br>You know I love you <br>You know it's true <br>I give you all my , babe <br>What more can I do <br><br>I'm walking by myself <br>I hope you'll understand <br>I just want to be your lovin' man <br><br>I said I'm walking by myself <br>I hope you'll understand <br>I just want to be your lovin' <br>I just want to be your lovin' <br>I just want to be your lovin' man <br>That's right]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Walking By Myself (Live)" label="Walking By Myself (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Oh_Pretty_Woman_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Oh Pretty Woman (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Oh_Pretty_Woman_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Oh Pretty Woman (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, pretty woman <br>Sure's the rising sun <br>Says all your cheap paint and powder <br>Ain't gonna help you none <br><br>'Cause she's a pretty woman <br>Right down to her bone <br>So you might as well <br>Leave your skin alone <br><br>Pretty woman <br>What's the matter with you <br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br><br>Oh, pretty woman <br>Whatcha gonna do <br>You kept on foolin' around <br>Till I got stuck on you <br><br>So you can drop your mess <br>And come down off your throne <br>Stop using my poor heart <br>As just a stepping stone <br><br>Pretty woman <br>What's the matter with you <br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br><br>Oh, pretty woman <br>That's all right for you <br>Now you just go on doing <br>What you wanna do <br><br>But someday when you think <br>That you've got it made <br>You're gettin' water deep enough <br>So you can't wade <br><br>Pretty woman <br>What's the matter with you <br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br><br>Oh, pretty woman <br>Oh, pretty woman <br>Oh, pretty woman <br>Oh, pretty woman <br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br>No <br><br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br>No <br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br><br>Oh, pretty woman <br>I just can't make you love me <br>Oh, no]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Oh Pretty Woman (Live)" label="Oh Pretty Woman (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Always_There_For_You_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Always There For You (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Always_There_For_You_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Always There For You (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The rhythm of our lives is changing day by day <br>It seems no matter what I do or what I say <br>that I'm always there for you <br>but you're never here for me <br><br>So many times you take me halfway to my dreams <br>but then you close the door, and every time it seems <br>that I'm always there for you <br>but you're never here for me <br>Yes, I'm always there for you <br>but you're never here for me <br><br>The rhythm of our lives is changing day by day <br>It seems no matter what I do or what I say <br>that I'm always there for you <br>but you're never here for me <br>Yes, I'm always there for you <br><br>I am always there for you <br>but you're never here for me <br>Yes, I'm always there for you <br>but you're never here for me <br><br>I'm always there for you <br>I'm always there for you <br>I'm always there for you <br>I'm always there for you]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Always There For You (Live)" label="Always There For You (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Ive_Found_My_Love_In_You_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - I`ve Found My Love In You (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Ive_Found_My_Love_In_You_Live/" title="Gary Moore - I`ve Found My Love In You (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can still remember <br>Like it was yesterday <br>The pain inside my heart <br>As you turned to walk away <br><br>I don't know, I don't care <br>What the people say <br>I don't know, I don't care <br>I love you anyway <br><br>For I have found my love in you <br>And I have found a love so true <br><br>I can still remember <br>Like it was just the other day <br>I could have done without those stories <br>While you're so far away <br><br>I don't know, I don't care <br>What my friends all say <br>I don't know, I don't care <br>I love you anyway <br><br>For I have found my love in you <br>And I have found a love so true <br><br>Ooh that first sweet night together <br>I will remember it forever <br>I put my heart on the line <br>Though I knew I was wrong, I would keep holding on <br><br>Do you still remember <br>All those times ago <br>When you lay like a flame in my arms <br>And I could never let you go <br><br>For I have found my love in you <br>And I have found a love so true <br>Yes, I have found my love in you <br>And I have found a love so true]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="I`ve Found My Love In You (Live)" label="I`ve Found My Love In You (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Cold_Wind_Blows_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Cold Wind Blows (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Cold_Wind_Blows_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Cold Wind Blows (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sun don't shine round here no more <br>Since my baby walked on out that door <br>She broke my heart , make no mistake <br>All i did was give <br>All she did was take <br>But don't you know , where she goes <br>The cold wind blows <br><br>Well my baby told so many lies <br>I couldn't see through my blinded eyes <br>She choked me up with her bad , bad seed <br>Took the flowers i gave her and strangled them with weeds <br>But don't you know, where she goes <br>The cold wind blows <br><br>I ain't gonna cry no more <br>I ain't gonna cry no more <br>I ain't gonna cry no more <br>Cry no more <br><br>Sun don't shine round here no more <br>Since my baby walked on out that door <br>She broke my heart , make no mistake <br>All i did was give <br>All she did was take <br>But don't you know , where she goes <br>The cold wind blows <br>The cold wind blows <br><br>I ain't gonna cry no more <br>I ain't gonna cry no more <br>I ain't gonna cry no more <br>I ain't gonna cry no more <br>Cry no more <br>Cry no more <br>Yeah , cry no more <br>Yeah , cry no more]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Cold Wind Blows (Live)" label="Cold Wind Blows (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/One_Fine_Day_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - One Fine Day (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/One_Fine_Day_Live/" title="Gary Moore - One Fine Day (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One of these days we'll be together <br>One of these days we'll be as one <br>Love and illumination <br>All across every nation <br><br>One fine day, we will walk in the sunshine <br>One fine day, we will reach to the stars <br><br>One of these days we'll be together <br>One of these days we'll be as one <br>Love and illumination <br>All across every nation <br><br>One fine day, we will walk in the sunshine <br>One fine day, we will reach to the stars <br><br>Even as we speak, time marches on <br>Even as we speak, the devil's plan goes on <br><br>One fine day we'll be together <br>One fine day we'll be as one <br>One fine day <br>One fine day]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="One Fine Day (Live)" label="One Fine Day (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/One_Good_Reason_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - One Good Reason (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/One_Good_Reason_Live/" title="Gary Moore - One Good Reason (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Take me out of here <br>This place is getting much too small <br>Make me disappear <br>Vanish through the nearest wall <br><br>Give me one good reason why i should stay <br>Give me one good reason to go on this way <br>Give me one good reason why i should stay with you <br>With you <br><br>Take me out of here <br>This place is closing in on me <br>Make it disappear <br>Somewhere else i wanna be <br><br>Give me one good reason why i should stay <br>Give me one good reason to go on this way <br>Give me one good reason why i should stay with you <br>With you <br><br>Give me one good reason why i should stay <br>Give me one good reason to go on this way <br>Give me one good reason why i should stay with you <br>With you <br>With you <br><br>Take me out of here]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="One Good Reason (Live)" label="One Good Reason (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Jumping_At_Shadows_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Jumping At Shadows (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Jumping_At_Shadows_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Jumping At Shadows (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What can you say <br>There isn't much to tell <br>I'm going downhill <br>and I blame myself <br>I've been jumpin' at shadows <br>thinking 'bout my life <br><br>Everybody points their hand at me <br>I know I'm just a picture <br>of what I should've been <br>I've been jumpin' at shadows <br>thinking 'bout my life <br><br>What can you say <br>There isn't much to tell <br>I'm going downhill <br>and I blame myself <br>I've been jumpin' at shadows <br>thinking 'bout my life]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Jumping At Shadows (Live)" label="Jumping At Shadows (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Stop_Messing_Around_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Stop Messing Around (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Stop_Messing_Around_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Stop Messing Around (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, baby please stop messin' around <br>You're messin' around with my heart <br>Baby please stop messin' around <br>You're messin' around with my heart <br>And if you don't stop messin' baby <br>Pretty soon we're gonna have to part <br><br>Oh, baby please stop messin' around <br>You're messin' around all the time <br>Baby please stop messin' around <br>You're messin' around all the time <br>And if you don't stop messin' baby <br>You're gonna be someone elses baby, not mine <br><br>Squeeze me baby till my face turn cherry red <br>Roll me so hard, I'll fall right out of bed <br>Please stop messin' around <br>You're messin around all the time <br>If you don't stop messin' baby <br>You're gonna be someone elses baby, not mine <br><br>Squeeze me baby till my face turn cherry red <br>Roll me so hard, I'm gonna fall right out of bed <br>Please stop messin' around <br>You're messin around all the time <br>If you don't stop messin' baby <br>You're gonna be someone elses baby, not mine <br>Yeah]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Stop Messing Around (Live)" label="Stop Messing Around (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/The_Blues_Is_Alright_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - The Blues Is Alright (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/The_Blues_Is_Alright_Live/" title="Gary Moore - The Blues Is Alright (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Want you to hear me when I say <br>that the blues is back <br>and it's here to stay <br><br>I wanna tell you a story <br>a story all about the blues <br>I want you to listen to me baby <br>while I sing it to you <br>Want you to hear me when I say <br>that the blues is back <br>and it's here to stay <br><br>I used to have me somebody <br>she mean't the whole world to me <br>But she left me for someone else <br>left my heart in misery <br>Yes, she did <br>But I knew the day she left me <br>that the blues was gonna be a part of me <br>Yes, it was <br><br>Since you left me with the blues <br>it was the last thing I thought I could use <br>But I'm glad that you left me <br>left me with the blues <br>If you hadn't given me the blues <br>I wouldn't find myself someone sweet as you <br><br>And I'm gonna tell you <br>I said hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>I said hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Allright , allright <br>Allright , allright <br>every day and night <br><br>Here we go Albert <br>One more time <br><br>Since you left me with the blues <br>it was the last thing I thought I could use <br>But I'm glad that you left me <br>left me with the blues <br>If you hadn't given me the blues <br>I wouldn't find myself someone sweet as you <br><br>And I'm gonna sing it <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>I said hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Allright , allright <br>Allright , allright <br>every day and night <br><br>I said hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>I said hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Allright , allright <br>It's allright , allright <br>Every day and night <br><br>One more time <br><br>I said hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>I said hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>It's allright , allright <br>It's allright , allright <br>It's allright , allright <br>It's allright , allright <br>It's allright every day and every night <br><br>Yes, it is <br>Want you to hear me when I say <br>That the blues is back <br>And it's here to stay <br>The blues is allright]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="The Blues Is Alright (Live)" label="The Blues Is Alright (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Since_I_Met_You_Baby_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Since I Met You Baby (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Since_I_Met_You_Baby_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Since I Met You Baby (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I used to wake up in the morning with an aching head <br>I couldn't remember anything I'd said <br>My friends told me I was getting out of line <br>If it wasn't for you baby, I'd be doing time <br><br>Since I met you baby <br>you've made a new man of me <br>Since I met you baby <br>I'm happy as a man could be <br>Yes, I am <br><br>I used to think I was better than the rest <br>Ain't no doubt about it, I was no second best <br>Didn't seem to matter what was right or what was wrong <br>I did some crazy things before you came along <br><br>Since I met you baby <br>you've made a new man of me <br>Since I met you baby <br>I'm happy as a man could be <br>Yes, I am <br><br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>I'm happy as a man could be <br>One more time <br><br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Since I met you baby <br>Well, since I met you baby <br>I'm happy as a man could be <br>Yes, I am <br><br>Happy as a man can be <br>You tell 'em Gary <br>Yeah]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Since I Met You Baby (Live)" label="Since I Met You Baby (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/All_Your_Love_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - All Your Love (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:39:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:39:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/All_Your_Love_Live/" title="Gary Moore - All Your Love (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All your lovin' is lovin' <br>All your kissin' is kissin' <br>All your lovin' is lovin' <br>All your kissin' is kissin' <br>Before I met you baby <br>I never knew what I was missin' <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>When I say I love you baby <br>Gotta say you love me too <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>When I say I love you baby <br>You gotta say you love me too <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>Before I met you baby <br>I never knew what I was missin' <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>Before I met you baby <br>I never knew what I was missin']]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="All Your Love (Live)" label="All Your Love (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Key_To_Love_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Key To Love (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Key_To_Love_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Key To Love (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I never realized that you were in pain <br>Wanna help you honey, let me see you again <br>Hurts my soul baby, when I find you're feeling rough, yeah <br>Life is so bad baby <br>when do I find the key to love <br><br>The smile on your face wipe away those tears <br>Life is gonna get better as you live through those years <br>Hurts my soul baby, when I find you're feeling rough, ooh <br>Life is so bad baby <br>when do I find the key to love <br><br>Somewhere in this world, the one you're waiting for <br>gonna come along baby, turn the key to your door <br>Hurts my soul baby, when I find you're feeling rough, yeah <br>Life is so bad baby <br>when do I find the key to love <br><br>When do I find the key to love]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Key To Love (Live)" label="Key To Love (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/You_Dont_Love_Me_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - You Don`t Love Me (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/You_Dont_Love_Me_Live/" title="Gary Moore - You Don`t Love Me (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You don't love me, woman <br>You don't love me, yes I know <br>You don't love me, woman <br>You don't love me, yes I know <br>Well I'm gonna tell everybody <br>Stay away of my back <br><br>Well I'm gonna talk to your mother <br>I'm gonna talk to your father too <br>Well I'm gonna talk to your mother <br>I'm gonna talk to your father too <br>Well I'm gonna tell everybody <br><br>What those young girls will do to you <br><br>Well I'm gonna talk to your mother <br>I'm gonna talk to your father too <br>Well I'm gonna talk to your mother <br>I'm gonna talk to your father too <br>Well I'm gonna tell everybody <br>What those young girls will do to you <br><br>You don't love me, woman <br>You don't love me, yes I know <br>You don't love me, woman <br>You don't love me, yes I know <br>Well I'm gonna tell everybody <br>Stay away of my back]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="You Don`t Love Me (Live)" label="You Don`t Love Me (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Need_Your_Love_So_Bad_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Need Your Love So Bad (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Need_Your_Love_So_Bad_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Need Your Love So Bad (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Need someone's hand <br>To lead me through the night <br>Need someone's arms <br>To hold and squeeze me tight <br>'Cause when the night begins <br>I'm at an end <br>Because I need your love so bad <br><br>Need some lips <br>To feel next to mine <br>Need someone to stand up <br>And tell me when I'm lyin' <br>When the lights are low <br>And it's time to go <br>That's when I need your love so bad <br><br>Why don't you give it up <br>Bring it on home to me <br>Or write it on a piece of paper, darlin' <br>So it can be read to me <br>Tell me that you love me <br>And stop driving me mad <br>Beacause I <br>I need your love so bad <br><br>Need your soft voice <br>Talk to me at night <br>Don't want you to worry baby <br>'Cause I know we can make everything allright <br>Listen to my plea baby <br>Bring it home to me <br>Because I need your love so bad]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Need Your Love So Bad (Live)" label="Need Your Love So Bad (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Merry-Go-Round_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Merry-Go-Round (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Merry-Go-Round_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Merry-Go-Round (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I first met you baby <br>I didn't even know your name <br>When I first met you baby <br>I didn't even know your name <br>Oh, I was feelin' low on the ground <br>Bad luck and evil women were to blame <br><br>I never realized <br>How sweet and kind one woman can be <br>I never realized, people <br>How sweet and kind a woman can be <br>Oh, but when I looked in your eyes <br>I knew true love had come to me <br>Yeah <br><br>Take my hand <br>Hold it tight and don't let go <br>Take my hand, take my hand <br>Hold it tight and don't let go <br>'Cause our love is like a merry go round <br>Forever and ever round it goes]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Merry-Go-Round (Live)" label="Merry-Go-Round (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/I_Loved_Another_Woman_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - I Loved Another Woman (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/I_Loved_Another_Woman_Live/" title="Gary Moore - I Loved Another Woman (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My baby's gone and left me cryin' by myself <br>My baby's gone and left me cryin' by myself <br>I loved another woman, now I lost my best gal <br><br>She was a real good woman <br>Never done me no harm <br>Was a real good woman <br>Never done me no harm <br>I loved another woman <br>Now she's up and she's gone <br><br>Well, come back baby <br>I won't do you no wrong <br>Come back baby <br>I won't do you no wrong <br>I loved another woman <br>And I won't do that no more <br><br>Wow wow wow wow <br>Wow wow wow wow <br>Wow wow wow wow <br>Wow wow wow wow <br>Wow wow wow wow <br>Wow wow wow wow <br><br>Wow wow wow wow <br>Wow wow wow wow <br>Wow wow wow wow <br>Wow wow wow wow <br>Wow wow wow wow <br>Wow wow wow wow]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="I Loved Another Woman (Live)" label="I Loved Another Woman (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Oh_Pretty_Woman_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Oh Pretty Woman (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Oh_Pretty_Woman_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Oh Pretty Woman (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, pretty woman <br>Sure's the rising sun <br>Says all your cheap paint and powder <br>Ain't gonna help you none <br><br>'Cause she's a pretty woman <br>Right down to her bone <br>So you might as well <br>Leave your skin alone <br><br>Pretty woman <br>What's the matter with you <br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br><br>Oh, pretty woman <br>Whatcha gonna do <br>You kept on foolin' around <br>Till I got stuck on you <br><br>So you can drop your mess <br>And come down off your throne <br>Stop using my poor heart <br>As just a stepping stone <br><br>Pretty woman <br>What's the matter with you <br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br><br>Oh, pretty woman <br>That's all right for you <br>Now you just go on doing <br>What you wanna do <br><br>But someday when you think <br>That you've got it made <br>You're gettin' water deep enough <br>So you can't wade <br><br>Pretty woman <br>What's the matter with you <br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br><br>Oh, pretty woman <br>Oh, pretty woman <br>Oh, pretty woman <br>Oh, pretty woman <br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br>No <br><br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br>No <br>Can't make you love me <br>No matter what I do <br><br>Oh, pretty woman <br>I just can't make you love me <br>Oh, no]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Oh Pretty Woman (Live)" label="Oh Pretty Woman (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Long_Grey_Mare_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Long Grey Mare (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Long_Grey_Mare_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Long Grey Mare (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I got a long grey mare <br>She won't let me ride <br>I got a long grey mare <br>She won't let me ride <br>She makes me brush her in the morning <br>Put her to bed every night, yeah <br><br>Long grey mare <br>Why can't we be just like before <br>Long grey mare <br>Why can't we be just like before <br>We used to ride so hard <br>Oh, till we couldn't take no more, yeah <br><br>Long grey mare <br>Don't I feed you every day <br>Long grey mare <br>Well, don't I feed you every day <br>And when I dig you with my spur <br>You turn around the other way]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Long Grey Mare (Live)" label="Long Grey Mare (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/If_You_Be_My_Baby_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - If You Be My Baby (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/If_You_Be_My_Baby_Live/" title="Gary Moore - If You Be My Baby (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If you be my baby <br>Tell you what I'll do <br>I'll give you so much lovin' <br>You gotta love me too <br>If you be my baby <br>If you be my baby <br>If you be my baby <br>I'm gonna keep you satisfied, yeah <br><br>Now listen to me baby <br>Just what I'm talkin' 'bout <br>You got something woman <br>Make a dumb man scream and shout <br>If you be my baby <br>If you be my baby <br>If you be my baby <br>I'm gonna keep you satisfied, yeah <br><br>Lookin' for a woman <br>Never done no wrong <br>Cook my meals in the daytime <br>And love me all night long <br>If you be my baby <br>If you be my baby <br>Said, if you be my baby <br>Well, I'm gonna keep you satisfied, ah <br><br>If you be my baby <br>I tell you what I'll do <br>I'll give you so much loving <br>You gotta love me too <br>If you be my baby <br>If you be my baby <br>If you be my baby <br>I'm gonna keep you satisfied, yeah]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="If You Be My Baby (Live)" label="If You Be My Baby (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/The_Blues_Is_Alright_Live_Feat_Albert_Collins/</id><title>Gary Moore - The Blues Is Alright (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/The_Blues_Is_Alright_Live_Feat_Albert_Collins/" title="Gary Moore - The Blues Is Alright (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Want you to hear me when I say <br>that the blues is back <br>and it's here to stay <br><br>I wanna tell you a story <br>a story all about the blues <br>I want you to listen to me baby <br>while I sing it to you <br>Want you to hear me when I say <br>that the blues is back <br>and it's here to stay <br><br>I used to have me somebody <br>she mean't the whole world to me <br>But she left me for someone else <br>left my heart in misery <br>Yes, she did <br>But I knew the day she left me <br>that the blues was gonna be a part of me <br>Yes, it was <br><br>Since you left me with the blues <br>it was the last thing I thought I could use <br>But I'm glad that you left me <br>left me with the blues <br>If you hadn't given me the blues <br>I wouldn't find myself someone sweet as you <br><br>And I'm gonna tell you <br>I said hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>I said hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Allright , allright <br>Allright , allright <br>every day and night <br><br>Here we go Albert <br>One more time <br><br>Since you left me with the blues <br>it was the last thing I thought I could use <br>But I'm glad that you left me <br>left me with the blues <br>If you hadn't given me the blues <br>I wouldn't find myself someone sweet as you <br><br>And I'm gonna sing it <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>I said hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Allright , allright <br>Allright , allright <br>every day and night <br><br>I said hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>I said hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Allright , allright <br>It's allright , allright <br>Every day and night <br><br>One more time <br><br>I said hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>I said hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>Hey, hey, the blues is allright <br>It's allright , allright <br>It's allright , allright <br>It's allright , allright <br>It's allright , allright <br>It's allright every day and every night <br><br>Yes, it is <br>Want you to hear me when I say <br>That the blues is back <br>And it's here to stay <br>The blues is allright]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="The Blues Is Alright (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins)" label="The Blues Is Alright (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Stop_Messing_Around_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Stop Messing Around (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Stop_Messing_Around_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Stop Messing Around (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, baby please stop messin' around <br>You're messin' around with my heart <br>Baby please stop messin' around <br>You're messin' around with my heart <br>And if you don't stop messin' baby <br>Pretty soon we're gonna have to part <br><br>Oh, baby please stop messin' around <br>You're messin' around all the time <br>Baby please stop messin' around <br>You're messin' around all the time <br>And if you don't stop messin' baby <br>You're gonna be someone elses baby, not mine <br><br>Squeeze me baby till my face turn cherry red <br>Roll me so hard, I'll fall right out of bed <br>Please stop messin' around <br>You're messin around all the time <br>If you don't stop messin' baby <br>You're gonna be someone elses baby, not mine <br><br>Squeeze me baby till my face turn cherry red <br>Roll me so hard, I'm gonna fall right out of bed <br>Please stop messin' around <br>You're messin around all the time <br>If you don't stop messin' baby <br>You're gonna be someone elses baby, not mine <br>Yeah]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Stop Messing Around (Live)" label="Stop Messing Around (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/King_Of_The_Blues_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - King Of The Blues (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/King_Of_The_Blues_Live/" title="Gary Moore - King Of The Blues (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[He was born in Mississippi 1924 <br>He was born in Mississippi 1924 <br>Left his home with no money <br>He had to pay his dues <br>But he knew the time was comin' <br>When he'd be king of the blues <br>King of the blues <br><br>Lost his heart to a woman <br>Lucy was her name <br>Lost his heart to a woman <br>Lucy was her name <br>Yes, it was <br>When he hears her sing so sweetly <br>He knows he just can't lose <br>When he holds her in his arms he knows that <br>He's the king of the blues <br><br>He's a Hunter with a Crosscut Saw <br>Born Under A Bad Sign <br>Caught his baby messin' down the Laundromat <br>He Almost Lost his Mind <br>Yeah <br><br>He was born in Mississippi 1924 <br>He was born in Indianola, Mississippi 1924 <br>Yes, he was <br>He doesn't need no jester to keep him amused <br>He's got Lucy by his side <br>He's making headline news <br>Doesn't need no palace <br>Like Freddie down in Dallas <br>You can call him what you like <br>I call him king of the blues <br><br>That's right <br>Mister, Albert King of the blues <br>Yeah <br>King of the blues <br>Let me hear ya]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="King Of The Blues (Live)" label="King Of The Blues (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Further_On_Up_The_Road_Live_Feat_Albert_Collins/</id><title>Gary Moore - Further On Up The Road (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Further_On_Up_The_Road_Live_Feat_Albert_Collins/" title="Gary Moore - Further On Up The Road (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Further on up the road <br>Someone's gonna hurt you like you hurt me <br>Further on up the road <br>Someone's gonna hurt you like you hurt me <br>Further on up the road <br>Just you wait and see <br><br>Now you're laughing pretty baby <br>But one day you'll be cryin' <br>You're laughing pretty baby <br>But one day you'll be cryin' <br>Further on up the road <br>You'll see I wasn't lyin' <br><br>Further on up the road <br>Someone's gonna hurt you like you hurt me <br>Further on up the road <br>Someone's gonna hurt you like you hurt me <br>Further on up the road <br>Just you wait and see <br>Here we go <br><br>Now you're laughing pretty baby <br>But one day you'll be cryin' <br>You're laughing pretty baby <br>But one day you'll be cryin' <br>Further on up the road <br>You'll see I wasn't lyin' <br><br>Further on up the road <br>Someone's gonna hurt you like you hurt me <br>Further on up the road <br>Someone's gonna hurt you like you hurt me <br>Further on up the road <br>Just you wait and see, yeah <br><br>Now you're laughing pretty baby <br>But one day you'll be cryin' <br>You're laughing pretty baby <br>But one day you'll be cryin' <br>Further on up the road <br>You'll see I wasn't lyin' <br><br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road <br><br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road <br>Further on up the road, yeah <br>Further on up the road <br>Someone's gonna hurt you]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Further On Up The Road (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins)" label="Further On Up The Road (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Cold_Cold_Feeling_Live_Feat_Albert_Collins/</id><title>Gary Moore - Cold Cold Feeling (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Cold_Cold_Feeling_Live_Feat_Albert_Collins/" title="Gary Moore - Cold Cold Feeling (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sun don't shine 'round here no more <br>Since my baby walked on out that door <br>She broke my heart, make no mistake <br>All I did was give <br>All she did was take <br>But don't you know <br>Where she goes <br>The cold wind blows <br><br>Well, my baby told so many lies <br>I couldn't see through my blinded eyes <br>She choked me up with her bad, bad seed <br>Took the flowers I gave her <br>And strangled them with weeds <br>But don't you know <br>Where she goes <br>The cold wind blows <br><br>I ain't gonna cry no more <br>I ain't gonna cry no more <br>I ain't gonna cry no more <br>Cry no more <br><br>Sun don't shine 'round here no more <br>Since my baby walked on out that door <br>She broke my heart, make no mistake <br>All I did was give <br>And all she did was take <br>But don't you know <br>Where she goes <br>The cold wind blows <br>The cold wind blows <br><br>I ain't gonna cry no more <br>I ain't gonna cry no more <br>I ain't gonna cry no more <br>I ain't gonna cry no more <br>Ain't gonna cry no more <br>Cry no more <br>Gonna cry no more <br>Ain't gonna cry no more]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Cold Cold Feeling (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins)" label="Cold Cold Feeling (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Too_Tired_Live_Feat_Albert_Collins/</id><title>Gary Moore - Too Tired (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Too_Tired_Live_Feat_Albert_Collins/" title="Gary Moore - Too Tired (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>I laid down last night, too tired to wake <br>I had a chill this morning, too tired to shake <br>I got a good poker hand, too tired to win <br>I can hear my baby knockin', too tired to let her in <br><br>I'm tired <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm tired <br>Too tired, too tired for anything <br><br>I'm too tired to walk <br>Too tired to run <br>I can hear my baby callin' <br>Too tired, too tired <br>I'm tired <br>Yes, I'm tired <br>I'm tired <br>I'm too tired for anything <br><br>Take over Albert, I'm too tired for this <br><br>I'm tired of prospherity <br>I'm tired of luck <br>I'm sittin' on a pin <br>I'm too tired to get up <br><br>I'm tired <br>I declare I'm tired <br>I'm too tired <br>too tired for anything <br><br>Oh, Albert I'm tired <br>You better take over Albert <br>I'm too tired baby]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Too Tired (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins)" label="Too Tired (Live) (Feat. Albert Collins)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Moving_On_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Moving On (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Moving_On_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Moving On (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm gonna leave this place tomorrow <br>I'm gonna leave this town behind <br>I'll be gone before the morning <br>On the other side of the mound <br><br>That's why I'm moving on <br>I'm moving on <br>I've been hanging around too long <br>It's time I was moving on <br><br>Oh, well I'm tired of the same old faces <br>And I'm sick of the same old names <br>I'm getting bored with the same old places <br>Everybody starts to look the same <br><br>That's why I'm moving on <br>I'm moving on <br>I've been hanging around too long <br>It's time I was moving on <br><br>Move it for me <br><br>I've been tryin' to settle down here <br>But my feet just won't stay still <br>And I've heard that the grass is greener <br>On the other side of the hill <br><br>That's why I'm moving on <br>I'm moving on <br>I've been hanging around too long <br>It's time I was moving on <br><br>Give me one more for the go <br><br>I'm gonna leave this town tomorrow <br>I'm gonna leave this place behind <br>You can bet your bottom dollar <br>All my troubles will be far behind <br><br>That's why I'm moving on <br>I'm moving on <br>I've been hanging around too long <br>It's time I was moving on <br><br>I've been hanging around too long <br>It's time I was moving on <br><br>Said I've been hanging around too long <br>It's time I was moving on <br>Get out of here]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Moving On (Live)" label="Moving On (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Texas_Strut_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Texas Strut (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Texas_Strut_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Texas Strut (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One two three four <br>Let me tell you about the Texas blues <br><br>I went down south to Dallas <br>To hear those cowboys wail <br>Came across that Billy Gibbons <br>Ridin' on that ZZ trail <br><br>I just can't lose with the Texas blues <br>I said I just can't lose with the Texas blues <br>The Texas blues <br><br>Got myself in Double Trouble <br>When I saw that Texas Flood <br>Stevie said The Sky Is Crying <br>Superstition's in his blood <br><br>I just can't lose with the Texas blues <br>I said I just can't lose with the Texas blues <br>The Texas blues <br>How how how how <br><br>Come on <br><br>I heard that Houston Twister <br>He could run you off the tracks <br>When he plays that Cold Cold Feeling <br>You get the shivers down your back <br><br>I just can't lose with the Texas blues <br>I said I just can't lose with the Texas blues <br>The Texas blues <br>A how how how how <br><br>Well, I'm going back to Dallas <br>Won't go waitin' for no bus <br>Ridin' off into the sunset <br>You won't see my heels for dust <br><br>I just can't lose with the Texas blues <br>I said I just can't lose with the Texas blues <br>I said I just can't lose with the Texas blues <br>And I just can't lose with the Texas blues <br>The Texas blues <br>Texas blues <br>A how how how how <br>A how how how how]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Texas Strut (Live)" label="Texas Strut (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/You_Dont_Love_Me_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - You Don`t Love Me (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/You_Dont_Love_Me_Live/" title="Gary Moore - You Don`t Love Me (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You don't love me, woman <br>You don't love me, yes I know <br>You don't love me, woman <br>You don't love me, yes I know <br>Well I'm gonna tell everybody <br>Stay away of my back <br><br>Well I'm gonna talk to your mother <br>I'm gonna talk to your father too <br>Well I'm gonna talk to your mother <br>I'm gonna talk to your father too <br>Well I'm gonna tell everybody <br><br>What those young girls will do to you <br><br>Well I'm gonna talk to your mother <br>I'm gonna talk to your father too <br>Well I'm gonna talk to your mother <br>I'm gonna talk to your father too <br>Well I'm gonna tell everybody <br>What those young girls will do to you <br><br>You don't love me, woman <br>You don't love me, yes I know <br>You don't love me, woman <br>You don't love me, yes I know <br>Well I'm gonna tell everybody <br>Stay away of my back]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="You Don`t Love Me (Live)" label="You Don`t Love Me (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Midnight_Blues_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - Midnight Blues (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/Midnight_Blues_Live/" title="Gary Moore - Midnight Blues (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's the darkest hour <br>Of the darkest night <br>It's a million miles <br>From the morning light <br><br>Can't get no sleep <br>Don't know what to do <br>I've got those midnight blues <br><br>When the shadows fall <br>I feel the night closing in <br>There must be some reason <br>For this mood I'm getting in <br><br>Can't get no sleep <br>Don't know what to do <br>I've got those midnight blues <br><br>Every evening after sundown <br>As the light begins to fade <br>I feel so low, but I just don't know <br>Why these blues won't go away <br><br>Every evening after sundown <br>As the light begins to fade <br>I feel so low, but I just don't know <br>Why these blues won't go away <br><br>It's the darkest hour <br>Of the darkest night <br>It's a million miles <br>To the morning light <br><br>Can't get no sleep <br>Don't know what to do <br>I've got those midnight blues <br>I've got those midnight blues <br>I've got those midnight blues <br>I've got those midnight blues]]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="Midnight Blues (Live)" label="Midnight Blues (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/All_Your_Love_Live/</id><title>Gary Moore - All Your Love (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:40:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:40:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Moore/All_Your_Love_Live/" title="Gary Moore - All Your Love (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All your lovin' is lovin' <br>All your kissin' is kissin' <br>All your lovin' is lovin' <br>All your kissin' is kissin' <br>Before I met you baby <br>I never knew what I was missin' <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>When I say I love you baby <br>Gotta say you love me too <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>That I got in store for you <br>When I say I love you baby <br>You gotta say you love me too <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>Before I met you baby <br>I never knew what I was missin' <br><br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>All your lovin' pretty baby <br>Before I met you baby <br>I never knew what I was missin']]></content><category term="Gary Moore" label="Gary Moore"/><category term="All Your Love (Live)" label="All Your Love (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/데니스프로젝트/사랑이_바람될때_그대는_눈물되어_Feat노훈/</id><title>데니스프로젝트 - 사랑이 바람될때 그대는 눈물되어 (Feat.노훈) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:46:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:46:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%B0%EB%8B%88%EC%8A%A4%ED%94%84%EB%A1%9C%EC%A0%9D%ED%8A%B8/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C%EB%90%A0%EB%95%8C_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%8A%94_%EB%88%88%EB%AC%BC%EB%90%98%EC%96%B4_Feat%EB%85%B8%ED%9B%88/" title="데니스프로젝트 - 사랑이 바람될때 그대는 눈물되어 (Feat.노훈) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑이 바람이 될 때 <br>그대는 눈물이 되어 <br>내겐 아직도 네 모습이 선명해 보여 <br>돌아갈 순 없을까 너를 볼 수 있을까 <br>사랑이 바람이 될 때 <br>그대는 눈물이 되어 <br>내겐 아직도 네 모습이 선명해 보여 <br>돌아갈 순 없을까 너를 볼 수 있을까 <br>정말로 사랑했을까 돌아보면 말야 <br>난 분명해 너와 같은 세상에서 살아 <br>너의 일부가 되고 싶을 뿐이였는데 <br>다시 생각해보니 맞아 내 욕심인 게 <br>한숨을 내뱉고 생각에 잠기면 <br>그때의 나로 돌아가고 싶어 한번 더 <br>어려운 말은 필요 없어 네가 필요해 <br>간절한 이 마음을 알아줄 사람이 없네 <br>걱정돼 솔직히 나보다 네가 <br>아니 네가 없는 내 모습이 걱정돼 진짜 <br>내가 뭘 할 수 있겠니 너 없는 하루 <br>단 하루라도 너와의 흔적이 전부 <br>답답해 소리치고 싶어 돌아와 <br>내가 아니 였어 그때 너에게 한말 <br>장난 이라고 다시 되돌리고 싶다고 <br>반복해 봐도 현실은 나 홀로 <br>사랑이 바람이 될 때 <br>그대는 눈물이 되어 <br>내겐 아직도 네 모습이 선명해 보여 <br>돌아갈 순 없을까 너를 볼 수 있을까 <br>사랑이 바람이 될 때 <br>그대는 눈물이 되어 <br>내겐 아직도 네 모습이 선명해 보여 <br>돌아갈 순 없을까 너를 볼 수 있을까 <br>사랑이 바람이 될 때 <br>그대는 눈물이 되어 <br>내겐 아직도 네 모습이 선명해 보여 <br>돌아갈 순 없을까 너를 볼 수 있을까 <br>사랑이 바람이 될 때 <br>그대는 눈물이 되어 <br>내겐 아직도 네 모습이 선명해 보여 <br>돌아갈 순 없을까 너를 볼 수 있을까 <br>도대체 이게 뭐야 누가 나 좀 말려봐 <br>너 아닌 사람에게 미쳐가고 날 좀 봐 <br>네가 떠나고 난 뒤 내 맘은 하얀 백지 <br>아무것도 할 수 없게 되 버린 건지 <br>너 역시 나와 같기를 바래 아직까지 <br>행복하지 마라 조금만 더 참아 <br>불쌍해 아니 한심해 보여 내가 <br>자꾸만 다른 사람 얼굴에서 보여 네가 <br>걱정돼 솔직히 나보다 네가 <br>아니 네가 없는 내 모습이 걱정 돼 진짜 <br>내가 뭘 할 수 있겠니 너 없는 하루 <br>단 하루라도 너와의 흔적이 전부 <br>답답해 소리치고 싶어 돌아와 <br>내가 아니 였어 그때 너에게 한말 <br>장난 이라고 다시 되돌리고 싶다고 <br>반복해 봐도 현실은 나 홀로 <br>사랑이 바람이 될 때 <br>그대는 눈물이 되어 <br>내겐 아직도 네 모습이 선명해 보여 <br>돌아갈 순 없을까 너를 볼 수 있을까 <br>사랑이 바람이 될 때 <br>그대는 눈물이 되어 <br>내겐 아직도 네 모습이 선명해 보여 <br>돌아갈 순 없을까 너를 볼 수 있을까 <br>사랑이 바람이 될 때 <br>그대는 눈물이 되어 <br>내겐 아직도 네 모습이 선명해 보여 <br>돌아갈 순 없을까 너를 볼 수 있을까 <br>사랑이 바람이 될 때 <br>그대는 눈물이 되어 <br>내겐 아직도 네 모습이 선명해 보여 <br>돌아갈 순 없을까 너를 볼 수 있을까 <br>]]></content><category term="데니스프로젝트" label="데니스프로젝트"/><category term="사랑이 바람될때 그대는 눈물되어 (Feat.노훈)" label="사랑이 바람될때 그대는 눈물되어 (Feat.노훈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PINE/Blue_Jacket/</id><title>PINE - Blue Jacket - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:46:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:46:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PINE/Blue_Jacket/" title="PINE - Blue Jacket - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can drag you by your feet until you fall in love with me <br>Call me baby, it would mean so much to me <br>I just want you to see the good in me <br>I just want you to see the good in us <br> I need your love more than ever <br>I can wait here until you want to walk with me <br>Take my hand it would mean so much to me <br>I need you now more than ever <br>I need your touch more than ever <br>I need your love more than ever]]></content><category term="PINE" label="PINE"/><category term="Blue Jacket" label="Blue Jacket"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PINE/Jilt/</id><title>PINE - Jilt - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:46:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:46:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PINE/Jilt/" title="PINE - Jilt - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I'm home I always seem to be alone <br>Is having you supposed to make a difference <br>It won't <br>Let's rest our eyes for another night <br>Would you miss me when I'm not here <br>Can we rest our eyes just for tonight <br>Where have you gone Has it been that long <br>I wonder what we look like with the sun in our eyes <br>Are we that blind <br>I told you the truth I'll be okay this time This time <br>I hope one day we're not waiting anymore <br>because the clock is always running out and so are you <br>I know one day we won't have to wait anymore <br>because the clock has stopped and we're alone on your floor <br> Cause I'm so sick of this pillow talk with you <br>You can see right through me like a window <br>I scream honesty, are you here with me <br>Tell me everything while you fall asleep]]></content><category term="PINE" label="PINE"/><category term="Jilt" label="Jilt"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PINE/Unrest/</id><title>PINE - (Un)rest - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:46:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:46:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PINE/Unrest/" title="PINE - (Un)rest - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You left me in the corner of my mind, running out of time <br>I couldn't sleep without the sense of you <br>I tossed and turned all night <br>It feels so empty and cold when you're not here, I need you near <br> Hold me til I sleep so I feel you in my dreams <br>Where are your secrets <br>I want to know what you're thinking about <br>Does it drag you down the way it does to me <br>Strip the sheets, I won't fall asleep <br>I'm exhausted, I need your body with me <br>These restless nights have got the best of me and <br>I can't fall asleep without the rest of me <br>Hold me til I sleep, so I feel you in my dreams <br>I'll take this disease, you and me]]></content><category term="PINE" label="PINE"/><category term="(Un)rest" label="(Un)rest"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PINE/Viable/</id><title>PINE - Viable - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:46:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:46:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PINE/Viable/" title="PINE - Viable - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let's hope i don't bring you to your knees <br>cause there's not a bone in my body that screams <br>Let this be <br>Did you want to sleep alone <br>Cause theres walls that we could use <br>I think i've lost myself in you <br>I feel the friction in our sheets <br>building up walls we don't intend to keep <br>Please disappoint me <br> I've always wondered what it felt like to see you alive <br>I just don't have time to let you waste mine <br>Lay me down, lay me down and tell me <br>You're gonna be here for longer than this summer <br>cause what really last forever]]></content><category term="PINE" label="PINE"/><category term="Viable" label="Viable"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PINE/Dolya/</id><title>PINE - Dolya - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:46:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:46:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PINE/Dolya/" title="PINE - Dolya - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I started a new page and everything has got me going insane <br>I feel drained, is it okay to say I won't stay <br>I think there's days that make me feel okay <br>Am I a coward for being afraid <br> It's too late to turn around <br>I've come accustomed to this sound <br>Push me around, hell I know it's hard <br>Stubborn and lazy sometimes it feels like it's just me now <br>I don't want to be the one to just give up <br>The only person to blame is me for doubting myself <br>I wish it was easy to be just who we wanted to be <br>I pushed you away and I watched you go <br>I know, I know it was ours It'll never be the same <br>This is the way it has to be without you, without me <br>This is how it's going to be without you You had to leave]]></content><category term="PINE" label="PINE"/><category term="Dolya" label="Dolya"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Promised_Ones_Big_Chocolate_Remix/</id><title>Blessthefall - Promised Ones (Big Chocolate Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:47:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:47:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Promised_Ones_Big_Chocolate_Remix/" title="Blessthefall - Promised Ones (Big Chocolate Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br><br>A deadly sight again <br>Our death rings <br>Out for now <br><br>So look at how I fight <br><br>There will be blood <br>There will be blood <br><br>No one can take this From us <br>I taste it and it's so close <br><br>There will be blood <br>There will be blood <br>On our hands <br><br>We are the promised ones <br>And nothings in our way <br>They can't stop <br><br>They'll never stop us <br>Tell all our families <br><br>We'll pray before them all <br>We will heal and we'll never die <br><br>Now they have no where to go <br>We know we've gone to far <br>To keep it all away <br><br>Sleep walkers in my life <br>There will be blood <br>There will be blood <br><br>We'll brace this storm together <br>I taste the end it's so close <br><br>There will be blood <br>There will be blood <br>On our hands <br><br>There will be blood <br>There will be blood <br>On our hands <br><br>We are the promised ones <br>And nothings in our way <br>They can't stop <br><br>They'll never stop us <br>Tell all our families <br><br>Well pray before them all <br>We will heal and we'll never die <br><br>Now they have no where to go <br><br>Well make it hard to find light <br>We have nothing to lose <br><br>Well make it hard to find light <br>We have nothing to lose <br><br>Oh <br><br>Nothing to lose <br>Nothing to lose <br><br>Don't you know <br><br>We are the promised ones <br>And nothings in our way <br>They can't stop <br><br>They'll never stop us <br>Tell all our enemies <br><br>We'll pray before the all <br>We will heal and we'll never die <br><br>We'll never die]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Promised Ones (Big Chocolate Remix)" label="Promised Ones (Big Chocolate Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Meet_Me_At_The_Gates/</id><title>Blessthefall - Meet Me At The Gates - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:47:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:47:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Meet_Me_At_The_Gates/" title="Blessthefall - Meet Me At The Gates - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe in softly, take my hand <br>We're saying goodbye but this is not the end <br>Your body's sinking, oh my soul <br>I'll see you on the other side when it is my turn <br><br>The sky will open up <br>I've waited long to feel your touch <br>So meet me at the gates <br>and wash these tears away <br><br>On this morning the music ends <br>I'm down on my knees by your hospital bed <br>So how can I live when I'm watching you die <br>I'll see you on the other side when it is my turn <br><br>Every breath I take like I can't escape <br>and I'm too afraid <br>Of letting go of you <br><br>I found the secret <br>To wash away <br>All this sadness]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Meet Me At The Gates" label="Meet Me At The Gates"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Till_The_Death_Of_Me/</id><title>Blessthefall - Till The Death Of Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:47:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:47:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Till_The_Death_Of_Me/" title="Blessthefall - Till The Death Of Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Save me, I'm looking in from the outside <br>Save me, as water fills my lungs <br>Save me, I'm reaching up for the surface <br>Save me before I choke <br><br>Take me on, I'm here, I'm ready <br><br>I don't want to live forever <br>I just want to live for you <br>If this world falls down around us <br>We'll be here shining through <br><br>And I know sometimes we move too fast <br>And leave our ghosts behind us <br>But now they're in front of me <br>Don't give up on me just yet <br>I know that you won't, I'm too hard to forget <br>Is this really what you want for me <br>Now I need to believe <br>Is this really where you want me to be <br>This is our struggle, we need to believe <br><br>When I'm gone don't cry for me <br>My spirit will live on <br>If you put your faith in me I could be the one <br>I'll live on <br><br>I still believe]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Till The Death Of Me" label="Till The Death Of Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Undefeated/</id><title>Blessthefall - Undefeated - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:47:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:47:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Undefeated/" title="Blessthefall - Undefeated - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We won't fall when we're under the gun <br>When all your heroes have failed you <br><br>You'll never show your face, you are a coward <br>We'll never let you win ever again, never again <br>Preach your gospel <br>Choke on your fortune and glory <br><br>No matter what they say we're not the ones who lost our way <br>We're fighting for our lives <br>It's not enough to say that we were the ones who lost our way <br>We're fighting for our lives <br><br>All you built is in ruins <br>All you loved has been destroyed <br><br>and now's the time you'll be forgotten <br>and now's the time, your time to be <br>Forgotten under when walls crash down around you]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Undefeated" label="Undefeated"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Dont_Say_Goodbye/</id><title>Blessthefall - Don`t Say Goodbye - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:47:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:47:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Dont_Say_Goodbye/" title="Blessthefall - Don`t Say Goodbye - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[YEAH <br>Do you remember when you lost hope <br>And faith in this world <br>This world <br>When will it change <br><br>Don't say goodbye <br>Say goodbye cause I know you can try to <br>Open your eyes it's all inside <br>You will wake from this nightmare <br>I know you'll find a better way <br><br>Now it seems like you're bleeding just to feel alive <br>Your arms always tell the story <br>And it looks like you're living just to pass the time <br>Digging deeper are you trying to find <br>Find the strength to carry on there is salvation <br>Keep holding on, keep holding <br><br>Don't say goodbye <br>Say goodbye cause I know you can try to <br>Open your eyes it's all inside <br>You will wake from this nightmare <br>I know you'll find a better way <br><br>A better way <br>A better way <br>A better way <br><br>You've gone too far even though I know you're dying to let go <br>You've gone too far, you've given up <br>Now you have to tell yourself where did you go wrong <br>And stop yourself from falling down <br>I can see you running, so far away, so far away <br>I can see you running, so far away, away <br>Don't you give up, don't give up]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Don`t Say Goodbye" label="Don`t Say Goodbye"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Bones_Crew/</id><title>Blessthefall - Bones Crew - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:47:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:47:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Bones_Crew/" title="Blessthefall - Bones Crew - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This August came and went, turned me upside down <br>Now I'm getting out of this town <br>and I told all my friends <br>I'm never coming back again, I'm going far away <br><br>Ten thousand miles from here <br>all the things that could have been, but now <br>Ten thousand miles from you <br>all the things I should have said, somehow <br>it's all that I could do <br><br>It's been a year since I've looked at your face <br>and I'm starting to get over, over you <br>Everything's changed <br>I'm never coming back again, I'm going far away <br><br>Cause finding home is not easy <br>and nothing's ever what I planned it to be <br>and if I told you that I missed you <br>You know I never tried to lie to you I meant it all along <br>Now I have only ten thousand miles]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Bones Crew" label="Bones Crew"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/40_Days/</id><title>Blessthefall - 40 Days... - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:47:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:47:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/40_Days/" title="Blessthefall - 40 Days... - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let's start at one <br>And count the days <br>Let's hope to God that time flies like they say <br>Cause this instance can't distance my heart from yours tonight <br>But I'm lying awake now and I'm holding your picture <br>It's so cold here without you <br><br>And I need you now, cause it's killing me <br>And I wish somehow, you were here with me <br>When I fall asleep I feel you with me <br>Till I fall asleep and you are with me <br><br>Could this be more <br>I've been up all night riding subway lines <br>Now we're sleeping on your floor <br><br>Can we make this a lifetime, you're all I want right now <br>Life keeps telling me I need to go <br>But what if I wanna stay <br>Cause I'm lost here without you <br><br>And I need you now, cause it's killin me <br>And I wish somehow, you were here with me <br><br>When I fall asleep, I feel you with me <br>Till I fall asleep, and you are with me <br><br>I've found a love I've never had before, you changed me <br>And I will wait however long it takes, you changed me <br>You say the words that I've been thinking <br>I'll never let you go <br><br>And I need you now, cause it's killing me <br>And I wish somehow, you were here with me <br><br>When I fall asleep, I feel you with me <br>Till I fall asleep, and you are with me <br><br>You changed me <br>You changed me <br><br>Next stop is Davisville, Davisville station]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="40 Days..." label="40 Days..."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/The_Reign/</id><title>Blessthefall - The Reign - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:47:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:47:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/The_Reign/" title="Blessthefall - The Reign - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I swear that this time it's real <br>I promise that I will keep true <br>My heart belongs to you <br><br>So let your love reign in my hallow land <br>Been waiting all my life to feel this, make me whole again <br>Just try and save me, just hold me in your hands <br>Been waiting all my life to feel this, make me whole again <br><br>All the time we spent just breaking out of this <br>we made it out <br>We are the ones with hearts of gold <br>I'm still the kid you used to know and I've got a lot to say <br>Make me the light for the rest of the world <br><br>You pulled me from my hell <br>You saved me from myself <br>and now this is who I am <br>at the end of the road]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="The Reign" label="The Reign"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Im_Bad_News_In_The_Best_Way/</id><title>Blessthefall - I`m Bad News, In The Best Way - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:47:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:47:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Im_Bad_News_In_The_Best_Way/" title="Blessthefall - I`m Bad News, In The Best Way - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tell me, what did you think when you found me lost <br>and my hope was fading <br>Tell me, what did you say to make me feel again <br>your voice could take me <br>Don't let the darkness surround me <br>lift me up, I'll let you in <br><br>I said I'm sorry and I won't forget the past regrets <br>and now that's over <br>I said I'm sorry you're my only one the past is gone <br>and all that's over, not losing you <br><br>Please take me home, stay with me tonight <br>Please take me home, I'm not losing you <br>I said that you are the one for me]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="I`m Bad News, In The Best Way" label="I`m Bad News, In The Best Way"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Bottomfeeder/</id><title>Blessthefall - Bottomfeeder - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:47:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:47:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Bottomfeeder/" title="Blessthefall - Bottomfeeder - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Keep moving down the line, what's sitting here is mine <br>You've taken far too long, go back where you belong <br>This place is not for the weak, this place is not for the weak <br>They've all been begging for the truth, it's over now it's over now <br><br>We gave our lives for this, it's all we have, it's all we'll ever know <br>We sacrificed for this, when it's said and done we'll have our scars to show <br>We'll have the scars to show <br><br>I am destruction, you'll never be the death of me <br>You are deception, I am the one that you betray <br><br>We gave our lives for this, it's all we have, it's all we'll ever know <br>We sacrificed for this, when it's said and done we'll have our scars to show <br>Our scars to show <br>We'll have our scars to show <br>From now 'till the end <br>From now until the end <br><br>It's set in stone now there's no turning back <br>We'll stand our ground, we are unbroken <br><br>We are unbroken <br>We are unbroken <br>We are unbroken]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Bottomfeeder" label="Bottomfeeder"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Promised_Ones/</id><title>Blessthefall - Promised Ones - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:47:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:47:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Promised_Ones/" title="Blessthefall - Promised Ones - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Watch as we start again, a different chapter now <br>So welcome to our fight, there will be blood <br>No one can take this from us <br>I taste the end it's so close, there will be blood <br>There will be blood on our hands <br><br>No one can take this from us <br>I taste the end it's so close, there will be blood <br>There will be blood on our hands <br><br>We are the promised ones and nothing's in our way <br>They can try but they'll never stop us <br>Tell all our enemies we're ready for the war <br>We've been here and we'll never die <br>Now they have nowhere to go <br><br>And now we've come too far to give it all away <br>So welcome to our lives, there will be blood <br>We'll brave this storm together <br>I taste the end it's so close, there will be blood <br>There will be blood on our hands you are nothing, you are nothing like us <br><br>We are the promised ones and nothing's in our way <br>They can try but they'll never stop us <br>Tell all our enemies we're ready for the war <br>We've been here and we'll never die <br>Now they have nowhere to go <br><br>We'll meet you on the front lines, we have nothing to lose <br>We'll meet you on the front lines, we have nothing to lose <br><br>Nothing to lose <br>Nothing to lose <br><br>Don't you know <br>We are the promised ones <br>And nothing's in our way <br>They can try <br>But they'll never stop us <br>Tell all our enemies <br>We're ready for the war <br>We've been here and we'll never die <br>We'll never die]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Promised Ones" label="Promised Ones"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Awakening/</id><title>Blessthefall - Awakening - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:47:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:47:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Awakening/" title="Blessthefall - Awakening - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We are the saints <br>We're taking over <br><br>We are the saints <br>We are the promised ones <br>We're taking over <br>With hearts like loaded guns <br>We are the saints <br>We are the promised ones <br>We're taking over <br>With hearts like loaded guns <br>We are the saints <br>We are the promised ones <br>We're taking over <br>With hearts like loaded guns <br>We are the saints <br>We are the promised ones <br>We're taking over <br>With hearts like loaded guns <br>We are the saints <br>We are the promised ones <br>We're taking over <br>With hearts like loaded guns]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Awakening" label="Awakening"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박수홍/Sorry_Mom_Remix/</id><title>박수홍 - Sorry Mom (Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:49:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:49:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%88%98%ED%99%8D/Sorry_Mom_Remix/" title="박수홍 - Sorry Mom (Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry Mom Sorry Mom <br>Sorry Mom Sorry Mom <br>Love you Mom Sorry Mom <br>하지만 내 맘이 시키는 대로 <br>내 몸이 원하는 대로 <br>Sorry Mom <br>Love you Mom Sorry Mom <br>하지만 내 맘이 시키는 대로 <br>내 몸이 원하는 대로 <br>Sorry Mom <br>Sorry Mom 맘 Sorry <br>Sorry Mom 맘 Sorry <br>Love you Mom Sorry Mom <br>하지만 내 맘이 시키는 대로 <br>내 몸이 원하는 대로 <br>Sorry Mom <br>Love you Mom Sorry Mom <br>하지만 내 맘이 시키는 대로 <br>내 몸이 원하는 대로 <br>Sorry Mom <br>Sorry Mom 맘 Sorry <br>Sorry Mom 맘 Sorry <br>]]></content><category term="박수홍" label="박수홍"/><category term="Sorry Mom (Remix)" label="Sorry Mom (Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박수홍/Clubber_Feat_오정현_김지수/</id><title>박수홍 - Clubber (Feat. 오정현, 김지수) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:49:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:49:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%88%98%ED%99%8D/Clubber_Feat_%EC%98%A4%EC%A0%95%ED%98%84_%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%80%EC%88%98/" title="박수홍 - Clubber (Feat. 오정현, 김지수) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Attention Baby Avenue <br>Attention Baby Avenue You <br>Attention Baby Avenue You <br>Avenue You You You <br>Lover Lover Clubber <br>어머니 Yo Let's Party Yeah <br>오늘도 모두 놀러 나와 향수 <br>필수품 장착 <br>차에서 내릴 땐 항상 한 명씩 <br>여유 있게 가 <br>나이는 숫자에 불과 <br>남들에게 휘둘리지 마 <br>그 비트도 내 몸에 딱 맞아 <br>예약을 다 끝냈으니까 <br>I Like That I Like That <br>오늘 밤도 난 Fly 예 <br>I Like That I Like That <br>늦바람 탐 My Body <br>더 뭐가 날 또 미치게 할까 <br>Right 엄마 난 걱정 마 <br>I Feel This <br>뮤직과 이비자 갈 거야 <br>Everyday I Just Wanna Be With You <br>Everytime I Thinking About With You <br>Oh Oh Yeah Yeah <br>Oh Take Me To The Party Tonight <br>Attention Baby Avenue You <br>Attention Baby Avenue You <br>오늘도 모두 놀러 나와 향수 <br>필수품 장착 <br>차에서 내릴 땐 항상 한 명씩 <br>여유 있게 가 <br>나이는 숫자에 불과 <br>남들에게 휘둘리지 마 <br>그 비트도 내 몸에 딱 맞아 <br>예약을 다 끝냈으니까 <br>I Like That I Like That <br>오늘 밤도 난 Fly 예 <br>I Like That I Like That <br>늦바람 탐 My Body <br>더 뭐가 날 또 미치게 할까 <br>Right 엄마 난 걱정 마 <br>I Feel This <br>뮤직과 이비자 갈 거야 <br>Everyday I Just Wanna Be With You <br>Everytime I Thinking About With You <br>Oh Oh Yeah Yeah <br>Oh Take Me To The Party Tonight <br>Attention Baby Avenue You <br>Attention Baby Avenue You <br>Everyday I Just Wanna Be With You <br>Everytime I Thinking About With You <br>Oh Oh Yeah Yeah <br>Oh Take Me To The Party Tonight <br>뛰어 <br>Attention Baby Avenue You <br>Attention Baby Avenue You <br>]]></content><category term="박수홍" label="박수홍"/><category term="Clubber (Feat. 오정현, 김지수)" label="Clubber (Feat. 오정현, 김지수)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Indiginis/A_Love_Lost_Feat_Hannah/</id><title>Indiginis - A Love Lost (Feat. Hannah) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:49:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:49:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Indiginis/A_Love_Lost_Feat_Hannah/" title="Indiginis - A Love Lost (Feat. Hannah) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lately I've been thinkin' 'bout how you used to hold me <br>My mind keeps goin' 'round and 'round, oh could you still miss me <br>Is there any chance you'd still take me back <br>'Cause without you I've forgotten how to breath <br><br>You were, you were my steady ground <br>I got stuck, stuck in the heavy crowd <br>All there's left is a storm cloud <br>A love lost, love lost <br>I need you now <br><br>I need you now <br>I need you now <br><br>It took me a while to understand that you were the one <br>The kind of man who loved me through the good, the bad <br>I know I crossed the line, I went off track <br>Is there any chance you'd still take me back <br>'Cause without you it's all pitch black <br><br>You were, you were my steady ground <br>I got stuck, stuck in the heavy crowd <br>All there's left is a storm cloud <br>A love lost, love lost <br>I need you now <br><br>You were, you were my steady ground <br>I got stuck, stuck in the heavy crowd <br>All there's left is a storm cloud <br>A love lost, love lost <br>I need you now <br><br>I send you my love <br>I give you my heart <br>Will you come back to me <br>Let's go back to the start <br><br>I need you now <br>I need you now <br><br>You were, you were my steady ground <br>I got stuck, stuck in the heavy crowd <br>All there's left is a storm cloud <br>A love lost, love lost <br>I need you now <br>I need you now <br>I need you now <br>Ooh, a love lost, love lost <br>I need you now]]></content><category term="Indiginis" label="Indiginis"/><category term="A Love Lost (Feat. Hannah)" label="A Love Lost (Feat. Hannah)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/외로움_증폭_장치/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 외로움 증폭 장치 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:50:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:50:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%99%B8%EB%A1%9C%EC%9B%80_%EC%A6%9D%ED%8F%AD_%EC%9E%A5%EC%B9%98/" title="발라드 공장 - 외로움 증폭 장치 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 미쳤죠 <br>내가 또 왜 날 이렇게 <br>모든 게 다 한심하게 <br>우 살다니 <br>뭐가 그렇게 <br>내가 또 왜 어린 건지 <br>모든 게 다 어려운 건지 <br>우 쉽지가 않네요 <br><br>시계바늘 위로 올라가 초침으로 심장을 찔러서 <br>톱니바퀴 안으로 들어가 태엽으로 시간을 돌리는 <br>시계바늘 위로 올라가 초침으로 심장을 찔러서 <br>톱니바퀴 안으로 들어가 태엽으로 시간을 돌리는 나 <br><br>내가 미웠죠 <br>내가 또 무뎌져 가네 <br>모든 게 무너져 가네 <br>우 살다니 <br>모두 그렇게 <br>내가 또 왜 못했는지 <br>모든 게 왜 떠나는지 <br>우 쉽지가 않네요 <br><br>시계바늘 위로 올라가 초침으로 심장을 찔러서 <br>톱니바퀴 안으로 들어가 태엽으로 시간을 돌리는 <br>시계바늘 위로 올라가 초침으로 심장을 찔러서 <br>톱니바퀴 안으로 들어가 <br>시간을 돌리는 나]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="외로움 증폭 장치" label="외로움 증폭 장치"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/칵테일_사랑/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 칵테일 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:50:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:50:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%B9%B5%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%BC_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="발라드 공장 - 칵테일 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마음 울쩍한날엔 거리를 걸어보고 향기로운 칵테일에 취해도 보고 <br>한편의 시가 있는 전시회장도 가고 밤새도록 그리움에 편지 쓰고파 <br><br>모짜르트 피아노 협주곡 21번 그 음악을 내 귓가에 속삭여주며 <br>아침 햇살 눈부심에 나를 깨워 줄 그런 연인이 내게 있으면 <br>나는 아직 순수함을 느끼고 싶어 어느작은 우체국앞 계단에 앉아 <br>후리지아 꽃향기를 내게 안겨 줄 그런 연인을 만나 봤으면 <br><br>마음 울쩍한날엔 거리를 걸어보고 향기로운 칵테일에 취해도 보고 <br>한편의 시가 있는 전시회장도 가고 밤새도록 그리움에 편지 쓰고파 <br><br>모짜르트 피아노 협주곡 21번 그 음악을 내 귓가에 속삭여주며 <br>아침 햇살 눈부시게 나를 깨워 줄 그런 연인이 내게 있으면 <br>나는 아직 순수함을 느끼고 싶어 어느작은 우체국앞 계단에 앉아 <br>후리지아 꽃향기를 내게 안겨 줄 그런 연인을 만나 봤으면 <br><br>마음 울쩍한날엔 거리를 걸어보고 향기로운 칵테일에 취해도 보고 <br>한편의 시가 있는 전시회장도 가고 밤새도록 그리움에 편지 쓰고파 <br><br>창밖에는 우울한 비가 내리고 있어 내마음도 그 비따라 우울해지네 <br>누가 내게 눈부신 사랑을 가져 줄까 이세상은 나로 인해 아름다운데 <br><br>마음 울쩍한날엔 거리를 걸어보고 향기로운 칵테일에 취해도 보고 <br>한편의 시가 있는 전시회장도 가고 밤새도록 그리움에 편지 쓰고파]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="칵테일 사랑" label="칵테일 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/사랑을_할꺼야/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 사랑을 할꺼야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:50:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:50:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%84_%ED%95%A0%EA%BA%BC%EC%95%BC/" title="발라드 공장 - 사랑을 할꺼야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이젠 나도 널 잊겠어 너무 힘이 들잖아 <br>원하는 대로 해줄순 있지만 난 더 이상 해줄께 없어 <br><br>그런 나를 욕하지마 후회할 지도 몰라 <br>철없는 생각 시간이 흐르면 그땐 이미 늦은 걸 <br><br>모든 것을 주는 그런 사랑을 해봐 <br>받으려고만 하는 그런 사랑 말고 <br>너도 알고 있잖아 끝이 없는걸 <br>서로 참아야만 하는 걸 <br><br>사랑을 할꺼야 사랑을 할 거야 아무도 모르게 너만을 위하여 <br>나를 지켜봐줘 나를 지켜봐줘 아무도 모르는 사랑을 <br><br>모든 것을 주는 그런 사랑을 해봐 <br>받으려고만 하는 그런 사랑 말고 <br>너도 알고 있잖아 끝이 없는걸 <br>서로 참아야만 하는 걸 <br><br>사랑을 할꺼야 사랑을 할 거야 아무도 모르게 너만을 위하여 <br>나를 지켜봐줘 나를 지켜봐줘 아무도 모르는 사랑을 워~ <br><br>사랑을 할꺼야 사랑을 할 거야 <br>아무도 모르게 너만을 위하여 <br>나를 지켜봐줘 나를 지켜봐줘 <br>아무도 모르는 사랑을]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="사랑을 할꺼야" label="사랑을 할꺼야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/사랑해도_될까요/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 사랑해도 될까요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:50:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:50:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4%EB%8F%84_%EB%90%A0%EA%B9%8C%EC%9A%94/" title="발라드 공장 - 사랑해도 될까요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[문이 열리네요 그대가 들어오죠 <br>첫 눈에 난 내 사람인걸 알았죠 <br>내 앞에 다가와 고갤 숙이며 비친 얼굴 <br>정말 눈이 부시게 아름답죠 <br><br>웬일인지 낯설지가 않아요 <br>설레고 있죠 내 맘을 모두 가져간 그대 <br><br>조심스럽게 얘기할래요 용기내 볼래요 <br>나 오늘부터 그대를 사랑해도 될까요 <br><br>처음인걸요 분명한 느낌 놓치고 싶지 않죠 <br>사랑이 오려나봐요 그대에겐 늘 좋은것만 줄께요 <br><br>웬일인지 낯설지가 않아요 <br>설레고 있죠 내 맘을 모두 가져간 그대 <br><br>참 많은 이별 참 많은 눈물 잘 견뎌냈기에 <br>좀 늦었지만 그대를 만나게 됐나봐요 <br><br>지금 내 앞에 앉은 사람을 사랑해도 될까요 <br>두근거리는 맘으로 그대에게 고백할께요 <br><br>조심스럽게 얘기할래요 용기 내볼래요 <br>나 오늘부터 그대를 사랑해도 될까요 <br><br>처음인걸요 이 느낌 놓치고 싶지 않죠 <br>사랑이 오려나봐요 그대에겐 늘 좋은것만 줄께요 <br><br>내가 그대를 사랑해도 될까요]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="사랑해도 될까요" label="사랑해도 될까요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/그대안의_블루/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 그대안의 블루 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:50:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:50:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EC%95%88%EC%9D%98_%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8/" title="발라드 공장 - 그대안의 블루 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 난 눈을 감아요 빛과 그대 모습 사라져 <br>이제 어둠이 밀려오네 <br>저 파란 어둠 속에서 그대 왜 잠들어가나 <br>세상은 아직 그대 곁에 있는데 <br><br>사랑은 아니지만 우리의 만남 <br>어둠은 사라지네 오~~ <br>시간은 빛으로 물들어 또 다시 흐르네 <br>내 눈빛 속 그대 <br><br>난 난 꿈을 꾸어요 그대와의 시간은 멈춰지고 <br>이제 어둠이 밀려오네 <br>빛 바랜 사랑 속에서 그대 왜 잠들려하나 <br>시간은 오~ 아직 그대 곁에 있는데 <br><br>사랑은 아니지만 우리의 만남 <br>어둠은 사라지네 오~ <br>시간은 빛으로 물들어 또 다시 흐르네 <br>그대 눈빛 속에 나 <br>내 눈~빛 속 그대]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="그대안의 블루" label="그대안의 블루"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/순정/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 순정 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:50:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:50:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%88%9C%EC%A0%95/" title="발라드 공장 - 순정 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's clear night How Y' all fell tonight <br>Alright let's get it on wit some new wave trance <br>if you're ready to groove let me hear you say <br>yeah~ One Two Three Go! <br><br>워 워 워~~~ <br>나를 포기했어 너만 사랑했어 그것만으로도 부족했었나 <br>바보 같은 내게 내게 이럴 수 있어 <br>영원히 함께 있자고 죽어도 같이 죽자고 <br>눈물로써 맹세했는데 다 필요 없어 <br><br>너의 행복 찾아 나를 떠난다면 이제 와서 나는 어떡하라고 <br>다시 생각해봐 내게 이러면 안돼 <br>너 없인 살 수가없어 제발 날 도와 달라고 <br>애원하며 붙잡고싶어 <br><br>워 워 워~~~ <br>어느날 갑자기 슬픈 내게로 다가와 <br>사랑만 주고서 멀리 떠나가 버린 너 <br><br>get down and find yo cutie jump around and <br>shake yo booty <br>이해 못해 너의 그런 의미 why me 진정 나를 사랑했니 <br>heart breakin, love rackin 너에게 모든 걸 맡긴, now <br>you packin <br>왜 착한 나를 자꾸 울려, don't wanna let's you go! <br><br>사랑하면 뭐해 정은 줘서 뭐해 순정 바쳐 고작 눈물뿐인데 <br>사랑한게 죄야 너를 원망 않겠어 <br>나 떠나 행복하기를 간절히 기도할께요 <br>단 내 사랑은 잊지 말아줘 <br><br>워 워 워~~~ <br>어느날 갑자기 슬픈 내게로 다가와 <br>사랑만 주고서 멀리 떠나가 버린 너]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="순정" label="순정"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/사랑의_대화/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 사랑의 대화 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:50:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:50:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%98_%EB%8C%80%ED%99%94/" title="발라드 공장 - 사랑의 대화 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 그대를 사랑해 그대 곁에 있고 싶어요 <br>나도 그대가 좋아 이 세상 모두가 변한다 해도 <br>난 그대만 생각할래요 <br><br>그대 반짝이는 두눈을 보면 내마음 나도 모르게 포근해 <br>그대 미소짓는 얼굴을 보면 내맘도 흐뭇해 그대여 아아 <br><br>사랑하는 나의 님이여(사랑하는 나의 님이여) <br>하늘처럼 소중한 그대여(그대여) <br>내인생의 불을 밝혀주신 님이여 <br>그대 내곁에만 있어 준다면 <br>아무도 부럽지 않아요 <br><br>내 맘 알고 있는지 그대마음 알고 싶어요 <br>그대 사랑한다면 아무런애기도 필요친 안아 <br>난 그대를 정말 사랑해 <br><br>그대 반짝이는 두눈을 보면 내마음 나도 모르게 포근해 <br>그대 미소짓는 얼굴을 보면 내맘도 흐뭇해 그대여 아아 <br><br>사랑하는 나의 님이여(사랑하는 나의 님이여) <br>하늘처럼 소중한 그대여(그대여) <br>내인생의 불을 밝혀 주신 님이여 <br>그댄 내 곁에만 있어준다면 <br>아무도 부럽지 않아요 <br><br>사랑하는 나의 님이여(사랑하는 나의 님이여) <br>하늘처럼 소중한 그대여(그대여) <br>내 인생의 불을 밝혀 주신 님이여 <br>그대 내곁에만 있어준다면 <br>아무도 부럽지 않아요 <br>그대여]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="사랑의 대화" label="사랑의 대화"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/이_어둠의_이_슬픔/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 이 어둠의 이 슬픔 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:50:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:50:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%9D%B4_%EC%96%B4%EB%91%A0%EC%9D%98_%EC%9D%B4_%EC%8A%AC%ED%94%94/" title="발라드 공장 - 이 어둠의 이 슬픔 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꺼지는 듯 흔들리는 도시의 가로등 <br>가슴에 흐르는 너나의 슬픔이 <br>한조각 슬픈 노래소리로 <br>어둠에 흩어져가네 <br>허공을 가득메운 눈물같은 네온등 <br>이슬에 흐려지는 그대의 눈빛이 <br>한조각 어두운 바람소리로 <br>한없이 깊어 만가네 <br><br>돌아선 그대 다시한번 말을 해주오 <br>오직 나만을 사랑했다고 <br>떠나는 그대 다시한번 고백해주오 <br>나 그대만을 사랑했다고 <br>불빛에 머문 젖은 나의 눈빛 <br>허공속에 뿌려버리고 <br>가슴을 태운 이 어둠의 상심 <br>허무한 사연이어라 <br><br>어두워진 방안에 누워 창밖을 봐요 <br>바람결에 사라지는 그대의 그 뒷모습 <br>우-우-우 <br>사랑 이별 슬픔은 한없이 흘러만가네 <br><br>돌아선 그대 다시한번 말을 해주오 <br>오직 나만을 사랑했다고 <br>떠나는 그대 다시한번 고백해주오 <br>나 그대만을 사랑했다고 <br>불빛에 머문 젖은 나의 눈빛 <br>허공속에 뿌려버리고 <br>가슴을 태운 이 어둠의 상심 <br>허무한 사연이어라]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="이 어둠의 이 슬픔" label="이 어둠의 이 슬픔"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/바다에_누워/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 바다에 누워 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:50:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:50:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%A4%EC%97%90_%EB%88%84%EC%9B%8C/" title="발라드 공장 - 바다에 누워 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다 하나의 모습으로 태어나 바다에 누워 해저문 노을을 바라다본다 <br>설익은 햇살에 젖은 파도는 눈물인듯 씻기워 간다 <br><br>일만의 눈부심이 가라앉고 밀물의 움직임 속에 <br>뭇별도 제각기 누워 잠잔다 마음은 물결처럼 흘러만 간다 <br><br>저 바다에 누워 외로운 물새 될까 <br>물살의 깊은 속을 항구는 알까 <br>저 바다에 누워 외로운 물새 될까 <br>딥디리딥딥 디비디비딥 <br><br>딥딥딥디리 딥딥딥디리 딥딥디리 딥딥디립디 <br>딥딥딥디리 딥딥딥디리 딥딥디리 딥딥디립디 <br><br>다 하나의 모습으로 태어나 바다에 누워 해저문 노을을 바라다본다 <br>설익은 햇살에 젖은 파도는 눈물인듯 씻기워 간다 <br><br>일만의 눈부심이 가라앉고 밀물의 움직임 속에 <br>뭇별도 제각기 누워 잠잔다 마음은 물결처럼 흘러만 간다 <br><br>저 바다에 누워 외로운 물새 될까 <br>물살의 깊은 속을 항구는 알까 <br>저 바다에 누워 외로운 물새 될까 <br>딥디리딥딥 디비디비딥 <br><br>딥딥딥디리 딥딥딥디리 딥딥디리 딥딥디립디 <br>딥딥딥디리 딥딥딥디리 딥딥디리 딥딥디립디]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="바다에 누워" label="바다에 누워"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/이별이야기/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 이별이야기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:50:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:50:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC%EA%B8%B0/" title="발라드 공장 - 이별이야기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이렇게 우린 헤어져야 하는 걸 서로가 말은 못하고 <br>마지막 찻잔 속에 서로의 향기가 되어 <br>진한 추억을 남기고파 <br><br>우리는 서로 눈물 흘리지 마요 서로가 말은 같아도 <br>후회는 않을 거야 하지만 그대 모습은 <br>나의 마음을 아프게 해 <br><br>그대 내게 말로는 못하고 <br>탁자 위에 물로 쓰신 마지막 그 한마디 <br>서러워 이렇게 눈물만 <br>그대여 이젠 안녕 <br><br>우리는 서로 눈물 흘리지 마요 <br>서로가 말은 같아도 <br>후회는 않을 거야 하지만 그대 모습은 <br>나의 마음을 아프게 해 <br><br>그대 내게 말로는 못하고 <br>탁자 위에 물로 쓰신 마지막 그 한마디 <br>서러워 이렇게 눈물만 <br>그대여 이젠 안녕 <br><br>그대여 이젠 안녕]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="이별이야기" label="이별이야기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/준비없는_이별/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 준비없는 이별 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:50:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:50:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%A4%80%EB%B9%84%EC%97%86%EB%8A%94_%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84/" title="발라드 공장 - 준비없는 이별 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지난시간 내곁에서 머물러 행복했던 시간들이 <br>고맙다고 다시 또 살게되도 당신을 만나겠다고 <br>아 그말해야 할텐데 떠나는 그대라도 <br>편하게 보내줘야 할텐데 <br><br>눈을 감아 지워질수 있다면 잠이들면 그만인데 <br>보고플땐 어떻해야 하는지 오는 밤이 두려워져 <br>아 그댈 보낼 오늘이 수월할 수 있도록 <br>미운기억을 주지 그랬어 <br><br>하루만 오늘더 하루만 준비할 수 있도록 시간을 내게 줘 <br>안돼 지금은 이대로 떠나는 널 그냥 볼수는 없어 <br>차라리 나 (차라리 나) 기다리라 말을 해 <br><br>아무것도 미안해 하지마 아무것도 걱정하지 말고 <br>나는 괜찮아 그래도 사는 동안 함께 나눈 추억이 있잖아 <br>다행이야 감사할께 <br><br>아 그댈 보낼 오늘이 수월할 수 있도록 <br>미운기억을 주지 그랬어 <br><br>하루만 오늘더 하루만 준비할 수 있도록 시간을 내게 줘 <br>안돼 지금은 이대로 떠나는 널 그냥 볼수는 없어 <br>차라리 나 (차라리 나) 기다리라 말을 해 <br><br>영원토록 바라볼 수 있도록]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="준비없는 이별" label="준비없는 이별"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lynyrd_Skynyrd/Sweet_Home_Alabama_Live___Hamburg_1974/</id><title>Lynyrd Skynyrd - Sweet Home Alabama (Live / Hamburg 1974) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:51:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:51:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lynyrd_Skynyrd/Sweet_Home_Alabama_Live___Hamburg_1974/" title="Lynyrd Skynyrd - Sweet Home Alabama (Live / Hamburg 1974) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Big wheels keep on turning <br>Carry me home to see my kin <br>Singing songs about the Southland <br>I miss Alabamy once again <br>And I think its a sin, yes <br><br>Well I heard mister Young sing about her <br>Well, I heard ole Neil put her down <br>Well, I hope Neil Young will remember <br>A Southern man don't need him around anyhow <br><br>Sweet home Alabama <br>Where the skies are so blue <br>Sweet Home Alabama <br>Lord, I'm coming home to you <br><br>In Birmingham they love the gov' nor boo, boo, boo <br>Now we all did what we could do <br>Now Watergate does not bother me <br>Does your conscience bother you <br>Tell the truth <br><br>Sweet home Alabama <br>Where the skies are so blue <br>Sweet Home Alabama <br>Lord, I'm coming home to you <br>Here I come Alabama <br><br>Now Muscle Shoals has got the Swampers <br>And they've been known to pick a song or two <br>Lord they get me off so much <br>They pick me up when I'm feeling blue <br>Now how about you <br><br>Sweet home Alabama <br>Where the skies are so blue <br>Sweet Home Alabama <br>Lord, I'm coming home to you <br><br>Sweet home Alabama <br>Oh sweet home baby <br>Where the skies are so blue <br>And the guv'nor's true <br>Sweet Home Alabama <br>Lordy <br>Lord, I'm coming home to you <br>Yea, yea Montgomery's got the answer]]></content><category term="Lynyrd Skynyrd" label="Lynyrd Skynyrd"/><category term="Sweet Home Alabama (Live / Hamburg 1974)" label="Sweet Home Alabama (Live / Hamburg 1974)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lynyrd_Skynyrd/Free_Bird_Live___Hamburg_1974/</id><title>Lynyrd Skynyrd - Free Bird (Live / Hamburg 1974) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:51:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:51:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lynyrd_Skynyrd/Free_Bird_Live___Hamburg_1974/" title="Lynyrd Skynyrd - Free Bird (Live / Hamburg 1974) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If I leave here tomorrow <br>Would you still remember me <br>For I must be traveling on now <br>'Cause there's too many places I've got to see <br><br>But if I stayed here with you, girl <br>Things just couldn't be the same <br>'Cause I'm as free as a bird now <br>And this bird you can not change, oh, oh, oh, oh <br>And this bird you can not change <br>And this bird you can not change <br>Lord knows I can't change <br><br>Bye, bye, baby, it's been a sweet love, yeah <br>Though this feeling I can't change <br>But please don't take it so badly <br>'Cause Lord knows I'm to blame <br><br>But if I stayed here with you, girl <br>Things just couldn't be the same <br>'Cause I'm as free as a bird now <br>And this bird you'll never change, oh, oh, oh, oh <br>And this bird you cannot change <br>And this bird you cannot change <br>Lord knows, I can't change <br>Lord, help me, I can't change <br><br>Lord, I can't change <br>Won't you fly high, free bird, yeah]]></content><category term="Lynyrd Skynyrd" label="Lynyrd Skynyrd"/><category term="Free Bird (Live / Hamburg 1974)" label="Free Bird (Live / Hamburg 1974)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lynyrd_Skynyrd/Workin_For_MCA_Live___Hamburg_1974/</id><title>Lynyrd Skynyrd - Workin` For MCA (Live / Hamburg 1974) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:51:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:51:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lynyrd_Skynyrd/Workin_For_MCA_Live___Hamburg_1974/" title="Lynyrd Skynyrd - Workin` For MCA (Live / Hamburg 1974) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Seven years of hard luck, comin' down on me <br>From the Florida border, yea up to Nashville Tennessee <br>I worked in every joint you can name, mister every honkytonk <br>Along come Mr Yankee Slicker, sayin' maybe you're what I want <br><br>Want you to sign your contract <br>Want you to sign today <br>Gonna give you lots of money <br>Workin' For MCA <br><br>9000 dollars, that's all we could win <br>But we smiled at the Yankee Slicker with a big ol' Southern grin <br>They're gonna take me out to California gonna make me a superstar <br>Just pay me all of my money and mister maybe you won't get a scar <br><br>Want you to sign your contract <br>Want you to sign today <br>Gonna give you lots of money <br>Workin' For MCA <br><br>Suckers took my money since I was seventeen <br>If it ain't no pencil pusher, it got to be a honkytonk queen <br>But I'll sign my contract baby, and I wan't you people to know <br>That every penny that I make, I'm gonna see where my money goes <br><br>Want you to sign your contract <br>Want you to sign today <br>Gonna give you lots of money <br>Workin' For MCA]]></content><category term="Lynyrd Skynyrd" label="Lynyrd Skynyrd"/><category term="Workin` For MCA (Live / Hamburg 1974)" label="Workin` For MCA (Live / Hamburg 1974)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lynyrd_Skynyrd/Free_Bird_Live/</id><title>Lynyrd Skynyrd - Free Bird (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T15:51:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T15:51:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lynyrd_Skynyrd/Free_Bird_Live/" title="Lynyrd Skynyrd - Free Bird (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If I leave here tomorrow <br>Would you still remember me <br>For I must be traveling on now <br>'Cause there's too many places I've got to see <br><br>But if I stayed here with you, girl <br>Things just couldn't be the same <br>'Cause I'm as free as a bird now <br>And this bird you can not change, oh, oh, oh, oh <br>And this bird you can not change <br>And this bird you can not change <br>Lord knows I can't change <br><br>Bye, bye, baby, it's been a sweet love, yeah <br>Though this feeling I can't change <br>But please don't take it so badly <br>'Cause Lord knows I'm to blame <br><br>But if I stayed here with you, girl <br>Things just couldn't be the same <br>'Cause I'm as free as a bird now <br>And this bird you'll never change, oh, oh, oh, oh <br>And this bird you cannot change <br>And this bird you cannot change <br>Lord knows, I can't change <br>Lord, help me, I can't change <br><br>Lord, I can't change <br>Won't you fly high, free bird, yeah]]></content><category term="Lynyrd Skynyrd" label="Lynyrd Skynyrd"/><category term="Free Bird (Live)" label="Free Bird (Live)"/></entry></feed>