<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:17:00+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/타투_TATU/Oh_Pls_Girl_기다려줘/</id><title>타투 (TATU) - Oh Pls Girl (기다려줘) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:34:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:34:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%80%ED%88%AC_TATU/Oh_Pls_Girl_%EA%B8%B0%EB%8B%A4%EB%A0%A4%EC%A4%98/" title="타투 (TATU) - Oh Pls Girl (기다려줘) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh pls girl <br>기다려줘 벌 때까지 데이트비용 <br>Oh pls girl <br>기다려줘 금방 갈게 꽃다발 들고 <br>아직은 허리띠를 못 풀어 <br>네 앞에서 바지를 벗을 때 까지 <br>지금은 허리띠를 못 풀어 <br>네 앞에서 바지를 벗을 때 까지 <br>그녀가 회사 갈 때 난 집에서 <br>고양이 사료를 퍼 주고 있어 <br>&amp; SOFA에 누워 With I-PHONE <br>FACEBOOK Bitch <br>들에게 관심을 주고 <br>컴퓨터를 켜고 스피커를 틀지 <br>대다수는 모를 <br>이 기분을 적어내지 <br>몇몇들은 매일 <br>이 느낌을 내게 묻지 <br>말해봤자 니들이 <br>알겠냐라며 웃고 말지 <br>후회한적은 없어 <br>다만 너가 만약 <br>내 삶의 일부가 <br>된 다면 아마 <br>날 미워할지도 몰라 <br>가진게 꿈과 <br>자존심뿐이라 <br>Maybe sometime You'll realize <br>주고받는 문자 사이마다 <br>혹시 내가 <br>드러나진 않을까 라면서 <br>가슴 조려 <br>이쯤 되면 사귀자란 <br>말을 꺼내도 될 것 같은데 <br>밥먹자는 말로 돌려 <br>you know <br>Oh pls girl <br>기다려줘 벌 때 까지 데이트비용 <br>Oh pls girl <br>기다려줘 금방 갈게 꽃다발 들고 <br>아직은 허리띠를 못 풀어 <br>네 앞에서 바지를 벗을 때 까지 <br>지금은 허리띠를 못 풀어 <br>네 앞에서 바지를 벗을 때 까지 <br>너가 퇴근 하는 시간 맞춰 <br>전화를 걸어 <br>일이 많은 가봐 <br>오늘은 받지를 않아 <br>사랑은 타이밍이라고 <br>배웠는데 왜 하필 <br>벌써 나타났니 <br>생각하며 문자를남겨 <br>넌 내가 아는 사람들 <br>중에 유일해 <br>만나본 여자들과도 <br>감히 비교 못해 <br>Uh 얼굴만큼 <br>마음도 예쁘네 <br>때론 진지한 가치관에 <br>넋을 놓고 바라 볼때 <br>I Feel Love <br>난 거짓말을 못해 <br>이 노래 전부 <br>너에 대한 말인데 <br>난 못해 말을 <br>만약 이 노래를 <br>너가 듣고 나에게 <br>누구냐 물어본다면 <br>그때는 말할 수 있게 <br>물어봐줘 내 삶에 <br>관한 얘기를 <br>할 수 있을 것 같아 <br>유일히 너에게는 <br>조만간 밥 한번 먹자 <br>아 그때는 영화를 <br>물론 action 말고 <br>아름다운 로맨스를 uh <br>Oh pls girl <br>기다려줘 벌 때 까지 데이트비용 <br>Oh pls girl <br>기다려줘 금방 갈게 꽃다발 들고 <br>아직은 허리띠를 못 풀어 <br>네 앞에서 바지를 벗을 때 까지 <br>지금은 허리띠를 못 풀어 <br>네 앞에서 바지를 벗을 때 까지 <br>I wanna love like a Fairy tale <br>그래 그렇게 남들은 <br>꿈 깨라 말하지만 <br>만약 내 옆에 너가 있다면 <br>gonna be alright okay <br>난 오늘도 너의 <br>배경이 되기를 꿈꿔 <br>아침이 오면 그날 <br>위해 펜을 잡아 <br>조금만 더 그 자리에서 <br>날 기다려줘 <br>ma baby <br>Oh pls girl <br>기다려줘 벌 때 까지 데이트비용 <br>Oh pls girl <br>기다려줘 금방 갈게 꽃다발 들고 <br>아직은 허리띠를 못 풀어 <br>네 앞에서 바지를 벗을 때 까지 <br>지금은 허리띠를 못 풀어 <br>네 앞에서 바지를 벗을 때 까지 <br>Oh pls girl <br>기다려줘 벌 때 까지 데이트비용 <br>Oh pls girl <br>기다려줘 금방 갈게 꽃다발 들고 <br>아직은 허리띠를 못 풀어 <br>네 앞에서 바지를 벗을 때 까지 <br>지금은 허리띠를 못 풀어 <br>네 앞에서 바지를 벗을 때 까지 <br>Yeah <br>]]></content><category term="타투 (TATU)" label="타투 (TATU)"/><category term="Oh Pls Girl (기다려줘)" label="Oh Pls Girl (기다려줘)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ging_Ging_깅_깅/10000Km/</id><title>Ging, Ging (깅, 깅) - 10,000Km - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:34:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:34:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ging_Ging_%EA%B9%85_%EA%B9%85/10000Km/" title="Ging, Ging (깅, 깅) - 10,000Km - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무도 없는 언덕길 신발끈을 매 <br>초록빛 가득한 길을 달려 내려가 <br>더 이상 파랄 수 없을 만큼 <br>새파란 하늘 <br>아래로 내려갈수록 가까워지네 <br>내 눈 앞에 흰 구름 <br>거리는 10000km <br>내게 말을 해줘 <br>손에 닿을 때까지 달려갈 거야 <br>내게 다가와줘 <br>너의 진짜 모습으로 <br>내게 말을 해줘 <br>손에 닿을 때까지 달려갈 거야 <br>내게 다가와줘 <br>너의 진짜 모습으로 <br>아무도 없는 우주에 다시 힘을 내 <br>검은 빛 가득한 길을 달려 올라가 <br>저곳에 지구보다 <br>푸른 나의 정거장 <br>점점 더 가까워짐을 알 수가 있어 <br>내 눈 앞에 푸른 별 <br>거리는 10000km <br>내게 말을 해줘 <br>손에 닿을 때까지 달려갈 거야 <br>내게 다가와줘 <br>너의 진짜 모습으로 <br>내게 말을 해줘 <br>손에 닿을 때까지 달려갈 거야 <br>내게 다가와줘 <br>너의 진짜 모습으로 <br>내게 말을 해줘 내게 다가와줘 <br>내게 다가와줘 <br>내게 말을 해줘 <br>손에 닿을 때까지 달려갈 거야 <br>내게 다가와줘 <br>너의 진짜 모습으로 <br>내게 말을 해줘 <br>손에 닿을 때까지 달려갈 거야 <br>내게 다가와줘 <br>너의 진짜 모습으로 <br>]]></content><category term="Ging, Ging (깅, 깅)" label="Ging, Ging (깅, 깅)"/><category term="10,000Km" label="10,000Km"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ging_Ging_깅_깅/구름구름/</id><title>Ging, Ging (깅, 깅) - 구름구름 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:34:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:34:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ging_Ging_%EA%B9%85_%EA%B9%85/%EA%B5%AC%EB%A6%84%EA%B5%AC%EB%A6%84/" title="Ging, Ging (깅, 깅) - 구름구름 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[구름 속을 날아가네 <br>구름 속을 날아가네 <br>구름 속을 날아 하얀 여름을 지나 <br>다시 구름 속 <br>구름 속을 날아 하얀 여름을 지나 <br>다시 구름 속을 <br>뚜렷한 구름을 만나게 되면 <br>계단을 걷듯이 올라가네 <br>구름 름 름 타고 날아가 슈슈슈 <br>블루 루 베리 스무디 <br>마신다 쭉쭉쭉 <br>예쁜 꽃만 따다 바구니에 담아 <br>구름 위로 올려줘 <br>분홍빛 산란한 쿠션이 부숭숭 <br>뽀송거리는 쿠션같은 <br>솜털구름 위에 누워 뒹굴 <br>바쁘게 지나가는 비행기 <br>손을 들어 모두 hello <br>여긴 내 1st class seat <br>마카다미아는 됐어 솜사탕 <br>all day &amp; night <br>아무 일 없이 살고파요 <br>저물어가는 하늘에 누워 <br>가까워진 어둠을 맞아 <br>찰싹거리며 부서지는 <br>물결을 따라 고양이 운다 <br>눈부시게 더운 여름을 지나 <br>숨어 구름 속에 <br>언제나 빨간날처럼 <br>구름 속을 날아가네 <br>구름 속을 날아가네 <br>]]></content><category term="Ging, Ging (깅, 깅)" label="Ging, Ging (깅, 깅)"/><category term="구름구름" label="구름구름"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stormzex/별_바라기_Feat_V_Flower/</id><title>Stormzex - 별 바라기 (Feat. V Flower) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:34:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:34:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stormzex/%EB%B3%84_%EB%B0%94%EB%9D%BC%EA%B8%B0_Feat_V_Flower/" title="Stormzex - 별 바라기 (Feat. V Flower) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[고마워요 날 사랑해줘서 <br>사랑받지 못한 꽃의 <br>매마른 마음은 <br>꺾을 수 밖에 없어 <br>가시투성이인 <br>나의 바램은 <br>이런게 아니었는데 <br>어디에 있나요 <br>시들어가는 나 <br>당신이란 빛을 <br>빼앗아가버리는 <br>기나긴 밤이 두려워서 <br>고마워요 날 사랑해줘서 <br>고마워요 날 사랑해줘서 <br>사랑받지 못한 꽃은 <br>꺾여진 몸을 <br>일으켜 보려했어 <br>홀로 남겨진 <br>꽃의 바램은 <br>이런게 아니었는데 <br>어디에 있나요 <br>시들어가는 나 <br>당신이란 힘을 <br>잃어버린 나는 <br>영원한 잠이 두려워서 <br>고마워요 날 사랑해줘서 <br>고마워요 날 사랑해줘서 <br>고마워요 날 사랑해줘서 <br>고마워요 날 사랑해줘서 <br>고마워요 날 사랑해줘서 <br>고마워요 날 사랑해줘서 <br>]]></content><category term="Stormzex" label="Stormzex"/><category term="별 바라기 (Feat. V Flower)" label="별 바라기 (Feat. V Flower)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아이씨사이다/No_More_No_More_노모-_노모-/</id><title>아이씨사이다 - No More No More (노모- 노모-) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:36:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:36:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%94%A8%EC%82%AC%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%A4/No_More_No_More_%EB%85%B8%EB%AA%A8-_%EB%85%B8%EB%AA%A8-/" title="아이씨사이다 - No More No More (노모- 노모-) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보고 싶은 건 전부 가려져 있어 <br>누군가 걸어놓는 모자이크 <br>나는 노모를 더 원해요 <br>똑같은 말들 갈 곳 잃은 슬로건 <br>어차피 그들만의 전쟁 <br>오빤 내 맘 뭣도 몰라요 <br>별 달린 사람들 <br>그 손에 놀아나는 법 <br>이제 더러워서 나 <br>조금 개겨볼까 해 <br>지금 난 무쏘의 뿔 <br>박아 버려 미친 세상 <br>부셔 버려 I'm Public enemy <br>박아 버려 I want no more shit <br>토할 것 같은 쓰레기들의 콜라보 <br>비겁한 뉴스들은 고작 <br>엄한 연예인들 벗겨요 <br>별 달린 사람들 <br>욕심에 감춰지는 법 <br>이젠 지겨워서 나 <br>조금 개겨볼까 해 <br>달리자 무쏘의 뿔 <br>박아 버려 미친 세상 <br>부셔 버려 I'm Public enemy <br>Already get ready for shit <br>박아 버려 I want no more shit <br>노모가 좋아요 <br>다 볼 수 있는 투명함 <br>깨끗한 화질로 워어 <br>감춰진 세상은 전부 다 부셔버려 <br>번지수 틀린 고통 없게 <br>박아 버려 미친 세상 <br>부셔 버려 I'm Public enemy <br>Already get ready for shit <br>박아 버려 I want no more shit <br>박아 버려 미친 세상 <br>부셔 버려 I'm Public enemy <br>Already get ready for shit <br>박아 버려 I want no more shit <br>]]></content><category term="아이씨사이다" label="아이씨사이다"/><category term="No More No More (노모- 노모-)" label="No More No More (노모- 노모-)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/03소1059/슈가보이_Feat_김옐_Of_사려니숲/</id><title>03소1059 - 슈가보이 (Feat. 김옐 Of 사려니숲) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:39:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:39:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/03%EC%86%8C1059/%EC%8A%88%EA%B0%80%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EC%98%90_Of_%EC%82%AC%EB%A0%A4%EB%8B%88%EC%88%B2/" title="03소1059 - 슈가보이 (Feat. 김옐 Of 사려니숲) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[두근두근대는 내 맘 <br>들키고 싶진 않아 <br>언제까지 아닌 척 <br>내 맘 속이며 지내야해 <br>모르는 척 다가가 <br>볼에 깜짝 키스 해버릴까 <br>날 보며 웃어주는 니 미소에 <br>하늘 걷는 기분이야 <br>너도 알고 있잖아 <br>그만 먼저 말해줘 <br>your Love <br>두근대는 내 맘 아니 <br>떨리는 심장이 <br>더 기다리면 울지몰라 <br>하루 종일 니 생각에 <br>빨개진 내 두 볼이 <br>더 기다리면 나도 몰라 <br>너는 나만의 슈가보이 <br>긴가민가한 우리 사이 <br>오늘로 끝나는거니 <br>멀리서 다가오는 니 모습에 <br>수줍은 맘 어떡하죠 <br>너도 알고 있잖아 <br>그만 먼저 말해줘 <br>your Love <br>두근대는 내 맘 아니 <br>떨리는 심장이 <br>더 기다리면 울지몰라 <br>하루 종일 니 생각에 <br>빨개진 내 두 볼이 <br>더 기다리면 나도 몰라 <br>두근대는 내 맘 아니 <br>떨리는 심장이 <br>더 기다리면 울지몰라 <br>하루 종일 니 생각에 <br>빨개진 내 두 볼이 <br>더 기다리면 나도 몰라 <br>너는 나만의 슈가보이 <br>]]></content><category term="03소1059" label="03소1059"/><category term="슈가보이 (Feat. 김옐 Of 사려니숲)" label="슈가보이 (Feat. 김옐 Of 사려니숲)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하이런/세월아_세월아/</id><title>하이런 - 세월아 세월아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:42:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:42:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%EB%9F%B0/%EC%84%B8%EC%9B%94%EC%95%84_%EC%84%B8%EC%9B%94%EC%95%84/" title="하이런 - 세월아 세월아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람따라 구름따라 흘러온 청춘아 <br>네가 가니 사랑도 가잖니 <br>바쁜 걸음 놓자는데 뭐 그리 급하더냐 <br>사랑하고 정 나누며 쉬어가 보자 <br>세월아 세월아 가지를 마라 <br>사랑도 미움도 같이 가잔다 <br>사랑 사랑 사랑 사랑 내 사랑이야 <br>사랑 한번 꽃 피워보자 <br><br>세월따라 님따라 흘러온 청춘아 <br>네가 가니 사랑도 가잖니 <br>바쁜 걸음 놓자는데 뭐 그리 급하더냐 <br>한잔 술에 시름 잊고 쉬어가 보자 <br>세월아 세월아 가지를 마라 <br>사랑도 미움도 같이 가잔다 <br>사랑 사랑 사랑 사랑 내 사랑이야 <br>사랑 한번 꽃 피워보자]]></content><category term="하이런" label="하이런"/><category term="세월아 세월아" label="세월아 세월아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김민철/Piston_2016_Remastering/</id><title>김민철 - Piston (2016 Remastering) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:43:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:43:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%AF%BC%EC%B2%A0/Piston_2016_Remastering/" title="김민철 - Piston (2016 Remastering) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지루했던 일상의 <br>칼을 들었어 <br>The Passion The Freedom <br>바둥되며 살던 나 <br>진리를 알았지만 <br>너무나 진부해 <br>A Nation A People <br>모두 하나를 위해 <br>달려 가잖아 <br>You are not alone <br>Forever with us <br>그래 <br>내가 이제는 정말 <br>집으로 돌아가네 <br>시들었던 내 일상의 <br>물을 주셨어 <br>목마르지 않고 <br>시들지 않는 물을 <br>진리를 알았지만 <br>지금 어디로 <br>A Religion The Trust <br>모두 하나를 향해 <br>달려 가잖아 <br>You are not alone <br>Together with you <br>그래 <br>내가 이제는 정말 <br>쉼터로 돌아가네 <br>We are the brotherhood <br>너의 지난 죄를 <br>인정한다면 <br>I wish you <br>그렇게 할수만 있다면 <br>용서 할께요 <br>우리가 함께 누리며 <br>만들어 가요 <br>You are not alone <br>Together with us <br>그래 <br>내가 이제는 너를 <br>집으로 초대할게 <br>좋은집과 좋은차와 <br>좋은여자를 <br>원해도 내가 <br>채울순 없지만 yeah <br>You You are not alone <br>Together with you <br>이제는 <br>내가 널위해 이끌어 줄께 <br>편하게 와서 쉬고 가 <br>]]></content><category term="김민철" label="김민철"/><category term="Piston (2016 Remastering)" label="Piston (2016 Remastering)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김민철/Tell_Me_Why_2016_Remastering/</id><title>김민철 - Tell Me Why (2016 Remastering) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:43:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:43:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%AF%BC%EC%B2%A0/Tell_Me_Why_2016_Remastering/" title="김민철 - Tell Me Why (2016 Remastering) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[부족했었니 <br>말해주지 그랬어 <br>조금 더 널 <br>아끼고 위하는 <br>내가 되었을텐데 <br>힘들었었니 <br>말해주지 그랬어 <br>지난 내 모습을 버리고 <br>너를 따랐을텐데 <br>우연히 그 거리에서 <br>너를 보게되었던 <br>나 아닌 사람과 <br>행복한 그모습 <br>적어도 넌 나에게 <br>말해줘야 했었고 <br>뜨거웠던 가슴이 <br>식어가고 있다고 <br>미련한 바보처럼 <br>너를 보내야 하나 <br>Never say goodbye <br>부족했었니 <br>말해주지 그랬어 <br>가진 것이 많지 않아서 <br>넌 이해못했는지 <br>힘들었었니 <br>말해주지 그랬어 <br>서로 다른삶을 <br>살아온 날이 <br>길었던거야 <br>아니길 바랬던 <br>너의 마지막 변명은 <br>내곁에 있어도 <br>항상 외로웠다고 <br>적어도 넌 나에게 <br>말해줘야 했었고 <br>뜨거웠던 가슴이 <br>식어가고 있다고 <br>미련한 바보처럼 <br>너를 보내야 하나 <br>Never say goodbye <br>적어도 넌 나에게 <br>말해줘야 했었고 <br>뜨거웠던 가슴이 <br>식어가고 있다고 <br>미련한 바보처럼 <br>너를 보내야 하나 <br>Never say goodbye <br>Never say goodbye <br>]]></content><category term="김민철" label="김민철"/><category term="Tell Me Why (2016 Remastering)" label="Tell Me Why (2016 Remastering)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리노_Lino/사랑일까/</id><title>리노 (Lino) - 사랑일까 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:43:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:43:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%85%B8_Lino/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%BC%EA%B9%8C/" title="리노 (Lino) - 사랑일까 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 만나러 가는 길이면 <br>이렇게 설레는데 <br>거울 앞에서 내 모습 <br>몇 번을 본지 몰라 <br>너와 함께하는 일은 <br>언제나 내 가슴을 <br>콩닥콩닥 두근대게 만들어 <br>이런 게 사랑일까 <br>사랑을 하면 하면 할수록 <br>넌 내 안에 점점 더 커져 <br>이런저런 생각을 또 하다가 <br>아깐 이 말을 깜빡했어 <br>정말 세상에서 내게 <br>가장 소중한 사람은 너야 <br>갑자기 네가 보고 싶어 <br>모두 잠든 시간 꿈속에도 <br>너 있는 곳 우주라 해도 <br>내가 너를 볼 수 있다면 <br>날아서 날아서 갈 거야 <br>널 바래다주는 길이면 <br>헤어지기 싫어서 <br>네 손잡고 동네를 <br>몇 바퀴나 돈지 몰라 <br>혼자 집에 가는 길은 <br>언제나 외롭지만 <br>네 목소릴 들으면 다 괜찮아 <br>이런 게 사랑일까 <br>사랑을 하면 하면 할수록 <br>넌 내 안에 점점 더 커져 <br>이런저런 생각을 또 하다가 <br>아 스르륵 잠기는 두 눈을 <br>꼭 참아보려다가 결국 <br>잠들기 전 눈을 감아도 또 <br>갑자기 네가 보고 싶어 <br>모두 잠든 시간 꿈속에도 <br>너 있는 곳 우주라 해도 <br>내가 너를 볼 수 있다면 <br>날아서 날아서 갈 거야 <br>너를 안아주고 싶어 <br>심장소리가 들리게 <br>작은 떨림마저 느끼도록 <br>이런 소중한 느낌 <br>오래오래 간직하고파 <br>너와 나 um <br>갑자기 네가 보고 싶어 <br>모두 잠든 시간 꿈속에도 <br>너 있는 곳 우주라 해도 <br>내가 너를 볼 수 있다면 <br>날아서 날아서 갈 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="리노 (Lino)" label="리노 (Lino)"/><category term="사랑일까" label="사랑일까"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리노_Lino/걸어가요/</id><title>리노 (Lino) - 걸어가요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:43:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:43:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%85%B8_Lino/%EA%B1%B8%EC%96%B4%EA%B0%80%EC%9A%94/" title="리노 (Lino) - 걸어가요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[두 손에 잡힐 듯 <br>잡히지 않아 <br>꼭 쥐면 쥘수록 <br>흘러내리고 말아 <br>마음은 더 급해지고 <br>상처는 깊어만 가 <br>난 세상에 이렇게 <br>홀로 남겨진 것 같아 <br>내일은 또 다를 거라 <br>두 손을 꼭 쥐어봐도 <br>달라지는 건 <br>또 나를 떠나가는 사람 <br>많은 사람들은 <br>자꾸만 이렇게 말해 <br>늦을지도 몰라 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어가야 해 <br>난 말야 뛰고 싶지 않아요 <br>조금은 늦더라도 <br>빨리 뛰어가다 <br>저기 예쁜 꽃마저도 <br>볼 수 없다면 <br>그냥 걸어 걸어 걸어 <br>난 걸어갈래요 <br>다들 빠르게 뛰어서 <br>나만 멈춘 듯 보일까 <br>아님 정말 뛰는 법을 <br>잊어버린 걸까 <br>누가 말해주지 않아 <br>잠깐 쉬어도 괜찮아 <br>걱정하지 마 <br>넌 더 멀리 날아갈 수 있어 <br>많은 사람들은 <br>자꾸만 이렇게 말해 <br>늦을지도 몰라 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어가야 해 <br>난 말야 뛰고 싶지 않아요 <br>조금은 늦더라도 <br>빨리 뛰어가다 <br>저기 예쁜 꽃마저도 <br>볼 수 없다면 <br>그냥 걸어 걸어 걸어 <br>난 걸어갈래요 <br>숨이 차올라서 <br>더는 뛸 수가 없고 <br>그대로 주저앉아 <br>울고 싶으면 멈춰도 돼요 <br>걱정 말아요 <br>늦지 않을 거예요 <br>뒤를 돌아보면 <br>내가 곁에 있을 테니 <br>함께 걸어가요 <br>난 말야 뛰고 싶지 않아요 <br>조금은 늦더라도 <br>빨리 뛰어가다 <br>저기 예쁜 꽃마저도 <br>볼 수 없다면 <br>그냥 걸어 걸어 걸어 <br>난 걸어갈래요 <br>]]></content><category term="리노 (Lino)" label="리노 (Lino)"/><category term="걸어가요" label="걸어가요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TOLB/내일의_역/</id><title>TO.LB - 내일의 역 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:44:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:44:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TOLB/%EB%82%B4%EC%9D%BC%EC%9D%98_%EC%97%AD/" title="TO.LB - 내일의 역 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[열 가지 작은 바램과 <br>이겨내야 하는 천 가지 도전들 <br>그 박탈당한 꿈을 주워 끌어안고 <br>난 또다시 바람 속을 걸어 <br>하루의 끝에서 열차를 타고 <br>어디든지 갈 때면 <br>내 지나간 꿈 눈부신 기억 <br>창밖을 스쳐 가네 <br>내 얼굴을 가진 꼬마 아이가 <br>마주 앉아 웃으며 <br>수고했다고 어깰 피라고 <br>나를 위로하지만 <br>너에게 조금 더 든든한 <br>어른이고 싶어도 <br>나 하나 지키기 힘들어 <br>또다시 고개만 떨구네 <br>열 가지 작은 바램과 <br>이겨내야 하는 천 가지 도전들 <br>한 걸음걸음 날아오는 작은 돌에 <br>난 또다시 두 무릎을 꿇어 <br>사 분 후 미래를 말해주는 <br>전철의 안냇말 <br>내일의 나는 일 년 후 나는 <br>왜 얘기해 주지 않는지 <br>세상은 또 한 번 멈추어 <br>우리들에게 묻는다 <br>불안한 안갯속 경고음 <br>저 멀리 메아리쳐 울리네 <br>열 가지 작은 바램과 <br>이겨내야 하는 천 가지 도전들 <br>한 걸음걸음 날아오는 작은 돌에 <br>무릎을 꿇었지만 이게 끝은 아냐 <br>언젠가 다시 또 너와 <br>마주하는 나를 미리 그려보며 <br>그 박탈당한 꿈을 주워 끌어안고 <br>난 또다시 바람 속을 걸어 <br>내일로 <br>내일로 내일로 내일로 <br>열 가지 작은 바램과 <br>이겨내야 하는 천 가지 도전들 <br>한 걸음걸음 날아오는 작은 돌에 <br>무릎을 꿇었지만 이게 끝은 아냐 <br>수많은 기적들이 날 기다릴 테니 <br>저 이상을 손에 넣는 그 날까지 <br>그 박탈당한 꿈을 주워 끌어안고 <br>난 또다시 바람 속을 걸어 <br>열 가지 작은 바램과 <br>이겨내야 하는 천 가지 도전들 <br>그 박탈당한 꿈을 주워 끌어안고 <br>난 또다시 <br>]]></content><category term="TO.LB" label="TO.LB"/><category term="내일의 역" label="내일의 역"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TOLB/여기_내가_있을_테니/</id><title>TO.LB - 여기 내가 있을 테니 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:44:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:44:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TOLB/%EC%97%AC%EA%B8%B0_%EB%82%B4%EA%B0%80_%EC%9E%88%EC%9D%84_%ED%85%8C%EB%8B%88/" title="TO.LB - 여기 내가 있을 테니 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꿈에서 보았던 <br>그 어린아이가 <br>놀이터에서 그네 타며 <br>즐거워하네 <br>더 높은 세상을 <br>보고 싶은 너는 <br>지칠 때까지 발을 구르지 <br>하지만 아무리 <br>높이 뛰려 해도 <br>혼자 힘으론 맘처럼 <br>잘되지 않아 <br>혼자서 오르기에 <br>힘이 든다면 <br>내가 너를 받쳐줄 테니 <br>이렇게 하나 둘 셋 <br>하늘 높이 날아봐 <br>눈을 들어 앞을 봐 <br>해가 저물고 있어 <br>저 해 따라 저물어 <br>내려오겠지만 <br>다시 오를 거야 <br>걱정은 하지 마 <br>여기 내가 있을 테니 <br>해가 떨어져 <br>빛이 사라지고 <br>친구 같았던 <br>모랫바닥은 <br>싸늘해져도 <br>네 뒤에서 <br>내가 손잡아줄 테니 <br>내가 항상 여기 있을 테니 <br>이렇게 하나 둘 셋 <br>하늘 높이 날아봐 <br>눈을 들어 나를 봐 <br>내가 여기에 있어 <br>저 별 따라 여행을 <br>떠나보는 거야 <br>또 해가 뜰 거야 <br>걱정은 하지 마 <br>여기 내가 있을 테니 <br>이렇게 하나 둘 셋 <br>하늘 높이 날아봐 <br>눈을 들어 앞을 봐 <br>해가 떠오르는 걸 <br>저 해 따라 <br>다시 떠나보는 거야 <br>자 가보자 걱정은 하지 마 <br>여기 내가 있을 테니 <br>]]></content><category term="TO.LB" label="TO.LB"/><category term="여기 내가 있을 테니" label="여기 내가 있을 테니"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/데니스프로젝트/놔_Feat_노훈/</id><title>데니스프로젝트 - 놔 (Feat. 노훈) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:45:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:45:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%B0%EB%8B%88%EC%8A%A4%ED%94%84%EB%A1%9C%EC%A0%9D%ED%8A%B8/%EB%86%94_Feat_%EB%85%B8%ED%9B%88/" title="데니스프로젝트 - 놔 (Feat. 노훈) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[좀더 보여주겠지 <br>그래 네 눈에 맺힌 <br>거짓 눈물이겠지 <br>결관 꺼져줘 That's it <br>투명한 사랑은 <br>이제 어울리지 않아 <br>따뜻한 공기보단 <br>이제 차가울 테니까 <br>좀더 보여주겠지 <br>그래 네 눈에 맺힌 <br>거짓 눈물이겠지 <br>결관 꺼져줘 That's it <br>투명한 사랑은 <br>이제 어울리지 않아 <br>따뜻한 공기보단 <br>이제 차가울 테니까 <br>어긋난 사랑의 태도 <br>이건 분명치 않대도 <br>너무 예의 없어 너는 <br>우리의 관계에서도 <br>하고싶었겠지 날 <br>떠나려는 이별의 말도 <br>근데 착한사람 <br>인척하는 난 네가 싫어 <br>놔 그래 놔 제발 <br>놔주길 바랬어 <br>꿈이 라도 좋으니 <br>떠나길 바랬어 <br>사랑은 무슨 얼어죽을 <br>장난하지 말아 <br>근데 이제보니 <br>너란여잘 알것만 같아 <br>내가 전화 했을때도 <br>받지 않는 통화 중 <br>그보다 중요했겠지 <br>그 놈과의 연애 중 <br>친구가 봤다는 <br>말을 믿지 않았는데 <br>마지막 까지도 <br>더럽게 확인시켜 줬네 <br>친구 만나러 간다길래 <br>그런 줄 알았어 <br>네 생일인데 넌 <br>놔주길 바랬어 <br>그 친구가 그 친구였다니 <br>뭐 거짓말은 아닌데 <br>인스타에서 봤던 <br>그때 그놈이었던 거네 <br>좀더 보여주겠지 <br>그래 네 눈에 맺힌 <br>거짓 눈물이겠지 <br>결관 꺼져줘 That's it <br>투명한 사랑은 <br>이제 어울리지 않아 <br>따뜻한 공기보단 <br>이제 차가울 테니까 <br>좀더 보여주겠지 <br>그래 네 눈에 맺힌 <br>거짓 눈물이겠지 <br>결관 꺼져줘 That's it <br>투명한 사랑은 <br>이제 어울리지 않아 <br>따뜻한 공기보단 <br>이제 차가울 테니까 <br>좀더 보여주겠지 <br>그래 네 눈에 맺힌 <br>거짓 눈물이겠지 <br>결관 꺼져줘 That's it <br>투명한 사랑은 <br>이제 어울리지 않아 <br>따뜻한 공기보단 <br>이제 차가울 테니까 <br>좀더 보여주겠지 <br>그래 네 눈에 맺힌 <br>거짓 눈물이겠지 <br>결관 꺼져줘 That's it <br>투명한 사랑은 <br>이제 어울리지 않아 <br>따뜻한 공기보단 <br>이제 차가울 테니까 <br>지금 생각해보니 <br>그때는 귀여운줄 알았던 <br>네 행동들은 <br>다 싸가지가 바가지 <br>예의 없던 행동들은 <br>다 시작인 거고 <br>그렇게 시원하게 <br>내 통수를 친거지 <br>잤지 안잤어 <br>유치했던 질문만 <br>도데체 뭘 바라고 <br>너에게 마지막 <br>더러운꼴을 보여 <br>그냥 이제 제발 놔줘 <br>저기서 기다리고 있는 <br>저놈에게 좀 꺼져 <br>다 지우고 싶어 <br>너와의 기억을 전부 <br>위로는 필요 없어 <br>내가 사랑이란 것을 <br>두번 다시 할 수 <br>있을지 모르겠지만 <br>너같은 여자는 <br>이제 잘 알것만 같아 <br>비가와 근데 술 마셔서 <br>잠들것 같아 <br>눈물을 보이는 <br>어리석은 놈은 아냐 <br>이제는 모른척 하고 <br>그냥 좀 지나가줘 <br>다음에 만나도 <br>밥 먹을 일은 없어 <br>좀더 보여주겠지 <br>그래 네 눈에 맺힌 <br>거짓 눈물이겠지 <br>결관 꺼져줘 That's it <br>투명한 사랑은 <br>이제 어울리지 않아 <br>따뜻한 공기보단 <br>이제 차가울 테니까 <br>좀더 보여주겠지 <br>그래 네 눈에 맺힌 <br>거짓 눈물이겠지 <br>결관 꺼져줘 That's it <br>투명한 사랑은 <br>이제 어울리지 않아 <br>따뜻한 공기보단 <br>이제 차가울 테니까 <br>좀더 보여주겠지 <br>그래 네 눈에 맺힌 <br>거짓 눈물이겠지 <br>결관 꺼져줘 That's it <br>투명한 사랑은 <br>이제 어울리지 않아 <br>따뜻한 공기보단 <br>이제 차가울 테니까 <br>좀더 보여주겠지 <br>그래 네 눈에 맺힌 <br>거짓 눈물이겠지 <br>결관 꺼져줘 That's it <br>투명한 사랑은 <br>이제 어울리지 않아 <br>따뜻한 공기보단 <br>이제 차가울 테니까 <br>]]></content><category term="데니스프로젝트" label="데니스프로젝트"/><category term="놔 (Feat. 노훈)" label="놔 (Feat. 노훈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BIG_Shorry/Coke_Gang_Bang_Feat_Mugshot/</id><title>B.I.G Shorry - Coke Gang Bang (Feat. Mugshot) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:48:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:48:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BIG_Shorry/Coke_Gang_Bang_Feat_Mugshot/" title="B.I.G Shorry - Coke Gang Bang (Feat. Mugshot) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You were a got shot <br>We are motherfuckin' COKE GANG <br>I'm gonna gang bang <br>We are motherfuckin' COKE GANG <br>Coke로 난 Gang bang <br>니네 좆같은 목구멍을 난 맴매 <br>목구멍으로 넘어가는 순간 콕 콕 <br>코르가즘이 느껴지는 검은 종족 <br>Coke로 난 Gang bang <br>니네 좆같은 목구멍을 난 맴매 <br>목구멍으로 넘어가는 순간 콕 콕 <br>코르가즘이 느껴지는 검은 종족 <br>뱅뱅 돌지 너의 이성이 상실 <br>이유가 뭐냐하면 너 아까 마신 <br>Coke에 정신이 혼미해진 순간 <br>훅 하고 들어오지 반항은 Give up <br>Coke로 GANG BANG 허나 이건 합법 <br>놀라지마 Coke는 편의점에 팔어 <br>나는 합법적으로 콜라를 해 <br>You got it 합법적으로 콜라를 해 <br>Coke로 GANG BANG 정신은 뱅뱅 <br>머리는 댕댕 DAMM <br>느끼는거 미소가 보여 <br>너도 좋으면서 반항하지 말어 <br>Hold up Hold up 잔이 비었네 <br>목젖이 쉴 생각은 하지를 말어 <br>탄산이 들어옴에 거부하지 말어 <br>포기하고 느껴 Word up Word up <br>Coke로 난 Gang bang <br>니네 좆같은 목구멍을 난 맴매 <br>목구멍으로 넘어가는 순간 콕 콕 <br>코르가즘이 느껴지는 검은 종족 <br>Coke로 난 Gang bang <br>니네 좆같은 목구멍을 난 맴매 <br>목구멍으로 넘어가는 순간 콕 콕 <br>코르가즘이 느껴지는 검은 종족 <br>C C 냉기 챙기고 <br>콜라만큼 차가워 Mr. Cold blood <br>목구멍을 향해 겨누지 <br>45도 기울이고 흘러가는 감촉 <br>마치 4WD Range Rover <br>흔들리지 빨간 이쁜이 Pretty <br>한 번 더 밀어 넣지 <br>Oh God 남은 콜라 어딨어 <br>What the 파란녀석 <br>Ain't nobody gimme Pepsi <br>밥에 우유를 말아먹을 쉐끼 <br>아무거나 입에 들이붓지 <br>네 취향 의심스러워 Pepsi Porno <br>너 변태맞지 huh <br>진짜는 진짜를 알아보지 <br>역시는 역시 C O K E <br>Coke Gang Bang <br>식도로 느껴지는 코르가즘 <br>화끈한 녀석 너의 목구멍을 태워 <br>이건 차가운데 뜨거 <br>Oh 차가운데 뜨거 <br>Coke로 난 Gang bang <br>니네 좆같은 목구멍을 난 맴매 <br>목구멍으로 넘어가는 순간 콕 콕 <br>코르가즘이 느껴지는 검은 종족 <br>Coke로 난 Gang bang <br>니네 좆같은 목구멍을 난 맴매 <br>목구멍으로 넘어가는 순간 콕 콕 <br>코르가즘이 느껴지는 검은 종족 <br>]]></content><category term="B.I.G Shorry" label="B.I.G Shorry"/><category term="Coke Gang Bang (Feat. Mugshot)" label="Coke Gang Bang (Feat. Mugshot)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공영근/그리움_Duet_안량희_유환영/</id><title>공영근 - 그리움 (Duet 안량희, 유환영) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:48:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:48:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%EC%98%81%EA%B7%BC/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9B%80_Duet_%EC%95%88%EB%9F%89%ED%9D%AC_%EC%9C%A0%ED%99%98%EC%98%81/" title="공영근 - 그리움 (Duet 안량희, 유환영) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이제와 용길내 <br>당신께 전화를 걸어보내요 <br>그토록 길고 길었던 <br>시간이 지난후에야 <br>비로서 난 <br>난 그대없이 살수없음을 <br>늦은 지금에서야 <br>나 알게되고 깨달았음을 <br>그때의 내 마음 <br>지금의 내 마음 <br>난 변함없이 <br>너를 그리워하고 있고 <br>너의 눈동자에 맺혔던 눈물 <br>그 눈물의 기억을 <br>이젠 이젠 지우고 싶어 <br>그리워 니가 그리워 <br>미안해 정말 미안해 <br>이젠 너를 <br>슬프게 하지 않을께 <br>길고 긴 시간 지나고 <br>이제야 알게 된 나는 <br>그대와 함께한 <br>시간의 행복을 <br>너와 함께 지나던 <br>이 거리엔 이젠 나혼자 <br>쓸쓸해진 발걸음이 <br>어딘갈 향하고 있고 <br>행복했던 그대의 모습 <br>이젠 사라져 <br>하루하루 눈가엔 <br>눈물이 마르질 않네 <br>그때의 내 마음 <br>지금의 내 마음 <br>난 변함없이 <br>너를 그리워하고 있고 <br>너의 눈동자에 맺혔던 눈물 <br>그 눈물의 기억을 <br>이젠 이젠 지우고 싶어 <br>그리워 니가 그리워 <br>미안해 정말 미안해 <br>이젠 너를 <br>슬프게 하지 않을께 <br>길고 긴 시간 지나고 <br>이제야 알게된 나는 <br>그대와 함께한 <br>시간의 행복을 <br>그대와 함께한 <br>시간의 행복을 <br>]]></content><category term="공영근" label="공영근"/><category term="그리움 (Duet 안량희, 유환영)" label="그리움 (Duet 안량희, 유환영)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공영근/봄나비_Vocal_안량희/</id><title>공영근 - 봄나비 (Vocal 안량희) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:48:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:48:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%EC%98%81%EA%B7%BC/%EB%B4%84%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84_Vocal_%EC%95%88%EB%9F%89%ED%9D%AC/" title="공영근 - 봄나비 (Vocal 안량희) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[산들산들 봄바람 불어오는 <br>이 거리를 거니는데 <br>개나리와 벚꽃향기 가득한 <br>이곳에는 그대와 나 <br>날아다녀 훨훨 날아다녀 <br>봄 언덕 위 바람을 따라 <br>구름위에 반짝이는 저 햇살 <br>그곳으로 날아가네 <br>어제도 오늘도 이 거리 위에서 <br>널 기다리면서 하루를 보내고 <br>설레임 가득한 봄 언덕 위에는 <br>초록빛 새싹이 나를 반기네 <br>라라라라 라라라라라라라 <br>라라 라라라라 라라라 <br>라라라라 라라라라라 라라 <br>라라라라 라라라라 <br>날아다녀 훨훨 날아다녀 <br>봄 언덕 위 바람을 따라 <br>구름위에 반짝이는 저 햇살 <br>그곳으로 날아가네 <br>이렇게 오늘도 이거리 위에서 <br>너와 함께 하루하루를 보내고 <br>봄향기 따뜻한 해앳살 가득한 <br>이곳에는 그대와 나 <br>]]></content><category term="공영근" label="공영근"/><category term="봄나비 (Vocal 안량희)" label="봄나비 (Vocal 안량희)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/모두의MR/읽지않음_Unread_MR/</id><title>모두의MR - 읽지않음 (Unread) (MR) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:52:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:52:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AA%A8%EB%91%90%EC%9D%98MR/%EC%9D%BD%EC%A7%80%EC%95%8A%EC%9D%8C_Unread_MR/" title="모두의MR - 읽지않음 (Unread) (MR) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[안 볼 거 알면서 <br>그냥 나 혼자서 <br>너에게 못했던 <br>수 많은 말들을 이제 와 보내 <br>확인할 거라고 <br>생각한 적 없어 <br>이렇게 안 하면 <br>미안한 맘에 내가 못 견딜까 봐 <br>내 메시지만 종일 <br>기다리던 너에게 <br>정작 나는 그 땐 왜 <br>그 흔한 말 한 번 못했는지 <br>이젠 몇 일을 보내도 <br>울며 애원을 해 봐도 <br>넌 관심 조차 없는데 <br>읽지 않은 사랑한단 말 <br>읽지 않은 보고 싶단 말 <br>읽지 않을 거 알면서도 또 <br>다시 돌아와 달란 말 <br>난 바보처럼 이제 와 <br>혼자 보내고 있어 <br>끝난 사람인 거 다 알면서 너무 <br>바보처럼 <br>그 땐 넌 내 곁에 <br>있던 게 아니라 <br>내 어깨에 있었고 <br>고된 삶은 너무 버거웠어 <br>모자란 나보다 <br>너무나 고귀한 <br>널 위해 사느라 <br>그깟 한 마디 하긴 바빴었어 <br>읽지 않은 사랑한단 말 <br>읽지 않은 보고 싶단 말 <br>읽지 않을 거 알면서도 또 <br>다시 돌아와 달란 말 <br>난 바보처럼 이제 와 <br>혼자 보내고 있어 <br>끝난 사람인 거 다 알면서 너무 <br>시간이 휘몰아쳐 휩쓸려 가는 <br>니 추억을 니 기억을 <br>억지로 안아 붙잡고 있어 <br>이젠 읽었으면 좋겠어 <br>너무 사랑해서 모자랐던 <br>내 맘을 이젠 좀 읽어 줘 <br>읽지 않은 사랑한단 말 <br>읽지 않은 보고 싶단 말 <br>읽지 않을 거 알면서도 또 <br>다시 돌아와 달란 말 <br>난 바보처럼 이제 와 <br>혼자 보내고 있어 <br>끝난 사람인 거 다 알면서 너무 <br>바보처럼]]></content><category term="모두의MR" label="모두의MR"/><category term="읽지않음 (Unread) (MR)" label="읽지않음 (Unread) (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤길/춘천역에서_MR/</id><title>윤길 - 춘천역에서 (MR) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:53:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:53:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EA%B8%B8/%EC%B6%98%EC%B2%9C%EC%97%AD%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C_MR/" title="윤길 - 춘천역에서 (MR) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가랑비 부슬부슬 <br>내리는 춘천역에서 <br>잊고 살던 그 사람 <br>우연히 만날 줄이야 <br>횡단보도 하얀 점선에 <br>할 말을 내려놓고 <br>그날처럼 엇갈린다 <br>서글픈 우리의 사랑 <br>기억도 가물가물 <br>희미한 시간속으로 <br>멀어져간 그 사람 <br>또 다시 만날 줄이야 <br>횡단보도 하얀 점선에 <br>할 말을 내려놓고 <br>그날처럼 엇갈린다 <br>서글픈 우리의 사랑 <br>그날처럼 엇갈린다 <br>서글픈 우리의 사랑]]></content><category term="윤길" label="윤길"/><category term="춘천역에서 (MR)" label="춘천역에서 (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤길/내려놨는데/</id><title>윤길 - 내려놨는데 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:53:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:53:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EA%B8%B8/%EB%82%B4%EB%A0%A4%EB%86%A8%EB%8A%94%EB%8D%B0/" title="윤길 - 내려놨는데 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이만큼 온것도 <br>행복한데 나 <br>왜 눈물이 나나 <br>가슴이 아프지만 <br>내려놨는데 <br>다 내려놨는데 <br>무슨 미련 또 남은 걸까 <br>올가미 같은 세상아 <br>그래도 더 바칠 <br>눈물이 있다면 <br>눈물이 남아 있다면 <br>그것도 나의 것 <br>그것도 나의것 <br>기꺼이 받아주리라 <br>이만큼 온것도 <br>행복한데 나 <br>왜 눈물이 나나 <br>곡절도 많았지만 <br>내려놨는데 <br>다 내려놨는데 <br>무슨 미련 또 남은 걸까 <br>올가미 같은 세상아 <br>그래도 못버린 <br>이별이 있다면 <br>이별이 남아 있다면 <br>이제는 가거라 <br>이제는 가거라 <br>다시는 오지 말아라 <br>다시는 오지 말아라 <br>]]></content><category term="윤길" label="윤길"/><category term="내려놨는데" label="내려놨는데"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤길/장대비/</id><title>윤길 - 장대비 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:53:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:53:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EA%B8%B8/%EC%9E%A5%EB%8C%80%EB%B9%84/" title="윤길 - 장대비 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[당신 마음을 <br>내게서 돌린 <br>그 남자가 누군지 <br>물어보고 싶지만 <br>한순간에 밀려난 <br>내가 너무 초라해 <br>말없이 돌아섭니다 <br>멀어지는 옛사랑의 <br>그림자를 밟으며 <br>원점으로 가는 이 순간 <br>울지마 울지말자 <br>울지말자 했는데 <br>소나기 소나기 <br>장대같이 쏟아지는 비 <br>당신 마음을 <br>내게서 돌린 <br>그 남자가 누군지 <br>물어보고 싶지만 <br>한순간에 밀려난 <br>내가 너무 초라해 <br>말없이 돌아섭니다 <br>멀어지는 옛사랑의 <br>그림자를 밟으며 <br>원점으로 가는 이 순간 <br>울지마 울지말자 <br>울지말자 했는데 <br>소나기 소나기 <br>장대같이 쏟아지는 비 <br>]]></content><category term="윤길" label="윤길"/><category term="장대비" label="장대비"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤길/스쳐간_사랑/</id><title>윤길 - 스쳐간 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:53:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:53:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EA%B8%B8/%EC%8A%A4%EC%B3%90%EA%B0%84_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="윤길 - 스쳐간 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밤 늦은 카페 혼자 남아서 <br>이별의 잔을 마셔 <br>버렸다 불빛에 날아와 <br>흐르는 음악에 미련을 <br>던져버렸다 <br>사랑은 다 그런 거라고 <br>내 자신을 위로하면서 <br>어차피 이렇게 <br>끝내야만 했다고 쓴웃음에 <br>너를 묻었다 잊어달라는 <br>말도 더는 내게 <br>하지마 다시 사랑에 <br>빠져 울지 않으리 <br>저 창밖에 바람처럼 <br>스쳐간 사랑이라고 <br>말할테야 <br>밤 늦은 카페 혼자 남아서 <br>고독이 싫어 취해버렸다 <br>지울 수 없었던 수 많은 <br>얼굴이 술잔에 피어올랐다 <br>사랑은 다 그런 거라고 <br>내 자신을 위로하면서 <br>어차피 이렇게 <br>끝내야만 했다고 쓴웃음에 <br>너를 묻었다 잊어달라는 <br>말도 더는 내게 <br>하지마 다시 사랑에 <br>빠져 울지 않으리 <br>저 창밖에 바람처럼 <br>스쳐간 사랑이라고 <br>말할테야 <br>저 창밖에 바람처럼 <br>스쳐간 사랑이라고 <br>말할테야 <br>]]></content><category term="윤길" label="윤길"/><category term="스쳐간 사랑" label="스쳐간 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤길/텅빈_한나절/</id><title>윤길 - 텅빈 한나절 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:53:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:53:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EA%B8%B8/%ED%85%85%EB%B9%88_%ED%95%9C%EB%82%98%EC%A0%88/" title="윤길 - 텅빈 한나절 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[풀잎도 마른 외로운 언덕에 <br>늙은 말 한필 <br>쓸쓸히 서 있고 <br>계절 잃은 낙엽이 <br>뒹구는 저 길로 <br>지나는 한줄기 <br>무심한 바람만 <br>우체부도 오지않는 <br>이 텅빈 한나절 <br>상심한 그리움이 <br>덧없이 쌓여도 지친 맘 <br>기다림은 가고 또 가는데 <br>누가 있어 이 깊은 <br>침묵을 깨고 <br>내이름을 불러줄까 불러줄까 <br>우 <br>우체부도 오지않는 <br>이 텅빈 한나절 <br>상심한 그리움이 <br>덧없이 쌓여도 지친 맘 <br>기다림은 가고 또 가는데 <br>누가 있어 이 깊은 <br>침묵을 깨고 <br>내이름을 불러줄까 불러줄까 <br>우 <br>]]></content><category term="윤길" label="윤길"/><category term="텅빈 한나절" label="텅빈 한나절"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤길/도찐_개찐/</id><title>윤길 - 도찐 개찐 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:54:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:54:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EA%B8%B8/%EB%8F%84%EC%B0%90_%EA%B0%9C%EC%B0%90/" title="윤길 - 도찐 개찐 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[일등한다고 누가 상 주나 <br>꼴등한다고 누가 벌 주나 <br>박수 받으면 더 좋겠지만 <br>야유는 싫어 싫어 <br>그래서 열심히 하는거야 <br>눈물이 아니면 웃음이지 뭐 <br>사는건 또찐개찐 <br>긴 세월 많은 사연 <br>얼키고 설킨 세상 <br>나 잘났다고 떵떵거려도 <br>인생은 또찐개찐 <br>왜 안되냐고 징징거려도 <br>인생은 또찐개찐 <br>일등한다고 누가 상 주나 <br>꼴등한다고 누가 벌 주나 <br>박수 받으면 더 좋겠지만 <br>야유는 싫어 싫어 <br>그래서 열심히 하는거야 <br>눈물이 아니면 웃음이지 뭐 <br>사는건 또찐개찐 <br>긴 세월 많은 사연 <br>얼키고 설킨 세상 <br>나 잘났다고 떵떵거려도 <br>인생은 또찐개찐 <br>왜 안되냐고 징징거려도 <br>인생은 또찐개찐 <br>눈물이 아니면 웃음이지 뭐 <br>사는건 또찐개찐 <br>긴 세월 많은 사연 <br>얼키고 설킨 세상 <br>나 잘났다고 떵떵거려도 <br>인생은 또찐개찐 <br>왜 안되냐고 징징거려도 <br>인생은 또찐개찐 <br>인생은 또찐개찐 <br>]]></content><category term="윤길" label="윤길"/><category term="도찐 개찐" label="도찐 개찐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤길/홍천강_400리/</id><title>윤길 - 홍천강 400리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:54:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:54:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EA%B8%B8/%ED%99%8D%EC%B2%9C%EA%B0%95_400%EB%A6%AC/" title="윤길 - 홍천강 400리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[태극강변 허리를 안고 <br>흘러가는 사백리 홍천강아 <br>구비구비 사연을 엮어 <br>서리서리 눈물이더냐 <br>바람에 옥수수 잎이 <br>소곤대는 고개를 넘어 <br>금학산 팔봉산에 <br>안기어 산다 <br>홍천강아 홍천강아 <br>너는 안다 나의 마음을 <br>잣나무숲 골짜기 지나 <br>인삼향기 바람에 날아가면 <br>송아지도 엄마를 찾는 <br>산골마을 정다웁구나 <br>황금물결 논길을 따라 <br>풍악소리 걸어놓고 <br>가리산 공작산에 <br>노을이 진다 <br>홍천강아 홍천강아 <br>너는 안다 나의 청춘을 <br>]]></content><category term="윤길" label="윤길"/><category term="홍천강 400리" label="홍천강 400리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤길/가로등/</id><title>윤길 - 가로등 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:54:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:54:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EA%B8%B8/%EA%B0%80%EB%A1%9C%EB%93%B1/" title="윤길 - 가로등 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가지를 떠난 잎새는 <br>바람이 데려가지만 <br>이대로 우리 떠나면 <br>어디서 다시 만나리 <br>추억같은 가로등만 <br>홀로 선 골목 저 끝에 <br>술 취한 사내 하나 <br>나처럼 밤이 늦었네 <br>어쩌다 길을 잃었나 <br>나처럼 길을 잃었나 <br>이제는 믿지 말아요 <br>사랑의 약속 같은 건 <br>추억같은 가로등만 <br>홀로 선 골목 저 끝에 <br>술 취한 사내 하나 <br>나처럼 밤이 늦었네 <br>어쩌다 길을 잃었나 <br>나처럼 길을 잃었나 <br>이제는 믿지 말아요 <br>사랑의 약속 같은 건 <br>이제는 믿지 말아요 <br>사랑의 약속 같은 건 <br>]]></content><category term="윤길" label="윤길"/><category term="가로등" label="가로등"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤길/미운_사람아/</id><title>윤길 - 미운 사람아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:54:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:54:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EA%B8%B8/%EB%AF%B8%EC%9A%B4_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C%EC%95%84/" title="윤길 - 미운 사람아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가슴에 오래 살았죠 <br>나 실컷 괴롭혔었죠 <br>끝끝내 못 버린 미련 때문에 <br>보내지 못한 사람아 <br>이제는 놓으리라 놓으리라 <br>이 못난 사랑의 끈을 <br>아 아 미운 사람아 <br>눈물이 가슴 젖는 밤 <br>늦었지만 행복을 빈다 <br>내가슴에 오래 살았죠 <br>나 실컷 괴롭혔었죠 <br>끝끝내 못 버린 미련 때문에 <br>보내지 못한 사람아 <br>이제는 놓으리라 놓으리라 <br>이 못난 사랑의 끈을 <br>아 아 미운 사람아 <br>눈물이 가슴 젖는 밤 <br>늦었지만 행복을 빈다 <br>늦었지만 너를 보낸다 <br>]]></content><category term="윤길" label="윤길"/><category term="미운 사람아" label="미운 사람아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤길/춘천역에서/</id><title>윤길 - 춘천역에서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:54:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:54:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EA%B8%B8/%EC%B6%98%EC%B2%9C%EC%97%AD%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C/" title="윤길 - 춘천역에서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가랑비 부슬부슬 <br>내리는 춘천역에서 <br>잊고 살던 그 사람 <br>우연히 만날 줄이야 <br>횡단보도 하얀 점선에 <br>할 말을 내려놓고 <br>그날처럼 엇갈린다 <br>서글픈 우리의 사랑 <br>기억도 가물가물 <br>희미한 시간속으로 <br>멀어져간 그 사람 <br>또 다시 만날 줄이야 <br>횡단보도 하얀 점선에 <br>할 말을 내려놓고 <br>그날처럼 엇갈린다 <br>서글픈 우리의 사랑 <br>그날처럼 엇갈린다 <br>서글픈 우리의 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="윤길" label="윤길"/><category term="춘천역에서" label="춘천역에서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤길/밤기차에/</id><title>윤길 - 밤기차에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:54:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:54:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EA%B8%B8/%EB%B0%A4%EA%B8%B0%EC%B0%A8%EC%97%90/" title="윤길 - 밤기차에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[못잊어 운다고 돌아오나요 <br>사랑은 감옥이더라 <br>겁없이 사랑한 내 모든 것이 <br>원점으로 돌아간 지금 <br>가물가물 멀어지는 <br>밤기차에 몸을 싣고 <br>잊을 때까지 잊을 때까지 <br>어디든지 가고 싶어라 <br>밤기차에 몸을 싣고 <br>이제와 뉘우친다고 돌아오나요 <br>사랑은 감옥이더라 <br>철없이 내던진 내 젊은 날이 <br>눈물자욱 얼룩진 지금 <br>가물가물 멀어지는 <br>밤기차에 몸을 싣고 <br>잊을 때까지 잊을 때까지 <br>어디든지 가고 싶어라 <br>밤기차에 몸을 싣고 <br>밤기차에 몸을 싣고 <br>]]></content><category term="윤길" label="윤길"/><category term="밤기차에" label="밤기차에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/용빈/보라카이/</id><title>용빈 - 보라카이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:54:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:54:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9A%A9%EB%B9%88/%EB%B3%B4%EB%9D%BC%EC%B9%B4%EC%9D%B4/" title="용빈 - 보라카이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈부신 하늘의 태양과 <br>기분 좋은 시원한 바람과 <br>향기로운 너와 하는 모든 게 <br>설레는 꿈같아 <br>구름 위를 날아가듯이 <br>파도와 하나가 되듯이 <br>따라가 볼래 <br>달콤한 바람에 젖은 너를 <br>보라카이 보라카이 <br>바람에 날리는 잊지 못할 순간을 <br>보라카이 보라카이 <br>별빛에 젖어서 <br>스며드는 향기를 느껴볼래 <br>오랜 세월에 익숙해져 <br>자연스러워진 풍경이 <br>파도소리와 함께 <br>내 마음을 모두 다 적시고 <br>여러 가지 색깔 속에서 <br>아름다운 향기 속에서 <br>찾아가 볼래 <br>내 가슴 속에 스며든 너를 <br>보라카이 보라카이 <br>바람에 날리는 잊지 못할 순간을 <br>보라카이 보라카이 <br>별빛에 젖어서 스며드는 향기를 <br>보라카이 <br>바람에 날리는 잊지 못할 순간을 <br>별빛에 젖어서 <br>스며드는 향기를 느껴볼래 <br>]]></content><category term="용빈" label="용빈"/><category term="보라카이" label="보라카이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/Si_Te_Vas/</id><title>Jose Maria Ruiz - Si Te Vas - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:59:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:59:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/Si_Te_Vas/" title="Jose Maria Ruiz - Si Te Vas - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No hace falta que lo digas <br>y ya me he dado cuenta <br>cual es el problema <br><br>No eres santa y <br>sin respuesta <br>se queda mi vida <br>tengo el alma herida <br><br>Si tu te vas <br>muere el corazon desangrado <br>no pasa el tiempo <br>y estoy desesperado <br><br>Si tu te vas <br>muere el corazon destrozado <br>me quedo solo <br>triste y enamorado <br><br>Y si ya no sientes nada por mi <br>me vengare <br>y te buscare <br><br>Te enamorare <br>como aquel dia <br>en tu balcon <br>pura poesia <br><br>¿Pero tu de que vas <br>no me puedes dejar <br>como un nino llorando <br>yo que tanto te amado <br><br>Si amarte es un pecado <br>que me encierren sin pena <br>esta dulce condena que me mata y me envenena <br><br>Si tu te vas <br>muere el corazon desangrado <br>no pasa el tiempo <br>y estoy desesperado <br><br>Si tu te vas <br>muere el corazon destrozado <br>me quedo solo <br>triste y enamorado <br><br>Y si te vas me muero <br>no puedo conmigo me quema el desespero <br>es perder todo y volver a empezar de cero <br>eso no quiero <br>sabes que espero <br>tenerte a mi lado porque te quiero <br><br>Mami es que parece mentira <br>que no te importe dejarme esta herida <br>y me dejas sufriendo con tu partida <br>pero veremos que el tiempo decida <br><br>Si estas cadenas se rompen <br>voy por ti <br>ya no puedo tenerte <br>junto a mi <br><br>Si no me amas no vuelvas <br>no vuelvas <br>me danaste el corazon <br><br>Terminaste la escena <br>y esta condena <br>se va muriendo <br>se fue tu tiempo <br>con esta cancion <br><br>No hace falta que lo digas <br>y ya me he dado cuenta <br>cual es el problema <br><br>No eres santa y <br>sin respuesta <br>se queda mi vida <br>tengo el alma herida <br><br>Si tu te vas <br>muere el corazon desangrado <br>no pasa el tiempo <br>y estoy desesperado <br><br>Si tu te vas <br>muere el corazon destrozado <br>me quedo solo <br>triste y enamorado]]></content><category term="Jose Maria Ruiz" label="Jose Maria Ruiz"/><category term="Si Te Vas" label="Si Te Vas"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/Buenos_Dias_Princesa/</id><title>Jose Maria Ruiz - Buenos Dias Princesa - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:59:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:59:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/Buenos_Dias_Princesa/" title="Jose Maria Ruiz - Buenos Dias Princesa - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Un dia mas llega primero a la estacion <br>buscara con sus pasos torpes el mismo vagon <br><br>Un dia lleno de nervios mientras cruza la ciudad <br>temblara como 60 anos justo para atras <br><br>Lluvia igual a sol <br>necesita verla un dia mas <br>para verle el corazon <br>su soledad <br><br>Buenos dias princesa <br>le dice de nuevo al llegar <br>quien eres su amor <br>preguntara mirandolo mal <br><br>Se sienta a su lado <br>y otra vez <br>el le entrega una flor <br>y que importa si en realidad <br>ni recuerdas su nombre <br><br>Se quedo igual que un vaso de cristal <br>Ese ayer del que el habla con tanta felicidad <br><br>Su memoria es <br>esa niebla que <br>empana al ventanal <br>que difuminara el cielo un dia mas <br><br>Buenos dias princesa <br>le dice de nuevo al llegar <br>quien eres su amor <br>preguntara mirandolo mal <br><br>Se sienta a su lado <br>y otra vez <br>el le entrega una flor <br>y que importa si en realidad <br><br>No lo ves <br>vuelve a casa <br>en el mismo tren que ayer <br>mirara que infinito es el mar <br><br>Buenos dias princesa <br>le dice de nuevo al llegar <br>quien eres su amor <br>preguntara mirandolo mal <br><br>Se sienta a su lado <br>y otra vez <br>el le entrega una flor <br>y que importa si en realidad <br>ni recuerdas su nombre]]></content><category term="Jose Maria Ruiz" label="Jose Maria Ruiz"/><category term="Buenos Dias Princesa" label="Buenos Dias Princesa"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/Simplemente_Me_Canse/</id><title>Jose Maria Ruiz - Simplemente Me Canse - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:59:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:59:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/Simplemente_Me_Canse/" title="Jose Maria Ruiz - Simplemente Me Canse - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No lo quieres entender <br>yo lo unico que quiero es irme de una vez <br>acabar con este juego <br>prenderle fuego a tus recuerdos <br>para no volverte a ver <br><br>Cuantas veces tuve que escuchar <br>'te prometo que voy a cambiar' <br>tantas que me olvide de mi <br>una noche tras otra mas <br>el silencio es soledad <br><br>Simplemente me canse <br>de tus caricias oxidadas aranandome la piel <br>de cada beso suplicado <br>de tu forma de querer <br>se marchitaron <br>mis mejores primaveras en tus manos <br><br>Simplemente me canse <br>de tus estupidas manias <br>de tus gestos <br>de cada lagrima de gritos y de celos <br>no me preguntes por ello <br><br>Simplemente me canse <br><br>Poco queda que aclarar <br>hoy tengo listo el equipaje <br>ya no hay vuelta atras <br>dejame vivir tranquilo <br>olvidame asi de tu vida <br>no me vuelvas a llamar <br><br>Cuantas veces tuve que escuchar <br>'te prometo que voy a cambiar' <br>tantas que me olvide de mi <br>una noche tras otra mas <br>el silencio es soledad <br><br>Simplemente me canse <br>de tus caricias oxidadas aranandome la piel <br>de cada beso suplicado <br>de tu forma de querer <br>se marchitaron <br>mis mejores primaveras en tus manos <br><br>Simplemente me canse <br>de tus estupidas manias <br>de tus gestos <br>de cada lagrima de gritos y de celos <br>no me preguntes por ello <br><br>Simplemente me canse <br><br>Simplemente me canse <br>de cada lagrima de gritos y de celos <br>no me preguntes por ello <br><br>Simplemente me canse]]></content><category term="Jose Maria Ruiz" label="Jose Maria Ruiz"/><category term="Simplemente Me Canse" label="Simplemente Me Canse"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/Demasiado_Breve/</id><title>Jose Maria Ruiz - Demasiado Breve - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:59:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:59:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/Demasiado_Breve/" title="Jose Maria Ruiz - Demasiado Breve - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tu miras lunas <br>yo el amanecer <br>tu te marchas al verme volver <br><br>Me desangro sabiendo que <br>huyes de mi <br>te columpias en nuestro jardin <br><br>Tu en el papel <br>de reina desdichada <br>tambien las comprendido <br><br>Yo en el papel <br>de principe encantado <br>que suena ser feliz <br><br>Y las alas que se fueron viendo <br><br>Fuimos un cuento demasiado breve <br>que tu olvidaste <br>y yo leo mil veces <br>para vivirlo otra vez <br>sin prisa <br>tacho el dolor <br>mientras tu te despistas <br><br>Fuimos un cuento demasiado breve <br>que se deshace como el agua en nieve <br>una pelicula que <br>se acaba <br>para variar <br>no acaba con beso al final <br><br>Yo pinto lienzos y tu quieres borrar <br>los colores de un bosque de azar <br><br>De nostalgia te vistes <br>en el corazon <br>yo atrapado en mi ciencia ficcion <br><br>Tu en el papel <br>de reina desdichada <br>tambien las comprendido <br><br>Yo en el papel <br>de principe encantado <br>que suena ser feliz <br><br>Y la magia que se va muriendo <br><br>Fuimos un cuento demasiado breve <br>que tu olvidaste <br>y yo leo mil veces <br>para vivirlo otra vez <br>sin prisa <br>tacho el dolor <br>mientras tu te despistas <br><br>Fuimos un cuento demasiado breve <br>que se deshace como el agua en nieve <br>una pelicula que <br>se acaba <br>para variar <br>no acaba con beso al final <br><br>Y busco aquellos suenos que perdimos <br>tu risa que curaba todo el frio <br>tu nombre en el margen de mis libros <br><br>Demasiado breve <br><br>Sin prisa <br><br>Fuimos un cuento demasiado breve <br>que tu olvidaste <br>y yo leo mil veces <br>para vivirlo otra vez <br>sin prisa <br>tacho el dolor <br>mientras tu te despistas <br><br>Fuimos un cuento demasiado breve <br>que se deshace como el agua en nieve <br>una pelicula que <br>se acaba <br>para variar <br>no acaba con beso al final]]></content><category term="Jose Maria Ruiz" label="Jose Maria Ruiz"/><category term="Demasiado Breve" label="Demasiado Breve"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/Si_Te_Quedas_Con_El/</id><title>Jose Maria Ruiz - Si Te Quedas Con El - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:59:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:59:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/Si_Te_Quedas_Con_El/" title="Jose Maria Ruiz - Si Te Quedas Con El - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A tus pies puse entera mi vida <br>cuantas noches he prendido tu pelo <br>cada estrella, que en tus ojos negros <br>el cielo incendio para ti <br><br>Cuantos suenos sobre tu almohada <br>dejamos caer el silencio <br>en la fagrua que forja los miedos <br>puse mi mano por ti <br><br>Y no fue suficiente <br>maldito sea el destino <br>que puso en tu camino <br>alguien que merece tu amor <br><br>Si te quedas con el <br>dile que hay en su piel <br>un lugar donde el sabor de mis besos <br><br>Si te quedas con el <br>al menos, mientele <br>como has hecho conmigo tanto tiempo <br><br>Arrancame el dolor <br>que envenena el silencio <br>Si te quedas con el <br><br>Me entregue desnudandome el alma <br>dibujando en tu piel mis recuerdos <br>primaveras bajo tu ventana <br>a cambio de nada de tu interes <br><br>Y no fue suficiente <br>maldito sea el destino <br>que puso en tu camino <br>alguien que merece tu amor <br><br>Si te quedas con el <br>dile que hay en su piel <br>un lugar donde el sabor de mis besos <br><br>Si te quedas con el <br>al menos, mientele <br>como has hecho conmigo tanto tiempo <br><br>Arrancame el dolor <br>que envenena el silencio <br><br>Si te quedas con el <br>dile que hay en su piel <br>un lugar donde el sabor de mis besos <br><br>Si te quedas con el <br>al menos, mientele <br>como has hecho conmigo tanto tiempo <br><br>Arrancame el dolor <br>que envenena el silencio <br><br>Si te quedas con el]]></content><category term="Jose Maria Ruiz" label="Jose Maria Ruiz"/><category term="Si Te Quedas Con El" label="Si Te Quedas Con El"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/No_Te_Pido_Mas/</id><title>Jose Maria Ruiz - No Te Pido Mas - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:59:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:59:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/No_Te_Pido_Mas/" title="Jose Maria Ruiz - No Te Pido Mas - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Antes de que niegues <br>lo que ha sido nuestro amor <br>que resetees <br>la memoria al corazon <br><br>Antes de barrer <br>los mil trozos de un dia mas <br>de este palacio de cristal <br>que se derrumba <br><br>Reconoceme <br>que ha sido hermoso e irrepetible <br>venga atrevete <br>sabes bien que es imposible <br>que otra luz <br>apague el brillo de este sol <br>antes de verme en el olvido <br><br>Quizas <br>no te importe decirlo <br>y borrarme del alma <br>las frases amargas <br>que escupes sin pensar <br><br>No te pido mas <br>que mejor de testigo <br>si hoy me huele la piel a tus abrazos <br>si no lo sone <br>dime la verdad <br>de lo que vivi contigo <br><br>Antes de que ardan <br>en la hoguera de San Juan <br>las viejas fotos <br>y el humo te haga al fin llorar <br><br>Antes de saber <br>que hay otro nombre que quizas <br>llegue a curar la soledad <br>que yo no supe a tiempo <br><br>Reconoceme <br>que ha sido hermoso e irrepetible <br>venga atrevete <br>sabes bien que es imposible <br>que otra luz <br>apague el brillo de este sol <br>antes de verme en el olvido <br><br>Quizas <br>no te importe decirlo <br>y borrarme del alma <br>las frases amargas <br>que escupes sin pensar <br><br>No te pido mas <br>que mejor de testigo <br>si hoy me huele la piel a tus abrazos <br>si no lo sone <br>dime la verdad <br>de lo que vivi contigo <br><br>Quizas <br>no te importe decirlo <br>y borrarme del alma <br>las frases amargas <br>que escupes sin pensar <br><br>No te pido mas <br>que mejor de testigo <br>si hoy me huele la piel a tus abrazos <br>si no lo sone <br>dime la verdad <br>de lo que vivi contigo <br><br>Tu dime <br>dime la verdad <br><br>De lo que vivi contigo]]></content><category term="Jose Maria Ruiz" label="Jose Maria Ruiz"/><category term="No Te Pido Mas" label="No Te Pido Mas"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/Quiero_Besar_Tu_Boca/</id><title>Jose Maria Ruiz - Quiero Besar Tu Boca - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:59:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:59:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/Quiero_Besar_Tu_Boca/" title="Jose Maria Ruiz - Quiero Besar Tu Boca - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cuando estas cerca no se <br>como decirte lo que por ti siento <br>marcame <br>cuantas noches me invente tu piel a oscuras <br><br>Cuando estas cerca no se <br>como mirarte sin que notes nada <br>sin que el <br>sepa que mientras te tenga me derrumba <br><br>Y ahora este dolor <br>me esta matando <br>me hace naufragar <br><br>Esta condena <br>de amarte <br>sin poderte acariciar <br><br>Quiero besar tu boca <br>quiero vivir la vida <br>quiero sentir contigo como hace tiempo <br>aunque no sentia <br><br>Quiero besar tu boca <br>cerrar bien que serias <br>quiero sentirte cerca <br>volverte loca con mis caricias <br><br>Quiero besar tu boca <br><br>Tu mi razon <br>mi por que <br>alejas la pena <br>tu la pones contra la pared <br>cuando estas cerca de mi <br>nada me asusta <br><br>Es tan dificil <br>lo se <br>poder descubrir de nuevo todo juntos <br>renacer <br>solo quiero despertar atado a tu cintura <br><br>Y ahora este dolor <br>me esta matando <br>me hace naufragar <br><br>Esta condena <br>de amarte <br>sin poderte acariciar <br><br>Quiero besar tu boca <br>quiero vivir la vida <br>quiero sentir contigo como hace tiempo <br>aunque no sentia <br><br>Quiero besar tu boca <br>cerrar bien que serias <br>quiero sentirte cerca <br>volverte loca con mis caricias <br><br>Quiero besar tu boca <br><br>Quiero besar tu boca <br>quiero vivir la vida <br>quiero sentir contigo como hace tiempo <br>aunque no sentia <br><br>Quiero besar tu boca <br>cerrar bien que serias <br>quiero sentirte cerca <br>volverte loca con mis caricias <br><br>Quiero besar tu boca]]></content><category term="Jose Maria Ruiz" label="Jose Maria Ruiz"/><category term="Quiero Besar Tu Boca" label="Quiero Besar Tu Boca"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/Como_Te_Mereces/</id><title>Jose Maria Ruiz - Como Te Mereces - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T11:59:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T11:59:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jose_Maria_Ruiz/Como_Te_Mereces/" title="Jose Maria Ruiz - Como Te Mereces - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yo solo buscaba un beso con el que olvidar <br>una historia tan absurda y por casualidad <br>esa noche, de repente, estabas por alli <br>detras de mi <br><br>Tu buscabas un abrazo para reparar <br>cicatrices de un romance que termina mal <br>y de pronto tropezaste <br>con un quizas <br><br>Borro mi cuenta, nada te dijiste tu <br>un clavo saca a otro, pensaria yo <br>y salimos abrazados <br>riendo sin pensar <br><br>Que seria un milagro <br>que esto funcionase al despertar <br>si tan solo vimos <br>de heridas de la soledad <br><br>Y seria un milagro <br>que al final me amases de verdad <br>y yo te quisiera <br>como te mereces <br>hoy te abrazo un poco mas <br><br>Solo buscame una excusa para hacerme ver <br>lo que lo de anoche, francamente, estuvo bien <br>con la luz del dia no parece todo igual <br>en realidad <br><br>Y ahora somos como extranos al amanecer <br>preguntandonos que hacemos aun en este hotel <br>entre sabanas revueltas <br>tratando de entender <br><br>Que seria un milagro <br>que esto funcionase al despertar <br>si tan solo vimos <br>de heridas de la soledad <br><br>Y seria un milagro <br>que al final me amases de verdad <br>y yo te quisiera <br>como te mereces <br>hoy te abrazo un poco mas <br><br>Que seria un milagro <br>que esto funcionase al despertar <br>si tan solo vimos <br>de heridas de la soledad <br><br>Y seria un milagro <br>que al final me amases de verdad <br>y yo te quisiera <br>como te mereces <br>hoy te abrazo un poco mas]]></content><category term="Jose Maria Ruiz" label="Jose Maria Ruiz"/><category term="Como Te Mereces" label="Como Te Mereces"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/멜로디_정_Melody_Jung/A_Single_Day_With_Guitar_강기훈/</id><title>멜로디 정 (Melody Jung) - A Single Day (With Guitar 강기훈) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:01:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:01:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A9%9C%EB%A1%9C%EB%94%94_%EC%A0%95_Melody_Jung/A_Single_Day_With_Guitar_%EA%B0%95%EA%B8%B0%ED%9B%88/" title="멜로디 정 (Melody Jung) - A Single Day (With Guitar 강기훈) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[해가 떠요 하루가 시작되죠 <br>해야할 일들 만날 사람들이 <br>그대 앞에 놓여있네요 <br>오늘 하루 어떻게 해야할까요 <br>숨을 깊게 마시고 천천히 내쉬며 <br>그대여 생각해봐요 <br>오늘이 마지막 날이라면 <br>무엇을 하고싶죠 <br>그대가 이 하루를 산다면 <br>어떤 사람이고싶죠 <br>A single day <br>If you live a single day <br>A single day <br>If you live a single day <br>오늘이 마지막 날이라면 <br>무엇을 하고싶죠 <br>그대가 이 하루를 산다면 <br>어떤 사람이고싶죠 <br>A single day <br>If you live a single day <br>A single day <br>If you live a single day <br>A single day <br>If you live a single day <br>A single day <br>If you live a single day <br>]]></content><category term="멜로디 정 (Melody Jung)" label="멜로디 정 (Melody Jung)"/><category term="A Single Day (With Guitar 강기훈)" label="A Single Day (With Guitar 강기훈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이루펀트/Newport_Feat_San_E/</id><title>이루펀트 - Newport (Feat. San E) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:03:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:03:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%A3%A8%ED%8E%80%ED%8A%B8/Newport_Feat_San_E/" title="이루펀트 - Newport (Feat. San E) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh 제발 내 눈에 <br>보이는게 너에게도 <br>잘 보였음 좋겠어 <br>아니면 외로워 <br>저 풍경은 우릴 <br>Holy한 상태로 <br>이끌거야 그러니 <br>꽉 잡아볼래 내 손 <br>내가 이상주의자냐 <br>묻는다면 Alright <br>하지만 속물이 되지 <br>않는다는 정도의 <br>현실감 나도 좋아 걱정마 <br>이번 여행의 예산은 <br>전부 짜놨으니까 So <br>이젠 널 에스코트 해 <br>서울을 벗어날거야 <br>자 벨트 얼른 매 <br>묻지 말아줘 <br>우리의 행선지에 대해서 <br>이미 놀거리는 <br>다 예정돼있어 <br>나 구두도 새로 샀고 <br>Flow도 새로 타 <br>땡기는게 생겼다면 <br>여기 메뉴 봐 <br>쌀국수면 Vetnam <br>햄버거면 Manhattan <br>Are you feeling better now <br>Come on <br>우 무슨 얘기를 들었건 <br>Don't matter I'm feeling good <br>오 떠날거야 무조건 <br>여긴 밀치거나 밀릴 뿐 <br>Hey 네 맘을 메꿔놔야 돼 <br>You 구멍을 메꿔놔야 돼 <br>Hey 그래서 널 데리고 가야겠어 <br>You 널 데리고 가야겠어 <br>I feel like smokin' Newport <br>I feel like smokin' Newport <br>I feel like smokin' Newport <br>I feel like smokin' Newport <br>I feel like smokin' Newport <br>드르르르륵 캐리어 끌고 <br>들뜬듯한 호흡 <br>브르르르르 춤을 추는 <br>나의 Flipflop Flipflop 워우 <br>완전 Tom Hanks <br>Airport 집이라도 된 기분이야 <br>지난달 시부야에서 쓴 영수증 <br>백팩 속 빼곡한 체 캘리포니아 <br>와이키키 해변의 <br>오렌지빛 노을 지는 해 <br>너의 눈에 러브샷 건배 <br>달리 보여 녹아내리는 시계 <br>Knock 문 열어 봐 <br>내가 너희 집 앞에다 <br>세계를 갖다 놨으니까 <br>여권은 됐어 <br>걍 내 입술에다 찍어주면 돼 <br>참 잘했어요 <br>반짝반짝한 그 립밤 <br>꿈이 꿈을 가지는 거란건 <br>딱 죽는 기분 같을거야 <br>얼른 들어 암보험 <br>You only live once <br>뭣 같은 우물 안 출구는 <br>니 눈 앞야 Like 원 <br>Smokin' Newport <br>에펠탑에 걸터앉은 청량감 <br>덜컹 이제 창문 열어 봐 <br>연기처럼 흘러 나올거야 <br>Oh my god <br>우 무슨 얘기를 들었건 <br>Don't matter I'm feeling good <br>오 떠날거야 무조건 <br>여긴 밀치거나 밀릴 뿐 <br>Hey 네 맘을 메꿔놔야 돼 <br>You 구멍을 메꿔놔야 돼 <br>Hey 그래서 널 데리고 가야겠어 <br>You 널 데리고 가야겠어 <br>I feel like smokin' Newport <br>I feel like smokin' Newport <br>I feel like smokin' Newport <br>I feel like smokin' Newport <br>I feel like smokin' Newport <br>떠나자 매일 품는 생각인데 <br>생각은 왜 생각보다 어려운지 <br>너와 나 So stressed out <br>승모근 위에서 좀 내려와라 <br>버거운 짐 Hiccup <br>딸꾹질과 공황 장애 등 <br>현대병에 답은 <br>담배 술 아냐 <br>바로 공항 Let's fly <br>자 여행이란 러닝머신 위 <br>뛰어올라 삶을 태우자 <br>Calorie burning <br>널 가꾸는건 좋아 <br>But 바꾸지는 마 <br>지금 입고 있는 옷은 <br>너가 아냐 벗어봐 <br>Feel good 얼마만야 <br>이런 기분 <br>태양을 연인 삼아 <br>Let's da da da dance <br>Who whoop vibe <br>so positive <br>누구든지 환영해요 <br>New port parade <br>비록 시작은 남이지만 <br>오 영원한 친구 <br>지금 이 순간만큼은 Brother <br>우 무슨 얘기를 들었건 <br>Don't matter I'm feeling good <br>오 떠날거야 무조건 <br>여긴 밀치거나 밀릴 뿐 <br>Hey 네 맘을 메꿔놔야 돼 <br>You 구멍을 메꿔놔야 돼 <br>Hey 그래서 널 데리고 가야겠어 <br>You 널 데리고 가야겠어 <br><br>]]></content><category term="이루펀트" label="이루펀트"/><category term="Newport (Feat. San E)" label="Newport (Feat. San E)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아리/오늘_같은_날_Inst/</id><title>아리 - 오늘 같은 날 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:04:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:04:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EB%A6%AC/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98_%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EB%82%A0_Inst/" title="아리 - 오늘 같은 날 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자꾸 눈을 뗄 수가 없어 <br>여전히 예뻐서 죽겠어 <br>yeah <br>매번 나를 보며 웃는 너 <br>혹시 내 맘 알아버렸나 <br>모르겠어 <br>어쩜 그리 둔하니 <br>이렇게 티를 내도 <br>감이 없어 <br>이렇게 좋은 날 <br>우연히 둘인데 <br>좀처럼 오지 않는 기횐데 <br>바보처럼 눈치만 봐 <br>답답해 죽겠지만 <br>그런 니가 난 좋아 <br>Maybe love <br>애만 자꾸 타들고 <br>Maybe love <br>Maybe this is love <br>사랑 그 한마디 <br>우리를 맺어주죠 <br>너만 보면 자꾸 얼어서 <br>말을 걸지 못해 죽겠어 <br>yeah <br>자주 내 주위에 있는 널 <br>설마 너도 애태우는지 <br>모르겠어 <br>어쩜 그리 둔하니 <br>이렇게 티를 내도 <br>감이 없어 <br>이렇게 좋은 날 <br>우연히 둘인데 <br>좀처럼 오지 않는 기횐데 <br>바보처럼 눈치만 봐 <br>답답해 죽겠지만 <br>그런 니가 난 좋아 <br>Maybe love <br>애만 자꾸 타들고 <br>Maybe love <br>Maybe this is love <br>사랑 그 한마디 <br>우리를 맺어주죠 <br>항상 네 옆에서 <br>발맞추고 싶어 <br>하얀 너의 미소 내 눈 속에 <br>담아두고 싶어 <br>매일 바래다주면서 <br>안아주고 싶어 <br>이쯤에서 니 의견 어떤지 <br>묻고 싶어 <br>이렇게 좋은 날 <br>우연히 둘인데 <br>좀처럼 오지 않는 기횐데 <br>바보처럼 눈치만 봐 <br>답답해 죽겠지만 <br>그런 니가 난 좋아 <br>Maybe love <br>애만 자꾸 타들고 <br>Maybe love <br>Maybe this is love <br>사랑 그 한마디 <br>우리를 맺어주죠 <br>]]></content><category term="아리" label="아리"/><category term="오늘 같은 날 (Inst.)" label="오늘 같은 날 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아리/오늘_같은_날/</id><title>아리 - 오늘 같은 날 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:05:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:05:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EB%A6%AC/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98_%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EB%82%A0/" title="아리 - 오늘 같은 날 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자꾸 눈을 뗄 수가 없어 <br>여전히 예뻐서 죽겠어 <br>yeah <br>매번 나를 보며 웃는 너 <br>혹시 내 맘 알아버렸나 <br>모르겠어 <br>어쩜 그리 둔하니 <br>이렇게 티를 내도 <br>감이 없어 <br>이렇게 좋은 날 <br>우연히 둘인데 <br>좀처럼 오지 않는 기횐데 <br>바보처럼 눈치만 봐 <br>답답해 죽겠지만 <br>그런 니가 난 좋아 <br>Maybe love <br>애만 자꾸 타들고 <br>Maybe love <br>Maybe this is love <br>사랑 그 한마디 <br>우리를 맺어주죠 <br>너만 보면 자꾸 얼어서 <br>말을 걸지 못해 죽겠어 <br>yeah <br>자주 내 주위에 있는 널 <br>설마 너도 애태우는지 <br>모르겠어 <br>어쩜 그리 둔하니 <br>이렇게 티를 내도 <br>감이 없어 <br>이렇게 좋은 날 <br>우연히 둘인데 <br>좀처럼 오지 않는 기횐데 <br>바보처럼 눈치만 봐 <br>답답해 죽겠지만 <br>그런 니가 난 좋아 <br>Maybe love <br>애만 자꾸 타들고 <br>Maybe love <br>Maybe this is love <br>사랑 그 한마디 <br>우리를 맺어주죠 <br>항상 네 옆에서 <br>발맞추고 싶어 <br>하얀 너의 미소 내 눈 속에 <br>담아두고 싶어 <br>매일 바래다주면서 <br>안아주고 싶어 <br>이쯤에서 니 의견 어떤지 <br>묻고 싶어 <br>이렇게 좋은 날 <br>우연히 둘인데 <br>좀처럼 오지 않는 기횐데 <br>바보처럼 눈치만 봐 <br>답답해 죽겠지만 <br>그런 니가 난 좋아 <br>Maybe love <br>애만 자꾸 타들고 <br>Maybe love <br>Maybe this is love <br>사랑 그 한마디 <br>우리를 맺어주죠 <br>]]></content><category term="아리" label="아리"/><category term="오늘 같은 날" label="오늘 같은 날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HONEY_SLEEP/HONEY_SLEEP_Feat_MC_Meta_Deepflow_DJ_HUNTEr/</id><title>HONEY SLEEP - HONEY SLEEP (Feat. MC Meta, Deepflow, DJ HUNTEr) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:05:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:05:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HONEY_SLEEP/HONEY_SLEEP_Feat_MC_Meta_Deepflow_DJ_HUNTEr/" title="HONEY SLEEP - HONEY SLEEP (Feat. MC Meta, Deepflow, DJ HUNTEr) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘밤도 난 원해 <br>Honey Sleep <br>난 선택해야돼 <br>on my one hunnit ways <br>죽이는걸 골라서 <br>배열해 하나씩 <br>걔들이 듣고 꼴릴만하게 <br>Holly shit <br>난 이게 내 밥줄 <br>꽤나 멋있지 <br>Yo 놈팽이 Rappers <br>졸라매 허리띠 <br>야 대체 잠이와 <br>난 윗집 아랫집 <br>다 싹 깨워 놓고 <br>태평이 Honey Sleep <br>밤새 머린 띵 <br>난 이게 어울리지 <br>다 찢지못하면 <br>다 찢고서 원위치 <br>너넨 졸립지 <br>스페어 볼링핀 <br>전부 쓰러지고 <br>나만 저 멀리있지 <br>난 저 멀리있지 <br>Lyrical 올림픽 <br>승리의 트로피와 <br>월계수 머리띠 <br>공책을 덮고 <br>I just wanna sleep <br>열여섯줄 마침표 <br>뒤에는 Zzz <br>난 원해 Honey Sleep <br>밤새 머린 띵 <br>난 잘 수 없어 찢지 못하면 <br>다 찢고서 원위치 <br>난 원해 Honey Sleep <br>난 원해 Honey Sleep <br>밤새 머린 띵 <br>난 잘 수 없어 찢지 못하면 <br>다 찢고서 원위치 <br>난 원해 Honey Sleep <br>Nightmare Nightmare <br>칼에 손바닥을 베어 <br>눈 뜨네요 <br>Freddy Freddy <br>불러내요 수를 새요 <br>몇날 며칠 눈 <br>감아도 깨어있네요 <br>내 팔 다리 다 <br>Freddy Freddy <br>손끝에 줄로 묶여있네요 <br>Master Master <br>내 머리 위로 받들어 <br>모실꺼야 내 Master <br>불경한 건 금 밖으로 <br>내 못난 영감으로 <br>못잡아 감각으로 <br>뒤쳐져 싹 다 불러 <br>시간은 다 파묻어 <br>무덤을 열었네요 <br>나를 보는 눈은 왜요 <br>의심을 버린다면 <br>누릴 수 있는대요 <br>그 던젼 안에 <br>아이템은 레어래요 <br>갖지 못한다면 네임드란 <br>타이틀은 떼어내요 <br>달빛으로 만든 길을 <br>따라 갔지 뻥 <br>육체는 죽었지만 <br>의미는 살아남지 뻥 <br>내가 싸고 토해놓은 <br>냄새때메 뭐 <br>오늘밤도 꿀잠 자긴 <br>글렀다고 허 <br>난 원해 Honey Sleep <br>밤새 머린 띵 <br>난 잘 수 없어 찢지 못하면 <br>다 찢고서 원위치 <br>난 원해 Honey Sleep <br>난 원해 Honey Sleep <br>밤새 머린 띵 <br>난 잘 수 없어 찢지 못하면 <br>다 찢고서 원위치 <br>난 원해 Honey Sleep <br>밤새 머린 띵 <br>난 잘 수 없어 찢지 못하면 <br>다 찢고서 원위치 <br>난 원해 Honey Sleep <br>난 원해 Honey Sleep <br>밤새 머린 띵 <br>난 잘 수 없어 찢지 못하면 <br>다 찢고서 원위치 <br>난 원해 Honey Sleep <br>]]></content><category term="HONEY SLEEP" label="HONEY SLEEP"/><category term="HONEY SLEEP (Feat. MC Meta, Deepflow, DJ HUNTEr)" label="HONEY SLEEP (Feat. MC Meta, Deepflow, DJ HUNTEr)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/황치열/그리워_그리워서_이영_Ver/</id><title>황치열 - 그리워 그리워서 (이영 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:05:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:05:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%A9%EC%B9%98%EC%97%B4/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9B%8C_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9B%8C%EC%84%9C_%EC%9D%B4%EC%98%81_Ver/" title="황치열 - 그리워 그리워서 (이영 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그리워 그리워서 (이영 Ver.) <br><br>저 구름에 달빛에 <br>내 마음 보일까 <br>빛바랜 담장 아래 <br>나 숨어봅니다 <br>이름없는 들꽃도 <br>늘 함께하는데 <br>왜 난 홀로 눈물만 <br>흘리고 있는지 <br>그리워 그리워서 <br>더는 못 잊을 사람 <br>눈물이 가슴이 <br>그댈 부르고 있어 <br>사랑해 사랑해서 <br>더는 못 보낼 사람 <br>그대 뒤에서 갈 곳을 잃어 <br>울고만 있어 그대 <br>눈 앞에서 날리는 <br>그대 옷자락에 <br>내 마음만 안긴 채 <br>나 돌아서는데 <br>그리워 그리워서 <br>더는 못 잊을 사람 <br>눈물이 가슴이 <br>그댈 부르고 있어 <br>사랑해 사랑해서 <br>더는 못 보낼 사람 <br>그대 뒤에서 갈 곳을 잃어 <br>울고만 있어 그대 <br>내게 단 한 사람 <br>수많았던 기억 속으로 <br>그리워 그리워서 <br>더는 못 잊을 사람 <br>눈물이 가슴이 <br>그댈 부르고 있어 <br>사랑해 사랑해서 <br>더는 못 보낼 사람 <br>그대 뒤에서 갈 곳을 잃어 <br>울고만 있어 <br>그대 <br>]]></content><category term="황치열" label="황치열"/><category term="그리워 그리워서 (이영 Ver.)" label="그리워 그리워서 (이영 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cam/Want_It_All/</id><title>Cam - Want It All - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:08:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:08:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cam/Want_It_All/" title="Cam - Want It All - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Been a sittin' 'round a coward, broken all that I can break <br>Cried my eyes out in a bathroom stall of every western state <br>Still, I ain't stoppin' cause there's more that I can take <br>Got my angels and my demons and I think we all agree <br>If you're gonna go for something, better make it everything <br>I believe in the end I'll see that it's alright, alright <br>Babe, I'll put my heart on the line <br><br>I want it all <br>Don't want no rocking chair regrets <br>I got that fire and it's burning in my chest <br>Gonna keep on living 'til I hear the last call <br>And I, I, I want it all <br><br>Bet my life on it <br>Made my bed, gonna lie on it <br>Made up my mind that I won't just get by or get lost in it <br>I won't listen to your rumors, I won't listen to your doubts <br>Too much ain't enough, so don't try to slow me down <br>Know what I'm thinking that I want it now <br>Yeah, it's alright, alright <br>Babe, I'll put my heart on the line <br><br>I want it all <br>Don't want no rocking chair regrets <br>I got that fire and it's burning in my chest <br>Gonna keep on living 'til I hear the last call <br>And I, I, I want it all <br><br>The song inside me won't be turned down <br>I know I'm making my old self proud <br>Love without conditions, no inhibitions <br>I know I'm gonna lose sometimes <br><br>I want it all <br>Don't want no rocking chair regrets <br>I got that fire and it's burning in my chest <br>Got a whole lot of living that I haven't done yet <br>And I, I, I, I <br>I want it all <br><br>I want it all <br>Don't want no rocking chair regrets <br>I got that fire and it's burning in my chest <br>Gonna keep on living 'til I hear the last call <br>And I, I, I want it all <br>I want it all <br>I want it all <br>I want it, want it all]]></content><category term="Cam" label="Cam"/><category term="Want It All" label="Want It All"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lea_Michele/Louder/</id><title>Lea Michele - Louder - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:08:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:08:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lea_Michele/Louder/" title="Lea Michele - Louder - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come out of the shadow <br>Step into the light <br>This could be the moment <br>Are you ready to fight <br>Don't you know you know <br>You're not the only one <br>Why so low so low <br>What are you waiting for <br>All I ever hear are whispers <br>All I ever hear are whispers <br>But I just wanna hear your voice <br>Don't be afraid <br>Why don't you scream a little <br>louder <br>Turn it up <br>I know you can <br>Come on and scream a little louder <br>Oh oh hoh oh hoh <br>Why don't you scream a little <br>louder <br>Oh oh hoh oh hoh <br>Why don't you scream a little <br>louder <br>Wanna be remembered <br>Stand out in the crowd <br>Don't choke on the fire <br>It's tryin' to burn you out <br>Why so low so low <br>What are you waiting for <br>All I ever hear are whispers <br>All I ever hear are whispers <br>But I just wanna hear your voice <br>Don't be afraid <br>Why don't you scream a little <br>louder <br>Turn it up <br>I know you can <br>Come on and scream a little louder <br>Oh oh hoh oh hoh <br>Why don't you scream a little <br>louder <br>Oh oh hoh oh hoh <br>Why don't you scream a little <br>louder <br>Come out of the shadow <br>Step into the light <br>This could be the moment <br>It could change your life <br>All I ever hear are whispers <br>But I just wanna hear your voice <br>Don't be afraid <br>Why don't you scream a little <br>louder <br>Turn it up <br>I know you can <br>Come on and scream a little louder <br>Oh oh hoh oh hoh <br>Why don't you scream a little <br>louder <br>Turn it up <br>I know you can <br>Why don't you scream a little <br>louder <br>Oh oh hoh oh hoh <br>Why don't you scream a little <br>louder]]></content><category term="Lea Michele" label="Lea Michele"/><category term="Louder" label="Louder"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imani_Williams/Dont_Need_No_Money_Feat_Sigala__Blonde/</id><title>Imani Williams - Don`t Need No Money (Feat. Sigala &amp; Blonde) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:08:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:08:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imani_Williams/Dont_Need_No_Money_Feat_Sigala__Blonde/" title="Imani Williams - Don`t Need No Money (Feat. Sigala &amp; Blonde) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh baby <br>Wrapped up in your arms <br>feels like I made it <br>When I close my eyes <br>the world has faded <br>I used to say that love was <br>just a fool's game <br>Til you put it on me <br>Now I'm talking 'bout diamonds <br>in your eyes <br>I'm thinking 'bout loving <br>your for life <br>There's something 'bout you <br>That got me feeling like <br>that got me feeling like <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>As long as I got you oh <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>As long as I got you oh oo <br>oh oo oh oo oh oo <br>oh oo oh oo oh oo <br>As long as I got you <br>oh oo oh oo oh oo <br>oh oo oh oo oh oo <br>As long as I got you <br>So crazy <br>How I just can't came down <br>from what you gave me <br>On and on I go through <br>every cliche <br>I got this fever boy <br>you put it on me <br>Yeah you put it on me <br>I'm thinking 'bout stars <br>and butterflies <br>I'm thinking 'bout drowning <br>in your eyes <br>There's something 'bout you <br>That got me feeling like <br>that got me feeling like <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>As long as I got you oh <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>As long as I got you oh oo <br>oh oo oh oo oh oo <br>oh oo oh oo oh oo <br>As long as I got you <br>oh oo oh oo oh oo <br>oh oo oh oo oh oo <br>As long as I got you <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>As long as I got you <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>As long as I got you <br>Now I know my love <br>don't have a price <br>When you hold me close <br>yeah yeah <br>Tell you baby <br>I'd give it all for a love <br>that feels like <br>It's more than just the superficial <br>oh it's superficial oh <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need it yeah <br>As long as I got you <br>oh oo oh oo oh oo <br>oh oo oh oo oh oo <br>As long as I got you <br>oh oo oh oo oh oo <br>oh oo oh oo oh oo <br>As long as I got you <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>As long as I got you <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>I don't need no money <br>As long as I got you oh oo <br>]]></content><category term="Imani Williams" label="Imani Williams"/><category term="Don`t Need No Money (Feat. Sigala &amp; Blonde)" label="Don`t Need No Money (Feat. Sigala &amp; Blonde)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HER/Wait_For_It/</id><title>H.E.R. - Wait For It - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:08:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:08:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HER/Wait_For_It/" title="H.E.R. - Wait For It - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Uber on the way, my phone is chargin' <br>He keep callin' <br>I wanna pick it up, but I keep stallin' <br>I feel some type of way <br>It's late at night, and babe <br>I ain't get dressed for nothin' <br>I ain't put on this dress for nothin' <br>So I'm comin', baby <br><br>Chorus <br>Wait for it, wait for it, wait for it, yeah <br>I'ma need for you to wait for it, wait for it, wait for it <br>Baby can you wait for it, wait for it, wait for it <br>Baby can you wait for it Wait for it <br>Can you <br><br>Verse 2 <br>Yeah, I know you on the way, but now I want it <br>I can't take it <br>I'm merely tryna chill, but I'm impatient <br>Stay on my mind <br>Can't sleep at night <br>And I ain't get dressed for nothin' <br>I ain't put on this dress for nothin' <br>I know you're comin' <br><br>Chorus <br>Wait for it, wait for it, wait for it, yeah <br>I'ma need for you to wait for it, wait for it, wait for it <br>Baby can you wait for it, wait for it, wait for it <br>Baby can you wait for it Wait for it <br>Can you]]></content><category term="H.E.R." label="H.E.R."/><category term="Wait For It" label="Wait For It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nao/Bad_Blood/</id><title>Nao - Bad Blood - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:08:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:08:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nao/Bad_Blood/" title="Nao - Bad Blood - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're a holiday <br>A glass of ocean slipping <br>down my throat <br>And landed on my hopes <br>I'm dreaming <br>Off the maps no hidden grids <br>I'm fleeing <br>I worship you like holy days <br>Lying on my back <br>seeing clouds and rays <br>Drinking lime and bitter <br>from my lemonade <br>White horses <br>merry time won't do <br>Oh ooh <br>Oh ooh <br>Oh ooh <br>Oh ooh <br>Oh ooh <br>Oh ooh <br>Oh ooh <br>Do you remember the holiday <br>Slipped away <br>Time and place <br>I definitely remember <br>Lying on my back and seeing <br>Clouds and rays <br>We're dreaming <br>The feelings rule <br>Forever we're young <br>Pages unsung <br>Ooh <br>I feel that you remember <br>Dreaming of a past <br>that couldn't last <br>But now we're changing <br>refraining <br>I think it is the <br>know that it's the <br>I think it is the bad <br>bad blood <br>I think it is the <br>know that it's the <br>I think it is the bad <br>bad blood <br>Do you remember the riding <br>the passion <br>The falling over tripping on ice <br>Sharing advice taking it twice <br>But let us not forget the <br>Silent day drift away <br>Time and place <br>Oh you choose not to remember <br>Fly away counting days <br>I'm hiding from you ooh <br>I think it is the <br>know that it's the <br>I think it is the bad <br>bad blood <br>I think it is the <br>know that it's the <br>I think it is the bad <br>bad blood <br>I choose <br>For the rain not to fall <br>Exposing the sun on you <br>I lose <br>Don't tell me I'm goo goo <br>I know <br>And it's mad we were close oh <br>I choose <br>My head's now afloat <br>But my heart's drowning <br>pulse of you <br>I lose <br>Don't tell me I'm coo coo <br>Coo coo coo coo coo coo ooh ooh <br>I think it is the <br>know that it's the <br>I think it is the bad <br>bad blood <br>I think it is the <br>know that it's the <br>I think it is the bad <br>bad blood <br>I think it is the <br>know that it's the <br>I think it is the bad <br>bad blood <br>I think it is the <br>know that it's the <br>I think it is the bad bad <br>]]></content><category term="Nao" label="Nao"/><category term="Bad Blood" label="Bad Blood"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nervo/People_Grinnin_Feat_The_Child_Of_Lov/</id><title>Nervo - People Grinnin` (Feat. The Child Of Lov) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:08:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:08:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nervo/People_Grinnin_Feat_The_Child_Of_Lov/" title="Nervo - People Grinnin` (Feat. The Child Of Lov) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't you mind people grinnin' in your face <br>Don't mind people grinnin' in your face <br>You know your mother will talk about truth <br>Sisters and your brothers too <br>Don't you mind people grinnin' in your face <br><br>Don't you mind people grinnin' in your face <br>Don't mind people grinnin' in your face <br>You know your mother will talk about truth <br>Sisters and your brothers too <br>Don't you mind people grinnin' in your face <br><br>Don't care how you try to live <br>They'll talk about you still <br>Don't mind people grinnin' in your face <br><br>Just bear this in mind, a true friend is hard to find <br>Don't you mind people grinnin' in your face]]></content><category term="Nervo" label="Nervo"/><category term="People Grinnin` (Feat. The Child Of Lov)" label="People Grinnin` (Feat. The Child Of Lov)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eva_Shaw/Rise_N_Shine_Feat_Poo_Bear/</id><title>Eva Shaw - Rise N Shine (Feat. Poo Bear) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:08:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:08:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eva_Shaw/Rise_N_Shine_Feat_Poo_Bear/" title="Eva Shaw - Rise N Shine (Feat. Poo Bear) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The only way is up from here <br>don't look down <br>I only fell caught in the energy <br>all around me <br>Look to the sky don't need to <br>leave my feet on the ground <br>All night now <br>Rise and shine <br>Oh rise and shine <br>Don't let nobody <br>take your light away <br>Rise and shine <br>Rise and shine <br>Oh yeah yeah <br>The only way is up from here <br>don't look down <br>I only fell caught in the energy <br>all around me <br>Look to the sky don't need to leave <br>my feet on the ground <br>All night now <br>All night now <br>Spread my wings out <br>ain't no need to hide 'em <br>No I won't be that angel in disguise <br>Open up my heart <br>no need to fight it <br>When you see the love <br>just look in my eyes <br>Rise and shine <br>Oh rise and shine <br>Yeah yeah yeah <br>Don't let nobody <br>take your light away <br>Rise and shine <br>Rise and shine <br>Oh yeah yeah <br>Rise and shine <br>Oh rise and shine <br>Yeah yeah yeah <br>Don't let nobody <br>take your light away <br>Rise and shine <br>Rise and shine <br>Rise and shine <br>Oh yeah yeah <br>Oh rise and shine <br>Yeah yeah yeah <br>Don't let nobody <br>take your light away <br>Rise and shine <br>Rise and shine <br>Oh yeah yeah]]></content><category term="Eva Shaw" label="Eva Shaw"/><category term="Rise N Shine (Feat. Poo Bear)" label="Rise N Shine (Feat. Poo Bear)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Veronicas/Let_Me_Out/</id><title>The Veronicas - Let Me Out - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:08:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:08:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Veronicas/Let_Me_Out/" title="The Veronicas - Let Me Out - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can't take the rain <br>I can't take the pain <br>If you are gonna let me down <br>Do it now, let me down <br>I'm too scared to sleep <br>To see you in my dreams <br>If you are gonna me cry <br>Do it right, make me cry <br>Lovin you how much that I make you, me <br>You don't even know if you really need me <br>How can I find that love is the enemy <br>I'm torn in tears until you release me <br>If you think it's over <br>You think we're nowhere, just let me out <br>I'm making it easy <br>For you to go leave me, just let me out <br>You take your clothes indeed <br>I'm way out, breaking free <br>You can't keep this alive <br>We'll survive, push me aside <br>'Cause I can't run if you're coming on to me <br>And I can't hide if you've got the best of me <br>You leave me unsaid <br>It's all in my hand, we're better off dead <br>If you think it's over <br>You think we're nowhere, just let me out <br>I'm making it easy <br>For you to go leave me, just let me out <br>I can't take the rain <br>I can't take the pain <br>If you are gonna let me down <br>Do it now, let me down <br>If you think it's over <br>You think we're nowhere, just let me out <br>I'm making it easy <br>For you to go leave me, just let me out]]></content><category term="The Veronicas" label="The Veronicas"/><category term="Let Me Out" label="Let Me Out"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phoebe_Ryan/Dollar_Bill_Feat_Kid_Ink/</id><title>Phoebe Ryan - Dollar Bill (Feat. Kid Ink) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phoebe_Ryan/Dollar_Bill_Feat_Kid_Ink/" title="Phoebe Ryan - Dollar Bill (Feat. Kid Ink) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh yeah, Phoebe Ryan <br>Kid Ink <br><br>I'm living for the paycheck and the love Uh huh <br>I'm gonna be a legend just because You know <br>I've been working so hard Go hard to get respect <br>Wanna wheel, wanna deal, wanna feel like a president Yeah <br><br>Oh, oh, you can call me Call me <br>Money, money, money, money, money, money <br>Someday I'll be We'll be money, money <br><br>Cause baby I'm just living life <br>Giving my all, all day and night <br>Not gonna stop until <br>They're putting my face on the dollar bill <br>Dolla, dolla, dolla, dolla <br>Tell you I'm just feeling alive <br>It's about time, yeah the time is right <br>Not gonna stop until <br>They're putting my face on the dollar bill <br>Dolla, dolla, dolla, dolla <br>Money, money, money, money, money, money <br>It's all about the dollar bill <br>Money, money, money, money, money, money <br>You know <br><br>I don't need anybody Nah, nah I got myself <br>And I've been doing alright Alright without your help <br>I think they need a new face and I'm the one <br>I'mma rise, I'mma shine, I'mma fire just like the sun <br><br>Oh, oh, you can call me Call me <br>Money, money, money, money, money, money <br>Someday I'll be We'll be money, money <br><br>Cause baby I'm just living life <br>Giving my all, all day and night <br>Not gonna stop until <br>They're putting my face on the dollar bill <br>Dolla, dolla, dolla, dolla <br>Tell you I'm just feeling like <br>It's about time, yeah the time is right <br>Not gonna stop until <br>They're putting my face on the dollar bill <br>Dolla, dolla, dolla, dolla <br>Money, money, money, money, money, money <br>It's all about the dollar bill <br>Money, money, money, money, money, money <br>Money, money, money, money, money, money <br>It's all about the dollar bill <br>Money, money, money, money, money, money <br><br>I got money on my mind, mind, mind on my money <br>Tryna see my ID, here's a hundred <br>I ain't change but these chains to my stomach <br>I'm just tryna ball hard like it's any given Sunday, yeah <br>Drop, T Top when's it's sunny, doing ninety to a hundred <br>Feel the wind through your ponytail <br>Shopping in the summer, tryna fit the fall <br>Can't ship it next day, then we hit the mall <br>Ain't no reason tryna save my inches <br>Got paid and I spent it <br><br>Cause baby I'm just living life <br>Giving my all, all day and night <br>Not gonna stop until Nah, nah <br>They're putting my face on the dollar bill <br>Dolla, dolla, dolla, dolla <br>Tell you I'm just feeling like <br>It's about time, yeah the time is right Yeah <br>Not gonna stop until <br>They're putting my face on the dollar bill <br>Dolla, dolla, dolla, dolla <br>Money, money, money, money, money, money <br>It's all about the dollar bill <br>Money, money, money, money, money, money <br>Money, money, money, money, money, money <br>You know that, you know that, ah <br>Money, money, money, money, money, money <br>It's all about the dollar bill]]></content><category term="Phoebe Ryan" label="Phoebe Ryan"/><category term="Dollar Bill (Feat. Kid Ink)" label="Dollar Bill (Feat. Kid Ink)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucy_Rose/Like_An_Arrow/</id><title>Lucy Rose - Like An Arrow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucy_Rose/Like_An_Arrow/" title="Lucy Rose - Like An Arrow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, won't you comfort me <br>I don't feel like myself lately <br>Oh, won't you stay with me <br>'Cause when you're gone my vision's hazy <br><br>'Cause I was made for you <br>We were made like two <br><br>We took our chance <br>And we flew <br>Like an arrow <br>Like an arrow <br>We came to our <br>Sense to soar <br>Like an arrow <br>Like an arrow <br><br>Oh, won't you comfort me <br>Talk to me, you speak so sweetly <br>Oh, won't you stay with me <br>Nights are short when you are near me <br><br>'Cause I was made for you <br>We were made like two <br><br>We took our chance <br>And we flew <br>Like an arrow <br>Like an arrow <br>We came to our <br>Sense to soar <br>Like an arrow <br>Like an arrow <br><br>We took our chance <br>And we flew <br>Like an arrow <br>Like an arrow <br>We came to our <br>Sense to soar <br>Like an arrow <br>Like an arrow <br><br>'Cause I am on your side <br>I will comfort you <br>I'm in love with you <br><br>We took our chance <br>And we flew <br>Like an arrow <br>Like an arrow <br>We came to our <br>Sense to soar <br>Like an arrow <br><br>We took our chance <br>And we flew <br>Like an arrow <br>Like an arrow <br>We came to our <br>Sense to soar <br>Like an arrow <br>Like an arrow <br><br>We took our chance <br>And we flew <br>Like an arrow <br>Like an arrow <br>We came to our <br>Sense to soar <br>Like an arrow <br>Like an arrow]]></content><category term="Lucy Rose" label="Lucy Rose"/><category term="Like An Arrow" label="Like An Arrow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Marten/Bird/</id><title>Billie Marten - Bird - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Marten/Bird/" title="Billie Marten - Bird - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She's underwater again <br>Somebody's daughter and friend <br>In the night in the dark <br>In the cold as she walks far away <br>Nobody's watching <br>Drowning in words so sweet <br>Mild is the water <br>Caught as the bird once free <br>I don't mind <br>Hope is a distance unreached <br>Ink on a skin incomplete <br>And the faint sound of friends <br>as she nears <br>To the end she had peace <br>Nobody's watching <br>Drowning in words so sweet <br>Mild is the water <br>Caught as a bird once free <br>I don't mind <br>I don't mind <br>Where does a star go from here <br>Lost in the grip <br>Nobody's watching <br>Drowning in words so sweet <br>Mild is the water <br>Caught as a bird once free <br>Nobody's watching <br>Drowning in words so sweet <br>Mild is the water <br>Caught as a bird once free <br>I don't mind <br>I don't mind <br>I don't mind <br>I don't mind]]></content><category term="Billie Marten" label="Billie Marten"/><category term="Bird" label="Bird"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Izzy_Bizu/Trees__Fire/</id><title>Izzy Bizu - Trees &amp; Fire - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Izzy_Bizu/Trees__Fire/" title="Izzy Bizu - Trees &amp; Fire - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If I talked to me, do I need help <br>If I left to space, would you follow my smell <br>I'd walk on water just to cry for help <br>Cause trees and fire don't help themselves <br><br>I'm not a girl, don't have a world <br>I am nothing in-between <br>What's my name <br><br>If I was to slam doors, am I worth the chase <br>I know I don't mean half of what I say <br>I need your reassurance more than ever today <br>I'll save my truths for a rainy day <br><br>I'm not a girl, don't have a world <br>I am nothing in-between <br>What's my name <br><br>If I talked to me, do I need help <br>If I left to space, would you follow my smell <br>I'd walk on water just to cry for help <br>Cause trees and fire don't help themselves <br>Cause trees and fire don't help themselves]]></content><category term="Izzy Bizu" label="Izzy Bizu"/><category term="Trees &amp; Fire" label="Trees &amp; Fire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Grace/Boys_Boys_Boys/</id><title>Grace - Boys Boys Boys - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Grace/Boys_Boys_Boys/" title="Grace - Boys Boys Boys - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Boys, boys, boys, boys 2, 3, 4 <br><br>Ice cold in the summer, iced tea in the winter <br>I don't allow myself to fall, <br>but I fall every time that my heart's ever near ya <br>And I don't ever let 'em, spend a lot of time to forget 'em <br>'cause I know what they say about these boys, <br>they'll trip you when you fall, its a set up <br><br>So he's gorgeous, maybe he's a babe <br>But he ain't doing nothing but getting all in the way <br>Sweet nothings 'bout love will never ever mean a thing <br>Throw the bouquet, keep him away <br><br>There I go, there I go, there I go, woah <br>Try to live without them, but I'm stuck here in love again <br>There I go, there I go, there I go, woah <br>So d damn distracting, I just can't take my mind off them, boys <br><br>Boys, boys, boys <br>Boys 2, 3, 4 <br><br>Fluid like water, spit mad game to your daughter <br>But I know what mama say <br>I'm 'bout to get burned if I'm playing with the fire <br>So I don't ever let 'em, and when they cross the line, <br>I check 'em <br>See the sparkle in my eyes, cause love is blind, <br>it's just a matter of time 'til I friend them <br><br>So he's gorgeous, maybe he's a babe <br>But he ain't doing nothing but a getting all in the way <br>Sweet nothings 'bout love will never ever mean a thing <br>Throw the bouquet, keep him away <br><br>There I go, there I go, there I go, woah <br>Try to live without them, but I'm stuck here in love again <br>There I go, there I go, there I go, woah <br>So d damn distracting, I just can't take my mind off them boys <br><br>Boys, boys, boys, boys 2, 3, 4 <br>Boys, boys, boys 2, 3, 4 <br><br>Boys like girls, sugar sweet <br>Sweep 'em right up off they feet <br>Boys like girls who try to please <br>Show me that you're into me <br>I don't rush, I move with ease <br>Tell me that you love me but I won't believe <br>Stand my ground by any means <br>Me, myself is all I need <br><br>2, 3, 4 boys <br>Boys, boys, boys, boys 2, 3, 4 <br>Boys, boys, boys, boys 2, 3, 4 <br><br>Hey <br>Hey]]></content><category term="Grace" label="Grace"/><category term="Boys Boys Boys" label="Boys Boys Boys"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nelly_Furtado/Behind_Your_Back/</id><title>Nelly Furtado - Behind Your Back - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nelly_Furtado/Behind_Your_Back/" title="Nelly Furtado - Behind Your Back - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been talking about you <br>Behind your back <br>I've been telling people <br>that I've heard things <br>If they ask <br>If we ease up and burning up <br>Well it's a fact <br>I've been talking about you <br>Every chance I had <br>Is nothing bad is all I have <br>It's just a chance <br>to say your name baby <br>Is nothing bad is just a chance <br>Wanna talk about you <br>Behind your back <br>I've been talking about you <br>Behind your back <br>I know that talking is cheap <br>But baby do the math <br>You were one in a million <br>And my whole heart's in half <br>Have is never conscious <br>it's a word I have <br>I've been telling all my stories <br>to anyone that asks <br>I've been serving them up <br>in a half-empty glass <br>Don't go thinking <br>I've lost all my class <br>When I'm talking about you <br>Is nothing bad is all I have <br>It's just a chance <br>to say your name baby <br>Is nothing bad is just a chance <br>Wanna talk about you <br>Behind your back <br>Is nothing bad is all I have <br>It's just a chance to say your name <br>Again baby just a chance <br>It's all I have <br>Wanna talk about you <br>Behind your back <br>No is nothing bad <br>Is all I have <br>I'm hoping you'd give me <br>just a chance <br>If you came back <br>Another chance <br>To stop talking about you <br>Behind your back]]></content><category term="Nelly Furtado" label="Nelly Furtado"/><category term="Behind Your Back" label="Behind Your Back"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leikeli47/Girl_Gang/</id><title>Leikeli47 - Girl Gang - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leikeli47/Girl_Gang/" title="Leikeli47 - Girl Gang - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If you try to shut us down <br>We'll show you just how we get down <br>And just to even up the score <br>We're coming, kicking down your door <br><br>Y'all never played fair, so tell my why now should we care <br>Queen Bey told y'all a long time ago that we run the atmosphere <br>Did we build that Yeah Do we own that Yeah <br>We been in the studios, running playback <br>Shout out , the young gods <br>To all the G's like us, yeah, we go hard <br>See, this is how it feel to be a champion <br>We might fall down, but we never run <br>You wouldn't even what we overcome <br>Do you know all the shit we gotta overcome <br>But they ain't stopping nothing <br>T and my girls on top, straight stunting <br>And we abide by real strict codes <br>Hands of my ex and homies over hoes <br><br>If you try to shut us down <br>We'll show you just how we get down <br>And just to even up the score <br>We're coming, kicking down your door <br><br>We play our way, I'd rather be me <br>Do work all day, we don't see defeat <br>Did we fly that Yeah Can we buy that Yeah <br>We even running full court, making hella stacks Yeah <br>Shout out to Maya Moore, the young god <br>To all the girls like us, yeah, we go hard <br>See, this is how it feel to be a champion <br>We might fall down, but we never run <br>So proud of the shit that we overcome <br>Do you know all the shit we gotta overcome <br>We bow down to none, I wanna all my day one's <br>Time really does fly when you're having fun <br>But the party don't stop 'til we staring down the sun <br><br>If you try to shut us down <br>We'll show you just how we get down <br>And just to even up the score <br>We're coming, kicking down your door <br>If you try to shut us down <br>We'll show you just how we get down <br>And just to even up the score <br>We're coming, kicking down your door <br><br>Kick it, kick it <br>Kick it, kick it <br><br>If you try to shut us down <br>We'll show you just how we get down <br>And just to even up the score <br>We're coming, kicking down your door <br>If you try to shut us down <br>We'll show you just how we get down <br>And just to even up the score <br>We're coming, kicking down your door]]></content><category term="Leikeli47" label="Leikeli47"/><category term="Girl Gang" label="Girl Gang"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brooke_Fraser/St_Petersburg_IV_Fridays/</id><title>Brooke Fraser - St. Petersburg (IV Fridays) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brooke_Fraser/St_Petersburg_IV_Fridays/" title="Brooke Fraser - St. Petersburg (IV Fridays) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want to live in the element <br>I've spent my comfort and common sense <br>Have not imagened lost innocence <br><br>I'll bleed you dry, no I won't pretend <br>I'll be coming home but I don't know when <br><br>I've felt your fire, I've breathed your air <br>We turned and twisted, our bruises bare <br>I cursed the ground still I feel you everywhere <br><br>In a fickle world, there's no stubborn lung <br>I can feel your ghost, when will you give up <br>It's a funny thing I heard of once <br>The return of the prodigal son <br><br>The baby thrilled me, made me feel love <br>Flashes of myrrh and flames of wood <br>I don't feel guilty, maybe I should <br><br>In a fickle world, there's no stubborn lung <br>I can feel your ghost, when will you give up <br>It's a funny thing I heard of once <br>The return of the prodigal son <br><br>In a fickle world, there's no stubborn lung <br>I can feel your ghost, when will you give up <br>It's a funny thing I heard of once <br>The return of the prodigal son <br><br>I saw the painty St Petersberg <br>Repressed depiction of a return <br>I am the oil and pigment mixed <br>And I know nothing but I know this <br>I've been lost a long time in my head <br>I've followed all the signs but I was misled <br>I'll be coming home but I don't know when]]></content><category term="Brooke Fraser" label="Brooke Fraser"/><category term="St. Petersburg (IV Fridays)" label="St. Petersburg (IV Fridays)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon/Tired_Of_Talking/</id><title>Leon - Tired Of Talking - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon/Tired_Of_Talking/" title="Leon - Tired Of Talking - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do you sometimes let your hand slip away <br>Something just feels different about you babe <br>Don't wanna hear about your crazy drunk night out <br>I don't believe that you just passed out on the couch <br>I can see it, something in the way you move <br>You're acting like there's something left to prove <br>And all these lies they keep on slippin' out <br>I said I don't believe that you just passed out on the couch <br><br>On and on and on it goes <br>On and on and on it goes <br><br>Cause I've been nothing but good to you <br>Your howlin' into the night won't do <br>I'm tired of talking, talking, talking, talking <br>I've been nothing but good to you <br><br>Every moment my heart went black and cold <br>Nothing stings as much like never knowing <br>What you've been up to, whose bed you're crashing now <br>I wanna get rid of the feeling, turn it all around <br><br>Cause I've been nothing but good to you <br>Your howlin' into the night won't do <br>I'm tired of talking, talking, talking, talking <br>I've been nothing but good to you <br><br>Get out the door and disappear <br>When you get home I won't be here <br>Don't act surprised as if you cared <br>Don't even bother cause <br><br>Cause I've been nothing but good to you <br>Your howlin' into the night won't do <br>I'm tired of talking, talking, talking, talking <br>I've been nothing but good to you]]></content><category term="Leon" label="Leon"/><category term="Tired Of Talking" label="Tired Of Talking"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kloe/Liability/</id><title>Kloe - Liability - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kloe/Liability/" title="Kloe - Liability - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1, 2, 3, go <br><br>Wasn't looking for a salutation in your hip gyration <br>But the gear's amazing <br>Really sorry, I forgot your name <br>You think it's a such a shame <br>That I play the same game <br>I said I would never fuck him over, I did <br>Would've done the same if I were sober <br>Now you know, know <br><br>I said, I said, I'm sorry <br>For playing with his sanity <br>Somebody should have warned him <br>To stay away from girls like me, but <br><br>Oh baby if you want crazy <br>All eyes on me, all eyes on me, eh <br>No way, nobody can save me <br>All eyes on me, all eyes on me <br>I'm a liability, liability <br>Liability, liability <br>Oh baby if you want crazy <br>All eyes on me, all eyes on me, eh <br>All eyes on me, all eyes on me, eh, eh <br><br>He was talking but his youth evaded him <br>Have a band that's playing my ex-boyfriend <br>Now he's acting like he saw the signs <br>And he got a peace of mind <br>But he wants me this time <br><br>I said, I said, I'm sorry <br>For playing with his sanity <br>Somebody should have warned him <br>To stay away from girls like me, but <br><br>Oh baby if you want crazy <br>All eyes on me, all eyes on me, eh <br>No way, nobody can save me <br>All eyes on me, all eyes on me <br>I'm a liability, liability <br>Liability, liability <br>Oh baby if you want crazy <br>All eyes on me, all eyes on me, eh <br><br>All eyes on me, all eyes on me, eh <br>All eyes on me, all eyes on me, eh <br>All eyes on me, all eyes on me, eh <br>All eyes on me, all eyes on me, eh <br><br>Oh baby if you want crazy <br>All eyes on me, all eyes on me, eh <br>No way, nobody can save me <br>All eyes on me, all eyes on me <br>I'm a liability, liability <br>Liability, liability <br>Oh baby if you want crazy <br>All eyes on me, all eyes on me, eh]]></content><category term="Kloe" label="Kloe"/><category term="Liability" label="Liability"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Venior/Sugar_Rush/</id><title>Venior - Sugar Rush - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Venior/Sugar_Rush/" title="Venior - Sugar Rush - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know you do I know you <br>Think I saw you nahaha <br>Do I want you I do want you <br>Hashtag glorified douchebag <br>Don't know why, but you give me a hint of ADD <br>Can't see clearly <br>When you're near me <br>When you're near me <br><br>I like the way, like, like the way <br>I like the way you annoy me <br>I like the way, like, like the way <br>I like the way you destroy me <br><br>Sugar rush <br>From the tip of my tongue to the soles of my feet <br>It's bittersweet <br>Let the smoke fill my lungs bring the taste of the heat <br>Give me all <br>Give me more, more, more than I can handle <br>Sugar rush <br>From the soles of my feet to the tip of my tongue <br><br>You're my sugar rush <br>You're my sugar rush <br>You're my sugar, sugar, sugar, sugar rush <br>You're my sugar rush <br>I can't get enough <br>You're my sugar, sugar, sugar, sugar rush <br><br>Is it over when it's over <br>In the shower nahaha <br>Think it over, starting over <br>In the morning hahaha <br>Cut to the chase it's like a turtle race <br>I'm the rabbit, you're the cake <br>I'm the rabbit, you're the cake <br><br>I like the way, like, like the way <br>I like the way you annoy me <br>I like the way, like, like the way <br>I like the way you destroy me <br><br>Sugar rush <br>From the tip of my tongue to the soles of my feet <br>It's bittersweet <br>Let the smoke fill my lungs bring the taste of the heat <br>Give me all <br>Give me more, more, more than I can handle <br>Sugar rush <br>From the soles of my feet to the tip of my tongue <br><br>You're my sugar rush <br>You're my sugar rush <br>You're my sugar, sugar, sugar, sugar rush <br>You're my sugar rush <br>I can't get enough <br>Want my sugar, sugar, sugar, sugar rush <br><br>Do I know you <br>Think it over <br>When it's over <br>Do I want you <br>Think I want you <br>Is it over <br>I don't know you <br>Starting over <br>Uh <br><br>Sugar rush <br>From the tip of my tongue to the soles of my feet <br>It's bittersweet <br>Let the smoke fill my lungs bring the taste of the heat <br>Give me all <br>Give me more, more, more than I can handle <br>Sugar rush <br>From the soles of my feet to the tip of my tongue <br>I like the way, like, like the way <br>Iike the way you annoy me annoy me <br>I like the way, like, like the way like the way <br>I like the way you destroy me destroy me <br>I like the way, like, like the way <br>Like the way you annoy me <br>Sugar rush <br>From the soles of my feet to the tip of my tongue]]></content><category term="Venior" label="Venior"/><category term="Sugar Rush" label="Sugar Rush"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michelle_Treacy/Armageddon/</id><title>Michelle Treacy - Armageddon - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michelle_Treacy/Armageddon/" title="Michelle Treacy - Armageddon - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Uhh whooooo Uhh whooooo <br>Uhh whooooo Uhh whooooo <br>Uhh whooooo Uhh whooooo <br><br>You said way too many words <br>Dripping like poison on your tongue <br>You've been digging in the dirt <br>Now your final day has come <br><br>Diamonds in your eyes <br>Don't even apologize <br>Because all of the hurt <br>Is a blaze you can't out run <br><br>Boy I know that you're regrettin it <br>I see that you ain't gettin it <br>We've come to the end <br>No more lyin, no more beggin <br><br>Armageddon, armageddon <br>I'm gonna blow this up, this up <br>You say it's gonna be different this time <br>Boy, I don't give uh, I don't give uh <br><br>Armageddon <br>Uhh whooooo Uhh whooooo Uhh whooooo <br>Armageddon, armageddon <br>Uhh whooooo Uhh whooooo Uhh whooooo <br>Chorus end <br><br>Now I'm tearing down the walls <br>Destroying everything we had <br>Make you stand and watch it fall <br>With my knife deep in your back <br><br>No tears, no more lies <br>Your sins burned alive <br>Gonna sweep away it all <br>Like dust into the cracks <br><br>Boy I think you're forgettin it <br>You made the bed you're lying in <br>We've come to the end <br>Ain't no use in you denying <br><br>Armageddon, armageddon <br>I'm gonna blow this up, this up <br>You say it's gonna be different this time <br>Boy, I don't give uh, I don't give uh <br><br>Barely audible <br>Everything we had in flames <br>Armageddon <br>Everything we had in flames <br><br>Everything we had in flames <br>It's gone, it's gone <br>The only thing left is your shame <br>So long, so long, so long <br><br>Armageddon, armageddon <br>I'm gonna blow this up, this up <br>You say it's gonna be different this time <br>Boy, I don't give uh, I don't give uh]]></content><category term="Michelle Treacy" label="Michelle Treacy"/><category term="Armageddon" label="Armageddon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frankie/Gold/</id><title>Frankie - Gold - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frankie/Gold/" title="Frankie - Gold - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Money is a friend I trust, and I don't know why <br>You've never been too good to me, when you come around 'round 'round 'round <br>Shifting eyes never locked tight with your crooked smile <br>Haunting me I can't deny that we're going down down down down <br><br>Hit the beat, hit the beat harder <br>Making me, making me stronger <br>Tell me tell me do you feel the mist cause it's about to pour <br><br>Give me all your gold, now it's mine to hold <br>Let's not play the game, show 'em what's at stake <br>Everything we want is ours to take <br>Cause baby if it glows, then I'ma take it all <br>Gonna make this mine, grab it for all time <br>Try to bring us down, we only fly <br><br>Power has its hands on you, and I don't know why <br>I light it up with energy, burn it to the ground ground ground ground <br>Take me back to good old days, before we ever had a taste <br>When you, had nothing to lose <br><br>Hit the beat, hit the beat harder <br>Making me, making me stronger <br>Tell me tell me do you feel the mist cause it's about to pour <br><br>Give me all your gold, now it's mine to hold <br>Let's not play the game, show 'em what's at stake <br>Everything we want is ours to take <br>Cause baby if it glows, then I'ma take it all <br>Gonna make this mine, grab it for all time <br>Try to bring us down, we only fly <br><br>Cause it's raining gold x6 <br><br>Hit the beat <br>Making me <br>Hit the beat <br>Making me <br><br>Hit the beat, hit the beat harder <br>Making me, making me stronger <br>Tell me tell me do you feel the mist, cause it's about to pour <br><br>Give me all your gold, now it's mine to hold <br>Let's not play the game, show 'em what's at stake <br>Everything we want is ours to take <br>Cause baby if it glows, then I'ma take it all <br>Gonna make this mine, grab it for all time <br>Try to bring us down, we only fly <br><br>Cause it's raining gold x6]]></content><category term="Frankie" label="Frankie"/><category term="Gold" label="Gold"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pink/Try/</id><title>Pink - Try - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pink/Try/" title="Pink - Try - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh oh <br>Ever wonder about <br>what he's doing <br>How it all turned to lies <br>Sometimes I think that it's better <br>to never ask why <br>Where there is desire <br>There is gonna be a flame <br>Where there is a flame <br>Someone's bound to get burned <br>But just because it burns <br>Doesn't mean you're gonna die <br>You've gotta get up and try <br>and try and try <br>Gotta get up and try <br>and try and try <br>You gotta get up and try <br>and try and try <br>Eh eh eh <br>Funny how the heart <br>can be deceiving <br>More than just a couple times <br>Why do we fall in love so easy <br>Even when it's not right <br>Where there is desire <br>There is gonna be a flame <br>Where there is a flame <br>Someone's bound to get burned <br>But just because it burns <br>Doesn't mean you're gonna die <br>You've gotta get up and try <br>and try and try <br>Gotta get up and try <br>and try and try <br>You gotta get up and try <br>and try and try <br>Ever worry that it might be ruined <br>And does it make you wanna cry <br>When you're out there doing <br>what you're doing <br>Are you just getting by <br>Tell me are you just getting by by by <br>Where there is desire <br>There is gonna be a flame <br>Where there is a flame <br>Someone's bound to get burned <br>But just because it burns <br>Doesn't mean you're gonna die <br>You've gotta get up and try <br>and try and try <br>Gotta get up and try <br>and try and try <br>You gotta get up and try <br>and try and try <br>Gotta get up and try <br>and try and try <br>Gotta get up and try <br>and try and try <br>You gotta get up and try <br>and try and try <br>Gotta get up and try <br>and try and try <br>You gotta get up and try <br>and try and try <br>Gotta get up and try <br>and try and try <br>]]></content><category term="Pink" label="Pink"/><category term="Try" label="Try"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fifth_Harmony/Gonna_Get_Better/</id><title>Fifth Harmony - Gonna Get Better - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fifth_Harmony/Gonna_Get_Better/" title="Fifth Harmony - Gonna Get Better - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not gonna leave you now <br>Oh I know it's gon' get better <br>I'm not gonna leave you now <br>Oh I know it's gon' get better <br>I won't leave you for a money man <br>No matter what we go through <br>I'm not gonna leave you now <br>Oh I know it's gon' get better <br>I don't know <br>why you always think that I <br>Always think I'm unsatisfied <br>That I'm tempted by kings <br>with the finest of things <br>But you know <br>that ain't got no truth <br>I don't know <br>why you always think that I'm <br>Unhappy with our paradise <br>That I'm wanting the trees <br>that are growing the green <br>But you know all <br>that I want is you <br>I thought you know me better babe <br>Than to think <br>that I would do you that way <br>I don't need a house <br>in the hills and I <br>I don't need a man like Midas <br>I thought you knew me better babe <br>Than to think <br>that I would do you that way <br>I don't need a house <br>and a Benz I just <br>I just want your love <br>I'm not gonna leave you now <br>Oh I know it's gon' get better <br>I'm not gonna leave you now <br>Oh I know it's gon' get better <br>I won't leave you for a money man <br>No matter what we go through <br>I'm not gonna leave you now <br>Oh I know it's gon' get better <br>I don't know <br>why you always think that I <br>Always think I'm unsatisfied <br>That I'm tempted by kings <br>with the finest of things <br>But you know <br>that ain't got no truth <br>I don't know <br>why you always think that I'm <br>Unhappy with our paradise <br>That I'm wanting the trees <br>that are growing the green <br>But you know all <br>that I want is you <br>I thought you know me better babe <br>Than to think <br>that I would do you that way <br>I don't need a house <br>in the hills and I <br>I don't need a man like Midas <br>I thought you knew me better babe <br>Than to think <br>that I would do you that way <br>I don't need a house <br>and a Benz I just <br>I just want your love <br>I'm not gonna leave you now <br>Oh I know it's gon' get better <br>I'm not gonna leave you now <br>Oh I know it's gon' get better <br>I won't leave you for a money man <br>No matter what we go through <br>I'm not gonna leave you now <br>Oh I know it's gon' get better <br>Yeah yeah yeah hey <br>Yeah yeah yeah <br>Yeah yeah yeah no no <br>Yeah yeah yeah woo <br>I'm not gonna leave you now <br>Oh I know it's gon' get better <br>I'm not gonna leave you now <br>Oh I know it's gon' get better <br>I won't leave you for a money man <br>No matter what we go through <br>I'm not gonna leave you now <br>Oh I know it's gon' get better <br>I'm not gonna leave you now <br>Oh I know it's gon' get better <br>I'm not gonna leave you now <br>Oh I know it's gon' get better <br>I won't leave you for a money man <br>No matter what we go through <br>I'm not gonna leave you now <br>Oh I know it's gon' get better <br>]]></content><category term="Fifth Harmony" label="Fifth Harmony"/><category term="Gonna Get Better" label="Gonna Get Better"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jessica_Mauboy/What_Happened_To_Us_Feat_Jay_Sean/</id><title>Jessica Mauboy - What Happened To Us (Feat. Jay Sean) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jessica_Mauboy/What_Happened_To_Us_Feat_Jay_Sean/" title="Jessica Mauboy - What Happened To Us (Feat. Jay Sean) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I feel you <br>even though were apart <br>And without you <br>There's a hole in my heart <br>Oh baby baby <br>though I tried I just can't adjust <br>Oh boy what happened to us <br>happened to us happened to us <br>We were in love <br>We both felt the same <br>The good thing that <br>We had oh boy was insane <br>We had a bond <br>that would never break <br>why we let it go oh <br>We used to stay up all night long <br>Kissing to our favorite songs <br>Just tell me <br>where all went wrong <br>that's what I got to know oh <br>Cuz I feel you even though <br>We're apart and without you <br>There's a hole in my heart <br>oh baby baby though <br>I tried I just can't adjust <br>oh boy what happened to us <br>happened to us <br>Thought that I could get over you <br>Oh but baby <br>that is so far from true <br>oh baby baby <br>Got something <br>I want to discuss <br>Oh boy what happened to us <br>happened to us happened to us <br>I think that we oughta work it out <br>like air your love <br>I can't live without <br>So have mercy <br>Don't leave me in doubt <br>Saying I love <br>Still burns Still burns Still burns <br>I try to go my separate way <br>At first I thought it was okay <br>I miss you more with each day <br>So to you I turn <br>Cuz I feel you even though <br>We're apart and without you <br>There's a hole in my heart <br>oh baby baby though <br>I tried I just can't adjust <br>oh boy what happened to us <br>happened to us <br>Thought that I could get over you <br>Oh but baby <br>That is so far from true <br>oh baby baby <br>Got something <br>I want to discuss <br>Oh boy what happened to us <br>happened to us happened to us <br>I know that you saw me <br>with someone else <br>Believe me <br>I'm all by myself <br>Cuz I feel you even though <br>We're apart and without you <br>There's a hole in my heart <br>oh baby baby though <br>I tried I just can't adjust <br>oh boy what happened to us <br>happened to us <br>Thought that I could get over you <br>Oh but baby <br>That is so far from true <br>oh baby baby <br>Got something <br>I want to discuss <br>Oh boy what happened to us <br>happened to us happened to us <br>Cuz I feel you even though <br>We're apart and without you <br>There's a hole in my heart <br>oh baby baby though <br>I tried I just can't adjust <br>oh boy what happened to us <br>happened to us <br>What happened to us <br>oh boy what happened to us <br>happened to us]]></content><category term="Jessica Mauboy" label="Jessica Mauboy"/><category term="What Happened To Us (Feat. Jay Sean)" label="What Happened To Us (Feat. Jay Sean)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rita_Ora/Radioactive/</id><title>Rita Ora - Radioactive - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rita_Ora/Radioactive/" title="Rita Ora - Radioactive - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Palms to the sky <br>We unite <br>I feel it I feel it <br>I feel it feel feel it <br>We rise tonight <br>I'm checking you out <br>in your sweet desire <br>I'm coming over to make you mine <br>It's a crime boy you're so fine <br>I'm taking you out boy <br>It's a green light <br>I'm glad you came over <br>it was about time <br>It feels right <br>Boy You're so fine <br>This goes radioactive <br>Drop the ball <br>Let me feel the beat <br>This goes radioactive <br>Drop the ball <br>Let me feel the beat <br>Palms to the sky <br>You know I feel it <br>I feel it I feel it feel feel it <br>We rise tonight <br>Palms to the sky <br>We unite I feel it <br>I feel it I feel it feel feel it <br>We rise tonight <br>Moving on me <br>as the world ends <br>This nuclear heat <br>is a beautiful air <br>You might not live to tell <br>This goes radioactive <br>Drop the ball <br>Let me feel the beat <br>This goes radioactive <br>Drop the ball <br>Let me feel the beat <br>Palms to the sky <br>You know I feel it <br>I feel it I feel it feel feel it <br>We rise tonight <br>Palms to the sky <br>We unite I feel it <br>I feel it I feel it feel feel it <br>We rise tonight <br>Palms to the sky <br>You and I <br>Palms to the sky <br>You and I <br>Palms to the sky <br>You and I <br>We rise tonight <br>Palms to the sky <br>You know I feel it <br>I feel it I feel it feel feel it <br>We rise tonight <br>Palms to the sky <br>We unite I feel it <br>I feel it I feel it feel feel it <br>We rise tonight <br>We unite you and I <br>are right tonight <br>We unite you and I <br>are right tonight <br>We unite you and I <br>are right tonight <br>you and I are right tonight]]></content><category term="Rita Ora" label="Rita Ora"/><category term="Radioactive" label="Radioactive"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meghan_Trainor/Woman_Up/</id><title>Meghan Trainor - Woman Up - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meghan_Trainor/Woman_Up/" title="Meghan Trainor - Woman Up - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Woman up <br>Woman up <br>Woman up, up <br>Woman up <br>Woman up, up <br>Woman up, up, up, up, up <br><br>Put your favorite heels on <br>'Cause they make you feel strong <br>When you're lookin' good <br>You know you're gonna have a good time <br>Don't forget mascara <br>And to keep your head up <br>Like Madonna would <br>Rub her lipstick redder than wine <br><br>So let's go <br>Roll your bumper and whine slow <br>Show them you can shine, glow <br>'Cause you got the light now <br>You got the light now, ow <br><br>All my girls raise your hand <br>If you don't need a man <br>'Cause you're more than good enough <br>You gotta woman up, woman up <br>All my girls, we show, we groove <br>Just make them remember you <br>This one for all my girls <br>My girls who woman up, woman up <br><br>Mmhm <br>Woman up, woman up <br>Mwuah <br>Woman up, woman up <br>Mmhm <br>Woman up, woman up <br>Mwuah <br><br>When you wear your hair down <br>It's like you're wearing your crown <br>Wave to the crowd <br>And give them all a wink 'cause you're fine <br><br>So let's go <br>Roll your bumper and whine slow <br>Show them you can shine, glow <br>'Cause you got the light now, you got the light now <br>So let's go <br>Roll your bumper and whine slow <br>Show them you can shine, glow <br>'Cause you got the light now <br>You got the light now, ow <br><br>All my girls raise your hand <br>If you don't need a man <br>'Cause you're more than good enough <br>You gotta woman up, woman up <br><br>All my girls, we show, we groove <br>Just make them remember you <br>This one for all my girls <br>My girls who woman up, woman up <br><br>Mmhm <br>Woman up, woman up <br>Mwuah <br>Woman up, woman up <br>Mmhm <br>Woman up, woman up <br>Mwuah <br><br>Hey <br>All my girls raise your hand raise your hand <br>If you don't need a man time to take a stand, mhm <br>Woman up, woman up <br>Don't matter what you've been through no <br>Just make them remember you remember you, all my girls <br>Woman up, woman up <br><br>So let's go <br>Roll your bumper and whine slow <br>Show them you can shine, glow <br>'Cause you got the light now <br>You got the light now, <br>So ladies let's go <br>Roll your bumper and whine slow <br>Show them you can shine, glow <br>'Cause you got the light now <br>You got the light now <br><br>All my girls raise your hand <br>If you don't need a man <br>'Cause you're more than good enough <br>You gotta woman up, woman up <br>All my girls, we show, we groove <br>Just make them remember you <br>This one for all my girls <br>My girls who woman up, woman up <br>All my girls raise your hand <br>If you don't need a man <br>'Cause you're more than good enough <br>You gotta woman up, woman up <br>All my girls, we show, we groove <br>Just make them remember you <br>This one for all my girls <br><br>My girls who woman up, woman up]]></content><category term="Meghan Trainor" label="Meghan Trainor"/><category term="Woman Up" label="Woman Up"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Little_Mix/OMG/</id><title>Little Mix - OMG - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:09:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:09:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Little_Mix/OMG/" title="Little Mix - OMG - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh my gosh, I did it again <br>I don't even know how I did that <br>Need a round of applause <br>Just like cream to a kitty cat <br>Lining up at the door <br>Maybe it's the way I work it <br>My beach bring the boys to the shore <br>Maybe it's the way I flirt <br>That they get hurt, they just don't learn <br>I don't even know <br>Why they fall like dominoes <br>Oh my gosh, I did it again <br>He said I broke his heart, it keeps happening <br>I don't know why they always fall for me <br>Why they always fall for <br>Oh my gosh, I did it again <br>He said I broke his heart, it keeps happening <br>I don't know why they always fall for me <br>Why they always fall for <br>Them boys getting too ambitious <br>They should win an award <br>Got twenty more, plenty more fishes <br>But I still come first <br>Maybe I'm superstitious <br>I want to break this curse <br>They say they want to lay it on me <br>I'm their one and only girl <br>I don't even know <br>Why they fall like dominoes <br>Oh my gosh, I did it again <br>He said I broke his heart, it keeps happening <br>I don't know why they always fall for me <br>Why they always fall for <br>Oh my gosh, I did it again <br>He said I broke his heart, it keeps happening <br>I don't know why they always fall for me <br>Why they always fall for <br>Oh my gosh, I think I did it again <br>Broke his heart, why does this keep happening <br>Don't come crying when I say it's the end <br>I'm ringing the alarm, boy you better run on <br>Oh my gosh, I did it again <br>He said I broke his heart, it keeps happening <br>I don't know why they always fall for me <br>Why they always fall for <br>Oh my gosh <br>Oh my, oh my, oh oh oh <br>Oh my gosh <br>Oh my, oh my, oh oh oh <br>Oh my gosh]]></content><category term="Little Mix" label="Little Mix"/><category term="OMG" label="OMG"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마이큐/e_v_e_r_Y_d_a_y/</id><title>마이큐 - e v e r Y d a y - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:10:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:10:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B4%ED%81%90/e_v_e_r_Y_d_a_y/" title="마이큐 - e v e r Y d a y - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[또 하루가 저물어가네 <br>해질녘은 아름다운데 <br>나는 오늘밤도 <br>현실에 기대어 <br>사랑 노랠 불러 <br>오늘은 견딜 만해 <br>엄마 아빠에게 미안해 <br>생각하면 나도 모르게 <br>잘 해내야만 해 <br>잘 해내야만 해 <br>사실은 두려워 <br>비틀 비틀거리네 <br>꿈꾸는 건 자유잖아 <br>너 멈추지마 <br>원 없이 표현해도 돼 <br>너의 세상 <br>오늘이 마지막이라는 <br>생각해 봐 <br>Baby 넌 잘하고 있어 <br>네가 사는 세상에서 <br>최선을 다해 <br>꿈과 현실이 교차돼 <br>버리는 순간 <br>숨겼던 날개를 펼쳐봐 <br>넌 이제 하늘을 날 수 있어 <br>Won't you fly away <br>말은 참 많은 것 같은데 <br>모두 날 위한다 하지만 <br>아무 의미 없어 <br>아무 의미 없어 <br>혼자 걷고 있어 <br>내일은 또 어떨까 <br>Just another day <br>꿈꾸는 건 자유잖아 <br>너 멈추지마 <br>원 없이 표현해도 돼 <br>너의 세상 <br>오늘이 마지막이라는 <br>생각해 봐 <br>Baby 넌 잘하고 있어 <br>네가 사는 세상에서 <br>최선을 다해 <br>꿈과 현실이 교차돼 <br>버리는 순간 <br>숨겼던 날개를 펼쳐봐 <br>넌 이제 하늘을 날 수 있어 <br>Won't you fly away <br>I really 원해 원해 <br>원해 왔었다는 걸 <br>I really 원해 원해 <br>원해 왔었다는 걸 <br>I really 원해 원해 <br>원해 왔었다는 걸 <br>네가 좀 알았으면 해 <br>everYday <br>everYday <br>I really 원해 원해 <br>원해 왔었다는 걸 <br>everYday <br>everYday <br>]]></content><category term="마이큐" label="마이큐"/><category term="e v e r Y d a y" label="e v e r Y d a y"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동요나라/피노키오/</id><title>동요나라 - 피노키오 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:12:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:12:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EB%82%98%EB%9D%BC/%ED%94%BC%EB%85%B8%ED%82%A4%EC%98%A4/" title="동요나라 - 피노키오 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꼭두각시 인형 피노키오 <br>나는 네가 좋구나 <br>파란 머리 천사 만날 때는 <br>나도 데려가 주렴 <br><br>피아노 치고 <br>미술도 하고 <br>영어도 하면 바쁜데 <br><br>너는 언제나 <br>공부를 하니? <br>말썽장이 피노키오야 <br><br>우리 아빠 꿈 속에 <br>오늘 밤에 나타나 <br>내 얘기 좀 잘해 줄수 없겠니? <br>먹고 싶은 것이랑 <br>놀고 싶은 것이랑 <br>모두 모두 할 수 있게 해 줄래? <br><br><br>꼭두각시 인형 피노키오 <br>나는 네가 좋구나 <br>장난감의 나라 지날 때는 <br>나도 데려가 주렴 <br><br>숙제도 많고 <br>시험도 많고 <br>할일도 많아 바쁜데 <br><br>너는 어째서 <br>놀기만 하니? <br>청개구리 피노키오야 <br><br>우리 엄마 꿈 속에 <br>오늘 밤에 나타나 <br>내 얘기 좀 잘해 줄 수 없겠니? <br><br>먹지마라 살찐다 <br>하지마라 나쁘다 <br>그런 말 좀 하지 않게 해줄래? <br><br><br>꼭두각시 인형 피노키오 <br>나는 네가 좋구나 <br><br>파란 머리 천사 만날 때는 <br>나도 데려가 주렴 <br><br>학교 다니고 <br>학원 다니고 <br>독서실 가면 바쁜데 <br><br>너는 어째서 <br>게으름 피니? <br>제페토의 피노키오야 <br><br>엄마 아빠 꿈 속에 <br>오늘 밤에 나타나 <br>내 얘기 좀 잘해 줄 수 없겠니? <br>피노 키오 줄 타기 <br>꼭두 각시 줄 타기 <br><br>그런 아이 되지 않게 해줄래? <br><br>그런 아이 되지 않게 해줄래?]]></content><category term="동요나라" label="동요나라"/><category term="피노키오" label="피노키오"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정선경/복음의_기도/</id><title>정선경 - 복음의 기도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:13:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:13:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%84%A0%EA%B2%BD/%EB%B3%B5%EC%9D%8C%EC%9D%98_%EA%B8%B0%EB%8F%84/" title="정선경 - 복음의 기도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나의 주님께 기도 드리네 <br>오직 주의 뜻 이뤄지길 <br>나의 뜻보다 주 뜻 의지해 <br>우리 맘 주님께 드려 <br>나의 주님께 기도 드리네 <br>오직 주의 뜻 이뤄지길 <br>나의 뜻보다 주 뜻 의지해 <br>우리 맘 주님께 드려 <br>나를 향하신 <br>주님 뜻 기도해 <br>오늘 이시간 이곳에 <br>주의 영이 임하시고 <br>나의 마음을 <br>주님으로 채우니 <br>주의 사랑을 나 전하리 <br>나의 주님께 기도 드리네 <br>오직 주의 뜻 이뤄지길 <br>나의 뜻보다 주 뜻 의지해 <br>우리 맘 주님께 드려 <br>나를 향하신 <br>주님 뜻 기도해 <br>오늘 이시간 이곳에 <br>주의 영이 임하시고 <br>나의 마음을 <br>주님으로 채우니 <br>주의 사랑을 나 전하리 <br>나를 향하신 <br>주님 뜻 기도해 <br>오늘 이시간 이곳에 <br>마라나타 주 오소서 <br>나의 마음을 <br>주님으로 채우니 <br>주의 사랑을 나 전하리 <br>나를 향하신 <br>주님 뜻 기도해 <br>오늘 이시간 이곳에 <br>마라나타 주 오소서 <br>나의 마음을 <br>주님으로 채우니 <br>주의 사랑을 나 전하리 <br>주의 사랑을 나 전하리 <br>주의 사랑을 나 전하리 <br>]]></content><category term="정선경" label="정선경"/><category term="복음의 기도" label="복음의 기도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ricky_Blaze/Like_This_Feat_Sean_Paul/</id><title>Ricky Blaze - Like This (Feat. Sean Paul) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:13:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:13:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ricky_Blaze/Like_This_Feat_Sean_Paul/" title="Ricky Blaze - Like This (Feat. Sean Paul) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, <br>yeah, <br>yeah, <br>yeah, yeah, <br>oh, <br>oh <br><br>Do you know how it feels, <br>to wake up with someone that you love <br>It feels so real <br>my angel was sent from above <br>I like to see her smile <br>even when I look in her eyes <br>I get butterflies flies <br>I don't wanna change <br>I don't wanna change <br>I don't wanna change her love <br>I wanna change her last name, <br>give her mine, onto her <br>but feelings first baby girl you're my world <br>no other girl <br>I just wanna make this last forever <br><br>My queen she's next to me, <br>she's next to me, <br>I need <br>her loving feel <br>her loving feel <br>just stay right by my side <br>just you and I <br>just you and I <br>just you and I <br>just you and I <br><br>Baby girl you can tell your friends about us <br>no other girl <br>what's love if we don't fall in trust <br>I'm not trying to be the most perfect guy, <br>but do right in your eyes eyes, yeah <br>I know you're tired <br>I know you're tired <br>I know you're tired of the losers <br>But when love come my way, beggars can't be choosers <br>I just want to make you mine forever <br>ever, <br>ever, <br>ever, <br>forever <br><br>My queen she's next to me, <br>she's next to me, <br>I need <br>her loving feel <br>her loving feel <br>just stay right by my side <br>just you and I <br>just you and I <br>just you and I <br>just you and I <br><br>Little mama, you the, you the best 4X <br>Baby girl, you, you the best <br>Baby girl, you the, you the best <br><br>My Queen Oh <br><br>My queen she's next to me, <br>she's next to me, <br>I need <br>her loving feel <br>her loving feel <br>just stay right by my side <br>just you and I <br>just you and I <br>just you and I <br>just you and I <br><br>Just you and I <br>Forever <br>ever <br>ever <br>ever <br><br>oh <br>oh, oh <br>ohh <br>ohhhhh <br>just you and I <br>just you and I <br>just you and I]]></content><category term="Ricky Blaze" label="Ricky Blaze"/><category term="Like This (Feat. Sean Paul)" label="Like This (Feat. Sean Paul)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정연준_업타운/기도밖에_La_Oracion_Spanish_Ver_Feat_James_Zavaleta/</id><title>정연준 (업타운) - 기도밖에 La Oracion (Spanish Ver.) (Feat. James Zavaleta) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:13:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:13:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%97%B0%EC%A4%80_%EC%97%85%ED%83%80%EC%9A%B4/%EA%B8%B0%EB%8F%84%EB%B0%96%EC%97%90_La_Oracion_Spanish_Ver_Feat_James_Zavaleta/" title="정연준 (업타운) - 기도밖에 La Oracion (Spanish Ver.) (Feat. James Zavaleta) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[LA ORACION <br>LA ORACION <br>MI CORAZON QUEBRANTADO <br>ESCUCHA OH DIOS <br>PUES SOLO TU CONSUELO ME DAS <br>ERES MI ESCUDO Y MI SANADOR <br>BAJO DEL CIELO <br>GENTE QUE CONOZCO NUNCA <br>ENTENDERAN MI DOLOR <br>PUES SOLO TU CONTESTAS MI <br>ORACION ERES EL UNICO <br>A QUIEN ADORARE <br>TU ME GUIARAS A UN <br>LUGAR DE PAZ <br>PARA QUE YO TE <br>ADORE SIN SESAR <br>TU ME SOSTENDRAS Y EN T <br>ME APOYARE <br>TU ERES MI LUZ <br>EL CAMINO <br>TU ERES MI PAZ <br>TU ME GUIARAS <br>A UN LUGAR DE PAZ <br>DIOS Y MI REY <br>TOMA MI ADORACION <br>TU ME SOSTENDRAS <br>AUNQUE ESTOY LEJOS DE TI <br>MI ESPERANZA <br>ERES TU <br>EL CAMINO Y EL AMOR <br>LA ORACION <br>LA ORACION <br>MI CORAZON QUEBRANTADO <br>ESCUCHA OH DIOS <br>PUES SOLO TU <br>CONSUELO ME DAS <br>ERES MI ESCUDO Y SANADOR <br>]]></content><category term="정연준 (업타운)" label="정연준 (업타운)"/><category term="기도밖에 La Oracion (Spanish Ver.) (Feat. James Zavaleta)" label="기도밖에 La Oracion (Spanish Ver.) (Feat. James Zavaleta)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/라시드_LASID/Journey_Vocal_승현/</id><title>라시드 (LASID) - Journey (Vocal 승현) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:13:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:13:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9D%BC%EC%8B%9C%EB%93%9C_LASID/Journey_Vocal_%EC%8A%B9%ED%98%84/" title="라시드 (LASID) - Journey (Vocal 승현) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 처음 눈을 떴을 때 <br>깊은 어둠 속에 있어 <br>나 홀로 길을 헤멜 때 <br>한 줄기 빛이 없어 <br>모래 사막 눈 덮인 산 <br>거친 바다 모두 지나 <br>난 그 빛을 찾아 떠나네 <br>Journey <br>이제 여행을 떠나네 <br>한 줄기 빛을 찾아 <br>한 걸음 발을 떼어 <br>Journey <br>이 여행이 끝나는 날 <br>모든 어둠의 끝에 <br>빛을 보게 되리라 <br>Journey <br>이 멀고 험한 길에서 <br>무거워진 내 발걸음 <br>날 붙잡고 짖눌려진 채 <br>일어설 수 없게 했어 <br>차가웁게 굳어갈 때 <br>따스하게 감싸 주던 <br>난 그 빛에 다시 또 걷네 <br>Journey <br>이제 여행을 떠나네 <br>한 줄기 빛을 찾아 <br>한 걸음 발을 떼어 <br>Journey <br>이 여행이 끝나는 날 <br>모든 어둠의 끝에 <br>빛을 보게 되리라 <br>Journey <br>]]></content><category term="라시드 (LASID)" label="라시드 (LASID)"/><category term="Journey (Vocal 승현)" label="Journey (Vocal 승현)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/라시드_LASID/Journey_Vocal_이보희/</id><title>라시드 (LASID) - Journey (Vocal 이보희) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:13:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:13:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9D%BC%EC%8B%9C%EB%93%9C_LASID/Journey_Vocal_%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%B4%ED%9D%AC/" title="라시드 (LASID) - Journey (Vocal 이보희) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 처음 눈을 떴을 때 <br>깊은 어둠 속에 있어 <br>나 홀로 길을 헤멜 때 <br>한 줄기 빛이 없어 <br>모래 사막 눈 덮인 산 <br>거친 바다 모두 지나 <br>난 그 빛을 찾아 떠나네 <br>Journey <br>이제 여행을 떠나네 <br>한 줄기 빛을 찾아 <br>한 걸음 발을 떼어 <br>Journey <br>이 여행이 끝나는 날 <br>모든 어둠의 끝에 <br>빛을 보게 되리라 <br>Journey <br>이 멀고 험한 길에서 <br>무거워진 내 발걸음 <br>날 붙잡고 짖눌려진 채 <br>일어설 수 없게 했어 <br>차가웁게 굳어갈 때 <br>따스하게 감싸 주던 <br>난 그 빛에 다시 또 걷네 <br>Journey <br>이제 여행을 떠나네 <br>한 줄기 빛을 찾아 <br>한 걸음 발을 떼어 <br>Journey <br>이 여행이 끝나는 날 <br>모든 어둠의 끝에 <br>빛을 보게 되리라 <br>Journey <br>]]></content><category term="라시드 (LASID)" label="라시드 (LASID)"/><category term="Journey (Vocal 이보희)" label="Journey (Vocal 이보희)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/라시드_LASID/Journey_Vocal_윤현준/</id><title>라시드 (LASID) - Journey (Vocal 윤현준) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:13:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:13:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9D%BC%EC%8B%9C%EB%93%9C_LASID/Journey_Vocal_%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%84%EC%A4%80/" title="라시드 (LASID) - Journey (Vocal 윤현준) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 처음 눈을 떴을 때 <br>깊은 어둠 속에 있어 <br>나 홀로 길을 헤멜 때 <br>한 줄기 빛이 없어 <br>모래 사막 눈 덮인 산 <br>거친 바다 모두 지나 <br>난 그 빛을 찾아 떠나네 <br>Journey <br>이제 여행을 떠나네 <br>한 줄기 빛을 찾아 <br>한 걸음 발을 떼어 <br>Journey <br>이 여행이 끝나는 날 <br>모든 어둠의 끝에 <br>빛을 보게 되리라 <br>Journey <br>이 멀고 험한 길에서 <br>무거워진 내 발걸음 <br>날 붙잡고 짖눌려진 채 <br>일어설 수 없게 했어 <br>차가웁게 굳어갈 때 <br>따스하게 감싸 주던 <br>난 그 빛에 다시 또 걷네 <br>Journey <br>이제 여행을 떠나네 <br>한 줄기 빛을 찾아 <br>한 걸음 발을 떼어 <br>Journey <br>이 여행이 끝나는 날 <br>모든 어둠의 끝에 <br>빛을 보게 되리라 <br>Journey <br>Journey <br>Journey <br>]]></content><category term="라시드 (LASID)" label="라시드 (LASID)"/><category term="Journey (Vocal 윤현준)" label="Journey (Vocal 윤현준)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/라시드_LASID/Journey_Vocal_RuBic/</id><title>라시드 (LASID) - Journey (Vocal RuBic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:13:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:13:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9D%BC%EC%8B%9C%EB%93%9C_LASID/Journey_Vocal_RuBic/" title="라시드 (LASID) - Journey (Vocal RuBic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 처음 눈을 떴을 때 <br>깊은 어둠 속에 있어 <br>나 홀로 길을 헤멜 때 <br>한 줄기 빛이 없어 <br>모래 사막 눈 덮인 산 <br>거친 바다 모두 지나 <br>난 그 빛을 찾아 떠나네 <br>Journey <br>이제 여행을 떠나네 <br>한 줄기 빛을 찾아 <br>한 걸음 발을 떼어 <br>Journey <br>이 여행이 끝나는 날 <br>모든 어둠의 끝에 <br>빛을 보게 되리라 <br>Journey <br>이 멀고 험한 길에서 <br>무거워진 내 발걸음 <br>날 붙잡고 짖눌려진 채 <br>일어설 수 없게 했어 <br>차가웁게 굳어갈 때 <br>따스하게 감싸 주던 <br>난 그 빛에 다시 또 걷네 <br>Journey <br>이제 여행을 떠나네 <br>한 줄기 빛을 찾아 <br>한 걸음 발을 떼어 <br>Journey <br>이 여행이 끝나는 날 <br>모든 어둠의 끝에 <br>빛을 보게 되리라 <br>Journey <br>]]></content><category term="라시드 (LASID)" label="라시드 (LASID)"/><category term="Journey (Vocal RuBic)" label="Journey (Vocal RuBic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/라시드_LASID/Journey_Vocal_준현/</id><title>라시드 (LASID) - Journey (Vocal 준현) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:13:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:13:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9D%BC%EC%8B%9C%EB%93%9C_LASID/Journey_Vocal_%EC%A4%80%ED%98%84/" title="라시드 (LASID) - Journey (Vocal 준현) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 처음 눈을 떴을 때 <br>깊은 어둠 속에 있어 <br>나 홀로 길을 헤맬 때 <br>한 줄기 빛이 없어 <br>모래 사막 눈 덮인 산 <br>거친 바다 모두 지나 <br>난 그 빛을 찾아 떠나네 <br>Journey 이제 여행을 떠나네 <br>한 줄기 빛을 찾아 <br>한 걸음 발을 떼어 <br>Journey 이 여행이 끝나는 날 <br>모든 어둠의 끝에 <br>빛을 보게 되리라 <br>Journey <br>이 멀고 험한 길에서 <br>무거워진 내 발걸음 <br>날 붙잡고 짓눌려진 채 <br>일어설 수 없게 했어 <br>차가웁게 굳어갈 때 <br>따스하게 감싸 주던 <br>난 그 빛에 다시 또 걷네 <br>Journey 이제 여행을 떠나네 <br>한 줄기 빛을 찾아 <br>한 걸음 발을 떼어 <br>Journey 이 여행이 끝나는 날 <br>모든 어둠의 끝에 <br>빛을 보게 되리라 <br>Journey <br>]]></content><category term="라시드 (LASID)" label="라시드 (LASID)"/><category term="Journey (Vocal 준현)" label="Journey (Vocal 준현)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/라시드_LASID/Journey/</id><title>라시드 (LASID) - Journey - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:13:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:13:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9D%BC%EC%8B%9C%EB%93%9C_LASID/Journey/" title="라시드 (LASID) - Journey - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 처음 눈을 떴을 때 <br>깊은 어둠 속에 있어 <br>나 홀로 길을 헤맬 때 <br>한 줄기 빛이 없어 <br>모래 사막 눈 덮인 산 <br>거친 바다 모두 지나 <br>난 그 빛을 찾아 떠나네 <br>Journey 이제 여행을 떠나네 <br>한 줄기 빛을 찾아 <br>한 걸음 발을 떼어 <br>Journey 이 여행이 끝나는 날 <br>모든 어둠의 끝에 <br>빛을 보게 되리라 <br>Journey <br>이 멀고 험한 길에서 <br>무거워진 내 발걸음 <br>날 붙잡고 짓눌려진 채 <br>일어설 수 없게 했어 <br>차가웁게 굳어갈 때 <br>따스하게 감싸 주던 <br>난 그 빛에 다시 또 걷네 <br>Journey 이제 여행을 떠나네 <br>한 줄기 빛을 찾아 <br>한 걸음 발을 떼어 <br>Journey 이 여행이 끝나는 날 <br>모든 어둠의 끝에 <br>빛을 보게 되리라 <br>Journey <br>]]></content><category term="라시드 (LASID)" label="라시드 (LASID)"/><category term="Journey" label="Journey"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오철수/인사는_하고_가야지/</id><title>오철수 - 인사는 하고 가야지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:13:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:13:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EC%B2%A0%EC%88%98/%EC%9D%B8%EC%82%AC%EB%8A%94_%ED%95%98%EA%B3%A0_%EA%B0%80%EC%95%BC%EC%A7%80/" title="오철수 - 인사는 하고 가야지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[앞만 보고 가는 세월 <br>말도없이 가는 세월 <br>얄미운 세월아 <br>친구도 아닌 것이 <br>친구처럼 왔다가 <br>떠날 때는 멋대로 가는 세월 <br>아무리 염치없는 세월이지만 <br>인사는 하고 가야지 <br>야속한 세월이 나를 울려놓고는 <br>미안해요 죄송해요 <br>문안인사 못 드려서 <br>앞만 보고 가는 세월 <br>겁도 없이 가는 세월 <br>얄미운 세월아 <br>애인도 아닌 것이 <br>애인처럼 왔다가 <br>떠날 때는 멋대로 가는 세월 <br>아무리 인정없는 세월이지만 <br>인사는 하고 가야지 <br>야속한 세월이 나를 울려놓고는 <br>괜찮아요 고마워요 <br>문안인사 못 받아도 <br>아무리 인정없는 세월이지만 <br>인사는 하고 가야지 <br>야속한 세월이 나를 울려놓고는 <br>괜찮아요 고마워요 <br>문안인사 못 받아도 <br>문안인사 못 받아도 <br>]]></content><category term="오철수" label="오철수"/><category term="인사는 하고 가야지" label="인사는 하고 가야지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Summer_In_Paris/</id><title>Morris Albert - Summer In Paris - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:13:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:13:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Summer_In_Paris/" title="Morris Albert - Summer In Paris - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When the lights go out <br>And the sun goes down <br>And you linger there <br><br>Do you think sometimes <br>Of the fun we had <br>And the love we shared <br><br>In that house on the hill <br>Yes, we loved the night away <br>Sweet sunrise sweet sunrise <br><br>Do you miss me, <br>Once in a while, do you miss me <br>Now and again, do you go <br>To that house on the hill <br><br>Do you miss me, now and again, do you miss me <br>Once in a while, babe <br>Do you go to our house on the hill <br><br>As the days go by, <br>Do you sometimes think <br>Of the time we met <br>On that rainy night, how we sheltered there <br>All your clothes were wet <br><br>In that house on the hill <br>Yes, we loved the night away <br>Sweet sunrise sweet sunrise <br><br>Do you miss me, <br>Once in a while, do you miss me <br>Now and again, do you go <br>To that house on the hill <br><br>Do you miss me, <br>Once in a while, do you miss me <br>Now and again, do you go <br>To that house on the hill <br><br>In that house on the hill <br>Yes, we loved the night away <br>Sweet sunrise sweet sunrise <br><br>Do you miss me, <br>Once in a while, do you miss me <br>Now and again, do you go <br>To that house on the hill <br><br>Do you miss me, <br>Once in a while, do you miss me <br>Now and again, do you go <br>To that house on the hill]]></content><category term="Morris Albert" label="Morris Albert"/><category term="Summer In Paris" label="Summer In Paris"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Conversation/</id><title>Morris Albert - Conversation - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:13:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:13:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Conversation/" title="Morris Albert - Conversation - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tema da novela LOCOMOTIVAS <br><br>Can we have a conversation <br><br>Walk together for a while <br><br>Just for your own information <br><br>I have enough time for us <br><br>I'm getting tired of all these matters <br><br>I'm trying to bring back the beauty of our life <br><br>I need every minute to get to know you <br><br>Why not be happy and love all the love <br><br>Somebody who loves you is ready to give you <br><br>Let's get together and have a conversation <br><br>Getting together, conversation <br><br>I don't need a consolation <br><br>Let's walk together for a while, that's all <br><br>Our love is not a violation <br><br>There's plenty of time for us <br><br>I'm getting tired of all these matters <br><br>I'm trying to bring back the beauty of our life <br><br>I need every minute to get to know you <br><br>Just love this man who needs to love you <br><br>Let's get together and have a conversation <br><br>Getting together, conversation]]></content><category term="Morris Albert" label="Morris Albert"/><category term="Conversation" label="Conversation"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Mornings/</id><title>Morris Albert - Mornings - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:13:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:13:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Mornings/" title="Morris Albert - Mornings - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I Woke up this morning <br>Wanting every single bird to fly <br>Kissing every single flower of my life <br>Looking for the touching of your arms in my arms <br>I woke up this morning <br>I turned around and there you were right next to me <br>Your pillow brought me pictures of the night before <br>You said good morning <br>With the smile that I adore <br>I adore <br><br>This is my life <br>Day after day <br>This is the love that I love in you <br>This is your life <br>Day after day <br>This is the love that you love in me <br><br>We woke up this morning <br>We turned around and there we were right in next to us <br>Our pillow brought us pictures of the night before <br>we said good morning <br>With the smile that we adore <br>We adore <br><br>This is my life <br>Day after day <br>This is the love that I love in you <br>This is your life <br>Day after day <br>This is the love that you love in me <br><br>La, la, la]]></content><category term="Morris Albert" label="Morris Albert"/><category term="Mornings" label="Mornings"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Sweet_Loving_Man/</id><title>Morris Albert - Sweet Loving Man - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:13:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:13:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Sweet_Loving_Man/" title="Morris Albert - Sweet Loving Man - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Call me and let me <br>Hear you call me <br>Let me be your loving man <br>You have to call my name <br><br>And call me <br>And let me hear your lips say <br>You're my sweet loving man <br><br>Call me and let me <br>Hear you call me <br>Let me be your loving man <br>You have to call my name <br><br>And call me <br>And let me feel your lips say <br>You're my sweet loving man <br><br>Whenever you want me <br>I'll be around to you <br>Whenever you need me <br>I'll be at your <br>Side to love you <br><br>Whenever you see me <br>Whenever you touch me <br>You know I'm in love <br>And all I want is you <br><br>So let me hear you <br>Call me and let me <br>Hear you call me <br>Let me be your loving man <br>You have to call my name <br><br>And call me <br>And let me feel your lips say <br>You're my sweet loving man <br><br>Whenever you want me <br>I'll be around to you <br>Whenever you need me <br>I'll be at your <br>Side to love you <br><br>Whenever you see me <br>Whenever you touch me <br>You know I'm in love <br>And all I want is you <br><br>La la la la <br><br>You're my sweet loving man <br><br>La la la la <br><br>You're my sweet loving man]]></content><category term="Morris Albert" label="Morris Albert"/><category term="Sweet Loving Man" label="Sweet Loving Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Come_To_My_Life/</id><title>Morris Albert - Come To My Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:14:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:14:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Come_To_My_Life/" title="Morris Albert - Come To My Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Touching the fresh wind blowing <br>Watching the clouds passing by <br>Remembering facts of my days <br>Trying to make sure I'm alive <br><br>Baby, come, come to my life <br>Come, come to my life <br><br>Spending my whole nights by myself <br>Looking for somebody like you <br>Asking the world tell me who else <br>Could be another you <br><br>Baby, come, come to my life <br>Come, come to my life <br><br>Should be the life <br>Should be the life <br>Should be the life <br>Should be the life <br><br>Spending my whole nights by myself <br>Looking for somebody like you <br>Asking the world tell me who else <br>Could be another you <br><br>Baby, come, come to my life <br>Come, come to my life <br><br>Touching the fresh wind blowing <br>Watching the clouds passing by <br>Remembering facts of my days <br>Trying to make sure I'm alive <br>Baby, come, come to my life <br>Come, come to my life <br>Should be the life <br>Should be the life <br><br>Oh, I'm just spending my whole nights by myself <br>Everiday I come for somebody like you <br>You better listen to this words, sing a song <br>And I'm waiting for you <br>And ya will come back to me <br>I'm just waiting for you]]></content><category term="Morris Albert" label="Morris Albert"/><category term="Come To My Life" label="Come To My Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Memories/</id><title>Morris Albert - Memories - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:14:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:14:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Memories/" title="Morris Albert - Memories - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm your night <br>You're my destiny <br>I'm your song, you're my simphony <br>Right away we were loving each other <br>And some reasons made us say good-bye <br><br>Now, I'm lonely in the sea, girl <br>Crying thinking 'bout you <br>I was calling your name <br>But the waves are the same <br>They don't let me hear your voice <br><br>I was on my way <br>I was happy to be alone <br>Now I fell in love and I feel <br>There's something wrong <br>Who am I sitting at my table <br>Eating memories, drinking love <br><br>Now, I am in love <br>I've left you so far away <br>Trying to find myself <br>The man from yesterday <br>Who am I, sitting at my table <br>Eating memories, drinking love]]></content><category term="Morris Albert" label="Morris Albert"/><category term="Memories" label="Memories"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Shes_My_Girl/</id><title>Morris Albert - She`s My Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:14:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:14:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Shes_My_Girl/" title="Morris Albert - She`s My Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She's my girl <br>When the sun goes down <br>When the moon comes up <br>When the light is off <br><br>She's my friend <br>When I need a friend <br>When I want her love I can have it <br><br>Oooh We've got everything we need we need <br>We share everything we have <br>We have sadness and happiness Oh Darling <br><br>Oooh We cry and laugh everytime everytime <br>We love all the love we feel <br>And we feel all the love we make <br><br>Na na na na na na , <br><br>She's my girl <br>When the sun goes down <br>When the moon comes up <br>When the light is off <br><br>She's my woman <br>When I need a woman <br>When my body is asking <br>We can love <br><br>Oooh We've got everything we need we need <br>We share everything we have <br>We have sadness and happiness Oh Darling <br><br>Oooh We cry and laugh everytime everytime <br>We love all the love we feel <br>And we feel all the love we make <br><br>Na na na na na na, <br><br>She's my girl]]></content><category term="Morris Albert" label="Morris Albert"/><category term="She`s My Girl" label="She`s My Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Feelings/</id><title>Morris Albert - Feelings - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:14:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:14:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Morris_Albert/Feelings/" title="Morris Albert - Feelings - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Feelings nothing <br>more than feelings <br>Trying to forget my feelings of love <br>Teardrops rolling down on my face <br>Trying to forget my feelings of love <br>Feelings for all my life I'll feel it <br>I wish I've never met you <br>girl you'll never come again <br>Feelings wo-o-o feelings <br>Wo-o-o feel you again in my arms <br>Feelings feelings like <br>I've never lost you <br>And feelings like <br>I've never have you again in my heart <br>Feelings for all my life I'll feel it <br>I wish I've never met you <br>girl you'll never come again <br>Feelings feelings like <br>I've never lost you <br>And feelings like <br>I've never have you again in my life <br>Feelings wo-o-o feelings <br>Wo-o-o feelings again in my arms <br>Feelings wo-o-o feelings <br>wo-o-o feelings wo-o-o <br>]]></content><category term="Morris Albert" label="Morris Albert"/><category term="Feelings" label="Feelings"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amaranthe/Maximize/</id><title>Amaranthe - Maximize - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:14:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:14:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amaranthe/Maximize/" title="Amaranthe - Maximize - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hello is there someone out there who can hear me scream <br>What you hear is not the same in a mystical dream <br>I know if you read between the lines it is serene <br>There's a darkness in the shadows you can fear <br><br>Higher louder overdrive <br>Can you be the one to lift me higher <br>The future can be brighter <br>Someone be my guiding light <br>Maybe I can give what you require <br>Can't stop rewind so mesmerize <br><br>Mesmerize <br>Maximize me <br>Let's go beyond reality <br>If you can see what I see <br>Hypnotize maximize me <br>Let's take it to eternity <br>Believe the will inside of me <br><br>Come home to a life you never wanted to be real <br>I'm crawling deep within you in control <br>Bring me dignity to free this soul <br>Nothing ever lets me <br><br>Turn into the overdrive <br>Let me change my destiny forever <br>And no one will forget me <br>Let me swim against the tide <br>Maybe I will yearn for your desire <br>Maximize I'm mezmerized <br><br>Mesmerize <br>Maximize me <br>Let's go beyond reality <br>If you can see what I see <br>Hypnotize maximize me <br>Let's take it to eternity <br>Believe the will inside of me <br><br>Higher louder overdrive <br>Can you be the one to lift me higher <br>The future can be brighter <br>Someone be my guiding light <br>Maybe I can give what you require <br>Can't stop rewind so mesmerize <br><br>Mesmerize <br>Maximize me <br>Let's go beyond reality <br>If you can see what I see <br>Hypnotize maximize me <br>Let's take it to eternity <br>Believe the will inside of me]]></content><category term="Amaranthe" label="Amaranthe"/><category term="Maximize" label="Maximize"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Deolinda_Kinzimba/Primeira_Vez/</id><title>Deolinda Kinzimba - Primeira Vez - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:15:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:15:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Deolinda_Kinzimba/Primeira_Vez/" title="Deolinda Kinzimba - Primeira Vez - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Encontrei as palavras <br>que nem sempre contavas <br>tirei um pouco do que e meu <br><br>se desminto disfarcas <br>em conversas e farcas <br>porque que nao me convences de tudo o que passou <br><br>Eu pedi aos ceus <br>que voasses de mim <br>leva os teus compromissos sem fim <br>esse tempo ja passou, ja me arruinou <br>nao ha mais nenhum talvez <br>nesta primeira vez <br>oohh ohhh nesta primeira vez <br>ohh ohh <br><br>Perdi todas nocao <br>do que estava pra vir <br>na prova de uma ilusao nao sabia sair <br>mas tudo ficou bem mais claro <br>encontrei me de novo <br>estou bem melhor assim, aprendi a sorrir pra mim <br><br>Eu pedi aos ceus <br>que voasses de mim <br>leva os teus compromissos sem fim <br>esse tempo ja passou, ja me arruinou <br>nao ha mais nenhum talvez <br>nesta primeira vez <br>eu sei que e bem melhor se for assim <br>nao ha mais a fazer <br>nesta primeira vez <br><br>Eu pedi aos ceus <br>que voasses de mim <br>leva os teus compromissos sem fim <br>esse tempo ja passou, ja me arruinou <br>nao ha mais nenhum talvez <br>nesta primeira vez <br>oohh ohhh nesta primeira vez <br>ohh ohh]]></content><category term="Deolinda Kinzimba" label="Deolinda Kinzimba"/><category term="Primeira Vez" label="Primeira Vez"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MAAD/90s_Love/</id><title>MAAD - 90`s Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:15:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:15:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MAAD/90s_Love/" title="MAAD - 90`s Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They don't love you like I do, not nobody <br>They can't feel you like I do, yeah nobody <br>Ain't no sunshine when you're gone, cloudy days roll on and on <br>But we keep fighting, we keep fighting, yeah <br><br>I fell in love with a real one <br>Got a feeling that it's gonna last <br>Caught up in emotions <br>And we can't let the moment pass <br>All I need is your body here right next to me <br>All over me in ecstasy <br><br>Hold on to me, don't ever let go <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this no more <br>What we got is special for sure <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this no more <br><br>They don't love you like I do, not nobody <br>They can't fuck you like I do, yeah nobody <br>Ain't no sunshine when you're gone, cloudy days roll on and on <br>But we keep fighting, we keep fighting, oh yeah yeah yeah yeah <br><br>I fell in love with a real one <br>Got a feeling that it's gonna last <br>Caught up in emotions <br>And we can't let the moment pass <br>All I need is your body here right next to me <br>All over me in ecstasy <br><br>Hold on to me, don't ever let go <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this no more <br>What we got is special for sure <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this no more <br><br>They don't love you like I do, not nobody <br>No not nobody <br><br>Hold on to me, don't ever let go <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this no more <br>What we got is special for sure <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this no more <br>Hold on to me, don't ever let go <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this no more <br>What we got is special for sure <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this <br>Damn, they don't make 'em like this no more]]></content><category term="MAAD" label="MAAD"/><category term="90`s Love" label="90`s Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/방구석/기적이_뭐_별거_있나_Remake_Ver/</id><title>방구석 - 기적이 뭐 별거 있나 (Remake Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:16:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:16:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%A9%EA%B5%AC%EC%84%9D/%EA%B8%B0%EC%A0%81%EC%9D%B4_%EB%AD%90_%EB%B3%84%EA%B1%B0_%EC%9E%88%EB%82%98_Remake_Ver/" title="방구석 - 기적이 뭐 별거 있나 (Remake Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기적이 뭐 별거 있나 <br>오늘이 기적인것을 <br>기적이 뭐 별거 있나 <br>당신이 기적인것을 <br>아침에 눈을 비비고 <br>당신을 바라보는 것 <br>이렇게 노래하는게 바로 <br>기적이 뭐 별거 있나 <br>오늘이 기적인 것을 <br>기적이 뭐 별거 있나 <br>우리가 기적인 것을 <br>당신과 마주 앉아서 <br>이렇게 웃고 떠들고 <br>이 노랠 들려주는게 바로 <br>당신과 마주 앉아서 <br>이렇게 웃고 떠들고 <br>이 노랠 들려주는게 바로 <br>기적이 뭐 별거 있나 <br>오늘이 기적인것을 <br>기적이 뭐 별거 있나 <br>우리가 기적인 것을 <br>]]></content><category term="방구석" label="방구석"/><category term="기적이 뭐 별거 있나 (Remake Ver.)" label="기적이 뭐 별거 있나 (Remake Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/방구석/뒤통수/</id><title>방구석 - 뒤통수 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:16:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:16:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%A9%EA%B5%AC%EC%84%9D/%EB%92%A4%ED%86%B5%EC%88%98/" title="방구석 - 뒤통수 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 던진 말들이 <br>내 뒤통수를 때릴 땐 <br>내가 던진 말들의 <br>형체도 알아볼 수 없지 <br>내가 던진 말들이 <br>내 뒤통수를 때릴 땐 <br>내 말에 살이 붙어 <br>무겁게 나를 때리지 <br>가볍게 던졌던 <br>무심코 던졌던 <br>말들이 돌고 돌아서 <br>나를 때릴 때 <br>조금씩 단단해져 <br>벽돌처럼 되면 <br>내 뒤통수는 <br>남지도 않겠네 <br>내가 던진 말들이 <br>내 뒤통수를 때릴 땐 <br>내가 던진 말들의 <br>형체도 알아볼 수 없지 <br>내가 던진 말들이 <br>내 뒤통수를 때릴 땐 <br>내 말에 살이 붙어 <br>무겁게 나를 때리지 <br>가볍게 던졌던 <br>무심코 던졌던 <br>말들이 돌고 돌아서 <br>나를 때릴 때 <br>조금씩 단단해져 <br>벽돌처럼 되면 <br>내 뒤통수는 <br>남지도 않겠네 <br>한다리 건너면 <br>진실은 사라지고 <br>두다리 세다리 건너면 <br>가볍게 던졌던 <br>무심코 던졌던 <br>말들이 돌고 돌아서 <br>나를 때릴 때 <br>조금씩 단단해져 <br>벽돌처럼 되면 <br>내 뒤통수는 <br>남지도 않겠네 <br>]]></content><category term="방구석" label="방구석"/><category term="뒤통수" label="뒤통수"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/방구석/잘_알지도_못하면서/</id><title>방구석 - 잘 알지도 못하면서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:16:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:16:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%A9%EA%B5%AC%EC%84%9D/%EC%9E%98_%EC%95%8C%EC%A7%80%EB%8F%84_%EB%AA%BB%ED%95%98%EB%A9%B4%EC%84%9C/" title="방구석 - 잘 알지도 못하면서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아마도 난 <br>내가 아는 것 말곤 <br>몰랐었나봐 <br>그런데 난 <br>내가 모르는 것도 <br>몰랐었나봐 <br>내가 알고 있는 것들 <br>그게 전부라고 믿고 <br>내가 알고 있는 것만 <br>가르치려 했었나봐 <br>미안해 실은 <br>개뿔도 모르면서 <br>좀 더 아는 척을 <br>하고 싶던거야 <br>혹시나 내가 <br>같잖아 보였다면 <br>니가 보고 있는 <br>그게 내가 맞아 <br>내가 알고 있는 것들 <br>그게 전부라고 믿고 <br>내가 알고 있는 것만 <br>가르치려 했었나봐 <br>미안해 실은 <br>개뿔도 모르면서 <br>좀 더 아는 척을 <br>하고 싶던거야 <br>혹시나 내가 <br>같잖아 보였다면 <br>니가 보고 있는 <br>그게 내가 맞아 <br>미안해 실은 <br>개뿔도 모르면서 <br>좀 더 아는 척을 <br>하고 싶던거야 <br>혹시나 내가 <br>같잖아 보였다면 <br>니가 보고 있는 <br>그게 내가 맞아 <br>]]></content><category term="방구석" label="방구석"/><category term="잘 알지도 못하면서" label="잘 알지도 못하면서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/방구석/아주_흉한_괴물_이야기/</id><title>방구석 - 아주 흉한 괴물 이야기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:16:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:16:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%A9%EA%B5%AC%EC%84%9D/%EC%95%84%EC%A3%BC_%ED%9D%89%ED%95%9C_%EA%B4%B4%EB%AC%BC_%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC%EA%B8%B0/" title="방구석 - 아주 흉한 괴물 이야기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흉한 모습을 한 괴물이 있었어 <br>사람들은 모두 그를 싫어했어 <br>온통 가시로 뒤덮여 있어서 <br>사람들은 다가 갈 수 없었어 <br>다가가면 멀어지고 <br>도망가면 돌던지고 <br>가시들은 거세지고 <br>벗어날 수 없는 내 꿈속 <br>알아 알아 그게 나라는 걸 <br>벗어나려 해도 <br>떠날 수 없단걸 <br>달아나려 달음질해봐도 <br>내 꿈속의 나는 <br>점점 더 흉해지는걸 <br>슬픈 눈을 가진 괴물이 있었어 <br>사람들은 모두 그를 싫어했어 <br>온통 가시로 뒤덮여 있어서 <br>사람들은 다가 갈 수 없었어 <br>다가가면 멀어지고 <br>도망가면 돌던지고 <br>가시들은 거세지고 <br>벗어날 수 없는 내 꿈속 <br>알아 알아 그게 나라는 걸 <br>달아나려 해도 떠날 수 없단걸 <br>인정 하려 다가가려 해도 <br>가시에 찔려서 더욱 아파지는걸 <br>가시는 길어지고 <br>길어지고 <br>점점 더 길어지고 <br>길어지고 <br>가시는 변해가고 <br>변해가고 <br>그 이는 변해가고 <br>그 이는 잃어가고 <br>]]></content><category term="방구석" label="방구석"/><category term="아주 흉한 괴물 이야기" label="아주 흉한 괴물 이야기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/방구석/깡소주/</id><title>방구석 - 깡소주 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:16:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:16:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%A9%EA%B5%AC%EC%84%9D/%EA%B9%A1%EC%86%8C%EC%A3%BC/" title="방구석 - 깡소주 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[솔까말 깡소주가 <br>달고 맛있다는 말은 <br>절대 이해할 수 없어 <br>정말 이상하지 <br>남들은 깡소주가 <br>시원하고 부드럽다고 <br>말을 하는데 정말 이상하지 <br>냉수가 더 시원하잖아 <br>냉수는 리필도 공짠데 <br>진짜 우리가 좋아하는 건 <br>내가 좋아서 좋아하는 건지 <br>아니면 남들이 좋다고 하니까 <br>그냥 그게 좋은 건지 <br>가끔은 나도 헷갈려 <br>내가 깡소주를 싫어하는 것이 <br>내 미각이 유별나고 <br>지랄맞아서 진짜 그런건지 <br>나는 잘 모르겠어 <br>동아리 선배들은 <br>내가 인생을 몰라서 <br>소주가 쓰다고 <br>가오를 잡았지 <br>십구년이 지나도 난 여전히 <br>깡소주가 입에 쓴것을 <br>정말 이상하지 <br>내가 인생을 헛살았나 <br>나도 이제는 애가 셋인데 <br>진짜 우리가 좋아하는 건 <br>내가 좋아서 좋아하는 건지 <br>아니면 남들이 좋다고 하니까 <br>그냥 그게 좋은건지 <br>가끔은 나도 헷갈려 <br>내가 깡소주를 싫어하는 것이 <br>내 미각이 유별나고 <br>지랄맞아서 진짜 그런건지 <br>나는 잘 모르겠어 <br>술자리에서 술은 안먹고 <br>안주빨만 세우는 사람은 왜 <br>죄인처럼 취급받는 것이 <br>당연한 것인지 <br>소주 대신에 <br>탄산을 시켜먹는 <br>사람은 어째서 늘 <br>구석에 찌그러져서 <br>조용히 해야 하는 건지 <br>아직 잘모르겠어 <br>진짜 우리가 좋아하는 건 <br>내가 좋아서 좋아하는 건지 <br>아니면 남들이 좋다고 하니까 <br>그냥 그게 좋은건지 <br>가끔은 나도 헷갈려 <br>내가 깡소주를 싫어하는 것이 <br>내 미각이 유별나고 <br>지랄맞아서 진짜 그런건지 <br>나는 잘 모르겠어 <br>]]></content><category term="방구석" label="방구석"/><category term="깡소주" label="깡소주"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/방구석/그때는_왜_몰랐을까/</id><title>방구석 - 그때는 왜 몰랐을까 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T12:17:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T12:17:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%A9%EA%B5%AC%EC%84%9D/%EA%B7%B8%EB%95%8C%EB%8A%94_%EC%99%9C_%EB%AA%B0%EB%9E%90%EC%9D%84%EA%B9%8C/" title="방구석 - 그때는 왜 몰랐을까 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 항상 중요한 사실은 <br>한발 늦게 알게 되는걸까 <br>모두들 말해줬다는데 <br>왜 그땐 들리지 않았을까 <br>왜 항상 후회할 일들은 <br>한발 늦게 알게 되는걸까 <br>모두들 말렸었다는데 <br>왜 그땐 들리지 않았을까 <br>그때는 왜 몰랐을까 <br>모두들 말했다는데 <br>지나가는 바람도 내게 <br>이야기 해줬다는데 <br>그때는 왜 몰랐을까 <br>모두들 말했다는데 <br>아마도 모르는 사실은 <br>들어도 결국 모르는건가봐 <br>왜 가끔 책을 다시 보면 <br>볼때 마다 새로운걸까 <br>그때는 정독했었는데 <br>왜 그땐 보이지 않았을까 <br>왜 그때 감동했던 것이 <br>다시 보면 유치한걸까 <br>그때는 심각했었는데 <br>지금은 왜 우습기만할까 <br>그때는 왜 몰랐을까 <br>모두들 말했다는데 <br>지나가는 바람도 내게 <br>이야기 해줬다는데 <br>그때는 왜 몰랐을까 <br>모두들 말했다는데 <br>아마도 모르는 사실은 <br>들어도 결국 모르는건가봐 <br>그때는 왜 몰랐을까 <br>모두들 말했다는데 <br>지나가는 바람도 내게 <br>이야기 해줬다는데 <br>그때는 왜 몰랐을까 <br>모두들 말했다는데 <br>아마도 모르는 사실은 <br>들어도 결국 모르는건가봐 <br>]]></content><category term="방구석" label="방구석"/><category term="그때는 왜 몰랐을까" label="그때는 왜 몰랐을까"/></entry></feed>