<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:05:29+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/T-NAP/Big_Picture/</id><title>T-NAP - Big Picture - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:05:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:05:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/T-NAP/Big_Picture/" title="T-NAP - Big Picture - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 우릴 못 봐 우린 끝에 와있어 <br>Everybody show your T-NAP <br>Sign's up <br>뭘 바라던 간에 <br>예상과는 다르겠지 <br>초라했던 과거완 달리 <br>이제는 우리는 용의 머리 <br>그래 우리 2년 전 수원 바닥에서 <br>우리 소릴 낼 때 꿈에 그리던 걸 <br>무대에 올림 <br>I'm fucked up it's not bluffing <br>입에 물린 흉기 터진 혀의 물집 <br>백지 위에 그린 IDEN의 그림 <br>CoCo의 드럼이 만들어낸 문집 <br>Including music Keep diffusing <br>A with my big bros <br>T-NAP rolling in the beat <br>all body close up <br>피보다 진하게 <br>긴 말은 필요 없어 <br>빈 말은 하지 않어 <br>진짜 배기여 Made in <br>T-NAP kick that ass shit <br>비켜 싹 다 인구 10의 행진 <br>다음 차례 나와 싫어하게 되겠지 <br>우릴 깔라면 <br>매일 길러야 돼 개인기 <br>획일한 래핑에 <br>생채기를 새길 <br>내 제 2의 재림에 행길을 채우지 <br>채우다 못해 흘러서 넘치게 돼 <br>결국엔 번지게 돼 <br>단단히 걸어 반반하니 <br>들어올 생각은 차라리 <br>가만히 있는 게 너네들의 미래를 <br>생각하는 방향이 <br>될 것임에 분명하지 <br>Make things never been told <br>전부 싹 다 부실 때까지 <br>We work harder and harder <br>매 순간이 다할 때까지 <br>아싸리 하지 말길 <br>어차피 볼 수 없을 위치 <br>U can’t see 빙신 In ma crew <br>there’s no fuckin' bitches <br>시간을 할애 바빠도 <br>각자 시간을 쪼개 <br>유지하는 이유 무대 위 조명 <br>Spot light 받는 기분 <br>근본 없는 놈들의 개벽 <br>시간은 새벽 <br>동 트기 직전 술잔을 채워 건배 <br>오늘보다 죽여주는 내일 위해 <br>어제도 오늘도 Rappin' all day <br>넌 내 갠취를 베끼는 래핑을 해 <br>객기로 했던 애들과 Nancy는 <br>Chase us wack fake <br>T-NAP is taking a nap <br>But 제대로 해 또 밤 새울 때 <br>너네들이 말한 <br>소리들을 이끌어내 <br>그 티끌 안에 보이는 구멍 속에 <br>시끄런 각도들을 <br>비틀어 깨 Andy dufresne <br>20년만의 탈옥처럼 <br>난 20년 아냐 <br>Stephen russell의 감옥처럼 <br>너네들의 귀를 들락날락 거려 <br>날 따라 잡으려면 <br>우리들의 이름부터 가르쳐둔 <br>뒤에 우리 몽타주를 공개해 <br>동네 to 홍대 사이 <br>공개된 공공의 적을 못 본 채하며 <br>지나가는 병신들을 볼 때마다 <br>Wow what u gonna do man <br>Keep going real <br>내 형제가 지켜왔던 태도 <br>Hell yeah <br>우리가 지켜내고 있었던 Ghetto <br>I can’t see the them thing <br>날 무시했던 Fake asses rest in peace <br>Rest in peace <br>난 그때 그어줄 니 목에 기스 <br>Hold up <br>관은 직접 만든 Home made <br>이 자리 초대된 사람들은 <br>10명의 유령 <br>마주칠 때마다 <br>항상 Faker들은 놀래 <br>너네 장례식에 준비해 샴페인 <br>잔을 비워 목을 축여 그 담에 <br>기도를 Amen Sorry for fake man <br>내일 되면 형제와 <br>잔을 따라 또 건배 <br>내 집 내 일 내 빚 내일로 <br>잊게 만들어주는 이름이 생겼지 <br>Yeah T-NAP in here 더는 뒤돌아 <br>보는 짓 No 우리 리듬이 생겼지 <br>이제 올라가는 신호탄은 <br>폭탄이 되어 <br>우리 목표는 높아지고파 <br>이제 여긴 <br>너의 겉치레 벗겨내고 <br>맨 몸에다 우리 <br>색을 덧칠해 <br>멋진 한 폭 그려질 때 <br>두 번째 수채화를 그려내 <br>우리 곁에 그린 옆에 그려진 <br>겉의 풍경에 묻어낸 <br>혼에 풀어낸 우리에 대해 <br>What should I do <br>감상하면 돼 <br>이제는 타이틀 걸어놔 <br>차이를 지켜봐 한 곳만 파 <br>그리고 봐 너네가 바라봤던 <br>그 그림인가 <br>우리가 만들어 가는 것들을 <br>더 자세히 지켜만 봐야 돼 <br>그 길을 봐 <br>고개를 위로 치켜 올려 <br>이 곡이 공개 되면서 <br>바뀌겠지 너네가 보던 시야 전체 <br>10색의 물감을 <br>모두의 땀에 풀어 <br>섞어낸 색깔에 기초해 <br>수채화를 그려 <br>아무도 알 수 없지 <br>우리 미래에 대한 건 <br>허나 확실한 거 하나 <br>그려지는 Big picture <br>점점 커져나가는 중 <br>우리 밑그림은 <br>길바닥 이젠 돼가고 있어 <br>Yeah Real future <br>]]></content><category term="T-NAP" label="T-NAP"/><category term="Big Picture" label="Big Picture"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더블캐슬/off/</id><title>더블캐슬 - off - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:06:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:06:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/off/" title="더블캐슬 - off - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[더 이상 허락된 시간이 얼마 없어 <br>오늘도 술잔을 채우고 비워 <br>이 호흡도 이제 곧 조만간 멈춰 <br>이 시간도 이제 날 놓아줘 어서 <br>이젠 살고싶은 마음도 <br>죽고싶은 마음도 그 어떤 마음도 <br>전혀 사라진걸 모은 돈도 <br>하루하루가 무의미한 채로 <br>나는 왜 사는가에 대한 <br>질문은 답이 없어 zero <br>내가 가는 곳은 날 한줌의 재로 <br>만들어 낼 뿐이고 <br>이제 난 어디로 가야돼 <br>내 인생은 Gps off shit <br>that's no oh oh <br>더 이상 허락된 시간이 얼마 없어 <br>오늘도 술잔을 채우고 비워 <br>이 호흡도 이제 곧 조만간 멈춰 <br>이 시간도 이제 날 놓아줘 어서 <br>내 삶은 on 끝나면 off <br>호흡 끊어질까 잠들 수 없어 오늘도 <br>내가 쓴 가사가 무서워 <br>이게 마지막이 될까 <br>오늘은 살았던 내가 내일은 사라질까 <br>손 끝에 남은 차가운 반응 <br>감각의 마지막은 언젠가 찾아올 <br>꺼져가는 난 어디로 갈까 하는 <br>아주 작은 기대감 <br>그 외에 검고 검은 공간 <br>신을 믿지 않는 날 <br>밀어 넣을 그곳으로 <br>더 이상 허락된 시간이 얼마 없어 <br>오늘도 술잔을 채우고 비워 <br>이 호흡도 이제 곧 조만간 멈춰 <br>이 시간도 이제 날 놓아줘 어서 <br>]]></content><category term="더블캐슬" label="더블캐슬"/><category term="off" label="off"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더블캐슬/오만원_Remix_Feat_Tase/</id><title>더블캐슬 - 오만원 Remix (Feat. Tase) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:06:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:06:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/%EC%98%A4%EB%A7%8C%EC%9B%90_Remix_Feat_Tase/" title="더블캐슬 - 오만원 Remix (Feat. Tase) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 버는 돈은 하루 오만원 <br>고작 오만원 고작 오만원 <br>고작 오만원 고작 오만원 <br>맨날 욕 먹고 뛰어다니면 <br>받는 오만원 <br>내가 버는 돈은 하루 오만원 <br>고작 오만원 고작 오만원 <br>고작 오만원 고작 오만원 <br>맨날 욕 먹고 뛰어다니면 <br>받는 오만원 <br>한달 30일 출근하면 월 150만원 <br>5천억 부자들의 지갑에 쌓인 오만원 <br>거스름 돈은 거슬려 <br>신사임당 미만 잡 <br>내 지갑에 한장만 있어도 <br>행복 할거야 <br>지폐에 그려진 국내 최초 여성 <br>국내 최초 여성 대통령이 <br>나왔는데 HELL조선 <br>시장경제체제 그딴거 <br>다 필요없어 금수저 <br>흙수저는 안 보이는데 가서 <br>흙이나 퍼 먹어 <br>사랑하고 결혼하고 애 낳고 uh <br>결국 또 노예양성 <br>술 담배 없이 버틸 수 있는 <br>시간이 없어 <br>죽고 싶어도 죽어버릴 시간이 없어 <br>온몸에 땀이 범벅 일에 찌들어 <br>신원조회도 안돼 엄지에 지문이 없어 <br>이게 사람 사는건지 <br>도대체 왜 사는건지 <br>죽는게 답인거지 난 돈 벌어도 거지 <br>내가 버는 돈은 하루 오만원 <br>고작 오만원 고작 오만원 <br>고작 오만원 고작 오만원 <br>맨날 욕 먹고 뛰어다니면 <br>받는 오만원 <br>내가 버는 돈은 하루 오만원 <br>고작 오만원 고작 오만원 <br>고작 오만원 고작 오만원 <br>맨날 욕 먹고 뛰어다니면 <br>받는 오만원 <br>오만원 오만원 난 가진적이 없어 <br>매장에서 돈 벌어 거스름돈 그 정도 <br>부정하기 전엔 돈 벌어도 <br>적자 go bottom <br>더블캐슬 잠안와 같이 24시간 모자라 <br>지갑은 남자 전용 휴게실 <br>그 마저도 경제 불황 <br>언젠가 지갑 터지겠지 그땐 되겠지 <br>우리 부모님은 실업자 <br>직장은 취미 생활 <br>많이 벌고 또 벌어서 <br>지갑은 짐이 된다 <br>일급 5만원 월급 150 부족해 <br>내겐 오직 <br>장비 여자친구 데이트 라인업 <br>합주 이런것에 <br>uh 가계부 작성 힙합 스웩 <br>그 이전에 <br>코가 석자니까 쟤네는 <br>신경 안 쓴다 전해 <br>ey 근데 왜 내가 이런거에 <br>신경 써야해 <br>난 여기 있는 애들과 갈건데 <br>저기 돈 밭에 오만원 <br>내가 버는 돈은 하루 오만원 <br>고작 오만원 고작 오만원 <br>고작 오만원 고작 오만원 <br>맨날 욕 먹고 뛰어다니면 <br>받는 오만원 <br>내가 버는 돈은 하루 오만원 <br>고작 오만원 고작 오만원 <br>고작 오만원 고작 오만원 <br>맨날 욕 먹고 뛰어다니면 <br>받는 오만원 <br>]]></content><category term="더블캐슬" label="더블캐슬"/><category term="오만원 Remix (Feat. Tase)" label="오만원 Remix (Feat. Tase)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더블캐슬/자본주의_Feat_Tase/</id><title>더블캐슬 - 자본주의 (Feat. Tase) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:06:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:06:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/%EC%9E%90%EB%B3%B8%EC%A3%BC%EC%9D%98_Feat_Tase/" title="더블캐슬 - 자본주의 (Feat. Tase) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자본주의 맹점 모든 것이 선택 <br>하지만 가지 수가 달라 원래 <br>많은 놈이 많이 갖는 system <br>돈 없으면 나가 죽어 <br>난 벌써 수백번도 더 죽어나가 <br>아직도 통장엔 100도 없어 내가 <br>번 돈은 수천 이어도 쓴게 더 많아 <br>인생은 약처럼 쓴데 <br>가난이 낫지는 않아 <br>이 세상이 어떻게 돌아가든 상관없어 <br>이 세상은 나와는 달라 <br>여유로워 보여 <br>이 세상은 거짓을 가볍게 뱉어 <br>이 세상은 무서운 진실을 <br>무겁게 덮어 <br>이 세상은 돈이면 다돼 <br>누군가 말해 너희 부모님을 탓 해 <br>우리 부모님은 열심히 살았는데 <br>내가 이렇게 된 건 <br>누구 탓을 해야 돼 <br>누구의 잘못도 될 수 없어 <br>가진걸 똑같이 나눌 수 없어 <br>우리가 사는 자본주의 잘못은 없어 <br>가진걸 똑같이 나눌 수 없어 <br>이 세상이 어떻게 돌아가든 상관없어 <br>이 세상은 나와는 달라 <br>여유로워 보여 <br>이 세상은 거짓을 가볍게 뱉어 <br>이 세상은 무서운 진실을 <br>무겁게 덮어 <br>수많은 돈 수많은 곡 볼 수없는 <br>모습 벗은 돈은 야하지 않아 더럽지 <br>겁없이 뛰어든 철학 <br>뒤에 죽었단 전화뿐 <br>이게 무슨 말인지 <br>이해하려면 사회생활 좀 <br>30만원 그들의 월세 생명을 연장해 <br>건장했던 청년과 아가씨는 옷 벗네 <br>이자를 갚지 못해 악순환 연속돼 <br>이게 우리 또래 현실 몇 만은 더 돼 <br>집나간 현재 앞 보기엔 <br>힘없어 고개 숙이지 <br>문이지 끝의 질문은 죽음이지 <br>아름다운 청춘이 <br>무릎 꿇어 입을 쓰지 <br>댓가는 돈 10만원 얼굴에 흩뿌리지 <br>몇은 그리지 니 꿈을 지키지 <br>그 뒤엔 30분의 고통 후에 <br>니가 바란 돈이지 <br>so easy 삶의 그 끝과 포기한 인생 <br>건강 썩은 미래는 올가미 <br>목 조이네 <br>이 세상이 어떻게 돌아가든 상관없어 <br>이 세상은 나와는 달라 <br>여유로워 보여 <br>이 세상은 거짓을 가볍게 뱉어 <br>이 세상은 무서운 진실을 <br>무겁게 덮어 <br>]]></content><category term="더블캐슬" label="더블캐슬"/><category term="자본주의 (Feat. Tase)" label="자본주의 (Feat. Tase)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더블캐슬/월세가_얼마니/</id><title>더블캐슬 - 월세가 얼마니 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:06:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:06:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/%EC%9B%94%EC%84%B8%EA%B0%80_%EC%96%BC%EB%A7%88%EB%8B%88/" title="더블캐슬 - 월세가 얼마니 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[월세가 얼마니 포함된 관리비 <br>벌레는 덤이지 벽에는 곰팡이 <br>월세가 얼마니 포함된 관리비 <br>벌레는 덤이지 벽에는 곰팡이 <br>월세가 얼마니 포함된 관리비 <br>화장실은 좁고 <br>머리가 천장에 닿아 <br>여기 혹시 호빗이 살았나 <br>호빗이 지었나 <br>내 키는 작은데 왜 이래 <br>옆집은 외국인 국적이 스페인 <br>새벽에 들어와 떠들어 <br>덕분에 새벽에 작업해 녹음까지 <br>옆 집은 떡을 쳐 소리가 쩔어 <br>야동을 틀었나 <br>이렇게 사는 게 자괴감 들어 <br>난 또 윗 집은 애새끼들 <br>뛰어 다녀 울고 불고 <br>그 집은 엄마가 성격이 괴팍해 <br>월세가 얼마니 포함된 관리비 <br>벌레는 덤이지 벽에는 곰팡이 <br>월세가 얼마니 포함된 관리비 <br>벌레는 덤이지 벽에는 곰팡이 <br>아침 10시 불법 복사 <br>tape 뽕짝이 <br>우리 집 앞에서 볼륨을 키우지 <br>가판대를 뒤집어 박살내버려 <br>그래도 다시 와 너무나 끈질겨 <br>그딴 거 안 팔려 <br>그러니까 그만 좀 괴롭혀 <br>이 동네 정말로 왜이래 씨발 <br>월세가 얼마니 포함된 관리비 <br>벌레는 덤이지 벽에는 곰팡이 <br>월세가 얼마니 포함된 관리비 <br>벌레는 덤이지 벽에는 곰팡이 <br>난 밤낮 없이 술을 쳐 들이부어 <br>섞어 부어 이젠 그것도 귀찮아 <br>그냥 부어 <br>straight 잔에 따라먹어 <br>내가 누구 때문에 이렇게 살어 <br>내가 누구 때문에 이렇게 살어 <br>집주인 눈치는 안 보고 살려고 <br>더 이상 월세는 안 밀려 <br>그만 좀 재촉해 <br>니년이 뒤지기 싫으면 <br>얌전히 입 닫고 <br>집 안에 들어가 문 잠궈 <br>니 새끼 장례식 치르기 싫으면 <br>그만 좀 괴롭혀 <br>니 새끼 장례식 치르기 싫으면 <br>그만 좀 괴롭혀 <br>월세가 얼마니 포함된 관리비 <br>벌레는 덤이지 벽에는 곰팡이 <br>월세가 얼마니 포함된 관리비 <br>벌레는 덤이지 벽에는 곰팡이 <br>]]></content><category term="더블캐슬" label="더블캐슬"/><category term="월세가 얼마니" label="월세가 얼마니"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더블캐슬/은팔찌/</id><title>더블캐슬 - 은팔찌 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:06:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:06:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/%EC%9D%80%ED%8C%94%EC%B0%8C/" title="더블캐슬 - 은팔찌 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 차는 은팔찌 <br>경찰 뜨고 수갑이 <br>그들이 원하는 합의금 <br>따라붙지 경찰이 <br>피의자 다들 날 그렇게 불렀지 <br>아무도 오지 말아 오지 말아 <br>너무 마셔 오줌 마려 오줌 마려 <br>위스키와 담배 찰떡궁합 관계 <br>잔에서 손을 안 떼 마셔버려 밤새 <br>아무도 움직이지 말아 <br>내가 랩을 할 때 <br>지금부터 랩 하는 놈이 범인 <br>이제 수갑 찰 때 <br>철컹 철컹 은팔찌와 2 chainz <br>문을 걷어차줘 <br>경찰서에 들어갈 때 <br>내가 차는 은팔찌 <br>경찰 뜨고 수갑이 <br>그들이 원하는 합의금 <br>따라붙지 경찰이 <br>피의자 다들 날 그렇게 불렀지 <br>내 check card 점검시간이 <br>밤 11시부터 새벽 5시까지 <br>였을 뿐이었지 <br>새벽까지 술에 취한 채 끌려갔지 <br>잡혀가 혐의가 무전취식 <br>신분증에 핸드폰까지 뺏겼지 <br>니네가 뭔데 내걸 뺏지 <br>돈은 있는데 결제가 <br>안 되는 걸 어떻게 하지 <br>소리쳐도 소 귀에 경 읽기 <br>조서도 안 쓸 거면 <br>집이나 보내주지 <br>내가 차는 은팔찌 <br>경찰 뜨고 수갑이 <br>그들이 원하는 합의금 <br>따라붙지 경찰이 <br>피의자 다들 날 그렇게 불렀지 <br>경찰서에 들어간 것도 <br>벌써 다섯 번째 <br>모두 좋게 끝냈지만 <br>끝에 기록은 남은 채 <br>날 조회하면 표정부터 달라지네 <br>죄인을 대하는 그 표정 <br>역겹네 그게 날 화나게 해 <br>내가 차는 은팔찌 <br>경찰 뜨고 수갑이 <br>그들이 원하는 합의금 <br>따라붙지 경찰이 <br>피의자 다들 날 그렇게 불렀지 <br>]]></content><category term="더블캐슬" label="더블캐슬"/><category term="은팔찌" label="은팔찌"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더블캐슬/도망가/</id><title>더블캐슬 - 도망가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:06:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:06:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/%EB%8F%84%EB%A7%9D%EA%B0%80/" title="더블캐슬 - 도망가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보기 싫은 것들 눈 돌린 지 오래 <br>지금 난 나와 다른 사람이 <br>어떻든 상관 안 해 <br>그러니까 신경 좀 꺼줄래 <br>난 다르거든 <br>과거의 실수 따윈 반복 안 해 <br>붉게 물 들어가는 눈 니 앞에서 <br>검게 타 들어가는 중 니 옆에서 <br>뒤늦은 후회는 소용없어 <br>땅을 쳐도 피만 나와 주먹에서 <br>서서히 빠져들어가 누가 널 <br>꺼내지도 못해 그 상황에서 <br>불행의 뫼비우스 띠 안에서 <br>고통의 나날 그건 대물림 됐어 <br>침몰하는 여기선 <br>탈출하지 못한 채로 <br>영원히 흐르는 눈물의 말로 <br>아무도 믿지마 이 땅 위에서 <br>You &amp; I 도망가 하루빨리 그곳에서 <br>You &amp; I 도망가 하루빨리 그곳에서 <br>You &amp; I 도망가 하루빨리 그곳에서 <br>You &amp; I 도망가 하루빨리 그곳에서 <br>You &amp; I 도망가 하루빨리 그곳에서 <br>도망가 이곳은 불안한 <br>그런 장면 연출되고 있잖아 <br>도망가 그만 정신차려 <br>수백 번 외쳐봐도 안되잖아 <br>정말 난 그 꼴이 <br>정말 보기가 어렵고 역겨우니까 <br>이젠 다 잊고 살래 <br>치료가 필요할 것 같애 <br>트라우마가 생길 것 같으니까 <br>너에게 난 혐오 아닌 혐오 <br>좀 비슷하지 기억 속에 남은 혐오 <br>함께 한지도 오래 됐지만 <br>적응 안되 서로 <br>그래서 난 서로 멀어지고만 싶어 <br>근데 여긴 너무 좁잖아 <br>이건 큰 문제고 <br>또 다른 문제로 잊혀진 채로 <br>또 술에 취해 빠져 들어가 <br>헤어나오질 못하고 <br>이제 그만 뛰쳐나와 현실로 <br>You &amp; I 도망가 하루빨리 그곳에서 <br>You &amp; I 도망가 하루빨리 그곳에서 <br>You &amp; I 도망가 하루빨리 그곳에서 <br>You &amp; I 도망가 하루빨리 그곳에서 <br>You &amp; I 도망가 하루빨리 그곳에서 <br>우린 서로 다른 곳을 봐 <br>그게 맞는 것 같다고 봐 <br>너에게서 도망가는 <br>날 너무 탓 하지는 마 <br>그게 누가 됐든 <br>그게 맞는 거라고 봐 <br>난 참을 만큼 참았었고 <br>난 성장하고 끊임없이 인내하고 <br>이제 이해하길 바랄 뿐 내 선택을 <br>너와 난 다른 길을 <br>가고 있을 거라고 <br>내가 원하는 길은 <br>안정되고 편안함뿐 <br>네가 걷는 길은 <br>위태롭기만 해 위험할 뿐 <br>내게 남은 건 꿈에 대한 갈망 <br>니 꿈을 지지하지 <br>아니 지지하지 않고 <br>그대로 남는다면 <br>내 선택은 변치 않고 <br>내 선택이 달랐다면 <br>그건 너무 위험하고 <br>근데 차라리 이게 나아 <br>근데 차라리 이게 나아 <br>You &amp; I 도망가 하루빨리 그곳에서 <br>You &amp; I 도망가 하루빨리 그곳에서 <br>You &amp; I 도망가 하루빨리 그곳에서 <br>You &amp; I 도망가 하루빨리 그곳에서 <br>You &amp; I 도망가 하루빨리 그곳에서 <br>]]></content><category term="더블캐슬" label="더블캐슬"/><category term="도망가" label="도망가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더블캐슬/비정상/</id><title>더블캐슬 - 비정상 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:06:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:06:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/%EB%B9%84%EC%A0%95%EC%83%81/" title="더블캐슬 - 비정상 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[딴 남자들과는 달라 <br>나쁜 남자 아니란 걸 알아 <br>I might be shining like a 천사 <br>난 사람이 아냐 아마 천사 <br>너의 맘 모두가 알아 <br>눈이 마주치고 그땐 알아 봐 <br>may be 느낌이 통해 나도 알아 <br>그래 난 사람이 아닌가 봐 아마 천사 <br>사람들이 말해 나 천사 같대 <br>악마의 반대 천사 같대 그래 맞네 <br>그걸 봤네 등뒤에 펼친 날개 <br>숨기려고 해도 전혀 감출 길이 없네 <br>일이 없네 스트레스 받을 일이 <br>모든 일이 하늘의 뜻 그걸 알게 된 후 <br>사람들이 뭐라 말해도 <br>한숨으로 돌리고 <br>날아 오는 돌직구 유연하게 피하고 <br>날 내려다보는 방법을 <br>터득하게 된 이후 <br>달라진 건 나 하나 이제 만나 너와 나 <br>빠져들어 you &amp; i 후회는 나중에 하고 <br>언젠가 만나 너랑 나 <br>]]></content><category term="더블캐슬" label="더블캐슬"/><category term="비정상" label="비정상"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더블캐슬/성공을_논해/</id><title>더블캐슬 - 성공을 논해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:06:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:06:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/%EC%84%B1%EA%B3%B5%EC%9D%84_%EB%85%BC%ED%95%B4/" title="더블캐슬 - 성공을 논해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니가 왜 내 성공을 논해 <br>내가 부러운 건 아닐 거라 생각해 <br>사실 너보다 못 벌잖아 돈도 <br>여자친구도 없고 연애할 돈도 없고 <br>시간은 더 더욱 없고 <br>피곤에 쩔어 편히 쉬고 싶어 <br>시간이 부족해 <br>시간이 부족해 <br>시간이 부족해 <br>근데 그런 니가 왜 <br>내 성공을 논해 <br>내가 꿈을 쫓아 다니는 게 <br>뭐가 이상해 <br>꿈을 포기해버린 니가 <br>더 이상해 이상해 <br>도대체 뭐가 정상인데 <br>난 날 비정상이라고 생각해 <br>근데 넌 나보다 더 비정상 같애 <br>혼자 성공하는 게 뭐 어때 서 <br>니가 왜 내 성공을 논해 <br>내가 살아 남기 위한 방식일 뿐 <br>니가 왜 내 성공을 논해 <br>난 사실 성공이란 단어 <br>어울리지 않을 뿐 <br>니가 왜 내 성공을 논해 <br>내가 살아 남기 위한 방식일 뿐 <br>니가 왜 내 성공을 논해 <br>난 사실 성공이란 단어 <br>어울리지 않을 뿐 <br>친구인 척 뒤에서 까 <br>진짜 친구를 논해 <br>진짜 어이가 없네 <br>이 세상에 진짜 친구가 있기는 해 <br>니 자신을 돌아봐 넌 누군가의 <br>진짜 친구이기는 해 <br>그냥 즐기자고 놀면 편해 <br>거기서 더 가면 너만 심각해 <br>진지 할 때 진지해 <br>술이나 마셔 기분 좋게 <br>고민 털어놓고 싶음 <br>맨 정신에 말해 <br>이상하게 비꼬지 말고 <br>니 생각 제대로 말해 <br>니 고민에 난 비 공감해 <br>니 비공감에 내 성공을 포함해 <br>니가 왜 성공을 논해 <br>니가 왜 내 성공을 논해 <br>내가 살아 남기 위한 방식일 뿐 <br>니가 왜 내 성공을 논해 <br>난 사실 성공이란 단어 <br>어울리지 않을 뿐 <br>니가 왜 내 성공을 논해 <br>내가 살아 남기 위한 방식일 뿐 <br>니가 왜 내 성공을 논해 <br>난 사실 성공이란 단어 <br>어울리지 않을 뿐 <br>]]></content><category term="더블캐슬" label="더블캐슬"/><category term="성공을 논해" label="성공을 논해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더블캐슬/이제_그만_일어나_Feat_2Poo/</id><title>더블캐슬 - 이제 그만 일어나 (Feat. 2Poo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:06:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:06:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/%EC%9D%B4%EC%A0%9C_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A7%8C_%EC%9D%BC%EC%96%B4%EB%82%98_Feat_2Poo/" title="더블캐슬 - 이제 그만 일어나 (Feat. 2Poo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[별로 기다리진 않았지 at 2035 <br>내일 올 줄 알았지 <br>블랙호크 자전거도 <br>그냥 누워 쉬고 있었지 <br>새 청소기 결제하고 <br>주식으로 돈도 벌었지 <br>트럼프가 당선 되도 <br>한 달에 150 월급 <br>지겨워 죽겠어 월 150 <br>모아지지도 않는 돈 <br>새 장비에 갖다 부어 <br>매년 받아 선물 <br>올해는 오븐과 그릴 <br>10만원은 상품권 <br>johnnie walker 사먹어야지 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>작업 못한 날은 잠 안 와 불면증 <br>뿌듯하지 못한 하루가 빠듯하듯 <br>돈은 못 벌어도 괜찮으니까 <br>지금 이 시간 동안 <br>kick &amp; snare 멈추지 않기를 <br>더 바라는 게 없어 <br>쉬는 날 내 작은방 <br>추운 겨울 보일러는 꺼둬 <br>열심히 살아서 <br>좀 피곤하지 오늘은 <br>피곤하길 바래 피곤할수록 <br>빠르게 나오지 내 앨범은 <br>100곡이 넘게 쌓인 작업물 <br>다 꺼내 들어보고 고르고 <br>고른 비트 이걸로 됐어 <br>편히 잠들겠지 오늘밤 <br>아니 잠들 수 없지 바로 <br>다음 앨범 작업 들어가거든 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>hey hey 꿈 깨 <br>뭐가 어떻고 붐뱁 <br>그 랩 구분 해가며 <br>랩하면 쟤가 널 숭배 <br>그딴 거 묻지도 따지지 <br>않지 난 이순재 <br>그만 자고 날 따라오며 <br>터뜨리지 축배 <br>팬들 같은 낙서 <br>종합 비타민 잘 써 <br>니가 잘 때 저기 불 같은 <br>애들 보고 반성 <br>정신차려 그런 <br>실력으로는 아니 돼 <br>어서 두 눈을 뜨고 잠에서 깨 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만하고 자러 가 이제 <br>이제 그만하고 자러 가 이제 <br>이제 그만하고 자러 가 이제 <br>이제 그만하고 자러 가 이제 <br>이제 그만하고 자러 가 이제 <br>이제 그만하고 자러 가 이제 <br>이제 그만하고 자러 가 이제 <br>아니 계속하고 자지마 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>이제 그만 자고 일어나 이제 <br>]]></content><category term="더블캐슬" label="더블캐슬"/><category term="이제 그만 일어나 (Feat. 2Poo)" label="이제 그만 일어나 (Feat. 2Poo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더블캐슬/1004/</id><title>더블캐슬 - 1004 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:06:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:06:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/1004/" title="더블캐슬 - 1004 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[딴 남자들과는 달라 <br>나쁜 남자 아니란 걸 알아 <br>I might be shining like a 천사 <br>난 사람이 아냐 아마 천사 <br>너의 맘 모두가 알아 <br>눈이 마주치고 그땐 알아 봐 <br>may be 느낌이 통해 나도 알아 <br>그래 난 사람이 아닌가 봐 아마 천사 <br>사람들이 말해 나 천사 같대 <br>악마의 반대 천사 같대 그래 맞네 <br>그걸 봤네 등뒤에 펼친 날개 <br>숨기려고 해도 전혀 감출 길이 없네 <br>일이 없네 스트레스 받을 일이 <br>모든 일이 하늘의 뜻 그걸 알게 된 후 <br>사람들이 뭐라 말해도 <br>한숨으로 돌리고 <br>날아 오는 돌직구 유연하게 피하고 <br>날 내려다보는 방법을 <br>터득하게 된 이후 <br>달라진 건 나 하나 이제 만나 너와 나 <br>빠져들어 you &amp; i 후회는 나중에 하고 <br>언젠가 만나 너랑 나 <br>]]></content><category term="더블캐슬" label="더블캐슬"/><category term="1004" label="1004"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Alive_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>Milky Chance - Alive (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Alive_Acoustic_Ver/" title="Milky Chance - Alive (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Think they saw us to share the school <br>Something we need to look every on <br>But that is made up past the moon <br>Fit in the numb for our love <br>Then you do your thing aside <br>Promise at least I get in steady <br>All that I want is that you found <br>Something that makes you stop believing <br><br>I felt my love for you this time <br>Other side, I'm feeling so alive <br>You didn't feel anything at all <br>After all, Makes me feeling small <br>I felt my love for you this time <br>Other side, I'm feeling so alive <br>You didn't feel anything at all <br>After all, Makes me feeling small <br><br>Plenty of time we need to grow <br>Let's take the truth and slow it down <br>There's a lot of love we have to show <br>Maybe it's something faking out <br>Many times we were in trouble <br>I can't deny that I have made some <br>But in the end there's things to know <br>That I was stressed, rushing and breathing <br><br>I felt my love for you this time <br>Other side, I'm feeling so alive <br>You didn't feel anything at all <br>After all, Makes me feeling small <br>I felt my love for you this time <br>Other side, I'm feeling so alive <br>You didn't feel anything at all <br>After all, Makes me feeling small <br><br>Then makes me feeling small <br>Then makes me feeling small <br>Then makes me feeling small]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Alive (Acoustic Ver.)" label="Alive (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Cold_Blue_Rain_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>Milky Chance - Cold Blue Rain (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Cold_Blue_Rain_Acoustic_Ver/" title="Milky Chance - Cold Blue Rain (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cold blue rain <br>I don't wanna think about it <br>Same old place <br>Makes me wanna think about it <br>See your face <br>Remembering that I'm mad about you <br>So why embrace, All the things that you do <br><br>I know that we'll be forever <br>Forever together as one <br>And our hearts will share the same shelter <br>We share a place under the same sun <br>I know that we'll be forever <br>Forever together as one <br>And our hearts will share the same shelter <br>We share a place under the same sun <br><br>Ay Yea aay <br><br>Cold blue rain <br>I don't wanna think about it <br>Same old place <br>That I won't ever want to leave <br>Feel your face <br>Knowing that I'm mad about you <br>So why embrace, you <br>Make me feel like my dreams come true <br><br>I know that we'll be forever <br>Forever together as one <br>And our hearts will share the same shelter <br>We share a place under the same sun <br>I know that we'll be forever <br>Forever together as one <br>And our hearts will share the same shelter <br>We share a place under the same sun <br><br>Yea aay, yeah <br><br>Under the same sun <br>Under the same sun <br>Under the same sun <br>Under the same sun <br><br>Under the same sun <br>Under the same sun]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Cold Blue Rain (Acoustic Ver.)" label="Cold Blue Rain (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Heartless/</id><title>Milky Chance - Heartless - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Heartless/" title="Milky Chance - Heartless - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Remember, That someday the heartless will go <br>Remember, That someday the heartless will go <br>Remember, That someday the heartless will go <br>Remember, That someday the heartless will go <br>Those people know the way <br>Those people know the way <br>Those people know the way <br>Those people know the way <br><br>Remember, That someday the heartless will go <br>Remember, That someday the heartless will go <br>Remember, That someday the heartless will go <br>Remember, That someday the heartless will go]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Heartless" label="Heartless"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Piano_Song/</id><title>Milky Chance - Piano Song - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Piano_Song/" title="Milky Chance - Piano Song - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want you to sit me down <br>Let it go, Just wasting come <br>I was listening to the crooked sound <br>Of a life that was way too loud <br>You're asking me, I don't ever crow <br>I'm just trying to turn it into the blue <br>Is it something that we have to found <br>Out of nothing on a fragile ground <br>Out of nothing on a fragile ground <br><br>Have you ever seen, How far it is <br>To the place where we oughta dream <br>Can you better hear the storming folks <br>Whispering in fear, roars the most <br>Have you ever seen, How far it is <br>To the place where we oughta dream <br>Can you better hear the storming folks <br>Whispering in fear, roars the most <br><br>I want you to lock that door <br>That has always made you want to move <br>Will you ever find a way out there <br>Returning to the room we used to share <br>You're asking me, I don't ever crow <br>I was trying to turn myself into you <br>Is it something that we have to found <br>Out of nothing on a fragile ground <br>Out of nothing on a fragile ground <br><br>Have you ever seen, How far it is <br>To the place where we oughta dream <br>Can you better hear the storming folks <br>Whispering in fear, roars the most <br>Have you ever seen, How far it is <br>To the place where we oughta dream <br>Can you better hear the storming folks <br>Whispering in fear, roars the most]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Piano Song" label="Piano Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Alive/</id><title>Milky Chance - Alive - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Alive/" title="Milky Chance - Alive - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Think they saw us to share the school <br>Something we need to look every on <br>But that is made up past the moon <br>Fit in the numb for our love <br>Then you do your thing aside <br>Promise at least I get in steady <br>All that I want is that you found <br>Something that makes you stop believing <br><br>I felt my love for you this time <br>Other side, I'm feeling so alive <br>You didn't feel anything at all <br>After all, Makes me feeling small <br>I felt my love for you this time <br>Other side, I'm feeling so alive <br>You didn't feel anything at all <br>After all, Makes me feeling small <br><br>Plenty of time we need to grow <br>Let's take the truth and slow it down <br>There's a lot of love we have to show <br>Maybe it's something faking out <br>Many times we were in trouble <br>I can't deny that I have made some <br>But in the end there's things to know <br>That I was stressed, rushing and breathing <br><br>I felt my love for you this time <br>Other side, I'm feeling so alive <br>You didn't feel anything at all <br>After all, Makes me feeling small <br>I felt my love for you this time <br>Other side, I'm feeling so alive <br>You didn't feel anything at all <br>After all, Makes me feeling small]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Alive" label="Alive"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Peripeteia/</id><title>Milky Chance - Peripeteia - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Peripeteia/" title="Milky Chance - Peripeteia - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Broken hearts made of stone, Did we lose our sensitivity <br>Now you can find them all alone, watching flaming dreams go by <br>You're trying to catch the break of dawn, Blame it on your curiosity <br>So eternally, your inner dreams come back and out into the sun, Into the sun <br><br>Now we have a lot of love to give <br>But it's not with each to all the misery <br>I dream of a past that we could have <br>Feel like we made up so entirely <br>Now we have a lot of love to give <br>But it's not with each to all the misery <br>I dream of a past that we could have <br>Feel like we made up so entirely <br><br>You stick around, You got it bad but no one's out there you can listen to <br>It seems to be so hard to find the colorful state of mind <br>But still you're trying to catch it all, Blame it on your own philosophy <br>Eventually, your inner dreams come back and out into the sun, Into the sun <br><br>Now we have a lot of love to give <br>But it's not with each to all the misery <br>I dream of a past that we could have <br>Feel like we made up so entirely <br>Now we have a lot of love to give <br>But it's not with each to all the misery <br>I dream of a past that we could have <br>Feel like we made up so entirely <br><br>Now we have a lot of love to give <br>But it's not with each to all the misery <br>I dream of a past that we could have <br>Feel like we made up so entirely <br>Now we have a lot of love to give <br>But it's not with each to all the misery <br>I dream of a past that we could have <br>Feel like we made up so entirely]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Peripeteia" label="Peripeteia"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Losing_You/</id><title>Milky Chance - Losing You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Losing_You/" title="Milky Chance - Losing You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They say that I'm 'bout to lose you tell me why <br>It's been a lot of confusion still we try <br>They say that I'm 'bout to lose you tell me why <br>It's been a lot of confusion still we try <br><br>Need to make some time <br>Who's to say, If I'm alright <br>And take another lie <br>Til they drop the common lie <br>Then how to tell a lie <br>Who's to blame for such a try <br>Want to make it right <br>With you, Just gotta hold me tight <br><br>They say that I'm about to lose you tell me why <br>It's been a lot of confusion still we try <br>They say that I'm about to lose you tell me why <br>It's been a lot of confusion still we try <br><br>Need to make some time <br>Who's to say, If I'm alright <br>And take another lie <br>Til they drop the common lie <br>Then how to tell a lie <br>Who's to blame for such a try <br>Want to make it right <br>With you, Just gotta hold me tight <br><br>We need to make some time <br>Running for the common lie <br>We need to make some time <br>Running for the common lie <br>We need to make some time <br>Running for the common lie <br>Running for the common lie]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Losing You" label="Losing You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Cocoon/</id><title>Milky Chance - Cocoon - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Cocoon/" title="Milky Chance - Cocoon - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Eh ah, eh ah, eh ah, eh oh <br>Eh ah, eh ah, oh <br>Eh ah, eh ah, eh ah, eh oh <br>Eh ah, eh ah, oh <br><br>I know that you must feel like facing with a ruin, facing with a ruin <br>I messed it up as always, I'm afraid of losing, I'm afraid of losing <br>I made you thinking oh so wrong <br>I made you feeling the worst <br>And I don't how to get along <br>With myself when I'm weakened <br>When I'm weakened <br><br>So let's go back to our cocoon <br>On the blackened afternoon <br>I see your heart is beating too <br>Let me bleed instead of you <br>So let's go back to our cocoon <br>On the blackened afternoon <br>I see your heart is beating too <br>Let me bleed instead of you <br>Let me bleed, let me bleed <br>Eh ah, eh ah <br>Let me bleed, let me bleed <br>Eh ah, eh ah <br>Instead of you <br><br>I've been always playing <br>Solid as I'm waving, solid as I'm waving <br>So I became a liar, I've been underrating <br>Overestimated <br>I made it really hard for you <br>Hard for you to love me <br>But there's so many things we could do <br>And all we need is escaping, escaping <br><br>So let's go back to our cocoon <br>On the blackened afternoon <br>I see your heart is beating too <br>Let me bleed instead of you <br>So let's go back to our cocoon <br>On the blackened afternoon <br>I see your heart is beating too <br>Let me bleed instead of you <br>Let me bleed, let me bleed <br>Eh ah, eh ah <br>Let me bleed, let me bleed <br>Eh ah, eh ah <br>Instead of you <br><br>Eh ah, eh ah, oh <br>Eh ah, eh ah <br><br>So let's go back to our cocoon <br>On the blackened afternoon <br>I see your heart is beating too <br>Let me bleed instead of you <br>So let's go back to our cocoon <br>On the blackened afternoon <br>I see your heart is beating too <br>Let me bleed instead of you <br>Let me bleed, let me bleed <br>Let me bleed, let me bleed <br>Let me bleed, now I will bleed <br>Instead of you]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Cocoon" label="Cocoon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Bad_Things_Feat_Izzy_Bizu/</id><title>Milky Chance - Bad Things (Feat. Izzy Bizu) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Bad_Things_Feat_Izzy_Bizu/" title="Milky Chance - Bad Things (Feat. Izzy Bizu) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Getting through to you <br>Is what I'm aiming for <br>Won't you hear me now <br>Like you've done before <br><br>Are we going round in circles <br>Are we running out of time, Are we <br>Are we losing something precious <br>Are we hanging onto something special <br>I think so <br><br>'Cause when you're conquering <br>My day and night <br>Easing, The pain inside <br>Got me laughing, All of the time <br>Keep the bad things out of my mind <br>Out of my mind <br><br>Eyes caressing my skin <br>Undressing my every flaw <br>Ooh will we sink or swim <br>We're blinded on an empty shore <br><br>Are we going round in circles <br>Are we running out of time, are we <br>Are we losing something precious <br>Are we hanging onto something special <br>I think so <br><br>'Cause when you're conquering <br>My day and night <br>Easing, The pain inside <br>Got me laughing, All of the time <br>Keep the bad things out of my mind <br>Out of my mind <br><br>I don't mind wasting time <br>Let's stop and smell the roses <br>I don't mind wasting time <br>Let's stop and smell the roses <br>Ooh, How I know the odds are set high <br>As ever need to hang me out to dry <br>Ooh help me please my hands are tied <br>Don't have the courage just to tell you goodbye <br><br>'Cause when you're conquering <br>My day and night <br>Easing <br>The pain inside <br>Got me laughing <br>All of the time <br>Keep the bad things out of my mind <br><br>Out of my mind <br><br>'Cause when you're conquering <br>My day and night <br>Easing, The pain inside <br>Got me laughing <br>All of the time <br>Keep the bad things out of my mind <br>Out of my mind <br>'Cause when you're conquering <br>My day and night <br>Easing, The pain inside <br>Got me laughing, All of the time <br>Keep the bad things out of my mind <br>Out of my mind <br><br>I don't mind wasting time <br>Let's stop and smell the roses <br>I don't mind wasting time <br>Let's stop and smell the roses]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Bad Things (Feat. Izzy Bizu)" label="Bad Things (Feat. Izzy Bizu)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Stay/</id><title>Milky Chance - Stay - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Stay/" title="Milky Chance - Stay - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[After all that's been really tough for us <br>Trying to make it for you <br>Knowing that it could be the last, thing I've done for you <br>It's the end as a a always, confused <br>Spend my time, trying to read our past <br>Remembering that feeling <br><br>Don't fool around, run away <br>'Cause there is someone who wants you to stay <br>Don't fool around, run away <br>'Cause there is someone who wants you <br>Wants you to stay eh eh yeah eh eh <br>Wants you to stay eh eh yeah eh eh <br>Wants you to stay eh eh yeah eh eh <br>Wants you to stay <br>Wants you to stay <br><br>After overcoming hour after hour <br>Ignoring all your demons <br>You'll collapse on the cover of your darkness <br>Strangling with feelings <br>Yes it is yes, but a a always confusing <br>Be the one that you always wanted to be <br>Can you really see then <br><br>Don't fool around, run away <br>'Cause there is someone who wants you to stay <br>Don't fool around, run away <br>'Cause there is someone who wants you <br>Wants you to stay eh eh yeah eh eh <br>Wants you to stay eh eh yeah eh eh <br>Wants you to stay eh eh yeah eh eh <br>Wants you to stay <br>Wants you to stay <br><br>Don't fool around, run away <br>'Cause there is someone who wants you to stay <br>And don't fool around, run away <br>'Cause there is someone who wants you]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Stay" label="Stay"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Cold_Blue_Rain/</id><title>Milky Chance - Cold Blue Rain - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Cold_Blue_Rain/" title="Milky Chance - Cold Blue Rain - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cold blue rain <br>I don't wanna think about it <br>Same old place <br>Makes me wanna think about it <br>See your face <br>Remembering that I'm mad about you <br>So I embrace all the things that you do <br><br>I know that we'll be forever <br>Forever together as one <br>Our hearts will share the same shelter <br>We share a place under the same sun <br>I know that we'll be forever <br>Forever together as one <br>Our hearts will share the same shelter <br>We share a place under the same sun <br><br>My heart is running for your love <br>My heart is running for your love <br>My heart is running for your love <br>My heart <br>My heart is running for your love <br>My heart is running for your love <br>My heart is running for your love <br><br>Cold blue rain <br>Standing right in front of me <br>Same old place <br>That I won't ever want to leave <br>Feel your face <br>Knowing that I'm mad about you <br>So I embrace you <br>You make me feel like my dreams come true <br><br>I know that we'll be forever <br>Forever together as one <br>Our hearts will share the same shelter <br>We share a place under the same sun <br>I know that we'll be forever <br>Forever together as one <br>Our hearts will share the same shelter <br>We share a place under the same sun <br><br>My heart is running for your love <br>My heart is running for your love <br>My heart is running for your love <br>My heart <br>My heart is running for your love <br>My heart is running for your love <br>My heart is running for your love <br>My heart]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Cold Blue Rain" label="Cold Blue Rain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Clouds/</id><title>Milky Chance - Clouds - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Clouds/" title="Milky Chance - Clouds - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You came up in my heart <br>Like the sun and the stars <br>Maybe I'll be the moon <br>So we can shine pretty soon <br>Then we drift through the night <br>When it's getting too cold <br>I notice you'll be around <br>Living stories you've told <br><br>There's nothing ever out there but some gathering clouds <br>I just wanna take care of you my love <br>There's nothing ever out there but some gathering clouds <br>I just wanna take care of you my love <br><br>Of you my love <br>Of you my love <br>Of you my love <br>Of you my love <br><br>And then she stuck in my head <br>Like a radiant rose <br>Make me dreaming away <br>Feels like getting too close <br>I just want you to stay <br>Just don't leave me alone <br>Many times I was wrong, But your truth loving is strong <br><br>It's not the ever of it, But some gathering clouds <br>I just wanna take care of you my love <br>It's not the ever of it, But some gathering clouds <br>I just wanna take care of you my love <br><br>Of you my love <br>Of you my love <br>Of you my love <br>Of you my love <br>Of you my love <br>Of you my love <br>Of you my love <br>Of you my love]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Clouds" label="Clouds"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Doing_Good/</id><title>Milky Chance - Doing Good - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Doing_Good/" title="Milky Chance - Doing Good - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Calling you lovable <br>How are you feeling now <br>Making it all above <br>Falling for you somehow <br><br>I can't refuse you walking along the lonely way <br>Wish I could hear you everytime but all you say <br><br>Is I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing so good <br><br>Calling you lovable <br>How are you feeling now <br>Making it all above <br>Falling for you somehow <br><br>I can't refuse you walking along the lonely way <br>Wish I could hear you everytime but all you say <br><br>Is I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing so good <br><br>Calling you lovable <br>How are you feeling now <br>Making it all above <br>Falling for you somehow <br><br>I can't refuse you walking along the lonely way <br>Wish I could hear you everytime but all you say <br><br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Doing Good" label="Doing Good"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Firebird/</id><title>Milky Chance - Firebird - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Firebird/" title="Milky Chance - Firebird - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There may be some but none like you <br>We'll be understood 'cause you're the truth <br>Give me a few more off to do <br>Call is conquering the love for you <br><br>I keep my eyes wide open so I <br>Can see there's a rain drop falling away <br>But if your words get suddenly blurred <br>You 'member that the truth is always worth, seeing <br><br>You're like a firebird in the sky <br>Shining for a challenger in the night <br>Just like a firebird is your heart <br>Keeps me warm and anchory in the stars <br>You're like a firebird <br>You're like a firebird <br><br>Courageous wings make things go far <br>Lingering solitude can rip them off <br>So let the wind cross your ash thoughts <br>Giving you the strength to carry on <br><br>I keep my eyes wide open so I <br>Can see there's a rain drop falling away <br>But if your words get suddenly blurred <br>You 'member that the truth is always worth, seeing <br><br>You're like a firebird in the sky <br>Shining for a challenger in the night <br>Just like a firebird is your heart <br>Keeps me warm and anchory in the stars <br>You're like a firebird <br>You're like a firebird <br>You're like a firebird <br>You're like a firebird <br><br>You're like <br>You're like]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Firebird" label="Firebird"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Ego/</id><title>Milky Chance - Ego - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Ego/" title="Milky Chance - Ego - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ego, see your ego <br>Ego, see your ego, oh <br><br>I'm missing my miss of roses <br>Holding my head up high and <br>My head up high and <br>I know that she is stronger <br>Cause she can break the silence, break the silence <br>So meet me by the sea, you see it's ours <br>And our place to be somewhere else <br><br>Gold shimmering sand is making me thinking of her <br>Thinking of her <br>But I am at Half Moon Bay <br>It's just too far away <br>Just too far away <br>Gold shimmering sand is making me thinking of her <br>Thinking of her <br>But I am at Half Moon Bay <br>It's just too far away <br>Just too far away <br><br>Ego, see your ego <br>Ego, see your ego <br>Ego, see your ego <br>Ego, see your ego <br><br>When I'm seeing my miss of roses <br>The world is turning slower <br>Turning slower <br>And I guess that she's the strongest <br>That I have ever seen yet <br>Ever seen yet <br>And all along the way she'll need our love <br>Got to care of her now <br>Care of her now <br>So meet us by the sea, you see it's ours <br>And our place to be somewhere else <br><br>Gold shimmering sand is making me thinking of her <br>Thinking of her <br>But I am at Half Moon Bay <br>It's just too far away <br>Just too far away, and <br>Gold shimmering sand is making me thinking of her <br>Thinking of her <br>But I am at Half Moon Bay <br>It's just too far away <br>Just too far away <br><br>Ego, see your ego <br>Ego, see your ego <br>Ego, see your ego <br>Ego, see your ego <br>Just too far away <br>Ego, see your ego <br>Ego, see your ego <br>Just too far away <br>Ego, see your ego <br>Ego, see your ego]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Ego" label="Ego"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Blossom/</id><title>Milky Chance - Blossom - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:23:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:23:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Blossom/" title="Milky Chance - Blossom - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yes I'm tired of all this talking <br>'Cause everything you hear is empty words <br>But who am I, oh to say this <br>'Cause everything you hear is just words, yeah <br><br>You have to trust in someone, trust in someone, trust in someone <br>Cause the truth is <br><br>'Cause all I need is to see you <br>Blossom out, blossom out, blossom out <br>And all I feel, is that I need you <br>To blossom out, blossom out, blossom out <br>And all I need is to see you <br>Blossom out, blossom out, blossom out <br>And all I feel, is that I need you <br>To blossom out, blossom out, blossom out <br><br>And I'm tired of constant sorrow <br>'Cause everything you get is just worse <br>So what's the point of going somewhere <br>When everyone you see is just nothing but confused <br><br>You have to trust in someone, trust in someone, trust in someone <br>Cause the truth is <br><br>'Cause all I need is to see you <br>Blossom out, blossom out, blossom out <br>And all I feel, is that I need you <br>To blossom out, blossom out, blossom out <br>And all I need is to see you <br>Blossom out, blossom out, blossom out <br>And all I feel, is that I need you <br>To blossom out, blossom out, blossom out <br><br>'Cause all I need is to see you <br>Blossom out, blossom out, blossom out <br>And all I feel, is that I need you <br>To blossom out, blossom out, blossom out <br>To blossom out, blossom out, blossom out <br>To blossom out, blossom out, blossom out]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Blossom" label="Blossom"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/옥주현/단_한번의_순간_Before_And_After_You___One_Second_And_A_Million_Miles/</id><title>옥주현 - 단 한번의 순간 (Before And After You / One Second And A Million Miles) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:24:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:24:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A5%EC%A3%BC%ED%98%84/%EB%8B%A8_%ED%95%9C%EB%B2%88%EC%9D%98_%EC%88%9C%EA%B0%84_Before_And_After_You___One_Second_And_A_Million_Miles/" title="옥주현 - 단 한번의 순간 (Before And After You / One Second And A Million Miles) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[당신을 끌어안을 때 <br>그 숨결을 느낄 때 <br>내 안의 모든 건 새로워져 <br>휘몰아치는 키스에 <br>두 개로 부서진 나 <br>널 알기 전과 후 <br>우연처럼 다가온 너 <br>난 무너져 버렸어 <br>나에게 무슨 짓을 한거죠 <br>당신 품에 안겼을 때 <br>마주쳐 버린 운명 <br>이젠 알게 됐어 <br>부서진 내 모습 <br>널 알기 전과 후 <br>태어나 처음으로 <br>내가 세상 속에 있어 <br>카메라 뒤에서 바라만 보던 <br>그 곳 여기에 <br>태어나 처음으로 <br>내가 누군가의 일부 <br>나의 일부 나의 전부 <br>너를 놓칠 수 없어 <br>태어나 처음으로 <br>나를 이끄는 강한 빛 <br>우릴 가둘 것은 없어 <br>너와 나 함께라면 <br>태어나 처음으로 <br>나의 모든 걸 걸겠어 <br>이젠 나를 봐 프란체스카 <br>떠나자 <br>다가올 날들이 어떤 모습일지 <br>알 순 없지만 <br>그대 지금까지 몰랐던 <br>세계를 보게 될거야 <br>숨쉬는 거대한 세상을 <br>또 하나 말할 수 있는 건 <br>신이 창조한 이 시간 속에 <br>너와 나 단 한번의 순간 <br>또다시 오지 않을 순간 <br>너와 나 놓칠 순 없어 <br>지금 내 앞의 그대 <br>화려한 명예나 돈은 필요 없어 <br>당신이 없다면 아무 의미 없어 <br>이제 내 삶엔 오직 하나 그대 뿐 <br>놓칠 수는 없어 <br>그냥 날 믿어 <br>자유로운 너의 영혼을 봐 <br>꿈을 이룬 널 상상해 봐 <br>멈추지 않는 계절 속에 <br>오 너와 나 단 한번의 순간 <br>또 다시 오지 않을 순간 <br>너와 나 놓칠 순 없어 <br>지금 내 앞의 그대 <br>어쩔 수 없는 나 <br>널 알기 전과 후 <br>떠나자 <br>부서진 내 모습 <br>널 알기 전과 후 <br>떠나자 <br>말해줘요 내게 말해줘요 <br>어떻게 떠나요 <br>가방을 챙기고 문을 닫고 <br>돌아서면 되나요 <br>내가 누구인지 당신도 알잖아 <br>버릴 수 없잖아요 <br>말해줘요 어떻게 떠나요 <br>다가올 일들이 어떤 모습일지 <br>알 순 없지만 <br>분명히 우린 서로 느끼고 있어 <br>명백한 운명 <br>하나로 묶인 당신과 나 <br>절대로 끊어지지 않아 <br>우린 순간을 영원으로 바꿀거야 <br>널 떠나지 않아 <br>너와 나 단 한 번의 순간 <br>또 다시 오지 않을 순간 <br>너와 나 놓칠 순 없어 <br>지금 내 앞의 그대 <br>기나긴 시간을 건너 <br>기나긴 시간을 건너 <br>기나긴 시간을 건너 <br>기나긴 시간을 건너 <br>바로 너와 나 <br>단 한번의 순간 <br>지금 내 앞의 그대 <br>떠나자 <br>]]></content><category term="옥주현" label="옥주현"/><category term="단 한번의 순간 (Before And After You / One Second And A Million Miles)" label="단 한번의 순간 (Before And After You / One Second And A Million Miles)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BONNIE_X_CLYDE/Tonight/</id><title>BONNIE X CLYDE - Tonight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:24:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:24:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BONNIE_X_CLYDE/Tonight/" title="BONNIE X CLYDE - Tonight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Show me how, how to get you now <br>I've been thinking about, thinking about you now <br>Thinking about you now <br>Let me know when the feeling's right <br>I'mma take you there, take you down tonight <br>Take you down tonight <br><br>Tonight <br>Tonight <br>Tonight <br>Tonight <br><br>Are you down, down for the ride <br>I've been thinking about, thinking about you now <br>Thinking about you now <br>Will I know when the feeling's right <br>I'mma take you there, take you down tonight <br>Take you down tonight <br><br>Tonight <br>Tonight <br>Tonight <br>Tonight <br><br>Tonight <br>Tonight <br>Tonight <br>Tonight <br>Show me how <br>Are you down <br>Are you <br><br>Tonight]]></content><category term="BONNIE X CLYDE" label="BONNIE X CLYDE"/><category term="Tonight" label="Tonight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BONNIE_X_CLYDE/Out_Of_My_System/</id><title>BONNIE X CLYDE - Out Of My System - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:24:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:24:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BONNIE_X_CLYDE/Out_Of_My_System/" title="BONNIE X CLYDE - Out Of My System - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Getting you out of my system <br>Getting you out of my system <br>Getting you out of my system <br><br>You with my addiction <br>Gets you out of my system gets you out of my system <br><br>Getting you out of my system <br>Getting you out of my system <br><br>Getting you out of my system <br>Getting you out <br>Getting you out of my system <br>Getting you out]]></content><category term="BONNIE X CLYDE" label="BONNIE X CLYDE"/><category term="Out Of My System" label="Out Of My System"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BONNIE_X_CLYDE/Hooked/</id><title>BONNIE X CLYDE - Hooked - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:24:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:24:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BONNIE_X_CLYDE/Hooked/" title="BONNIE X CLYDE - Hooked - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm hooked on you <br>I'm hooked on you <br>I'm hooked on you <br>I'm hooked on you <br><br>I can't get enough <br>I'm hooked on you hooked on you <br>Hooked on you <br>I can't get enough <br>I'm hooked on you <br>Hooked on you <br><br>Love is like a drug <br>I'm hooked on you hooked on you <br>Hooked on you <br>I can't get enough <br>I'm hooked on you <br>Hooked on you <br><br>I can't get enough <br>I'm hooked on you <br>Hooked on you <br><br>I'm hooked on you <br>I'm hooked on you <br>Hooked on you]]></content><category term="BONNIE X CLYDE" label="BONNIE X CLYDE"/><category term="Hooked" label="Hooked"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BONNIE_X_CLYDE/Bass_Jam/</id><title>BONNIE X CLYDE - Bass Jam - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:24:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:24:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BONNIE_X_CLYDE/Bass_Jam/" title="BONNIE X CLYDE - Bass Jam - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We get wasted, in the basement <br>I don't know, I don't know where we're goin' <br>We play bass jams, in the basement <br>And I don't know, I don't know where do we go from here <br><br>Where do we go from here <br>Where do we go from here <br>Where do we go from here <br><br>Imma let the bass, take me away <br>Take me to a place away from here <br>Imma let the bass, run this place <br>Take me far away, away from here <br><br>Where do we go <br>Where do we go <br>Where do we go from here <br>Where do we go <br>Where do we go <br>Where do we go from here <br><br>Stay up all night, 'til the sunlight <br>And we don't know, we don't know what time it is <br>Playing bass jams, getting wasted <br>And we don't know, we don't know <br><br>Where do we go from here <br>Where do we go from here <br>Where do we go from here <br><br>Imma let the bass, take me away <br>Take me to a place away from here <br>Imma let the bass, run this place <br>Take me far away, away from here <br><br>Where do we go <br>Where do we go <br>Where do we go from here <br>Where do we go <br>Where do we go <br>Where do we go from here <br><br>Imma let the bass take me away <br>Imma let the bass take me away <br><br>Where do we go from here where do we go <br>Where do we go from here where do we go <br>Where do we go from here <br>Where do we go from here <br><br>Imma let the bass, take me away <br>Take me to a place away from here <br>Imma let the bass, run this place <br>Take me far away, away from here <br><br>Where do we go <br>Where do we go <br>Where do we go from here <br>Where do we go <br>Where do we go <br>Where do we go from here]]></content><category term="BONNIE X CLYDE" label="BONNIE X CLYDE"/><category term="Bass Jam" label="Bass Jam"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BONNIE_X_CLYDE/In_The_City/</id><title>BONNIE X CLYDE - In The City - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:24:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:24:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BONNIE_X_CLYDE/In_The_City/" title="BONNIE X CLYDE - In The City - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come to life <br>Come to life <br>In the city where we come, come alive <br>In the city where we come <br>It eats you alive <br><br>I won't wait any longer <br>This feeling inside <br>I won't wait any longer <br>You're taking over <br><br>In the city where we come, come alive <br>In the city where we come, come alive <br><br>I won't wait any longer <br>This feeling inside <br>I won't wait any longer <br><br>Come alive <br><br>In the city where we come, come alive <br>In the city where we come, it eats you alive <br><br>I won't wait any longer <br>This feeling inside <br>I won't wait any longer <br>You're taking over <br>You're taking over <br><br>In the city where we come, come alive <br>In the city where we come, come alive]]></content><category term="BONNIE X CLYDE" label="BONNIE X CLYDE"/><category term="In The City" label="In The City"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kev/Pushed_Away/</id><title>Kev - Pushed Away - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:24:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:24:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kev/Pushed_Away/" title="Kev - Pushed Away - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pushed away from me, p p pushed away from me <br><br>You wanna love me <br>I am not to love <br>You wanna trust me <br>But I trust no one <br>If you were to think I would do anything to protect you <br>You know I can't right my wrongs even though I'll be with you <br><br>You don't fit in in my life <br>You will be pushed away from me <br>P p pushed away from me <br>All my dark sides in my life <br>You will be pushed away from me <br>P p pushed away from me <br><br>Why don't you know me <br>You would understand <br>And when I am with you <br>I would hold your hand <br>If you were to think I would do anything to protect you <br>You know I can't right my wrongs even though I'll be with you <br><br>You don't fit in in my life <br>You will be pushed away from me <br>P p pushed away from me <br>All my dark sides in my life <br>You will be pushed away from me <br>P p pushed away from me <br><br>You wanna love me <br>I am not to love <br>You wanna trust me <br>But I trust no one <br>If you were to think I would do anything to protect you <br>You know I can't right my wrongs even though I'll be with you <br><br>You don't fit in in my life <br>You will be pushed away from me <br>P p pushed away from me <br>All my dark sides in my life <br>You will be pushed away from me <br>P p pushed away from me <br><br>P p pushed away from me <br><br>Pushed away from me, p p pushed away from me]]></content><category term="Kev" label="Kev"/><category term="Pushed Away" label="Pushed Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kev/Visionary/</id><title>Kev - Visionary - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:24:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:24:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kev/Visionary/" title="Kev - Visionary - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm still believing that there's another dream <br>A dream when you and I forget <br>That we skip the red lights <br>Cause we are almost there, yeah <br>We fight and fight until we win <br>We're gonna make it all alone Visionary <br>Cause you and I we're on the throne Visionary <br><br>Just let the midnight take you cause I'ma be there <br>I'll be the one you reach for <br>Hold on I swear <br>I'm on the clouds reaching <br>I am you know, visionary, visionary <br><br>We'll live forever <br>We know it's meant to be <br>A dream when you and I forget <br>And they say we're floating <br>It's time to let them see, yeah <br>We fight and fight until we win <br>We're gonna make it all alone Visionary <br>Cause you and I we're on the throne Visionary <br><br>Just let the midnight take you cause I'ma be there <br>I'll be the one you reach for <br>Hold on I swear <br>I'm on the clouds reaching <br>I am you know, visionary, visionary]]></content><category term="Kev" label="Kev"/><category term="Visionary" label="Visionary"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kev/Hometown/</id><title>Kev - Hometown - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:25:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:25:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kev/Hometown/" title="Kev - Hometown - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We'll be running from a place like this <br>We'll be fucking 'round for so long <br>And burning bridges in our hometown <br>Running fast and we don't slow down <br><br>Yeah we'll be searching for places <br>And we'll be running 'till the break of dawn <br>This time we both now that we can't go on <br>As long as we aim for the stars <br><br>Where do we go from here <br>We're always running though the red lights <br>All we wanted for a long time <br><br>Where do we go from here <br>Will we ever find the right side <br>All we wanted was to shine bright <br><br>When they saw us on the street they say <br>You should go back to where you came from <br>And the message's always coming away <br>And throw it like the way it shapes us <br><br>Now we'll be searching for places <br>And we'll be running 'till the break of dawn <br>This time we both now that we can't go on <br><br>Yeah we'll be searching for places <br>And we'll be running 'till the break of dawn <br>This time we both now that we can't go on <br>As long as we aim for the stars <br><br>Where do we go from here <br>We're always running though the red lights <br>All we wanted for a long time <br><br>Where do we go from here <br>Will we ever find the right side <br>All we wanted was to shine bright <br><br>No place where we can hide <br>We need to take this ride <br>I promise the world is ours <br>As long as we aim for the stars <br><br>Where do we go from here <br>We're always running though the red lights <br>All we wanted for a long time <br><br>Where do we go from here]]></content><category term="Kev" label="Kev"/><category term="Hometown" label="Hometown"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kev/Moments/</id><title>Kev - Moments - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:25:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:25:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kev/Moments/" title="Kev - Moments - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We have our moments <br>When the sun goes down <br>Taking over the city <br>We take over the crown <br>They say we are dreamers <br>That it's in our mind <br>But I feel it in my heart <br>I can feel it loud <br><br>We'll make the time stop <br>We'll make the beat drop <br>And we know this feeling <br>We can take it all <br>So get up now <br>We're gonna make it loud <br><br>You know where to find us <br>As the sun goes down <br>All over the city <br>All over the world <br>We live with the moments <br>That are in our minds <br>And I feel it in my heart <br>I can feel it loud <br><br>We'll make the time stop <br>We'll make the beat drop <br>And we know this feeling <br>We can take it all <br>So get up now <br>We're gonna make it loud <br><br>So you call me up <br>In the middle of the night <br>Standing all alone <br>And it's always dark <br>But when I warm up <br>And we feel the rush <br><br>So get up now <br>So get up now <br>We're gonna make it loud]]></content><category term="Kev" label="Kev"/><category term="Moments" label="Moments"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Romeo_Elvis/Drole_De_Question/</id><title>Romeo Elvis - Drole De Question - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:25:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:25:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Romeo_Elvis/Drole_De_Question/" title="Romeo Elvis - Drole De Question - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[En voila une drole de question <br>J'aurais pas passe des mois a t'faire la cour <br>Si j'avais d'autres femmes en tete <br>C'est toi ma raison d'etre, viens a la maison babe <br>J'ai pris des resolutions <br>En voila une drole de question <br>J'aurais pas passe des mois a t'faire la cour <br>Si j'avais d'autres femmes en tete <br>C'est toi ma raison d'etre, viens a la maison babe <br>J'ai pris des resolutions <br><br>Je veux que tu glisses sur le sol <br>Je veux qu'on s'epuise sur le divan <br>Je veux que tu passes un disque de Queen, j'veux du soleil <br>Je veux aller voir entre les cuisses dans le silence <br>Je veux que tu saches que j'ai la trique, j'suis au sommet <br>Tu vas devoir eteindre ma c'est ton probleme <br>Bebe j'suis toujours un romantique <br>T'es la seule femme dans ma vie <br>Les autres c'etait des fausses, c'etait des moches <br>Mais toi t'es trop belle <br>Tu m'as suivi a la maison <br>J'ai endormi tous tes soupcons <br>Dans une armoire montee par mes propres phrases <br>C'est toi ma raison d'etre, j'en ai plus dans la tete <br>Au probleme, sa solution <br>J'ai la weed, oublie la pression <br>Apres l'doobie faut pas stresser <br>Cherie tu me regardes comme si, un jour, j'allais te blesser <br>ca m'empeche d'avoir la trique qu'il faut pour qu'on puisse baiser comme des tortues <br><br>Je veux que tu glisses sur le sol <br>Je veux qu'on s'epuise sur le divan <br>Je veux que tu passes un disque de Queen, j'veux du soleil <br>Je veux aller voir entre les cuisses dans le silence <br>Je veux envoyer la dynamite sur tes problemes <br>Recolter le fruit de notre nuit, loin du sommeil <br>Bebe, j'suis toujours un romantique <br>Quand je parlais a d'autres fille <br>C'etait simplement pour leur dire <br>a quel point c'est toi la plus belle <br><br>En voila une drole de question <br>Je te jure c'est toi la plus belle <br>En voila une drole de question <br>Ouais vraiment, quand je t'embrasse c'est comme <br>Une sorte de dauphin sophistique <br><br>Corps contre corps, levres contre levres <br>Cherie c'est la seule facon qui marche pour coller <br>J't'aimais deja au college <br>L'amour au travail, c'est nul <br>Mais toi t'etais pas une collegue <br>Et si c'est pas toi, beh c'est pas toi <br>Et c'est pas une autre, promis <br>Pour toi j'abandonnerais le trone, peut etre le cro mi <br>Mais avant faut que tu me dises Je t'aime <br>Il faut que ca sorte de ta bouche <br>Comme dans un film de merde <br>Les filles d'avant c'etait des lope sa <br>On peut s'tromper mais je serai fidele <br>On est d'accord pour ce manege <br>Je te donne le love que tu merites meme si tu me rends le dixieme <br>J'ai tout note sur un carnet <br><br>En voila une drole de question, une drole de question <br>En voila une drole de question <br>En voila une drole de question <br>Une drole de questio]]></content><category term="Romeo Elvis" label="Romeo Elvis"/><category term="Drole De Question" label="Drole De Question"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Everywhere/Better_Off_Alone/</id><title>Everywhere - Better Off Alone - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:25:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:25:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Everywhere/Better_Off_Alone/" title="Everywhere - Better Off Alone - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You say I’m better off alone <br>On my own <br>Some try try to tie and bind <br>But you think I’m better on my own <br>Is it true <br>Tell me I’m in love with you <br>As long as it’s alright <br>Is it true is it true <br>Tell me I’m in love with you <br>Tell me you’re all mine <br>You claim I’m better off alone <br>On my own <br>So when you try try to make it right <br>You fail cuz I’ve fallen out of sight <br>Is it true <br>Tell me I’m in love with you <br>As long as it’s alright <br>Is it true is it true <br>Tell me I’m in love with you <br>Tell me you’re all mine <br>Cuz I’m better off alone <br>On my own I just can’t be <br>Please go on and rescue me <br>Is it true is it true <br>Tell me I’m in love with you <br>As long as it’s alright <br>Is it true is it true <br>Tell me I’m in love with you <br>Tell me you’re all mine <br>Cuz I’m better off alone <br>On my own I just can’t be <br>Please go on and rescue me <br>Cuz I’m better off alone <br>On my own I just can’t be <br>Please go on and rescue me <br>Come rescue me <br>Come rescue me <br>Come rescue me <br>Come rescue me <br>Cuz I’m better off alone <br>On my own I just can’t be <br>I’ll come back home <br>please rescue me <br>]]></content><category term="Everywhere" label="Everywhere"/><category term="Better Off Alone" label="Better Off Alone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Clouds_Feat_Jay_Park__Clara/</id><title>Dumbfoundead - Clouds (Feat. Jay Park &amp; Clara) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:25:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:25:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dumbfoundead/Clouds_Feat_Jay_Park__Clara/" title="Dumbfoundead - Clouds (Feat. Jay Park &amp; Clara) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dumbfoundead Jay Park Clara C <br>To all the people out there goin’ <br>through some tough times <br>This one’s for you <br>Yo <br>There's light <br>at the end of the tunnel <br>I haven't seen it <br>Not all of us become rockstars <br>and ballerinas <br>Even in California the sun <br>ain't always beamin’ <br>Can't predict the forecast <br>for all four seasons <br>We have dark days <br>Can't make your car payments <br>Workin’ a whackass job livin’ <br>in mom's basement <br>Some lands never get rain <br>so there's starvation <br>Some only see snow <br>through neighborhoods scarfaces <br>Not everything is set in stone <br>The weather changes <br>It's like god and the devils <br>trying <br>to entertain us <br>Walked in the treacherous storm <br>and overcame it <br>It is never an easy path <br>on the road to greatness <br>So don't you give me <br>that boo hoo hoo shit <br>We're movin’ on to dat <br>new new new shit <br>Look up into the clouds <br>and watch it blow away <br>Until my problems just go away <br>When the clouds are in the sky <br>Know that they're just passin’ by <br>There'll be sunshine <br>Yeah <br>If your days are stormy nights <br>Dry the raindrops from your eyes <br>There'll be sunshine <br>Yo everybody works hard <br>for their goals to achieve <br>But like the ocean is sea man <br>the motion is free <br>So nothin’ ever adds up <br>the way we want it to <br>I guess my math teacher was <br>just a substitute <br>Everybody hits a rough <br>patch turbulence in the sky <br>Life's a cow I made a burger <br>And I'm servin’ it <br>with some fries <br>Gotta make do <br>with the cards that are dealt <br>And though it's hard as hell <br>I know that God will help <br>Cuz although I live in Seattle <br>It's not always gonna rain <br>There'll be some sunny days <br>comin’ up this way <br>Everybody's wanted <br>to see me strugglin’ <br>Runnin’ away from pain <br>But I know the wondrous things <br>are comin’ to visit again someday <br>So no worries I just stand here <br>with a smirk on my face <br>Although I know some people out <br>there throwin’ dirt on my name <br>But it's all good <br>Still show ‘em some love <br>Cause unlike that girl <br>from the movie <br>I ain't holdin’ no grudge <br>When the clouds are in the sky <br>Know that they're just passin’ by <br>There'll be sunshine <br>Yeah <br>If your days are stormy nights <br>Dry the raindrops from your eyes <br>There'll be sunshine <br>I've been a little lost <br>But I'm not colorblind <br>I'll follow that yellow brick road <br>And put my fears behind <br>I I I I I I I I I <br>And on that yellow road <br>I'll find a wishing well <br>Cast a line and in time I know <br>I'll prevail <br>I I I I I I I I I <br>]]></content><category term="Dumbfoundead" label="Dumbfoundead"/><category term="Clouds (Feat. Jay Park &amp; Clara)" label="Clouds (Feat. Jay Park &amp; Clara)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jmajor7/커피_봄_너/</id><title>Jmajor7 - 커피, 봄, 너 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:25:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:25:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jmajor7/%EC%BB%A4%ED%94%BC_%EB%B4%84_%EB%84%88/" title="Jmajor7 - 커피, 봄, 너 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[카페에 앉아 너를 기다려 <br>약속 시간 보다 먼저 와서 <br>오늘 너랑 할 일들을 다시 확인해 <br>빠뜨린 건 혹시 없는지 <br>주문한 커피 한잔 나온다 <br>짙은 커피 향기를 맡으며 <br>약속 시간 설레임에 <br>발을 동동 굴려 <br>하고픈 게 너무 많잖아 <br>바람 타고 날리는 벚꽃 맞으며 <br>너랑 손을 잡고 <br>연인들이 가는 모든 곳 <br>분홍빛 세상으로 데려다줘 <br>사람들 수다 소리 가득해 <br>입안 가득 커피향 가득해 <br>문이 열리는 종소리 <br>고갤 돌렸을 때 <br>예쁜 미소 품고 오는 너 <br>바람 타고 날리는 벚꽃 맞으며 <br>너랑 손을 잡고 <br>연인들이 가는 모든 곳 <br>분홍빛 세상으로 데려다줘 <br>카페를 나와서 <br>수많은 연인들 속에 <br>떨어지는 벚꽃 밑에서 <br>예쁜 너의 얼굴에 <br>이보다 행복할 수 있을까 <br>바람 타고 날리는 벚꽃 맞으며 <br>너랑 손을 잡고 <br>연인들이 가는 모든 곳 <br>분홍빛 세상으로 데려다줘 <br>오늘 아침 커피와 부는 봄바람 <br>내 옆에 있는 너 <br>멀리서 들리는 이 노래 <br>이보다 더 행복할 수 있을까 <br>라라 라라 라라라 라라 라라라 <br>라 라라 라라라 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라라라 <br>라라 라라 라라라 라라 라라라 <br>라 라라 라라라 <br>]]></content><category term="Jmajor7" label="Jmajor7"/><category term="커피, 봄, 너" label="커피, 봄, 너"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노도/10_Prod_by_K_JUN/</id><title>노도 - 10 (Prod. by K JUN) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:26:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:26:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EB%8F%84/10_Prod_by_K_JUN/" title="노도 - 10 (Prod. by K JUN) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[2007년 9월 20여 명의 관객 <br>앞에서 시작된 OVC 역사적 항해 <br>어느덧 10년이 흘러 <br>우린 더 단단히 뭉쳐 <br>뱉은 말을 지키지 <br>Overclass the future <br>지금 니들이 동경하는 <br>그들이 동경한 우린 <br>여전히 노는 물이 다르게 <br>그려왔지 큰 그림 <br>숱한 풍파 겪어도 <br>처음 열정 그대로 <br>아직 건재해 그리고 올라 <br>더 큰 무대로 <br>글쓴이 약력소개 그냥 생략해도 돼 <br>high off life as always <br>지난 발자국 속에서 <br>큰 의밀 찾는 건 니들이 하도록 해 <br>우린 지금의 공기 지금의 소리 <br>그런 걸 기록해 <br>항상 파도를 타는 대신 <br>파도를 만들어왔지 <br>미안하지만 <br>what else is there for you <br>to do but watch me <br>so just watch how I do this <br>all eyes on me <br>가늠해봐 이 여정이 어디까진지 <br>헤아릴 수 없을 만큼 <br>긴 시간을 걸어서 여기까지 <br>잠시 내려 놓았던 <br>그 침묵을 끊어내 <br>모두가 이곳에 <br>다시 이뤄내 <br>We never chain it <br>절대 머물러 있지 않아 <br>We never chain it <br>기다림이 헛되지 않게 <br>We always stay here <br>누구보다 더 그 누구보다 <br>더욱 더 눈부시게 <br>We never tell a lie <br>난 그 자체로 빛나잖아 <br>1 for the O and 2 for the V and <br>3 for가 뭔지 모름 니 학점이 C네 <br>네 번째 점수는 D네 E는 없고 이제 <br>남은 F가 다섯 이퀄 새로 고침 이 씬에 <br>때가 되면 나타나 <br>니 밥상을 뒤집네 <br>음양을 안 가리네 <br>위 아래 안 따지네 <br>젊은 꼰대 나이가 벼슬 <br>OVC를 보면 피해 <br>넌 일해 우린 이해해 <br>늘 한 Class 더 위에 <br>많은 것이 바꼈네요 <br>since then everything has changed <br>every rappers dead in this game <br>we survivors 모두 살아 남았네 <br>것도 존나 멋있게 <br>각자 위치서 최상위 포식해 <br>가십거리와 논란거리 <br>교차로 다운타운 <br>그 중심에 서 외치지 <br>we still fucking here <br>우리 source의 vibe는 xxl <br>이 사이즈면 오버클래스 <br>대통령이야 새꺄 <br>헤아릴 수 없을 만큼 <br>긴 시간을 걸어서 여기까지 <br>잠시 내려 놓았던 <br>그 침묵을 끊어내 <br>모두가 이곳에 <br>다시 이뤄내 <br>We never chain it <br>절대 머물러 있지 않아 <br>We never chain it <br>기다림이 헛되지 않게 <br>We always stay here <br>누구보다 더 그 누구보다 <br>더욱 더 눈부시게 <br>We never tell a lie <br>난 그 자체로 빛나잖아 <br>We never chain it <br>절대로 우린 머물러 있지 않아 <br>We never chain it <br>기다림이 헛되지 않게 <br>We always stay here <br>누구보다 더 그 누구보다 <br>더욱 더 눈부시게 <br>We never tell a lie <br>난 그 자체로 빛나잖아 <br>여전히 그대로네 <br>나는 너희들의 주네 <br>나는 구 이자 다시 신이 돼 돌아와 <br>새 것을 창조하심 <br>나 자신이 노래의 <br>마지막을 장식하시며 <br>좋았노라 보네 <br>모든 게 좋았노라 보네 <br>]]></content><category term="노도" label="노도"/><category term="10 (Prod. by K JUN)" label="10 (Prod. by K JUN)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스윙스/Royalty_Prod_by_Havoc_of_Mobb_Deep/</id><title>스윙스 - Royalty (Prod. by Havoc of Mobb Deep) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:26:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:26:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%EC%9C%99%EC%8A%A4/Royalty_Prod_by_Havoc_of_Mobb_Deep/" title="스윙스 - Royalty (Prod. by Havoc of Mobb Deep) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Overclass What it do <br>몇 년만 we back <br>이름처럼 여전해 우리는 맨 위에 <br>난 hustle해 from 10 pm to 10 pm <br>오랜만에 모이니 조금은 센치해 <br>시간이 홀딱 지나갔어 <br>우린 10년 친구 <br>다 젖게 한다고 하대 <br>내 rap은 자위기구 <br>I keep it raw like <br>노량진 난 호랑이 <br>이런 또라이는 영국 뿐 <br>그 담이 오빠지 <br>어쨌든 주인공은 나 <br>상댈 죽이고는 왕이 됐어 <br>난 royalty 구린 놈은 가 <br>진짜 저리 가라고 <br>여자와 술이 오니까 <br>Seoul city <br>여기는 이제 우리 도시야 <br>이젠 시골 다방 알바생도 알아 <br>나는 Swings <br>haters 늙어가며 <br>칼을 갈아 나는 king <br>다 가져도 모자라 <br>좀 더 갖겠다는 태도 <br>OVC Just Music <br>we the shit forever <br>Royalty royalty Havoc and OVC <br>순수 고귀한 혈통 왕족 시뻘건 피 <br>흐르는 손목 위에 로얄오크 <br>audemars p <br>Feeling like a king feeling <br>like a king <br>we back 그 많고 많던 haters 어딨어 <br>we back 그 많고 많던 fans 어딨어 <br>we back 그 많고 많던 critics <br>어딨어 <br>royalty royalty hands up <br>or bend ya knee <br>거봐 Overclass 아무리 <br>시대가 변해도 우린 long run해 <br>No one can do it better <br>yo OV on the HAV <br>is the lord finesse <br>Uh all eyes on us <br>이건 classic이 될 조건 다 갖췄어 <br>Dope beats phat rhymes <br>ill lyrics <br>한마디로 sick with it <br>자 다 같이 늴리리야 늴리리 <br>느껴봐 original infamous sound <br>그 안에 OVC의 더 깊어진 style <br>너희가 여태 들은 것들과는 차원이 <br>다르다는 걸 깨닫게 될 거야 자연히 <br>Step by step wack과의 gap <br>확장시킬 시발점이 될 <br>이 죽여주는 track <br>우린 언제 어디라도 <br>그저 판만 깔리면 제대로 <br>놀 줄 알고 달궈나 It's real swag <br>Royalty royalty Havoc and OVC <br>순수 고귀한 혈통 왕족 시뻘건 피 <br>흐르는 손목 위에 로얄오크 <br>audemars p <br>Feeling like a king feeling <br>like a king <br>we back 그 많고 많던 haters 어딨어 <br>we back 그 많고 많던 fans 어딨어 <br>we back 그 많고 많던 critics <br>어딨어 <br>royalty royalty hands up <br>or bend ya knee <br>역사는 과거와 현재 사이의 <br>끊임없는 대화 <br>암흑 시대의 막을 내린 <br>오버클래스 르네상스 <br>여기 다시 모인 OVC의 <br>모든 킹과 퀸 <br>여러 왕조의 조상 뿌리 <br>원형 건국신화지 <br>Yangnom Sanggom Sifanom <br>with Collage Trilogy <br>새로운 시대의 여명이 <br>누군가의 모가지엔 길로틴 <br>확신도 없이 혁명의 <br>선두에 나설 리 없지 <br>확신범들 운명적인 <br>십자가의 짊어짐 <br>자문해봐 예술가들인가 <br>선동가 무리인가 <br>후대의 평가는 단지 <br>승리에 딸린 전리품인가 <br>크루의 탄생과 유지가 <br>그린 빛과 그림자 <br>10주년 맞이 Collage의 Drop <br>모든 질문의 답 <br>We’re the Crew <br>서로 구속할 일도 강요할 일 <br>따위도 없는 True Prosumers <br>장기적 가치 <br>투자하는 부류 <br>애먼 출처의 적대적 Rumors <br>안주 삼아 잔을 들어 <br>Celebrate 삶을 즐겨 <br>Royalty royalty Havoc and OVC <br>순수 고귀한 혈통 왕족 시뻘건 피 <br>흐르는 손목 위에 로얄오크 <br>audemars p <br>Feeling like a king feeling <br>like a king <br>we back 그 많고 많던 haters 어딨어 <br>we back 그 많고 많던 fans 어딨어 <br>we back 그 많고 많던 critics <br>어딨어 <br>royalty royalty hands up <br>or bend ya knee <br>Overclass it's in my blood <br>and they say <br>대세라는 건 언제나 <br>새로운 이름들로 늘 대체되는 법 <br>조그만 바닥이지만 <br>이 곳에 매체라는 것 <br>그런 게 있다는 사실을 <br>인정한다면 넌 더는 <br>부정하는 게 불가능해 <br>who influenced who <br>uh 억압받던 무리를 <br>구원한 하나의 구세주 <br>uh this ain't a history lesson <br>this ain't who is who <br>uh it's something like mathematics <br>and what is due is due <br>uh 십일조를 바쳐 <br>내가 어디 사용하든 <br>uh 책임질 수 있으니까 <br>니들의 고막은 <br>uh 10 years deep <br>우연과 필연의 황금비로 <br>만들어진 역사 <br>예상 못 했지 나 역시도 <br>이 조합은 억지로는 못 만드는 거 <br>새로운 시대의 문을 <br>활짝 열고선 바로 잠그는 거 <br>when you hop on the wagon <br>곧바로 폐차하는 거 <br>머리 나쁜 애들의 머리 속 <br>꽃무늬 세탁하는 거 <br>]]></content><category term="스윙스" label="스윙스"/><category term="Royalty (Prod. by Havoc of Mobb Deep)" label="Royalty (Prod. by Havoc of Mobb Deep)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/키디비_KittiB/초속_5cm_Inst/</id><title>키디비 (KittiB) - 초속 5cm (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:26:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:26:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%82%A4%EB%94%94%EB%B9%84_KittiB/%EC%B4%88%EC%86%8D_5cm_Inst/" title="키디비 (KittiB) - 초속 5cm (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[시간은 tic toc 잘 흘러가지 <br>어느새 너도 가벼운 차림 <br>각자의 겨울은 <br>지난밤의 꾼 꿈처럼 <br>희미한 기억이 되어가지 <br>너와 걷고 있는 분홍빛 길 <br>무심한 두 팔의 흔들림이 <br>서로 막 스치다가 <br>꽉 잡아버리는 손깍지 <br>심쿵하는 feelin' <br>네게 한 걸음 가까이 <br>두 걸음 가까이 <br>내 속도를 눈치채 줘 <br>내 입술 점점 <br>너의 입술 위로 다가가면 <br>너도 다가와 줘 <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will come to your lip <br>like a cherry tree <br>너도 나와 같다면 <br>다시 발걸음을 돌려서 내게로 <br>이 밤 수놓는 벚꽃을 봐 <br>헤어지기는 너무 아쉬워 <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will come to your lip <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will come to your lip <br>내가 걷는 속도에 맞춰 <br>느려져도 되겠니 <br>부끄러 앞만 보고 얘기하다 <br>니 얼굴이 보고 싶어지면 <br>슬쩍 투정을 내뱉지 <br>다리 아프다며 가리켜 <br>나무 아래 벤치 <br>Hey 가볍게 <br>샌드위치 싸왔는데 맛볼래 <br>나 원래 이런 거 잘 못해 <br>맛은 기대하지 말고 <br>먹으라며 건네 <br>반짝이는 눈빛으로 나를 보며 <br>진심 가득 담긴 고마움을 <br>전하는 그 입술을 <br>훔치고 싶어 문득 <br>느껴 대담해질 시간이 왔음을 <br>걸음이 느리다고 <br>절대로 그것도 <br>느리게 하지는 않아 <br>니가 나로 물드는 <br>속도는 잴 수 없을 정도로 <br>빠르게 빠져 <br>내 시간은 온통 너로 인해 <br>다시 써지겠지 <br>끝내 봄날이 와 <br>겨울은 가고 <br>하얀 일기장은 채워지겠지 <br>오색빛 수채화로 <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I wiil come to your lip <br>like a cherry tree <br>햇살 새소리 볼 빨개진 미소와 <br>I feel <br>I feel <br>석양 바람 싱그런 꽃내음과 <br>I feel <br>you <br>너도 나와 같다면 <br>다시 발걸음을 돌려서 내게로 <br>이 밤 수놓는 벚꽃을 봐 <br>헤어지기는 너무 아쉬워 <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will come to your lip <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will come to your lip <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will come to your lip <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will come to your lip <br>]]></content><category term="키디비 (KittiB)" label="키디비 (KittiB)"/><category term="초속 5cm (Inst.)" label="초속 5cm (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/키디비_KittiB/초속_5cm/</id><title>키디비 (KittiB) - 초속 5cm - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:26:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:26:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%82%A4%EB%94%94%EB%B9%84_KittiB/%EC%B4%88%EC%86%8D_5cm/" title="키디비 (KittiB) - 초속 5cm - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[시간은 tic toc 잘 흘러가지 <br>어느새 너도 가벼운 차림 <br>각자의 겨울은 <br>지난밤의 꾼 꿈처럼 <br>희미한 기억이 되어가지 <br>너와 걷고 있는 분홍빛 길 <br>무심한 두 팔의 흔들림이 <br>서로 막 스치다가 <br>꽉 잡아버리는 손깍지 <br>심쿵하는 feelin' <br>네게 한 걸음 가까이 <br>두 걸음 가까이 <br>내 속도를 눈치채 줘 <br>내 입술 점점 <br>너의 입술 위로 다가가면 <br>너도 다가와 줘 <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will come to your lip <br>like a cherry tree <br>너도 나와 같다면 <br>다시 발걸음을 돌려서 내게로 <br>이 밤 수놓는 벚꽃을 봐 <br>헤어지기는 너무 아쉬워 <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will come to your lip <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will come to your lip <br>내가 걷는 속도에 맞춰 <br>느려져도 되겠니 <br>부끄러 앞만 보고 얘기하다 <br>니 얼굴이 보고 싶어지면 <br>슬쩍 투정을 내뱉지 <br>다리 아프다며 가리켜 <br>나무 아래 벤치 <br>Hey 가볍게 <br>샌드위치 싸왔는데 맛볼래 <br>나 원래 이런 거 잘 못해 <br>맛은 기대하지 말고 <br>먹으라며 건네 <br>반짝이는 눈빛으로 나를 보며 <br>진심 가득 담긴 고마움을 <br>전하는 그 입술을 <br>훔치고 싶어 문득 <br>느껴 대담해질 시간이 왔음을 <br>걸음이 느리다고 <br>절대로 그것도 <br>느리게 하지는 않아 <br>니가 나로 물드는 <br>속도는 잴 수 없을 정도로 <br>빠르게 빠져 <br>내 시간은 온통 너로 인해 <br>다시 써지겠지 <br>끝내 봄날이 와 <br>겨울은 가고 <br>하얀 일기장은 채워지겠지 <br>오색빛 수채화로 <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I wiil come to your lip <br>like a cherry tree <br>햇살 새소리 볼 빨개진 미소와 <br>I feel <br>I feel <br>석양 바람 싱그런 꽃내음과 <br>I feel <br>you <br>너도 나와 같다면 <br>다시 발걸음을 돌려서 내게로 <br>이 밤 수놓는 벚꽃을 봐 <br>헤어지기는 너무 아쉬워 <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will come to your lip <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will come to your lip <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will come to your lip <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will run to your heart <br>like a cherry tree <br>I will come to your lip <br>]]></content><category term="키디비 (KittiB)" label="키디비 (KittiB)"/><category term="초속 5cm" label="초속 5cm"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김홍민/내_마음은/</id><title>김홍민 - 내 마음은 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:27:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:27:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%99%8D%EB%AF%BC/%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C%EC%9D%80/" title="김홍민 - 내 마음은 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[따스한 햇살이 내리는 <br>거리에서 우연히 그녈 보았어 <br>슬쩍 슬쩍 눈치 못 채게 <br>자꾸만 시선이 가는 걸 <br>오 그녀가 다가오는데 <br>내 모습 자꾸 신경 쓰이는데 <br>오 그녀가 지나간 자리엔 <br>향긋한 바람이 불어와 <br>거친 파도가 일렁이듯이 <br>거친 폭풍이 몰아치듯이 <br>내 마음은 <br>따뜻한 이 날씨완 다르게 <br>요동치고 있어 <br>머리 속엔 온통 그녀가 <br>도통 앞도 보이지가 않아 <br>자꾸 뒤를 돌아보게 돼 <br>그녀는 어디로 가고 있을까 <br>오 내 발걸음은 점점 더 <br>무거워 무거워 지는데 <br>오 내 소심한 마음을 <br>주체할 수가 없어 <br>용기를 내볼까 <br>거친 파도가 일렁이듯이 <br>거친 폭풍이 몰아치듯이 <br>내 마음은 <br>따뜻한 이 날씨완 다르게 <br>요동치고 있어 <br>발걸음을 돌려 <br>그녀를 향해 달려가 <br>내리쬐는 햇살과 <br>살랑거리는 나뭇잎 <br>모두가 나를 응원하고 있어 <br>몸은 더 가벼워지고 내 마음은 <br>거친 파도는 더 높아만 가고 <br>거친 폭풍은 더 세게 몰아쳐 <br>내 마음은 <br>따뜻한 이 날씨완 다르게 <br>요동치고 있어 <br>]]></content><category term="김홍민" label="김홍민"/><category term="내 마음은" label="내 마음은"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kidz_Bop_Kids/Cant_Stop_The_Feeling/</id><title>Kidz Bop Kids - Can`t Stop The Feeling! - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:28:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:28:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kidz_Bop_Kids/Cant_Stop_The_Feeling/" title="Kidz Bop Kids - Can`t Stop The Feeling! - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I got this feeling inside my bones <br>It goes electric, wavey when I turn it on <br>All through my city, all through my home <br>We're flying up, no ceiling, when we're in our zone <br><br>I got that sunshine in my pocket <br>Got that good soul in my feet <br>I feel that hot blood in my body when it drops, ooh <br>I can't take my eyes up off it, moving so phenomenally <br>Room on lock the way we rock it, so don't stop <br><br>And under the lights when everything goes <br>Nowhere to hide when I'm getting you close <br>When we move, well, you already know <br>So just imagine, just imagine, just imagine <br>Nothing I can see but you when you dance, dance, dance <br>Feeling good, good, dancing here with you <br>So just dance, dance, dance, come on <br>All those things I shouldn't do <br>But you dance, dance, dance <br>And ain't nobody leaving soon, so keep dancing <br><br>I can't stop the feeling <br>So just dance, dance, dance <br>I can't stop the feeling <br>So just dance, dance, dance, come on <br><br>Ooh, it's something magical <br>It's in the air, it's in my blood, it's rushing on <br>Don't need no reason, don't need control <br>I fly so high, no ceiling, when I'm in my zone <br><br>'Cause I got that sunshine in my pocket <br>Got that good soul in my feet <br>I feel that hot blood in my body when it drops, ooh <br>I can't take my eyes up off it, moving so phenomenally <br>Room on lock the way we rock it, so don't stop <br><br>And under the lights when everything goes <br>Nowhere to hide when I'm getting you close <br>When we move, well, you already know <br>So just imagine, just imagine, just imagine <br>Nothing I can see but you when you dance, dance, dance <br>Feeling good, good, dancing here with you <br>So just dance, dance, dance, come on <br>All those things I shouldn't do <br>But you dance, dance, dance <br>And ain't nobody leaving soon, so keep dancing <br><br>I can't stop the feeling <br>So just dance, dance, dance <br>I can't stop the feeling <br>So just dance, dance, dance <br>I can't stop the feeling <br>So just dance, dance, dance <br>I can't stop the feeling <br>So keep dancing, come on <br><br>I can't stop the, I can't stop the <br>I can't stop the, I can't stop the <br>I can't stop the feeling <br><br>Nothing I can see but you when you dance, dance, dance <br>I can't stop the feeling <br>Feeling good, good, dancing here with you <br>So just dance, dance, dance, come on <br>I can't stop the feeling <br>All those things I shouldn't do <br>But you dance, dance, dance <br>I can't stop the feeling <br>And ain't nobody leaving soon, so keep dancing <br><br>Everybody sing <br>I can't stop the feeling <br>Got this feeling in my body <br>I can't stop the feeling <br>Got this feeling in my body <br>I can't stop the feeling <br>Wanna see you move your body <br>I can't stop the feeling <br>Got this feeling in my body <br>Break it down <br>Got this feeling in my body <br>Can't stop the feeling <br>Got this feeling in my body, come on]]></content><category term="Kidz Bop Kids" label="Kidz Bop Kids"/><category term="Can`t Stop The Feeling!" label="Can`t Stop The Feeling!"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Safaree/Love_You_Now_Feat_Josh_K/</id><title>Safaree - Love You Now (Feat. Josh K) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:30:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:30:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Safaree/Love_You_Now_Feat_Josh_K/" title="Safaree - Love You Now (Feat. Josh K) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When we first met you laughed at me <br>Who'd a known for 12 years you'd laugh with me <br>We started out as a group, told no lies we just spoke the truth <br>I used to cheer you on in the booth <br>We dreamed about cars that ain't have a roof <br>So I'mma fast forward to now <br>We in the industry now, look how it ruined us wow <br>Behind doors I'm the man <br>Calculated and I planned <br>What a shame, it took a split for them to know I was your man <br>Got so tired of hidin' it <br>Head high with no pride in it <br>Guess I wasn't cool enough cause in our pictures we hidin' it <br>Everytime it went south, I be sleepin' on the couch <br>Hotel room for one, thinkin' what is this about <br>I took the good with the bad <br>Always heated I was mad <br>In our pictures yeah we're smilin' but inside I'm feelin' sad <br><br>Did the good outweigh the bad or did the bad outweigh the good <br>You ain't do it all alone we took ourselves up out the hood <br>Yeah we made it on the rise ain't no green in my eyes <br>Cause we both went to sleep in the same bed of lies <br><br>Why do people you love the most always want to hurt you <br>How can I trust you again when I'm not around you <br>But when I'm down and out and it's cold outside <br>Where were you <br>And when you needed me I was always there <br>Now where are you <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Why do people you love the most always want to hurt you <br>Why do people you love the most always want to hurt you <br>Why do people you love the most always want to hurt you <br>Why do people you love the most always want to hurt you <br><br>Yeah I was a backbone, a little caught up in the light <br>All I did was hold you down, before it all you was my wife <br>Real life behind the scenes, all I did was really help <br>To them you just a billboard, I cared about your health <br>I don't care about the wealth <br>I ain't care about your fame <br>I ain't care about no flawless VVS's in your chain <br>I ain't sayin' I'm the best, no one will love you like I did <br>12 years up in flames, thought you woulda had my kid <br>Year 3 got engaged, now we movin' out of rage <br>I ain't never think our book woulda ended on this page <br>Had to watch you kiss Nas and pretend it's all cool <br>Inside I was feelin' like a motherfuckin' fool <br>Life revolves around a bitch show me a man that won't cheat <br>Said I was overreactin' but you did like <br>Said I was overreactin' guess you did like <br><br>Did the good outweigh the bad or did the bad outweigh the good <br>You ain't do it all alone we took ourselves up out the hood <br>Yeah we made it on the rise ain't no green in my eyes <br>Cause we both went to sleep in the same bed of lies <br><br>Why do people you love the most always want to hurt you <br>How can I trust you again when I'm not around you <br>But when I'm down and out and it's cold outside <br>Where were you <br>And when you needed me I was always there <br>Now where are you <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Why do people you love the most always want to hurt you <br>Why do people you love the most always want to hurt you <br>Why do people you love the most always want to hurt you <br>Why do people you love the most always want to hurt you <br><br>I ain't playin' tit for tat, I don't wanna pull you down <br>I'm not into circus acts and I don't even like clowns <br>I ain't even gonna front like I never watch your show <br>And I'm still your biggest fan and I don't need a front row <br>Yeah I know I'm not perfect, you was payin' all the bills <br>You remember what you told me when you wasn't on the pills <br>If the shoe was on the other foot I'd make sure you're straight <br>I ain't playin' kiddy games and I ain't fallin' for the bait <br>Tell your momma, tell your brothers, I still love them like my own <br>I don't bother reachin' out because it's too close to home <br>But now we're not together I don't feel you wish the best <br>Can't believe we not friends, smh, what a mess <br>That's between me and you, it was always me and you <br>We ain't do this off opinions, it was only me and you <br>Then you let somebody new come and whisper in your ear <br>Didn't think he woulda told you that was my biggest fear <br><br>Did the good outweigh the bad or did the bad outweigh the good <br>You ain't do it all alone we took ourselves up out the hood <br>Yeah we made it on the rise ain't no green in my eyes <br>Cause we both went to sleep in the same bed of lies <br><br>Why do people you love the most always want to hurt you <br>How can I trust you again when I'm not around you <br>But when I'm down and out and it's cold outside <br>Where were you <br>And when you needed me I was always there <br>Now where are you <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Why do people you love the most always want to hurt you <br>Why do people you love the most always want to hurt you <br>Why do people you love the most always want to hurt you <br>Why do people you love the most always want to hurt you]]></content><category term="Safaree" label="Safaree"/><category term="Love You Now (Feat. Josh K)" label="Love You Now (Feat. Josh K)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Retrovision/Over_Again_Feat_Micah_Martin/</id><title>Retrovision - Over Again (Feat. Micah Martin) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:31:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:31:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Retrovision/Over_Again_Feat_Micah_Martin/" title="Retrovision - Over Again (Feat. Micah Martin) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My father told me when I was young <br>Don't play with fire because it's fun <br>But with the flames we fell in love <br><br>We burned the cities down, down, down <br>The fire won't you listen <br>You won't get lonely if you fall in love <br>Over and over again and again <br><br>Over and over agaaain <br><br>My mother told me when I was young <br>We soon expire I'm sorry son <br>You won't be lonely if you fall in love <br>Over and over agaaain <br><br>I'm living my life according to the law of attraction <br>It's lights camera action <br>I never wanna die <br>You're living a life with no direction <br>I thought you learned your lesson <br>I thought you learned your lesson <br><br>Over and over againnn]]></content><category term="Retrovision" label="Retrovision"/><category term="Over Again (Feat. Micah Martin)" label="Over Again (Feat. Micah Martin)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Craig_G/Long_Time/</id><title>Craig G - Long Time - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:31:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:31:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Craig_G/Long_Time/" title="Craig G - Long Time - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I couldn't believe it was her, it was like a dream <br>but there she was, just like I remembered her <br><br>Oh, such a long time <br>Yea, I mean I am what I am man, you know <br>I'm a forty something year old rapper, but you know why <br>Cause I love this shit man, I watched every facet, know what I mean <br>I seen it grow from listening to party jams <br>all the way to records, all the way to super stardom, you know <br>For y'all don't know, let me, let me explain a little something <br><br>OK, set up the speakers plug that amp in the light pole <br>Rope off the booth for them fellas that had a tight flow <br>I was 9 years old, amazed at the control the <br>MC had over the crowd by making them say Ow <br>The Fantastic Five and the Cold Crush, they battled <br>And if they heard that tape man, trust me, you really had to <br>Play it for any and everybody from your boombox <br>They huddle around your JVC like they sang doo wop <br>But Kool Moe Dee took out Busy Bee on the random <br>That tape was equivalent to a loaded Phantom and <br>He really earth slammed him, that Baw Biddy Baw was completely dope <br>Before some routine from some TV show, man <br><br>Oh, such a long time <br>Took a long time <br>Such a long long time <br>Oh, such a long time <br>Took a long time <br>Such a long long time <br><br>Then came commentating, illustrating <br>When I heard them first two words I was like OK then <br>Vocabulary really's about to take control now <br>And if you read a lot, you'd be comfortable with your pronouns <br>Fearless Four told me that there were problems in the world <br>Boogie Boys explained to me what was a fly girl fly girl <br>But when I heard that jam called Sucker MCs <br>The first thing I noticed was that boom bap beat <br>And Run looked like my brother, DMC like my cousin <br>No costumes at all man, none of the gear custom <br>Represented my taste peasy head and still get paid <br>Live Aid a hundred thousand looking like they never shaved and they bodied it <br><br>Oh, such a long time <br>Took a long time <br>Such a long long time <br>Oh, such a long time <br>Took a long time <br>Such a long long time <br><br>And then we hit the 90s when Nas dropped Illmatic <br>That west coast chronic, Dre and snoop were hard at it <br>Ready to die and 36 chambers <br>Onyx was screaming back the fuck up to strangers <br>OC was telling cats they times limited <br>P rock and CL smooth dropped the join that was gimick less <br>Brand Nubian was telling people slow down <br>Naughty by nature, Mobb Deep riding dirty, out of town <br>A tribe called quest, they were the midnight marauders <br>Stepped in the arena, GangStarr loved to slaughter <br>The Liks were in LA, cracking champagne bottles <br>Now its a digital underground sound that's full throttle <br><br>Oh, such a long time <br>Took a long time <br>Such a long long time <br>Oh, such a long time <br>Took a long time <br>Such a long long time]]></content><category term="Craig G" label="Craig G"/><category term="Long Time" label="Long Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meyhem_Lauren/Dragon_VS_Wolf_Feat_Action_Bronson/</id><title>Meyhem Lauren - Dragon V.S. Wolf (Feat. Action Bronson) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:32:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:32:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meyhem_Lauren/Dragon_VS_Wolf_Feat_Action_Bronson/" title="Meyhem Lauren - Dragon V.S. Wolf (Feat. Action Bronson) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You know who it is, shut the fuck up yeah <br><br>Wack raps smell like cushioned Jordan's <br>I'm on that uptown haze <br>Standing on the corner till the morning sun rays up <br>This game is like Dragon Vs Wolf <br>Understand this, ain't nothing ever faze us <br>Truth, shouts to samo high <br>I'm a perfect mix of Van Damme and Van Gogh high <br>Man eat pussy, shoot him with the Mango 9 <br>Got the six trade jumping like the Kangol sign <br>I despise so many paintings, I'mma make a statement <br>I no longer eat bacon <br>I no longer bet the mortgage on the Ravens <br>I will no longer hide the drugs inside the play pen <br>I will no longer shave my face because I'm godly <br>Pick up your pace, young rap this is my hobby <br>Crack will make the fiends do aerobics in the lobby <br>Drop 7000 on a collie <br>Views from the train <br>Ain't nothing was the same <br>Views from the train bitch <br>Ain't nothing was the same bitch <br><br>Flexing like a box spring <br>I keep a good dam talking but it's not spring <br>Making my rocks bling <br>Hit 'em with hot steam <br>All these bitches love me, that's past desire <br>They treat my penis like a pacifier <br>Festive attire, past to retire <br>Looking like the cash you admire <br>I'm a G, run up in your crib and demand steak <br>Pretty bitches rub my feet 'til their hands break <br>Caked up, like a 8 baller in humidity <br>Cocaine talks, and tells me bag me and get rid of me <br>Queens niggas at the finish line <br>Word to the watch on my wrist, I keep exquisite time <br>But I'm usually on CPT <br>Then click this free food like it's EBT, run me]]></content><category term="Meyhem Lauren" label="Meyhem Lauren"/><category term="Dragon V.S. Wolf (Feat. Action Bronson)" label="Dragon V.S. Wolf (Feat. Action Bronson)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meyhem_Lauren/Flexxin/</id><title>Meyhem Lauren - Flexxin - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:32:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:32:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meyhem_Lauren/Flexxin/" title="Meyhem Lauren - Flexxin - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Muthafucka <br>C'mon son <br>N niggas don't flex right <br>C'mon <br>What buildings you been in <br>What blocks niggas know you on <br>Fuck these niggas talking about son <br>Nigga we been in these streets <br>Swervin in and outta yeah all types of shit uh huh <br>C'mon yo laurenavich <br><br>Yo, dollar bills, dicks sucks, drop tops and big trucks <br>Lifestyle lux, A plus we live plush uh <br>Perfection, all that I strive for, Provide for <br>Bronsolinio and D stacks niggas I'd ride for <br>Queens get it, Queens did it what <br>Keep a bald head right under the clean fitted <br>Tilt to the side in the whip how I rock it <br>Gah od damn might hop out holdin a rocket <br>Live shit my gun smokes, cuban link jump ropes <br>Bag up a smart bitch, hit her with dumb strokes <br>Mink game right, fuck rockin them slum coats <br>Won't slap hands with them niggas that sell notes fuck em <br>I'm OG wit it but I'm not that old <br>Your money ain't long if your knot can fold <br>Sellin weight while I celebrate <br>Fall back while I delegate, Launy <br><br>Fly shit for ever it's Lauren <br>Niggas know the drill, stay sharp, peace to my pen uhhh <br>Got me out of state now I'm Flexxin <br>All my niggas gotta get their checks in <br>Then we back to New York <br>Live niggas always give me support, you know the drill <br>Ain't no fuckin around <br>Niggas act up we shuttin em down, Laundel <br><br>Remain chiseled while my name fizzled uh huh <br>Broke the work then the cane drizzled coke <br>The game sizzled, It got hot like Rhianna <br>CDs freezed and breeze dropped the llama <br>Silk on, six days outta the week <br>On the seventh rock nothing cause I'm out with a freak <br>In the kitchen buck naked, shorty givin me beak <br>Had to pull my zipper up so she was able to speak <br>My lifes golden, 24 karat, traumatic <br>Shit happens all day long my niggas had it <br>Still got it, Cartier optic <br>My niggas share profit, I keep a red watch lit shine <br>My niggas knuckle up and shoot fair ones <br>Yall niggas cry for help and shoot flair guns pussy <br>We was never the same <br>Lo key but I'm out for the fame, fuck with me <br><br>Fly shit for ever it's Lauren <br>Niggas know the drill, stay sharp, peace to my pen uhhh <br>Got me out of state now I'm Flexxin <br>All my niggas gotta get their checks in <br>Then we back to New York <br>Live niggas always give me support, you know the drill <br>Ain't no fuckin around <br>Niggas act up we shuttin em down, Laundel]]></content><category term="Meyhem Lauren" label="Meyhem Lauren"/><category term="Flexxin" label="Flexxin"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meyhem_Lauren/Bonus_Round_Feat_Action_Bronson_Roc_Marciano__Big_Body_Bes/</id><title>Meyhem Lauren - Bonus Round (Feat. Action Bronson, Roc Marciano &amp; Big Body Bes) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:32:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:32:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meyhem_Lauren/Bonus_Round_Feat_Action_Bronson_Roc_Marciano__Big_Body_Bes/" title="Meyhem Lauren - Bonus Round (Feat. Action Bronson, Roc Marciano &amp; Big Body Bes) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I used to do Old Miss Mary's niece <br>Flood the virgin mary piece <br>Sixth floor shit, niggas snort shit <br>My money caused shit <br>Horse dick, curl your toes like a corn chip <br>Mama's fried chicken, it glisten <br>I never once in life touched a chitterling <br>The dream that came to fruition up in the kitchen <br>Hot air conditioning, one hand niggas water whipping <br>My dress code is the coldest <br>Stretch your colon <br>The Beethoven, paper folding, the latest clothing <br>A player's chosen, playing oceans, no Frank Ocean <br>Sterling chapel with the strap on it <br>Looking like dyke pussy with the strap on it <br>The dope is pure, I could tap on it <br>My line, feds got the tap on it <br>Range Rover, I'm a slave owner <br>8 Coronas on drink coasters, snake poachers <br>Gator coats and suede loafers, break your focus <br>Jealous haters break my naked sculptures <br><br>On the road to riches, trying to fuck all these bitches, trying to fuck all these bitches <br>On the road to riches, On the road to riches, trying fuck all these bitches <br><br>Crash the lex like the bonus round <br>And my hair stay perfect <br>My son's chest frozen like some sherbet <br>My mother's name engraved on the burner <br>Daddy didn't believe I was an earner <br>Till I showed up in the lamb with the safari window <br>I been the shit, you motherfuckers hardly been dope <br>Me and money go together like bacardi and coke <br>Drive on the right side, numb like a stroke <br>As the sun hit my features, my dun hide the gun in the pizza <br>Catch him while he playing FIFA <br>Mix the chemicals in beakers with new sneakers <br>Deuce eaters at the theater <br>My mind been clearer since I'm drinking juice <br>Shit it's summertime, I think I'll paint the lincoln blue <br>I know you never thought I'd make it through <br>Dutty Wining on my jamaican boo <br>Wray and Nephew for the whole crew <br><br>On the road to riches, trying to fuck all these bitches, trying to fuck all these bitches <br>On the road to riches, On the road to riches, trying fuck all these bitches <br><br>Yeah nigga I'm L <br>Bought your bitch a wax, then I took a trip to Brazil <br>Hold the gun right, keep an extra clip to refill <br>Crossing over on pollock like we whipping the pill <br>Gotta shake em like Shammgod, working my hand god <br>Straight fish, barely eat food of the land god <br>New York built me, not guilty <br>The Lex filthy, half a bottle hennesy white, trilby <br>Still swerving, eating poached, ham and gruyere <br>One love to my nigga pierre <br>Doggy we here <br>Get top from a thot, let a shot in the air <br>Zip up, grip up, hit a spot then appear <br>Been accused and we not in the clear <br>We crime niggas, TEC 9 niggas, write fly rhyme niggas <br>VVS won't peep the way my shine glitters <br>Whole squad tatted up like Yakuza <br>We ain't worried about getting jobs you fucking loser <br>Shout out to the dealer, one love to the user <br>It's , peace to my calf <br>Got workers on the strip, Lord, peace to my staff <br>Concubine and a half of while in the bath <br>Trying to climb different levels of math, I'm trying to stash <br>On the road to riches, trying to fuck all these bitches I'm trying to fuck all these bitches Uh <br><br>Yeah ma, Allow me to show you myself I want to take you out a night on the town Pull up in some fly shit My drivers name is Javier Take you on a horse carriage ride down grand concourse That's the night I fell in love with you That's the same night I stole money out your purse I mean, I'm not here to impress nobody but myself Big fucking body, yeah all types of shit Catch me rolling down Lenox, I got rims on a fiend What's up I'm a man of many mistakes, Thousand dollar sex moves You should've been known me bitch]]></content><category term="Meyhem Lauren" label="Meyhem Lauren"/><category term="Bonus Round (Feat. Action Bronson, Roc Marciano &amp; Big Body Bes)" label="Bonus Round (Feat. Action Bronson, Roc Marciano &amp; Big Body Bes)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meyhem_Lauren/Vintage/</id><title>Meyhem Lauren - Vintage - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:32:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:32:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meyhem_Lauren/Vintage/" title="Meyhem Lauren - Vintage - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Shit, got pulled over on the way over here <br>The police hands in my pocket <br>Niggas asked me why I had so much money on me <br>I told them niggas cause I'm good at life <br>Fuck outta here Lauren <br>Yo, we in the building, uh <br><br>Vintage on the whip whip <br>Vintage on the Knit <br>YSL frames older than my dick <br>Vintage on the whip whip <br>Vintage on the Knit <br>YSL frames older than my dick <br>I'm in love with the mirror <br>New frames on, I couldn't see clearer <br>I'm in love with the mirror <br>New frames on, I couldn't see clearer <br><br>Certainly certified, rock a badge of honor <br>Before the coke we used to traffic marijuana <br>Criminal rap shit shit, fuck a backflip flip <br>We trying to front flip, all my niggas front shit <br>Gang consignment known for slang alignment <br>Catch me chillin while that thing is <br>I made the call nigga uhh <br>Shit's foul, no ball nigga <br>Spilled some Henny in the hall nigga <br>Fuck it <br>Peace to Hologram and Action my brothas <br>For those two I would shoot like John Paxson uh <br>I would chop like Michael White in Marea <br>Think I'm shining now you need to peep a different layer <br>I'm just gettin ready <br>Bread is flowin in but it's about to get steady <br>Cuban link neck brace, my chain is so heavy <br>Get brain, collect fetty, it's life <br><br>Vintage on the whip whip <br>Vintage on the Knit <br>YSL frames older than my dick <br>Vintage on the whip whip <br>Vintage on the Knit <br>YSL frames older than my dick <br>I'm in love with the mirror <br>New frames on, I couldn't see clearer <br>I'm in love with the mirror <br>New frames on, I couldn't see clearer <br><br>I walk through the sea keeps shinin <br>Street lion, keep eyeing <br>We buying, we selling <br>God forbid my niggas get knocked we not tellin <br>I still hit the telly <br>Wit a hood bitch that got extensions and the belly <br>Get steamed fish from El Puerto 4 in the mornin <br>Hit the triborough back home picture me soarin <br>Carmine on the pedal on the pedal <br>I'm a muthafuckin rebel I'm a rebel <br>Carmine on the pedal on the pedal <br>I'm a muthafuckin rebel I'm a rebel <br><br>Vintage on the whip whip <br>Vintage on the Knit <br>YSL frames older than my dick <br>Vintage on the whip whip <br>Vintage on the Knit <br>YSL frames older than my dick <br>I'm in love with the mirror <br>New frames on, I couldn't see clearer <br>I'm in love with the mirror <br>New frames on, I couldn't see clearer]]></content><category term="Meyhem Lauren" label="Meyhem Lauren"/><category term="Vintage" label="Vintage"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meyhem_Lauren/Sauce_Feat_Hologram/</id><title>Meyhem Lauren - Sauce (Feat. Hologram) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:32:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:32:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meyhem_Lauren/Sauce_Feat_Hologram/" title="Meyhem Lauren - Sauce (Feat. Hologram) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ball with a capital B <br>Gotta floss on 'em <br>High gloss on 'em <br>Throw a little sauce on 'em <br>We been stunting <br>I'm the top of the top <br>You been fronting <br><br>Got my chest out, rocking silk while I get milk <br>Bitch niggas try to play, fuck around and get killed <br>Pardon my violence, but I ain't fucking around <br>Violators violate, then we bucking them down <br>Gorilla mind stayed a little more civil <br>Dirty in the whip, see police then I wiggle <br>Swerve supreme with herb to steam <br>Light your bitch up, then I serve your queen <br>I'm king of this real shit <br>Write raps for niggas who built shit <br>Carrying steel clips <br>Crispy like veal strips <br>It's me <br>Don't speak much <br>I breeze through to let them see <br>I'm doing good, Lord <br>You a hood fraud <br>We the opposite <br>I get it popping, dick <br>Circling blocks in different flavors <br>If not next door, dancing Merengue with my neighbors <br><br>Ball with a capital B <br>Gotta floss on 'em <br>High gloss on 'em <br>Throw a little sauce on 'em <br>We been stunting <br>I'm the top of the top <br>You been fronting <br><br>Sixty inch flat <br>Net game on mute nigga <br>Bluetooth, beats stay on loop nigga <br>Instrumental keep playing for us <br>I keep sinning, keep praying for us <br>Ain't nothing free, keep paying for us <br>I'm just saying <br>Change the channel, see what KD got on his feet <br>Them shits would look hot in the street <br>The beat stop <br>See feds on the block <br>Watch <br>I speed while I flee from a cop <br>Hit the weed while I listen to Pac, little nigga <br>I don't got about four or five chains on <br>I'm just on another song getting my game on <br>I don't wear gray fox <br>You might see me in some Kobes with NBA socks <br>Get to the garage, pull the car in <br>Nothing foreign <br>Go American <br>Pulling up in a Mercury <br>But, I'm rolling around on Earth, you see <br>Other worldly molecular structure <br>Jumping on a record and I flex like a muscular <br>I never disrespect when in the present of customers <br>So, never disrespect when in the presence of hustlers <br>You fucking bitch <br><br>Ball with a capital B <br>Gotta floss on 'em <br>High gloss on 'em <br>Throw a little sauce on 'em <br>We been stunting <br>I'm the top of the top <br>You been fronting]]></content><category term="Meyhem Lauren" label="Meyhem Lauren"/><category term="Sauce (Feat. Hologram)" label="Sauce (Feat. Hologram)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meyhem_Lauren/Not_Guilty/</id><title>Meyhem Lauren - Not Guilty - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:32:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:32:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meyhem_Lauren/Not_Guilty/" title="Meyhem Lauren - Not Guilty - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, we straight swervin on em <br>Skydive graciously and what not <br>Yo yo yo yo <br><br>Flexing Queens style in the meanwhile <br>My watch got the mean dial <br>Flooded with rocks just like a fiend vial <br>Supreme child, cuddle still <br>Never had a struggle meal <br>Intelligent but my demeanor got a rugged feel <br>Dangerous like you starin down the barrel til the slug reveal <br>Dont affiliate with fake cause I'm in love with real <br>Uh, niggas will shoot at ya <br>Jackson Heights nights with the connect playing Cumbia <br>We gold chain niggas, cocaine niggas <br>Son you ain't paid you gettin soul train figures <br>Swervin in another region, lookin exotic <br>Might just see me in your bitches pelvis, movin erotic <br>Rockin the good Nike, bare chest, no white t <br>Real niggas get ahead they just like me <br>Draped in black leather sliced thinner than prosciuto <br>This bitch is actin up so I'm about to get a new ho <br>Lauren <br><br>Peace to crimes to I never did and places I've never been <br>I'm a G, I'm a plead not guilty til the end, what not guilty <br>Not guilty til the end <br>I'm a G, I'm a plead not guilty til the end <br>Peace to crimes to I never did and places I've never been <br>I'm a G, I'm a plead not guilty til the end, what not guilty <br>Not guilty til the end <br>I'm a G, I'm a plead not guilty til the end <br><br>Yo, yo, yo, yo <br>On the low shinin like a fog light fog light <br>Get money nigga, never been the rob type rob type <br>Breitling on my wrist since I'm twenty one <br>Became a man bought a watch and a gun <br>Never looked back, cooked crack, controllin a fiend <br>Is how I feel every day when I'm chasin my dream <br>Queens niggas could vouch for me, Brooklyn as well <br>Fuck talkin to the police put me right in the cell, fuck it <br>Shit, hopefully not though, Jesus face blessin me <br>Peep how the rocks blow, Picasso with rock blow, nigga I'm not yo <br>Average motherfucker talkin bout that he got dough <br>Ya'll pose no threat, I'll feel safe when we hammer less <br>Carhartts cuff, the foam posits look amethyst <br>Fuck King of New York, I wanna be King of the World <br>Breeze through, do my thing with your girl, I'm in her <br><br>Peace to crimes to I never did and places I've never been <br>I'm a G, I'm a plead not guilty til the end, what not guilty <br>Not guilty til the end <br>I'm a G, I'm a plead not guilty til the end <br>Peace to crimes to I never did and places I've never been <br>I'm a G, I'm a plead not guilty til the end, what not guilty <br>Not guilty til the end <br>I'm a G, I'm a plead not guilty til the end]]></content><category term="Meyhem Lauren" label="Meyhem Lauren"/><category term="Not Guilty" label="Not Guilty"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meyhem_Lauren/Aggressive_Metal/</id><title>Meyhem Lauren - Aggressive Metal - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:32:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:32:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meyhem_Lauren/Aggressive_Metal/" title="Meyhem Lauren - Aggressive Metal - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yo <br>Yo, that nigga just <br>Son, he lit him up, son <br>He lit the nigga up like a Christmas tree, son <br>Like it was the Fourth of July, son <br>I mean, yo <br>That shit <br>Yo, that nigga was trying to fucking cook the nigga, son <br>I mean, like, that shit's fucked up, son <br>That nigga hit the nigga up like he was just like Shish kebab <br>Like, he was just meat, nigga <br>Like, like he was nothing <br>Yo, that shit's fucked up, man <br><br>Yeah, yeah <br>AKA Lauren Avicii <br>It's all Queens everything <br>Yo <br><br>Swerving like we dodging potholes <br>My niggas got those <br>Gifted with the jewels on <br>That's how you rock hoes <br>I don't even hit them with G <br>I speak a thousand <br>Champagne sprinkled in cups while niggas browsing <br>'84 Guccis on, wrist on chill <br>Eat steak, move flake while we get this meal <br>Street corner music for my niggas that dump <br>Let the Glock shake the block like the box to the trunk <br>Sway patch up a precise, we looking cleanly <br>I been fresh, a dirtbag bitch couldn't be friendly <br>Pop bottle, pop tags, pop collars <br>Niggas get popped for acting like they block scholars <br>Falsely, I've been implicated in a scandal <br>That shit is untrue like me seen rocking a sandal <br>I'm a Nike head <br>If not, I rock a Gucci kick <br>Welcome to Queens where niggas show you how to Uzi spit <br><br>Doing good, I'm talking real refinement <br>Doggy, I'm straight like a wheel alignment <br>Prescribe work to heal a client <br>Aggressive metal protects metal that's precious <br>My whole team stars, we never settle for benches <br>My whip big body like Bes' <br>We reckless <br>Finesse this fucking lifestyle <br>I'm thinking right now <br>I don't get scared of police like I'm a White child <br>I speak success fluently <br> I'm just doing me <br>Swipe to the left like we using Tinder <br>Leave your skin cut up there like we <br>Stacking papes looking like apes that need crates <br>Peace to niggas fucking with birds and big eights <br>It's Laurenovich]]></content><category term="Meyhem Lauren" label="Meyhem Lauren"/><category term="Aggressive Metal" label="Aggressive Metal"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rod_Da_God/Fairytale/</id><title>Rod Da God - Fairytale - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:33:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:33:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rod_Da_God/Fairytale/" title="Rod Da God - Fairytale - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I Hope that dis aint no fairytale <br>I want to lick on your motherfucking skin <br>Cause dat shit be tasting like caramel <br>Life without been feeling kinda strange <br>Well I see that you are doing very well <br>Ha you lookin very well <br>I miss the way your perfume smell <br>I miss the way you blow on my line <br>To make sure im feeling well <br>I miss the way you look in my eyes <br>I swear im getting back wit you girl <br>Taking bout my chick on the side <br>She aint fucking wit you girl <br>Tell your friends that they can be quiet <br>Cause its me and you against that world <br>Me and you against the world <br>I don't give a fuck bout no side chick <br>I cant leave you trapped In the closet <br>You got me high like a poilet <br>I make nothing but deposits <br>Nigga played you he in trouble <br>Need my money on a double <br>Pop the pussy like a bubble <br>She dig in me just like a shovel <br>I know you reamber those nights when <br>we would fall asleep on the fucking phone <br>And I know you reamber them nights when <br>I hit it right as soon as we got fucking home <br>And I know that shit wasn't right <br>Talking to them hoes and doing you fucking wrong <br>Damn <br>Now im on my fucking own <br>On my fucking own <br>on my fucking own <br>She keep on calling me phycio <br>Her mama was there so I cant hit from the front <br>so I had to sneak through the side door <br>I really hate that I broke your little heart <br>I didn't think that you would cry though <br>We would break up to make up to break up again <br>Shit it was a good try though <br>Now shit now its goodbye hoe <br>It aint no motherfucking secret <br>Breaking my heart into pieces <br>I know the game I used to teach it <br>Cause these niggas hating for no motherfucking reason <br>I cant believe it <br>Whenever you leaving I hate to see you leaving <br>You got me gritting and greaving <br>I take my time when im doing my thing <br>Even if my phone keep on ringing]]></content><category term="Rod Da God" label="Rod Da God"/><category term="Fairytale" label="Fairytale"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Twiddle/When_It_Rains_It_Pours_2017_Ver/</id><title>Twiddle - When It Rains It Pours (2017 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:33:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:33:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Twiddle/When_It_Rains_It_Pours_2017_Ver/" title="Twiddle - When It Rains It Pours (2017 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You wake to greet the brand new day <br>Look up realize you're late <br>Rush out to make your plane <br>Can't find your keys again <br>The rent's been due for weeks <br>You need this gig to eat <br>Your car starts to leak <br>The engine's really weak <br>It won't start up in time <br>You try to find a ride <br>The bills weren't paid on time <br>Your cell phone lost the line <br>The problems wont go away <br>They keep piling on your plate <br>You just want to escape <br>You need to re awake <br><br>Awake now listen to the words I'm <br>Saying in this line that your life will be just fine and <br>Troubles do not stay they <br>Get replaced with good times <br>Now you got a great life <br>Smile as you walk by <br>Thinking about the Day <br><br>Its late your legs wont rest today <br>Your body seems to ache <br>Your mind will win the race <br>Burning by your sleep again <br>The light blooms from the sun <br>The long dark night un done <br>Another day of fun <br>Waiting for some luck to come <br>You keep hoping for a day <br>For things to go your way <br>When all decisions have been made <br>And karma's finally found its way <br>The drinks they pass the time <br>They help you to unwind <br>The guilt is killing me inside <br>Your eyes they need to reawake <br><br>Awake now listen to the words I'm <br>Saying in this line that your life will be just fine and <br>Troubles do not stay they <br>Get replaced with good times <br>Now you got a great life <br>Smile as you walk by <br>Thinking about the Day <br><br>Its grey the rain pours down my face <br>The tears become erased <br>A cleansing of my fate <br>Splashing down into my grin <br>My eyes become alive <br>A feeling left behind <br>A hidden world untied <br>Creating all you see today <br>The clouds they went away <br>Forever did I wait <br>But karma found my plate <br>Now Im smiling in the sun <br>We'll meet again someday <br>You smile and than ill say <br>When it rains it pours all day <br>Until love can find its way <br><br>now listen to the words I'm <br>Saying in this line that your life will be just fine and <br>Troubles do not stay they <br>Get replaced with good times <br>Now you got a great life <br>Smile as you walk by <br>Thinking about the Day]]></content><category term="Twiddle" label="Twiddle"/><category term="When It Rains It Pours (2017 Ver.)" label="When It Rains It Pours (2017 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/RJ/Get_Rich_Feat_Iamsu/</id><title>RJ - Get Rich (Feat. Iamsu!) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:34:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:34:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/RJ/Get_Rich_Feat_Iamsu/" title="RJ - Get Rich (Feat. Iamsu!) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Huhh look <br>Niggas rap rich but I been broke <br>Last night I had a dream bout a kicked doe' <br>I used to cross state lines just to get dope <br>Wanna press my line gotta fish for it <br>I'm all alone in a crowd don't touch me, smoking I'm frustrated <br>Lie to my girl and she bring it up months later <br>Nah I ain't a ho i just crush a lot <br>Ball soft re rock til' I whip the watch <br>Mustard hit me from the yacht drunk laughing at chop <br>They said it's grind time a gang of niggas want yo spot <br>Look, a gang of these new niggas wanna be Pac <br>That's why a gang of these lil' niggas gone get shot <br>It's hard to grow up <br>Niggas ain't fucking with you so what <br>Sit yo ass down get ya dough up <br>I don't ever judge with my nose up <br>Ima blow uppppppp, Oooooh about money on that note <br>Bitch I'm 100 to the point you get taxed for it <br>If I ever need ya hand I'll ask for it, until then Ima be on my shit like <br><br>Ooooooooohh ooohh ooh, I'mma get rich on you <br>And I'mma be richer than you, I'mma get rich like <br>Oooooohh ooohh ooh, I'mma get rich on you <br>and I'mma be richer than you, cuz I'm on my shit like <br>Ooooooooohh ooohh ooh, I'mma get rich on you <br>And I'mma be richer than you, I'mma get rich like <br>Oooooohh ooohh ooh, I'mma get rich on you <br>and I'mma be richer than you, cuz I'm on my shit like <br><br>Ooooh Ooooh Ooh, I'ma be richer than you <br>Two or three bitches came through, I'm tryna fuck something <br>I told her back back it up for a Young G <br>Remember hoes used to call a nigga ugly <br>Two chains on mouth full of gold teeth <br>OG Chiefed up, try me n' get creased up <br>Couldn't make the cut even with a knife on <br>So bad had to hit it with the lights on <br>Body like a stallion, I'm finna take her home <br>She told me keep that shit a secret, just for me to know <br>She got an ass so fat I gotta hold that <br>I'ma throw this money on it no tax <br>You can quote that, sign sincerely yours <br>I swear I grind all the time make me need it more <br><br>Ooooooooohh ooohh ooh, I'mma get rich on you <br>And I'mma be richer than you, I'mma get rich like <br>Oooooohh ooohh ooh, I'mma get rich on you <br>and I'mma be richer than you, cuz I'm on my shit like <br>Ooooooooohh ooohh ooh, I'mma get rich on you <br>And I'mma be richer than you, I'mma get rich like <br>Oooooohh ooohh ooh, I'mma get rich on you <br>and I'mma be richer than you, cuz I'm on my shit like <br><br>And we never going back so I know it's clear <br>Call the teller every night so I know it's there <br>Only find truth in your account and in your mirror <br>Counting checks cause I'm deaf nigga Kobe stare <br>Ooh the pussy so tight I had to claim her <br>Got yo deal on yo side fail call Kramer <br>Danger, Dying is cheap living ain't free <br>Niggas is cool but niggas ain't me <br>AP whippin' the jury til the court come <br>Get to the millions as a civilian gotta be worth something <br>I only like bitches who go and find bitches <br>they all getting fined even when they find bitches <br>10 Summers like a motherfucking shy sentence <br>You ain't getting business girl stay out my business <br>Why would they sit and ignore calls from niggas <br>Don't call us back or broke richer than all y'all niggas it's Razor <br><br>Ooooooooohh ooohh ooh, I'mma get rich on you <br>And I'mma be richer than you, I'mma get rich like <br>Oooooohh ooohh ooh, I'mma get rich on you <br>and I'mma be richer than you, cuz I'm on my shit like <br>Ooooooooohh ooohh ooh, I'mma get rich on you <br>And I'mma be richer than you, I'mma get rich like <br>Oooooohh ooohh ooh, I'mma get rich on you <br>and I'mma be richer than you, cuz I'm on my shit like]]></content><category term="RJ" label="RJ"/><category term="Get Rich (Feat. Iamsu!)" label="Get Rich (Feat. Iamsu!)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Curry/Threatz_Feat_Yung_Simmie__Robb_Bank/</id><title>Denzel Curry - Threatz (Feat. Yung Simmie &amp; Robb Bank$) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:35:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:35:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Denzel_Curry/Threatz_Feat_Yung_Simmie__Robb_Bank/" title="Denzel Curry - Threatz (Feat. Yung Simmie &amp; Robb Bank$) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nigga Klan be the set, we don't take kindly to threats <br>Nigga we don't take kindly to threats <br>Bitch SS be the set, we don't take kindly to threats <br>We don't take kindly to threats <br>Nigga Klan be the set, we don't take kindly to threats <br>We don't take kindly to threats <br>Bitch SS be the set, we don't take kindly to threats <br>Nah we don't take kindly to threats <br><br>Slide for the free, kill for the fee <br>Pull out the stick then I pull out the ski <br>Put a motherfucker face on a white tee <br>That's what a nigga get being PIE <br>Sweet, nigga you DIE <br>Sleep, motherfucker that's six feet <br>Deep, no tender, no love, no care <br>But a nigga here still gon' creep <br>TLC put it to ya Lisa Lo' that's a nigga left <br>Eye, kill a nigga, get ghost, that <br>Patrick Swayze, come equipped with a vest <br>I'mma point that shit to your motherfucking neck <br>K's all in my trunk <br>So you best to get a chopper <br>It's nothing but goon action <br>I ain't talking Waka Flocka <br>That 275 goons <br>Bout' to do a fucking Gank <br>Bumping Waka Flocka Flame <br>In a underwater tank <br>Cause nigga die right now <br>Bullet or a fucking shank <br>Niggas always tryna' be <br>The hardest in the fucking paint <br><br>Never take kind to the threats <br>I be off for your neck 'for you reach for the TEC, Simmie <br>Niggas gon' hear me then fear me, feel me <br>Whole bunch of green in my Philly, turn up <br>Whole bunch of niggas if you run up <br>Tryna' act hard with your gun up, I shoot your son up <br>Grinding till the sun up, middle finger flashed <br>That's a one up, I'm a young gutta <br>Dog I mutter, Curry said cut 'em with his butter <br>Leave them boys wet like water <br>Off with his neck, posted with the set <br>I don't take kindly to threats, take kindly to threats <br>Ratchet for life, I'm hood, tryna' smoke bad but I'm good <br>Bust a nigga head for the cake <br>Jumping over gates can't wait <br>Nine to the face, fuck nigga you ain't safe <br><br>Nigga Klan be the set, we don't take kindly to threats <br>Nigga we don't take kindly to threats <br>Bitch SS be the set, we don't take kindly to threats <br>We don't take kindly to threats <br>Nigga Klan be the set, we don't take kindly to threats <br>We don't take kindly to threats <br>Bitch SS be the set, we don't take kindly to threats <br>Nah we don't take kindly to threats <br><br>Savage life nigga <br>You don't wanna see me live <br>Pop more than a quarter, so tell that dime piece <br>Bitch, don't kill my vibe, man <br>I know your bitch love me <br>I know your bitch want me <br>She let me pillow pet that kitty <br>When she climb under this Snuggie <br>Bitch, South Florida <br>I only smoke mid in Broward <br>But end the flame of that Magic Dragon <br>And kill that Charmander, bitch <br>Gone on you niggas <br>Two phones on you niggas <br>Think I made it <br>You don't wanna see me ball on you niggas, bitch <br><br>Nigga Klan be the set, we don't take kindly to threats <br>Nigga we don't take kindly to threats <br>Bitch SS be the set, we don't take kindly to threats <br>We don't take kindly to threats <br>Nigga Klan be the set, we don't take kindly to threats <br>We don't take kindly to threats <br>Bitch SS be the set, we don't take kindly to threats <br>Nah we don't take kindly to threats]]></content><category term="Denzel Curry" label="Denzel Curry"/><category term="Threatz (Feat. Yung Simmie &amp; Robb Bank$)" label="Threatz (Feat. Yung Simmie &amp; Robb Bank$)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전지윤/Cliche/</id><title>전지윤 - Cliche - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:35:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:35:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%A7%80%EC%9C%A4/Cliche/" title="전지윤 - Cliche - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She Said I'll be okay but <br>I don't want you feeling okay too <br>영화에서나 볼 법한 Cliche <br>You ain't a thing <br>넌 뭐라도 되는 것 같이 굴기를 너무 <br>좋아하긴 해도 Cliche <br>Dressin up like a kid with that <br>high waist <br>너는 말해 이게 예쁜 것 같아 <br>거기다가 나는 꼭 말해야해 <br>그래 썩 어울리는 것 같아 <br>All you want is nothing more but <br>흔한 Cliche <br>예상 가능한 말 <br>난 질린 듯 해 <br>You're nothing more than a <br>Cliche <br>Cliche <br>You're nothing more than a <br>Cliche <br>Cliche <br>You're nothing more than a <br>Cliche <br>Cliche <br>You're nothing more than a <br>Cliche <br>so don't even try <br>just give it up <br>we're keep wasting <br>give it up <br>we're keep wasting <br>give it up <br>we're keep wasting our time <br>you just don't worth it <br>so we don't even need to say <br>goodbye <br>뭐 분위기 잘 타고 <br>말도 막힘 없이 잘해 <br>딱 봐도 닳고 닳았네 <br>나는 너의 몇번째 <br>궁금하긴 하지만 마냥 <br>기다리진 않아 <br>거기서 거기겠지 <br>내가 만났던 그들과 <br>별반 다를게 없어 <br>이제 더이상 찾을게 없어 <br>시시해 <br>뭘해도 네꺼다 뭐든 어울려 <br>너는 말해 나는 변함없다고 <br>그 말이 진심이길 어리석게 <br>결국 이젠 믿지도 않아 <br>all you wants nothing <br>more but 흔한 cliche <br>예상 가능한 말 난 질린듯 <br>You're nothing more than a <br>Cliche <br>Cliche <br>You're nothing more than a <br>Cliche <br>Cliche <br>You're nothing more than a <br>Cliche <br>Cliche <br>You're nothing more than a <br>Cliche <br>Cliche <br>just give it up <br>we're keep wasting <br>give it up <br>we're keep wasting <br>give it up <br>we're keep wasting our time <br>you just don't worth it <br>so we don't even need to say <br>goodbye <br>또 만날법한 인연 <br>또 같은 말의 반복 <br>난 오늘도 너와의 <br>보이지 않는 다툼에 하루가 <br>또 가네 <br>오 의미없어 이젠 하나도 <br>오 재미없어 이런것들 <br>just give it up <br>we're keep wasting <br>give it up <br>we're keep wasting <br>give it up <br>we're keep wasting our time <br>you just don't worth it <br>so we don't even need to say <br>goodbye <br>goodbye <br>goodbye <br>goodbye <br>goodbye <br>goodbye <br>goodbye <br>goodbye <br>goodbye <br>goodbye <br>goodbye <br>goodbye <br>we don’t even need to say <br>]]></content><category term="전지윤" label="전지윤"/><category term="Cliche" label="Cliche"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스윗소로우/짜리리릿_Sign_Feat_김이지_of_꽃잠프로젝트/</id><title>스윗소로우 - 짜리리릿 (Sign) (Feat. 김이지 of 꽃잠프로젝트) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:35:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:35:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%EC%9C%97%EC%86%8C%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B0/%EC%A7%9C%EB%A6%AC%EB%A6%AC%EB%A6%BF_Sign_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80_of_%EA%BD%83%EC%9E%A0%ED%94%84%EB%A1%9C%EC%A0%9D%ED%8A%B8/" title="스윗소로우 - 짜리리릿 (Sign) (Feat. 김이지 of 꽃잠프로젝트) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I just got 너의 눈빛 속의 Sign <br>느꼈어 너와 눈키스 하는 사이 <br>아무도 모르게 너의 눈빛이 내게만 <br>비밀스럽게 속삭였어 <br>짜리리릿 했던 거야 우리 둘 사이 <br>You got a sign <br>어젯밤 너와 눈이 마주친 그 순간 <br>너랑 나만 빼고 모두 Black out <br>멈춰 버린 것만 같았어 <br>혹시나 내가 또 바보처럼 <br>착각할 수 있어 <br>딴 데 보는 척하면서 Check out <br>너를 확인하다 Oh my god <br>눈부시게 내게 다가와 <br>날 둘러싼 너의 OK Sign <br>Babe 마치 꿈처럼 다가온 너 <br>무슨 말이 더 필요하겠어 <br>I just got 너의 눈빛 속의 Sign <br>느꼈어 너와 눈키스 하는 사이 <br>그 누구도 모르게 너의 눈빛이 내게만 <br>비밀스럽게 말해 줬어 <br>짜리리릿 했던 거야 우리 둘 사이 <br>사실 난 말야 아주 오래 전부터 널 말야 <br>단지 기다렸던 것 뿐 너와 만나게 되면 <br>같은 맘일지도 몰라 <br>좋아 네가 느낀 내 눈빛이 다 맞아 <br>우리 처음 만난 날 <br>눈부시게 내게 다가와 <br>날 둘러싼 너의 OK Sign <br>Babe 마치 운명처럼 다가와 <br>같은 심장이 뛰고 있잖아 <br>I just got 너의 눈빛 속의 Sign <br>너와 나눈 많은 눈빛 속의 Sign <br>느꼈어 너와 눈키스 하는 사이 <br>그만큼 나도 원했어 너의 눈빛이 내게만 <br>비밀스럽게 말해 주길 <br>짜리리릿 했던거야 우리 둘 사이 <br>I just got 너의 눈빛 속의 Sign <br>느꼈어 터질 듯 떨리는 맘 <br>그런 말 이제 알았어 내 사람을 만나면 <br>한눈에 알아본다는 걸 <br>꿈같은 이 순간 <br>짜리리릿 했던거야 우리 둘 사이 <br>아무도 모르는 둘만의 Sign <br>짜리리릿 했던거야 우리 둘 사이 <br>You got a sign <br>]]></content><category term="스윗소로우" label="스윗소로우"/><category term="짜리리릿 (Sign) (Feat. 김이지 of 꽃잠프로젝트)" label="짜리리릿 (Sign) (Feat. 김이지 of 꽃잠프로젝트)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/Tinindo_Trincando/</id><title>Novos Baianos - Tinindo Trincando - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:36:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:36:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/Tinindo_Trincando/" title="Novos Baianos - Tinindo Trincando - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Eu vou assim <br>E venho assim <br>Eu vou assim <br>E venho assim <br><br>Porque quem invade nao <br>Nao chega, nao <br>Chega nao porque pera ai <br>Sou mesmo assim <br>Sou mesmo assim <br>Sou mesmo assim <br>Assim <br><br>Um dia assim <br>Um dia assado <br>Um dia assim <br>No duro tinindo <br>Tinindo trincando]]></content><category term="Novos Baianos" label="Novos Baianos"/><category term="Tinindo Trincando" label="Tinindo Trincando"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/A_Menina_Danca/</id><title>Novos Baianos - A Menina Danca - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:36:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:36:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/A_Menina_Danca/" title="Novos Baianos - A Menina Danca - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Quando eu cheguei tudo, tudo <br>Tudo estava virado <br>Apenas viro me viro <br>Mas eu mesma viro os olhinhos <br><br>So entro no jogo porque <br>Estou mesmo depois <br>Depois de esgotar <br>O tempo regulamentar <br><br>De um lado o olho desaforo <br>Que diz meu nariz arrebitado <br>E nao levo para casa, mas se voce vem perto eu vou la <br>Eu vou la <br><br>No canto do cisco <br>No canto do olho <br>A menina danca <br><br>E dentro da menina <br>A menina danca <br>E se voce fecha o olho <br>A menina ainda danca <br>Dentro da menina <br>Ainda danca <br><br>Ate o sol raiar <br>Ate o sol raiar <br>Ate dentro de voce nascer <br><br>Nascer o que ha <br><br>Quando eu cheguei tudo, tudo <br>Tudo estava virado <br>Apenas viro me viro <br>Mas eu mesma viro os olhinhos]]></content><category term="Novos Baianos" label="Novos Baianos"/><category term="A Menina Danca" label="A Menina Danca"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/Anos_70/</id><title>Novos Baianos - Anos 70 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:36:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:36:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/Anos_70/" title="Novos Baianos - Anos 70 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Olha so a luz que nos leva e a luz do chegar, do chegar <br>Olha a luz que esta na estrela esta em todo lugar <br>E a razao da vida e <br><br>E a razao da vida e amar <br><br>Olha so a agua da chuva e a mesma do mar, do mar <br>Olha o silencio na noite e a flor do luar <br>E a razao da vida e <br>E a razao da vida e amar <br><br>Ah, e Beatles, viver ouvindo Joao, assim como John <br>Deixando marcas na imagem e no som <br>Ah, e Beatles, viver ouvindo Joao, assim como John <br>Deixando marcas na imagem e no som, e no som]]></content><category term="Novos Baianos" label="Novos Baianos"/><category term="Anos 70" label="Anos 70"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/Colegio_De_Aplicacao/</id><title>Novos Baianos - Colegio De Aplicacao - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:36:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:36:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/Colegio_De_Aplicacao/" title="Novos Baianos - Colegio De Aplicacao - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No ceu, azul, azul fumaca <br>Uma nova raca <br>Saindo dos predios para as pracas <br>Uma nova raca <br><br>No ceu, azul, azul fumaca <br>Uma nova raca <br>Saindo dos predios para as pracas <br><br>Uma nova raca <br><br>No ceu, azul, azul fumaca <br>As palavras correm pelos pensamentos <br>No ceu, azul, azul fumaca <br>A vida e a morte calcam igual <br>Uma geracao em busca <br>Nem o bem, nem o mal <br>O proprio passo e a razao <br>No ceu, azul, azul fumaca <br>Uma nova raca <br>Saindo dos predios para as pracas <br>Uma nova raca <br>No ceu, azul, azul fumaca <br>Uma nova raca <br>Saindo dos predios para as pracas <br>Uma nova raca <br>No ceu, azul, azul fumaca <br>Uma nova raca <br>Saindo dos predios para as pracas <br>Uma nova raca]]></content><category term="Novos Baianos" label="Novos Baianos"/><category term="Colegio De Aplicacao" label="Colegio De Aplicacao"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/Infinito_Circular/</id><title>Novos Baianos - Infinito Circular - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:36:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:36:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/Infinito_Circular/" title="Novos Baianos - Infinito Circular - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sim, toda poesia <br>Que no coracao havia <br>O vento levou <br>O vento levou <br><br>E o que se chama amor <br>Como petalas no chao <br>A perder a cor <br>A perder a cor a flor <br><br>Mas, o sol todo dia <br>So pra quem sabe olhar <br>Ilumina e aquece <br>Sim, o sol todo dia <br>So pra quem sabe olhar <br>Ilumina e aquece <br>Toda a beleza que ha <br><br>Salve o que e permitido <br>Pelo infinito circular <br>Pra que a poesia <br>Possa com alegria ao coracao voltar <br><br>Sim, nossa ausencia fez <br>Fez por merecer <br>Ou a chuva regar nosso amor <br>E outra vez no jardim uma flor <br>Ou a chuva regar <br>Nosso amor e outra vez no jardim <br>Uma flor <br><br>Mas, o sol todo dia <br>So pra quem sabe olhar <br>Ilumina e aquece <br>Sim, o sol todo dia <br>So pra quem sabe olhar <br>Ilumina e aquece <br>Toda a beleza que ha <br><br>Sim, nossa ausencia fez <br>Fez por merecer <br>Ou a chuva regar nosso amor <br>E outra vez no jardim, uma flor <br>Ou a chuva regar <br>Nosso amor e outra vez no jardim <br>Uma flor]]></content><category term="Novos Baianos" label="Novos Baianos"/><category term="Infinito Circular" label="Infinito Circular"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/O_Misterio_Do_Planeta/</id><title>Novos Baianos - O Misterio Do Planeta - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:36:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:36:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/O_Misterio_Do_Planeta/" title="Novos Baianos - O Misterio Do Planeta - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Vou mostrando como sou <br>E vou sendo como posso <br>Jogando meu corpo no mundo <br>Andando por todos os cantos <br>E pela lei natural dos encontros <br>Eu deixo e recebo um tanto <br>E passo aos olhos nus <br>Ou vestidos de lunetas <br>Passado, presente <br>Participo sendo o misterio do planeta <br><br>O triplice misterio do stop <br>Que eu passo por e sendo ele <br>No que fica em cada um <br>No que sigo o meu caminho <br>E no ar que fez e assistiu <br>Abra um parenteses, nao esqueca <br>Que independente disso <br>Eu nao passo de um malandro <br>De um moleque do Brasil <br>Que peco e dou esmolas <br>Mas ando e penso sempre com mais de um <br>Por isso ninguem ve minha sacola]]></content><category term="Novos Baianos" label="Novos Baianos"/><category term="O Misterio Do Planeta" label="O Misterio Do Planeta"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/Acabou_Chorare/</id><title>Novos Baianos - Acabou Chorare - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:36:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:36:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/Acabou_Chorare/" title="Novos Baianos - Acabou Chorare - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Acabou chorare, ficou tudo lindo <br>De manha cedinho, tudo ca ca ca, na fe fe fe <br>No bu bu li li, no bu bu li lindo <br>No bu bu bolindo <br>No bu bu bolindo <br>No bu bu bolindo <br><br>Talvez pelo buraquinho, invadiu me a casa <br>Me acordou na cama <br>Tomou o meu coracao e sentou na minha mao <br><br>Abelha, abelhinha <br><br>Acabou chorare <br>Faz zum zum pra eu ver, faz zum zum pra mim <br><br>Abelho, abelhinho escondido faz bonito <br>Faz zum zum e mel <br>Faz zum zum e mel <br>Faz zum zum e mel <br><br>Inda de lambuja tem o carneirinho, presente na boca <br>Acordando toda gente, tao suave me, que suavemente <br>Inda de lambuja tem o carneirinho, presente na boca <br>Acordando toda gente, tao suave me, que suavemente <br><br>Abelha, carneirinho <br><br>Acabou chorare no meio do mundo <br>Respirei eu fundo, foi se tudo pra escanteio <br>Vi o sapo na lagoa, entre nessa que e boa <br><br>Fiz zum zum e pronto <br>Fiz zum zum e pronto <br>Fiz zum zum]]></content><category term="Novos Baianos" label="Novos Baianos"/><category term="Acabou Chorare" label="Acabou Chorare"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/Preta_Pretinha/</id><title>Novos Baianos - Preta Pretinha - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:36:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:36:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Novos_Baianos/Preta_Pretinha/" title="Novos Baianos - Preta Pretinha - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Enquanto eu corria <br>Assim eu ia <br>Lhe chamar <br>Enquanto corria a barca <br>Lhe chamar <br>Enquanto corria a barca <br>Lhe chamar <br>Enquanto corria a barca <br><br>Por minha cabeca nao passava <br>So, somente, so <br>Assim vou lhe chamar <br>Assim voce vai ser <br>So, so, somente, so <br>Assim vou lhe chamar <br>Assim voce vai ser <br>So, somente, so <br>Assim vou lhe chamar <br>Assim voce vai ser <br>So, so, somente, so <br>Assim vou lhe chamar <br>Assim voce vai ser <br><br>Laia Larara Lararara Larara <br>Preta <br>Preta, Preta, Pretinha <br>Preta, Preta, pretinha <br>Preta, Preta, Pretinha <br><br>Enquanto eu corria <br>Assim eu ia <br>Lhe chamar <br>Enquanto corria a barca <br>Lhe chamar <br>Enquanto corria a barca <br>Lhe chamar <br>Enquanto corria a barca <br><br>Por minha cabeca nao passava <br>So, somente, so <br>Assim vou lhe chamar <br>Assim voce vai ser <br>So, so, somente, so <br>Assim vou lhe chamar <br>Assim voce vai ser <br>So, somente, so <br>Assim vou lhe chamar <br>Assim voce vai ser <br>So, so, somente, so <br>Assim vou lhe chamar <br>Assim voce vai ser <br><br>Laia Larara Lararara Larara <br>Preta <br>Preta, Preta, Pretinha <br>Preta, Preta, pretinha <br>Preta, Preta, Pretinha <br><br>Abre a porta e a janela <br>E vem ver o sol nascer <br><br>Eu sou um passaro <br>Que vivo avoando <br>Vivo avoando <br>Sem nunca mais parar <br>Ai, ai, ai, ai, saudade <br>Nao venha me matar <br>Ai, ai, ai, ai, saudade <br>Nao venha me matar <br>Ai, ai, saudade <br>Nao venha me matar <br>Ai, ai, ai, ai, saudade <br>Nao venha me matar <br><br>Lhe chamar]]></content><category term="Novos Baianos" label="Novos Baianos"/><category term="Preta Pretinha" label="Preta Pretinha"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Handsome_Ghost/Beauty___Bends__/</id><title>Handsome Ghost - Beauty / Bends : - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:37:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:37:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Handsome_Ghost/Beauty___Bends__/" title="Handsome Ghost - Beauty / Bends : - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Call it a quick fix, quick fix, quick fix <br>Call it the glue between the glass <br>Find me in basements, wasted, drink sick <br>Holding a faded treasure map <br><br>I could be better to you <br>As sure as the stars surround <br>Edge of the bed in your room <br>Your clothes on the frozen ground <br><br>Beauty and the bends <br>We could start again, we could start again <br>Honey, here I am, holding on <br>Noises in the night, I could get it right for once <br>Beauty and the bends <br>We could start again, we could start again <br>Honey, here I am, holding on <br>Noises in the night, I could get it right <br><br>I could get it right, I will get it right <br>I could get it right, I will get it right <br><br>All of my secrets, secrets, secrets <br>Digging up ten feet underneath <br>Buried in bed rock, back lots, shades drawn <br>Praying this wave may wash me clean <br><br>I could be better to you <br>As sure as the stars surround <br>Edge of the bed in your room <br>Your clothes on the frozen ground <br><br>Beauty and the bends <br>We could start again, we could start again <br>Honey, here I am, holding on <br>Noises in the night, I could get it right for once <br>Beauty and the bends <br>We could start again, we could start again <br>Honey, here I am, holding on <br>Noises in the night, I could get it right <br><br>I could get it right, I will get it right <br>I could get it right, I will get it right <br><br>I could get it right, I will get it right <br>I could get it right, I will get it right <br><br>Beauty and the bends <br>We could start again, we could start again <br>Honey, here I am, holding on <br>Noises in the night, I could get it right for once <br>I could get it right, I will get it right <br>Beauty and the bends <br>We could start again, we could start again <br>Honey, here I am, holding on <br>Noises in the night, I could get it right <br><br>I could get it right, I will get it right <br>I could get it right, I will get it right <br>I could get it right, I will get it right <br>I could get it right, I will get it right <br>Get it right for once]]></content><category term="Handsome Ghost" label="Handsome Ghost"/><category term="Beauty / Bends :" label="Beauty / Bends :"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scarlet_Pleasure/Deja_Vu/</id><title>Scarlet Pleasure - Deja Vu - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:37:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:37:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scarlet_Pleasure/Deja_Vu/" title="Scarlet Pleasure - Deja Vu - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My deja vu <br>Like so many nights before <br>We're so wavy on the floor <br>Gentle dancing maybe feel a little fancy <br>Deja vu <br><br>Alors alors <br>Broken hearts and sweet liqueur <br>Where did you go, my karaoke senorita <br>With the frozen margarita <br>Deja vu <br><br>Blue eve on my Vespa <br>Take me to local cities <br>Take me to local fiesta <br>I know it's a fine line but <br>I'm on vacay on a half time 'cause <br>I need the space to get over you <br><br>Blue nights on my Vespa <br>Take me to local cities <br>Take me to local fiesta <br>I know it's a fine line but <br>I'm on vacay on a half time plus <br>I need the space to get over you <br><br>My deja vu <br>Like so many nights before <br>We're so wavy on the floor <br>Gentle dancing maybe feel a little fancy <br>Deja vu <br><br>Alors alors <br>Broken hearts and sweet liqueur <br>Where did you go, my karaoke senorita <br>With the frozen margarita <br>Deja vu <br><br>Cold breeze by the ocean <br>Radio gives me a feelin' <br>Radio give me emotions playin' <br>Cliches from the 80s and <br>All it does is remind me that <br>I need the space to get over you <br><br>My deja vu <br>Like so many nights before <br>We're so wavy on the floor <br>Gentle dancing maybe feel a little fancy <br>Deja vu <br><br>Alors alors <br>Broken hearts and sweet liqueur <br>Where did you go, my karaoke senorita <br>With the frozen margarita <br>Deja vu]]></content><category term="Scarlet Pleasure" label="Scarlet Pleasure"/><category term="Deja Vu" label="Deja Vu"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tchami/World_To_Me_Feat_MNEK/</id><title>Tchami - World To Me (Feat. MNEK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:38:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:38:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tchami/World_To_Me_Feat_MNEK/" title="Tchami - World To Me (Feat. MNEK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby, you should know that you mean the world to me <br>And you have found a home, a place I don't want to leave <br>I don't know where I belong, yeah yeah <br>But I try, oh I've been waiting so long <br>You mean the world to me <br>You mean the world to me <br><br>You mean the world to me, mean the world to me <br>You mean the world to me, mean the world to me <br>Mean the world to me <br><br>Baby, you should know that my love stays running deep <br>Even if I have to fly, I cross all seven seas <br>I don't want you to feel alone <br>I'm right side on every inch of the globe <br><br>You mean the world to me, mean the world to me <br>You mean the world to me, mean the world to me <br>You mean the world to me, mean the world to me <br>You mean the world to me, mean the world to me <br>Mean the world to me <br><br>World to me, world to me <br>World to me, world to me <br>World to me, world to me <br>World to me, world to me <br>Mean the world to me, mean the world to me <br>Mean the world to me, mean the world to me <br>Mean the world to me, mean the world to me <br>Mean the world to me, mean the world to me <br>Mean the world to me, mean the world to me]]></content><category term="Tchami" label="Tchami"/><category term="World To Me (Feat. MNEK)" label="World To Me (Feat. MNEK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dream_Ami/はやく逢いたい___Hayaku_Aitai_빨리_만나고싶어/</id><title>Dream Ami - はやく逢いたい / Hayaku Aitai (빨리 만나고싶어) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:38:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:38:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dream_Ami/%E3%81%AF%E3%82%84%E3%81%8F%E9%80%A2%E3%81%84%E3%81%9F%E3%81%84___Hayaku_Aitai_%EB%B9%A8%EB%A6%AC_%EB%A7%8C%EB%82%98%EA%B3%A0%EC%8B%B6%EC%96%B4/" title="Dream Ami - はやく逢いたい / Hayaku Aitai (빨리 만나고싶어) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[콘나니 다레카오 오모- 키모치 오시에테쿠레테 <br>시와아세다요 오네가이 하나사나이데네 <br>하야쿠 하야쿠 아이타이 <br>토시노 와리니 오사나잇-테 <br>이마마데 이와레테키타케도 손-나 와타시오 이토오시 소-니？ <br>미츠메테루 코토바니 데키나이 와타시노 키모치닷테 <br>싯테이테 손-나 아나타니 토키메이테마스 <br>네에 스킷테 키이타라 타메이키 츠키나가라 <br>챤-토 코타에테쿠레루 아나타가 스키 <br>콘나니 다레카오 오모- 키모치 오시에테쿠레테 <br>아리가토-토 이마나라 스나오니 이에루토 와캇타노 <br>나미다가 아후레테 토마라나쿠테 키즈이타라 모- <br>하시리다시테타 오네가이 하나사나이데네 <br>하야쿠 하야쿠 아이타이 <br>스키나 키모치토 와가마마와 이츠모 히레이 시테루카라 <br>코마라세챠-시 키즈츠케챠-시 고멘나사이 <br>이소가시이 아이마오 눗테 카케테 쿠레루 뎅-와모 <br>춋-토 스네테루 와타시노 타메 키세츠가 카와루 타비니 <br>후타리노 칸케이모 카왓테이쿠카나 스코시 후아은다케토 <br>오시에테호시이 아나타오 못-토 캇코와루이 토코로모 젠-부 <br>미세타쿠나이 키모치모 우케토메루카라 와타시니 데키루 코토가 아루나라 <br>스베테오 스테테 마못테쿠요 소노 테오 하나사나이카라 <br>하야쿠 하야쿠 아이타이 <br>카케히키와 토쿠이쟈나이 스나오테 이타이 <br>오토나토카 칸-케이나쿠테 <br>I miss you 콘나니 다레카오 오모- 키모치 오시에테 쿠레데 <br>아리카토-토 이마나라 스나오니 이에루토 와캇타노 <br>나미다가 아후레테 토마라나쿠테 키즈이타라 모- <br>하시리시다시테타 소라니와 호라 나가레보시 <br>하야쿠 하야쿠 아이타이]]></content><category term="Dream Ami" label="Dream Ami"/><category term="はやく逢いたい / Hayaku Aitai (빨리 만나고싶어)" label="はやく逢いたい / Hayaku Aitai (빨리 만나고싶어)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/솔비/너는_어때/</id><title>솔비 - 너는 어때 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:38:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:38:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%94%EB%B9%84/%EB%84%88%EB%8A%94_%EC%96%B4%EB%95%8C/" title="솔비 - 너는 어때 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 뭐해 바쁘진 않니 <br>신촌 홍대 자주 다니니 <br>아직도 매운 카레집 단골이니 <br>난 좀 그래 바뀌질 않네 <br>별 일 없이 똑같이 지내 <br>아직도 가끔 니 사진을 봐 <br>요즘 너는 어때 늘 생각해 <br>우리 놀던 그 때 그리워해 <br>시간 지나면 잊혀질거라 <br>생각했는데 <br>이제 와서 니가 더 뚜렷해 <br>예전보다 널 더 그리워해 <br>시간 있으면 잊지 말고 <br>돌아와줘 <br>많이 바빠 정신이 없어 <br>홍대 간 지 참 오래 됐어 <br>입맛이 바뀌어서 매운 건 안 먹어 <br>아는 동생 대쉬 하는데 <br>왠지 몰라 안 끌리는 건 <br>아직 너를 다 못 잊었나봐 <br>요즘 너는 어때 늘 생각해 <br>우리 놀던 그 때 그리워해 <br>시간 지나면 잊혀질거라 <br>생각했는데 <br>이제 와서 니가 더 뚜렷해 <br>예전보다 널 더 그리워해 <br>시간 있으면 잊지 말고 <br>돌아와줘 <br>요즘 너는 어때 늘 생각해 <br>우리 놀던 그 때 그리워해 <br>시간 지나면 잊혀질거라 <br>생각했는데 <br>이제 와서 니가 더 뚜렷해 <br>예전보다 널 더 그리워해 <br>시간 있으면 잊지 말고 <br>돌아와줘 <br>]]></content><category term="솔비" label="솔비"/><category term="너는 어때" label="너는 어때"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/RJ/Only_One/</id><title>RJ - Only One - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:39:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:39:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/RJ/Only_One/" title="RJ - Only One - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Huh, huh, huh, huuuuuuuuhhh <br><br>I'm the only one popping in the hood now <br>I'm in the hood now ×2 <br>I'm the only one popping in the hood now <br>Huh <br>I'm the only one popping in the hood now <br>Anybody else Anybody else <br>Anybody else poppin' I done helped 'em out <br>Anybody else poppin' I done gave 'em life <br>I done birthed so many hits need a mid wife <br><br>Oooh I fucked up showed a little bit of recipe <br>You know it's us when you see these niggas' pedigree <br>Got my nuts in your DNA <br>Got my nuts in your DNA <br>I bust in your feda face <br>I'm the only one popping I'm a top gun <br>I can barely feel your shots in this Teflon <br>My bitch trippin' had to beat her like a step son <br>Then we kiss and we make up without the Revlon <br><br>I'm the only one poppin' in the hood now <br>Uggh <br>I'm the only one poppin' inna, inna, inna, inna, inna, inna, inna inna, inna hood now <br>I'm the only one poppin' in the hood now <br>Anybody else poppin' I done helped 'em out <br>Anybody else poppin' I done gave 'em life <br>Anybody else poppin' I done I done I done I done ooooooooohh <br>I'm the only one poppin' in the hood now <br><br>She just pulled my unit out <br>She's doing it like you are not me <br>I won't even count the body <br>You do what you want when you popping <br><br>I swear you niggas mediocre <br>We heat the oven bake the <br>I been cooking like I'm feeding Oprah <br>Gotta keep it roasting <br>Whip the rooster like a test in roastin <br>Sick a shooter out that Chevy Nova <br>Send a hollow through the bedroom poster <br>Any nigga got a problem then arrest the culture <br>I been fucking all the cheerleaders pressing the coachs <br>Screaming fuck who next and whoever the closest <br><br>I'm the only nigga poppin' in the muthafucking hood now <br>I'm the only nigga poppin' in the hood now <br>I'm in the hood now, I'm in the hood now, hood now, I'm in the hood <br><br>She just pulled my unit out <br>She's doing it like you are not me <br>I won't even count the body <br>You do what you want when you popping <br>She just pulled my unit out <br>She's doing it like you are not me <br>I won't even count the body <br>You do what you want when you popping]]></content><category term="RJ" label="RJ"/><category term="Only One" label="Only One"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/T2/Heartbroken/</id><title>T2 - Heartbroken - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:39:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:39:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/T2/Heartbroken/" title="T2 - Heartbroken - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, 'fessions to, I do, I, I do <br>Oh, oh, fessi ession 'fessions too <br>Oh, oh, 'fessions to, I do, I, I too <br>Oh, oh, fessi ession, do come true <br><br>Sitting here at home <br>Thinking 'bout you all alone <br>Wondering where are love went wrong <br>Got a confession to make <br>Since you made me happier <br>Now all I can do is hurt <br>When you left you took my heart <br>Got a confession to make <br><br>I'm heartbroken, without your love <br>I'm Heartbroken, yes I've had enough <br>I'm Heartbroken <br>And I don't know what to say <br>I've never felt this way <br>I'm heartbroken, without your love <br>I'm Heartbroken, yes I've had enough <br>I'm Heartbroken <br>And I don't know what to say <br>I've never felt this way <br><br>Oh, 'fessions to, I do, I, I do <br>Oh, oh, fessi ession 'fessions too <br>Oh, oh, 'fessions to, I do, I, I too <br>Oh, oh, fessi ession, do come true <br><br>I'm heartbroken, without your love <br>I'm Heartbroken, yes I've had enough <br>I'm Heartbroken <br>And I don't know what to say <br>I've never felt this way <br>I'm heartbroken, without your love <br>I'm Heartbroken, yes I've had enough <br>I'm Heartbroken <br>And I don't know what to say <br>I've never felt this way <br><br>Have something so true <br>I realised I meant nothing to you <br>I guess you thought I was your fool <br>Got a confession to make <br>Now I realise the truth <br>I don't want anything to do with you <br>It's just the way I was attracted to you <br>Got a confession to make <br><br>I'm heartbroken, without your love <br>I'm Heartbroken, yes I've had enough <br>I'm Heartbroken <br>And I don't know what to say <br>I've never felt this way <br>I'm heartbroken, without your love <br>I'm Heartbroken, yes I've had enough <br>I'm Heartbroken <br>And I don't know what to say <br>I've never felt this way]]></content><category term="T2" label="T2"/><category term="Heartbroken" label="Heartbroken"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/T2/Heartbroken_Edit/</id><title>T2 - Heartbroken (Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:39:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:39:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/T2/Heartbroken_Edit/" title="T2 - Heartbroken (Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, 'fessions to, I do, I, I do <br>Oh, oh, fessi ession 'fessions too <br>Oh, oh, 'fessions to, I do, I, I too <br>Oh, oh, fessi ession, do come true <br><br>Sitting here at home <br>Thinking 'bout you all alone <br>Wondering where are love went wrong <br>Got a confession to make <br>Since you made me happier <br>Now all I can do is hurt <br>When you left you took my heart <br>Got a confession to make <br><br>I'm heartbroken, without your love <br>I'm Heartbroken, yes I've had enough <br>I'm Heartbroken <br>And I don't know what to say <br>I've never felt this way <br>I'm heartbroken, without your love <br>I'm Heartbroken, yes I've had enough <br>I'm Heartbroken <br>And I don't know what to say <br>I've never felt this way <br><br>Oh, 'fessions to, I do, I, I do <br>Oh, oh, fessi ession 'fessions too <br>Oh, oh, 'fessions to, I do, I, I too <br>Oh, oh, fessi ession, do come true <br><br>I'm heartbroken, without your love <br>I'm Heartbroken, yes I've had enough <br>I'm Heartbroken <br>And I don't know what to say <br>I've never felt this way <br>I'm heartbroken, without your love <br>I'm Heartbroken, yes I've had enough <br>I'm Heartbroken <br>And I don't know what to say <br>I've never felt this way <br><br>Have something so true <br>I realised I meant nothing to you <br>I guess you thought I was your fool <br>Got a confession to make <br>Now I realise the truth <br>I don't want anything to do with you <br>It's just the way I was attracted to you <br>Got a confession to make <br><br>I'm heartbroken, without your love <br>I'm Heartbroken, yes I've had enough <br>I'm Heartbroken <br>And I don't know what to say <br>I've never felt this way <br>I'm heartbroken, without your love <br>I'm Heartbroken, yes I've had enough <br>I'm Heartbroken <br>And I don't know what to say <br>I've never felt this way]]></content><category term="T2" label="T2"/><category term="Heartbroken (Edit)" label="Heartbroken (Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scotty_Cain/Throw_Them_Bitches/</id><title>Scotty Cain - Throw Them Bitches - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:39:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:39:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scotty_Cain/Throw_Them_Bitches/" title="Scotty Cain - Throw Them Bitches - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nigga we throw them bitches x2 <br>Mafia <br><br>My team flash racks <br>We got these niggas mad <br>I see yo bitch I flex just cuz she got a lot of ass <br>Nigga go to trippin <br>Bitch don't make me flash <br>CainMusik an' 54 gon' get on a nigga ass <br>We throw them bitches <br>Beat a nigga ass put him through the flo' <br>We throw them bitches <br>Fuck talking bitch Imma dive and break yo nose <br>We throw them bitches <br>He tryna' run Get a nice grip to his clothes <br>Beat his ass out the do' <br>Get in that zone and act some mo' <br>We throw them bitches <br><br>Mafia <br>All I ever wanted was a stack that's full of hundreds <br>Mine gone, even thoughts, got me feeling 'hunned <br>Hurt my heart to see my brother Chad Cain wanted <br>Oh yeah, dude, imma' wack yo rattin' ass for pointin' <br>Mobbin' in the old school Monte Carlo <br>In all black, wack and never rat, we ain't no Marlo <br>Chopper wack, I'll up this bitch and knock off all yo car doors <br>My cousin Joseph from hittin' licks, free bro Marco <br>Throw them bitches <br>My youngins throw them bitches <br>And beef We throw bullets out the clips until they empty <br>I'm a menace, but bitch I'm still in it <br>Go get a nigga just for bringin' me up in they mentions <br>Money Bitch I get it, get a air bowl then flip it <br>Tryna jack Bitch I got this Glock that got extensions <br>I don't think you niggas really with this like I'm with this <br>Chopper really school a nigga, call it early dismiss <br>Mafia <br><br>My team flash racks <br>We got these niggas mad <br>I see yo bitch I flex just cuz she got a lot of ass <br>Nigga go to trippin <br>Bitch don't make me flash <br>CainMusik an' 54 gon' get on a nigga ass <br>We throw them bitches <br>Beat a nigga ass put him through the flo' <br>We throw them bitches <br>Fuck talking bitch Imma dive and break yo nose <br>We throw them bitches <br>He tryna' run Get a nice grip to his clothes <br>Beat his ass out the do' <br>Get in that zone and act some mo' <br>We throw them bitches <br><br>I got clutchin' habbits, so I got bustin' habbits <br>Maneuver throw the city and the realluns' just for bustin at ya' <br>I told you don't make me flash, don't make me flash <br>See you done that bad, I gotta bust ya ass <br>Fuckin' 'round with Harley Ken I got my rollin' racks <br>Big stacks, I do numbers once I make it back <br> hollin' fuck ya, you know I'm gonna do you <br>You see me in this chair, can't fight I gotta shoot ya <br><br>Money can't be the fuckin' dope charge <br>Know some rich naggas from cocain behind bars <br>Two big meats, my nigga Cut was the sickest <br>He showed me how to make a meal ticket in the kitchen <br>Whip it up, Whip it up, Whip it up I'm tryna get rich <br>Now I live the fuckin' life of a superstar <br>Yeah, I'm flashy, every night I'm in a different car <br>I ain't finna' throw them bitches, finna kill ya boy <br><br>My team flash racks <br>We got these niggas mad <br>I see yo bitch I flex just cuz she got a lot of ass <br>Nigga go to trippin <br>Bitch don't make me flash <br>CainMusik an' 54 gon' get on a nigga ass <br>We throw them bitches <br>Beat a nigga ass put him through the flo' <br>We throw them bitches <br>Fuck talking bitch Imma dive and break yo nose <br>We throw them bitches <br>He tryna' run Get a nice grip to his clothes <br>Beat his ass out the do' <br>Get in that zone and act some mo' <br>We throw them bitches <br><br>Get the business clear, Niggas pussy, I'm the only son <br>Catch him talkin this lil' shit <br>Bat him in his front <br>I touched 20 bands <br>Then I went crazy, It's me, I'm mark <br>Valet park the 'vette at Nemus I am not a star, yeah <br>I be on yo bitch <br>I low key yo bitch <br>She bought me some kicks <br>Then she got dismissed <br>I'm trainin', I'm trainin', I'm throwing like I'm Russel <br>Out his body, make him do Pilates on the muscle <br>What up <br><br>A nigga know I keep a pocket full of C Notes, Swisher fulla' weed <br>A clip fulla' hollows to make you busters bleed <br>In the club wit a big ass pistol like, Who gon' murder me <br>Put ya hands on me I bet I turn this to a murder scene <br>Glocks with beams, all us we be clutchin, Either that or choppas <br>All of them be ready to go bang at you and yo lil' partners <br>Dreaded up like I'm a Rasta, but I'm out of Ghosttown <br>Play me, it's gon' go down, send orders if you up clown <br><br>My team flash racks <br>We got these niggas mad <br>I see yo bitch I flex just cuz she got a lot of ass <br>Nigga go to trippin <br>Bitch don't make me flash <br>CainMusik an' 54 gon' get on a nigga ass <br>We throw them bitches <br>Beat a nigga ass put him through the flo' <br>We throw them bitches <br>Fuck talking bitch Imma dive and break yo nose <br>We throw them bitches <br>He tryna' run Get a nice grip to his clothes <br>Beat his ass out the do' <br>Get in that zone and act some mo' <br>We throw them bitches]]></content><category term="Scotty Cain" label="Scotty Cain"/><category term="Throw Them Bitches" label="Throw Them Bitches"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/매시드_Mashed/태도/</id><title>매시드 (Mashed) - 태도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:39:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:39:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%A4%EC%8B%9C%EB%93%9C_Mashed/%ED%83%9C%EB%8F%84/" title="매시드 (Mashed) - 태도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[네 태도 네 랩에 비하면 Role model <br>내가 뜨진 않았어도 나는 좀 알아 <br>진짜로 가지 못한다면 꿈도 못 가져 <br>나의 쌔끈함을 못 이겨 도망쳐 <br>이미 짓밟힌 너로서는 또 만나도 또 져 <br>넌 거품이 넘쳐 거만하고 랩은 졸려 <br>자 믿고 보는 거야 나는 말이야 <br>무한도전 같이 활동 안 하고 싶어 <br>소름이 도져 <br>고정된 시선이 항상 멈추는 곳은 <br>뭔가에 이끌린 듯 귀가 끌리는 곡들 <br>또는 뭔가 할 수 있다 말하지 나란 놈은 <br>하루도 안 쉬고 가사 쓰고 바로 해 녹음 <br>뱀의 꼬리 될 수 없지 88년생 용의 띠 <br>말만 하지 말고 행동하면 다시 보겠지 <br>승수야 형이 행동으로 바로 보여줌 <br>가식으로 말해 아마 3년 아니 5년쯤 <br>누군 네게 말하지 요즘 style로 <br>요즘 유행이 뭔데 해봐 말로 <br>불러 내 이름 약속해 내 길을 <br>두 번은 안 흔들려 찾았어 의미를 <br>누군 네게 말하지 요즘 style로 <br>요즘 유행이 뭔데 해봐 말로 <br>불러 내 이름 약속해 내 길을 <br>두 번은 안 흔들려 찾았어 의미를 <br>아마 한 달 봤지 스윙스 형 괜찮아 <br>의욕만 앞서서 형한테 목 멨잖아 <br>그때부터 나는 직진 <br>다른 래퍼들을 찢기 <br>특히 못 하는 애 씹기 <br>디스 아냐 진짜 일찍 <br>그만뒀으면 좋겠어 아마 나보다 더 <br>네가 말하는 게으름은 진짜 나도 많아 <br>그냥 잘한다고 말해 알아서 나 잘하게 <br>계속 늘 수 있다 최면 걸고 계속 발악해 <br>바람에도 흔들리지 않고 직진 가는 배 <br>40분 만에 쓰고 나는 개 나른해 <br>가늘게 살긴 싫고 굳이 말하면 두껍게 <br>허언증은 없네 두 얼굴에 두 허세 <br>앞으로 내 인생이 어디로 갈진 몰라 <br>뭐가 있겠어 그냥 하는 거지 존나 <br>열심히 할 테니까 날 보면 쳐줘 박수 <br>오늘도 바로 예약하고 <br>새로 하는 tattoo <br>누군 네게 말하지 요즘 style로 <br>요즘 유행이 뭔데 해봐 말로 <br>불러 내 이름 약속해 내 길을 <br>두 번은 안 흔들려 찾았어 의미를 <br>누군 네게 말하지 요즘 style로 <br>요즘 유행이 뭔데 해봐 말로 <br>불러 내 이름 약속해 내 길을 <br>두 번은 안 흔들려 찾았어 의미를 <br>]]></content><category term="매시드 (Mashed)" label="매시드 (Mashed)"/><category term="태도" label="태도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Priestess/Torno_Domani/</id><title>Priestess - Torno Domani - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:42:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:42:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Priestess/Torno_Domani/" title="Priestess - Torno Domani - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Le diciassette, guarda che faccia <br>Mi faccio un te, guardo la tazza <br>Fuori gia buio, che vuoi che faccia <br>Dentro di me, ci vive un'altra <br>Mi muovo in casa come un fantasma <br>Lodate Priestess, piena di grazia <br>Mia madre dice che sono pazza <br>La bocca amara, esala e poi l'ansia <br>Le diciannove, non trovo le chiavi <br>Io non rispondo, eri tu che chiamavi <br>Giorni imperfetti come gli umani <br>Poi mi addormento, i sogni strani <br>Torno domani <br><br>Lala lalala la, torno domani <br>Lala lalala la, torno domani <br>Lala lalala la, torno domani <br><br>Sono le sette e mi alzo dal letto <br>Una ballata suona dentro il petto <br>Prendo le calze terzo cassetto <br>Anestesia del mio corpo deserto <br>All'anulare l'anello mancante <br>Tutta la vita che scorre un istante <br>Parto alle nove, mi metto al volante <br>Parte il controllo la mia aggravante <br><br>Lala lalala la, torno domani <br>Lala lalala la, torno domani <br>Lala lalala la, torno domani]]></content><category term="Priestess" label="Priestess"/><category term="Torno Domani" label="Torno Domani"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Priestess/Maria_Antonietta/</id><title>Priestess - Maria Antonietta - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:42:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:42:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Priestess/Maria_Antonietta/" title="Priestess - Maria Antonietta - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Camere oscure, sapore di erba <br>Le canne e i caffe, i vicini son fuori di testa <br>Un po' come me <br>Alzo il volume, sotterro i pensieri e la merda <br>Freddi col cuore, ti spezza <br>L'ansia, le pare e i cliche <br>L'ansia, le pare e i cliche <br>La mia stella buona sai dov'e <br>Impressione fredda di un Monet <br>Lingua d'oc, je vous parlez francais <br>La tristezza, Creme Brulee, l'ultimo dessert <br>Che non voglio condividere con te <br>Poi rimango a scrivere fino alle tre <br><br>E se non rispondi, vado fuori di testa <br>E se mi assecondi, vado fuori di testa <br>Fiori per me, erba per te, noi fuori di testa <br>Fiori per me, erba per te, noi fuori di testa <br><br>Ho perso la testa per te <br>Maria Antonietta, Maria Antonietta <br>Ho perso la testa per te <br>Maria Antonietta, Maria Antonietta <br>Ho perso la testa per te <br>Maria Antonietta <br>Ho perso la testa per te <br>Ho perso la testa per te <br><br>E le vedi in giro tutte queste Barbie <br>Tutte uguali, fatte in serie <br>Con il tipo incamiciato, con i dindin e la fuoriserie <br>Ma, questa sera <br>Esco e ci sto male <br>Niente di personale, con in bocca un personale <br>Tra le mani fragranza di hashish <br>Girane una poi baciami, aspetta mi lasci <br>Noi siamo ammalati, influenza, tu spero ci passi <br>Fanculo gli altri eh <br>Noi siamo perfetti, matti, nati per essere fatti <br>Ti tengo stretto non scappi <br><br>E se non rispondi, vado fuori di testa <br>E se mi assecondi, vado fuori di testa <br>Fiori per me, erba per te, noi fuori di testa <br>Fiori per me, erba per te, noi fuori di testa <br><br>Ho perso la testa per te <br>Maria Antonietta, Maria Antonietta <br>Ho perso la testa per te <br>Maria Antonietta, Maria Antonietta <br>Ho perso la testa per te <br>Maria Antonietta <br>Ho perso la testa per te <br>Ho perso la testa per te <br><br>Ho perso la testa per te <br>Maria Antonietta, Maria Antonietta <br>Ho perso la testa per te <br>Maria Antonietta, Maria Antonietta <br>Ho perso la testa per te <br>Maria Antonietta <br>Ho perso la testa per te <br>Ho perso la testa per te]]></content><category term="Priestess" label="Priestess"/><category term="Maria Antonietta" label="Maria Antonietta"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tommy_Genesis/Empty/</id><title>Tommy Genesis - Empty - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:42:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:42:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tommy_Genesis/Empty/" title="Tommy Genesis - Empty - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What, what, what, what <br>Check, eheh <br>Sometimes I feel really alone <br><br>I make you better but you make me sad <br>I make you better but you make me sad <br>I make you better but you make me sad <br>If you hurt me, I will hurt you back <br>I'm a bad bitch if you notice me, I swish by <br>Swish Swish <br>I'm a bad bitch if you notice me, I swish by <br>Swish swish Swish swish <br>She is evil, have you tried <br>Beautiful silicone doll that takes everything <br>Am I bad, or am I in love <br>Do I want this, or am I empty <br>Do I fuck with it, or am I lost <br>Am I strong, or am I empty <br>Get it off, no means no, no means no <br><br>I ain't empty ho <br>I ain't empty ho <br>I ain't empty ho <br>Eh, no means no, no means no <br>I ain't empty ho <br>I ain't empty ho <br>I ain't empty ho <br>No means no, no means no <br><br>No means no <br>Are you sick of all the bodies <br>Are you sick of being empty <br>Are you sick baby Are you sick baby Are you sick baby <br>Do you want my blood Do you want my love Are you sick <br>Am I pretty on the inside, am I baby <br>Am I pretty on the inside, am I baby <br>Am I pretty on the inside, am I baby <br>Do I make your dick fixate or are you still in love with her <br><br>I ain't empty ho <br>I ain't empty ho <br>I ain't empty ho <br>Eh, no means no, no means no <br>I ain't empty ho <br>I ain't empty ho <br>I ain't empty ho <br>No means no, no means no <br><br>Fuck every ex you ever had <br>Fuck every girl you'll ever fuck <br>Fuck everyone <br>Fuck everyone <br>Fuck everyone <br>Fuck everyone <br>Fuck every ex you ever had <br>Fuck every girl you'll ever fuck <br>Fuck everyone <br>Fuck everyone <br>Fuck everyone <br>Fuck everyone]]></content><category term="Tommy Genesis" label="Tommy Genesis"/><category term="Empty" label="Empty"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gael_Faye/Irruption/</id><title>Gael Faye - Irruption - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:43:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:43:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gael_Faye/Irruption/" title="Gael Faye - Irruption - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[On sort en trombe, en nombre, on se deverse en plaine <br>En centaines, en millions, en milliards ou en milliemes <br>De quelques simples gouttes a des marees humaines <br>Des jaillissements d'aurore pour eclairer des emblemes <br>Des lanternes dans la tete, si l'on plonge dans les tenebres <br>On nous appelle PD, blancos, bougnoules ou bien negres <br>On vit dans la riposte, on reflechit apres coup <br>On vit extra muros donc on arrive par vos egouts <br>Nous sommes des cargaisons de femmes voilees, des youyous stridents <br>Des rastas, des casquettes tournees, des voyous prudents <br>Des espoirs accroches, des paradis assassines <br>Des parents epuises enfantant des gosses meprises <br>De la marmaille bruyante, des petits morveux frises <br>Engraisses d'allocations qui donnent des pretextes a voter <br>Trouver des bouc emissaires, les egorger pour l'Aid <br>Mourir dans une clairiere sans treillis pour ce pays <br>L'affiche est couleur sang, et Manouchian vient pas d'Auvergne <br>Le tirailleur t'emmerde, il a feconde ta grand mere <br>On investit Brongniart, le dos au mur comme Jean Pierre Thorn <br>On s'en fout du grand soir parce que la nuit, c'est bien trop morne <br>On veut meme pas de soleil et des eclipses pour faire l'amour <br>Pour que l'instant soit bref, intense comme un fruit qu'on savoure <br>Aux armes miraculeuses on a lu Cesaire et Prevert <br>On viendra vous faire la guerre avec la parole poudriere <br>On n'designe plus l'ennemi, parce qu'il est partout meme en nous <br>On va mourir debout parce qu'on a vecu a genoux <br>On est sourds aux slogans elimes par trop de manifs <br>On devient arrogants on veut rimer comme des canifs <br>On n'a plus 20 ans mais on n'aura jamais 60 <br>Car on bouffe du bisphenol a l'heure d'une planete suffocante <br>On fait de nous des enfants pour nous interdire des luttes <br>Donc non, pan Peter Pan on va redevenir adultes <br>On a coince nos rages entre le merite et l'heritage <br>Et les puissants confisquent ce que les pauvres se partagent <br>a leurs chaises musicales, personne ne joue, personne s'assoit <br>On occupe du terrain, etre indigne ca va de soi <br>Angela ke fend'tchou aw pendant que ton papa est pas la <br>On va ouvrir les portes de Soledad ou Attica <br>Pharmaco dependants des OGM pour nous doper <br>J'ai recrache l'assiette, monte le cheval et galope <br>Braque un RER dilligence l'Apache de Belleville <br>Viendra crier vengeance comme Balavoine arrive en ville <br>Ils veulent nous assigner des places, et nous faire saigner <br>Les amoureux aux bancs publics n'arreteront jamais de s'aimer <br>Depuis que nos checks ressemblent a des poignees de main de Montoire <br>On ne laissera personne parler au nom de nos espoirs <br>On n'est pas des victimes, encore moins des condamnes <br>On arrivera de l'aube en irruption spontanee]]></content><category term="Gael Faye" label="Gael Faye"/><category term="Irruption" label="Irruption"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vild_Smith/Send_Nudes/</id><title>Vild Smith - Send Nudes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:43:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:43:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vild_Smith/Send_Nudes/" title="Vild Smith - Send Nudes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yay <br>Yay <br><br>Smid dine bukser og din bluse Yay <br>Smid din BH og din trusse Yay <br>Lav et lille photoshoot Yay <br>Bare lige der midt inde i din sture <br><br>Pose for mig baby send mig en snap <br>Jeg har brug for noget lige nu <br>Send en video hvor du flexer dine tricks <br>Ellers har vi et issue <br>For jeg er afhaengig af det shit <br>Jeg ma ha mig et fix og det kan ikk ga hurtigt nok <br>For jeg er sa vild med dine skills <br>Jeg far chills pa min krop <br>For du er sa fine kan ikk holde det ud <br>Lad der ikk ga for lang tid mellem dine skud <br>Jeg ved godt det er pa vej jeg ma bare holde ud <br>Men hvor lang tid kan det tage <br>Helt aerligt kom nu <br><br>Lav dit eget photoshoot <br>Men husk at smid din bluse <br>Maske os din trusse <br>Send nu bare de nudes <br>Ja send min nu bare de nudes <br>Jeg lover ikke at vise dem til dudes <br>Ja send min nu bare de nudes <br>Ellers er det slut <br>Det var de nudes <br>Ja resultatet af dit photoshoot <br>Ja send min nu bare de nudes <br>Ellers er det slut <br><br>Lad mig se dig ga i bro <br>Lad mig se dig ga i split <br>Lad mig se dig taende din blitz <br>Snap snap <br>Som var der en paparazzi <br>Fuck et filter bare send dem til mig <br>Jeg lover ingen af mine venner bliver bekendte med dig <br>Fuck et filter bare send dem til mig <br>Du skinner selv nar sommer bliver til vinter <br><br>Lav dit eget photoshoot <br>Men husk at smid din bluse <br>Maske os din trusse <br>Send nu bare de nudes <br>Ja send min nu bare de nudes <br>Jeg lover ikke at vise dem til dudes <br>Ja send min nu bare de nudes <br>Ellers er det slut <br>Det var de nudes <br>Ja resultatet af dit photoshoot <br>Ja send min nu bare de nudes <br>Ellers er det slut <br><br>Jeg har en stor database den er proppet med dudes <br>Som jeg kan sidde her og nyde sammen med vodka og juice <br>Jeg ser pa nogen uden bluse ogsa nogen der er nude <br>Der er nogen der er baby clean ogsa nogen der har tusch <br>Send min nu bare de nudes <br>Jeg lover ikke at vise dem til dudes <br>Ja send min nu bare de nudes <br>Ellers er det slut <br>Det var de nudes <br>Ja resultatet af dit photoshoot <br>Ja send min nu bare de nudes <br>Ellers er det slut <br><br>Yaay]]></content><category term="Vild Smith" label="Vild Smith"/><category term="Send Nudes" label="Send Nudes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Corey_King/Ibaraki/</id><title>Corey King - Ibaraki - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:44:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:44:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Corey_King/Ibaraki/" title="Corey King - Ibaraki - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Leaning on the settling mound <br>Impeached by the hums <br>Of sweltering mouths that label <br><br>You and I and all that's around <br>East of the Sun <br>With Blaring amounts of breakthroughs <br><br>Hone in on the pictures allowed <br>Framed and hung to cripple the route that able <br><br>We are bound to find us an out <br>The final outcome's approaching the sound <br>So make room <br><br>All I need is silence somehow <br>To keep all the mush from trickling down <br>We're the same old chained song <br><br>You and I and all that's around <br>The feast for the lust and sentenced somehow <br>We're the same old chained song <br><br>Leaning on the slippery mound <br>Embraced by the tongues <br>Of cynical hounds to virtue <br><br>We are wronged <br>The yeast of the town <br>Waited for years to get off the ground to sus you out <br><br>All I need is silence somehow <br>To keep all the mush from trickling down <br>We're the same old chained song <br><br>You and I and all that's around <br>The feast for the lust and sentenced somehow <br>We're the same old chained song]]></content><category term="Corey King" label="Corey King"/><category term="Ibaraki" label="Ibaraki"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alex_Aiono/Work_The_Middle_Acoustic/</id><title>Alex Aiono - Work The Middle (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:44:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:44:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alex_Aiono/Work_The_Middle_Acoustic/" title="Alex Aiono - Work The Middle (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come and meet me where the lights low <br>Where it's just me and you <br>Girl take me to the night show <br>Give me a front row view <br>Baby don't say no, no, no, no <br>You know what I wanna do, yeah <br>I could be your maestro and never play you for a fool <br><br>Oh, yeah I'm three seconds from way to gone I know <br>And I'm two seconds from blowing up your phone <br>You're the one I wanna see when I get home <br>Don't leave me alone <br><br>Come and meet me at the afterparty <br>Bring your body, mama work the middle <br>Just a little don't tell nobody <br>Bring your body, mama work the middle <br>Come and meet me at the afterparty <br>Bring your body, mama work the middle <br>Just a little don't tell nobody <br>Bring your body, mama work the middle <br>Just a little <br><br>Oh, I, oh, I <br>Oh, I, oh, I <br><br>After the little photo <br>I keep my eyes glued to you <br>Don't keep me waiting solo <br>I already ditched the crew <br>Baby don't say no, no, no, no <br>You know what I wanna do, wanna do for you, wanna do for you, yeah <br><br>Oh, yeah I'm three seconds from way to gone I know <br>And I'm two seconds from blowing up your phone <br>You're the one I wanna see when I get home <br>Don't leave me alone <br><br>Come and meet me at the afterparty <br>Bring your body, mama work the middle <br>Just a little don't tell nobody <br>Bring your body, mama work the middle <br>Come and meet me at the afterparty <br>Bring your body, mama work the middle <br>Just a little don't tell nobody <br>Bring your body, mama work the middle <br>Just a little <br><br>Oh, I, oh, I <br>Oh, I, oh, I <br>Come and meet me yeah <br><br>Come and meet me at the afterparty <br>Bring your body, mama work the middle <br>Just a little don't tell nobody <br>Bring your body, mama work the middle <br>Come and meet me at the afterparty <br>Bring your body, mama work the middle <br>Just a little don't tell nobody <br>Bring your body, mama work the middle <br>Just a little hey <br><br>Where it's just me and you girl <br>Oh, I, oh, I <br>Oh, I, oh, I <br>It's just me and you, girl]]></content><category term="Alex Aiono" label="Alex Aiono"/><category term="Work The Middle (Acoustic)" label="Work The Middle (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Miss_Mulatto/Response_Diss/</id><title>Miss Mulatto - Response Diss - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:44:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:44:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Miss_Mulatto/Response_Diss/" title="Miss Mulatto - Response Diss - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Latto let her know <br>Stupid <br>Now these folks talking bout they <br>Talking about they getting money <br>But ain't getting money Dummy <br>Talking bout they booking shows <br>But ain't booking shows Dummy <br><br>You wasn't talking about nothing <br>When I touched down in Houston <br>Cause you know better huh Stupid <br><br>First thing first <br>When you grew some balls <br>Stop playing you couldn't even pick up the phone <br>When I called <br>What I did in Houston <br>I dare you to pull that in the south <br>15 with 15 bodies <br>My flow nasty like her drawls <br><br>Lil thot thot <br>How both of yo parents in the crack pot <br>Pipe down <br>Cause we both know yee ain't what you rap about <br>You a joke <br>Tell yo mama come work at my store <br>Shoulda never quit her job <br>Just to bring a L home <br>I'm too old <br>My lil sister 14 and she on go <br>I swear to god when we see you <br>Either one of us gon wipe yo nose <br><br>I did a show in yo city and I left untouched <br>I'm the princess in the A and the H <br>Now what's up <br>You ain't gon buck huh <br>And let's not get on yo daddy <br>That man really gay <br>Cause yo mama a tranny <br>I already peeped huh <br>Why her voice so deep <br>Ima beat this girl to sleep <br>Have her counting white sheep <br><br>Ohh she talkin' hard <br>That lisp got her trippin huh <br>Ima put some money on her head like she strippin <br><br>I know yo daddy a roadie <br>Just tell me what he sniffin crackhead <br>Ima put a dent in her head <br>Like she peter griffin <br>Yeah she got me bent <br>Talkin' bout she that rich girl you's a lie <br>Girl they use yo rap game check <br>To pay the rent <br><br>Don't flex <br>You text my phone <br>Talkin bout Girl let's be friend's <br>Really feel bad for the H <br>This who yall let represent <br>By the way you really soft <br>You cried in the rap game house everyday Lil crybaby <br>And no I didn't sign <br>I keep everything I make <br>Tell the truth <br>Let's just be honest <br>They shoulda let you win that chain <br>Cause I know you tired of asking <br>Johnny Dane to borrow bling <br>This big ole facts <br>I'm finna call the facts <br>I would beat you up <br>But yo mama already does that <br><br>She want beef it's a plate <br>Call me ugly Issa hate <br>And my heart might pump kool aid <br>Cause sweet girls like you get ate <br>You get booked <br>When promoters can't afford me <br>Ran this girl up out her city <br>Like I did extortion <br>Stomp her out and put her on a shoe like Jordan <br>I just killed this baby <br>Like she did her abortion <br><br>Ohh no you didn't <br>Yeah y'all know who I be <br>Folks get hard on twitter <br>But can't pick up the phone <br>Really run my city fa real <br>laughs <br>The real princess dat way <br>Ahh <br>You really look up to me though <br>Tell the truth yeah <br>I can be yo mama lil girl <br>Stop playing with me <br>I ain't even finna call my daddy on yo daddy <br>And I run the A <br>All the way to the H <br>And yo mama can get it too <br>And I run the A <br>All the way to the H <br>ya lil sister, ya lil brother <br>Goofy <br>Put a cape on it <br>I bet they be SUPA mad]]></content><category term="Miss Mulatto" label="Miss Mulatto"/><category term="Response Diss" label="Response Diss"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chris_Jeday/Ahora_Dice_Feat_J_Balvin_Ozuna__Arcangel/</id><title>Chris Jeday - Ahora Dice (Feat. J. Balvin, Ozuna &amp; Arcangel) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:45:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:45:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chris_Jeday/Ahora_Dice_Feat_J_Balvin_Ozuna__Arcangel/" title="Chris Jeday - Ahora Dice (Feat. J. Balvin, Ozuna &amp; Arcangel) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby <br>Chris Jeday Chris Jeday <br>Austin baby <br>J Balvin man <br>Ozuna baby, Ozuna <br><br>No quiere saber na' de mi <br>Ay dime que fue lo que yo hice mal <br>Te pusieron en contra de mi <br>Al que fue no se lo voy a perdonar <br><br>Ahora dice que no me conoce, no no no no no <br>Y si me ha visto se supone que en el pasado fue <br>Yo si me acuerdo como lo haciamos <br>Como en la cama nos matabamos Let go, come on <br><br>Ahora dice que no me conoce, no no no no no <br>Y si me ha visto se supone que en el pasado fue <br>Yo si me acuerdo como lo haciamos <br>Como en la cama nos matabamos <br><br>Se que te pasas negando, todo lo que tu y yo haciamos <br>Queda en tu mente grabado todas las veces que nos desvestiamos <br>Ahora me paso pensando, como tu puedes vivir asi <br>Diciendo que no sabes lo que entre sabanas tu te entregaba a mi <br><br>Solo yo, he podido llegarle <br>Tu cuerpo sabe elevarse <br>Y cuando tus piernas temblaban <br>No decia nada ya no <br><br>Dialogando con el dinero <br>No quiero interrupciones <br>Esa es la prioridad <br>Bastante lista de opciones <br><br>Estoy con la colombiana que sepa manana y la copa no llega a Paris <br>Llamate al ruso que baje los kilos de oro que llegan a la calle de Brasil <br><br>Solo yo he podido llegarle <br>Tu cuerpo sabe, elevarse <br>Y cuando tus piernas temblaban <br>No decia nada, nada no no <br><br>Ahora dice que no me conoce, no no no no no <br>Y si me ha visto se supone que en el pasado fue <br>Yo si me acuerdo como lo haciamos <br>Como en la cama nos matabamos <br><br>Y ahora dice que no me conoce, no no no no no <br>Y si me ha visto se supone, que en el pasado fue <br>Yo si me acuerdo como lo, haciamos <br>Cuando en la cama nos matabamos J Balvin man <br><br>Por mas que me niegues a mi, no puedes escaparte <br>Si era tu luz de mi sombra y me seguias a todas partes <br>Nos lograron separar, tu no quisiste escuchar <br>Fue mas importante que dijo la gente, que a donde podiamos llegar <br><br>En el mundo de mi estan hablando <br>Diciendo mil cosas <br>Que me ven por aqui, que me ven por alla <br>Por mi vida famosa <br><br>Tu me conoces de anos atras, sabes como es la cosa <br>Tu sabes que yo soy real <br>Te lo dije una vez <br><br>Y se que nuestro amor es periodico de ayer <br>Que tu no lo quieres leer, que ni por la calle tu me quieres ver <br>Si sales de party me escuchas a mi, siempre te preguntan por mi baby <br>Dime que se siente ser el fantasma que te atormenta a ti <br><br>Dime que paso mami, todo iba normal <br>Te hablaron de mi, te dejaste llevar <br>Tu cuerpo me estaba empezando a amar <br>Y por culpa de la gente, ahora te toca olvidar <br><br>Yo se que eres infeliz, pero te pasas mintiendo <br>Fingiendo que eres feliz, mami yo no te entiendo <br>Ahora el te pone a llorar, tambien te pone a sufrir <br>Mientras yo te ponia a viajar, yo linda te hacia lucir <br><br>Solo yo he podido llegarle <br>Tu cuerpo sabe elevarse <br>Y cuando tus piernas temblaban <br>No me decia nada nada no no <br><br>Ahora dice que no me conoce, no no no no no <br>Y si me ha visto se supone que en el pasado fue <br>Yo si me acuerdo como lo haciamos <br>Como en la cama nos matabamos <br><br>Y ahora dice que no me conoce, no no no no no <br>Y si me ha visto se supone que en el pasado fue <br>Yo si me acuerdo como lo haciamos <br>Como en la cama nos matabamos <br><br>J Balvin man <br>Ozuna <br>Ozuna man <br>Arca <br>Ozuna <br>Arca man <br>Austin baby <br>Asi es como es <br>Chris Jeday <br><br>Ahora dice <br>Ahora dice]]></content><category term="Chris Jeday" label="Chris Jeday"/><category term="Ahora Dice (Feat. J. Balvin, Ozuna &amp; Arcangel)" label="Ahora Dice (Feat. J. Balvin, Ozuna &amp; Arcangel)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/갓플로우Gatt_Flow/사랑하는_너에게_Feat_봄날/</id><title>갓플로우(Gatt Flow) - 사랑하는 너에게 (Feat. 봄날) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:45:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:45:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%93%ED%94%8C%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B0Gatt_Flow/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%84%88%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_Feat_%EB%B4%84%EB%82%A0/" title="갓플로우(Gatt Flow) - 사랑하는 너에게 (Feat. 봄날) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너의 그 눈빛에 <br>난 점점 더 빠져들어 가 <br>너의 그 입술을 <br>난 자꾸만 쳐다보게 돼 <br>매일 아침을 깨우는 <br>너의 목소리 <br>일어나자마자 <br>웃게 만드는 나의 알람 <br>누구보다 많았던 잠도 <br>너로 인해 많이 줄어든 것 같아 <br>참 신기한 일이지 사랑이란 게 <br>너는 강요한 적 없는데 <br>나 변해가는 게 <br>나름 괜찮은 거 같아 내겐 매일이 <br>마치 꿈꾸는 거 같아 매일 매일이 <br>니가 날 보며 <br>환하게 웃어줄 땐 <br>내 입꼬리도 거울 보듯 <br>같이 따라가 <br>힘이 들고 지친 기분은 <br>너의 손이 나와 포개지면 <br>한 순간에 달아나 <br>도대체 날 어떻게 만든 거야 <br>마치 영화 속의 <br>주인공이 된 것 같이 <br>모든 게 아름다워 보여 <br>관객은 없어도 돼 <br>내가 충분하게 줄게 너의 로열티 <br>너의 그 눈빛에 <br>난 점점 더 빠져들어 가 <br>너의 그 입술을 <br>난 자꾸만 쳐다보게 돼 <br>하루가 지나면 점점 <br>처음보다는 무덤덤해 <br>질 줄 알았던 내 걱정 <br>보통의 연애는 무작정 사랑하다 <br>식어가는 일이라는 <br>일반적인 걱정 <br>Sweet 하고 Deep 하게 <br>내 맘을 흔드는 너 <br>잠깐 쉿 하고 하던 일은 Skip 해 <br>이 멜로디에 담긴 <br>내 기분이 또 채워줄게 <br>전혀 없게 네게 빈틈이 <br>어서 왔으면 해 <br>따뜻하고 긴 봄이 <br>포개졌으면 해 <br>부드러운 너의 손이 <br>나의 손과 마주한 채 <br>경치 좋은 어딘가를 <br>여유롭게 거닐곤 해 <br>너를 곁에 두고 걸을 땐 <br>니가 아닌 모든 것엔 무감각 <br>걸음은 당당 <br>드라마 주인공이 된 듯 <br>시선을 받아 <br>너로 인해 가능한 <br>이 모든 일에 난 감사해 <br>너의 그 눈빛에 <br>난 점점 더 빠져들어 가 <br>너의 그 입술을 <br>난 자꾸만 쳐다보게 돼 <br>널 보고 있을 땐 <br>시간이 멈춰 버린 것 같아 <br>니가 쳐다볼 때면 <br>심장이 내게 아닌 것 같아 <br>널 보고 있을 땐 <br>시간이 멈춰 버린 것 같아 <br>니가 쳐다볼 때면 <br>심장이 내게 아닌 것 같아 <br>사랑한다는 게 <br>만만치 않아 <br>잠깐 쉬어야지 <br>하는 찰나에 <br>내게 확 들어와버린 너 <br>사람 맘이란 게 <br>변하지 않을 것 같다가도 <br>어느 순간 계절처럼 <br>다 변해버리네 <br>가벼운 걸음걸이 <br>너를 만나러 갈 때면 <br>모두 그런 거지 사랑한다는 일 <br>지금 순간의 행복 <br>한 순간으로만 남지 않길 <br>너의 그 눈빛에 <br>난 점점 더 빠져들어 가 <br>너의 그 입술을 <br>난 자꾸만 쳐다보게 돼 <br>]]></content><category term="갓플로우(Gatt Flow)" label="갓플로우(Gatt Flow)"/><category term="사랑하는 너에게 (Feat. 봄날)" label="사랑하는 너에게 (Feat. 봄날)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루크/다시_사랑하지_않아/</id><title>루크 - 다시 사랑하지 않아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:45:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:45:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%ED%81%AC/%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%98%EC%A7%80_%EC%95%8A%EC%95%84/" title="루크 - 다시 사랑하지 않아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑하지 않을래 <br>마음을 주는 일도 <br>닳아지고 없어지는 일도 <br>이젠 너무 지쳐 싫어 <br>이제 너를 끝으로 <br>내게 어떤 누구도 <br>들어올 수 없도록 <br>굳게 닫아두고 곁에 아무도 <br>오지 못하게 막아 서서 <br>다신 내 맘 다치지 않게 <br>다시 사랑하지 않아 <br>그 누구도 원치 않아 <br>혼자도 나쁘지 않아 <br>또 다른 누군가 <br>다치게 하는 일도 <br>더는 못하겠어 <br>사람에게 닫힌 맘 <br>사랑에게 다친 맘 <br>이제 일어날 힘도 없어 <br>닫아두고 곁에 아무도 <br>오지 못하게 막아 서서 <br>다신 내 맘 다치지 않게 <br>오 다시 사랑하지 않아 <br>그 누구도 원치 않아 <br>혼자도 나쁘지 않아 <br>또 다른 누군가 <br>다치게 하는 일도 <br>더는 못하겠어 <br>]]></content><category term="루크" label="루크"/><category term="다시 사랑하지 않아" label="다시 사랑하지 않아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanilla_Mousse/Bomijota/</id><title>Vanilla Mousse - Bomijota - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:45:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:45:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanilla_Mousse/Bomijota/" title="Vanilla Mousse - Bomijota - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[상큼한 꽃향기에 <br>흰 눈이 녹아가고 <br>따뜻한 봄이 오네요 <br>이런 내 맘 알까 <br>설레는 내 맘 알까 <br>아무도 모르게 살며시 감춰요 <br>진한 핑크 빛 진달래 <br>노랗게 물든 민들레 <br>홀씨 되어 너의 곁에 <br>살며시 날아 가볼까 <br>니가 좋아 너무 좋아 <br>봄을 닮은 니가 좋은걸 <br>어쩜 좋아 니가 좋아 <br>붉게 물든 내 맘 for you <br>거리엔 모두 연인 손잡고 <br>팔짱끼고 서로를 보며 웃네요 <br>이런 내 맘 알까 <br>부러운 내 맘 알까 <br>아무도 모르게 살며시 감춰요 <br>난 봄이 좋다 봄이 좋아 <br>널 닮은 봄이 너무 좋다 <br>따사로운 향기로운 <br>이 봄이 난 너무 좋다 <br>니가 좋아 너무 좋아 <br>봄을 닮은 니가 좋은걸 <br>어쩜 좋아 니가 좋아 <br>붉게 물든 내 맘 for you <br>붉게 물든 내 맘 for you <br>]]></content><category term="Vanilla Mousse" label="Vanilla Mousse"/><category term="Bomijota" label="Bomijota"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노리플라이_no_reply/여정/</id><title>노리플라이 (no reply) - 여정 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:45:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:45:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EB%A6%AC%ED%94%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4_no_reply/%EC%97%AC%EC%A0%95/" title="노리플라이 (no reply) - 여정 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이토록 새파란 하늘에 <br>이토록 그리움만 <br>남아있는 듯해 <br>멀어지는 것들과 <br>붙들고 있던 것 <br>저만치 흘러가는 <br>강물에 떠밀려 간다 <br>영원할 것 같던 <br>그리운 마음들 모두 <br>수많은 바램들 모두 <br>끝없이 흘러 <br>아무리 애를 써봐도 <br>벗어날 수 없던 너의 영혼 <br>설레는 밤 <br>간절했던 꿈 <br>모두 두고 간다 <br>남아있는 미련과 <br>목마른 감정들 <br>봄 날의 웅성임도 <br>파도에 부서져 간다 <br>영원할 것 같던 <br>그리운 마음들 모두 <br>수많은 바램들 모두 <br>끝없이 흘러 <br>아무리 애를 써봐도 <br>벗어날 수 없던 너의 영혼 <br>별이 지던 <br>잠들지 않는 밤 <br>말 없는 외침들 <br>난 눈을 감는다 <br>끝이 없는 어둠이 나의 앞에 <br>나의 눈으론 가늠할 수 없는 <br>좁은 이 길 보이지 않는 사랑 <br>무엇보다 깊은 <br>내게 주어진 끝 없는 질문에 <br>그저 걷는다 <br>사랑했던 모든 순간 <br>아득한 물결 너머로 <br>멀어져 간다 <br>돌아보면 멈출까 봐 <br>더 멀리 가야만 해 <br>날 부르는 그 곳으로 <br>]]></content><category term="노리플라이 (no reply)" label="노리플라이 (no reply)"/><category term="여정" label="여정"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노리플라이_no_reply/우리들/</id><title>노리플라이 (no reply) - 우리들 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:45:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:45:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EB%A6%AC%ED%94%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4_no_reply/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%93%A4/" title="노리플라이 (no reply) - 우리들 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[똑같은 하루 속에 <br>텅 빈 마음을 숨겨둔 채 <br>시시한 농담에 웃어대며 그렇게 <br>긴 하루 지나가고 <br>엉킨 마음을 끌어안고 <br>난 불을 끈 채로 <br>오늘도 내 마음은 <br>흘러가는 꿈이여 <br>여전히 내겐 <br>다 어려운 일인걸 <br>흘러가는 꿈 어디쯤엔가 <br>아파했던 난 널 만났고 <br>서로의 꿈에 기대어 있던 <br>철 없던 우리들 <br>또 이렇게 그 자리 <br>아파했던 시간 <br>막연했던 미래 <br>그 모든 게 <br>끝나긴 하는 걸까 <br>여전히 내겐 <br>어려운 일인걸 <br>흘러가는 꿈 어디쯤엔가 <br>아파했던 난 널 만났고 <br>서로의 꿈에 기대어 있던 <br>나약한 우리들 <br>또 이렇게 그 자리 <br>어디로 가야 할까 <br>알 수 없는 건 그대론데 <br>난 무얼 찾기에 <br>오늘도 널 부를까 <br>이런 날 아는지 <br>]]></content><category term="노리플라이 (no reply)" label="노리플라이 (no reply)"/><category term="우리들" label="우리들"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노리플라이_no_reply/아름다운_시절/</id><title>노리플라이 (no reply) - 아름다운 시절 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:45:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:45:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EB%A6%AC%ED%94%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4_no_reply/%EC%95%84%EB%A6%84%EB%8B%A4%EC%9A%B4_%EC%8B%9C%EC%A0%88/" title="노리플라이 (no reply) - 아름다운 시절 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무것도 <br>보이지 않는 것 같다 느낄 때 <br>빛을 잃은 날들 <br>설레임도 어느새 <br>그냥 그 자리에 머문 듯 <br>외로이 걸을 때 <br>한번 더 서로를 <br>바라봐 준다면 <br>Come on come on <br>다시 사라지지 않게 <br>아름다운 날들 이 잔에 가득 채워 <br>Come on come on <br>다시 쏟아지지 않게 <br>견뎌내 왔잖아 <br>다시 꿈을 꾸자 <br>다시 노래하자 <br>오 어느새 희망은 조금씩 <br>읽다가 만 책처럼 <br>낯설게 느껴져 <br>난 그래도 지금 <br>서로를 바라볼 수 있다는 것 <br>그것 만으로도 빛나고 있음을 <br>Come on come on <br>다시 사라지지 않게 <br>아름다운 날들 <br>이 잔에 가득 채워 <br>Come on come on <br>다시 쏟아지지 않게 <br>견뎌내 왔잖아 <br>다시 꿈을 꾸자 다시 노래하자 <br>Come on come on <br>다시 사라지지 않게 <br>Come on come on <br>다시 흔들리지 않게 <br>Come on come on come on <br>긴긴 밤을 버텨왔나요 <br>Come on come on come on <br>그만큼 자라났죠 그댄 지금도 충분해 <br>그걸로 충분해 <br>Come on come on <br>다시 사라지지 않게 <br>아름다운 날들 이 잔에 가득 채워 <br>Come on come on <br>다시 쏟아지지 않게 <br>견뎌내 왔잖아 <br>다시 꿈을 꾸자 다시 노래하자 <br>아무것도 보이지 <br>않는 것 같다 느낄 때 <br>설레임도 어느새 점점 <br>무뎌져 간다 해도 <br>아름다운 시절 <br>Come on come on come on <br>오늘을 기억해 <br>Come on come on come on <br>]]></content><category term="노리플라이 (no reply)" label="노리플라이 (no reply)"/><category term="아름다운 시절" label="아름다운 시절"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노리플라이_no_reply/별/</id><title>노리플라이 (no reply) - 별 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:45:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:45:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EB%A6%AC%ED%94%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4_no_reply/%EB%B3%84/" title="노리플라이 (no reply) - 별 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[반짝이는 화려한 도시의 밤 <br>아침이면 사라질 불빛들 <br>쉴 곳 없는 사람들 모두 떠나고 <br>머리 위로 길을 밝혀준 별들은 <br>그 어디에 <br>캄캄한 하늘을 바라본다 <br>쏟아지는 별 수많은 무리들 <br>영원 같은 밤 하늘이 <br>꺼질듯한 어둠 넘어 타오르고 <br>쏟아지는 마음 날 향한 그대의 별 <br>넌 나의 꿈만을 이루려 했기에 <br>아무것도 볼 수가 없었어 <br>다시 우린 만나게 될 수 있을까 <br>넓은 세상 각자의 길을 걷다가 <br>그 언젠가 <br>긴 시간을 이해하게 될까 <br>쏟아지는 별 수많은 무리들 <br>영원 같은 밤 하늘이 <br>꺼질듯한 어둠 넘어 타오르고 <br>쏟아지는 마음 날 향한 그대의 별 <br>넌 나의 꿈만을 이루려 했기에 <br>아무것도 볼 수가 없었어 <br>쏟아지는 별 <br>쏟아지는 별들은 <br>닫혀있던 널 향한 <br>길을 알고 있을 텐데 <br>가리워진 빛 날 향한 그대의 별 <br>눈부신 세상에 익숙해졌는지 <br>아무것도 볼 수가 없었어 <br>끝없이 펼쳐진 오래된 꿈들을 <br>손 닿을 수 없는 먼 곳에 <br>쏟아지는 별 숨가쁜 세상에 서서 <br>캄캄한 하늘을 바라본다 <br>]]></content><category term="노리플라이 (no reply)" label="노리플라이 (no reply)"/><category term="별" label="별"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노리플라이_no_reply/곁에_있어/</id><title>노리플라이 (no reply) - 곁에 있어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:45:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:45:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EB%A6%AC%ED%94%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4_no_reply/%EA%B3%81%EC%97%90_%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4/" title="노리플라이 (no reply) - 곁에 있어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[무거운 맘을 붙잡고 <br>집 앞을 서성이다가 <br>또 다시 문을 등질 때 <br>희미한 불빛 익숙한 그림자 <br>고단한 세월에 작아져 버린 <br>내가 모든 것인 오 그대만이 <br>오 그대 오늘도 <br>텅 빈 식탁을 채우고 <br>멈춰버린 이야기에 슬퍼하나요 <br>수많은 사람들 <br>모두 날 떠나버려도 <br>그댄 항상 여기 있죠 내게 있죠 <br>내가 이제 그대 곁을 지켜줄게 <br>남루한 소매 끝자락 <br>적시던 고단한 날에 <br>힘겹게 문을 열곤 했던 나에게 <br>말없이 그저 날 안아준 <br>그 아름다운 날들 반짝이네 <br>오 그대 오늘도 <br>텅 빈 식탁을 채우고 <br>멈춰버린 이야기에 슬퍼하나요 <br>수많은 사람들 <br>모두 날 떠나버려도 <br>그댄 항상 여기 있죠 늘 내게 있죠 <br>내가 이제 그대 곁을 지켜줄게 <br>오 그대 오늘도 <br>여기 빈 식탁에 앉아 <br>행여 내가 아파 무너지지 않게 <br>두 손을 모으고 <br>나를 위해 기도하죠 <br>모두가 날 떠난 뒤에도 그댄 항상 <br>곁에 있죠 나를 위해 늘 살아왔죠 <br>이젠 내가 그대 곁을 늘 지켜줄게 <br>]]></content><category term="노리플라이 (no reply)" label="노리플라이 (no reply)"/><category term="곁에 있어" label="곁에 있어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노리플라이_no_reply/버스_정류장/</id><title>노리플라이 (no reply) - 버스 정류장 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:45:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:45:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EB%A6%AC%ED%94%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4_no_reply/%EB%B2%84%EC%8A%A4_%EC%A0%95%EB%A5%98%EC%9E%A5/" title="노리플라이 (no reply) - 버스 정류장 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[차가운 노을 짙어지고 <br>어느새 해가 지던 <br>텅 빈 그 정류장 <br>불빛은 아직 희미해도 <br>기억해 손 흔들던 모습이 <br>요즘 난 말이 없어졌어 <br>정류장에 기대어 <br>네 어깨에 턱을 괴고 <br>가만히 널 안고 있으면 <br>불안함도 희망도 <br>가득 태운 차들이 <br>위태롭게 우릴 스쳐가 <br>정류장에 기대어 <br>울먹이는 널 안고서 <br>젖어가는 내 어깨 넘어 <br>스쳐가는 사람들 <br>차가워진 거리에 <br>우린 점점 빛을 잃어가 <br>이제는 그 자리에 <br>아름답던 시절 우리 <br>너와 내가 기대왔던 날 <br>멀어져 간다 <br>점점 멀어져 간다 <br>]]></content><category term="노리플라이 (no reply)" label="노리플라이 (no reply)"/><category term="버스 정류장" label="버스 정류장"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노리플라이_no_reply/Reply/</id><title>노리플라이 (no reply) - Reply - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T17:45:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T17:45:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EB%A6%AC%ED%94%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4_no_reply/Reply/" title="노리플라이 (no reply) - Reply - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모든 게 끝을 알 수 없었고 <br>두 손 가득 잡힐 듯 멀어지고 <br>어디가 내가 가야 할 길인지 <br>쉬어갈 곳 없는 밤 <br>꿈은 점점 멀어져 <br>내 모든 게 흩어지고 있어 <br>앞을 볼 수 없어서 <br>끝내 주저 앉던 그 순간에 <br>노랫소리 <br>나를 일으켜준 <br>그 노래에 <br>대답 할게 이젠 <br>수없이 많은 날은 스쳐가고 <br>멈춰버린 발자국 <br>헤매일 것만 같은 나 <br>내 모든 게 흩어지고 있어 <br>앞을 볼 수 없어서 <br>끝내 주저 앉던 그 순간에 <br>노랫소리 <br>나를 일으켜준 <br>그 노래에 <br>대답할게 이젠 <br>캄캄한 길을 밝혀 주었던 <br>또다시 일어설 수 있었던 <br>그 노래 <br>그 노래 <br>모든 게 사라질 때까지 <br>희미한 빛이 되어 <br>흩어지겠지만 나 그래도 <br>노래 할게 이 노랠 부를게 <br>누군가의 <br>빛이 되길 이젠 <br>]]></content><category term="노리플라이 (no reply)" label="노리플라이 (no reply)"/><category term="Reply" label="Reply"/></entry></feed>