<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:49:21+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Korn/Next_In_Line/</id><title>Korn - Next In Line - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:24:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:24:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Korn/Next_In_Line/" title="Korn - Next In Line - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It hurts to breathe but I don't care The weight of the world, the thoughts I couldn't bear The city sleeps, I'm making plans The less you know, the better understand Then I look and see that place It fools me every time Digging deeper pulls me under Am I wasting time, or next in line? I pace and fret, my blood, it burns The reason we know but still we never learn The clocks stand still, my legs grow weak It says it's done, I beg it not to speak Then I look and see that place It fools me every time Digging deeper pulls me under Am I wasting time, or next in line? First you're gonna get your memory, you're a fucking fray Never wanna, never gonna end up in that display Then I look and see that place It fools me every time Digging deeper pulls me under Am I wasting time, or next in line? Then I look and see that place It fools me every time Digging deeper pulls me under Am I wasting time, or next in line?]]></content><category term="Korn" label="Korn"/><category term="Next In Line" label="Next In Line"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Korn/When_Youre_Not_There/</id><title>Korn - When You`re Not There - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:24:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:24:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Korn/When_Youre_Not_There/" title="Korn - When You`re Not There - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's a pretty thing there to hold your head It's like the sanity is hanging on a thread The flesh is cold and needs some nails And the look you give, it never fails I love the way you hurt me I love that you don't care My love is dark and twisted And I scream when you're not there It's the interesting way, it fills my brain [?] but never the same I love it when you're heavy and crack a smile The best is when you make it last a while I love the way you hurt me I love that you don't care My love is dark and twisted And I scream when you're not there Can't seem to get away This ghost I'll never find It haunts me 'til this day I can't get back my mind I love the way you hurt me I love that you don't care My love is dark and twisted And I scream when you're not there]]></content><category term="Korn" label="Korn"/><category term="When You`re Not There" label="When You`re Not There"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Korn/Die_Yet_Another_Night/</id><title>Korn - Die Yet Another Night - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:24:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:24:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Korn/Die_Yet_Another_Night/" title="Korn - Die Yet Another Night - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sick of all these things I tried Sick of all these lies (Nobody cares you're just a bad man Nobody wants you're a dead man) Wake me from my darkest dream Read me from my mind (Nobody cares you're just a bad man Nobody wants you're a dead man) No problem I've got time to kill (Nobody cares you're just a bad man Nobody wants you're a dead man) Slave everyone I've had my fill (Nobody cares you're just a bad man Nobody wants you're a dead man) Do what you say, do want you want to [x4] We rip upon the flesh and lift to see And looking on all the faces along the way The terror grips me closely and holds me tight And hope I get to Die yet another night Throw a wrench into my world Throw me in the fire (Nobody cares you're just a bad man Nobody wants you're a dead man) Death come over to me one time We should get much higher (Nobody cares you're just a bad man Nobody wants you're a dead man) No problem I've got time to kill (Nobody cares you're just a bad man Nobody wants you're a dead man) Slave everyone I've got my fill (Nobody cares you're just a bad man Nobody wants you're a dead man) Do what you say, do want you want to [x4] We rip upon the flesh and lift to see And looking on all the faces along the way The terror grips me closely and holds me tight And hope I get to Die yet another night Don't get close to me Safe for you All this suffering left to do Don't get close to me Safe for you All this suffering left to do All this suffering left to do All this suffering left to do We rip upon the flesh and lift to see And looking on all the faces along the way The terror grips me closely and holds me tight And hope I get to Die yet another night We rip upon the flesh and lift to see And looking on all the faces along the way The terror grips me closely and holds me tight And hope I get to Die yet another night]]></content><category term="Korn" label="Korn"/><category term="Die Yet Another Night" label="Die Yet Another Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Korn/Everything_Falls_Apart/</id><title>Korn - Everything Falls Apart - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:25:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:25:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Korn/Everything_Falls_Apart/" title="Korn - Everything Falls Apart - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Close your eyes, fall asleep! Broken promises that you never keep! Drift away tonight! Just drift away tonight! We used to dream, we used to laugh! No one could tell us that this would never last! This ain't a love song! I would never give you one! No more secrets, no more lies! No more feelings or surprise! No more whispered words or lullabies! Go fuck your lies! Everything, everything falls with us! Everything, everything always does! Everything, everything falls all apart! I've given up, it's all I could take! My hands are shaking, my body could break! I will be lonely now! Come on and take me out! I used to care, I used to try! But what's the use it always ends with goodbye! This ain't a love song! I'd never give you one! No more secrets, no more lies! No more feelings or surprise! No more whispered words or lullabies! Go fuck your lies! Everything, everything falls with us! Everything, everything always does! Everything, everything falls all apart! THERE IS NOTHING IN MY HEAD! (There is a voice in my head)... There is nothing, there's nothing! IN MY HEAD! Everything, everything falls with us! Everything, everything always does! Everything, everything falls all apart! [x2] All apart! [x2] These are voices in my head!...]]></content><category term="Korn" label="Korn"/><category term="Everything Falls Apart" label="Everything Falls Apart"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Korn/The_Hating/</id><title>Korn - The Hating - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:25:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:25:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Korn/The_Hating/" title="Korn - The Hating - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The hating, it's pulled inside of me They're trying to test my sanity It's in there waiting, it's all make believe And they're ripping the child within me Cheating the time that I have left My soul cause it's at the beginning Giving back all that I can give Controlling my mind that is disease Holding, my hate that is released Scolding the hand that keeps me fed That keeps me fed That keeps me fed That keeps me I feel it all come crashing down on me I feel alone and torn apart I wasted time to let it get to me An angry mouth with a broken heart Searching for something that is safe Hurting my pride that is detest Turning my anger towards your flesh Rotting, we're hoping ain't that bad Spilling the blood that's on the bed Scolding the hand that keeps me fed The hand that keeps me fed I feel it all come crashing down on me I feel alone and torn apart I wasted time to let it get to me An angry mouth with a broken heart The hating, it's pulled inside of me They're trying to test my sanity It's in you waiting, it's all make believe And they're ripping the child within me The hating, it's pulled inside of me They're trying to test my sanity It's in you waiting, it's all make believe And they're ripping the child within me No!]]></content><category term="Korn" label="Korn"/><category term="The Hating" label="The Hating"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Korn/Black_Is_The_Soul/</id><title>Korn - Black Is The Soul - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:25:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:25:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Korn/Black_Is_The_Soul/" title="Korn - Black Is The Soul - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[As it all falls down, you will walk away Or you will stand my ground and accept my faith I'm made of faceless cries, that twists my every dream And almost every night I hear the demon sing Why are we going on this way? Why do we play these games in vain? Nothing's gonna break it down and build us back again So why do go back that could leave this way? Black is the soul that's led astray You're leading me to places I can never follow Happiness is found in darkest ways And as I searched around, I've made nothing but mistakes I'm made of faceless cries, that twists my every dream And almost every night I hear the demon sing Why are we going on this way? Why do we play these games in vain? Nothing's gonna break it down and build us back again So why do go back that could leave this way? Black is the soul that's led astray You're leading me to places I can never follow And when you scream you push me so much further and And when I leave, I always would walk back again And when you cry the tears are cleansing bitterness I'm out of time, I'm slowly dying give me back my LIFE! Just give me back my life [x4] Why are we going on this way? Why do we play this game Nothing's gonna break it down and build us back again So why do go back that could leave this way? Black is the soul that's led astray You're leading me to places I can never follow As it all falls down, you will walk away Or you will stand my ground, there's nothing left to say]]></content><category term="Korn" label="Korn"/><category term="Black Is The Soul" label="Black Is The Soul"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/무지개오락실/어른이/</id><title>무지개오락실 - 어른이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:25:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:25:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B4%EC%A7%80%EA%B0%9C%EC%98%A4%EB%9D%BD%EC%8B%A4/%EC%96%B4%EB%A5%B8%EC%9D%B4/" title="무지개오락실 - 어른이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[미안하단 너의 말 굳이 듣고파서 <br>마음에 없어도 돼 <br>입으로 나오기만 해 <br>땡깡피는 나는 <br>어른인 척 하는 어른이 <br>그래서 떠난거니 <br>계속 연락 안받니 <br>미안하다고 <br>니 말은 다 맞고 내 말은 다 틀려 <br>인정할게 할테니 <br>오빠 그만 전화 끊어 <br>뚝 뚝 끊어진 전화기 속 액정 <br>예의없는 걸로 치면 너는 백점 <br>황당해서 폰만 간만히 바라보는 <br>내 표정은 누가 봐도 개 쩖 <br>이래서 어린애랑 <br>연애하면 안된다며 <br>친구들 앞에서 치는 손사래 <br>집에 가는 길 불 꺼진 <br>가게 유리창에 비친 건 <br>익숙치 않은 내 모습 혼자네 <br>너무했나 내가 <br>아냐 잘못된 걸 말해준 건데 <br>지가 뭔데 괜히 나에게 화를 내 <br>혼자 씩씩 거리다가도 내일이면 <br>분명 후회할 걸 뻔히 아는데 <br>미안하단 너의 말 굳이 듣고파서 <br>마음에 없어도 돼 <br>입으로 나오기만 해 <br>땡깡피는 나는 <br>어른인 척 하는 어른이 <br>그래서 떠난거니 <br>계속 연락 안받니 <br>사실 문제가 발생하거나 <br>싸움이 벌어지면 <br>늘 말을 많이 하는 것은 <br>내 쪽이었지 <br>꼴에 난 랩퍼에다가 <br>또 국문학과잖아 <br>아주 신나게 따졌지 <br>너를 몰아 세우면서 <br>아마 그때 니가 먼저 <br>사과를 했던 건 <br>더 잘못해서가 아니라 <br>우리 관계를 <br>더 생각해서였단 걸 몰랐어 <br>멍청하게 굴다가 혼자 남겨져서 <br>유치한 방식으로 <br>잘잘못을 따지고 <br>어른인 척 굴던 것들이 <br>창피하게 느껴지고 <br>지금은 삭제목록 속 <br>니 얼굴들을 엄지로 쓰다듬으며 <br>후회하고 있지 모든 걸 <br>조금 더 괜찮은 내가 될게 <br>너에게 불편한 인간으로 남는 게 <br>너무 싫어 일단 너 일 끝나고 나서 <br>정리해서 다시 말할게 <br>그때는 받어 <br>미안하단 너의 말 굳이 듣고파서 <br>마음에 없어도 돼 <br>입으로 나오기만 해 <br>땡깡피는 나는 <br>어른인척 하는 어른이 <br>그래서 떠난거니 <br>계속 연락 안받니 <br>난 그냥 어른이고 싶은 <br>어린이었지 <br>난 그냥 어른이고 싶은 <br>어린이었지 <br>니가 잘못한 거니까 <br>빨리빨리 사과해 <br>너무 잘난 나머지 <br>이렇게 혼자 남았네 <br>난 그냥 어른이고 싶은 어린이 <br>난 그냥 어른이고 싶은 어린이 <br>애들은 제대로된 어른이 필요해 <br>넌 지금 어디니 넌 지금 어디니 <br>미안하단 너의 말 굳이 듣고파서 <br>마음에 없어도 돼 <br>입으로 나오기만 해 <br>땡깡피는 나는 <br>어른인척 하는 어른이 <br>그래서 떠난거니 <br>계속 연락 안받니 <br>]]></content><category term="무지개오락실" label="무지개오락실"/><category term="어른이" label="어른이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인더루프_In_The_Roof/가끔/</id><title>인더루프_In_The_Roof - 가끔 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:27:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:27:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EB%8D%94%EB%A3%A8%ED%94%84_In_The_Roof/%EA%B0%80%EB%81%94/" title="인더루프_In_The_Roof - 가끔 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가끔 이 길을 걸으면 <br>너의 기억이 떠올라 <br>그냥 별일 없이 지내는지 <br>금세 변한 날씨에 <br>넣어놨던 겉옷을 꺼내고 <br>다시 돌아올 이 계절과 <br>달리 거기 없을 너 <br>아무렇지 않은 듯 <br>하루하루 지나는 날 속에 <br>유난히 별들이 <br>빛나는 밤이 오면 <br>맘이 아려와 <br>가끔 이 길을 걸으면 <br>너의 기억이 떠올라 <br>그냥 별일 없이 지내는지 <br>뒤돌아선 그 날밤 <br>너의 볼에 흐르던 눈물을 <br>되돌릴 수 있을 거라 <br>믿었던 어리석은 나 <br>낯설어진 새벽의 공기 <br>이제는 편하게 날 감싸도 <br>이상해 점점 <br>너의 마지막 표정은 <br>선명해져와 <br>다시 돌아갈 수 <br>있을 거라고 생각 했던 <br>우리 이야기를 <br>슬픈 소설 속 변하지 <br>않을 엔딩으로 남겨둬 <br>가끔 이 길을 걸으면 <br>너의 기억이 떠올라 <br>그냥 별일 없이만 지내줘 <br>]]></content><category term="인더루프 (In The Roof)" label="인더루프 (In The Roof)"/><category term="가끔" label="가끔"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/계피/스르르_Inst/</id><title>계피 - 스르르 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:27:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:27:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%84%ED%94%BC/%EC%8A%A4%EB%A5%B4%EB%A5%B4_Inst/" title="계피 - 스르르 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언제쯤 끝이 날 수 있을까 <br>길고 긴 눈물 속의 상처가 <br>야속하게 또 흐르네 밤 하늘에 <br>널 그리다 또 지우다 스르르 <br>추워진 길거리를 걸으면 <br>따스했던 그 날이 <br>스며들어 안겨와 <br>그대 그 뒷모습이 이렇게 아파 <br>멀어져 떠나간 <br>그대 보이지 않아 허전하다 <br>바람에 날려오던 향기가 <br>마치 너일 것 같아 <br>그대 그 뒷모습이 이렇게 아파 <br>멀어져 떠난 떠난 그렇게 떠난 <br>그대 보이지 않아 허전하다 <br>잠이 들어 스르르 <br>]]></content><category term="계피" label="계피"/><category term="스르르 (Inst.)" label="스르르 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/계피/스르르/</id><title>계피 - 스르르 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:27:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:27:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%84%ED%94%BC/%EC%8A%A4%EB%A5%B4%EB%A5%B4/" title="계피 - 스르르 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언제쯤 끝이 날 수 있을까 <br>길고 긴 눈물 속의 상처가 <br>야속하게 또 흐르네 밤 하늘에 <br>널 그리다 또 지우다 스르르 <br>추워진 길거리를 걸으면 <br>따스했던 그 날이 <br>스며들어 안겨와 <br>그대 그 뒷모습이 이렇게 아파 <br>멀어져 떠나간 <br>그대 보이지 않아 허전하다 <br>바람에 날려오던 향기가 <br>마치 너일 것 같아 <br>그대 그 뒷모습이 이렇게 아파 <br>멀어져 떠난 떠난 그렇게 떠난 <br>그대 보이지 않아 허전하다 <br>잠이 들어 스르르 <br>]]></content><category term="계피" label="계피"/><category term="스르르" label="스르르"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/심은경/엔딩송/</id><title>심은경 - 엔딩송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:28:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:28:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%AC%EC%9D%80%EA%B2%BD/%EC%97%94%EB%94%A9%EC%86%A1/" title="심은경 - 엔딩송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[삼거리 슈퍼지나 <br>기울어진 전봇대 <br>유모차 누운 <br>아기 부러워 <br>멋진 모자 새신발에 <br>고양이도 키우고 <br>커다란 비행기 <br>타고 싶어 <br>사람들은 젊을때 <br>고생 좀 하라지만 <br>나는 맛있는 게 <br>더 먹고 싶어 <br>어쩌면 나는 커서 <br>내가 된 걸까 <br>아직은 알 수가 없는 <br>내일과 모레 <br>걷다보면 혼자는 심심해 <br>우리 둘이 천천히 <br>가고 싶은 <br>그곳이 어디라도 <br>나는 너와 함께 <br>걸어 갈꺼야 <br>영화는 재밌게 <br>보셨나요 <br>조심히 살펴가세요 <br>가방 지갑 <br>핸드폰 잘 챙기고 <br>우리 다음에 <br>또 다시 만나요 <br>오늘도 지각이다 <br>꼬불꼬불 등굣길 <br>골목엔 땡땡무늬 할머니 <br>떡볶이 노래방 <br>피씨방 친구집 <br>새로운 곳에도 <br>가고 싶어 <br>아빠는 인생에 <br>보충 수업 <br>없다 하지만 <br>나는 집에가서 <br>눕고만 싶어 <br>어쩌면 나는 커서 <br>내가 된걸까 <br>아직은 알 수가 없는 <br>내일과 모레 <br>걷다 보면 <br>혼자는 외로워 <br>우리 둘이 천천히 <br>가고 싶은 <br>그때엔 언제라도 <br>우린 씩씩하게 <br>걸어갈꺼야 <br>영화는 재밌게 <br>보셨나요 <br>조심히 돌아가세요 <br>콜라 팝콘 <br>주차권 잘 챙기고 <br>우리 다음에 <br>또 다시 만나요 <br>삼거리 슈퍼지나 <br>기울어진 전봇대 <br>유모차 누운 <br>아기 부러워 <br>멋진 모자 새신발에 <br>고양이도 키우고 <br>커다란 비행기 <br>타고 싶어 <br>사람들은 젊을때 <br>고생 좀 하라지만 <br>나는 맛있는 게 <br>더 먹고 싶어 <br>어쩌면 나는 커서 <br>내가 된 걸까 <br>아직은 알 수가 없는 <br>내일과 모레 <br>걷다보면 혼자는 심심해 <br>우리 둘이 천천히 <br>가고 싶은 <br>그곳이 어디라도 <br>나는 너와 함께 <br>걸어 갈꺼야 <br>영화는 재밌게 <br>보셨나요 <br>조심히 살펴가세요 <br>가방 지갑 <br>핸드폰 잘 챙기고 <br>우리 다음에 <br>또 다시 만나요 <br>]]></content><category term="심은경" label="심은경"/><category term="엔딩송" label="엔딩송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/어쿠루브/If_U_love_me_Inst/</id><title>어쿠루브 - If U love me (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:29:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:29:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%B4%EC%BF%A0%EB%A3%A8%EB%B8%8C/If_U_love_me_Inst/" title="어쿠루브 - If U love me (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If U love me <br>너의 싱그러운 미소를 닮은 <br>저 아침 햇살과 함께 <br>잠에서 깨어 <br>꿈같은 매일을 너와 함께해 <br>Love U <br>이 말로는 널 향한 내 맘을 <br>다 표현할 수가 없어 <br>I love you forever forever <br>첨봤을 때부터 느꼈어 <br>바라고 바라던 사람이었어 <br>나도 몰래 빠져들어가 <br>이젠 주체할수도 없는걸 <br>너도 알고 있잖아 <br>서로 느끼고 있잖아 <br>I just wanna fallin love with you <br>더는 숨길 수 없는걸 <br>감추려 하지마 <br>내 맘과 같다면 <br>Babe <br>If U love me <br>너의 싱그러운 미소를 닮은 <br>저 아침 햇살과 함께 <br>잠에서 깨어 <br>꿈같은 매일을 너와 함께해 <br>Love U <br>이 말로는 널 향한 내 맘을 <br>다 표현할 수가 없어 <br>I love you forever forever <br>첨봤을 때는 난 몰랐어 <br>내가 원하던 사람이 너일지 <br>널 만날때마다 느꼈어 <br>이젠 솔직히 말할게 <br>Oh Yeah <br>너만 생각하는 걸 <br>매일 상상하게 되는 걸 <br>I just wanna fallin love <br>with you ma baby <br>숨길 수도 없어 <br>감당할 수 없어 <br>이젠 너에게 말할게 <br>If U love me <br>너의 싱그러운 미소를 닮은 <br>저 아침 햇살과 함께 <br>잠에서 깨어 <br>꿈같은 매일을 너와 함께해 <br>Love U <br>이 말로는 널 향한 내 맘을 <br>다 표현할 수가 없어 <br>I love you forever forever <br>Spend my life time with U <br>I wanna spend my life time loving U <br>너와 함께 해 매일이 더 소중해 <br>너와 함께 있어서 내 삶이 변해 <br>]]></content><category term="어쿠루브" label="어쿠루브"/><category term="If U love me (Inst.)" label="If U love me (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/어쿠루브/If_U_love_me_Feat_동경/</id><title>어쿠루브 - If U love me (Feat. 동경) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:29:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:29:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%B4%EC%BF%A0%EB%A3%A8%EB%B8%8C/If_U_love_me_Feat_%EB%8F%99%EA%B2%BD/" title="어쿠루브 - If U love me (Feat. 동경) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If U love me <br>너의 싱그러운 미소를 닮은 <br>저 아침 햇살과 함께 <br>잠에서 깨어 <br>꿈같은 매일을 너와 함께해 <br>Love U <br>이 말로는 널 향한 내 맘을 <br>다 표현할 수가 없어 <br>I love you forever forever <br>첨봤을 때부터 느꼈어 <br>바라고 바라던 사람이었어 <br>나도 몰래 빠져들어가 <br>이젠 주체할수도 없는걸 <br>너도 알고 있잖아 <br>서로 느끼고 있잖아 <br>I just wanna fallin love with you <br>더는 숨길 수 없는걸 <br>감추려 하지마 <br>내 맘과 같다면 <br>Babe <br>If U love me <br>너의 싱그러운 미소를 닮은 <br>저 아침 햇살과 함께 <br>잠에서 깨어 <br>꿈같은 매일을 너와 함께해 <br>Love U <br>이 말로는 널 향한 내 맘을 <br>다 표현할 수가 없어 <br>I love you forever forever <br>첨봤을 때는 난 몰랐어 <br>내가 원하던 사람이 너일지 <br>널 만날때마다 느꼈어 <br>이젠 솔직히 말할게 <br>Oh Yeah <br>너만 생각하는 걸 <br>매일 상상하게 되는 걸 <br>I just wanna fallin love <br>with you ma baby <br>숨길 수도 없어 <br>감당할 수 없어 <br>이젠 너에게 말할게 <br>If U love me <br>너의 싱그러운 미소를 닮은 <br>저 아침 햇살과 함께 <br>잠에서 깨어 <br>꿈같은 매일을 너와 함께해 <br>Love U <br>이 말로는 널 향한 내 맘을 <br>다 표현할 수가 없어 <br>I love you forever forever <br>Spend my life time with U <br>I wanna spend my life time loving U <br>너와 함께 해 매일이 더 소중해 <br>너와 함께 있어서 내 삶이 변해 <br>]]></content><category term="어쿠루브" label="어쿠루브"/><category term="If U love me (Feat. 동경)" label="If U love me (Feat. 동경)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/God_Only_Knows/</id><title>Michael_Buble - God Only Knows - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:29:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:29:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/God_Only_Knows/" title="Michael_Buble - God Only Knows - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I may not always love you <br>But long as there are <br>stars above you <br>You never need to doubt it <br>I'll make you so sure about it <br>God only knows <br>what I'd be without you <br>If you should ever leave me <br>Though life would <br>still go on believe me <br>The world could show <br>nothing to me <br>So what good would <br>living do me <br>God only knows <br>what I'd be without you <br>God only knows <br>what I'd be without you <br>God only knows <br>what I'd be without you <br>If you should ever leave me <br>Well life would still <br>go on believe me <br>The world could show nothing to me <br>So what good would living do me <br>God only knows <br>what I'd be without you <br>God only knows <br>what I'd be without you <br>God only knows <br>what I'd be without you <br>]]></content><category term="Michael Buble" label="Michael Buble"/><category term="God Only Knows" label="God Only Knows"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/Take_You_Away/</id><title>Michael_Buble - Take You Away - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:30:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:30:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/Take_You_Away/" title="Michael_Buble - Take You Away - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I see you're forcing that smile <br>And it's been a while <br>Since you've had a break <br>Oh you can't get it right <br>As hard as you've tried <br>Things ain't going your way <br>So baby take my hand <br>'Cause I've got a plan to get us <br>Straight outta here <br>Start packing your bag <br>Got a plane to catch <br>So let's disappear <br>The world keeps spinning <br>and we can't stop it <br>Let's slip out <br>when no one's watching <br>So baby let's go <br>Let me take you away <br>Let's hit the road <br>I'll be your escape <br>Let's travel the globe <br>We're leaving today <br>We'll chart the unknown <br>Let me take you away <br>We don't need to go far <br>To stare at the stars <br>And change our point of view <br>Gonna get you to dance <br>Make some sweet romance <br>Babe it's all about you <br>Kick your shoes off and laugh <br>It's time to relax <br>The sun will warm us all <br>Ain't no time to rethink <br>Grab a lemon drink <br>And let the good times roll <br>The world keeps spinning <br>and we can't stop it <br>Let's slip out <br>when no one's watching <br>So baby let's go <br>Let me take you away <br>Let's hit the road <br>I'll be your escape <br>Let's travel the globe <br>We're leaving today <br>We'll chart the unknown <br>Let me take you away <br>As long as it's you and me <br>It doesn't have to be so far away <br>So why don't we go on home <br>and just put down and say ay ay ay <br>So baby let's go <br>Let me take you away <br>Let's hit the road <br>I'll be your escape <br>Let's travel the globe <br>We're leaving today <br>We'll chart the unknown <br>Let me take you away <br>So baby let's go <br>Let me take you away <br>Let's hit the road <br>I'll be your escape <br>Let's travel the globe <br>We're leaving today <br>We'll chart the unknown <br>Let me take you away <br>So baby let's go <br>Let me take you away <br>Let's hit the road <br>I'll be your escape <br>Let's travel the globe <br>We're leaving today <br>We'll chart the unknown <br>Let me take you away <br>]]></content><category term="Michael Buble" label="Michael Buble"/><category term="Take You Away" label="Take You Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/Nobody_But_Me_Alternate_W_Trumpet_Ver/</id><title>Michael_Buble - Nobody But Me (Alternate W/Trumpet Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:30:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:30:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/Nobody_But_Me_Alternate_W_Trumpet_Ver/" title="Michael_Buble - Nobody But Me (Alternate W/Trumpet Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby I get a little bit jealous <br>But how the hell can I help it <br>When I'm thinkin' on you <br>Maybe I might <br>get a little reckless <br>But you gotta expect that <br>What else can a boy do <br>My momma taught me <br>how to share <br>But I'll be selfish <br>and I don't care <br>Cause I want you <br>I need you all for me <br>And I don't want anybody <br>loving my baby <br>Nobody nobody nobody <br>nobody nobody but me hey <br>And I don't want anybody <br>thinking just maybe <br>Nobody nobody nobody <br>nobody nobody but me <br>And I know when you got a lovely lady <br>It might drive the boys crazy <br>When she's looking so fine woah <br>I know know <br>know that no one <br>would ever blame me <br>The only thing <br>that could save me <br>Is just knowing you're mine <br>My papa told me <br>once or twice <br>Don't be cruel <br>but don't be too nice <br>Cause I want you <br>I need you all for me <br>Cause I don't want <br>anybody loving my baby <br>Nobody nobody nobody <br>nobody nobody but me hey <br>And I don't want anybody <br>thinking just maybe <br>Nobody nobody nobody <br>nobody nobody but me <br>I'll know I can be a bit jealous <br>But how the hell can I help it <br>I'm so in love with you <br>I don't want anybody loving my baby <br>Nobody nobody nobody <br>nobody nobody but me hey <br>I don't want anybody loving my baby <br>Nobody nobody nobody <br>nobody nobody but me <br>Oh my papa told me once or twice <br>Don't be cruel don't be too nice <br>My baby needs the lines from me <br>Oh and I know how to share <br>But I'll be selfish I don't care <br>My baby don't need no one but me <br>]]></content><category term="Michael Buble" label="Michael Buble"/><category term="Nobody But Me (Alternate W/Trumpet Ver.)" label="Nobody But Me (Alternate W/Trumpet Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/This_Love_Of_Mine/</id><title>Michael_Buble - This Love Of Mine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:30:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:30:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/This_Love_Of_Mine/" title="Michael_Buble - This Love Of Mine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This love of mine goes on and on <br>Though life is <br>empty since you have gone <br>You're always on my mind <br>though out of sight <br>It's lonesome through the day <br>But oh the night <br>I cry my heart out <br>it's bound to break <br>Since nothing matters let it break <br>I ask the sun and the moon <br>the stars that shine <br>What's to become of it <br>this love of mine <br>I ask the sun and the moon <br>the stars that shine <br>What's to become of it <br>this love of mine This love of mine <br>]]></content><category term="Michael Buble" label="Michael Buble"/><category term="This Love Of Mine" label="This Love Of Mine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/My_Baby_Just_Cares_For_Me/</id><title>Michael_Buble - My Baby Just Cares For Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:30:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:30:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/My_Baby_Just_Cares_For_Me/" title="Michael_Buble - My Baby Just Cares For Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My baby don't care for shows <br>My baby don't care for clothes <br>My baby just cares for me <br>My baby don't care <br>for furs and laces <br>My baby don't care <br>for high-tone places <br>Indoor just in style <br>And even Mr Clooney's smile <br>It's something she don't see <br>My baby don't care who knows it <br>My baby just cares for me <br>Oh Brando just ain't a star <br>And even smile <br>It's something she don't see <br>It's something she can't see <br>I wonder what's wrong with baby <br>She ain't scared to show it <br>She don't cares who knows it <br>My baby just cares for <br>Ah she just says her prayers for <br>My baby just cares for me <br>Only cares for <br>me She only loves me <br>]]></content><category term="Michael Buble" label="Michael Buble"/><category term="My Baby Just Cares For Me" label="My Baby Just Cares For Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/Someday_Feat_Meghan_Trainor/</id><title>Michael_Buble - Someday (Feat. Meghan Trainor) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:30:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:30:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/Someday_Feat_Meghan_Trainor/" title="Michael_Buble - Someday (Feat. Meghan Trainor) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I love seeing you happy <br>I miss seeing that smile <br>It's been such a long time <br>And although I don't have you <br>I know now that I need to <br>And somehow make you mine <br>And I won't lie <br>It's hard seeing you with him <br>'Cause I know <br>he can't hold you like I can <br>Someday maybe <br>when we're old and gray <br>We could be in love once more <br>Till then I won't give <br>my love away <br>Darling I'm forever only yours <br>I remember that love song <br>I sang every word wrong <br>But you didn't mind <br>No no <br>And I'll admit that I miss you <br>But only if you do <br>'Cause you know that I'm shy <br>And I can't lie <br>It's hard seeing you with her <br>'Cause I know <br>she can't love you like I can <br>Someday maybe <br>when we're old and gray <br>We could be in love once more <br>Till then I won't give <br>my love away <br>Darling I'm forever only yours <br>And my love then <br>what's for you then <br>We all got nothing to lose <br>'Cause I'm forever only yours <br>in love once more <br>once more once more <br>No need to complicate it <br>The smile is worth the wait yeah <br>I'm forever only yours hey yeah <br>Someday maybe <br>Someday maybe <br>Someday maybe <br>I'll be yours whoa baby <br>Someday maybe someday maybe <br>Someday maybe someday maybe <br>Someday maybe I'll be yours <br>someday maybe I'll be yours <br>Someday maybe <br>when we're old and gray <br>We could be in love once more <br>Till then I won't give <br>my love away <br>Darling I'm forever only yours <br>And my love then <br>what's for you then <br>We all got nothing to lose <br>'Cause I'm forever only yours <br>someday I'll be yours <br>No need to complicate it <br>The smile is worth the wait yeah <br>I'm forever only yours <br>someday maybe <br>I'm forever only yours <br>only yours <br>I'm singing now <br>I'm forever only yours <br>]]></content><category term="Michael Buble" label="Michael Buble"/><category term="Someday (Feat. Meghan Trainor)" label="Someday (Feat. Meghan Trainor)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/I_Wanna_Be_Around/</id><title>Michael_Buble - I Wanna Be Around - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:30:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:30:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/I_Wanna_Be_Around/" title="Michael_Buble - I Wanna Be Around - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wanna be around <br>to pick up the pieces <br>When somebody breaks your heart <br>Some somebody twice as smart as I <br>A somebody who will swear to be true <br>Like you used to do with me <br>Who'll leave you to learn <br>That misery loves company <br>wait and see <br>I wanna be there <br>to see how he does it <br>When he breaks your heart to bits <br>Let's see if the puzzle fits so fine <br>And that's when I'll discover <br>that revenge is sweet <br>As I sit there applaudin' from <br>a front-row seat <br>When somebody breaks your heart <br>Like you broke mine <br>And that's when I'll discover <br>that revenge is sweet <br>As I sit there applaudin' from <br>a front-row seat <br>When somebody breaks your heart <br>Like you is gonna break your heart <br>Just like you broke mine <br>]]></content><category term="Michael Buble" label="Michael Buble"/><category term="I Wanna Be Around" label="I Wanna Be Around"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/브로큰마인드/Yellow/</id><title>브로큰마인드 - Yellow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:30:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:30:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A1%9C%ED%81%B0%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B8%EB%93%9C/Yellow/" title="브로큰마인드 - Yellow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Microphone test <br>Battle Beat 뜨거 <br>래퍼들은 피해 <br>여자들은 Sexappeal 느껴 <br>Ich Dreh durch xtc <br>whack MC 부셔 <br>이기적 다 뺏어 너네 <br>Garanty 부터 <br>BROKN European <br>c'est la Vie 부러워 <br>영어 독어 다해 Bro <br>일단 mes amis 불러 <br>Nick ta mere <br>거리는 telavive 부터 <br>Marocane 500gramm 짜리 <br>handling 뚫어 <br>Berlin 구석에서 <br>Amsterdam 180 <br>Autobahn 타고 <br>Cops gonna stop <br>한마디 열받아 싸움나고 <br>Yes I'm yellow <br>Bumblebee 처럼 <br>Therefor u look at me <br>like a 다람쥐 처럼 <br>Brokn 오히려 벌받아 <br>법따라 봤자 <br>우리 동네에는 <br>없잖아 열받아 <br>우린 우리 멋대로 해 <br>이건 Frankfurt <br>우린 우리 법대로해 <br>Hello hello <br>나는 yellow yellow <br>찢어진 눈들이 <br>어둠 속을 걸어 <br>Hello hello <br>나는 yellow yellow <br>찢어진 눈들이 <br>안개 속을 걸어 <br>Hello hello <br>나는 yellow yellow <br>같은 yellow가 아닌 <br>나는 빛나는 yellow <br>Psst Alda Sorry <br>너는 간지가 안나 <br>walla 뭘하던 간에 <br>순한 강아지 같아 <br>난 강한 G 같아 <br>독일 paradies 살아 <br>내꺼 듣고나선 널 더이상 <br>바라지 않아 ah <br>이건 독일 교포 <br>weed Flow with porno flair <br>And I drop atomic bombs <br>call me North Korea <br>Rapper들은 talkshow 해야 하니 <br>Never drop it like me boi <br>늘 나 Bro 하지만 늘 <br>the Chinese boi <br>fick dich spasst <br>그래 우린 차이나 <br>I'm high from my style <br>I'm With ma 패거리 <br>every 불타는 Freitag <br>Komm wir ziehen durch die <br>City Frankfurt is ma <br>hood ficker <br>Sex drugs and rock n roll <br>경찰 입단속 시켜 <br>나는 hennessy <br>Wodka energy 빨어 <br>FKK Oase Style bro <br>난 Quality 알어 <br>남 다른 coffeeshop에 <br>메뉴판 다 외워 <br>안개 속 뚫고 가는 <br>내 몸은 가벼워 <br>Hello hello <br>나는 yellow yellow <br>찢어진 눈들이 <br>어둠 속을 걸어 <br>Hello hello <br>나는 yellow yellow <br>찢어진 눈들이 <br>안개 속을 걸어 <br>Hello hello <br>나는 yellow yellow <br>같은 yellow가 아닌 <br>나는 빛나는 yellow <br>비켜 du ficker <br>이건 Yellow hello <br>I am coming <br>with ma tres record fellows <br>Psst Alda sorry <br>너는 간지가 안나 <br>이거 듣고 나서 <br>널 더이상 바라지 않아 <br>비켜 du ficker <br>이건 Yellow hello <br>I am coming <br>with ma tres record fellows <br>Yes i am Yellow <br>bumblbee 처럼 <br>Motherfuckers look at me <br>like a 다람쥐처럼 <br>비켜 du ficker <br>이건 Yellow hello <br>I am coming <br>with ma tres record fellows <br>Psst Alda sorry <br>너는 간지가 안나 <br>이거 듣고 나서 <br>널 더이상 바라지 않아 <br>비켜 du ficker <br>이건 Yellow hello <br>I am coming <br>with ma tres record fellows <br>Yes i am Yellow <br>bumblbee 처럼 <br>Motherfuckers look at me <br>like a 다람쥐처럼 <br>]]></content><category term="브로큰마인드" label="브로큰마인드"/><category term="Yellow" label="Yellow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/Today_Is_Yesterdays_Tomorrow/</id><title>Michael_Buble - Today Is Yesterday`s Tomorrow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:30:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:30:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Buble/Today_Is_Yesterdays_Tomorrow/" title="Michael_Buble - Today Is Yesterday`s Tomorrow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm leaving my patience <br>my motivation <br>put them on separate teams <br>Baby I found someone I really need <br>Well baby are you with it <br>or maybe it's not important <br>what you do to me <br>You had me find my sense <br>of urgency <br>Time flies <br>I wish I would have met <br>with someone psychic <br>'Cause my mind it took some time <br>for me to realize it <br>'Cause today <br>is yesterday's tomorrow <br>While you're getting longer <br>the feeling's getting stronger <br>I can't wait I can't wait anymore <br>'Cause today <br>is yesterday's tomorrow <br>I don't know the numbers <br>but the future is a part of us <br>I can't wait I can't wait anymore <br>Anymore yeah <br>I know that you're hoping <br>that this is the note <br>that you will see <br>In the case <br>I ain't got nothing on me <br>But going with Allie hurry the <br>The kind of love <br>that lasts eternally <br>And I know that someone said <br>that it could end in heartache <br>But my dear <br>you only feel the chances <br>that we don't take <br>'Cause today <br>is yesterday's tomorrow <br>While you're getting longer <br>the feeling's getting stronger <br>I can't wait I can't wait anymore <br>'Cause today <br>is yesterday's tomorrow <br>I don't know the numbers <br>but the future is a part of us <br>I can't wait I can't wait anymore <br>Anymore yeah <br>Don't let it pass babe <br>'Cause the future comes fast <br>Oh ooh ooh <br>'Cause today <br>is yesterday's tomorrow <br>While you're getting longer <br>the feeling's getting stronger <br>I can't wait I can't wait anymore <br>'Cause today <br>is yesterday's tomorrow <br>I don't know the numbers <br>but the future is a part of us <br>I can't wait I can't wait anymore <br>Anymore yeah <br>Today is yesterday's tomorrow <br>Today is yesterday's tomorrow <br>Today is yesterday's tomorrow <br>Today is yesterday's tomorrow <br>Today is yesterday's tomorrow <br>Today is yesterday's tomorrow <br>Today is yesterday's tomorrow <br>Today is yesterday's tomorrow <br>]]></content><category term="Michael Buble" label="Michael Buble"/><category term="Today Is Yesterday`s Tomorrow" label="Today Is Yesterday`s Tomorrow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Addicted/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Addicted - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:30:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:30:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Addicted/" title="Gucci_Mane - Addicted - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro] When I was on drugs so bad, you know, I talked different I was drinking lean like crazy everyday, I was out my mind [Hook] Hi my name is Gucci Mane, I'm addicted to everything Bad bitches, fast cars, weed, and promethazine Hi my name is Gucci Mane, I'm addicted to everything Diamond chains, assault rifles, skrip clubs, and gambling Hi my name is Gucci Mane, I'm addicted to everything Fast cars, bad bitches, weed, and promethazine Hi my name is Gucci Mane, I'm addicted to everything Diamond chains, assault rifles, skrip clubs, and gambling [Verse 1] Hi my name is Gucci Mane, I'm addicted to everything Bad bitches, fast cars, weed and promethazine Diamond chains, tennis chains, assault rifles, gambling Sellin' dope and trickin' folks that run in my family My daddy was an alcoholic, momma she's a junkie daughter Cousin smokin' crack, I guess she forgot all my aunt done taught her Plus I got two brothers that I don't know from a addicted father And all the pain I caused my mother, bet she wish she had a daughter Sellin sets out my momma window, tryna' get a new starter Treat sun Valley like Decatur, mountain park like port Arthur I know my family dysfunctional So God please help these country folks Tired and broke, in need of hope Sheet rock, heroin, crack, and coke [Hook] Hi my name is Gucci Mane, I'm addicted to everything Bad bitches, fast cars, weed, and promethazine Hi my name is Gucci Mane, I'm addicted to everything Diamond chains, assault rifles, skrip clubs, and gambling Hi my name is Gucci Mane, I'm addicted to everything Bad bitches, fast cars, weed, and promethazine Hi my name is Gucci Mane, I'm addicted to everything Diamond chains, assault rifles, skrip clubs, and gambling [Verse 2] Gucci Mane a local joker, man that nigga regional (loco) And people won't be happy til I'm confined to Georgia regional The third week out of rehab he forgetting what they teachin' him Like why you smokin' blunts and sippin' lean and you a millionaire Wrecked my yellow lamb, high on drugs I didn't give a care Smashed my black Ferrari two weeks later, now it need repair Demons in my ear, got me seein' things wasn't even there People in my circle say they care, but they don't really care But I can't blame nobody but myself, it starts with myself Cause rap can bring you wealth, but that wealth can destroy your health Lookin' in the mirror at myself, had to catch my breath And tell myself that ""Gucci, you an addict!"" That's the first step [Hook] Hi my name is Gucci Mane, I'm addicted to everything Bad bitches, fast cars, weed, and promethazine Hi my name is Gucci Mane, I'm addicted to everything Diamond chains, assault rifles, skrip clubs, and gambling Hi my name is Gucci Mane, I'm addicted to everything Bad bitches, fast cars, weed, and promethazine Hi my name is Gucci Mane, I'm addicted to everything Diamond chains, assault rifles, skrip clubs, and gambling]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Addicted" label="Addicted"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Out_The_Zoo/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Out The Zoo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:30:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:30:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Out_The_Zoo/" title="Gucci_Mane - Out The Zoo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro] (Listen to this track bitch) Woah, Wop Hah, Wop Woah, sheesh Burr, toy Skrt, Wizzop [Verse 1] I take the good with the bad, and the bad with the good The plug sent the goods, so I had to flood the hood The plug sent the bag, then I offed that too That made me a bigger asset to the plug But tell me how you feel when your plug tell on ya Your partner in crime, own thugs tell on ya Talking 20 years, 30 years, 50 years In the cell feeling drunk like you drunk 80 beers Homicide though, genocide when I ride When we die, only God know where the bullets fly In my Hummer truck, bullets coming through my car door I got contract killers staying at my condo Got a hole up your folk cause they sholl ain't bluffin' Gotta vest up cause I sholl ain't ducking Standing in the cold on the corner, Flat Shoals Sold his soul to the devil for a Mac-11 100 bricks of pure coke, white like heaven My Mexican, Catholic connect doing confession Sitting in the pin, son just turned seven I progress then regress and this shit is getting depressing But I count my stash 'fore I count my blessings And I load my weapon 'fore I eat my breakfast The skreets keep talking and the snitches keep telling Your whole life can change in a motherfucking second [Hook] Out the cage in a rage like I escaped out the zoo They playing games with me when they know that I'm a fool Set it off like Queen Latifah, give me the loot or I'mma shoot You nincompoops so rude-a-poo, you tuti-fruit, you through I'm an animal, a cannibal, they say I'm on the loose Animal, a cannibal, they say I'm on the loose Gucci Mane La Flare, you prolly seen me on the news Out the cage in a rage like I escaped out the zoo [Verse 2] I might manic, I go in a panic, don't see nothing but red Off my meds, I can't sleep cause I hear voices in my head This lil devil on my left shoulder say ""shoot him in the dreads"" While an angel on the right whisper ""just shoot him in the leg"" I admit that I might need some help, I guess I made a step Man they think I need a shrink cause I fear God but don't fear death I'm so selfish, I bought 80 pints to drink 'em by myself A swimming pool full of drank, I dive in like I'm Michael Phelps Louis glasses, Ferragamo belt, I'm Gucci Mane XL YSL with the new Gazelles that match my blue Chevelle Bitches laughing like I'm Dave Chappelle cause I stay fresh as hell Zone 6, Zone 6. You don't like it? Kill yourself [Hook] Out the cage in a rage like I escaped out the zoo They playing games with me when they know that I'm a fool Set it off like Queen Latifah, give me the loot or I'mma shoot You nincompoops, so rude-a-poo, you tuti-fruit, you through I'm an animal, a cannibal, they say I'm on the loose Animal, a cannibal, they say I'm on the loose Gucci Mane La Flare, you prolly seen me on the news Out the cage in a rage like I escaped out the zoo]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Out The Zoo" label="Out The Zoo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Hi-Five/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Hi-Five - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:30:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:30:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Hi-Five/" title="Gucci_Mane - Hi-Five - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro] Brrrr, Metro Wop, hah It's big Gucci, catch up Metro, Wizzop If Young Metro don't trust you I'm gon shoot you [Verse 1] I put eight mill in my crib to inspire ya When you worth like twenty mill, the kids admire ya When your rap sheet look like mine, no one will hire ya But when you sign yourself like I did, they can't fire ya You want your club so loud then put me on the flier (it's Gucci) I'm on fire like Richard Pryor, my price gettin' higher How you gon' take my title, drivin' a car without a title? I'm whippin' through rush hour Charlotte traffic in a Spyder Slide up on ya bitch like a race car driver Dive off in that pussy like a deep sea diver Niggas from my hood know me from cheap, cheap powder But niggas on your block say you'se a real weak coward [Hook] High five, low five I left them niggas hangin', they get no five Gucci Mane, they say that I got nine lives Six Flags Over Georgia, I got nine rides High five, low five I left them bitches hangin', they get no five Gucci Mane they say that I got nine lives Come go to Gucci World, cause I got nine rides [Verse 2] Fuck yo jam of the week, I put grams on the street So much money, gave metro a hundred grand for the beat (Metro) So much ice around my bezel you can't see, the Patek I'm Felipe, in Felipe's, with a freak, she petite From the beach, to the skreet, from the skreet, to the suite Put my bone in her mouth, told her bon appetit I done sold so many keys they should deport me to Belize Cause I'm shining on these niggas like a desert with no trees From the hat on my head to the shoes on my feet Every garment on my body, man, it come from overseas In them 'partments I was raised I sold like 50,000 P's You want Gucci on your song, that's at least a hundred G's Wop [Hook] High five, low five I left them niggas hangin' they get no five Gucci Mane they say that I got nine lives Six Flags Over Georgia, I got nine rides High five, low five I left them bitches hangin', they get no five Gucci Mane they say that I got nine lives Come go to Gucci World cause I got nine rides]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Hi-Five" label="Hi-Five"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Love_Her_Body/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Love Her Body - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:31:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:31:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Love_Her_Body/" title="Gucci_Mane - Love Her Body - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Zaytoven! Huh Metro Boomin want some more, nigga! [Verse 1] You know I'm a gangster I'ma need for you to pray for me I know these niggas want you, I'mma need for you to wait for me Love and loyalty, it's not a day she goes unfaithfully Cause cain't nobody fuck you like me, yeah it ain't no replacing me Baby girl, you're more than beautiful, you put your trust in me Know I keep that blammer on me, know I'm your security Girl you got me invested in you, this is our community Thankful for this opportunity, treat you like family I can't even explain it but lil mama bring out the best in me I can't break this shit off if I wanted to, it's destiny I can't even explain it, but lil mama bring out the freak in me I'mma break her off in the back seat of my Bentley [Hook] Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body, body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body, body? [Verse 2] Baby you a goddess and I'm not being dishonest I can't even be modest, cause I'm in love with your body You worth more than money and you taste sweeter than honey Your walk is so hypnotic, you erotic plus exotic-xotic People say I'm trippin' I ain't thankin' bout these bitches We can share my rise, I give a damn they say I'm trickin' Super bad bitch I need it, first time I just did it, did it I can turn you up, I'm filthy, make you laugh I'm super silly We can hold hands in Lenox I don't give a damn who with me These haters need mind their business Tell the valet bring my Benzes Please beg my pardon, this not Dolly I'm the Trap God, she the goddess Good brain like she went to college These hoes jellyfish, she can't be solid [Hook] Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body, body? Gucci! Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body, body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body? Do I love my bitch or am I in love with her body, body?]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Love Her Body" label="Love Her Body"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Icy_Lil_Bitch/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Icy Lil Bitch - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:31:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:31:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Icy_Lil_Bitch/" title="Gucci_Mane - Icy Lil Bitch - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro] (Zaytoven) Burr, Ziggy Burr, Gucci Wop [Hook] She an icy lil bitch, the bitch is so icy Burr, burr, burr, burr But she a sheisty lil bitch, the bitch is so sheisty Bling-bling, blaww blaww She an icy lil bitch, the bitch is so icy Burr, burr, burr, burr But she a sheisty lil bitch, the bitch is so sheisty Bling-bling, bling-blaww [Verse 1] Man the bitch got fresh at the mouth so I iced her She said something so slick I disliked her If you ain't getting no cash like this, you can't pipe her But if you rock a watch like this, it entice her Man I can't even front on the chick cause she grinding Necklace full of diamonds, wrist and fist blinding The type of chick that Guwop like, you can't find It's a clause in my young bitch contract you can't sign Her closet like Rodeo got all type of designers And every time she leave up out the house, niggas remind her That she the baddest bitch in the world, and they want her But she just a material girl just like Madonna [Hook] She an icy lil bitch, the bitch is so icy Burr, burr, burr, burr But she a sheisty lil bitch, the bitch is so sheisty Bling-bling, bling-blaww She an icy lil bitch, the bitch is so icy Burr, burr, burr, burr But she a sheisty lil bitch, the bitch is so sheisty Bling-bling, bling-blaww [Verse 2] Chilling in the pent playing jazz, she got jazzy She's a pretty lil bitch, but her mouth is too nasty The way she do the trick with her tongue, the bitch had me She's a spoiled girl, rotten, so bad, I play daddy See I'm the type of rich, that I give before you ask me I got the type of dick make a rich girl start harassing I started in the trap, then I switched and started rapping She started drinking shots of Patron and started laughing Ciroc and passion fruit now she sucking me with a passion A fire breathing dragon, she riding me like a taxi We started off as friends, and then we started smashing Soon as she got a good dose of the macking she start bragging [Hook] She an icy lil bitch, the bitch is so icy Burr, burr, burr, burr But she a sheisty lil bitch, the bitch is so sheisty Bling-bling, bling-blaww She an icy lil bitch, the bitch is so icy Burr, burr, burr, burr But she a sheisty lil bitch, the bitch is so sheisty Bling-bling, bling-blaww]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Icy Lil Bitch" label="Icy Lil Bitch"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Right_On_Time/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Right On Time - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:31:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:31:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Right_On_Time/" title="Gucci_Mane - Right On Time - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro] Right on time (it's Gucci) Right on time (Ziggy) Right on time (Zaytoven) [Verse 1] Got two hoes they flyin' in, right on time, right on time And that thing just kicked in, right on time, right on time See that pack just touched down, right on time, right on time Guwop headed to your town, right on time, right on time Tis lil freak done hit my line, right on time, right on time And I'ma hit that from behind, right on time, right on time Can't get that jawn off my mind, right on time, right on time Why this lil monster so fine, right on time, right on time I just wired a half a mil, right on time, right on time Just so my roof could disappear, right on time, right on time This hoe keep eating prescription pills, right on time, right on time Somebody give this bitch a cell, right on time, right on time [Hook] Right on time, right on time, right on motherfuckin' time Right on time, right on time, right on motherfuckin' time Right on time, right on time, right on motherfuckin' time Man I just walked in the club right on motherfuckin' time Right on time, right on time, right on time, right on time Right on time, right on time, right on time, right on time Right on time, right on time, right on motherfuckin' time Man these hoes done hit the club right on motherfuckin' time [Verse 2] Right on time, right on time, Gucci back it's right on time I forgot so many bitches man, I shoulda wrote them down Roll me up then wind me down right on motherfuckin' time And my watch so stupid icy I can't even tell the time These niggas lyin' they commit a crime then they drop a dime If you's a man why you bitch up nigga? stand and do your time Right on time, I'ma freestyle ain't got time to write a rhyme And so many want a feature man that they done made a line I know she yours, but just for tonight I'm fuckin' her like she mine She give you pussy but she give me stomach, I'm one of a kind Made her vomit, gush out like a comet, hit her in the eye But she a big girl then she ask for more, man she didn't even cry [Hook] Right on time, right on time, right on motherfuckin' time Right on time, right on time, right on motherfuckin' time Right on time, right on time, right on motherfuckin' time Man I just walked in the club right on motherfuckin' time Right on time, right on time, right on time, right on time Right on time, right on time, right on time, right on time Right on time, right on time, right on motherfuckin' time Man these hoes done hit the club right on motherfuckin' time Wop]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Right On Time" label="Right On Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Wop/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Wop - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:31:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:31:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Wop/" title="Gucci_Mane - Wop - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[London Wizzop [Verse 1] Fuck that nigga, look at this nigga wrist I'm a project nigga with a rich nigga dick I got a hollywood smile, but I'm from zone 6 I stunt so fuckin' hard I'm on my own dick Baby think that she the shit because her man play for the Knicks But my bitch keep turnin' up cause her man pay for the bricks If she make me cum real quick, I give the bitch a stack Here's a rack for you, a rack for her, give everyone a rack I'm a gentleman, a gangster, and a motherfuckin' player You a square, I'm La Flare, yeah the Multi-Millionaire Million here, million there I got millions everywhere All these rappers are my kids so I got children everywhere Wop [Hook] These bitches wanna fuck when they see the 'Wop The club be goin' up, when they see the 'Wop We pilin' hoes in the truck, when they see the 'Wop These niggas put they jewelry up when they see the 'Wop You know some shooters on the bus, when you see the 'Wop You know these girls start actin' up, when they see the 'Wop You know these boys start actin' tough, when they see the 'Wop The baddest bitches leave with us, when they see the Wop [Verse 2] Baby say she wanna come stand where the G's at She gotta nose for it, she know where the cheese at But all that attitude you brought you need to leave that Fuckin' me's a privilege, I don't really need that I can feed you bitch but I don't need the feedback Just tryna chill and get some head and lean my seat back Most of these niggas broke, I know you probably peeped that But if I said I had ten mill' would you believe that Think I'm the realest man alive I do believe that (its Gucci) I'm leavin' Onyx with two hoes that dance at Magic I drop my top in less than two seconds, its magic And if I don't make a mill' this month, then it's tragic [Hook] These bitches wanna fuck when they see the 'Wop The club be goin' up, when they see the 'Wop We pilin' hoes in the truck, when they see the Wop These niggas put they jewelry up when they see the Wop You know some shooters on the bus, when you see the Wop You know these girls start actin' up, when they see the Wop You know these boys start actin' tough, when they see the Wop The baddest bitches leave with us when they see the Wop [Outro] Fuck that nigga, look at this nigga wrist Fuck that nigga, look at this nigga wrist Fuck that nigga, look at this nigga wrist I said fuck that nigga, look at this nigga, wrist]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Wop" label="Wop"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Dirty_Lil_Nigga/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Dirty Lil Nigga - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:31:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:31:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Dirty_Lil_Nigga/" title="Gucci_Mane - Dirty Lil Nigga - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro] Ha, niggas it's Woptober Guwop (Southside) It's that season, Wizzop If Young Metro don't trust you, I'm gon' shoot you [Hook] Came up in the hood lil dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga Might break in your house, he a dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, old dirty lil nigga Ain't shaved ain't bathed, dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga On the block for days, old dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga Came up in the hood lil dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga Might break in your house, he a dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, old dirty lil nigga Ain't shaved ain't bathed, dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga On the block for days, old dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga [Verse 1] Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga Catch him in the city, bout 30 lil niggas Keep a cup full of lean, he a muddy lil nigga Got a knife on a chopper, he'll cut a lil nigga He a bad lil jit with a bad lil chick Tryna hit a big lick and come up fast real quick Put a mask on quick then take your shit Know these dirty lil niggas don't play that shit 10 out of 10 got a tool on 'em Tryna catch a sucker slipping with them jewels on 'em Wolves foaming at the mouth, got drool on 'em Young nigga with a bunch of tattoos on 'em Got a Mossberg, Metro Boom on 'em Like a nigga walking round with a broom on 'em Catch a nigga with them bags then zoom on 'em Fuck homework, see 'em then move on 'em [Hook] Came up in the hood lil dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga Might break in your house, he a dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, old dirty lil nigga Ain't shaved ain't bathed, dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga On the block for days, old dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga Came up in the hood lil dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga Might break in your house, he a dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, old dirty lil nigga Ain't shaved ain't bathed, dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga On the block for days, old dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga [Verse 2] It's something that we doing ain't working nigga Cause these lil niggas be murking niggas Project baby, no father figure Only 15 and he a father nigga Spend all day tryna rob a nigga 20 lil jits and they mobbing with 'em Lil bitty nigga with a big extendo Don't nobody want problems with 'em Dirty lil nigga, he the runt of the litter His dope fiend auntie was his baby sitter Hard head mama can't do nothing with him But get on her knees and pray the skreets don't kill him The skreets don't kill him, then the law gon' get him Better listen to me kid, it's a fucked up system Y'all might don't feel him but I damn sure feel him Cause I was just in a jail cell fucked up with him [Hook] Came up in the hood lil dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga Might break in your house, he a dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, old dirty lil nigga Ain't shaved ain't bathed, dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga On the block for days, old dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga Came up in the hood lil dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga Might break in your house, he a dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, old dirty lil nigga Ain't shaved ain't bathed, dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga On the block for days, old dirty lil nigga Dirty lil nigga, he a dirty lil nigga]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Dirty Lil Nigga" label="Dirty Lil Nigga"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Money_Machine_Feat_Rick_Ross/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Money Machine (Feat. Rick Ross) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:31:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:31:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Money_Machine_Feat_Rick_Ross/" title="Gucci_Mane - Money Machine (Feat. Rick Ross) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wop money <br>Honorable C Note <br>Florescent lamps in my crib <br>providing life for my seeds <br>I'm a get money marine <br>I sent coke in submarines <br>Irrigation machines <br>hydraulic water machines <br>My money counting machine <br>sound like a sewing machine <br>Cash machine on the dresser <br>machine gun with <br>that compressor <br>Dope presser machine <br>I'm re rocking everything <br>Claim I'm laundering money <br>but where the washing machines <br>They know my trap house <br>pump out quarters <br>like a slot machine <br>In a futuristic whip look like <br>a time machine <br>Old school dropped a lil <br>one fine machine <br>Making chips off coke and <br>soda like a vending machine <br>Dog food with the quinoa <br>in my blending machine <br>Sip so much Codeine and <br>Sprite I need a soda machine <br>So I can sit it next to <br>my joint rolling machine <br>And it's placed parallel <br>to the Carbon 15 <br>With the scope <br>monkey nuts <br>and the infrared beam <br>The machine don't make the man <br>the man make the machine <br>So many try to sabotage <br>can't stop the regime <br>Call me 'Wop the puppet master <br>I'm just pulling the strings <br>Screaming please don't look at the <br>puppet like American Me <br>Take a tour with me a-down south <br>American G <br>Tryna flood the dirty south <br>East Atlanta <br>and streets <br>With this high grade <br>uncut Colombian tea <br>Yeah I got it for cheap <br>but you ain't get it from me <br>Got this high grade <br>uncut Colombian tea <br>Yeah I got it for cheap <br>but you can't get it for free <br>My money machine <br>my money machine <br>My money machine <br>go beep-beep <br>My money machine <br>my money machine <br>My money machine <br>go beep-beep <br>My money machine <br>my money machine <br>My money machine <br>my money machine <br>My money machine <br>my money machine <br>My money machine <br>my beep <br>My money machine <br>my money machine <br>My money machine <br>go beep-beep <br>My money machine <br>my money machine <br>My money machine <br>go beep-beep <br>8 figure niggas man <br>When I say boss I mean that <br>ya heard me <br>I'm so fuck what I sold <br>my toilet seats solid gold <br>You should see my new palace <br>cause that bitch bigger than Lowe's <br>I'm a 8 figure nigga <br>I run the check to the ceiling <br>Since Gucci came home <br>bitches back in they feelings <br>I'm in Dubai on parole <br>I Abu Dhabi my hoes <br>If she fuck all the rappers <br>she say hip hop in her soul <br>100 grand in all twenties <br>they said that I couldn't <br>50 grand to my bitch just <br>cause her ex was looking <br>Red bottom boss <br>I call the yayo caucasian <br>Choppers sleep on the couch <br>ready for home invasions <br>These pussies watching my Snap <br>they know that I'm strapped <br>On the road to the riches <br>bitches I'm running my laps <br>My money machine <br>my money machine <br>My money machine <br>go beep-beep <br>My money machine <br>my money machine <br>My money machine <br>go beep-beep <br>My money machine <br>my money machine <br>My money machine <br>my money machine <br>My money machine <br>my money machine <br>My money machine <br>my beep <br>My money machine <br>my money machine <br>My money machine <br>go beep-beep <br>My money machine <br>my money machine <br>My money machine <br>go beep-beep <br>Wizop beep racks <br>]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Money Machine (Feat. Rick Ross)" label="Money Machine (Feat. Rick Ross)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/The_Left/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - The Left - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:31:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:31:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/The_Left/" title="Gucci_Mane - The Left - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro] The left, the left Leftie, hah [Hook] Please don't make me slap you with the left, the left You a fake so I'm gon' dap you with the left, the left I feel like I'm the last real nigga left, the left It's like I'm on an island by myself, the left Please don't make me slap you with the left, the left You a fake so I'm gon' dap you with the left, the left I feel like I'm the last real nigga left, the left It's like I'm on an island by myself, the left [Verse 1] God please protect me if this shit go left Cause I can cook a kilo by my God damn self In the kitchen water whipping with the left I don't know Redman, but I know who got the meth I feel like I'm a one man BMF Cause I can lock a trap down by myself You waiting on Gucci to go broke, then hold your breath This shit ain't cut, it's raw, this shit gon' sell itself But don't let your right hand man know what your left hand doing My homeboys called the cops on me and I ain't even tripping But how you call yourself a G and hang around snitches? These niggas going left like crazy, acting like bitches [Hook] Please don't make me slap you with the left, the left You a fake so I'm gon' dap you with the left, the left I feel like I'm the last real nigga left, the left It's like I'm on an island by myself, the left Please don't make me slap you with the left, the left You a fake so I'm gon' dap you with the left, the left I feel like I'm the last real nigga left, the left It's like I'm on an island by myself, the left [Verse 2] Gucci Mane the leftie, pockets so hefty Wrist so fucking rocky I can't even take a selfie Right wrist glaring but my left hand glowing Limping, kicking, pimping like my left leg broken I offered her two thou, I tried to help her She took too long to come, that's why I left her I'm Gucci Mane, I eat millions for breakfast I came back in a 'Rari like I left some I'm in a droptop Rolls Royce I feel like I left some I got like 50 thou on me, who wanna fuck some? A lot of haters salty, they feel like I left 'em But all the beefs that Gucci had, Gucci addressed them [Hook] Please don't make me slap you with the left, the left You a fake so I'm gon' dap you with the left, the left I feel like I'm the last real nigga left, the left It's like I'm on an island by myself, the left Please don't make me slap you with the left, the left You a fake so I'm gon' dap you with the left, the left I feel like I'm the last real nigga left, the left It's like I'm on an island by myself, the left]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="The Left" label="The Left"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Aggressive/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Aggressive - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:31:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:31:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Aggressive/" title="Gucci_Mane - Aggressive - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Aggressive Hah, grrr, grrr, grrr Hah, grrrr, it's Wizzop, grrrr, hah (Zaytoven) [Hook] All this cash got me feeling aggressive All this ice got me feeling aggressive This drop top Rolls is so aggressive It got these hoes getting so aggressive All this ice got me feeling aggressive All this cash got me feeling aggressive This drop top Rolls is so aggressive It got these hoes getting so aggressive [Verse 1] I'm Gucci Mane the legend, I don't fuck with you peasants I'm too heavy to be petty, boy is you balling or begging? Please stop calling me, nigga, cause I can't spare not a second I gives a fuck bout a record, I got a criminal record These boys so scared of big Gucci, they make subliminal records Most of these rappers is pussy, they making feminine records It ain't a nigga in the industry that I wanna meet Your favorite rapper a sucker that's not surprising to me You can't be talking to the police then try signing with me I ain't cosigning these niggas, I'm only vouching for me I ain't letting these soft ass niggas stand on no couches with me You niggas wasn't in no trap house stacking up ounces with me, pussy [Hook] All this cash got me feeling aggressive All this ice got me feeling aggressive This drop top Rolls is so aggressive It got these hoes getting so aggressive All this ice got me feeling aggressive All this cash got me feeling aggressive This drop top Rolls is so aggressive It got these hoes getting so aggressive [Verse 2] I'm a business of building the man with the millions You'se collateral damage cause boy you just a civilian You'se a sheep in a wolf outfit boy you just a chameleon And you blend in good, but I'll hurt more than your feelings I'm a monster, a mobster, a contract killer I'm a convict, a conman, an ex-drug dealer I'm the bricks man, hit man, jack boy, kick man Knock your door off the hinges, I hit big licks and All my people like heaters, we don't like features We love each other, but we don't like people We crazy and violent and they can't teach us Preachers couldn't reach us but the hoes gon' greet us Cause we balling on you suckers, bitch want more on the bleachers You niggas real dick riders, male cheerleaders And you can't compete with Gucci so just follow the leader Cause I'm still that boy from Zone 6 that might follow your Regal, pussy [Hook] All this cash got me feeling aggressive All this ice got me feeling aggressive This drop top Rolls is so aggressive It got these hoes getting so aggressive All this ice got me feeling aggressive All this cash got me feeling aggressive This drop top Rolls is so aggressive It got these hoes getting so aggressive [Outro] Grrr]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Aggressive" label="Aggressive"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Intro__Fuck_12/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Intro: Fuck 12 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:31:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:31:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Intro__Fuck_12/" title="Gucci_Mane - Intro: Fuck 12 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Huh? Huh? [Verse] I still don't give a fuck how a fuckboy feel How you gon' keep it real and your diamonds not real? I do it so big, I make a hater feel little I can't tell you why they hating, but I have an idea You never liked me, probably don't like me still But a nigga liking me ain't never paid my bills I'm the realest nigga living, let's get one thing clear And if you wanna get it popping, we can do it right here I ain't never been embarrassed, I ain't never felt fear I got post-traumatic skresses like I can't shed tears I ain't even been out 6 months, but I spent 6 mil Got a million dollar grin and a 10 million dollar crib And my heart done turned burr-burr like my adlibs In the kitchen going skrt-skrt tryna make a mil Got these bitches screaming Bling-Blaww, diamonds in my ear I send my shooters then it's pow-pow, another tatted tear Yeah it's 2016, so it's Guwop year When I was 16, I was making drug deals These niggas say they getting money, I can't really tell I made more money than them and I was in a jail cell [Hook] I'ma say it once again, trust God, fuck 12 A real skreet nigga will never ever call 12 Say it once again, trust God, fuck 12 A real skreet nigga will never ever call 12 Wop, Wop, Wop, Wop [Interlude] I'm down on that red, this right here gon' get hard. Gon' get hard. Every day I'm getting fucking harder, I am... [Outro] Wop, fuck 12, Wop, fuck 12 Wop, Wop]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Intro: Fuck 12" label="Intro: Fuck 12"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Yo_Me_Escapare/</id><title>Tini - Yo Me Escapare - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:31:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:31:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Yo_Me_Escapare/" title="Tini - Yo Me Escapare - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hoy lo se me hace bien que me mires <br>Hasta el sol me elevas tu <br>Van en sol, van en mi <br><br>No olvides <br>Mi corazon, lo tienes tu <br>Yo me pregunto <br>Cada despertar <br>Que me esta pasando <br>Locura total <br>Me derrites, me derrites <br>Voy a mil, mil, mil <br>Yo Me Escapare <br>Y en tus brazos viajare <br>De tu aire perdere <br>Y me perdere, y me perdere <br>Yo Me Escapare <br>En tus alas volare <br>De tu aire perdere <br>Y me perdere, y me perdere <br><br>No hay final <br>Es el amor, me avecina <br>Nunca me he sentido asi <br>Cuando ese beso que me das <br>Se termina <br>Solo lo quiero repetir <br><br>Yo me pregunto <br>Cada despertar <br>Que me esta pasando <br>Locura total <br>Me derrites, me derrites <br>Voy a mil, mil, mil <br>Yo Me Escapare <br>Y en tus brazos viajare <br>De tu aire perdere <br>Y me perdere, y me perdere <br>Yo Me Escapare <br>En tus alas volare <br>De tu aire perdere <br>Y me perdere, y me perdere <br><br>En tus besos, en tus besos, en tus besos <br><br>En tus brazos, en tus brazos, en tus brazos <br><br>Yo Me Escapare <br>Y en tus brazos viajare <br>De tu aire perdere <br>Y me perdere, y me perdere <br>Yo Me Escapare Yo me escapare <br>En tus alas volare <br>De tu aire perdere <br>Y me perdere, y me perdere <br><br>En tus besos, en tus besos, en tus besos <br>En tus brazos, en tus brazos, en tus brazos]]></content><category term="Tini" label="Tini"/><category term="Yo Me Escapare" label="Yo Me Escapare"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Lo_Que_Tu_Alma_Escribe/</id><title>Tini - Lo Que Tu Alma Escribe - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:32:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:32:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Lo_Que_Tu_Alma_Escribe/" title="Tini - Lo Que Tu Alma Escribe - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Aqui <br>una foto nuestra tomaras <br>sin modificar la luz <br><br>inRead invented by Teads <br>asi sera mas simple <br>cuidar que yo brille <br>tal como me miras tu <br><br>Y ya <br>dime que piensas solamente en mi <br>frente a frente, dimelo <br>es casi un desafio, hay demasiado ruido <br>pero al menos intentemoslo <br><br>No hay palabras que inventar <br>yo lo veo en tu mirar <br>deja el corazon hablar <br>puedo en lo que tu alma escribe <br>Yo quiero abrazarte al sol <br>solos al amanecer <br>no preciso de tu voz <br>puedo de lo que tu alma escribe <br><br>Que tal <br>Conectamos sin corriente <br>solo lapiz y papel <br>tu alcanzas mi ventana <br>y dejas en mi almohada <br>la nota que yo leere <br><br>Intenta estar en el presente <br>y del manana olvidate <br>no hay imagen que exprese <br>lo que ven tus ojos descubriendome <br><br>No hay palabras que inventar <br>yo lo veo en tu mirar <br>deja el corazon hablar <br>puedo oir lo que tu alma escribe <br>Yo quiero abrazarte al sol <br>solos al amanecer <br>no preciso de tu voz <br>puedo oir lo que tu alma escribe <br>puedo oir que tu al, alma escribe <br>lo que el al, alma escribe <br>lo que el al, alma <br>puedo oir lo que tu alma escribe <br><br>Escribelo, anotalo por hoy <br>es magico, anotalo por hoy <br>es magico, escribelo por hoy <br>escribelo, escribelo por hoy <br><br>No hay palabras que inventar <br>yo lo veo en tu mirar <br>deja el corazon hablar <br>puedo oir que tu alma escribe <br>Yo quiero abrazarte al sol <br>solos al amanecer <br>no preciso de tu voz <br>puedo oir lo que tu alma escribe <br>puedo oir lo que tu al, alma escribe <br>lo que el al, alma escribe <br>lo que el al, alma <br>puedo oir lo que tu alma escribe <br>No hay palabras que inventar <br>yo lo veo en tu mirar <br>deja el corazon hablar <br>puedo oir lo que tu alma escribe <br>Yo quiero abrazarte al sol <br>solos al amanecer <br>no preciso de tu voz <br>puedo oir lo que tu alma escribe]]></content><category term="Tini" label="Tini"/><category term="Lo Que Tu Alma Escribe" label="Lo Que Tu Alma Escribe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Si_Tu_Te_Vas/</id><title>Tini - Si Tu Te Vas - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:32:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:32:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Si_Tu_Te_Vas/" title="Tini - Si Tu Te Vas - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[si tu te vas, me volvere a enamorar <br>me volvere a desarmar <br>una vez mas <br><br>si tu te vas <br>oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>si tu tu si tu te vas <br>oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>aqui estoy otra vez sufriendote <br>debo estar loca adicta al ayer <br>falso brillante no cambias la piel tuuu <br>hoy me pregunto cuando Aprendere <br>tocando el fuego yo me quemare <br>tanto me empujas que me haces caer <br>tuuuuuu <br>si tu te vas <br>me volvere a enamorar <br>me volvere a desarmar <br>una vez mas <br>si tu te vas hay pierdo el sentido <br>muero de frio <br>no puedo mas <br>si tu te vas <br>si tu tu si tu te vas <br>oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>recuerdas las tardes sonando volar <br>tu mano en mi mano mirando el mar <br>me cuesta entender porque me haces llorar <br>tuuuuuuu <br>noches sin piedad en la oscuridad <br>hoy lo veo con claridad claridad <br>cuando me entrege <br>deje de respirar <br>si tu te vas <br>me volvere a enamorar <br>me volvere a desarmar <br>una vez mas una vez mas <br>si tu te vas <br>hay pierdo el sentido <br>muero de frio muero de frio <br>no puedo mas <br>si tu te vas <br><br>noches sin piedad en la oscuridad <br>hoy lo veo con claridad claridad <br>cuando me entregue deje de respirar <br>si tu te vas <br>me volvere a enamorar <br>me volvere a desarmar <br>una vez mas <br>si tu te vas <br>hay pierdo el sentido <br>muero de frio <br>no puedo mas <br>si tu te vas <br>oh oh oh oh oh <br>si tu tu si tu te vas <br>oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>si tu te vas]]></content><category term="Tini" label="Tini"/><category term="Si Tu Te Vas" label="Si Tu Te Vas"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Sigo_Adelante/</id><title>Tini - Sigo Adelante - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:32:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:32:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Sigo_Adelante/" title="Tini - Sigo Adelante - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Me acostumbre a dejarte ganar <br>Me heriste con tu filo mortal <br>Sobre mi fuego echaste agua por ahogar la luz en mi <br><br>Pero hay un grito que no calla porque siempre estuvo ahi <br>Ven y enciende el mar bajo mis pies <br>Alma y corazon arrancame <br>Dices que solo me salvas tu y que estoy presa en tus brazos <br>Dejarte atras es importante <br>Sigo adelante <br>Sigo adelante <br>Voy a borrar el llanto de ayer <br>Volver al sitio aquel que ocupe <br>Me siento fuerte mas valiente <br>Al perderte yo aprendi que hay un mundo diferente a kilometros de ti <br>Ven y enciende el mar bajo mis pies <br>Alma y corazon arrancame <br>Dices que solo me salvas tu y que estoy presa en tus brazos <br>Dejarte atras es importante <br>Sigo adelante <br>Sigo adelante <br>Sigo adelante <br>Sigo adelante <br>Me imagine que eras unico el rey de la verdad <br>Hoy puedo ver que patetico tu fuiste en realidad <br>Ya te olvido me das pena <br>Estas tan perdido que das pena <br>Ven y enciende el mar bajo mis pies <br>Alma y corazon arrancame <br>Dices que solo me salvas tu y que estoy presa en tus brazos <br>Dejarte atras es importante <br>Sigo adelante <br>Sigo adelante]]></content><category term="Tini" label="Tini"/><category term="Sigo Adelante" label="Sigo Adelante"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Solo_Dime_Tu/</id><title>Tini - Solo Dime Tu - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:32:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:32:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Solo_Dime_Tu/" title="Tini - Solo Dime Tu - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tu bailabas solo y sin control <br>Nos miramos y el suelo se quebro <br><br>Todo arde, vamos lejos quiero escaparme <br>Solo dime tu, tu dime a donde y alli voy <br>Solo dime tu, tu dime a donde y alli voy, alli voy <br>Solo dime tu, tu dime a donde y alli voy, alli voy <br><br>Tus secretos siempre guardalos <br>El misterio me enciende el corazon yeah <br><br>Todo arde, vamos lejos quiero escaparme <br>Solo dime tu, tu dime a donde y alli voy <br>Solo dime tu, tu dime a donde y alli voy, alli voy <br>Solo dime tu, tu dime a donde y alli voy, alli voy <br><br>Todo arde, vamos lejos quiero escaparme <br>Solo dime tu, tu dime a donde y alli voy <br>Solo dime tu, tu dime a donde y alli voy, alli voy <br>Solo dime tu, tu dime a donde y alli voy, alli voy]]></content><category term="Tini" label="Tini"/><category term="Solo Dime Tu" label="Solo Dime Tu"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Handwritten/</id><title>Tini - Handwritten - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:32:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:32:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Handwritten/" title="Tini - Handwritten - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Could we <br>Take a picture of the two of us <br>and not really just of you <br><br>so we can have a secret <br>I swear that I would keep it <br>just between me and you <br><br>Will ya <br>Tell me you love me baby whisper it <br>face to face we tell the truth <br>we gotta make it happen <br>with so many distractions <br>and I don't know if we're getting through <br><br>do I have to say it loud <br>take the time to spell it out <br>if you're gonna write it down <br>baby could you make it hand handwritten <br>I just want to hold you close <br>me and you and nothing else <br>if you want to let me know <br>baby could you make it hand handwritten <br><br>maybe <br>we could take it back to basics <br>just a paper and a pen <br>tape into my window <br>Keep it under download <br>so I can find it in the end <br>when we're together let's just be there <br>no thinking two n's in the bins <br>no more e mail texts and no more sneaking texts <br>just wishing to be who I am <br><br>do I have to say it loud <br>take the time to spell it out <br>if you're gonna write it down <br>baby could you make it hand handwritten <br>I just want to hold you close <br>me and you and nothing else <br>if you want to let me know <br>baby could you make it hand handwritten <br>Baby could you make it hand hand handwritten <br>make it hand hand handwritten <br>make it hand hand hand <br>baby could you make it hand handwritten <br><br>it's not your fault I know I know I know <br>it's both of us I know I know I know, you know <br>it's not your fault I know I know I know <br>it's both of us I know I know I know <br><br>do I have to say it loud <br>take the time to spell it out <br>if you're gonna write it down <br>baby could you make it hand handwritten <br>I just want to hold you close <br>me and you and nothing else <br>if you want to let me know <br>Baby could you make it hand handwritten <br>baby could you make it hand hand handwritten <br>Make it hand hand handwritten <br>make it hand hand hand <br>Baby could you make it hand handwritten <br><br>do I have to say it loud <br>take the time to spell it out <br>if you're gonna write it down <br>baby could you make it hand handwritten <br>I just want to hold you close <br>me and you and nothing else <br>if you want to let me know <br>baby could you make it hand handwritten]]></content><category term="Tini" label="Tini"/><category term="Handwritten" label="Handwritten"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Finders_Keepers/</id><title>Tini - Finders Keepers - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:32:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:32:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Finders_Keepers/" title="Tini - Finders Keepers - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty is as pretty does <br>Baby she ain't looking so good right now <br>You and me so in love <br><br>Why'd anybody wanna shoot this flight down <br>Name callin' but we ain't fallin' <br><br>When a thing is set in stone <br>Always someone tryna chip away chip away <br>Only makes it double strong <br>Ain't nobody gonna strip away anything <br>No, love ain't a free free for all <br><br>Finders keepers <br>Just try to wipe this smile of my face <br>You made a believer <br>You made a believer out of me <br>I follow the leader <br>And my heart's the leader today <br>It's been a long road <br>We found love <br>No one can take it away <br>Finders keepers <br>Finders keepers <br><br>Yea, had to change to find the one <br>Had to fill in all the little holes in my heart <br>Turned to face the face of love <br>Boy the light is in your eyes right where you are <br>Heart stolen and i'm still falling <br><br>And the thing about a taker is <br>They just want without giving <br>And the thing about a hater is <br>They just hate what they're missing <br>No love ain't a free free for all <br><br>Finders keepers <br>Just try to wipe this smile of my face <br>You made a believer <br>You made a believer out of me <br>I follow the leader <br>And my heart's the leader today <br>It's been a long road <br>We found love <br>No one can take it away <br>Finders keepers <br>Finders keepers <br><br>Oh, keeper <br>Oh, keeper <br>Keeper <br><br>Finders keepers <br>Just try to wipe this smile of my face <br>You made a believer you made a believer <br>You made a believer out of me <br>I follow the leader i follow the leader <br>And my heart's the leader today <br>It's been a long road <br>We found love <br>No one can take it away <br>Finders keepers <br>Finders keepers <br>Finders keepers <br>Finders keepers]]></content><category term="Tini" label="Tini"/><category term="Finders Keepers" label="Finders Keepers"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Dont_Cry_for_Me/</id><title>Tini - Don`t Cry for Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:32:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:32:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Dont_Cry_for_Me/" title="Tini - Don`t Cry for Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I had my fair share of the good and the bad <br>I had my fair share of the happy and sad <br>Those broken pieces that I can't put back <br><br>Make up who I really am <br><br>So I live my whole life like there ain't no sequel <br>I dance on fine lines between good and evil <br>I play with fire to protect my people <br>But look back and smile in the end <br><br>When it's my time to go <br>Mama don't cry for me, don't cry for me oh no <br>'Cause I know where I'm going <br>So mama don't cry for me, don't cry for me <br>When it's my time to go <br>Mama don't cry for me, don't cry for me oh no <br>'Cause I know where I'm going <br>So mama don't cry for me, don't cry for me <br><br>And when I'm not there, have a drink for two <br>No need to think twice, I'll be there with you <br>Here's to the good times and the tears we've shared <br>Look back and smile in the end <br><br>When it's my time to go <br>Mama don't cry for me, don't cry for me oh no <br>'Cause I know where I'm going <br>So mama don't cry for me, don't cry for me <br>When it's my time to go <br>Mama don't cry for me, don't cry for me oh no <br>'Cause I know where I'm going <br>So mama don't cry for me, don't cry for me <br><br>Stare at the constellations you'll see my face <br>And if you pay attention you'll hear me say <br>Stare at the constellations you'll see my face <br>And if you pay attention you'll hear me say <br><br>When it's my time to go <br>Mama don't cry for me, don't cry for me oh no <br>'Cause I know where I'm going <br>So mama don't cry for me, don't cry for me <br>Yeaheah <br>When it's my time to go <br>Mama don't cry for me, don't cry for me oh no <br>'Cause I know where I'm going <br>So mama don't cry for me, don't cry for me]]></content><category term="Tini" label="Tini"/><category term="Don`t Cry for Me" label="Don`t Cry for Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/My_Stupid_Heart/</id><title>Tini - My Stupid Heart - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:32:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:32:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/My_Stupid_Heart/" title="Tini - My Stupid Heart - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My stupid heart <br>It's always falling in love <br>It's always falling apart <br><br>It's not too smart <br>My stupid heart <br><br>Ooohhhh <br><br>My my my my my stupid heart <br><br>Oooohhhh <br><br>Here I am want to get out in the rain <br>I must be crazy <br>Addicted to pain <br>I thought that I would be able to change <br><br>Youuuuuu <br><br>Oh <br><br>Youuuuuu <br><br>Asking myself will I ever learn <br>Touchin the flame, thinking I won't get burnt <br>After all we've been through <br>I thought I earned <br><br>Youuuuu <br><br>Ohhh <br><br>Youuuuuuuuuuu <br><br>My stupid heart <br>It's always falling in love <br>It's always falling a part <br>Lost in the dark <br><br>My stupid heart <br>One livin reasonnnn <br>Keeps on believinnn <br>It's not to smart <br>My stupid heart <br><br>Ooohhhhh <br><br>My my my my my stupid heart <br><br>Oooohhhhh <br><br>Remember the time that we layinn the grass <br>Your lips on my lips and your hand on mine yeahh <br>Can't understand why everything happend so fast <br><br>Youuuu <br><br>Oohhhh <br><br>Youuuu <br><br>You held on so tight <br>Days and days and nights <br>Now I finally see the light <br>See the light <br><br>When you think you ain't <br>You can not hear the mark <br><br>My stupid heart <br>It's always falling in love <br>It's always falling a part <br>Lost in the dark <br>Lost in the dark <br><br>My stupid heart <br>One livinnn reason <br>Keeps on believinnn <br>Keeps on believinnn <br>It's not too smart <br>My stupid heart <br><br>You held on so thight <br>Days days and nights <br>Now I finally see the light <br>See the light <br><br>When you think you ain't <br>You can not hear the mark <br>Mark <br><br>You beat heaaartttt <br>It's always falling in love <br>It's always falling in love <br>It's always falling apart <br>Lost in the dark <br>Lost in the dark <br><br>My stupid heart <br>One livinnn reason <br>Keeps on believinnn <br>It's not too smart <br>My stupid heart <br><br>Oohhhhh <br><br>My my my my my stupid heart <br><br>Ooohhhhh <br><br>My stupid heart]]></content><category term="Tini" label="Tini"/><category term="My Stupid Heart" label="My Stupid Heart"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Got_Me_Started/</id><title>Tini - Got Me Started - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:32:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:32:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Got_Me_Started/" title="Tini - Got Me Started - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I remember what you said <br>I can't get you out my head <br>Every night's a crazy party <br><br>I don't wanna wake up from it <br><br>I feel you like a hurricane <br>A perfect song inside my brain <br>You should hear the things you say <br>You should hear the <br>Every word makes me insane <br>Every word makes me insane <br><br>We can't stop once we get started <br>Baby, you got me started <br>Even though you're so far away <br>I'm feeling you on my body <br><br>We can't stop onve we get started <br>Baby, you got me started <br>Even though you're so far away <br>I'm feeling you on my body <br><br>Oh, yea <br>Oh, yea <br>Once we get started <br><br>Oh <br>Once we get started <br>Oh, oh <br>Once we get started <br><br>I could fix your lonely pain <br>Close your eyes and think of me <br>I could be your ecstasy i can be your <br>Magic power in your veins, ha, ha <br><br>We can't stop onve we get started <br>Baby, you got me started <br>Even though you're so far away <br>I'm feeling you on my body <br><br>We can't stop onve we get started <br>Baby, you got me started <br>Even though you're so far away <br>I'm feeling you on my body <br><br>Oh, yea <br>Oh, yea <br>Once we get started <br><br>Somewhere where we more than just a fantasy <br>There'll be no more hide and seek <br><br>And if you want me i'm only a blink away <br>Close your eyes and look for me <br><br>'Cause your love <br>Is keepin' me up <br>Your love <br>Is keepin' me up <br>Your love <br>Is keepin' me going <br>Your love <br>Is keepin' me high <br><br>Somewhere where we more than just a fantasy <br>Close your eyes and look for me <br>Oh, yea <br>Oh <br>Oh <br>Yeah <br>We can't stop onve we get started <br>Yeah <br>Baby you have me started <br>Even though you're so far away <br>I'm feeling you on my body <br><br>We can't stop onve we get started <br>Baby you have me started <br>Even though you're so far away <br>I'm feeling you on my body <br><br>We can't stop onve we get started <br>Uhh <br>Even though you're so far away <br>I'm feeling you on my body <br><br>We can't stop onve we get started <br>Baby you have me started]]></content><category term="Tini" label="Tini"/><category term="Got Me Started" label="Got Me Started"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Still_Standing/</id><title>Tini - Still Standing - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:32:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:32:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Still_Standing/" title="Tini - Still Standing - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I used to let you tear me apart <br>I let your words fly through me like darts <br>You pour your water on my fire <br><br>Try to dim the light in me <br>There's something naked <br>Something sacred <br>That you're never gonna see <br><br>Let the rain crash down over my head <br>You can rip my heart out of my chest <br>You tell me that you're my parachute <br>And I can't make it without you <br>But I'll survive this crash landing <br>I'll be still standing, still standing <br><br>I'll wash the dirt and tears from my face wash the dirt and tears <br>And put my pieces back in their place oh oh oh <br>There's something primal <br>In survival <br>And I'm stronger then I seem <br>There is beauty in the broken, there's so much more to me <br><br>Let the rain crash down over my head <br>You can rip my heart out of my chest <br>You tell me that you're my parachute <br>And I can't make it without you <br>But I'll survive this crash landing <br>I'll be still standing, still standing <br>I'll be still standing, still standing <br><br>I used to think that you hung the moon <br>I'd hang on every word <br>But now I know that you tore me down <br>To build yourself up more <br>I feel sorry for you right now <br>I feel kind of sorry for you right now <br><br>Let the rain crash down over my head <br>You can rip my hear out of my chest <br>You tell me that you're my parachute <br>And I can't make it without you <br>But I'll survive this crash landing <br>I'll be still standing, still standing <br>I'll be still standing, still standing]]></content><category term="Tini" label="Tini"/><category term="Still Standing" label="Still Standing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Great_Escape/</id><title>Tini - Great Escape - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:32:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:32:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/Great_Escape/" title="Tini - Great Escape - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Easy come easy go for a minute <br>I can't keep my hands off you <br>You're a million dollar bill don't forget it <br><br>I wanna spend my time on you <br><br>And I been wondering <br>From morning to night <br>Stuck in delirium <br>I'm losing my mind <br>Do you feel it <br>Do you feel it <br>Feels so real, real, real <br><br>You're my great escape <br>Feels too good to give away <br>And with every breath I take <br>I can't help myself, I can't help myself <br>You're my great ecape <br>I won't let you get away <br>And with every breath I take <br>I can't help myself, I can't help myself <br><br>Ohhh ohh <br>Wide awake wanna stay tunnel vision <br><br>Falling for the sweetest sin <br>I wanna taste everything when we're kissing <br>I love it when we're skin to skin <br>And I been wondering <br>From morning to night <br>Stuck in delirium <br>I'm losing my mind <br>Do you feel it <br>Do you feel it <br>Feels so real, real, real <br><br>You're my great escape <br>Feels too good to give away <br>And with every breath I take <br>I can't help myself, I can't help myself <br>You're my great ecape <br>I won't let you get away <br><br>And with every breath I take <br>I can't help myself, I can't help myself <br>Ohhh ohh <br>I'll be running, I'll be running, I'll be running <br>I'll be running, I'll be running, I'll be running <br>You're my great escape <br>Feels too good to give away <br>And with every breath I take <br>I can't help myself, I can't help myself <br>You're my great ecape you're my great ecape <br>I won't let you get away <br>And with every breath I take <br>I can't help myself, I can't help myself <br>Ohhh ohh <br>I'll be running, I'll be running, I'll be running <br>I'll be running, I'll be running, I'll be running]]></content><category term="Tini" label="Tini"/><category term="Great Escape" label="Great Escape"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/All_You_Gotta_Do/</id><title>Tini - All You Gotta Do - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:32:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:32:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tini/All_You_Gotta_Do/" title="Tini - All You Gotta Do - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You get used to <br>Dancing all alone <br>Since I met you <br><br>You keep me on my toes <br><br>Let's go somewhere <br>I've got something I wanna show you <br>All you gotta do is say you want me <br>and I'll be yours be yours <br>All you gotta do is say you want me <br>and I'll be yours be yours <br>I'll be yours <br>All you gotta do is say you want me <br>and I'll be yours <br>I'll be yours <br><br>Keep your secrets <br>I like what I know <br>Keep me guessing <br>And I'll just keep you close, yea <br><br>Let's go somewhere <br>I've got something I wanna show you <br>All you gotta do is say you want me <br>and I'll be yours be yours <br>All you gotta do is say you want me <br>and I'll be yours be yours <br>I'll be yours <br>All you gotta do is say you want me <br>and I'll be yours <br>I'll be yours <br><br>Let's go somewhere <br>I've got something I wanna show you <br>All you gotta do is say you want me <br>and I'll be yours and I'll be yours <br>All you gotta do is say you want me <br>and I'll be yours <br>I'll be yours <br>All you gotta do is say you want me <br>and I'll be yours]]></content><category term="Tini" label="Tini"/><category term="All You Gotta Do" label="All You Gotta Do"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Mama_Kin/</id><title>Buckcherry - Mama Kin - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:36:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:36:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Mama_Kin/" title="Buckcherry - Mama Kin - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It ain't easy livin' like a gypsy <br>Tell ya, honey, how it feels <br>I've been dreamin' floatin' down stream <br><br>And losin' touch with all that's real <br>Whole lotta lover, keepin' undercover <br>Never knowin' where you been Oo yeah <br>You've been fadin', always out paradin' <br>Keep in touch with mama kin <br><br>You always got your tail on the wag <br>Spittin' fire from your mouth <br>Just like a dragon <br>You act like a perpetual drag <br>You better check it out <br>'Cause someday soon <br>You'll have to climb back on the wagon <br><br>It ain't easy livin' like you wanna <br>It's so hard to find piece of mind <br>Yes it is <br>The way I see it <br>You got to say 'shee it' <br>But don't forget to drop me a line <br><br>Bald as an egg at eighteen <br>And workin' for daddy's such a drag <br>You still stuff your mouth <br>With his beans <br>You better check it out or someday soon <br>You'll have to climb back on the wagon <br><br>Keep in touch with mama kin <br>Tell her where you gone and been <br>Livin' out your fantasy <br>Sleepin' late and smokin' tea <br>Keep in touch with mama kin <br>Tell her where you gone and been <br>Livin' out your fantasy <br>Sleepin' late and suckin' me, oh no <br><br>It ain't easy livin' like you wanna <br>It's so hard to find piece of mind <br>Yes it is <br>The way I see it <br>You got to say 'shee it' <br>But don't forget to drop me a line <br><br>Bald as an egg at eighteen <br>And workin' for daddy's just a drag <br>You still stuff your mouth <br>With his beans <br>You better check it out or someday soon <br>You'll have to climb back on the wagon <br><br>Keep in touch with mama kin <br>Tell her where you gone and been <br>Livin' out your fantasy <br>Sleepin' late and smokin' tea <br>Keep in touch with mama kin <br>Tell her where you gone and been <br>Livin' out your fantasy <br>Sleepin' late and suckin' me <br>Ohh, ow, ow, ow, yeah ow]]></content><category term="Buckcherry" label="Buckcherry"/><category term="Mama Kin" label="Mama Kin"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Gettin_Started/</id><title>Buckcherry - Gettin` Started - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:37:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:37:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Gettin_Started/" title="Buckcherry - Gettin` Started - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We're gettin' started <br>We're gettin' started <br>Well, I heard it on the street <br><br>The city never sleeps <br>Tell me where should I begin <br>Better stay on the track, never lookin' back <br>Started all over again <br>Let's put this all thing together <br>Lift my head up and I started to win <br>Say what you say <br>Givin' up like there's no tomorrow <br>Give it away <br>Always enough then we're just gettin' started <br>Living it up and we're just gettin' started <br>We're gettin' started <br>Gotta get up my ass <br>What can afford a scratch <br>You know I had a couple of dreams <br>And I made it through to the front <br>I know you think it's luck <br>But baby, you ain't seen what I've seen <br>Let's put this all thing together <br>Lift my head up, I'ma stay here til' I can see <br>Say what you say <br>Livin' up like there's no tomorrow <br>Give it away <br>Always enough and we're just gettin' started <br>Living it up and we're just gettin' it started <br>We're gettin' started <br>We're gettin' started <br>We're gettin' started <br>We're gettin' started <br>Say what you say <br>We're gettin' started <br>Livin' it up like there's no tomorrow <br>Give it away <br>We're gettin' started <br>Always enough and we're just gettin' started <br>Livin' it up and we're just gettin' started <br>Ah', say what you say <br>Livin' it up like there's no tomorrow <br>Give it away <br>Always enough and we're just gettin' started <br>Say what you say <br>Gettin' up like there's no tomorrow <br>Give it away <br>Always enough and we're just gettin' started <br>Livin' it up and we're just gettin' started <br>We're gettin' started x4]]></content><category term="Buckcherry" label="Buckcherry"/><category term="Gettin` Started" label="Gettin` Started"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/The_Feeling_Never_Dies_Feat_Gretchen_Wilson/</id><title>Buckcherry - The Feeling Never Dies (Feat. Gretchen Wilson) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:37:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:37:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/The_Feeling_Never_Dies_Feat_Gretchen_Wilson/" title="Buckcherry - The Feeling Never Dies (Feat. Gretchen Wilson) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've lost my mind, nothing making sense <br>Something isn't right and you say <br>Time is on my side, I'm never giving up <br>'Cause you know you've got to finish what you started <br>And this is what we wanted love <br><br>It's not enough that I hold ya <br>It's not enough that I take my time <br>You're still what I need and we are growing older <br>So look into my eyes <br>The feeling never dies <br><br>Oh cry, don't you cry <br>Everything's OK <br>We're gonna be alright and you say <br>Why Will we survive <br>I'm never giving up <br>'Cause you know you've got to finish what you started <br>And this is what we wanted love <br><br>It's not enough that I hold ya <br>It's not enough that I take my time <br>You're still what I need and we are growing older <br>So look into my eyes <br>'Cause baby I adore ya <br>I'm not going to change my mind <br>You're my dream, the one that's on my shoulder <br>It's only you and I <br>The feeling never dies <br><br>I can tell you anything <br>I can come straight from the heart <br>I can tell you anything <br>And you love me no matter what <br><br>It's not enough that I hold ya <br>It's not enough that I take my time <br>You're still what I need and we are growing older <br>So look into my eyes <br>Baby I adore ya <br>I'm not going to change my mind <br>You're my dream, the one that's on my shoulder <br>It's only you and I <br><br>It's not enough that I hold ya <br>It's not enough that I take my time <br>You're still what I need baby <br>Soul baby, the one that I adore <br><br>x3 <br>The feeling never dies <br>The feeling never dies <br><br>Oh don't you know the feeling never dies]]></content><category term="Buckcherry" label="Buckcherry"/><category term="The Feeling Never Dies (Feat. Gretchen Wilson)" label="The Feeling Never Dies (Feat. Gretchen Wilson)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Get_With_It/</id><title>Buckcherry - Get With It - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:37:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:37:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Get_With_It/" title="Buckcherry - Get With It - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Get with it, get with it <br><br>Help is on the way, what you need <br>You are the hottest thing that I've ever seen <br>I'm gonna have to keep my record clean <br>cause, oh my God, baby girl you're a serious thing <br>So I better get with it, get with it <br><br>She'll make your head trip, lick lips, beg like a dog <br>She'll make your heart beat, lose sleep, lost in a fog <br>She'll make your friends stop and stare with things that she wears <br>So you better get with it, hey Get with it, hey, hey <br><br>I can't concentrate I can't think <br>You got me feeling like I'm lost in a dream <br>I'm not the kind of guy to take it slow <br>Are you down Tell me now cause I'm ready to go <br>So you better get with it, get with it <br><br>She'll make your head trip, lick lips, beg like a dog <br>She'll make your heart beat, lose sleep, lost in a fog <br>She'll make your friends stop and stare with things that she wears <br>So you better get with it, hey Get with it, hey, hey <br><br>She'll make your head trip, lick lips, beg like a dog <br>She'll make your heart beat, lose sleep, lost in a fog <br>She'll make your friends stop and stare with things that she wears <br>So you better get with it, hey Get with it, hey, hey <br><br>She'll make the sun shine, so fine, bang like a bomb <br>She's got a strong mind, slow grind, making it hard <br>Make your friends stop and stare with things that she wears <br>So you better get with it, hey Get with it, hey <br>So you better get with it, hey Get with it, hey]]></content><category term="Buckcherry" label="Buckcherry"/><category term="Get With It" label="Get With It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Sex_Appeal/</id><title>Buckcherry - Sex Appeal - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:37:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:37:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Sex_Appeal/" title="Buckcherry - Sex Appeal - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I see you, I told you, I know you, I want it now <br>This rollercoaster is fucking us both around <br>Let's get this thing started we both know it's going down <br>Find a location and take this shit underground <br><br>Wanna know, wanna know, wanna know how you feel <br>Wanna know, wanna know, wanna know if it's real <br>Wanna take you home and see if we could strike up a deal <br>Wanna know what you think, cause I think we can sink <br>into a full glass overdose of sex appeal <br><br>The closer, the contact, the statement you're in the clouds <br>Yesterday morning you hardly would make a sound <br>I know what you want so lets stop with the spinning wheel <br>Open you up and I'll look for the stuff that's real <br><br>Wanna know, wanna know, wanna know how you feel <br>Wanna know, wanna know, wanna know if it's real <br>Wanna take you home and see if we could strike up a deal <br>Wanna know what you think, cause I think we can sink <br>into a full glass overdose of sex appeal <br><br>The moment I saw you, you felt like I had it made <br>You were a story and not just a single page <br>I look in your eyes and I know that you feel the same <br>'m here for the glory and not just to play the game <br><br>Wanna know, wanna know, wanna know how you feel <br>Wanna know, wanna know, wanna know if it's real <br>Wanna take you home and see if we could strike up a deal <br>Wanna know what you think, cause I think we can sink <br>into a full glass overdose of sex appeal]]></content><category term="Buckcherry" label="Buckcherry"/><category term="Sex Appeal" label="Sex Appeal"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Rains_Falling/</id><title>Buckcherry - Rain`s Falling - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:37:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:37:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Rains_Falling/" title="Buckcherry - Rain`s Falling - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So much that you mean to me <br>You got to go and tell your people to just let us be <br>I am ready to spend time with you Are you ready <br><br>We don't ever disagree <br>You remind me of what matters, when I struggle to see <br>It keeps raining Why am I so blue <br>It keeps raining Baby <br><br>Rain's falling, I hear you calling <br>Rain's falling, I miss you darling <br>Rain's falling, and summer's drifting away <br><br>Don't you ever change a thing <br>You are prettier than anything that I have seen <br>Baby, when can I see you I'm going crazy <br><br>When I'm far away from you, I am flooded with emotion don't know what to do <br>It keeps raining, why am I so blue, it keeps raining <br>Save me <br><br>Rain's falling, I hear you calling <br>Rain's falling, I miss you darling <br>Rain's falling, and summer's drifting away <br><br>I am ready to spend time with you Are you ready <br>Oh baby, when can I see you I'm going crazy <br><br>Rain's falling, I hear you calling <br>Rain's falling, I miss you darling <br>Rain's falling, and summer's drifting away <br>Drifting away <br>Drifting away <br>Drifting away <br>Drifting away <br><br>Rain's falling, I hear you calling <br>Drifting away]]></content><category term="Buckcherry" label="Buckcherry"/><category term="Rain`s Falling" label="Rain`s Falling"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Wood/</id><title>Buckcherry - Wood - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:37:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:37:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Wood/" title="Buckcherry - Wood - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She's got a body that will blow your mind, like a chrome plated gun in your eyes <br>I try and tell her but I'm misunderstood, you're giving me wood <br>She's got honey glaze apple skin, like a butterfly in the wind <br>I want to tell her when she'd in the mood, your giving me wood <br><br>You're giving me wood, I really hope you're in the mood <br>And if it gets any hotter, I'm gonna need some cold water <br><br>Wood, wood, wood, wood <br><br>She wants to play with it everyday, like a flower poking through the haze <br>she says she does it cause it feels so good, she's giving me wood <br><br>You're giving me wood, I really hope you're in the mood <br>And if it gets any hotter, I'm gonna need some cold water <br>You're giving me wood, oh baby tell me what to do <br>and if it gets any harder, you're gonna have to call a doctor <br><br>Wood, wood, wood, wood <br><br>You're giving me wood, I really hope you're in the mood <br>And if it gets any hotter I'm gonna need some cold water <br>You're giving me wood, oh baby tell me what to do <br>and if it gets any harder, you're gonna have to call a doctor <br><br>Wood, wood, wood, wood]]></content><category term="Buckcherry" label="Buckcherry"/><category term="Wood" label="Wood"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/The_Madness/</id><title>Buckcherry - The Madness - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:37:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:37:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/The_Madness/" title="Buckcherry - The Madness - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I got two sides of me <br>You can bet they're enemies <br>You got the good side then you got the madness <br>Fire lit and I'm ready to go <br>Out of step and my blood is cold <br>It's how it goes when you're in the grips of madness <br><br>Oh and I'm filled with steam <br>Oh lean, mean and green <br>Oh but I still believe <br>Oh <br><br>When your thoughts are not your own <br>and you feel like you have lost control <br>It's not a test you're dealing with the madness <br>Don't be scared by what you find <br>It's guaranteed to blow your mind <br>I must confess I really like the madness <br><br>I lost my sanity <br>You can rest when they bury me <br>From the west side staying alive with the madness <br>Take look into my eyes and see a fucked up state of mind <br>My crime is losing time to the madness <br><br>Oh and I'm filled with steam <br>Oh lean, mean and green <br>Oh but I still believe <br>Oh <br><br>When your thoughts are not your own <br>and you feel like you have lost control <br>It's not a test you're dealing with the madness <br>Don't be scared by what you find <br>It's guaranteed to blow your mind <br>I must confess I really like the madness <br><br>Break it down <br>Don't steal my soul <br>I'm not a motherfucker with a fuckin' heart of stone <br>Just a full time hard time headed straight for the madness <br>Can't you see I've had it <br><br>Oh and I'm filled with steam <br>Oh lean, mean and green <br>Oh but I still believe <br>Oh <br><br>When your thoughts are not your own <br>and you feel like you have lost control <br>It's not a test you're dealing with the madness <br>Don't be scared by what you find <br>It's guaranteed to blow your mind <br>I must confess I really like the madness <br><br>Oh and I'm filled with steam <br>Oh lean, mean and green <br>Oh but I still believe <br>Oh]]></content><category term="Buckcherry" label="Buckcherry"/><category term="The Madness" label="The Madness"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Cradle/</id><title>Buckcherry - Cradle - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:37:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:37:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Cradle/" title="Buckcherry - Cradle - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Always, always hateful <br>Crack the precious cradle <br>Yeah <br><br>Beauty comes to greet you in your prime <br>and soon enough you'll have to use your mind <br>Every year discovering your reasons <br>and all the things you've learned to present day <br>and history finds a way to teach us lessons <br>and now the world destruction comes our way <br><br>Always, always hateful <br>Crack the precious cradle <br>Calling on Mother Nature <br>didn't mean to kill her <br><br>Money in the hands of masterminds <br>Payback from an insecure decline <br>Working hard to rid the world of evil <br>Once again a testament of pain <br>The only way to treat this kind of problem <br>Gonna have to blow it all away <br><br>Always, always hateful <br>Crack the precious cradle <br>Calling on Mother Nature <br>didn't mean to kill her <br><br>Don't you swallow it's in the water <br>The free world has to pay <br>Biohazard in your letters <br>The free world has to play <br><br>Every year discovering your reasons <br>and all the things you've learned to present day <br>History finds a way to teach us lessons <br>and now the world destruction comes our way <br><br>Always, always hateful <br>Crack the precious cradle, yeah <br>Gotta get out, come on Gotta get out <br><br>Always, always hateful <br>Crack the precious cradle <br>Calling on Mother Nature <br>didn't mean to kill her]]></content><category term="Buckcherry" label="Buckcherry"/><category term="Cradle" label="Cradle"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/The_Feeling_Never_Dies/</id><title>Buckcherry - The Feeling Never Dies - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:37:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:37:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/The_Feeling_Never_Dies/" title="Buckcherry - The Feeling Never Dies - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've lost my mind, nothing making sense <br>Something isn't right and you say <br>Time is on my side, I'm never giving up <br>'Cause you know you've got to finish what you started <br>And this is what we wanted love <br><br>It's not enough that I hold ya <br>It's not enough that I take my time <br>You're still what I need and we are growing older <br>So look into my eyes <br>The feeling never dies <br><br>Oh cry, don't you cry <br>Everything's OK <br>We're gonna be alright and you say <br>Why Will we survive <br>I'm never giving up <br>'Cause you know you've got to finish what you started <br>And this is what we wanted love <br><br>It's not enough that I hold ya <br>It's not enough that I take my time <br>You're still what I need and we are growing older <br>So look into my eyes <br>'Cause baby I adore ya <br>I'm not going to change my mind <br>You're my dream, the one that's on my shoulder <br>It's only you and I <br>The feeling never dies <br><br>I can tell you anything <br>I can come straight from the heart <br>I can tell you anything <br>And you love me no matter what <br><br>It's not enough that I hold ya <br>It's not enough that I take my time <br>You're still what I need and we are growing older <br>So look into my eyes <br>Baby I adore ya <br>I'm not going to change my mind <br>You're my dream, the one that's on my shoulder <br>It's only you and I <br><br>It's not enough that I hold ya <br>It's not enough that I take my time <br>You're still what I need baby <br>Soul baby, the one that I adore <br>The feeling never dies <br>The feeling never dies <br>The feeling never dies <br>The feeling never dies <br>The feeling never dies <br>The feeling never dies <br>Oh don't you know the feeling never dies]]></content><category term="Buckcherry" label="Buckcherry"/><category term="The Feeling Never Dies" label="The Feeling Never Dies"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Wish_To_Carry_On/</id><title>Buckcherry - Wish To Carry On - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:37:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:37:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Wish_To_Carry_On/" title="Buckcherry - Wish To Carry On - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A wish to carry on, a wish to carry on <br>A wish to carry on, a wish to carry on, carry on <br><br>It's time again to break down all the walls <br>To be aware and say what you want <br>A wish to carry on <br><br>Do you feel like you've had enough <br>Do you feel like you're out of touch <br>Somebody came and pushed you away <br>Closed all the doors and left you to pray <br>You made a plan to do what you can, but do you understand <br><br>It's time again to break down all the walls <br>To be aware and say what you want <br>A wish to carry on <br>It's time again to live without a doubt <br>To free your mind and forgive yourself <br>A wish to carry on <br><br>I wanna change my state of mind <br>I wanna tell somebody how I feel inside <br>How I feel inside <br><br>I'm broken, I'm battered, I looked at what matters <br>I know that the truth is much stronger than fiction <br><br>It's time again to break down all the walls <br>To be aware and say what you want <br>A wish to carry on <br>It's time again to live without a doubt <br>To free your mind and forgive yourself <br>A wish to carry on <br>A wish to carry on <br><br>It's time again to live without a doubt <br>To free your mind and forgive yourself <br>A wish to carry on <br>A wish to carry on <br>A wish to carry on <br>Carry on, carry on]]></content><category term="Buckcherry" label="Buckcherry"/><category term="Wish To Carry On" label="Wish To Carry On"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Tight_Pants/</id><title>Buckcherry - Tight Pants - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:37:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:37:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Tight_Pants/" title="Buckcherry - Tight Pants - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you move, when you shake, sometimes it's more than I can take <br>From your face, down to your toes, there's something I think you should know <br><br>I like your tight pants, t t t tight pants <br>I like the way that you bust at the seams <br>When you wiggle that thing <br>So work it till it's hard, pack it with a thong <br>When you put your tight pants on <br><br>There's a spark, there's splash, every time that you shake your ass <br>When you walk, I know you know, your tight pants gonna steal the show <br><br>I like your tight pants, t t t tight pants <br>I like the way that you bust at the seams <br>When you wiggle that thing <br>I like your tight pants, t t t tight pants <br>I like the way that you sting like a bee <br>cause your every man's dream <br>So work it till it's hard, pack it with a thong <br>When you put your tight pants on <br><br>Don't ya feel proud when we take 'em down baby you're not fucking around <br>How I'm gonna last with that sweet ass a picture perfect hour glass <br>I wanna get in your t t t tight pants <br>I wanna get in your t t t tight pants <br>I wanna get in your t t t tight pants <br>I wanna get in your t t t tight pants <br><br>I like your tight pants, t t t tight pants <br>I like the way that you bust at the seams <br>When you wiggle that thing <br>I like your tight pants, t t t tight pants <br>I like the way that you sting like a bee <br>cause your every man's dream <br><br>So don't ya feel proud when we take 'em down baby you're not fucking around]]></content><category term="Buckcherry" label="Buckcherry"/><category term="Tight Pants" label="Tight Pants"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Bring_It_On_Back/</id><title>Buckcherry - Bring It On Back - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:37:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:37:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buckcherry/Bring_It_On_Back/" title="Buckcherry - Bring It On Back - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bring it on back <br>Bring it on back <br>Bring it on back <br>Is this a chain reaction <br><br>I've got control of what you need <br>If you get closer I will show what I mean <br>I know you're doing what you can <br>But I'm going faster I got a rocket in my hands <br><br>I got the speed and I got the power <br>I got the pull, just give me an hour <br>Get up on that wheel I'm rolling <br><br>Bring it on back <br>Bring it on back <br>Bring it on back <br>Is this a chain reaction <br><br>I see it play out in my head I know the outcome <br>I'll bee the first one at the end <br>I know that someone's got to lose <br>I'm not that someone I'm an outlaw not a fool <br><br>I got the speed and I got the power <br>I got the pull just give me an hour <br>Get up on that wheel I'm rolling <br><br>Bring it on back <br>Bring it on back <br>Bring it on back <br>Is this a chain reaction <br>Bring it on back <br>Bring it on back <br>Bring it on back <br>One hit control the action <br><br>I got the speed and I got the power <br>I got the pull just give me an hour <br>Get up on that wheel I'm rolling <br><br>Bring it on back <br>Bring it on back <br>Bring it on back <br>Is this a chain reaction <br>Bring it on back <br>Bring it on back <br>Bring it on back <br>One hit control the action <br><br>Bring it on back]]></content><category term="Buckcherry" label="Buckcherry"/><category term="Bring It On Back" label="Bring It On Back"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kotiteollisuus/Vieraan_Vallan_Aurinko/</id><title>Kotiteollisuus - Vieraan Vallan Aurinko - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:37:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:37:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kotiteollisuus/Vieraan_Vallan_Aurinko/" title="Kotiteollisuus - Vieraan Vallan Aurinko - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Kaukaa jostain <br>humalainen nauru raikaa <br>herrat kai siella <br><br>viettavat taas laatuaikaa <br>Konjakki laikkyy <br>on rinnuksilla kaviaarit <br>pihvit maistuu <br>kansan veresta marinadit <br><br>Pelko ja vaino <br>ja jatkuvaa terrorin uhkaa <br>aurinko paistaa <br>mut paallemme sataa tuhkaa <br>Teurastusta <br>nimeen uskontojen, rauhan <br>haaveillemme <br>saamme kaivaa joukkohaudan <br><br>Taivaanranta loistaa <br>paistaa jonkun vieraan vallan aurinko <br>Turhaan sita paetaan, vastaa <br>loppuun asti kanssain kuljetko <br><br>Olet puolellamme <br>tai sitten olet meita vastaan <br>niiden kanssa <br>saat marssia vaikka paskaan <br>Olet tyosi tehnyt <br>nyt kajahtakoon niskalaukaus <br>hymyillen kuolet <br>viimeinkin koitti vapaus <br><br>Taivaanrantaa <br>kaksin taalla katselemme <br>periksi emme <br>anna ja me astelemme <br>rakkauteen, vihaan <br>saalivien katseittenne alla <br>niin suurta voimaa <br>ei ole edes Jumalalla]]></content><category term="Kotiteollisuus" label="Kotiteollisuus"/><category term="Vieraan Vallan Aurinko" label="Vieraan Vallan Aurinko"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kotiteollisuus/Pahuus_Ja_Viha/</id><title>Kotiteollisuus - Pahuus Ja Viha - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:37:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:37:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kotiteollisuus/Pahuus_Ja_Viha/" title="Kotiteollisuus - Pahuus Ja Viha - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ala muistele <br>vanhoja aikoja <br>nyt on uudet pykalassa <br><br>hihassa assa <br>ja kuviot uudet <br><br>ala avaa <br>Pandoran rasiaa <br>tikusta asiaa <br>ala tee <br>nyt on uudet mahdollisuudet <br><br>Voit korjata <br>satoa vaikket koskaan mitaan <br>edes kylvanyt <br>ja nyt <br>jo uusi sato itaa <br><br>Voit tehda mita vaan <br>kaivaa toivon hatusta <br>ja rahaa sataa taivaalta <br>ja leipa tulee poytaan <br>tekematta mitaan <br><br>Mitaan ei ole <br>kiveen kirjoitettu <br>Mitaan ei ole <br>kirkossa kuulutettu <br>Mikaan ei ole <br>varmempaa kuin epavarmuus <br>ikiaikainen <br>ihmisen vajavaisuus ja <br><br>Pahuus ja Viha <br><br>Maailma ryostaa <br>sen, joka nukahtaa <br>ja silmaa valvovaa <br>et voi paeta koskaan <br>et edes paskalla <br><br>Aikamme <br>kirous lankeaa <br>on vitun ankeaa <br>se nahda painettuna <br>lehtien kannessa <br><br>On kauneutta kaikkialla <br>mut on vaikeeta tunnustaa sita aaneen <br>Vaikka maailma onkin vinossa <br>se on valmis ja, kumarrun sen aareen <br>Katson taivasta, sen rantaa ja <br>katson yota, naen kauniin aamuruskon <br>Vaikka ihmiseen en luotakaan <br>luotan kuitenkin siihen, etta uskon <br>kauneuteen]]></content><category term="Kotiteollisuus" label="Kotiteollisuus"/><category term="Pahuus Ja Viha" label="Pahuus Ja Viha"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아날로그/옛사랑_이야기_With_김민경/</id><title>아날로그 - 옛사랑 이야기 (With 김민경) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:40:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:40:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EB%82%A0%EB%A1%9C%EA%B7%B8/%EC%98%9B%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC%EA%B8%B0_With_%EA%B9%80%EB%AF%BC%EA%B2%BD/" title="아날로그 - 옛사랑 이야기 (With 김민경) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아주 오래전 옛사랑 이야기 <br>날 떠나려 했던 너와 <br>널 잡으려 했던 나 <br>아주 오래전 옛사랑 이야기 <br>날 떠나려 했던 너와 <br>널 잡으려 했던 나 <br>돌이킬 수가 없단걸 알아 <br>너무 오랜시간 흘러버렸지 <br>가끔 네 생각에 잠못들때면 <br>옛사진 꺼내어 보곤 해 <br>돌아서 보면 좋은 기억들 <br>추억에 잠든 오늘 밤 <br>널 만나러 가는 길 <br>돌이킬 수가 없단걸 알아 <br>너무 오랜시간 흘러버렸지 <br>가끔 네 생각에 잠못들때면 <br>옛사진 꺼내어 보곤 해 <br>돌이킬 수가 없단걸 알아 <br>너무 오랜시간 흘러버렸지 <br>가끔 네 생각에 잠못들때면 <br>옛사진 꺼내어 보곤 해 <br>아주 오래전 옛사랑 이야기 <br>날 떠나려 했던 너와 <br>널 잡으려 했던 나 <br>]]></content><category term="아날로그" label="아날로그"/><category term="옛사랑 이야기 (With 김민경)" label="옛사랑 이야기 (With 김민경)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아날로그/사랑이란_With_이준석/</id><title>아날로그 - 사랑이란 (With 이준석) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:40:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:40:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EB%82%A0%EB%A1%9C%EA%B7%B8/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4%EB%9E%80_With_%EC%9D%B4%EC%A4%80%EC%84%9D/" title="아날로그 - 사랑이란 (With 이준석) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑이란건 <br>원래 이런거니까 <br>이별에 아파하고 <br>눈물 흘리고 <br>그 이별에 큰 아픔 마저 <br>사랑이라 부를 테니까 <br>그 이별은 잠시만 <br>이 사랑은 잠시만 <br>우린 생각할 <br>시간이 필요해 <br>멀리 떠나 있어도 <br>서로 보지 않아도 <br>내가 생각나는지 <br>사랑이란 이별은 <br>나는 견딜 수 있어 <br>다시 만날 수 있단 <br>믿음으로 채워져 <br>사랑이란 이별에 <br>그 큰 아픔마저도 <br>받아들여야 해 <br>그래야 사랑일 테니까 <br>사랑이란 이별은 <br>나는 견딜 수 있어 <br>다시 만날 수 있단 <br>믿음으로 채워져 <br>사랑이란 이별에 <br>그 큰 아픔마저도 <br>받아들여야 해 <br>그래야 사랑일 테니까 <br>다시 만나게 되면 <br>꼭 물어봐야지 <br>왜 나를 떠나갔냐고 <br>사랑이란 이별은 <br>나는 견딜 수 있어 <br>다시 만날 수 있단 <br>믿음으로 채워져 <br>사랑이란 이별에 <br>그 큰 아픔마저도 <br>받아들여야 해 <br>그래야 사랑일 테니까 <br>]]></content><category term="아날로그" label="아날로그"/><category term="사랑이란 (With 이준석)" label="사랑이란 (With 이준석)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아날로그/사랑이라_부르던_With_김영승/</id><title>아날로그 - 사랑이라 부르던 (With 김영승) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:40:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:40:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EB%82%A0%EB%A1%9C%EA%B7%B8/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4%EB%9D%BC_%EB%B6%80%EB%A5%B4%EB%8D%98_With_%EA%B9%80%EC%98%81%EC%8A%B9/" title="아날로그 - 사랑이라 부르던 (With 김영승) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑 때문에 웃고 울고 <br>꿈만 같았던 우리 시간 <br>오늘 밤 꿈에서 널 보면 <br>꼭 손 잡아 줘야지 <br>돌아갈 수 없단걸 알아 <br>그만큼 멀리 와버렸잖아 <br>다음 사랑이란 난 없어 <br>내겐 그 사람 뿐이야 <br>사랑한단 말도 못했어 <br>바보같이 울기만 했었지 <br>다시 사랑할 수 있다면 <br>잡은 손 놓지 않을게 <br>사랑이라 부르던 <br>그댈 만난 시간들 <br>점점 흐릿해져 <br>어떻게 살아가 <br>그리움만이 남아 있네 <br>사랑이라 부르던 <br>그댈 만난 시간들 <br>지워 버렸나봐 <br>떠오르지 않아 <br>그리움만이 남아 있네 <br>사랑이라 부르던 <br>그댈 만난 시간들 <br>점점 흐릿해져 <br>어떻게 살아가 <br>그리움만이 남아 있네 <br>사랑이라 부르던 <br>그댈 만난 시간들 <br>지워 버렸나봐 <br>떠오르지 않아 <br>그리움만이 남아 있네 <br>]]></content><category term="아날로그" label="아날로그"/><category term="사랑이라 부르던 (With 김영승)" label="사랑이라 부르던 (With 김영승)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김규학/책갈피_속의_여인/</id><title>김규학 - 책갈피 속의 여인 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:42:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:42:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EA%B7%9C%ED%95%99/%EC%B1%85%EA%B0%88%ED%94%BC_%EC%86%8D%EC%9D%98_%EC%97%AC%EC%9D%B8/" title="김규학 - 책갈피 속의 여인 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ <br>1, 책갈피속에 감춰둔여인 저하늘만 아는그사람 <br> 이름마저 가저가버린 냉정했던 그--여인아 <br> 알아도 알아--도 알수없는게 사랑이라 말을했던가 <br> 가끔식 꺼내본다 내--사랑아 소중했던 그세월 그추억 <br> 책갈피속에 여인--아 <br><br>2, 책갈피속에 감춰둔여인 저하늘만 아는그사람 <br> 이름마저 가저가버린 냉정했던 그--여인아 <br> 알아도 알아--도 알수없는게 사랑이라 말을했던가 <br> 가끔식 꺼내본다 내--사랑아 소중했던 그세월 그추억 <br> 책갈피속에 여인--아 <br> 책갈피속에 여인--아 .]]></content><category term="김규학" label="김규학"/><category term="책갈피 속의 여인" label="책갈피 속의 여인"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임경화/킬러들의_수다/</id><title>임경화 - 킬러들의 수다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:43:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:43:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EA%B2%BD%ED%99%94/%ED%82%AC%EB%9F%AC%EB%93%A4%EC%9D%98_%EC%88%98%EB%8B%A4/" title="임경화 - 킬러들의 수다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어둡고 캄캄한 작은 방에서 <br>잘 알지도 못하는 누군가에게 <br>이유없는 복수를 꿈꾸고 있는 <br>그대는 킬러 <br>친구하나 없는 세상에서 <br>홀로 외로이 잠들었을까 <br>오지않을 사랑을 꿈꾸고 있는 <br>외로운 킬러 <br>좋은 무기도 필요없어 <br>몇마디의 욕설과 <br>근거없는 비방이면 돼 <br>많은 시간도 필요없어 <br>그저 떠오르는 상상과 <br>그럴듯한 추측이면 돼 <br>그댄 silent killer <br>그댄 faceless killer <br>좋은 무기도 필요없어 <br>몇마디의 욕설과 <br>근거없는 비방이면 돼 <br>많은 시간도 필요없어 <br>그저 떠오르는 상상과 <br>그럴듯한 추측이면 돼 <br>그댄 silent killer <br>그댄 faceless killer <br>의미없는 킬러들의 수다는 그만 <br>이 좋은 태양아래 <br>의미없는 킬러들의 수다는 그만 <br>이 좋은 태양아래 <br>이 좋은 태양아래 <br>이 좋은 태양아래 <br>이 좋은 태양아래 <br>]]></content><category term="임경화" label="임경화"/><category term="킬러들의 수다" label="킬러들의 수다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/All_I_Wanna_Do/</id><title>박재범 - All I Wanna Do - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:47:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:47:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/All_I_Wanna_Do/" title="박재범 - All I Wanna Do - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Girl Pardon me <br>I don't mean to be rude <br>But I got some paper <br>wanna spend it on you <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>Bottles on deck baby <br>for you and your crew <br>Baby swing by girl <br>you should come through <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>Oh girl look at you baby <br>almost lookin flyer than me <br>And I got that gold Rollie with bezel <br>and Louie Viton on my body <br>And I know this shit <br>don't impress yah <br>So no bullshit girl nothin extra <br>Girl l ain't with playin games <br>I wanna take u home <br>I'm just bein frank <br>Oh yeah <br>I've been fantising <br>about you girl all night <br>Put yo panties to the side <br>if it's alright <br>Girl Pardon me <br>I don't mean to be rude <br>But I got some paper <br>wanna spend it on you <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>Bottles on deck baby <br>for you and your crew <br>Baby swing by girl <br>you should come through <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>Let's kick it lets kick it <br>A lil bit of drinkin and a lil bit kissin <br>Ace Chico on the 1s and 2s <br>Yeah He be spinnin this shit <br>They pop that pussy it <br>be purring like a kitten <br>Yeah boy yeah boy <br>its Seattle to Seoul <br>It's AO to the MG Jay <br>and Cha Cha to Malone <br>Bump this in yo stereo <br>or on your mobile phone <br>Don't got time for childs play <br>cause all of us our grown <br>Oh shit <br>Don't be a hatin ass bitch boy <br>Don't be a hatin ass bitch boy <br>I don't care <br>We gettin rich boy <br>me and my homies gettin rich boy <br>I want them good vibes only <br>It's just me and my homies <br>And of u don't know me <br>Then u better stay <br>the fuck outta my section <br>Unless you Tinashe <br>Girl Pardon me <br>I don't mean to be rude <br>But I got some paper <br>wanna spend it on you <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>Bottles on deck baby <br>for you and your crew <br>Baby swing by girl <br>you should come through <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>Yeah yeah this one is <br>for them sexy ladies <br>Yeah yeah haters only motivate me <br>Yeah yeah this one is <br>for them sexy ladies <br>Yeah yeah <br>Girl Pardon me <br>I don't mean to be rude <br>But I got some paper <br>wanna spend it on you <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>Bottles on deck baby <br>for you and your crew <br>Baby swing by girl <br>you should come through <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="All I Wanna Do" label="All I Wanna Do"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/Me_Like_Yuh/</id><title>박재범 - Me Like Yuh - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/Me_Like_Yuh/" title="박재범 - Me Like Yuh - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can only do right by yah <br>I will never go deceive yah <br>I'll even dye hair blonde for yah <br>I can be your Justin Bieber <br>Give me that work like you Riri <br>Girl pop it like 3D grant <br>wish's like genie's <br>Oh Lemme see that thing baby <br>Trust in me this is the moment <br>you've be waiting for girl <br>all your live <br>Tell your friends that you don't <br>need a ride home cause <br>I got you tonight <br>The ubers on the way cause <br>I had a couple drink's tonight <br>But I'm more drunk of your love <br>Baby I just can't get enough <br>So baby girl <br>Wake up wake up <br>Let's get it started <br>Stay up stay up girl I be on it <br>Don't go to bed unless <br>your going with me <br>Phone blowing up <br>I'mma let the hotline bling <br>Baby me like yuh <br>I'll make you feel so good <br>Do you just like I should <br>I hope you know it <br>I hope you know it <br>I hope you know it <br>I hope you know it <br>The way you working that motion <br>Girl you got me in a trance <br>It's like I'm crossing the ocean <br>Journey to another land <br>Lay you right up in the sand <br>Oh you pulling on my pants <br>I wanna rock yo rock yo body <br>Girl you got me so excited <br>Trust in me this is the moment <br>I've waiting for girl all my life <br>I have no other intentions <br>but just to go and do you right <br>We be surfing wave's together <br>in the moment up all night <br>It's an unforgettable love <br>Baby I just can't get enough <br>Wake up wake up <br>Let's get it started <br>Stay up stay up girl I be on it <br>Don't go to bed unless <br>your going with me <br>Phone blowing up <br>I'mma let the hotline bling <br>Baby me like yuh <br>I'll make you feel so good <br>Do you just like I should <br>I hope you know it <br>I hope you know it <br>I hope you know it <br>I hope you know it <br>Baby look into my eyes <br>We inside your paradise baby <br>Paradise <br>Feel the breeze up on your skin <br>Capture it so it'll never end <br>Never end <br>Baby me like yuh <br>I'll make you feel so good <br>Do you just like I should <br>Baby me like yuh <br>I'll make you feel so good <br>Do you just like I should <br>I hope you know it <br>I hope you know it <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="Me Like Yuh" label="Me Like Yuh"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/I_Got_This/</id><title>박재범 - I Got This - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/I_Got_This/" title="박재범 - I Got This - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All I know is money right now <br>All I know is money right now <br>All I know is yo booty <br>in that tight dress <br>Nice legs friday night ay <br>Shit is lookin lovely right now <br>I know nothing bout that fake shit <br>Nothing bout that fake shit <br>I know nothin bout actin <br>brand new to my crew yeah <br>Its all about the fam <br>and the homies I came up with <br>All I know is positive vibes <br>No negative shit <br>Thank god I'm alive <br>I inspire the kids <br>Yeah my whip is foreign <br>And my chick be callin <br>And u know i stay fly <br>So my kicks be soarin <br>Let me flex one time <br>Just one time <br>Alight I'm over that shit <br>Yeah I'm over that shit <br>Look at the way <br>I move man they know what it is <br>What my purpose is <br>What my purpose is <br>A few mill coo for now <br>cause I worked for this <br>But in time I wanna be <br>up in yo mind redefine <br>How u lookin at the world <br>and the way that shit is <br>Imma be the one <br>Imma be the one <br>Watch me <br>Don't worry I got this <br>All I know is this fuckin money <br>We made nothin into something <br>One thing I do know for sure <br>Imma be the one <br>Don't worry I got this <br>Don't worry I <br>Don't worry I <br>Don't worry I <br>Don't worry I got this <br>Don't worry I <br>Don't worry I <br>Don't worry I <br>If you don't know you bout to find out <br>I mean every word out of my mouth <br>Workin to hard to be <br>Underappreciated <br>I'm the same one even back <br>when they were hatin <br>Move after move motha fuck <br>is what we be makin <br>Everyday is our B-day yeah <br>We be cakin <br>But some see the vision now and <br>They try to creep around <br>But I ain't worried one bit <br>Cause my mama wake every morning <br>she be praying for me now <br>My family too big to take any days off <br>So we grindin like <br>tommorow is uncertain <br>Cause the future isn <br>something u can purchase <br>So we showin out <br>till they close the curtains <br>At times I wanna press rewind <br>to a much simpler time oh no <br>AOMG fo life yeah <br>I'm always on my grind oh no <br>Pickin the otherside <br>that's like suicide <br>We bout to lettem <br>all know muhfucka let's go <br>All I know is this fuckin money <br>We made nothin into something <br>One thing I do know for sure <br>Imma be the one <br>Don't worry I got this <br>Don't worry I <br>Don't worry I <br>Don't worry I <br>Don't worry I got this <br>Don't worry I <br>Don't worry I <br>Don't worry I <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="I Got This" label="I Got This"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/전화기를_꺼놔_Remix_Feat_ELO/</id><title>박재범 - 전화기를 꺼놔 Remix (Feat. ELO) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/%EC%A0%84%ED%99%94%EA%B8%B0%EB%A5%BC_%EA%BA%BC%EB%86%94_Remix_Feat_ELO/" title="박재범 - 전화기를 꺼놔 Remix (Feat. ELO) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[미안해 <br>오늘 섹시하게 화장이 잘됐네 <br>옷도 많이 신경 쓴 것 같은데 <br>근데 <br>그 화장이 지워지고 <br>그 예쁜 옷도 벗고 <br>네 심장이 멎고 <br>Girl I'm gonna love you <br>곧 땀으로 온몸이 젖게 될 거야 <br>Baby 미안해 <br>내 방안이 좀 지저분하지 <br>시간 있었는데 일부러 안 치웠지 <br>왜냐면 어차피 소용없지 <br>바로 이곳이 더럽혀지지 <br>네 속옷은 방바닥에 <br>하지만 넌 지금 내 침대 위 <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>아무도 방해할 수 없게 <br>일루와 바로 내 옆에 <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>우리만의 세상으로 떠나 <br>눈을 마주 보고 <br>입술 깨물어줘 <br>머리 잡아당겨 줘 <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>Turn it off one time for a real one <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>Turn it off one time for a real one <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>Ring ring ring ring oh stop <br>Oh no no no no <br>Ring ring ring ring oh stop <br>아무도 방해할 수 없게 yeah <br>일루와 바로 내 옆에 right now <br>Kissin and huggin and we fuckin <br>내 허리가 부러질 때까지 <br>Turn off your damn phone right now <br>이 밤이 깊어질수록 <br>우리 색은 더 짙어지네 <br>Babay come to daddy <br>우린 미쳐가지 yeah <br>So we need sex sex therapy <br>Tonight <br>I be like hol' up wait a minute girl <br>어디가 너무 쳐다봐서 미안해 <br>근데 네가 너무 섹시해서 <br>눈을 뗄 수가 없어 <br>Got Damn 보고 싶어 <br>너의 몸몸몸매 몸몸몸매 <br>너의 몸몸몸매 몸몸몸매 <br>너의 몸몸몸매 <br>So baby 전화기를 꺼놔 <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>아무도 방해할 수 없게 <br>일루와 바로 내 옆에 <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>우리만의 세상으로 떠나 <br>눈을 마주 보고 <br>입술 깨물어줘 <br>머리 잡아당겨 줘 <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>Turn it off one time for a real one <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>Turn it off one time for a real one <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>전화기를 꺼놔 <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="전화기를 꺼놔 Remix (Feat. ELO)" label="전화기를 꺼놔 Remix (Feat. ELO)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/FOREVER_WITH_DJ_ALE_MORA_Feat_Cha_Cha_Malone/</id><title>박재범 - FOREVER (WITH DJ ALE MORA) (Feat. Cha Cha Malone) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/FOREVER_WITH_DJ_ALE_MORA_Feat_Cha_Cha_Malone/" title="박재범 - FOREVER (WITH DJ ALE MORA) (Feat. Cha Cha Malone) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이게 현실이 맞는 건지 <br>내가 잠을 덜 깼는지 <br>예전에 받았던 상처들이 잊혀지네 <br>손을 쭉 뻗다가 보면 <br>구름이 잡힐 때가 있지 <br>I'm never comin down <br>새들이 내 얼굴 알기 전까지 baby oh <br>세월이 지나도 <br>숫자가 바뀌어도 <br>난 이 꿈꿀래 <br>Every day <br>Every night <br>Forever <br>빗방울 소리가 들리네 <br>내 맘을 씻어내 <br>해는 언젠간 뜰 테니 걱정이 없네 <br>바다가 우릴 갈라놔도 <br>언젠가는 만나게 되어있지 <br>Oh 운명이란 건 절대 무시 못 해 <br>세월이 지나도 <br>숫자가 바뀌어도 <br>난 이 꿈꿀래 <br>Every day <br>Every night <br>Forever <br>Forever I wanna stay <br>don't wanna come down <br>My heart's in a better place <br>when you're around <br>Bleeding out emptiness whenever <br>you're somewhere far from me <br>I don't wanna take away <br>from what you've made <br>I just wanna know the place <br>from where you came <br>No need to see the world <br>when it's right here in front of me <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="FOREVER (WITH DJ ALE MORA) (Feat. Cha Cha Malone)" label="FOREVER (WITH DJ ALE MORA) (Feat. Cha Cha Malone)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/2nd_THOTS/</id><title>박재범 - 2nd THOTS - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/2nd_THOTS/" title="박재범 - 2nd THOTS - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[At first I didn't see it girl <br>Couldn't see past that <br>smile and that fat ass <br>You said you don't party much <br>Acting like you came straight <br>outta math class <br>Said you never met someone like me <br>Someone like me baby baby <br>I was caught up in your <br>Honesty honesty baby baby <br>But then I started asking' about you <br>I found out some thing's about you <br>Girl tell me that this <br>isn't true oh no no no <br>I heard you know some of my crew <br>They told me the things that you do <br>I really hate to admit it but <br>Oh girl I change my mind <br>o0o girl you ain't my type <br>I seen this shit before <br>Oh girl your no surprise <br>Oh girl I change my mine <br>o0o girl you ain't my type <br>I seen this shit before <br>Oh girl your no surprise <br>So I'm having 2nd THOTS about you <br>You You <br>THOTS about you <br>You You <br>THOTS about you <br>You You <br>Girl I really want it <br>But the homie's said <br>They saw you at industry parties <br>Dressing have naked girl <br>working that body <br>Hanging round VIP <br>Only talking to the <br>ones poppin' bottles <br>And who look like they be ballin' <br>You said you didn't know who I am <br>But I see you followed me <br>on Instagram <br>Girl I see you scheming <br>with a f*ckin' plan <br>Tryna' take my $ <br>like you Uncle Sam <br>And I almost fell for it <br>But the homie's let me know <br>Let me know about you <br>So I'm a ignore it <br>Stay clear outta view <br>stay clear away from you <br>Can't ride in my Foreign <br>No first class trips <br>no shrimp wight he dip <br>This could've been you <br>Could've all been you <br>Could've all been you but <br>Oh girl I change my mind <br>o0o girl you ain't my type <br>I seen this shit before <br>Oh girl your no surprise <br>Oh girl I change my mine <br>o0o girl you ain't my type <br>I seen this shit before <br>Oh girl your no surprise <br>So I'm having 2nd THOTS about you <br>You You <br>THOTS about you <br>You <br>THOTS about you <br>You You <br>You looking' so good girl <br>I really wish you weren't but <br>The truth still is girl <br>You a fake a$$ h** <br>You a fake a$$ h** <br>We could've been together <br>I would've f*cked you so good girl <br>But it will never happen cause <br>You a fake a$$ h** <br>You a fake a$$ h** <br>You a fake a$$ h** <br>You a fake a$$ h** <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="2nd THOTS" label="2nd THOTS"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/Me_Like_Yuh_K_Feat_Hoody/</id><title>박재범 - Me Like Yuh (K) (Feat. Hoody) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/Me_Like_Yuh_K_Feat_Hoody/" title="박재범 - Me Like Yuh (K) (Feat. Hoody) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너무나 완벽한 밤이야 <br>네 움직임에 나는 미쳐 <br>조금 더 가까이 다가와 <br>애타게 기다리고 있어 <br>gimme that work like you Riri <br>girl 너는 내 genie <br>난 소원을 빌지 <br>oh lemme see that thing baby <br>지금 이순간이 <br>내가 기다려왔던 그 시간이야 <br>나의 몸짓을 보면 <br>니가 뭘 원하는지 감이 와 <br>춤을 계속 춰 <br>밤새도록 안 피곤하니까 <br>네 눈빛에 난 취했어 <br>영원히 안 깨고 싶어 <br>so baby girl <br>wake up wake up <br>let’s get it started <br>stay up stay up girl <br>I be on it <br>집 가지마 나랑은 괜찮아 <br>리드할게 so baby 따라와 <br>baby me like yuh <br>거부할 수 없는 <br>너의 지금 모습 <br>I hope you know it <br>I hope you know it <br>I hope you know it <br>I hope you know it <br>Woo <br>마치 홀린 것같이 <br>어느새 네 앞에 <br>서있어 나도 모르게 <br>이끌려 알 수 없게 <br>예상 못 한 건 아니야 <br>오늘만 기다렸어 <br>oh let me see that ting baby <br>지금 이 순간은 <br>어느 조명도 여긴 필요 없어 <br>우리 둘이 주고받는 <br>눈빛이면 충분하니까 <br>Woo 아까 네가 건넨 <br>술에 취한 게 아니라 <br>네 눈빛에 난 취했어 <br>영원히 안 깨고 싶어 <br>you know <br>wake up wake up <br>let’s get it started <br>stay up stay up girl <br>I be on it <br>집 가지마 나랑은 괜찮아 <br>리드할게 so baby 따라와 <br>baby me like yuh <br>거부할 수 없는 <br>너의 지금 모습 <br>I hope you know it <br>I hope you know it <br>I hope you know it <br>I hope you know it <br>시원한 바람이 느껴져 <br>여기서 난 영원하고 싶어 <br>하늘이 우릴 내려봐 <br>저 별이 빛나도 <br>your my star <br>my star <br>baby me like yuh <br>거부할 수 없는 <br>너의 지금 모습 <br>baby me like yuh <br>거부할 수 없는 <br>너의 지금 모습 <br>I hope you know it <br>I hope you know it <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="Me Like Yuh (K) (Feat. Hoody)" label="Me Like Yuh (K) (Feat. Hoody)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/AQUAMAN/</id><title>박재범 - AQUAMAN - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/AQUAMAN/" title="박재범 - AQUAMAN - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come meet me <br>in the hot tub girl <br>I'll bring the Champagne <br>and you just bring <br>that body here <br>and we can do our thang <br>girl we can make <br>sweet love all night <br>till the sun shines <br>in our face <br>come meet me <br>in the hot tub girl <br>the hot tub girl <br>oh girl the candles are lit <br>and all that's left is me <br>kissing your lips <br>and lemme call you mama <br>cause we about <br>to make a baby <br>and before I go put it in <br>I'll go underwater girl <br>just like a fish <br>and the way <br>I stay down there <br>you gon' think <br>I'm Aquaman <br>baby oh <br>when I'm all up in it <br>I'm gonna get lost up <br>in yo sea <br>and I know <br>when I'm finished <br>you'll return this favor <br>back for me <br>Come meet me <br>in the hot tub girl <br>I'll bring the Champagne <br>and you just bring <br>that body here <br>and we can do our thang <br>girl we can make sweet <br>love all night <br>till the sun shines <br>in our face <br>come meet me <br>in the hot tub girl <br>the hot tub girl <br>oh girl the candles are lit <br>and all that's left is me <br>kissing your lips <br>and lemme call you mama <br>cause we about to <br>make a baby <br>and before I go put it in <br>I'll go underwater girl <br>just like a fish <br>and the way <br>I stay down there <br>you gon' think <br>I'm Aquaman <br>I'll be deep in your legs <br>I'll be making you wet <br>like it's my super power <br>you gon' think I'm Aquaman <br>I’ll be surfing your waves <br>the way I'm holding my breath <br>like I have super power's <br>you gon' think I'm Aquaman <br>baby I know you were <br>waiting on a hero <br>so I'm here <br>to save yah babe <br>I wanna know your taste <br>I'll put in you in my entourage <br>I'm vincent chase your Aquaman <br>make you come all night baby <br>I wan't stop <br>have a conversation <br>with it a lil' sexy talk <br>ooh lets rock <br>I'm so hard <br>after we done <br>with this exchange baby girl <br>you and I can get down <br>like its our job <br>and I'm a be <br>the best you ever had <br>so please baby girl <br>lets make it last <br>make it last <br>make it last <br>Come meet me <br>in the hot tub girl <br>I'll bring the Champagne <br>and you just bring <br>that body here <br>and we can do our thang <br>girl we can make sweet <br>love all night <br>till the sun shines <br>in our face <br>come meet me <br>in the hot tub girl <br>the hot tub girl <br>oh girl the candles are lit <br>and all that's left is me <br>kissing your lips <br>and lemme call you mama <br>cause we about <br>to make a baby <br>and before I go put it in <br>I'll go underwater girl <br>just like a fish <br>and the way I stay down there <br>you gon' think I'm Aquaman <br>I'll be deep in your legs <br>I'll be making you wet <br>like it's my super power <br>you gon' think I'm Aquaman <br>I’ll be surfing your waves <br>the way I'm holding my breath <br>like I have super power's <br>you gon' think I'm Aquaman <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="AQUAMAN" label="AQUAMAN"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/DRIVE_Feat_GRAY/</id><title>박재범 - DRIVE (Feat. GRAY) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/DRIVE_Feat_GRAY/" title="박재범 - DRIVE (Feat. GRAY) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모든 일들이 잘 안 풀리고 있을 때 <br>스트레스가 어깨에 가득 차 있을 때 <br>너만 보면 맘이 너무나도 편해져 <br>모든 고민 모든 걱정들이 싹 없어져 <br>내 차에 올라타 <br>바람 쐬러 가 <br>밥 먹지 말고 와 <br>전부 내가 해줄게 <br>So Let's go for a drive <br>Oh yeah girl 내 몸이 힘들어 <br>Oh yeah girl 내 맘도 힘들어 <br>이걸 치료할 수 있는 건 <br>너 하나뿐 girl only you <br>데리러 갈게 girl 저녁때쯤 <br>언제나 내가 누굴 필요로 했을 때 <br>You was always there fa sho <br>내가 Jay-z면 너는 나의 Beyonce <br>Together we can run the world <br>어떤 차로 픽업 갈까 <br>Take the Foreign <br>내 옆에는 네 자리 <br>전세기에 태울 수 있을 때까지 <br>It's all for me and you <br>I'm a keep on hustling <br>모든 일들이 잘 안 풀리고 있을 때 <br>스트레스가 어깨에 가득 차 있을 때 <br>너만 보면 맘이 너무나도 편해져 <br>모든 고민 모든 걱정들이 싹 없어져 <br>내 차에 올라타 <br>바람 쐬러 가 <br>밥 먹지 말고 와 <br>전부 내가 해줄게 <br>So Let's go for a drive <br>우리 열심히 일했잖아 <br>오늘 어디든지 떠나자 <br>Me and you <br>Girl I'll show you the world <br>세계적인 커플 Victoria와 Beckham <br>나 알잖아 기대해도 돼 <br>백이면 백 노력할게 girl <br>No matter what <br>I'll always be there you superman <br>꼭 지켜줄게 baby <br>길 잃을 일 없어 <br>I'm yo GPS girl <br>어디든 다 갈게 <br>cause you are so special <br>다음 단계로 가자 <br>on to the next level <br>걱정은 다 제껴 <br>우리만의 영원한 여행 <br>모든 일들이 잘 안 풀리고 있을 때 <br>스트레스가 어깨에 가득 차 있을 때 <br>너만 보면 맘이 너무나도 편해져 <br>모든 고민 모든 걱정들이 싹 없어져 <br>내 차에 올라타 <br>바람 쐬러 가 <br>밥 먹지 말고 와 <br>전부 내가 해줄게 <br>So Let's go for a drive <br>Let's go for a drive <br>Let's go for a drive baby <br>In this foreign car baby <br>All night long <br>Let's go for a drive <br>Let's go for a drive baby <br>You're the only one <br>that I want my girl <br>I'm not a CEO <br>But I got a lot of money <br>So Let's make a video <br>해변 도로를 누비고 싶어 <br>Baby are you gonna stay the night <br>모든 일들이 잘 안 풀리고 있을 때 <br>스트레스가 어깨에 가득 차 있을 때 <br>너만 보면 맘이 너무나도 편해져 <br>모든 고민 모든 걱정들이 싹 없어져 <br>내 차에 올라타 <br>바람 쐬러 가 <br>밥 먹지 말고 와 <br>전부 내가 해줄게 <br>So Let's go for a drive <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="DRIVE (Feat. GRAY)" label="DRIVE (Feat. GRAY)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/곁에_있어주길/</id><title>박재범 - 곁에 있어주길 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/%EA%B3%81%EC%97%90_%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4%EC%A3%BC%EA%B8%B8/" title="박재범 - 곁에 있어주길 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쉽다고 말하면 <br>그건 거짓말이지 <br>다툰만큼 서로를 <br>더 아끼게 됐지 <br>옆에 있을 때는 <br>항상 난 모르지 <br>없을 때는 또 네가 <br>너무 보고 싶지 <br>수많은 실수를 통해서 <br>너 없이 의미 없단 걸 <br>깨달았지 <br>이제 영원히 <br>It’s just you and me <br>I don’t never wanna <br>let u go no no <br>너를 안아줄 때 몸이 떨려 <br>내 시간이 멈춰버려 <br>my baby <br>백 년이 지나도 약속해 <br>Please love me the same <br>the same the same <br>365일 Everyday <br>Girl 네 사랑이 필요해 <br>너 하나만으로 충분해 <br>왜냐면 <br>인기는 언젠가는 <br>떨어지게 돼 <br>번 돈도 어디선가는 <br>쓰게 돼있어 <br>날 찾던 사람들도 <br>떠나겠지 <br>하지만 baby 넌 <br>내 곁에 있어주길 <br>내 곁에 있어주길 <br>변하지 않고 영원히 <br>내 곁에 있어주길 <br>Baby 난 네 덕분에 <br>사람이 됐지 <br>네가 아니었다면 <br>생각조차 하기 싫어 <br>my baby <br>네가 날 멋있게 <br>만들어 baby <br>신이 우릴 허락 안 해도 <br>나는 끝까지 널 사랑할래 <br>네가 없는 것보다 <br>차라리 죽는 게 더 나아 <br>모든 게 무의미해져 <br>I don’t never wanna <br>let u go no no <br>세상이 돌고 해가 떠도 <br>내 시간이 멈춰버려 <br>my baby <br>백 년이 지나도 약속해 <br>Please love me the same <br>the same the same <br>365일 Everyday <br>Girl 네 사랑이 필요해 <br>너 하나만으로 충분해 <br>왜냐면 <br>인기는 언젠가는 <br>떨어지게 돼 <br>번 돈도 어디선가는 <br>쓰게 돼있어 <br>날 찾던 사람들도 <br>떠나겠지 <br>하지만 baby 넌 <br>내 곁에 있어주길 <br>내 곁에 있어주길 <br>변하지 않고 영원히 <br>내 곁에 있어주길 <br>baby baby baby <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="곁에 있어주길" label="곁에 있어주길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/사실은/</id><title>박재범 - 사실은 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/%EC%82%AC%EC%8B%A4%EC%9D%80/" title="박재범 - 사실은 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 헤어지고 잠들기 전에 <br>니가 그리워서 <br>눈물 흘린 적은 없어 <br>나 요즘 잘 나가 쉴 새 없이 <br>여자한테 연락 와서 <br>니 생각은 나지도 않아 <br>내 옆에 있는 빈자리 <br>원래 니가 주인이지 <br>그 자릴 여러 명으로 <br>채워 넣어버렸지 <br>나 괜찮아 괜찮아 <br>요즘 이뻐졌더라 <br>하나도 배 안 아파 <br>근데 girl 솔직히 말하자면 <br>내가 고백할게 있어 <br>진심이 정확히 <br>어떤 건지 지금 말해줄게 <br>사실은 girl 난 아직까지 <br>몇 시간씩이나 몰래 <br>니 인스타를 훔쳐봐 <br>사실은 girl 난 자주 그래 <br>아직까지 친구 통해 <br>니 소식을 물어봐 <br>Baby 좀 초라하지만 <br>내가 그러는 이유는 <br>사실은 girl <br>난 아직도 널 사랑해 <br>다른 남자랑 <br>데이트하고 있을 때 <br>장염에 걸리길 바래 <br>니가 볼 일을 다 봤을 때 <br>화장실에 화장지가 없길 바래 <br>충전기를 잃어버린 상태에서 <br>배터리 없길 바래 <br>핸드폰 떨어트려서 <br>액정 깨지길 바래 <br>마법에 걸린 그런 날에 <br>고통이 더욱더 심하길 바래 <br>근데 girl 솔직히 말하자면 <br>난 너 원망하지 않아 <br>너를 놓친 내가 한심해서 <br>내 자신을 더 원망해 <br>Oh girl 나 아직까지 땅을 치며 <br>매일매일 널 놓친 걸 후회해 <br>사실은 girl 나는 바보처럼 <br>니가 돌아오는 날만 <br>기다리게 돼 <br>Baby 좀 초라하지만 <br>내가 그러는 이유는 <br>사실은 girl <br>난 아직도 널 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 사랑해 <br>1 2 3 4 <br>girl 솔직히 말하자면 <br>니가 떠난 그날부터 <br>나 홀로 어쩔 줄 몰라서 <br>정신을 못 차리겠어 <br>Oh girl 니가 없는 삶을 <br>살아가는 건 <br>의미 없다고 생각해 <br>사실은 girl 난 자신 없어 <br>니가 아니라면 <br>나는 다시는 사랑 못해 <br>너 없인 난 초라해 <br>Oh girl 그 이유는 <br>니가 날 날 완성시켜줬어 <br>제발 돌아와 줘 <br>사실은 내가 괜히 찔려서 <br>너를 의심하고 더 못해줬어 <br>Im so sorry so sorry so sorry <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="사실은" label="사실은"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/Only_One_Feat_Raz_Simone/</id><title>박재범 - Only One (Feat. Raz Simone) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/Only_One_Feat_Raz_Simone/" title="박재범 - Only One (Feat. Raz Simone) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I be working all the time all the time <br>So baby if you fine <br>hit my line hit my line <br>Yeah I got money on my mind <br>so I'm looking for a dime <br>If you down to f*ck <br>we can wine and dine <br>But don't think that <br>your the only one only one <br>Buncha models in my DM <br>I see 'em every weekend <br>But still they <br>not the only one only one <br>Muhfucka you ain't wavy like me <br>boy I think I might be <br>The only one only one yeah <br>Only one only one <br>The only one only one yeah <br>Only one only one <br>They hate to see the boy win <br>Yeah They wanna bury me <br>But haters only motivate me <br>No they do no worry me <br>At the present time <br>I continue getting currency <br>I'm lookin' of that stop you <br>at the airport security <br>Bomb pussy bomb pussy <br>All my homies yeah <br>they ride with me ride with me <br>All them snake yeah <br>they lie to me lie to me <br>If you f*cking with me <br>vibe with me vibe with me <br>Seattle 2 Seoul what I rep yeah <br>every step <br>Every city I go SALUTE yeah <br>mutual respect <br>AOMG till the death <br>I don't be waiting in line <br>but you better believe that I'm next <br>And if you get up in my way <br>we stepping on yo neck <br>And if you don't know <br>Muhfucka you about to find out <br>We about to blow <br>Bigger than you ever could imagine <br>I be working all the time all the time <br>So baby if you fine <br>hit my line hit my line <br>Yeah I got money on my mind <br>so I'm looking for a dime <br>If you down to f*ck <br>we can wine and dine <br>But don't think that <br>your the only one only one <br>Buncha models in my DM <br>I see 'em every weekend <br>But still they not the only one only one <br>Muhfucka you ain't wavy like me <br>boy I think I might be <br>The only one only one yeah <br>Only one only one <br>The only one only one yeah <br>Only one only one <br>When I was just a youngin <br>I had only one <br>I was a virgin- got a baby <br>fuckin only once <br>My momma said be careful child <br>cuz you my only son <br>You got a crazy life to live <br>but you got only one <br>So I'm Hittin these Joogs on the low <br>Keepin my pole <br>Everywhere that I go <br>Snakes in this jungle around <br>Watchin my steps <br>Buildin relationships slow <br>People be fake for a while <br>But the more steps you get in <br>all that fake shit'll show <br>I keep that machete on me <br>Wackin these weeds <br>Keepin all of my grass low <br>Hit the block and then we mob out <br>Sleepin I don't know what that about <br>I'm from the district <br>where them choppers out <br>I'm from the city <br>they don't talk about <br>just hoppin out then we poppin out <br>Even cops around <br>They just chalk it down <br>And if you don't know <br>Muhfucka you about to find out <br>We about to blow <br>Bigger than you ever could imagine <br>I be working all the time all the time <br>So baby if you fine <br>hit my line hit my line <br>Yeah I got money on my mind <br>so I'm looking for a dime <br>If you down to f*ck <br>we can wine and dine <br>But don't think that <br>your the only one only one <br>Buncha models in my DM <br>I see 'em every weekend <br>But still they not the only one only one <br>Muhfucka you ain't wavy <br>like me boy I think I might be <br>The only one only one yeah <br>Only one only one <br>The only one only one yeah <br>Only one only one <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="Only One (Feat. Raz Simone)" label="Only One (Feat. Raz Simone)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/Alone_Tonight_Feat_Sik-K/</id><title>박재범 - Alone Tonight (Feat. Sik-K) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/Alone_Tonight_Feat_Sik-K/" title="박재범 - Alone Tonight (Feat. Sik-K) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>So can you come with me <br>I don't wanna be alone to night <br>Can you keep me company <br>I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>So can you come with me <br>I don't wanna be alone to night <br>Can you keep me company <br>I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>No <br>Just got done with a show tonight <br>So much goin on in my life <br>I don't know if I'm wrong or right <br>I got mufuckas prayin prayin I fall <br>Women women that wanna <br>take my dough <br>But I'm focused focused <br>I don't notice notice <br>I'm still glowing glowin look at me ball <br>Ballin like Lebron I'm the king <br>I won't ever quit <br>I put that on everything <br>My names known worldwide <br>But I still need someone by my side <br>Oh baby r u down to ride <br>Lemme know <br>I don't gotta a lotta time cause <br>I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>So can you come with me <br>I don't wanna be alone to night <br>Can you keep me company <br>I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>So can you come with me <br>I don't wanna be alone to night <br>Can you keep me company <br>Ay ay you don't bring your man here <br>Ay 아주 좋아 오늘은 <br>내가 네 애인이야 <br>Ay ay ay Let me let me <br>spend my paper <br>뭘 하고 싶은지는 <br>I ain't gotta mention <br>Maybe maybe you can <br>spend your time on me <br>난 너랑 작업하러 <br>같이 갈래 작업실로 <br>네 Double D가 대신 대답하지 씰룩 <br>몇 시간만 지나면 네 몸은 see thru <br>I don't want no lonely nights <br>I can do you proper <br>어서 맘을 정해 <br>난 시간이 많진 않아 <br>Don't want no lonely nights ay <br>Baby you are my type <br>You don't want no lonely nights too <br>You gon love this pipe yah <br>I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>So can you come with me <br>I don't wanna be alone to night <br>Can you keep me company <br>I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>I be workin workin working <br>getting no sleep <br>So my momma worried <br>worried worried bout me <br>I'm tryna put whole team on <br>we hustlin we grindin all day <br>Like Kanye like we got nun to eat <br>Time be flying by I'm the kinna guy <br>Riding for my side it's a homicide <br>When I'm on the mic <br>they just cry and cry <br>We couldn't see eye to eye <br>if you were goliath height <br>I'm all the way the up oh <br>I'm not tryna fuck no <br>I just wanna love you <br>It's that turn down <br>Sip some henny in yo room now <br>Netflix is soundin real coo now <br>Resting my head right on u now <br>I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="Alone Tonight (Feat. Sik-K)" label="Alone Tonight (Feat. Sik-K)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/SOLO_Feat_Hoody/</id><title>박재범 - SOLO (Feat. Hoody) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/SOLO_Feat_Hoody/" title="박재범 - SOLO (Feat. Hoody) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby 솔직 할게 yeah <br>나 조금 당황했어 yeah <br>이런 경우는 처음이야 나한테 yeah <br>지금 어쩔 줄을 몰라 nah <br>나 원래 반대 입장이야 <br>나를 만나려고 다들 줄 서 있는데 <br>근데 네가 나타나서 멘붕 상태야 <br>내 자존심 갖다 버리고 와 <br>I don't care 널 갖고 싶어 baby <br>우리 부모님이 반대하셔도 <br>친구들이 바보라고 해도 <br>I don't care 널 갖고 싶어 baby <br>솔로이길 바래 <br>나도 얼마 전에 싱글 됐으니까 <br>너를 너무 원해 <br>제발 솔로이길 바래 <br>내가 바쁘더라도 <br>네가 원한다면 바로 은퇴할게 <br>제발 솔로이길 바래 <br>솔로이길 바래 솔로이길 바래 yeah <br>솔로이길 바래 솔로이길 바래 <br>솔로이길 바래 yeah <br>You got me like o0o0 <br>You got me like o0o0 <br>You got me like o0o0 <br>You got me like o0o0 <br>Single lady 누가 물을 땐 <br>난 그냥 거짓말로 아니라 했어 baby <br>oh 하지만 내 앞에 <br>진심인듯한 널 볼 땐 <br>Baby I'm solo from now on <br>모르겠어 진심인 건지 <br>한순간의 착각인 건지 <br>I don't know 왜 날 갖고 싶어 <br>Baby <br>얼마나 많은 여자들이 <br>널 만나려고 줄을 서 있는지 <br>I do know 그래서 불안해 <br>다 괜찮아 그냥 솔로이길 바래 girl <br>Aladdin and Jasmine <br>I'll show u a whole new world <br>매직 카펫 위에 올라타 girl <br>걱정하지 마 따라와 baby <br>보여줄 게 많은 걸 <br>콩깍지는 아닌 것 같아 <br>이름도 모르지만 baby 사랑해 <br>Nothing on you <br>I just wanna know yo name <br>첫 번째는 아니어도 <br>마지막이 되어줘 babay <br>솔로이길 바래 <br>나도 얼마 전에 싱글 됐으니까 <br>너를 너무 원해 <br>제발 솔로이길 바래 <br>내가 바쁘더라도 <br>네가 원한다면 바로 은퇴할게 <br>제발 솔로이길 바래 <br>솔로이길 바래 솔로이길 바래 yeah <br>솔로이길 바래 솔로이길 바래 <br>솔로이길 바래 yeah <br>You got me like o0o0 <br>You got me like o0o0 <br>You got me like o0o0 <br>You got me like o0o0 <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="SOLO (Feat. Hoody)" label="SOLO (Feat. Hoody)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/Limousine_Feat_KRNFX/</id><title>박재범 - Limousine (Feat. KRNFX) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/Limousine_Feat_KRNFX/" title="박재범 - Limousine (Feat. KRNFX) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You better wear that dress I like <br>It's a special kinda night <br>Imma take u for a ride <br>Hop in <br>Driver you can take yo time <br>Put that classic R and B on <br>Po' you something u can sip on <br>Cause we gon' get it on tonight <br>Champagne glasses on the door <br>Baby you can get comfortable <br>Don't worry I'll be good to you <br>Get used to this like its nothing new <br>It's just us two on the road <br>Driver put up the window please <br>Baby girl come close to me <br>The parties startin in here to night <br>In the Limousine <br>We be dancin We be movin <br>In the Limousine <br>Everybody feelin' good up <br>In the Limousine <br>Where we nasty but we classy <br>In the Limousine <br>Get loose now <br>Girl you know how I get down <br>Girl u know what's up <br>Get loose now <br>Girl you know how I get down <br>Girl u know what's up <br>There no need to go to clubs <br>We got everything u want <br>So baby girl lets have some fun <br>Until the mornin comes <br>You and me have that neon glow <br>Leather seats yeah <br>they feel so smooth <br>All we need is a stripper pole <br>Theres one thing I wanna know <br>Are we gonna get it on baby <br>I wanna make u mine baby <br>It's just between me and you <br>What happens here stays here <br>Girl you know what's up <br>In the Limousine <br>We be dancin We be movin <br>In the Limousine <br>Everybody feelin' good up <br>In the Limousine <br>Where we nasty but we classy <br>In the Limousine <br>Get loose now <br>Girl you know how I get down <br>Girl u know what's up <br>Get loose now <br>Girl you know how I get down <br>Girl u know what's up <br>We up in the Limousine right now <br>Baby take u round the town <br>u know my style <br>Tuxedo all black <br>and my pockets on fat <br>All the haters fall back <br>when they see us prowl <br>Feelin like its prom night <br>Between me and you its on right on <br>sight the dom on ice <br>I got that pipe my talk so nice <br>I might get u naked then <br>I'll be on u like white on rice <br>Just know the car aint broke <br>down if we pull ova <br>We can take few shots <br>like theres do ovas <br>We can get it poppin right now <br>the driver sneak peakin <br>through his back mirror <br>I don't ever act different <br>I'll never switch it up on ya <br>So don't u ever switch it up on me <br>Ooh la baby this nights <br>bout to get crazy <br>Up in this limo yeah you my lady <br>In the Limousine <br>We be dancin We be movin <br>In the Limousine <br>Everybody feelin' good up <br>In the Limousine <br>Where we nasty but we classy <br>In the Limousine <br>Get loose now <br>Girl you know how I get down <br>Girl u know what's up <br>Get loose now <br>Girl you know how I get down <br>Girl u know what's up <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="Limousine (Feat. KRNFX)" label="Limousine (Feat. KRNFX)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/All_I_Wanna_Do_K_Feat_Hoody_Loco/</id><title>박재범 - All I Wanna Do (K) (Feat. Hoody, Loco) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/All_I_Wanna_Do_K_Feat_Hoody_Loco/" title="박재범 - All I Wanna Do (K) (Feat. Hoody, Loco) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Girl 말해줘 네 마음 바로 지금 <br>Baby 같이 올라가자 하늘 위로 <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>너의 몸매 그린 것만 같아 미술 <br>오늘 의상처럼 네 마음도 씨쓰루 <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>Girl 뭐가 중요한지 <br>baby 바로 말해줄게 <br>나 지금 5천만원짜리 시계 찼지만 <br>나는 너를 훨씬 아끼지 babe <br>네가 원한다면 안 찰게 <br>허세 따위는 안 통하니까 <br>넌 정말 신기한 여자 <br>나를 노력하게 만드니까 <br>baby oh yeah <br>우리 둘의 밤을 상상했어 <br>girl all night <br>몸에 타투를 보여줘 <br>If it's alright <br>Girl 말해줘 네 마음 바로 지금 <br>Baby 같이 올라가자 하늘 위로 <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>너의 몸매 그린 것만 같아 미술 <br>오늘 의상처럼 네 마음도 씨쓰루 <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>어떡해 내 맘에 네가 들어오려 해 <br>쉽게 빠질까 봐 위험해 보여 <br>조심하려 할 때 <br>움직여지지 않아 <br>날 보는 네 시선이 내 몸을 감아 <br>하나로 얽혀 너와 나 <br>이제부턴 아무도 풀지 못해 <br>뻔하지 않게 우연같이 만나 baby <br>서로에게 녹아들어 <br>오늘밤 우리 기분은 저 하늘 구름 위 <br>네 몸에 타투를 보여줘 <br>이미 내 맘은 준비되어있어 <br>Boy 말할게 내 마음 바로 지금 <br>그래 같이 올라가자 하늘 위로 <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>네가 원한대로 내 대답은 Me too <br>이제부터 널 부르게 해줘 My boo <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>내가 하고 싶은 모든 것 뒤엔 <br>너와 함께 가 생략 되어 있지 <br>요즘 인기 많은 <br>교포오빠들과는 달라 <br>김치 향기가 배어있지 <br>덕분에 난 몰아 호랑이 <br>택 달린 옷은 방에 쌓여가고 있어 <br>밤에 입어 편하게 <br>이젠 너는 나 나는 너로 구분 짓고 <br>ALL I WANNA DO 라고 말해 편하게 <br>너의 옆자리를 상상할 거고 <br>그곳에는 내가 있게 될 거야 <br>그리고 너에 대해 장담하건대 <br>뭐든 할 수 있을 거라고 믿게 될 거야 <br>Girl 말해줘 네 마음 바로 지금 <br>Baby 같이 올라가자 하늘 위로 <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>너의 몸매 그린 것만 같아 미술 <br>오늘 의상처럼 네 마음도 씨쓰루 <br>All I wanna do is kick it with you <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="All I Wanna Do (K) (Feat. Hoody, Loco)" label="All I Wanna Do (K) (Feat. Hoody, Loco)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/Feature_Feat_Cha_Cha_Malone/</id><title>박재범 - Feature (Feat. Cha Cha Malone) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/Feature_Feat_Cha_Cha_Malone/" title="박재범 - Feature (Feat. Cha Cha Malone) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Alright alright <br>Baby you're the baddest <br>And you got me worked up <br>Ready to be a savage to ya <br>I've been waiting patiently <br>For you to take it off <br>I know you didn't come <br>Just to drink all of my cabernet <br>Hope what's on my mind is on your mind <br>Just let it marinate <br>Don't wanna waste no time <br>I know I wanna be inside <br>Oh ooh yeah <br>What I wanna do yeah <br>Wanna grab you by your booty <br>Girl let's shoot a movie <br>Baby you know <br>Once we get started <br>I can go on and on <br>And you'll be hitting <br>all them high notes <br>Featuring on my song <br>And it's like <br>Duh duh duh doo <br>Me and you are music making <br>Duh duh duh doo <br>Sexual collaboration <br>Duh doo da doo <br>Duh da doo <br>Duh doo da doo <br>Duh da doo <br>Duh doo da doo <br>Duh da doo <br>Harmonizing with your body <br>This gon' be your favorite song <br>Alright alright <br>Deeper than 10,000 leagues <br>But I'ma take you higher <br>higher than them Cali trees <br>Imma be the one <br>make you forget 'em all <br>All these ni**as try to 1-up me <br>But you don't take them calls <br>They ain't getting' to you nah <br>No feature from you nah <br>You're singing only for me yeah <br>And you know I feel like a winner <br>Every time I'm on you babe <br>on you babe <br>Oh ooh yeah <br>What I wanna do yeah <br>Wanna grab you by your booty <br>your booty <br>Lay it on me lay it on me <br>Once we get started <br>I can go on and on <br>And you'll be hitting <br>all them high notes <br>Featuring on my song <br>And it's like <br>Me and you are music making <br>Sexual collaboration <br>Duh doo da doo <br>Duh da doo <br>Duh doo da doo <br>Duh da doo <br>Duh doo da doo <br>Duh da doo <br>Harmonizing with your body <br>This gon' be your favorite song <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="Feature (Feat. Cha Cha Malone)" label="Feature (Feat. Cha Cha Malone)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/I_Dont_Disappoint/</id><title>박재범 - I Don`t Disappoint - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/I_Dont_Disappoint/" title="박재범 - I Don`t Disappoint - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been working all <br>working all day girl <br>Come and take this stress <br>take this stress away girl <br>So much bull shit <br>I need to get away from <br>A sex trip that's what <br>I need an erotic vacation <br>You got just what I like girl <br>So I'mma come and get it baby <br>Don't you go anywhere <br>stay right there <br>Sorry to keep you waiting girl <br>Baby baby baby <br>I've been thinking of you <br>I can't wait to go and fuck you right <br>Baby baby baby you know <br>I'm in that mood <br>To do nasty thing's <br>all through the night <br>I'm outchea makin this money <br>But we'll be makin love soon enough <br>This gon' be that <br>brag to your friends <br>about how good it was fuck <br>This gonna be that bed movin' all <br>across the room sexin' nothing <br>but the best girl <br>Expect nothing less from me <br>I don't disappoint <br>girl you know this here <br>I don't disappoint <br>girl you know this here <br>You'll get all the point's <br>when score this here <br>I don't disappoint <br>girl you know this here <br>Go put it on the see through <br>lingerie girl <br>You can be my lil cabaret girl <br>Treat that pole like a <br>9 to 5 work it yeah <br>I'mma beat it up no mercy yeah <br>I ain't finna front <br>I'm real thirsty yeah <br>You can be rough <br>just don't hurt me yeah <br>When it get to be that time <br>girl you always down to ride <br>Girl you my <br>Laumbourgini mercy yeah <br>You got just what I like girl <br>So I'mma come and get it baby <br>Don't you go anywhere <br>stay right there <br>Sorry to keep you waiting girl <br>Baby baby baby <br>I've been thinking of you <br>I can't wait to go and fuck you right <br>Baby baby baby you know <br>I'm in that mood <br>To do nasty thing's <br>I'm outchea makin this money <br>But we'll be makin love soon enough <br>This gon' be that <br>brag to your friends <br>about how good it was fuck <br>This gonna be that bed movin' all <br>across the room sexin' nothing <br>but the best girl <br>Expect nothing less from me <br>I don't disappoint <br>girl you know this here <br>I don't disappoint <br>girl you know this here <br>You'll get all the point's <br>when score this here <br>I don't disappoint <br>girl you know this here <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="I Don`t Disappoint" label="I Don`t Disappoint"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재범/Replay/</id><title>박재범 - Replay - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/Replay/" title="박재범 - Replay - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[일단 문부터 꽉 잠가 girl <br>이 노랜 19금이니까 <br>지금부터 집중해 <br>잘 들어 baby 내가 하는 말 <br>네 티부터 벗어 <br>바지도 벗어줘 <br>속옷은 벗지 마 <br>Bra랑 Panties는 내버려 둬 <br>너를 조금 더 <br>애타게 하고 싶어 <br>움직이지 말고 두 눈을 감고 있어 <br>내 타투가 네 몸에 닿는 걸 상상해 <br>난 서 있으니까 내 몸을 더 감상해 <br>오늘 밤 네 침대를 <br>바다로 만들고 싶어 <br>Back stroke <br>Front stoke <br>빠지고 싶어 빠지고 싶어 <br>Oh no 외로워지면 <br>이 노래를 틀어 <br>대신 너만 들어 너만 들어 <br>Oh This is for your ears only <br>너 혼자서 들어야만 해 baby <br>밤새도록 밤새도록 반복해 <br>밤새도록 밤새도록 반복해 <br>밤새도록 밤새도록 반복해 <br>느낌이 올 때까지 <br>Put this shit on REPLAY <br>]]></content><category term="박재범" label="박재범"/><category term="Replay" label="Replay"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하찌/하늘의_선물/</id><title>하찌 - 하늘의 선물 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%B0%8C/%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%84%A0%EB%AC%BC/" title="하찌 - 하늘의 선물 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하늘에서 내리고 <br>세상에게 바치고 <br>감탄하는 소리로 <br>당신 탄생 축하하오 <br>유쾌하게 달리는 <br>쾌사로다 쾌보다 <br>즐거움만 가득한 <br>애기 웃음 당신의 눈 <br>감사합니다 감사합니다 <br>당신의 아름다움 길이 빛날 <br>하늘에서 내리고 <br>세상에게 바치고 <br>감탄하는 소리로 <br>당신 탄생 축하하오 <br>감사합니다 감사합니다 <br>당신의 아름다움 길이 빛날 <br>하늘에서 내리고 <br>세상에게 바치고 <br>감탄하는 소리로 <br>당신 탄생 축하하오 <br>당신 탄생 축하하오 <br>당신 탄생 축하하오 <br>]]></content><category term="하찌" label="하찌"/><category term="하늘의 선물" label="하늘의 선물"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주환/This_Time_The_Dreams_On_Me/</id><title>김주환 - This Time The Dream`s On Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%ED%99%98/This_Time_The_Dreams_On_Me/" title="김주환 - This Time The Dream`s On Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Somewhere someday <br>We'll be close together wait and see <br>Oh by the way <br>This time the dream's on me <br>You'll take my hand <br>And you'll look at me adoringly <br>But as things stand <br>This time the dream's on me <br>It would be fun to be certain <br>That I'm the one <br>To know that I at least <br>Supply the shoulder you cry upon <br>To see you through <br>Till you're everything <br>you want to be <br>It can't be true <br>But this time the dream's on me <br>It would be fun to be certain <br>That I'm the one <br>To know that I at least <br>Supply the shoulder you cry upon <br>To see you through <br>Till you're everything <br>you want to be <br>It can't be true <br>But this time the dream's on me <br>]]></content><category term="김주환" label="김주환"/><category term="This Time The Dream`s On Me" label="This Time The Dream`s On Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주환/Its_All_Right_With_Me/</id><title>김주환 - It`s All Right With Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%ED%99%98/Its_All_Right_With_Me/" title="김주환 - It`s All Right With Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's the wrong time <br>and the wrong place <br>Though your face is charming <br>it's the wrong face <br>It's not her face <br>but such a charming face <br>That it's all right with me <br>It's the wrong song <br>in the wrong style <br>Though your smile is lovely <br>it's the wrong smile <br>It's not her smile <br>lovely smile <br>That it's all right with me <br>You can't know how happy <br>I am that we met <br>I'm strangely attracted to you <br>There's someone <br>I'm trying so hard to forget <br>Don't you want to forget <br>someone too <br>the wrong game <br>with the wrong chips <br>Though your lips are tempting <br>they're the wrong lips <br>They're not her lips <br>but they're such tempting lips <br>That if some night <br>you are free <br>all right it's all right <br>all right with me <br>You can't know how happy <br>I am that we met <br>I'm strangely attracted to you <br>There's someone <br>I'm trying so hard to forget <br>Don't you want to forget <br>someone too <br>It's the wrong game <br>with the wrong chips <br>Though your lips are tempting <br>they're the wrong lips <br>They're not her lips <br>but they're such tempting lips <br>That if some night <br>you are free <br>all right it's all right <br>it's all right with me <br>]]></content><category term="김주환" label="김주환"/><category term="It`s All Right With Me" label="It`s All Right With Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주환/So_In_Love/</id><title>김주환 - So In Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:48:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:48:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%ED%99%98/So_In_Love/" title="김주환 - So In Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Strange dear but true dear <br>When I'm close to you dear <br>The stars fill the sky <br>So in love with you am I <br>Even without you <br>My arms fold about you <br>You know darling why <br>So in love with you am I <br>In love with the night mysterious <br>The night when you first were there <br>In love with my joy delirious <br>When I knew that you could care <br>So taunt me and hurt me <br>Deceive me desert me <br>I'm yours till I die <br>So in love with you am I <br>In love with the night mysterious <br>The night when you first were there <br>In love with my joy delirious <br>When I knew that you could care <br>So taunt me and hurt me <br>Deceive me desert me <br>I'm yours till I die <br>So in love So in love <br>So in love with you my love am I <br>]]></content><category term="김주환" label="김주환"/><category term="So In Love" label="So In Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주환/Ive_Got_You_Under_My_Skin/</id><title>김주환 - I`ve Got You Under My Skin - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:49:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:49:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%ED%99%98/Ive_Got_You_Under_My_Skin/" title="김주환 - I`ve Got You Under My Skin - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've got you under my skin <br>I've got you deep in the heart of me <br>So deep in my heart that <br>you're really a part of me <br>I've got you under my skin <br>I tried so not to give in <br>I said to myself this affair <br>never will go so well <br>But why should I try to resist <br>when baby I know so well <br>I've got you under my skin <br>I'd sacrifice anything <br>come what might <br>For the sake of having you near <br>In spite of a warning voice <br>that comes in the night <br>And repeat repeats in my ear <br>Don't you know little fool <br>You never can win <br>Use your mentality <br>Wake up to reality <br>But each time that I do <br>Just the thought of you <br>Makes me stop before I begin <br>Because I've got you under my skin <br>I'd sacrifice anything <br>come what might <br>For the sake of having you near <br>In spite of a warning voice <br>that comes in the night <br>And repeats how it yells in my ear <br>Don't you know you fool <br>You never can win use your mentality <br>wake up to reality <br>But each time that I do <br>Just the thought of you <br>Makes me stop before I begin <br>'Cause I've got you under my skin <br>]]></content><category term="김주환" label="김주환"/><category term="I`ve Got You Under My Skin" label="I`ve Got You Under My Skin"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주환/Ive_Got_The_World_On_A_String_With_강예은/</id><title>김주환 - I`ve Got The World On A String (With 강예은) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:49:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:49:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%ED%99%98/Ive_Got_The_World_On_A_String_With_%EA%B0%95%EC%98%88%EC%9D%80/" title="김주환 - I`ve Got The World On A String (With 강예은) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've got the world on a string <br>sittin' on a rainbow <br>Got the string around my finger <br>What a world <br>what a life <br>I'm in love <br>I've got a song that I sing <br>I can make the rain go <br>anytime I move my finger <br>Lucky me <br>can't you see <br>I'm in love <br>Life is a beautiful thing <br>as long as I hold the string <br>I'd be a silly so and so <br>if I should ever let go <br>I've got the world on a string <br>sittin' on a rainbow <br>Got the string around my finger <br>What a world <br>what a life <br>I'm in love <br>Life is a beautiful thing <br>as long as I hold the string <br>I'd be a silly so and so <br>if I should ever let go <br>I've got the world on a string <br>sittin' on a rainbow <br>Got the string around my finger <br>What a world <br>what a life <br>I'm in love <br>]]></content><category term="김주환" label="김주환"/><category term="I`ve Got The World On A String (With 강예은)" label="I`ve Got The World On A String (With 강예은)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주환/Its_Only_A_Paper_Moon/</id><title>김주환 - It`s Only A Paper Moon - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:49:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:49:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%ED%99%98/Its_Only_A_Paper_Moon/" title="김주환 - It`s Only A Paper Moon - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It is only a paper moon <br>Sailing over a cardboard sea <br>But it wouldn't be make believe <br>If you believed in me <br>Yes it's only a canvas sky <br>Hangin' over a muslin tree <br>But it wouldn't be make believe <br>If you believed in me <br>Without your love <br>It's a honky tonk parade <br>Without your love <br>It's a melody played <br>in a penny arcade <br>It's a Barnum and Bailey world <br>Just as phony as it can be <br>But it wouldn't be make believe <br>If you believed in me <br>Without your love <br>It's a honky tonk parade <br>Without your love <br>It's a melody played <br>in a penny arcade <br>It's a Barnum and Bailey world <br>Just as phony as it can be <br>But it wouldn't be make believe <br>If you believed in me <br>If you believed in me <br>]]></content><category term="김주환" label="김주환"/><category term="It`s Only A Paper Moon" label="It`s Only A Paper Moon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주환/The_Gal_That_Got_Away/</id><title>김주환 - The Gal That Got Away - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:49:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:49:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%ED%99%98/The_Gal_That_Got_Away/" title="김주환 - The Gal That Got Away - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The night is bitter <br>The stars have lost their glitter <br>The winds get colder <br>And suddenly you're older <br>And all because of the gal <br>that got away <br>No more her eager call <br>The writing's on the wall <br>The dreams you dreamed <br>Have all gone astray <br>The gal that won you <br>Has run off and undone you <br>That great beginning <br>Has seen the final inning <br>Don't know what happened <br>It's all a crazy game <br>No more that all time thrill <br>For you've been through the mill <br>And never a new love <br>Will be the same <br>Good riddance goodbye <br>Every trick of hers you're on to <br>But fools will be fools <br>And where's she gone to <br>The road gets rougher <br>It's lonelier and tougher <br>With hope you burn up <br>Tomorrow she may turn up <br>There's just no let up <br>The live long night and day <br>Ever since this world began <br>There is nothing sadder than <br>A lose lost loser <br>Looking for the gal that got away <br>Good riddance goodbye <br>Every trick of hers you're on to <br>But fools will be fools <br>And where's she gone to <br>The road gets rougher <br>It's lonelier and tougher <br>With hope you burn up <br>Tomorrow she may turn up <br>There's just no let up <br>The live long night and day <br>Ever since this world began <br>There is nothing sadder than <br>A lose lost loser <br>Looking for the gal that got away <br>]]></content><category term="김주환" label="김주환"/><category term="The Gal That Got Away" label="The Gal That Got Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주환/Everytime_We_Say_Goodbye/</id><title>김주환 - Everytime We Say Goodbye - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:49:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:49:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%ED%99%98/Everytime_We_Say_Goodbye/" title="김주환 - Everytime We Say Goodbye - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Every time we say we say goodbye <br>I die a little <br>Every time we say goodbye <br>I wonder why a little <br>Why the gods above me <br>who must be in the know <br>Think so little of me <br>they allow you to go <br>When you're near <br>there's such an air <br>of spring about it <br>I can hear a lark somewhere <br>begin to sing about it <br>There's no love song finer <br>but how strange the change <br>from major to minor <br>every time we say goodbye <br>When you're near <br>there's such an air <br>of spring about it <br>I can hear a lark somewhere <br>begin to sing about it <br>There's no love song finer <br>but how strange the change <br>from major to minor <br>every time we say goodbye <br>]]></content><category term="김주환" label="김주환"/><category term="Everytime We Say Goodbye" label="Everytime We Say Goodbye"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주환/Just_One_Of_Those_Things/</id><title>김주환 - Just One Of Those Things - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:49:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:49:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%ED%99%98/Just_One_Of_Those_Things/" title="김주환 - Just One Of Those Things - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It was just one of <br>those things <br>Just one of those crazy flings <br>One of those bells that <br>now and then rings <br>Just one of those things <br>It was just one of <br>those nights <br>Just one of those <br>fabulous flights <br>A trip to the moon <br>on gossamer wings <br>Just one of those things <br>If we'd thought a bit <br>of the end of it <br>When we started <br>painting the town <br>We'd have been aware <br>that our love affair <br>Was too hot <br>not to cool down <br>So good-bye <br>dear dear and amen <br>Here's hoping we meet <br>now and then <br>It was great fun <br>But it was just one of <br>those things <br>If we'd thought a bit <br>of the end of it <br>When we started <br>painting the town <br>We'd have been aware <br>that our love affair <br>Was too hot <br>not to cool down <br>So good-bye <br>dear dear and amen <br>Here's hoping we meet <br>now and then <br>It was great fun <br>But it was just <br>great fun <br>But it was just <br>great fun <br>But it was just one of <br>those things <br>]]></content><category term="김주환" label="김주환"/><category term="Just One Of Those Things" label="Just One Of Those Things"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주환/Night_And_Day/</id><title>김주환 - Night And Day - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:49:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:49:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%ED%99%98/Night_And_Day/" title="김주환 - Night And Day - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Like the beat beat beat <br>of the tom-tom <br>When the jungle shadows fall <br>Like the tick tick tock <br>of the stately clock <br>As it stands against the wall <br>Like the drip drip drip <br>of the raindrops <br>When the summer <br>shower is through <br>So a voice within me keeps <br>repeating you you you <br>Night and day <br>you are the one <br>Only you beneath <br>the moon or under the sun <br>Whether near to me or far <br>Its no matter darling <br>where you are <br>I think of you <br>night and day <br>day in night why is it so <br>That this longing for you <br>follows wherever I go <br>In the roaring traffics boom <br>In the silence of my lonely room <br>I think of you <br>Night and day <br>night and day <br>Under the hide of me <br>There's an oh such a hungry <br>yearning burning inside of me <br>And this torment <br>wont be through <br>Til you let me spend my life <br>making love to you <br>Day and night <br>night and day <br>night and day <br>Under the hide of me <br>There's an oh such a hungry <br>yearning burning inside of me <br>And this torment <br>wont be through <br>Til you let me spend my life <br>making love to you <br>Day and night <br>night and day <br>night and day <br>night and day <br>night and day <br>night and day <br>night and day <br>]]></content><category term="김주환" label="김주환"/><category term="Night And Day" label="Night And Day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주환/Ill_Wind/</id><title>김주환 - Ill Wind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:49:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:49:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%ED%99%98/Ill_Wind/" title="김주환 - Ill Wind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Blow ill wind <br>Blow away <br>Let me rest today <br>You're blowin' me no good <br>No good <br>Go ill wind <br>Go away <br>Skies are oh so gray <br>Around my neighborhood <br>And that ain't good <br>You're only misleadin' <br>the sunshine I'm needin' <br>Ain't that a shame <br>It's so hard to keep up <br>with troubles that creep up <br>From out of nowhere <br>When love's to blame <br>So ill wind blow away <br>Let me rest today <br>You're blowin' me no good <br>No good <br>You're only misleadin' <br>the sunshine I'm needin' <br>Ain't that a shame <br>It's so hard to keep up <br>with troubles that creep up <br>From out of nowhere <br>When love's to blame <br>So ill wind blow away <br>Let me rest today <br>You're blowin' me no good <br>That's no good <br>]]></content><category term="김주환" label="김주환"/><category term="Ill Wind" label="Ill Wind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주환/That_Old_Black_Magic/</id><title>김주환 - That Old Black Magic - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:49:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:49:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%ED%99%98/That_Old_Black_Magic/" title="김주환 - That Old Black Magic - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[That old black magic has me <br>in its spell <br>That old black magic that you <br>weave so well <br>Those icy fingers up and down <br>my spine <br>The same old witchcraft <br>when your eyes meet mine <br>The same old tingle <br>that I feel inside <br>And then that elevator <br>starts its ride <br>And down and down I go <br>round and round I go <br>Like a leaf that's caught <br>in the tide <br>I should stay away <br>but what can I do <br>I hear your name <br>and I'm aflame <br>Aflame with such a <br>burning desire <br>That only your kiss <br>can put out the fire <br>'Cause you are the lover <br>I have waited for <br>The mate that fate <br>had me created for <br>And every time <br>your lips meet mine <br>Darling <br>down and down I go <br>round and round I go <br>In a spin <br>loving the spin that I'm in <br>Under that old black magic <br>called love <br>I should stay away <br>but what can I do <br>I hear your name <br>and I'm aflame <br>Aflame with such a <br>burning desire <br>That only your kiss <br>can put out the fire <br>'Cause you are the lover <br>I have waited for <br>The mate that fate <br>had me created for <br>And every time <br>your lips meet mine <br>Darling <br>down and down I go <br>round and round I go <br>In a spin <br>loving the spin that I'm in <br>Under that old black magic <br>called love <br>Under that old black magic <br>called love <br>Under that old black magic <br>called love <br>Under that old black magic <br>called love <br>]]></content><category term="김주환" label="김주환"/><category term="That Old Black Magic" label="That Old Black Magic"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주환/I_Love_You/</id><title>김주환 - I Love You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T00:49:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T00:49:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%ED%99%98/I_Love_You/" title="김주환 - I Love You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I love you <br>hums the April breeze <br>I love you <br>echo the hills <br>I love you <br>the golden dawn agrees <br>As once more she sees daffodils <br>It's spring again and <br>birds on the wing again <br>Start to sing again the old melody <br>I love you <br>that's the song of songs <br>And it all belongs to you and me <br>It's spring again and <br>birds on the wing again <br>Start to sing again the old melody <br>I love you <br>that's the song of songs <br>And it all belongs to you and me <br>]]></content><category term="김주환" label="김주환"/><category term="I Love You" label="I Love You"/></entry></feed>