<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:41:43+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스테파니_STEPHANIE/THE_BODY_SHOW_체조/</id><title>스테파니 (STEPHANIE) - THE BODY SHOW 체조 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:02:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:02:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%ED%8C%8C%EB%8B%88_STEPHANIE/THE_BODY_SHOW_%EC%B2%B4%EC%A1%B0/" title="스테파니 (STEPHANIE) - THE BODY SHOW 체조 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지금부터 더 바디 쇼 체조를 <br>시작합니다 <br>어깨운동 <br>옆구리운동 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>둘 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>셋 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>넷 둘 셋 넷 Style Style Style Style <br>골반운동 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>둘 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>셋 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>넷 둘 셋 넷 Style Style Style Style <br>등살 운동 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>둘 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>셋 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>넷 둘 셋 넷 Style Style Style Style <br>코어운동 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>둘 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>셋 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>넷 둘 셋 넷 Style Style Style Style <br>유산소운동 <br>척추강화운동 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>둘 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>셋 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>넷 둘 셋 넷 Style Style Style Style <br>전신운동 <br>종아리운동 <br>허벅지운동 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>둘 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>셋 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>넷 둘 셋 넷 Style Style Style Style <br>마무리 Style Style <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>둘 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>셋 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 일곱 Style <br>넷 둘 셋 넷 Style Style Style Style <br>]]></content><category term="스테파니 (STEPHANIE)" label="스테파니 (STEPHANIE)"/><category term="THE BODY SHOW 체조" label="THE BODY SHOW 체조"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/성진환/포근해_2016_Single_Ver/</id><title>성진환 - 포근해 (2016 Single Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:04:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:04:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%B1%EC%A7%84%ED%99%98/%ED%8F%AC%EA%B7%BC%ED%95%B4_2016_Single_Ver/" title="성진환 - 포근해 (2016 Single Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[팔베개는 아직 편하고 <br>뚜뚜뚜루뚜 <br>기지개는 아직 이른걸 <br>뚜뚜뚜루뚜 <br>이 부드러운 황금빛 <br>이불을 걷지 말아줘 <br>움직이지 좀 말고 <br>그냥 이대로 있어줘 <br>알람이 울리는 건 <br>이제 실눈을 뜨고 <br>서로를 바라보고 <br>괜히 한 번 웃어보고 <br>다시 너를 끌어안고 <br>남은 잠을 청해 볼 시간 <br>너무나 포근해 <br>빠져나갈 자신이 없어 <br>이 아침이 달콤해 <br>자꾸 늘어지고 싶어져 <br>매일 밤 너를 안고 <br>잠이 들 수 있다면 <br>단 하루도 <br>허무한 날이 없을 텐데 <br>아마 아직 꿈 속이라고 <br>믿고 싶은 마음 <br>안 열리는 커튼이라고 <br>우기고 싶은 마음 <br>너무나 포근해 <br>빠져나갈 자신이 없어 <br>이 아침이 달콤해 <br>자꾸 늘어지고 싶어져 <br>매일 밤 너를 안고 <br>잠이 들 수 있다면 <br>단 하루도 <br>허무한 날이 없을 텐데 <br>거북이랑 책방에 가서 <br>차를 마셨어 <br>잠꼬대라고 놀려도 좋아 <br>그냥 꼭 안아줘 <br>]]></content><category term="성진환" label="성진환"/><category term="포근해 (2016 Single Ver.)" label="포근해 (2016 Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/성진환/팔베개_2016_Single_Ver/</id><title>성진환 - 팔베개 (2016 Single Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:04:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:04:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%B1%EC%A7%84%ED%99%98/%ED%8C%94%EB%B2%A0%EA%B0%9C_2016_Single_Ver/" title="성진환 - 팔베개 (2016 Single Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 나의 오른팔 <br>난 너의 왼팔 <br>매일 밤 불을 끄면 <br>우린 서로의 팔이 되지 <br>이 불편한 기분이 좋아 <br>하루가 내겐 자유로와 너무 <br>어딘가 매여있고 싶어 <br>그게 너라서 나는 좋아 <br>어른이라면 <br>어른답게 <br>굴어야 하는거래 <br>하지만 24시간 <br>그럴 필욘 없잖아 <br>팔베개 팔베개 <br>내 오른팔은 <br>니 머리 뒤에 <br>팔베개 팔베개 <br>니 왼팔은 또 어디쯤에 <br>팔베개 팔베개 <br>말랑 말랑 <br>팔베개 팔베개 해줘 <br>꺼야 꺼야 할꺼야 <br>혼자서도 잘 할꺼야 <br>혼자 할 수 있는 일이 <br>많아지면 행복했지 <br>이젠 다 혼자 해야 하네 <br>생각도 결정도 <br>참을 때도 화 낼 때도 <br>혼자서 외로워야 하네 <br>어른이라면 <br>다들 겪고 살아야 하는 거래 <br>내가 정한 것도 아님 <br>억울할 수 있잖아 <br>팔베개 팔베개 <br>내 오른팔은 <br>니 머리 뒤에 <br>팔베개 팔베개 <br>니 왼팔은 또 어디쯤에 <br>팔베개 팔베개 <br>말랑 말랑 <br>팔베개 팔베개 해줘 <br>]]></content><category term="성진환" label="성진환"/><category term="팔베개 (2016 Single Ver.)" label="팔베개 (2016 Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/pH-1/Wavy/</id><title>pH-1 - Wavy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:05:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:05:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/pH-1/Wavy/" title="pH-1 - Wavy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[my mood is what i'm feelin like <br>난 하고 싶은 대로 하지 <br>sippin on that juice so tasty <br>you so wavy <br>juice so tasty <br>you so wavy <br>my mood is what i'm feelin like <br>난 하고 싶은 대로 하지 <br>sippin on that juice so tasty <br>you so wavy <br>juice so tasty <br>you so wavy <br>never good at <br>hiding my feelings <br>거짓말 할때면 찔림 <br>나 지금 속보이게 웃고 있어 <br>내 잇몸도 시림 <br>멋진 널 내가 만나게 <br>하신 이윤뭘까 <br>난 주의 속마음을 환히 <br>들여다보고 싶어 like 몰카 <br>i ain't gon lie <br>난 잘 몰라 <br>so many mysteries <br>but such is life though <br>my goal은 Michael 처럼 <br>멀리 날아올라 <br>jumpman 처럼 <br>네 마음에 쏙 골인하는 것 <br>넌 고민하는 척 <br>날 들었다 놨다해서 <br>나 발병나겠어 <br>너의 그 아름다움 앞에선 <br>뭣보다 어려워 <br>내 자신 봉인하는 법 <br>you so wavy <br>i got my juice so tasty <br>you so wavy <br>i got my juice so tasty <br>my mood is what i'm feelin like <br>난 하고 싶은 대로 하지 <br>sippin on that juice so tasty <br>you so wavy <br>juice so tasty <br>you so wavy <br>my mood is what i'm feelin like <br>난 하고 싶은 대로 하지 <br>sippin on that juice so tasty <br>you so wavy <br>juice so tasty <br>you so wavy <br>어쩌면 내 <br>단점은 매일 <br>네 생각하며 할 일을 <br>제 때에 못하는게 <br>and i and i and i never <br>know know how to love <br>도움이 필요해 나를 도와줘 <br>네 속을 보여줘 <br>절대 못놓아 널 <br>한눈에 반하고 말았어 <br>보는게 절대 모든게 <br>결코 아니지만서도 <br>현재 내 머린 비었어 <br>beyonce on my playlist <br>i'm drunk in love <br>i'll be your jay z <br>and our love is crazy <br>and i'll be your feature <br>but you ain't got to pay me <br>two can play this game <br>and i'll let you play me <br>but it's killing me softly <br>so please come save me <br>you so wavy <br>i got my juice so tasty <br>you so wavy <br>i got my juice so tasty <br>my mood is what i'm feelin like <br>la la la la la <br>난 하고 싶은 대로 하지 <br>la la la la la <br>my mood is what i'm feelin like <br>la la la la la <br>난 하고 싶은 대로 하지 <br>la la la la la <br>my mood is what i'm feelin like <br>난 하고 싶은 대로 하지 <br>sippin on that juice so tasty <br>you so wavy <br>juice so tasty <br>you so wavy <br>my mood is what i'm feelin like <br>난 하고 싶은 대로 하지 <br>sippin on that juice so tasty <br>you so wavy <br>juice so tasty <br>you so wavy <br>]]></content><category term="pH-1" label="pH-1"/><category term="Wavy" label="Wavy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤혜선/나의_왕자님/</id><title>윤혜선 - 나의 왕자님 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:05:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:05:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%99%95%EC%9E%90%EB%8B%98/" title="윤혜선 - 나의 왕자님 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 그대를 만난 건 <br>정말로 너무 큰 행운이라고 <br>내 곁에만 있어줘 <br>왕자님처럼 영원히 해 줄게 <br>가끔씩 우울할 때면 <br>가끔씩 짜증날 때면 <br>그댈 위해 준비해 온 <br>특급 칭찬도 해줄게 <br>그냥 내 곁에 있어줘 <br>왕자님처럼 해 줄게 <br>그냥 내 곁에 있어줘 <br>영원히 그대만 사랑해 <br>나 그대를 만난 건 <br>정말로 행복 큰 기쁨이라고 <br>내 곁에만 있어줘 <br>왕자님처럼 영원히 해 줄게 <br>가끔씩 우울할 때면 <br>가끔씩 짜증날 때면 <br>그댈 위해 준비해 온 <br>섹시댄스도 춰 줄게 <br>그냥 내 곁에 있어줘 <br>왕자님처럼 해 줄게 <br>그냥 내 곁에 있어줘 <br>영원히 그대만 사랑해 <br>가끔씩 우울할 때면 <br>가끔씩 짜증날 때면 <br>그댈 위해 준비해 온 <br>이벤트도 보여 줄게 <br>그냥 내 곁에 있어줘 <br>왕자님처럼 해 줄게 <br>그냥 내 곁에 있어줘 <br>영원히 그대만 사랑해 <br>영원히 그대만 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="윤혜선" label="윤혜선"/><category term="나의 왕자님" label="나의 왕자님"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤혜선/월화수목금토일/</id><title>윤혜선 - 월화수목금토일 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:05:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:05:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/%EC%9B%94%ED%99%94%EC%88%98%EB%AA%A9%EA%B8%88%ED%86%A0%EC%9D%BC/" title="윤혜선 - 월화수목금토일 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[월화수목금토일 난 듣고 싶어 <br>월화수목금토일 늘 보고 싶어 <br>그댈 사랑해 너만 사랑해요 <br>내 눈에는 너만 보여 <br>뒤돌아서면 보고싶고 <br>하루라도 못보면 미칠것만 같고 <br>널 처음 만난 그날보다 <br>지금이 오히려 더 좋은 것만 같아 <br>니 생각에 흐뭇한 <br>24시간 1440분 <br>그대 이름만 불러도 <br>벅찬 86400초 <br>월요일은 원래 만나는 날 <br>화요일은 화창하게 <br>수요일은 수수하게 <br>목요일은 목빠져라 기다려 <br>금요일은 금방갔음 좋겠어 <br>토요일은 토끼같은 그댈 안고 <br>일요일은 그댈 위해 요리해 <br>내 다이어리 스케줄은 <br>매일 매일 그댈 위해 준비해 <br>월화수목금토일 난 듣고 싶어 <br>월화수목금토일 늘 보고 싶어 <br>그댈 사랑해 너만 사랑해요 <br>내 눈에는 너만 보여 <br>월화수목금토일 난 듣고 싶어 <br>월화수목금토일 늘 보고 싶어 <br>그댈 사랑해 너만 사랑해요 <br>내 눈에는 너만 보여 <br>Everyday Everytime <br>이젠 니가 없으면 어색해 <br>Everything 니 모든게 익숙해져 <br>편안해져 더 좋아 <br>널 알기전에 나 어땠더라 <br>이젠 기억도 잘 나질 않아 <br>니가 없는 나의 하루는 <br>상상조차 할 수 없는 우웩 <br>월요일은 원래 만나는 날 <br>화요일은 화창하게 <br>수요일은 수수하게 <br>목요일은 목빠져라 기다려 <br>금요일은 금방갔음 좋겠어 <br>토요일은 토끼같은 그댈 안고 <br>일요일은 그댈 위해 요리해 <br>내 다이어리 스케줄은 <br>매일 매일 그댈 위해 준비해 <br>월화수목금토일 난 듣고 싶어 <br>월화수목금토일 늘 보고 싶어 <br>그댈 사랑해 너만 사랑해요 <br>내 눈에는 너만 보여 <br>월화수목금토일 난 듣고 싶어 <br>월화수목금토일 늘 보고 싶어 <br>그댈 사랑해 너만 사랑해요 <br>내 눈에는 너만 보여 <br>월요일부터 보고싶어 <br>화요일도 니 생각이 가득해 <br>수요일엔 달콤한 니 꿈을 꾸고 <br>목요일도 니 사진만 바라봐 <br>금요일엔 그대와 맥주한잔 <br>토요일은 와인에 멋진 음악 틀고 <br>그대와 나만의 화끈한 파티 <br>일요일엔 알콩달콩 달콤해 <br>너무 좋아 행복해 <br>월화수목금토일 난 듣고 싶어 <br>월화수목금토일 늘 보고 싶어 <br>그댈 사랑해 너만 사랑해요 <br>내 눈에는 너만 보여 <br>월화수목금토일 난 듣고 싶어 <br>월화수목금토일 늘 보고 싶어 <br>그댈 사랑해 너만 사랑해요 <br>내 눈에는 너만 보여 <br>]]></content><category term="윤혜선" label="윤혜선"/><category term="월화수목금토일" label="월화수목금토일"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤혜선/군화나_거꾸로_신지마/</id><title>윤혜선 - 군화나 거꾸로 신지마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:05:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:05:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/%EA%B5%B0%ED%99%94%EB%82%98_%EA%B1%B0%EA%BE%B8%EB%A1%9C_%EC%8B%A0%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88/" title="윤혜선 - 군화나 거꾸로 신지마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기다려줄께 항상 <br>남자라서 가는거잖아 <br>너야말로 군화나 <br>거꾸로 신지마 <br>나도 절대 고무신 따윈 <br>거꾸로 신지는 않을꺼야 <br>너야말로 군화나 <br>거꾸로 신지마 <br>나 솔직히 너무 많이 떨려 <br>입대할 생각에 잠도 안와 <br>밥도 못 먹어 <br>적당히 핑계대고 <br>빠졌으면 좋겠어 <br>사실 두려운 것도 있지만 <br>너랑 헤어지기 싫어서 그래 <br>니 얼굴 못 볼 세월이 <br>무엇보다 걱정되서 그래 <br>요즘 군대는 편한 거라고 <br>돈도 많이 준다고 그래 <br>남자라면은 <br>누구나 당연히 갔다와 <br>기다려줄께 항상 <br>남자라서 가는거잖아 <br>너야말로 군화나 <br>거꾸로 신지마 <br>나도 절대 고무신 따윈 <br>거꾸로 신지는 않을꺼야 <br>너야말로 군화나 <br>거꾸로 신지마 <br>나 솔직히 운동 너무 못해 <br>눈도 안 좋고 배도 나오고 <br>푸샵도 아예 못하고 <br>그런데도 신검 1급이야 <br>키 180에 미남 <br>우리 학교 킹카 <br>그 놈도 공익인데 <br>나 이런 놈야 <br>어때 나 멋있지 않냐 <br>요즘 군대는 편한 거라고 <br>돈도 많이 준다고 그래 <br>남자라면은 <br>누구나 당연히 갔다와 <br>기다려줄께 항상 <br>남자라서 가는거잖아 <br>너야말로 군화나 <br>거꾸로 신지마 <br>나도 절대 고무신 따윈 <br>거꾸로 신지는 않을꺼야 <br>너야말로 군화나 <br>거꾸로 신지마 <br>기다려줄께 항상 <br>남자라서 가는거잖아 <br>너야말로 군화나 <br>거꾸로 신지마 <br>나도 절대 고무신 따윈 <br>거꾸로 신지는 않을꺼야 <br>너야말로 군화나 <br>거꾸로 신지마 <br>]]></content><category term="윤혜선" label="윤혜선"/><category term="군화나 거꾸로 신지마" label="군화나 거꾸로 신지마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤혜선/메리투게더/</id><title>윤혜선 - 메리투게더 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:05:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:05:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/%EB%A9%94%EB%A6%AC%ED%88%AC%EA%B2%8C%EB%8D%94/" title="윤혜선 - 메리투게더 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 이제 더 이상 바랄게 없어 <br>날 보며 웃어주는 <br>니가 있으니까 <br>굿모닝 키스하고 <br>매일 같이 잠을 자고 <br>평생을 다 바쳐서 <br>메리 투게더 <br>사랑은 불쑥 내게 <br>찾아온거야 <br>언제나 꿈꿔왔던 <br>마 법 같은 일 <br>첫눈을 바라보며 <br>소원을 빌었죠 <br>이제는 현실이 된거야 <br>나 역시 더 이상 바랄게 없어 <br>내 곁엔 천사같은 <br>니가 있으니까 <br>사랑해 속삭이고 <br>마주 보며 밥을 먹고 <br>평생을 다 바쳐서 <br>메리 투게더 <br>가끔씩 괴롭고 <br>힘들때도 있겠지 <br>그럴때면 첫눈의 기적 떠올려 <br>언제나 기다렸던 <br>마법 같은 일 <br>이제는 현실이 된거야 <br>난 이제 더 이상 <br>바랄게 없어 <br>날 보며 웃어주는 <br>니가 있으니까 <br>굿모닝 키스하고 <br>매일 같이 잠을 자고 <br>평생을 다 바쳐서 <br>메리 투게더 <br>사랑은 행운 처럼 <br>찾아온거야 <br>언제나 꿈꿔왔던 <br>마법 같은 일 <br>겨울이 올때마다 <br>가슴이 설레죠 <br>사랑이 이루어 진거야 <br>난 이제 더 이상 바랄게 없어 <br>날 보며 웃어주는 <br>니가 있으니까 <br>사랑해 속삭이고 <br>마주 보며 밥을 먹고 <br>평생을 다 바쳐서 <br>메리 투게더 메리 투게더 <br>]]></content><category term="윤혜선" label="윤혜선"/><category term="메리투게더" label="메리투게더"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤혜선/모르는_척/</id><title>윤혜선 - 모르는 척 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:05:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:05:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/%EB%AA%A8%EB%A5%B4%EB%8A%94_%EC%B2%99/" title="윤혜선 - 모르는 척 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>이렇게 널 사랑해 <br>누가 뭐래도 <br>나는 너 하나뿐야 <br>이런 내 마음이 <br>시킨 사랑을 <br>어떻게 너에게 <br>전할 수 있을까 <br>사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>이렇게 널 사랑해 <br>얼마나 사랑해야 <br>날 알아줄까 <br>용기가 없어 <br>말하지 못하고 <br>어떻게 해야 <br>좋을지 몰라 워우워 <br>사랑한다는 말 <br>너무나 어려운거야 <br>니 눈빛만 봐도 알아 <br>난 느낄 수가 있잖아 <br>알면서 또 모르는 척 <br>니가 다가와주기를 <br>난 기다릴꺼야 <br>용기내 어서 <br>뭘 망설이니 <br>오늘도 니 생각에 <br>니 사진보다 잠이 들어 <br>꿈속에서 만난 너는 <br>어찌 그리 달콤한데 <br>니 입술은 달달한 <br>솜사탕보다도 달콤 새콤 <br>니 향기에 취한 건지 <br>잠에 취해 그런 건지 <br>매일 아침 날 설레게 <br>하는 니 카톡 카톡 <br>점심때면 스마일에 <br>즐점 즐점 하트 문자 <br>저녁은 같이 뭘 먹을까 <br>무슨 말을 할까 <br>헤어지기 싫은 시간은 <br>어느새 굿나잇 키스 <br>사랑한다는 말 <br>너무나 어려운거야 <br>니 눈빛만 봐도 알아 <br>난 느낄 수가 있잖아 <br>알면서 또 모르는 척 <br>니가 다가와주기를 <br>난 기다릴꺼야 <br>용기내 어서 <br>뭘 망설이니 <br>말하지 않아도 <br>너를 느낄 수 있어 <br>이제는 걱정 하지마 <br>이제 알아 <br>사랑한다는 말 <br>너무나 어려운거야 <br>니 눈빛만 봐도 알아 <br>난 느낄 수가 있잖아 <br>알면서 또 모르는 척 <br>니가 다가와주기를 <br>난 기다릴꺼야 <br>용기내 어서 <br>뭘 망설이니 <br>]]></content><category term="윤혜선" label="윤혜선"/><category term="모르는 척" label="모르는 척"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤혜선/울어도_울어도/</id><title>윤혜선 - 울어도 울어도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:05:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:05:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/%EC%9A%B8%EC%96%B4%EB%8F%84_%EC%9A%B8%EC%96%B4%EB%8F%84/" title="윤혜선 - 울어도 울어도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[울어도 울어도 <br>씻겨지지 않는건 <br>그댈 향한 내사랑 <br>영원한 추억입니다 <br>지워도 지워도 <br>지워지지 않는건 <br>그댈 향한 내마음 <br>간절한 사랑입니다 <br>어제만해도 몰랐죠 <br>이렇게 가슴 아플 줄 <br>사랑이 이렇게 <br>쉽게 떠난다는 걸 <br>몇 번의 이별과 <br>몇 번의 시련에 <br>강해진 줄 알았죠 <br>물러터진 내 심장 <br>한없이 울어도 <br>씻겨지지 않는건 <br>아무리 지워도 <br>지워지지 않는건 <br>허전한 그대의 <br>흔적들이라는 게 <br>사랑한 추억의 <br>무게만큼이라고 <br>울어도 울어도 <br>씻겨지지 않는건 <br>그댈 향한 내사랑 <br>영원한 추억입니다 <br>지워도 지워도 <br>지워지지 않는건 <br>그댈 향한 내마음 <br>간절한 사랑입니다 <br>오늘 하루는 왜 이렇게 <br>길고 허전한걸까 <br>떠난 이유는 <br>제대로 묻지도 못하고 <br>사랑한 마음도 <br>가져 갈순 없을까 <br>정말 날 사랑하긴 했는지 <br>한없이 울어도 <br>씻겨지지 않는건 <br>아무리 지워도 <br>지워지지 않는건 <br>허전한 그대의 <br>흔적들이라는 게 <br>사랑한 추억의 <br>무게만큼이라고 <br>떠나가던 마지막 그대의 모습 <br>기억하기 싫어 눈 감아버렸죠 <br>사랑해서 떠난다는 그말 듣기 <br>싫어서 귀를 닫아버렸죠 <br>울어도 울어도 <br>씻겨지지 않는건 <br>그댈 향한 내사랑 <br>영원한 추억입니다 <br>지워도 지워도 <br>지워지지 않는건 <br>그댈 향한 내마음 <br>간절한 사랑입니다 <br>울어도 울어도 <br>씻겨지지 않는건 <br>그댈 향한 내사랑 <br>영원한 추억입니다 <br>]]></content><category term="윤혜선" label="윤혜선"/><category term="울어도 울어도" label="울어도 울어도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤혜선/치료해줄래/</id><title>윤혜선 - 치료해줄래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:05:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:05:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/%EC%B9%98%EB%A3%8C%ED%95%B4%EC%A4%84%EB%9E%98/" title="윤혜선 - 치료해줄래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[금방이라도 울 것 같은데 <br>날 위로 해줄 사람이 없어 <br>마지막으로 널 생각하며 <br>남은 상처다 지워버릴래 <br>너와의 스토리 <br>이제는 저 멀리 <br>떠나가도 돼 <br>이젠 거짓말이 아니야 <br>너와의 스토리 <br>이제는 저 멀리 <br>떠나가도 돼 <br>너 하나쯤 잊어버리면 돼 <br>나 맘에 드는 사람 <br>이제 내게 와봐요 <br>내 맘 치료해줄래요 이제 <br>사랑하나 못 믿는데 <br>어떻하나요 <br>날 다시 돌려 줄래 <br>미소는 거짓말인데 <br>너에게 딱 속아 버렸네 <br>얼마나 더 많은 <br>여잘 울려야 되겠니 <br>끝까지 날 속이는건데 <br>사랑이 점점 멀어질 때 <br>두려워지는 걸 <br>두려워지는 걸 <br>너와의 스토리 <br>이제는 저 멀리 <br>떠나가도 돼 <br>이젠 거짓말이 아니야 <br>너와의 스토리 <br>이제는 저 멀리 <br>떠나가도 돼 <br>너 하나쯤 잊어버리면 돼 <br>나 맘에 드는 사람 <br>이제 내게 와 봐요 <br>내 맘 치료해줄래요 이제 <br>사랑하나 못 믿는데 <br>어떻하나요 <br>날 다시 돌려줄래 <br>바보 같은 나야 <br>누굴 원망하니 <br>다시는 이런 <br>사랑에 울지 않기 <br>살아가다보면 <br>다 겪는 일이야 <br>다시는 이런 <br>사랑 않할래 <br>나 맘에 드는 사람 <br>이제 내게 와 봐요 <br>내 맘 치료해줄래요 이제 <br>사랑하나 못 믿는데 <br>어떻하나요 <br>날 다시 돌려 줄래 <br>]]></content><category term="윤혜선" label="윤혜선"/><category term="치료해줄래" label="치료해줄래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤혜선/내_맘도_아파요/</id><title>윤혜선 - 내 맘도 아파요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:05:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:05:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%98%EB%8F%84_%EC%95%84%ED%8C%8C%EC%9A%94/" title="윤혜선 - 내 맘도 아파요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[만일 나 다시 <br>사랑할 수만 있다면 <br>그때도 내 사랑은 <br>당연히 또 넌데 <br>언제나 너의 숨결을 <br>느껴 보고 싶어 <br>그게 바로 운명이라 <br>생각했던 우리 인연 <br>참 힘들게도 내 가슴 <br>아프게 한 사람 <br>더 슬프게도 내 눈물 <br>마르게 한 사람 <br>잊을 줄 알았는데 <br>괜찮을 줄 알았는데 <br>시간이 해결할 줄 <br>알았는데 <br>그댈 생각하면 <br>내 맘도 아파요 <br>나도 모르게 <br>눈물도 흐르는걸요 <br>우리 추억 <br>떠오를때마다 <br>그냥 한편의 <br>영화를 감상하듯이 <br>다른 사람 얘기라고 <br>생각해줘요 <br>그래야 나도 편히 <br>떠날 수 있으니까 <br>참 아프게도 자존심 <br>버리게 한 사람 <br>더 쓰리게도 마지막 <br>사랑이 되버린 사람 <br>잊었다 믿었는데 <br>아플 줄은 몰랐는데 <br>시간이 해결할 줄 <br>알았는데 <br>다른 사랑을 만나면 <br>널 잊을 거라 생각했어 <br>아무리 노력해도 <br>그게 나는 안 되나봐 <br>왜 떠났니 한마디 <br>물어보지도 못하고 <br>니 뒷모습만 바라보다 <br>멍하니 울고야 말았어 <br>그댈 생각하면 <br>내 맘도 아파요 <br>나도 모르게 <br>눈물도 흐르는걸요 <br>우리 추억 <br>떠오를때마다 <br>그냥 한편의 <br>영화를 감상하듯이 <br>다른 사람 <br>얘기라고 생각해줘요 <br>그댈 생각하면 <br>내 맘도 아파요 <br>나도 모르게 <br>눈물도 흐르는걸요 <br>우리 추억 <br>떠오를때마다 <br>그냥 한편의 <br>영화를 감상하듯이 <br>다른 사람 <br>얘기라고 생각해줘요 <br>그래야 나도 편히 <br>떠날 수 있으니까 <br>]]></content><category term="윤혜선" label="윤혜선"/><category term="내 맘도 아파요" label="내 맘도 아파요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/배영경/가을밤/</id><title>배영경 - 가을밤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:05:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:05:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B0%EC%98%81%EA%B2%BD/%EA%B0%80%EC%9D%84%EB%B0%A4/" title="배영경 - 가을밤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가을밤 그대와 거닐던 <br>그 기억 따라서 <br>난 꿈을 꾸었지 <br>당신과 만났던 <br>그날 밤 그 기억이 <br>내겐 아직 남아있어 <br>우리가 부르던 그 노래 <br>넌 기억하는지 <br>넌 듣고 있는지 <br>당신과 부르던 그 노래 <br>그 멜로디 난 기억해 <br>가을밤 향기 나던 <br>우리의 노래들 <br>너와 자주 가던 <br>거리마다 물들인 날들 <br>어제 꿈에 너의 모습이 <br>닿을 듯 말 듯 <br>흐려진 기억이 <br>이젠 정말 안녕이라 <br>이젠 정말 안녕이라 <br>지워질 우리 사랑 <br>어제 꿈에 너의 모습이 <br>닿을 듯 말 듯 <br>흐려진 기억이 <br>이젠 정말 안녕이라 <br>이젠 정말 안녕이라 <br>지워질 우리 사랑 <br>어제 꿈에 너의 모습이 <br>닿을 듯 말 듯 <br>흐려진 기억이 <br>이젠 정말 안녕이라 <br>이젠 정말 안녕이라 <br>지워질 우리 사랑 <br>어제 꿈에 너의 모습이 <br>닿을 듯 말 듯 <br>흐려진 기억이 <br>이젠 정말 안녕이라 <br>이젠 정말 안녕이라 <br>지워질 우리 사랑 <br>그 기억이 내게 <br>아직 남아있어 <br>]]></content><category term="배영경" label="배영경"/><category term="가을밤" label="가을밤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송유진/다섯글자예쁜말_MR/</id><title>송유진 - 다섯글자예쁜말 (MR) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:07:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:07:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EC%9C%A0%EC%A7%84/%EB%8B%A4%EC%84%AF%EA%B8%80%EC%9E%90%EC%98%88%EC%81%9C%EB%A7%90_MR/" title="송유진 - 다섯글자예쁜말 (MR) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한손만으로도 세어 볼 수 있는 <br>아름다운 말 정겨운말 <br>한손만으로도 세어 볼 수있는 <br>다섯글자 예쁜말 <br>사랑합니다 고맙습니다 <br>감사합니다 안녕하세요 <br>아름다워요 노력할게요 <br>마음의 약속 꼭 지켜볼래요 <br>한손만으로도 세어 볼 수 있는 <br>다섯글자 예쁜말 <br>한손만으로도 세어 볼 수 있는 <br>아름다운말 정겨운말 <br>한손만으로도 세어 볼 수 있는 <br>다섯글자 예쁜 말 <br>사랑합니다 고맙습니다 <br>감사합니다 안녕하세요 <br>아름다워요 노력할게요 <br>마음의 약속 꼭 지켜볼래요 <br>한손만으로도 세어 볼 수 있는 <br>다섯글자 예쁜 말 <br>다섯글자 예쁜 말]]></content><category term="송유진" label="송유진"/><category term="다섯글자예쁜말 (MR)" label="다섯글자예쁜말 (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송유진/다섯글자예쁜말/</id><title>송유진 - 다섯글자예쁜말 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:07:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:07:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EC%9C%A0%EC%A7%84/%EB%8B%A4%EC%84%AF%EA%B8%80%EC%9E%90%EC%98%88%EC%81%9C%EB%A7%90/" title="송유진 - 다섯글자예쁜말 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한 손만으도 세어 볼 수 있는 <br>아름다운 말, 정겨운 말 <br>한 손만으로도 세어 볼 수 있는 <br>다섯 글자 예쁜 말 <br>사랑합니다. <br>고맙습니다. <br>감사합니다. <br>안녕하세요. <br>아름다워요. <br>노력할게요. <br>마음의 약속 꼭 지켜 볼래요 <br>한 손 만으로도 세어 볼 수 있는 <br>다섯 글자 예쁜 말 <br>한 손 만으로도 세어 볼 수 있는 <br>다섯 글자 예쁜 말]]></content><category term="송유진" label="송유진"/><category term="다섯글자예쁜말" label="다섯글자예쁜말"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Olivia_OBrien/Find_What_Youre_Looking_For/</id><title>Olivia O`Brien - Find What You`re Looking For - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:08:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:08:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Olivia_OBrien/Find_What_Youre_Looking_For/" title="Olivia O`Brien - Find What You`re Looking For - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I always knew you'd be the one <br>To break me down no it's not fun <br>To be the girl you hit and run <br>Wish you were sorry <br>for the things you've done <br>And after all you put me through <br>I'm sick and tired <br>of loving you more <br>I just can't give you <br>what you're looking for <br>I hope you find <br>what you're looking for <br>What you're looking for <br>Find what you're looking for <br>What you're looking for <br>Didn't give you <br>what you want <br>Gave you what you need <br>You beg me <br>please baby baby don't leave <br>I hope you find <br>what you're looking for <br>What you're looking for <br>Find what you're looking for <br>What you're looking for <br>They say you don't know <br>what you got <br>'Til it's too late <br>I'm already gone <br>I don't care <br>that you're not here <br>Won't wipe my eyes <br>cause there's no tears <br>I'm not what you wanted <br>I'm not what you need <br>Just not what you wanted <br>and that's fine with me <br>I don't why I cared so much <br>I'm doing fine <br>without your love <br>I hope you find <br>what you're looking for <br>What you're looking for <br>Find what you're looking for <br>What you're looking for <br>Didn't give you <br>what you want <br>Gave you what you need <br>You beg me <br>please baby baby don't leave <br>I hope you find <br>what you're looking for <br>What you're looking for <br>Find what you're looking for <br>What you're looking for <br>I always knew <br>that you were not about me <br>Always doing things <br>I like without me <br>Tryna front you <br>say you're just a bad boy <br>But I know you <br>you're nothing but a sad boy <br>You lie to me <br>you tell me that you love me <br>Saying that you put <br>no one above me <br>But I'm not dumb <br>I know just what you wanted <br>I never should've stayed <br>just being honest <br>I hope you find <br>what you're looking for <br>What you're looking for <br>Find what you're looking for <br>What you're looking for <br>Didn't give you what you want <br>Gave you what you need <br>You beg me <br>please baby baby don't leave <br>I hope you find <br>what you're looking for <br>What you're looking for <br>Find what you're looking for <br>What you're looking for <br>]]></content><category term="Olivia O`Brien" label="Olivia O`Brien"/><category term="Find What You`re Looking For" label="Find What You`re Looking For"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김가은/아무것도_하지_말아요/</id><title>김가은 - 아무것도 하지 말아요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:08:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:08:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EA%B0%80%EC%9D%80/%EC%95%84%EB%AC%B4%EA%B2%83%EB%8F%84_%ED%95%98%EC%A7%80_%EB%A7%90%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94/" title="김가은 - 아무것도 하지 말아요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너무 아쉬워하지 마요 <br>너무 힘들어 하지 말아요 <br>우리 어쩌면 이 시간이 <br>가장 소중한 기억이 될꺼야 <br>아직 아무도 모르잖아요 <br>잃어버린 건 잊어 버려요 <br>너무 힘이 들 때에는 그대 <br>아무것도 하지 말아요 <br>우리 그저 둘이서 함께 <br>서로 바라만 보고 있어요 <br>그대와 나만 <br>있으면 되요 <br>지금 이대로 <br>너무 조급해 하지 마요 <br>뭐든 해내려 하지 말아요 <br>가끔 이렇게 주저 앉아 <br>가장 따듯한 곳에 기대요 <br>너무 힘이 들 때에는 그대 <br>아무것도 하지 말아요 <br>우리 그저 둘이서 함께 <br>서로 바라만 보고 있어요 <br>그대와 나만 <br>있으면 되요 <br>지금 이대로 <br>바람이 <br>불어와 <br>모든게 <br>부서져 <br>날아가 버려도 <br>너무 아쉬워하지 마요 <br>너무 힘들어 하지 말아요 <br>그대와 나만 <br>있으면 되요 <br>지금 이대로 <br>]]></content><category term="김가은" label="김가은"/><category term="아무것도 하지 말아요" label="아무것도 하지 말아요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Sedaka/You_Mean_Everything_To_Me/</id><title>Neil Sedaka - You Mean Everything To Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:08:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:08:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Sedaka/You_Mean_Everything_To_Me/" title="Neil Sedaka - You Mean Everything To Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You are the answer to my lonely prayer <br>You are an angel from above <br>I was so lonely till you came to me <br>With the wonder of your love <br><br>I don't know how I ever lived before <br>You are my life <br>My destiny <br>Oh, my darling <br>I love you so <br>You mean everything to me <br><br>If you should ever, ever go away <br>There would be lonely tears to cry <br>The sun above would be never shine again <br>There would be teardrops in the sky <br><br>So hold me close and never let me go <br>And say our love will always be <br>Oh, my darling <br>I love you so <br>You mean everything to me (you mean everything to me) <br><br>So hold me close and never let me go <br>And say our love will always be <br>Oh, my darling <br>I love you so <br>You mean everything to me]]></content><category term="Neil Sedaka" label="Neil Sedaka"/><category term="You Mean Everything To Me" label="You Mean Everything To Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Sedaka/Next_Door_To_An_Angel/</id><title>Neil Sedaka - Next Door To An Angel - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:09:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:09:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Sedaka/Next_Door_To_An_Angel/" title="Neil Sedaka - Next Door To An Angel - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm living right next door to an angel <br>And I just found out today <br>I'm living right next door to an angel <br>And she only lives a house away <br><br>She used to be such a skinny little girl <br>But all of a sudden she's out of this world <br>I'm living right next door to an angel <br>And I'm gonna make that angel mine <br><br>Since I saw her this morning <br>I'm on cloud number nine <br>Found a Garden of Eden <br>At the house next door to mine <br><br>I took a look <br>And, oh, what a shock <br>To find a little bit of heaven right <br>On the block. <br>I'm living right next door to an angel <br>And I'm gonna make that angel mine <br><br>I can't believe that this is the girl next door <br>Her funny little face isn't funny no more <br>Sixteen and, oh, what a dream <br>Ain't it strange how she changed into such a lovely angel <br><br>Saw her walking down main street <br>And I couldn't believe my eyes <br>It used to be such a plain street <br>But now it's paradise <br><br>I feel so happy <br>I'm feeling so good <br>I'm the luckiest devil in the neighborhood <br>I'm living right next door to an angel <br>And I'm gonna make that angel mine]]></content><category term="Neil Sedaka" label="Neil Sedaka"/><category term="Next Door To An Angel" label="Next Door To An Angel"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Sedaka/Breaking_Up_Is_Hard_to_Do/</id><title>Neil Sedaka - Breaking Up Is Hard to Do - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:09:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:09:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Sedaka/Breaking_Up_Is_Hard_to_Do/" title="Neil Sedaka - Breaking Up Is Hard to Do - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Take Your Love Away Frim Me <br>Don't You Leave My Heart My Heart In Misery <br>If You Go Then I'll Be Blue <br>Cause Breaking Up Is Hsrd To Do <br><br>Remember When You Held Me Tight <br>And You Kissed Me All Through The Night <br>Think Of All That We've Been Through <br>And Breaking Up Is Hard To Do <br><br>(*They Say That Breaking Up Is Hard To Do <br>Now I Know <br>I Know That It's True <br>Don't Say That This Is The End <br>Instead Of Beaking Up I Wish That We Were Making Up Agin) <br><br>(** I Beg Of You Don't Say Goodbye <br>Can't We Give Our Love Another Try? <br>Come On. Baby. Let's Start Anew <br>Cause Breaking Up Is Hard To Do) <br><br>(*Repeat) <br><br>(*Repeat)]]></content><category term="Neil Sedaka" label="Neil Sedaka"/><category term="Breaking Up Is Hard to Do" label="Breaking Up Is Hard to Do"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alessia_Cara/Scars_To_Your_Beautiful_Luca_Schreiner_Remix/</id><title>Alessia Cara - Scars To Your Beautiful (Luca Schreiner Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:09:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:09:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alessia_Cara/Scars_To_Your_Beautiful_Luca_Schreiner_Remix/" title="Alessia Cara - Scars To Your Beautiful (Luca Schreiner Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She just wants to be beautiful <br>She goes unnoticed, she knows no limits <br>She craves attention, she praises an image <br>She prays to be sculpted by the sculptor <br>Oh, she don't see the light that's shining <br>Deeper than the eyes can find it <br>Maybe we have made her blind <br>So she tries to cover up her pain and cut her woes away <br>'Cause covergirls don't cry after their face is made <br><br>But there's a hope that's waiting for you in the dark <br>You should know you're beautiful just the way you are <br>And you don't have to change a thing <br>The world could change its heart <br>No scars to your beautiful, we're stars and we're beautiful <br>And you don't have to change a thing <br>The world could change its heart <br>No scars to your beautiful, we're stars and we're beautiful <br><br>She has dreams to be an envy, so she's starving <br>You know, covergirls eat nothing <br>She says beauty is pain and there's beauty in everything <br>What's a little bit of hunger <br>I could go a little while longer, she fades away <br>She don't see her perfect, she don't understand she's worth it <br>Or that beauty goes deeper than the surface <br>So to all the girls that's hurting <br>Let me be your mirror, help you see a little bit clearer <br>The light that shines within <br><br>There's a hope that's waiting for you in the dark <br>You should know you're beautiful just the way you are <br>And you don't have to change a thing <br>The world could change its heart <br>No scars to your beautiful, we're stars and we're beautiful <br><br>No better you than the you that you are <br>No better you than the you that you are <br>No better life than the life we're living <br>No better life than the life we're living <br>No better time for your shine, you're a star <br>No better time for your shine, you're a star <br>Oh, you're beautiful, oh, you're beautiful <br><br>And there's a hope that's waiting for you in the dark <br>You should know you're beautiful just the way you are <br>And you don't have to change a thing <br>The world could change its heart <br>No scars to your beautiful, we're stars and we're beautiful <br>And you don't have to change a thing <br>The world could change its heart <br>No scars to your beautiful, we're stars and we're beautiful]]></content><category term="Alessia Cara" label="Alessia Cara"/><category term="Scars To Your Beautiful (Luca Schreiner Remix)" label="Scars To Your Beautiful (Luca Schreiner Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/뽕짝히어로/사랑이란/</id><title>뽕짝히어로 - 사랑이란 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:10:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:10:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%BD%95%EC%A7%9D%ED%9E%88%EC%96%B4%EB%A1%9C/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4%EB%9E%80/" title="뽕짝히어로 - 사랑이란 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘쯤에 말할까 <br>내일까지 참을까 <br>너 하나만 사랑해 <br>약속하면 믿을까 <br>사랑이란 그런 것 <br>둘도 없이 좋은 것 <br>눈을 감아 보아도 <br>또렷하게 보이는 <br>사랑이란 그런 것 <br>끝도 없이 좋은 것 <br>너 하나만 있으면 <br>웃음질 수 있는 것 <br>밤을 꼬박 지새며 <br>수도 없이 하던 말 <br>너에게만 말할게 <br>사랑한단 한마디 <br>사랑이란 그런 것 <br>반짝이는 두 눈이 <br>너 하나만 보는 것 <br>너 하나만 담는 것 <br>사랑이란 그런 것 <br>두근대는 가슴이 <br>너 하나만 찾는 것 <br>너를 향해 뛰는 것 <br>사랑이란 그런 것 <br>둘도 없이 좋은 것 <br>눈을 감아 보아도 <br>또렷하게 보이는 <br>사랑이란 그런 것 <br>끝도 없이 좋은 것 <br>너 하나만 있으면 <br>웃음질 수 있는 것 <br>너와 함께 있으면 <br>살아갈 수 있는 것 <br>]]></content><category term="뽕짝히어로" label="뽕짝히어로"/><category term="사랑이란" label="사랑이란"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kidnap_Kid/Survive/</id><title>Kidnap Kid - Survive - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:11:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:11:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kidnap_Kid/Survive/" title="Kidnap Kid - Survive - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can't go on, without you Never comes a night, without you I can't go on, without you Never comes a night, without you I can't go on, without you Never comes a night... (Without you) (Without you) I can't go on, without you Never comes a night, without you I can't go on, without you Never comes a night, without you Never comes a nigh... I can't go on... Never comes a nigh... Never comes a nigh... (Without you) (Without you) (Without you) (Without you) (Without you) (without you) (Without you)]]></content><category term="Kidnap Kid" label="Kidnap Kid"/><category term="Survive" label="Survive"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Friction/Long_Gone_Memory_Ulterior_Motive_Remix_Feat_Arlissa/</id><title>Friction - Long Gone Memory (Ulterior Motive Remix) (Feat. Arlissa) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:13:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:13:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Friction/Long_Gone_Memory_Ulterior_Motive_Remix_Feat_Arlissa/" title="Friction - Long Gone Memory (Ulterior Motive Remix) (Feat. Arlissa) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ad Take away your love Take away your pain Now your ghost is long behind me When push comes to shove And they analyze my brain Will I see your ghost behind me All alone again I lost my closest friend You're better off a long gone memory All alone again A tale of mice and men You're better off a long gone memory Long gone memory Who's telling me Know your enemy Long gone memory Frozen in my mind Kiss to pass the time Stranger than in memory, you are [2x] I tried to call your bluff But we never beat the rain I still feel your ghost behind me When push comes to shove And they analyze my brain Will I see your ghost behind me All alone again I lost my closest friend You're better off a long gone memory All alone again A tale of mice and men You're better off a long gone memory Long gone memory Who's telling me Know your enemy Long gone memory [2x] Know your enemy]]></content><category term="Friction" label="Friction"/><category term="Long Gone Memory (Ulterior Motive Remix) (Feat. Arlissa)" label="Long Gone Memory (Ulterior Motive Remix) (Feat. Arlissa)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LUVAN_러반/Keep_It_Goin_On_Feat_PACER/</id><title>LUVAN (러반) - Keep It Goin` On (Feat. $PACER) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:15:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:15:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LUVAN_%EB%9F%AC%EB%B0%98/Keep_It_Goin_On_Feat_PACER/" title="LUVAN (러반) - Keep It Goin` On (Feat. $PACER) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[던져진 신발들 <br>널브러져 있는 옷가지들 <br>and babymaking music <br>그 가운데 있는 너와 나 <br>나는 너를 또 <br>넌 날 입고 있지 <br>구속에 꽃 핀 자유로움 <br>혼돈 속에 맺은 조화로움 <br>이 모든게 좋아 <br>Woo <br>It's such a beautiful night <br>It's such a perfect night <br>이 순간을 영원히 <br>keep it goin' on <br>keep it goin' on <br>너와 <br>Baby tell me what you want <br>I already know what you wanna <br>keep it goin' on <br>keep it goin' on <br>Turn off the light <br>off the phone <br>Close your eyes <br>take this vibe <br>이 jazzy함에 맞춰 <br>지금 우리만의 <br>dancing time <br>너의 흘러 내릴듯한 <br>loose한 fit <br>셔츠에 가려진 건 <br>porn star <br>Okkkkkk 내 akkkkka <br>너의 bababababe <br>i'm so wawawawave <br>Perfert한 이 vibe <br>음 달빛 좀 줘봐 yeah <br>Rock your body now <br>딱 줘봐 니 마음 <br>너와 나 <br>keep it goin' on <br>계속해 <br>From now until the end of time <br>It's such a beautiful night <br>It's such a perfect night <br>이 순간을 영원히 <br>keep it goin' on <br>keep it goin' on <br>너와 <br>Baby tell me what you want <br>I already know what you wanna <br>keep it goin' on <br>keep it goin' on <br>너와 <br>It's such a beautiful night <br>It's such a perfect night <br>이 순간을 영원히 <br>keep it goin' on <br>keep it goin' on <br>너와 <br>Baby tell me what you want <br>I already know what you wanna <br>keep it goin' on <br>keep it goin' on <br>너와 <br>]]></content><category term="LUVAN (러반)" label="LUVAN (러반)"/><category term="Keep It Goin` On (Feat. $PACER)" label="Keep It Goin` On (Feat. $PACER)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김문선/채채퐁_김치퐁_오프닝_주제가/</id><title>김문선 - 채채퐁 김치퐁 (오프닝 주제가) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:17:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:17:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%AC%B8%EC%84%A0/%EC%B1%84%EC%B1%84%ED%90%81_%EA%B9%80%EC%B9%98%ED%90%81_%EC%98%A4%ED%94%84%EB%8B%9D_%EC%A3%BC%EC%A0%9C%EA%B0%80/" title="김문선 - 채채퐁 김치퐁 (오프닝 주제가) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[채채리채채 채채채 퐁포로퐁퐁 채채퐁 <br>치치리치치 김치치 퐁포로퐁퐁 김치퐁 <br>채채퐁 김치퐁 채채 김치 퐁퐁퐁 (퐁퐁퐁) <br>세상을 구하려고 여기 왔다 <br>너의 이름 채채퐁 (채채퐁) <br>어서와 마법구슬 김치파워 김치퐁 (김치퐁) <br>매운맛에 놀랄 거야 시큼시큼 김치파워 <br>채채퐁 김치퐁 (퐁) <br>마무랑 망망 망망 무랑카 둥둥 바리바리 <br>도로붕붕 푸다다 삐리삐리 빠라뽀뽀뽀 <br>폴랑폴랑 샤라랑 <br>신비한 마법의 에너지통 <br>너의 이름 채채퐁 (채채퐁) <br>다섯개 반짝이는 마법구슬 김치퐁 (김치퐁) <br>날 부르면 어디든지 달려간다 김치파워 <br>채채퐁 김치퐁 (퐁) <br>채채리채채 채채채 퐁포로퐁퐁 채채퐁 <br>치치리치치 김치치 퐁포로퐁퐁 김치퐁 <br>채채퐁 김치퐁 채채 김치 퐁퐁퐁 (퐁퐁퐁) <br>세상을 구하려고 여기 왔다 <br>너의 이름 채채퐁 (채채퐁) <br>어서와 마법구슬 김치파워 김치퐁 (김치퐁) <br>매운맛에 놀랄 거야 시큼시큼 김치파워 <br>채채퐁 김치퐁 (퐁) <br>마무랑 망망 망망 무랑카 둥둥 바리바리 <br>도로붕붕 푸다다 삐리삐리 빠라뽀뽀뽀 <br>폴랑폴랑 샤라랑 <br>신비한 마법의 에너지통 <br>너의 이름 채채퐁 (채채퐁) <br>다섯개 반짝이는 마법구슬 김치퐁 (김치퐁) <br>날 부르면 어디든지 달려간다 김치파워 <br>채채퐁 김치퐁 (퐁) <br>채채리채채 채채채 퐁포로퐁퐁 채채퐁 <br>치치리치치 김치치 퐁포로퐁퐁 김치퐁 <br>채채퐁 김치퐁 채채 김치 퐁퐁퐁 (퐁퐁퐁) <br>채채퐁 김치퐁]]></content><category term="김문선" label="김문선"/><category term="채채퐁 김치퐁 (오프닝 주제가)" label="채채퐁 김치퐁 (오프닝 주제가)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박상길/샤랄랄라/</id><title>박상길 - 샤랄랄라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:19:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:19:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%83%81%EA%B8%B8/%EC%83%A4%EB%9E%84%EB%9E%84%EB%9D%BC/" title="박상길 - 샤랄랄라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한걸음 두 걸음 <br>맞춰 걸었던 <br>너의 두발이 <br>귀엽게만 보이는데 <br>쬐끄만 키에 <br>바보 같은 널 <br>바라보면서 괜히 <br>웃음만 지어 난 <br>오늘은 어떤 <br>약속이였는지 <br>오랜만에 보는 <br>너의 꾸민 모습에 <br>괜스레 아닌 척 <br>하고 있지만 <br>내 두 눈에 비친 <br>너는 취향저격 <br>하얀 원피스 <br>넌 샤랄랄랄라 <br>내 맘을 흔들어 <br>너의 향기 <br>또 샤랄랄랄라 <br>내 맘이 흔들려 <br>어설픈 장난에 <br>웃음 지었던 <br>너의 모습이 <br>귀엽게만 보이는데 <br>엉뚱한 너의 <br>말장난에 난 <br>재미 없다며 <br>너의 볼을 꼬집곤 해 <br>내일은 어떤 <br>약속이 있는지 <br>오랜만에 보는 <br>너의 들뜬 모습에 <br>괜스레 아닌 척 <br>하고 있지만 <br>내 두 눈에 비친 <br>너는 취향저격 <br>하얀 원피스 <br>넌 샤랄랄랄라 <br>내 맘을 흔들어 <br>너의 향기 <br>또 샤랄랄랄라 <br>내 맘이 흔들려 <br>네 얼굴에 <br>무슨 남친 이냐며 <br>익숙해진 듯한 <br>너와 나의 거리가 <br>아닌 척 하며 <br>떨려오는 건 <br>나의 착각인지 <br>두 눈을 감아도 <br>떠오르는 모습에 <br>난 잠시 너와의 <br>연애를 상상하곤 해 <br>하얀 원피스 <br>넌 샤랄랄랄라 <br>내 맘을 흔들어 <br>너의 향기 <br>또 샤랄랄랄라 <br>내 맘이 흔들려 <br>]]></content><category term="박상길" label="박상길"/><category term="샤랄랄라" label="샤랄랄라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BeatBurger/Music_is_Wonderful_Feat_BoA_Inst/</id><title>BeatBurger - Music is Wonderful (Feat. BoA) (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:19:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:19:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BeatBurger/Music_is_Wonderful_Feat_BoA_Inst/" title="BeatBurger - Music is Wonderful (Feat. BoA) (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무도 대답할 수 없죠 <br>삶이란 여행에 대해 <br>하루하루 지나기도 벅차죠 <br>말로는 표현할 수 있죠 <br>그리고픈 내 모습에 대해 <br>걱정과 두려움이 앞서 있지만 <br>의미 없는 세상이란 존재하지 않죠 <br>Music is wonderful <br>의미 없는 사람이란 존재하지 않죠 <br>Music is wonderful <br>아름다웠던 시간은 항상 왜 급해 <br>우릴 힘들게 하는 건 또 반복돼 <br>걱정하지들 말고 <br>뻔하게 또 너를 믿어 봐 <br>한 번 Never ever 매번 매일 달라 <br>Music is wonderful <br>Music is wonderful <br>Music is wonderful <br>어디를 가더라도 <br>또 의미를 찾는다고 <br>항상 생각 안에서 <br>날 자유롭게 만드는 건 나라고 <br>누가 뭐라고 해도 제일 잘 아는 건 <br>결국은 나뿐이라고 <br>가장 어두운 밤은 <br>해가 뜨기 전이라고 <br>조금 기다리면 돼 <br>귀를 닫아버린 소문 <br>입을 막아버린 Magic <br>타협이란 수갑을 채웠지만 <br>뜻대로 되게 할 순 없죠 <br>자유 속에 피는 꽃이 이제 <br>피어나기 시작한 지금 이 순간 <br>의미 없는 세상이란 존재하지 않죠 <br>Music is wonderful <br>의미 없는 사람이란 존재하지 않죠 <br>Music is wonderful <br>Music is wonderful <br>Music is wonderful <br>의미 없는 세상이란 존재하지 않죠 <br>Music is wonderful <br>의미 없는 사람이란 존재하지 않죠 <br>Music is wonderful <br>]]></content><category term="BeatBurger" label="BeatBurger"/><category term="Music is Wonderful (Feat. BoA) (Inst.)" label="Music is Wonderful (Feat. BoA) (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BeatBurger/Music_is_Wonderful_Feat_BoA/</id><title>BeatBurger - Music is Wonderful (Feat. BoA) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:19:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:19:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BeatBurger/Music_is_Wonderful_Feat_BoA/" title="BeatBurger - Music is Wonderful (Feat. BoA) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무도 대답할 수 없죠 <br>삶이란 여행에 대해 <br>하루하루 지나기도 벅차죠 <br>말로는 표현할 수 있죠 <br>그리고픈 내 모습에 대해 <br>걱정과 두려움이 앞서 있지만 <br>의미 없는 세상이란 존재하지 않죠 <br>Music is wonderful <br>의미 없는 사람이란 존재하지 않죠 <br>Music is wonderful <br>아름다웠던 시간은 항상 왜 급해 <br>우릴 힘들게 하는 건 또 반복돼 <br>걱정하지들 말고 <br>뻔하게 또 너를 믿어 봐 <br>한 번 Never ever 매번 매일 달라 <br>Music is wonderful <br>Music is wonderful <br>Music is wonderful <br>어디를 가더라도 <br>또 의미를 찾는다고 <br>항상 생각 안에서 <br>날 자유롭게 만드는 건 나라고 <br>누가 뭐라고 해도 제일 잘 아는 건 <br>결국은 나뿐이라고 <br>가장 어두운 밤은 <br>해가 뜨기 전이라고 <br>조금 기다리면 돼 <br>귀를 닫아버린 소문 <br>입을 막아버린 Magic <br>타협이란 수갑을 채웠지만 <br>뜻대로 되게 할 순 없죠 <br>자유 속에 피는 꽃이 이제 <br>피어나기 시작한 지금 이 순간 <br>의미 없는 세상이란 존재하지 않죠 <br>Music is wonderful <br>의미 없는 사람이란 존재하지 않죠 <br>Music is wonderful <br>Music is wonderful <br>Music is wonderful <br>의미 없는 세상이란 존재하지 않죠 <br>Music is wonderful <br>의미 없는 사람이란 존재하지 않죠 <br>Music is wonderful <br>]]></content><category term="BeatBurger" label="BeatBurger"/><category term="Music is Wonderful (Feat. BoA)" label="Music is Wonderful (Feat. BoA)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/장동우_인피니트/마음에_묻다_Feat_윤소윤/</id><title>장동우 (인피니트) - 마음에 묻다 (Feat. 윤소윤) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:19:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:19:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%B0_%EC%9D%B8%ED%94%BC%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8/%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C%EC%97%90_%EB%AC%BB%EB%8B%A4_Feat_%EC%9C%A4%EC%86%8C%EC%9C%A4/" title="장동우 (인피니트) - 마음에 묻다 (Feat. 윤소윤) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[받는 게 익숙했던 걸까 <br>편안함에 전에 <br>나를 잊었나 <br>한 번에 새긴 상처 <br>따른 책임과 추억 <br>이게 아닌데 <br>마음만 앞세워 <br>서툴렀어 늦을까 봐 <br>성급했어 서둘렀어 <br>섣불렀던 판단에 <br>서로를 등지네 <br>결국 end <br>이렇게 끝이 될 <br>시작이 보이는 길이지만 <br>택할 수밖에 없고 일일이 <br>사랑 이별 누구나 <br>한 번 겪는 견딜 수 <br>있을 정도의 아픔 <br>look deeper <br>노력해도 바꿀 수 없는 것 <br>무슨 짓을 해도 <br>절대 바뀔 수 없는 것 <br>사람 그대로 <br>모습의 다름 <br>잡을 수 없는 <br>그대의 손과 마음 <br>I know I still love you <br>붙잡을 수 없어 <br>woo woo I miss you whoo woo <br>I miss the day with you <br>매일 밤 너를 그려 <br>woo woo <br>어려워 잊어버릴 수 <br>없는 인연 <br>Beat the grief <br>안 돼 못 견뎌 <br>이뤄지지 않더라도 빌어 <br>제발 내 사람은 <br>데려가지 말아줘 <br>맘이 아프게 하는 걸까 <br>그걸 놓지 않으려 <br>하는 맘이 날 <br>아프게 하는 걸까 <br>아마도 영원 안에 <br>영원하게 살아주길 바라는 <br>착각이었겠지 <br>Can’t let it go <br>If you really want to know <br>다 말해줄 수 있어 <br>그렇게 사랑했던 <br>넌 어디 있니 <br>죽을 때까지 <br>관둘 수 없어 <br>묻어 덮으려 해도 <br>담을 용기가 작아 <br>숨어 몰랐던 척하기엔 <br>내가 내가 아닌 듯해 <br>보고 싶어도 <br>볼 수 없는 사람 <br>표현이 낯설어서 늦은 거라 <br>뒤늦은 후회에 <br>꺼내봤자 못 들을 수밖에 <br>그댄 멀리 다른 세상 <br>하늘을 보기에 <br>I know I still love you <br>붙잡을 수 없어 <br>woo woo I miss you <br>whoo woo <br>I miss the day with you <br>매일 밤 너를 그려 <br>woo woo <br>It’s time to end up <br>안될 걸 잘 알지만 <br>반복하겠지 <br>또 보고 싶겠지 난 <br>돌아올 곳이 달라져 <br>익숙해지기만 하면 돼 <br>It’s time to end up <br>잊을 수 없겠지만 <br>한번 더 해내어 볼게 <br>내게 말했던 대로 <br>처음 봤을 때 너밖에 <br>없다던 말 새겨보지만 <br>잘 안되잖아 <br>I know I still love you <br>붙잡을 수 없어 <br>woo woo I miss you <br>whoo woo <br>I miss you baby <br>I miss the day with you <br>매일 밤 너를 그려 <br>woo woo <br><br>]]></content><category term="장동우 (인피니트)" label="장동우 (인피니트)"/><category term="마음에 묻다 (Feat. 윤소윤)" label="마음에 묻다 (Feat. 윤소윤)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/산체스_Sanchez/가까이_와요_Feat_케이시/</id><title>산체스 (Sanchez) - 가까이 와요 (Feat. 케이시) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:19:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:19:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%82%B0%EC%B2%B4%EC%8A%A4_Sanchez/%EA%B0%80%EA%B9%8C%EC%9D%B4_%EC%99%80%EC%9A%94_Feat_%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4%EC%8B%9C/" title="산체스 (Sanchez) - 가까이 와요 (Feat. 케이시) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[맑았던 날 우리 흐렸던 날 <br>잊지 말고 Let's stay together <br>맑았던 날 우리 흐렸던 날 <br>잊지 말고 Let's stay together <br>가까이 와요 떨리는 걸요 <br>우리 둘이 가을 향기보다 짙은 밤 <br>오늘은 허락 없이 훔쳐요 <br>그대 입술을 천천히 <br>오늘 머리한 거 참 예쁘네 <br>한번 더 반할 것 같아 <br>친구들도 얘기해 우리 둘 <br>정말 잘 어울린대 <br>화장 안한 얼굴마저도 <br>예쁘면 어떻게 해 <br>나 너 때문에 불안해지는 걸 <br>여사친들 연락 오면 <br>괜시리 질투를 해 <br>걱정 마요 난 너밖에 없어 <br>가까이 와요 가까이 와요 <br>떨리는 걸요 떨리는 걸요 <br>우리 둘이 가을 향기보다 짙은 밤 <br>오늘은 허락 없이 훔쳐요 <br>그대 입술을 천천히 <br>I love you You love me too <br>You love me I love you too <br>닮아가는 우리 둘 어떡해요 <br>I love you You love me too <br>You love me I love you too <br>흠뻑 빠진 우리 둘 아이 몰라요 <br>요즘 연애 방식 참 건조해 <br>우리는 그러지 말자 <br>사랑만 하기에도 부족한데 <br>밀당이 왜 필요해 <br>맛있는 것 먹으러 가요 <br>오늘은 내가 살게 <br>경리단길 mexican food 어때요 <br>운동은 너무 하지 마요 <br>다칠까 봐 걱정 돼요 <br>나는 지금 그대로가 좋아 <br>Girl you know it can be a <br>sunny day or a rainy day <br>We don't know <br>But I promise you I'll be there <br>네 곁에 있을게 <br>I love you You love me too <br>You love me I love you too <br>닮아가는 우리 둘 어떡해요 <br>I love you You love me too <br>You love me I love you too <br>흠뻑 빠진 우리 둘 아이 몰라요 <br>맑았던 날 우리 흐렸던 날 <br>잊지 말고 Let's stay together <br>맑았던 날 우리 흐렸던 날 <br>잊지 말고 Let's stay together <br>]]></content><category term="산체스 (Sanchez)" label="산체스 (Sanchez)"/><category term="가까이 와요 (Feat. 케이시)" label="가까이 와요 (Feat. 케이시)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Hate_To_See_You_Go/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Hate To See You Go - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:19:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:19:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Hate_To_See_You_Go/" title="The Rolling Stones - Hate To See You Go - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Girl why you left me <br>left me here to cry <br>Know I love her <br>she's my desire <br>She's my desire <br>She's my desire <br>Came home this mornin' <br>about half past four <br>Found that note lyin' <br>on my floor <br>Girl why you left me <br>you just don't know <br>You heard some bad talk <br>somethin' that you said <br>Somethin' that you said <br>Somethin' that you said <br>Come on back baby <br>baby please don't go <br>I love you <br>you'll never know <br>You'll never know <br>You'll never know <br>My kind of baby <br>you know it's so <br>I gon' tell you <br>and it ain't no joke <br>No it ain't no joke <br>No it ain't no joke <br>It ain't no joke <br>Come on back baby <br>you know you done me wrong <br>You know I love you <br>please come on home <br>Come on back home <br>Come on back home <br>Come on back home <br>Come on back home <br>Come on back home <br>]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Hate To See You Go" label="Hate To See You Go"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nightly/No_Vacancy/</id><title>Nightly - No Vacancy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:19:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:19:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nightly/No_Vacancy/" title="Nightly - No Vacancy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Verse 1 <br>Break through the neon lights <br>Stay up to talk all night <br>Sneak in the windowpanes, you call my name <br>When I'm with you <br>Feels like fire <br><br>Verse 2 <br>Hey, but you feel it too <br>Inhale and exhale you <br>It's a little too much for me <br>Too much too soon <br>When I'm with you <br>It feels like fire <br><br>Hook <br>Nothing is easy, baby <br>I wish I could let you in <br>But inside of me <br>There's a sign that reads, 'no vacancy' <br><br>Verse 3 <br>Flashbacks to hotel rooms <br>Echoes of me and you <br>What I wouldn't give to be there one more time <br>Without you here <br>Feels like fire <br><br>Hook <br>Nothing is easy, baby <br>I wish I could let you in <br>But inside of me <br>There's a sign that reads, 'no vacancy' <br><br>Hook #2 <br>Nothing is easy, baby <br>I wish I could let you in <br>But inside of me <br>There's a sign that reads, 'no vacancy' <br>No vacancy x2 <br>X2]]></content><category term="Nightly" label="Nightly"/><category term="No Vacancy" label="No Vacancy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nightly/Honest/</id><title>Nightly - Honest - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:19:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:19:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nightly/Honest/" title="Nightly - Honest - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Are you happy now baby <br>With your eyelashes on <br>Is it a new revelation <br>Who you tryna cover up for <br>Yeah, I heard that you've been changing <br>Heard you got a new man <br>You've been doing things lately I don't understand <br><br>Pre-Chorus <br>Go ahead play pretend <br>The truth hurts but in the end <br><br>Hook <br>At least we were honest <br>Honestly, something isn't right <br>I know you're lying, babe <br>Lying with him at night <br>We used to sleep together <br>Through all the lows and highs <br>We used to see in color <br>Now it's just black and white <br>At least we were honest x2 <br><br>Verse 2 <br>It was so close baby <br>So close I locked every door <br>I used to tell you everything now I can't open up anymore <br>Guess I'm the one that's faking, oh <br>Guess I'm the one that's faking now <br><br>Hook <br>At least we were honest <br>Honestly, something isn't right <br>I know you're lying, babe <br>Lying with him at night <br>We used to sleep together <br>Through all the lows and highs <br>We used to see in color <br>Now it's just black and white <br>At least we were honest x2 <br><br>X2]]></content><category term="Nightly" label="Nightly"/><category term="Honest" label="Honest"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nightly/Talk_To_Me/</id><title>Nightly - Talk To Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:19:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:19:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nightly/Talk_To_Me/" title="Nightly - Talk To Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1] Often don't know my own [?] Haunted by the soft sound of your voice Watching, stealing glances for me Body language calling, oh, my name [Pre-Chorus] On and on I can't escape it [Chorus] When the lights are faded And he's not coming home Talk to me, talk to me Talk to me, talk to me If you need somebody And you're feeling all alone Talk to me, talk to me Talk to me, talk to me [Verse 2] Classic, touch you so electric Hold just like kinetic [?] Tragic, I know you could have it Baby, just imagine you and me [Pre-Chorus] On and on I can't escape it [Chorus] When the lights are faded And he's not coming home Talk to me, talk to me Talk to me, talk to me If you need somebody And you're feeling all alone Talk to me, talk to me Talk to me, talk to me [Pre-Chorus] On and on On and onI can't escape it [Chorus] When the lights are faded And he's not coming home Talk to me, talk to me Talk to me, talk to me If you need somebody And you're feeling all alone Talk to me, talk to me Talk to me, talk to me [Outro] Talk to me, talk to me Talk to me, talk to me Talk to me, talk to me Talk to me, talk to me]]></content><category term="Nightly" label="Nightly"/><category term="Talk To Me" label="Talk To Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/교회형들/뭐가_보여_Feat_박형균·노래하는_주뇽이/</id><title>교회형들 - 뭐가 보여 (Feat. 박형균·노래하는 주뇽이) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:19:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:19:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B5%90%ED%9A%8C%ED%98%95%EB%93%A4/%EB%AD%90%EA%B0%80_%EB%B3%B4%EC%97%AC_Feat_%EB%B0%95%ED%98%95%EA%B7%A0%C2%B7%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%A3%BC%EB%87%BD%EC%9D%B4/" title="교회형들 - 뭐가 보여 (Feat. 박형균·노래하는 주뇽이) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈을 떠 오늘 아침도 <br>아이폰을 켜서 <br>확인하지 알림도 <br>페이스북 인스타그램 <br>그런것들에 현혹돼 <br>버릇되어버린 죄 짓고 <br>살아가는 것 <br>그냥 보이는대로 보고 <br>곧이 곧대로 생각해 <br>이쯤에서 짚고 <br>넘어가야될것만 나는 같아 <br>태초에서도 그랬듯이 <br>먹음직도 보암직도 <br>선악과를 먹게 된거야 <br>하나님을 보고싶어 <br>정작 봐야할 것들을 못보게 돼 <br>그리스도로 절대 못 가게 해 <br>실상을 봐야해 <br>내가 보고 듣고 느끼는 것들이 <br>다 진짜는 아냐 정신 차려야해 <br>너가 지금 진짜로 보고 있는것이 <br>뭔지 알아야해 <br>빨간색 안경을 쓰면 뭐가 보여 <br>온통 빨간 세상이 보여 <br>내 생각을 쓰면 뭐가 보여 <br>불평과 불만 탐심이 보여 <br>하나님의 영을 쓰면 뭐가 보여 <br>못자국난 하나님의 손길이 보여 <br>못자국난 하나님의 손길이 보여 <br>못자국난 하나님의 손길이 보여 <br>What do you see in your eyes <br>누가 범사에 감사를 하게 될까 <br>일상의 모든 순간에 하나님과 <br>그 분의 손으로 행한 일을 봐 <br>You must say thanks a lot <br>다시 말해 감사가 없다는 건 <br>마음 속 은혜의 강이 가물어 <br>시야가 무뎌져서 <br>아무것에서도 <br>하나님이 보이지 않는 것 uh <br>가나안의 정탐꾼 같애 <br>내가 메뚜기 같대 <br>I need the 여호수아 갈렙 <br>같은 믿음으로 주 발 앞에 <br>내 자신이 상한 갈대 <br>임을 시인하며 나아갈 때 <br>쉬지 않고 내 기도에 응답해 <br>주시는 주의 <br>상이 맺혀 내 눈안에 <br>빨간색 안경을 쓰면 뭐가 보여 <br>온통 빨간 세상이 보여 <br>내 생각을 쓰면 뭐가 보여 <br>불평과 불만 탐심이 보여 <br>하나님의 영을 쓰면 뭐가 보여 <br>못자국난 하나님의 손길이 보여 <br>못자국난 하나님의 손길이 보여 <br>못자국난 하나님의 손길이 보여 <br>What do you see in your eyes <br>It tells you who you are <br>What do you see in your eyes <br>It tells you who you are <br>]]></content><category term="교회형들" label="교회형들"/><category term="뭐가 보여 (Feat. 박형균·노래하는 주뇽이)" label="뭐가 보여 (Feat. 박형균·노래하는 주뇽이)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나음/아시죠/</id><title>나음 - 아시죠 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:19:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:19:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EC%9D%8C/%EC%95%84%EC%8B%9C%EC%A3%A0/" title="나음 - 아시죠 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아시죠 당신 앞에서 <br>단둘이 이야기할 때 <br>어떤 말도 차마 하기가 어려울 때 <br>아시죠 아무것도 몰라서 <br>한 발자국 내딜 수 없고 <br>떨림 아닌 두렴 가운데 힘이 들 때 <br>아시죠 이 말 한 마디면 <br>많은 말 하지 않아도 <br>당신은 알고 계시죠 <br>아시죠 이 안에 있는 <br>어떠한 많은 의미를 <br>당신은 알고 계시죠 <br>아시죠 당신 앞에서 <br>단둘이 이야기할 때 <br>어떤 말도 차마 하기가 어려울 때 <br>아시죠 아무것도 몰라서 <br>한 발자국 내딜 수 없고 <br>떨림 아닌 두렴 가운데 힘이 들 때 <br>아시죠 이 말 한 마디면 <br>많은 말 하지 않아도 <br>당신은 알고 계시죠 <br>아시죠 이 안에 있는 <br>어떠한 많은 의미를 <br>당신은 알고 계시죠 <br>아시죠 알고 계시죠 <br>You know me better than I <br>You know me better than I 아시죠 우 <br>알아요 갇힌 내 고집 <br>당신이 함께 한다면 <br>더딛어 나갈 수 있죠 <br>알아요 당신의 기다림 <br>말보다 높은 그 사랑 <br>당신을 사랑하는 줄 <br>아시죠 이 말 한 마디면 <br>많은 말 하지 않아도 <br>당신은 알고 계시죠 <br>아시죠 이 안에 있는 <br>어떠한 많은 의미를 <br>당신은 알고 계시죠 <br>아시죠 아시죠 아시죠 아시죠 <br>]]></content><category term="나음" label="나음"/><category term="아시죠" label="아시죠"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucas__Steve/Love_On_My_Mind/</id><title>Lucas &amp; Steve - Love On My Mind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:20:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:20:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucas__Steve/Love_On_My_Mind/" title="Lucas &amp; Steve - Love On My Mind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Bridge] <br>I live without you <br>I can live without you <br>I can live without you <br>I can live without you <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I got love on my mind <br>And no usin' the rest of time <br>I got love on my mind <br>And no usin' the rest of time <br>I got love <br>I can live without you <br><br>[Drop] <br><br>I got love on my mind <br><br>[Verse] <br>When the heartache is over <br>I know I will be missin' you <br>Won't look over my shoulder <br>I know I can live without you <br><br>[Bridge] <br>I live without you <br>I can live without you <br>I can live without you <br>I can live without you <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I got love on my mind <br>And no usin' the rest of time <br>I got love on my mind <br>And no usin' the rest of time <br>I got love <br>I can live without you <br><br>[Drop] <br><br>I got love on my mind <br><br>[Bridge] <br>I live without you <br>I can live without you <br>I can live without you <br>I can live without you <br><br>I got love on my mind]]></content><category term="Lucas &amp; Steve" label="Lucas &amp; Steve"/><category term="Love On My Mind" label="Love On My Mind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/터보트로닉_Turbotronic/불타_Original_Mix/</id><title>터보트로닉 (Turbotronic) - 불타 (Original Mix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:20:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:20:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%84%B0%EB%B3%B4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A1%9C%EB%8B%89_Turbotronic/%EB%B6%88%ED%83%80_Original_Mix/" title="터보트로닉 (Turbotronic) - 불타 (Original Mix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[3 2 1 Come On <br>불타 불타 불타는 청춘 <br>불타는 이 밤 <br>Let's get up and dance <br>불타 불타 불타는 청춘 <br>불타는 내 맘 <br>I just wanna dance <br>Everybody 불타는 밤 <br>Put your hands in the air <br>Let me hear you say yeah <br>Are you ready 불타는 밤 <br>Feel the heat of the night <br>We’re gonna party tonight <br>3 2 1 Come On <br>불타 불타 불타는 청춘 <br>불타는 이 밤 <br>Let's get up and dance <br>불타 불타 불타는 청춘 <br>불타는 내 맘 <br>I just wanna dance <br>Everybody 불타는 밤 <br>Put your hands in the air <br>Let me hear you say yeah <br>Are you ready 불타는 밤 <br>Feel the heat of the night <br>We’re gonna party tonight <br>]]></content><category term="터보트로닉 (Turbotronic)" label="터보트로닉 (Turbotronic)"/><category term="불타 (Original Mix)" label="불타 (Original Mix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/터보트로닉_Turbotronic/불타_Original_Edit/</id><title>터보트로닉 (Turbotronic) - 불타 (Original Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:20:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:20:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%84%B0%EB%B3%B4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A1%9C%EB%8B%89_Turbotronic/%EB%B6%88%ED%83%80_Original_Edit/" title="터보트로닉 (Turbotronic) - 불타 (Original Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[3 2 1 Come On <br>불타 불타 불타는 청춘 <br>불타는 이 밤 <br>Let's get up and dance <br>불타 불타 불타는 청춘 <br>불타는 내 맘 <br>I just wanna dance <br>Everybody 불타는 밤 <br>Put your hands in the air <br>Let me hear you say yeah <br>Are you ready 불타는 밤 <br>Feel the heat of the night <br>We’re gonna party tonight <br>3 2 1 Come On <br>불타 불타 불타는 청춘 <br>불타는 이 밤 <br>Let's get up and dance <br>불타 불타 불타는 청춘 <br>불타는 내 맘 <br>I just wanna dance <br>Everybody 불타는 밤 <br>Put your hands in the air <br>Let me hear you say yeah <br>Are you ready 불타는 밤 <br>Feel the heat of the night <br>We’re gonna party tonight <br>]]></content><category term="터보트로닉 (Turbotronic)" label="터보트로닉 (Turbotronic)"/><category term="불타 (Original Edit)" label="불타 (Original Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Secret_Code/우리를_사랑하사_Feat_조선/</id><title>Secret Code - 우리를 사랑하사 (Feat. 조선) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:20:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:20:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Secret_Code/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%A5%BC_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC_Feat_%EC%A1%B0%EC%84%A0/" title="Secret Code - 우리를 사랑하사 (Feat. 조선) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주 하나님 우리를 사랑하사 <br>독생자 예수님 주셨을 때 <br>그 마음은 얼마나 아프셨을까 <br>하나님 그 크신 사랑의 마음이 <br>피를 흘려 우리를 살리려고 <br>십자가 사랑 보여주시고 <br>다시 오실 <br>그 날을 약속하시며 <br>주님의 능력 내게 주셨네 <br>하나님 크고 넓으신 사랑 <br>내 영혼이 기대하네 <br>지극히 높은 하나님 사랑 <br>내 영혼이 찬양하네 <br>주의 보혈 생명수 주시려고 <br>험한 그 십자가에 흘렀네 <br>하늘 나라 내게도 허락하시니 <br>영원한 안식 누리겠네 <br>하나님 우릴 사랑하셔서 <br>오래 참고 기다리네 <br>세상이 알지 못한 그 사랑 <br>나는 아네 아버지 마음 <br>하나님 우릴 사랑하셔서 <br>오래 참고 기다리네 <br>세상이 알지 못한 그 사랑 <br>나는 아네 아버지 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="Secret Code" label="Secret Code"/><category term="우리를 사랑하사 (Feat. 조선)" label="우리를 사랑하사 (Feat. 조선)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Secret_Code/내_기쁜_마음으로/</id><title>Secret Code - 내 기쁜 마음으로 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:20:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:20:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Secret_Code/%EB%82%B4_%EA%B8%B0%EC%81%9C_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C%EC%9C%BC%EB%A1%9C/" title="Secret Code - 내 기쁜 마음으로 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 기쁜 마음으로 <br>주님을 찬양하네 <br>영원한 나의 소망 <br>주님을 찬양해 <br>내 기쁜 마음으로 <br>주님을 노래하네 <br>사랑의 주님을 <br>내 영혼 노래해 <br>나의 기쁨 되시는 <br>우리 주님께 <br>가진 것 모두 다 드리리 <br>나 비록 마음은 <br>연약하지만 <br>주님은 내게 채우시리 <br>언제나 기쁨 되시는 <br>주님을 찬양 하리라 <br>즐거운 나의 <br>생활 속에 주님을 <br>영원히 살아계시는 <br>주님을 노래하리라 <br>슬픔이 가득할 때 <br>눈물 속에 주님을 <br>나의 기쁨 되시는 <br>우리 주님께 <br>가진 것 모두 다 드리리 <br>나 비록 마음은 <br>연약하지만 <br>주님은 내게 채우시리 <br>언제나 기쁨 되시는 <br>주님을 찬양 하리라 <br>즐거운 나의 <br>생활 속에 주님을 <br>영원히 살아계시는 <br>주님을 노래하리라 <br>슬픔이 가득할 때 <br>눈물 속에 주님을 <br>눈물 속에 주님을 <br>눈물 속에 주님을 <br>]]></content><category term="Secret Code" label="Secret Code"/><category term="내 기쁜 마음으로" label="내 기쁜 마음으로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Secret_Code/주바라기_Feat_조선/</id><title>Secret Code - 주바라기 (Feat. 조선) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:20:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:20:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Secret_Code/%EC%A3%BC%EB%B0%94%EB%9D%BC%EA%B8%B0_Feat_%EC%A1%B0%EC%84%A0/" title="Secret Code - 주바라기 (Feat. 조선) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어두운 세상 속에 <br>생명의 빛으로 다가오신 주님 <br>하루하루를 살아가는 동안에 <br>천국의 소망을 이루게 하소서 <br>참다운 사랑 속에 <br>영원한 생명을 약속하신 주님 <br>인생의 어려움이 닥쳐와도 <br>눈 들어 주 바라기 되게 하소서 <br>한없는 사랑 내게 주시니 <br>모두 감당할 수 조차 없어요 <br>오래 전부터 나를 먼저 아시고 <br>주님의 귀한 사랑을 알게 하셨네 <br>오 주여 나의 마음 드려서 <br>주님의 사랑을 노래해요 <br>오 주여 밤 하늘의 별님과 함께 <br>주님의 영원하심을 노래해요 <br>영원한 생명 내게 주시려고 <br>주님 골고다 언덕을 가셨죠 <br>십자가에서 흘린 주님의 피가 <br>우리를 살리려고 온 땅을 적셨네 <br>오 주여 내 모든 것 드려서 <br>영원한 그 나라를 노래해요 <br>오 주여 내게 주신 그 사랑으로 <br>주님을 세상 끝까지 <br>영원한 하나님 나라 <br>나 사는 동안 노래해요 <br>한 송이 주 바라기 되게 하소서 <br>]]></content><category term="Secret Code" label="Secret Code"/><category term="주바라기 (Feat. 조선)" label="주바라기 (Feat. 조선)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Secret_Code/나만_아니었어도/</id><title>Secret Code - 나만 아니었어도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:20:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:20:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Secret_Code/%EB%82%98%EB%A7%8C_%EC%95%84%EB%8B%88%EC%97%88%EC%96%B4%EB%8F%84/" title="Secret Code - 나만 아니었어도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나만 아니었어도 <br>주님 십자가 고통 <br>받지 않았을텐데 <br>나의 커다란 죄가 못이 되어 <br>주님의 고운 살을 찢고 있었네 <br>주님의 고통스런 얼굴 <br>찢긴 상처 나의 마음이 아파와요 <br>귀하게 흘리신 물과 피가 <br>십자가에 흘러 온 땅을 적시네 <br>나를 위해 사람의 모습으로 <br>십자가의 아픔을 당하신 주님 <br>하지만 아직도 죄짓는 <br>내 모습 때문에 <br>주님 고통 받지는 않을까 <br>주님 용서하세요 <br>주님이 날 이처럼 사랑하셨건만 <br>매일 주님 못 박았죠 <br>이제 주 사랑 하는 맘 <br>오늘 사랑한 것보다 <br>내일 더 사랑하며 <br>주님 나라 갈 때까지 <br>나를 위해 사람의 모습으로 <br>십자가의 아픔을 당하신 주님 <br>하지만 아직도 죄짓는 <br>내 모습 때문에 <br>주님 고통 받지는 않을까 <br>주님 용서하세요 <br>주님이 날 이처럼 사랑하셨건만 <br>매일 주님 못 박았죠 <br>이제 주 사랑 하는 맘 <br>오늘 사랑한 것보다 <br>내일 더 사랑하며 <br>주님 나라 갈 때까지 <br>주님 용서하세요 <br>주님이 날 이처럼 사랑하셨건만 <br>매일 주님 못 박았죠 <br>이제 주 사랑 하는 맘 <br>오늘 사랑한 것보다 <br>내일 더 사랑하며 <br>주님 나라 갈 때까지 <br>주님 나라 갈 때까지 <br>]]></content><category term="Secret Code" label="Secret Code"/><category term="나만 아니었어도" label="나만 아니었어도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한명길/슬픔이_저무는_풍경/</id><title>한명길 - 슬픔이 저무는 풍경 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:20:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:20:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EB%AA%85%EA%B8%B8/%EC%8A%AC%ED%94%94%EC%9D%B4_%EC%A0%80%EB%AC%B4%EB%8A%94_%ED%92%8D%EA%B2%BD/" title="한명길 - 슬픔이 저무는 풍경 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무도 찾지 않는 외로운 길 <br>그 길 끝에서 만난 작은 바닷가 <br>새하얀 조각배 차가운 모래알 <br>잔잔한 파도들의 속삭임들 <br>이제 우린 각자의 일상에 <br>새로운 삶을 위해 걸어 가고 있어 <br>아픈 추억들 슬픈 미련들 <br>모두 다 사라져 <br>아 아쉬움이 밀려와 <br>남아있던 작은 기다림 <br>끝내 감춰왔던 가슴속에 <br>슬픔이 저물어 가고 있어 <br>만남과 이별속에 써내려간 <br>추억의 일기장을 고이 내려놔 <br>더이상 미련도 불안한 내일도 <br>모두 다 사라져 <br>아 아쉬움이 밀려와 <br>남아있던 작은 기다림 <br>끝내 감춰왔던 가슴속에 <br>슬픔이 저물어 가고 있어 <br>노을빛 그려지는 넓은 수평선 <br>파도에 쓸려가는 남은 발자국 <br>아직은 어색한 불안한 내일도 <br>모두 다 사라져 <br>모두 다 사라져 <br>]]></content><category term="한명길" label="한명길"/><category term="슬픔이 저무는 풍경" label="슬픔이 저무는 풍경"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TonicK/놓칠_수_없는_사랑_Prod_By_조연/</id><title>Tonic.K - 놓칠 수 없는 사랑 (Prod. By 조연) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:20:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:20:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TonicK/%EB%86%93%EC%B9%A0_%EC%88%98_%EC%97%86%EB%8A%94_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_Prod_By_%EC%A1%B0%EC%97%B0/" title="Tonic.K - 놓칠 수 없는 사랑 (Prod. By 조연) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[놓칠 수 없는 사랑 <br>그대의 그 사랑 <br>여전히 난 그대를 <br>잊을 수가 없죠 <br>고마워요 그댄 내게 <br>사랑을 속삭였죠 <br>놓칠 수 없는 사랑 <br>난 잊을 수 없네 <br>끊을 수 없는 사랑 <br>포기할 수 없죠 <br>고마워요 그댄 내게 <br>사랑을 속삭였죠 <br>사랑해 난 너를 <br>잊을 수가 없어 <br>사랑해 난 널 <br>포기할 수 없어 <br>결코 놓칠 수 없는 나의 사랑 <br>늘 사랑해 목숨도 바칠게 <br>놓칠 수 없는 사랑 <br>난 잊을 수 없네 <br>끊을 수 없는 사랑 <br>포기할 수 없죠 <br>고마워요 그댄 내게 <br>사랑을 속삭였죠 <br>사랑해 난 너를 <br>잊을 수가 없어 <br>사랑해 난 널 <br>포기할 수 없어 <br>결코 놓칠 수 없는 나의 사랑 <br>늘 사랑해 목숨도 바칠게 <br>사랑해요 그대만을 <br>영원히 사랑해요 <br>사랑해요 그대만을 <br>영원히 사랑해요 <br>사랑해 난 너를 <br>잊을 수가 없어 <br>사랑해 난 널 <br>포기할 수 없어 <br>결코 놓칠 수 없는 나의 사랑 <br>늘 사랑해 목숨도 바칠게 <br>]]></content><category term="Tonic.K" label="Tonic.K"/><category term="놓칠 수 없는 사랑 (Prod. By 조연)" label="놓칠 수 없는 사랑 (Prod. By 조연)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Mary/</id><title>Agnes Obel - Mary - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:20:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:20:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Mary/" title="Agnes Obel - Mary - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Heaven hid her face <br>as we fell down <br>Age old habits echoed <br>in the ground <br>One old sing <br>and one would hold me down <br>They might listen <br>if I make no sound <br>Oh I know this <br>From my high school heart <br>That nothing is over <br>From a touch it will begin <br>Wide on the sky <br>In my house the silence rang <br>so loud <br>Under doorways <br>through the hallway down <br>Waiting for the secret <br>to grow out <br>oh what we do <br>when no one is around <br>Oh I know this <br>From my high school heart <br>That nothing is over <br>From a touch it will begin <br>Wide on the sky <br>In the dark <br>I hear you sing <br>Fingers move <br>and chords they ring <br>Be the witness of my shame <br>Swaying in the summer rain <br>Feathers falling <br>from your wing <br>In the dark <br>I hear you sing <br>Fingers move <br>and chords they ring <br>Be the witness of my shame <br>Swaying in the summer rain <br>Feathers falling <br>from your wing <br>In the dark <br>I hear you sing <br>]]></content><category term="Agnes Obel" label="Agnes Obel"/><category term="Mary" label="Mary"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Golden_Green/</id><title>Agnes Obel - Golden Green - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:20:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:20:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Golden_Green/" title="Agnes Obel - Golden Green - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All I have or should <br>want to be but never could <br>it’s coming at <br>it’s coming at <br>it’s coming at <br>it’s coming at <br>it’s coming at my heart <br>To spoil my soul with fire <br>All my eyes can see is <br>born out of your imagery <br>it’s coming at <br>it’s coming at <br>it’s coming at <br>it’s coming at <br>it’s coming at my heart <br>To scorch the earth with fire <br>tell me who you really love <br>tell me who you really love <br>tell me who you really love <br>Who are you to take over my mind <br>with your eyes on me <br>All for you I am climbing the sky <br>of golden green <br>Angel green and blue <br>I’m gonna leave my mind with you <br>I know I see I wanna be just free <br>I know it craves <br>it’s running through my veins <br>To spoil my soul with fire <br>tell me who you really love <br>tell me who you really love <br>Who are you to take over my mind <br>with your eyes on me <br>All for you I am climbing the sky <br>of golden green <br>Green <br>Green <br>Green <br>]]></content><category term="Agnes Obel" label="Agnes Obel"/><category term="Golden Green" label="Golden Green"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Citizen_Of_Glass/</id><title>Agnes Obel - Citizen Of Glass - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:20:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:20:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Citizen_Of_Glass/" title="Agnes Obel - Citizen Of Glass - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Rend a black drop from my heart <br>With the weight of days <br>The end of time has just begun <br>I hear it call your name <br>And no straining of the string <br>Can reverse what will begin <br>Some let go and some hold on <br>There is no mistake <br>If I could wash all ill away <br>Tell me would you stay <br>And no lovers sin <br>Can reverse what will begin <br>]]></content><category term="Agnes Obel" label="Agnes Obel"/><category term="Citizen Of Glass" label="Citizen Of Glass"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Trojan_Horses/</id><title>Agnes Obel - Trojan Horses - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:20:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:20:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Trojan_Horses/" title="Agnes Obel - Trojan Horses - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[These bare bones are made of glass <br>See-through to the marrow <br>when they pass <br>Seek through the keyhole <br>a fate is cast <br>Deep in the mirror smiling back <br>In shapes like these they run softly <br>Trojan horses Trojan horses <br>Trojan horses Trojan horses <br>Gardens grow in my eyes <br>Oh why do they <br>Gardens grow in my eyes <br>Oh why do they <br>Seek what I seek in a blinding flash <br>These bare bones are made of glass <br>In shapes like these they run softly <br>Trojan horses Trojan horses <br>with all the children <br>with all the children <br>I tell myself I wanna hide <br>I tell myself I wanna be lied to <br>Silent reader of my mind <br>do you know what I will ask of you <br>Tell me if you wanna hide <br>Tell me if you wanna be lied to <br>]]></content><category term="Agnes Obel" label="Agnes Obel"/><category term="Trojan Horses" label="Trojan Horses"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Stone/</id><title>Agnes Obel - Stone - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:20:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:20:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Stone/" title="Agnes Obel - Stone - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They say every sin will have <br>a thousand eyes <br>To guilty fools with guilty minds <br>But I most be cruel to be kind <br>Deep within a my head of stone <br>could I be of stone <br>could I be of stone <br>could I be of stone could I be could I be <br>Oh how the birds forget to sing <br>Do they know where I have been <br>Oh how I will leave you there again <br>Deep within my head of stone <br>could I be of stone <br>could I be of stone <br>could I be of stone could I be could I be <br>You are my only one <br>You are my only one <br>You are my lonely one <br>You are my only one <br>Oh for the trees did grow there <br>and the plants did spring <br>Oh for they know a lovers sin <br>Ain’t made of paper or of string <br>It’s cast into a head of stone <br>could I be of stone <br>could I be of stone <br>could I be of stone could I be could I be <br>]]></content><category term="Agnes Obel" label="Agnes Obel"/><category term="Stone" label="Stone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Its_Happening_Again/</id><title>Agnes Obel - It`s Happening Again - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:20:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:20:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Its_Happening_Again/" title="Agnes Obel - It`s Happening Again - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I swear it is true <br>The past isn't dead <br>It's alive it is happening <br>In the back of my head <br>No future no past <br>No laws of time <br>Can undo what is happening <br>When I close my eyes <br>And with the stars <br>and the moon <br>I woke up in the night <br>In the same place <br>to save me for my eyes <br>It's happening it's happening <br>It's happening it's happening <br>it's happening again <br>It's happening it's happening <br>It's happening it's happening <br>it's happening again <br>I took a day or two <br>to exile from the light <br>To unfold that prisoner <br>they call a mind <br>And for a brief moment <br>we could stop the time <br>But with the stars <br>and the moon <br>I woke up in the night <br>In the same place <br>it was sailing before my eyes <br>It's happening it's happening <br>It's happening it's happening <br>It's happening it's happening <br>It's happening it's happening <br>it's happening again <br>]]></content><category term="Agnes Obel" label="Agnes Obel"/><category term="It`s Happening Again" label="It`s Happening Again"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Familiar/</id><title>Agnes Obel - Familiar - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Familiar/" title="Agnes Obel - Familiar - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Can you walk on the water if I <br>you and I <br>Because your blood's <br>running cold <br>outside the familiar true to life <br>Can you walk on the water if I <br>you and I <br>Or keep your eyes <br>on the road and <br>live in the familiar <br>without you and I <br>It glows with gates of <br>gold to true life <br>For our love is a ghost that <br>the others can't see <br>It's a danger <br>Every shade of us <br>you fade down to keep <br>them in the dark on <br>who we are <br>This love is gonna <br>be the death of me <br>It's a danger <br>Cause our love is a ghost that <br>the others cant see <br>We took a walk to <br>the summit at night <br>you and I <br>To burn a hole in the old grip of <br>the familiar true to life <br>And the dark was opening wide <br>do or die <br>Under a mask of <br>vermillion ruling eyes <br>And our love is a ghost that <br>the others can't see <br>It's a danger <br>Every shade of us <br>you fade down to keep <br>them in the dark on <br>who we are <br>Gonna be the death of me <br>It's danger <br>Cause our love is a ghost that <br>the others cant see <br>]]></content><category term="Agnes Obel" label="Agnes Obel"/><category term="Familiar" label="Familiar"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Stretch_Your_Eyes/</id><title>Agnes Obel - Stretch Your Eyes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Agnes_Obel/Stretch_Your_Eyes/" title="Agnes Obel - Stretch Your Eyes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The darkness and the ghost <br>They dance so sweet and slow <br>Dug-out from below there <br>to damn the gods <br>A grip that will hold <br>So tight and close <br>Around my throat with <br>the weight of all our lives <br>You can give to my heart <br>Thousand words or more <br>You can give to my heart <br>Thousand words or more <br>The drum you stroke <br>Damn that beat so old <br>In the ground it grows there <br>To damn the sun <br>oh what will come to life <br>Gates of gold <br>In your head you hold <br>A kingdom molten <br>May the gods be on your side <br>You can give to my heart <br>Thousand words or more <br>You can give to my heart <br>Thousand words or more <br>]]></content><category term="Agnes Obel" label="Agnes Obel"/><category term="Stretch Your Eyes" label="Stretch Your Eyes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이창휘/묻어버린_아픔/</id><title>이창휘 - 묻어버린 아픔 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%B0%BD%ED%9C%98/%EB%AC%BB%EC%96%B4%EB%B2%84%EB%A6%B0_%EC%95%84%ED%94%94/" title="이창휘 - 묻어버린 아픔 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흔한게 사랑이라지만 <br>나는 그런 사랑 원하지 않아 <br>바라만 봐도 <br>괜히 그냥 좋은 <br>그런 사랑이 나는 좋아 <br>변한 건 세상이라지만 <br>우리 사랑 이대로 간직하면 <br>먼 훗날 함께 <br>마주앉아 둘이 <br>얘기 할 수 있으면 좋아 <br>어둠이 내려와 <br>거리를 떠돌면 <br>부는 바람에 <br>내 모든걸 맡길 텐데 <br>한순간 그렇게 쉽사리 살아도 <br>지금 이순간 나는 행복해 <br>어둠이 내려와 <br>거리를 떠돌면 <br>부는 바람에 <br>내 모든걸 맡길 텐데 <br>한순간 그렇게 쉽사리 살아도 <br>지금 이순간 나는 행복해 <br>지금 이순간 나는 행복해 <br>]]></content><category term="이창휘" label="이창휘"/><category term="묻어버린 아픔" label="묻어버린 아픔"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/베니차_Benny_Char/Freeway/</id><title>베니차 (Benny Char) - Freeway - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B2%A0%EB%8B%88%EC%B0%A8_Benny_Char/Freeway/" title="베니차 (Benny Char) - Freeway - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Like the sun <br>and the stars above our sky <br>Everyone around me <br>will see me shine <br>Nothing is going <br>to bring me down <br>Cause today is the day <br>I wear my crown <br>Open my eyes to see today <br>As everything’s going my way <br>With endless possibilities <br>I can do anything at ease <br>Cruising down the street <br>with no concern <br>Cruising down the street <br>to seize the day <br>Don’t care <br>if I took a wrong turn <br>We’re just guys driving <br>through the freeway <br>So what <br>I got dumped by girlfriend <br>So what <br>I lost my job it’s not the end <br>No one is going <br>to stop me this time <br>Cause this time <br>I’ll make this day mine <br>Open my eyes to see today <br>As everything’s going my way <br>With endless possibilities <br>I can do anything at ease <br>Cruising down the street <br>with no concern <br>Cruising down the street <br>to seize the day <br>Don’t care <br>if I took a wrong turn <br>We’re just guys driving <br>through the freeway <br>Cruising down the street <br>with no concern <br>Cruising down the street <br>to seize the day <br>Don’t care <br>if I took a wrong turn <br>We’re just guys driving <br>through the freeway <br>Cruising down the street <br>with no concern <br>Cruising down the street <br>to seize the day <br>Don’t care <br>if I took a wrong turn <br>We’re just guys driving <br>through the freeway <br>Cruising down the street <br>with no concern <br>Cruising down the street <br>to seize the day <br>Don’t care <br>if I took a wrong turn <br>We’re just guys driving <br>through the freeway <br>]]></content><category term="베니차 (Benny Char)" label="베니차 (Benny Char)"/><category term="Freeway" label="Freeway"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/베니차_Benny_Char/Star_Eyes/</id><title>베니차 (Benny Char) - Star Eyes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B2%A0%EB%8B%88%EC%B0%A8_Benny_Char/Star_Eyes/" title="베니차 (Benny Char) - Star Eyes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You taught me what true love is <br>When you walked in <br>And became my first love <br>Under the cherry blossoms <br>With angel hums <br>That made my heart feel numb <br>I get lost in your eyes <br>Your eyes sparkle like a star <br>Let’s fly into the Neverland <br>And we’ll dance <br>across the moon as I sing <br>As we soar <br>across the Milky Way <br>Cause I get lost in <br>Your star eyes <br>Where was I when I saw you <br>As I watch the star night <br>And kiss you a thousand skies <br>I’ll never let you go <br>As planet earth moves <br>As we watch the stars glow <br>I get lost in your eyes <br>Your eyes sparkle like a star <br>Let’s fly into the Neverland <br>And we’ll dance <br>across the moon as I sing <br>As we soar <br>across the Milkyway <br>Cause I get lost in <br>Your star eyes <br>Let’s fly into the Neverland <br>And we’ll dance <br>across the moon as I sing <br>As we soar <br>across the Milkyway <br>Cause I get lost in <br>Your star eyes <br>]]></content><category term="베니차 (Benny Char)" label="베니차 (Benny Char)"/><category term="Star Eyes" label="Star Eyes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DUVV/Tell_Me/</id><title>DUVV - Tell Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DUVV/Tell_Me/" title="DUVV - Tell Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tell me the way you're moving <br>Tell me the way you're grooving <br>Tell me what got you cruisin' <br>Tell me that <br>all you think about is love <br>Tell me the way you're walking <br>Tell me the way you're talking <br>Tell me the way you'll cool it <br>Tell me that <br>all you think about is love <br>You don't feel like <br>you used to <br>I was warm around you <br>I was cold to please you <br>You don't feel like <br>I should want to <br>Keep a grin just thinking of this <br>The lie that hung <br>right off of your lip <br>Tell me the way you're moving <br>Tell me the way you're grooving <br>Tell me what got you cruisin' <br>Tell me that <br>all you think about is love <br>Tell me the way you're walking <br>Tell me the way you're talking <br>Tell me the way you'll cool it <br>Tell me that <br>all you think about is love <br>all you think about is love <br>Are we just a memory <br>Cause I don't see you here with me <br>Or are just we reluctantly <br>Giving in to what we don't need <br>Loved ya trust ya <br>need ya want you <br>We might have said <br>Loved ya trust ya <br>need ya want you <br>Tell me the way you're moving <br>Tell me the way you're grooving <br>Tell me what got you cruisin' <br>Tell me that <br>all you think about is love <br>Tell me the way you're walking <br>Tell me the way you're talking <br>Tell me the way you'll cool it <br>Tell me that <br>all you think about is love <br>Tell me the way you're moving <br>Tell me the way you're grooving <br>Tell me what got you cruisin' <br>Tell me that <br>all you think about is love <br>Tell me the way you're walking <br>Tell me the way you're talking <br>Tell me the way you'll cool it <br>Tell me that <br>all you think about is love <br>all you think about is love <br>]]></content><category term="DUVV" label="DUVV"/><category term="Tell Me" label="Tell Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Fortress_Feat_어반자카파/</id><title>Far East Movement - Fortress (Feat. 어반자카파) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Fortress_Feat_%EC%96%B4%EB%B0%98%EC%9E%90%EC%B9%B4%ED%8C%8C/" title="Far East Movement - Fortress (Feat. 어반자카파) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[무슨 일이 있어도 <br>구름이 감싸 줄거야 <br>널 지켜줄게 영원하게 <br>내 품에 안전하게 <br>끝까지 네 편이 되어줄게 <br>변하지 않을 사랑 <br>무슨 일이 있어도 <br>Stand behind these fortress walls <br>Stand behind these fortress walls <br>하늘 위로 날아가 <br>Stand behind these fortress walls <br>하늘 위로 날아가 <br>무슨 일이 있어도 <br>구름이 감싸 줄거야 <br>널 지켜줄게 영원하게 <br>내 품에 안전하게 <br>끝까지 네 편이 되어줄게 <br>변하지 않을 사랑 <br>무슨 일이 있어도 <br>Stand behind these fortress walls <br>널 지켜줄게 영원하게 <br>내 품에 안전하게 <br>끝까지 네 편이 되어줄게 <br>변하지 않을 사랑 <br>무슨 일이 있어도 <br>Stand behind these fortress walls <br>]]></content><category term="Far East Movement" label="Far East Movement"/><category term="Fortress (Feat. 어반자카파)" label="Fortress (Feat. 어반자카파)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Forever_Survivor_Feat_Macy_Gray/</id><title>Far East Movement - Forever Survivor (Feat. Macy Gray) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Forever_Survivor_Feat_Macy_Gray/" title="Far East Movement - Forever Survivor (Feat. Macy Gray) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Forever <br>Forever Survivor <br>Sometimes the road <br>ain't that easy <br>And honey <br>all money ain't the same <br>I guess that love <br>ain't that sleezy <br>Sometimes the crowd <br>ain't that loud <br>Seems like the years fly away <br>But I find strength <br>when times get harder <br>I will survive another day <br>Reach the sky <br>smell the roses <br>I will play for you <br>like it's my last show <br>I'm Forever Survivor <br>Forever Survivor <br>So much stronger <br>so much wiser <br>It's the power <br>that's inside me <br>Forever Survivor <br>Forever Survivor <br>And I want to tell you <br>I want to shout <br>I want to scream it <br>out loud <br>Forever Survivor <br>Forever Survivor <br>Maybe the storm <br>will never end <br>Maybe my heart was <br>meant to break <br>If I get tomorrow <br>I'll try again <br>I'm gonna find a <br>better way <br>Tie up my shoes to <br>keep from falling <br>I'm counting <br>every step I take <br>Walking ahead <br>until I'm flying <br>I will survive another day <br>I'm a survivor <br>I'm a survivor <br>Forever <br>Forever <br>Forever <br>Forever <br>Survivor <br>Reach the sky smell the roses <br>I will play for you like <br>it's my last show <br>I'm Forever Survivor <br>Forever Survivor <br>So much stronger <br>so much wiser <br>It's the power <br>that's inside me <br>Forever Survivor <br>Forever Survivor <br>Forever Survivor <br>Forever Survivor <br>And I want to tell you <br>I want to shout <br>I want to scream it <br>out loud <br>Forever Survivor <br>Forever Survivor <br>Forever <br>I'm a Survivor <br>I am Forever <br>I'm a Survivor <br>]]></content><category term="Far East Movement" label="Far East Movement"/><category term="Forever Survivor (Feat. Macy Gray)" label="Forever Survivor (Feat. Macy Gray)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/FBG_Feat_Big_KRIT_MIKNNA/</id><title>Far East Movement - FBG$ (Feat. Big K.R.I.T., MIKNNA) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/FBG_Feat_Big_KRIT_MIKNNA/" title="Far East Movement - FBG$ (Feat. Big K.R.I.T., MIKNNA) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Going out every weekend <br>Spending all of my money <br>Now that I'm alone <br>I ain't got no time for lovin' <br>Ooh oooh I don't know <br>what to do with myself <br>Ooh oooh I don't know <br>what to do with myself <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Living on airplane mode <br>Never wanna change <br>with my LA flow <br>Different shoes different <br>legs through the valet doors <br>Put you on the payroll <br>not your everyday hoes <br>Private with the pimpin <br>keep it tinted Benzo <br>Fuck bitches get riches <br>be the fuckin m o <br>Cause I innovate <br>I don't play with imitate dough <br>Stay cuttin' mad <br>fishes up Hattori Hanzo <br>Flippin scales <br>sippin pales <br>Robbin bad bitches blind <br>watch me fingerbang in Braille <br>Pin the tails <br>yo I never fail <br>Gimme one night wit the fatty <br>kill the kitty <br>then I wish it well <br>Playa by the code <br>feed 'em thru the nose <br>White bitches diggin' <br>like an interview in vogue <br>Frosted wit' the cinnamon <br>I'm fuckin' witcha both <br>4 queens wit' the king <br>make a muthafucka fold <br>Going out every weekend <br>Spending all of my money <br>Now that I'm alone <br>I ain't got no time for lovin' <br>Ooh oooh I don't know <br>what to do with myself <br>Ooh oooh I don't know <br>what to do with myself <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>Fuck bitches get money <br>]]></content><category term="Far East Movement" label="Far East Movement"/><category term="FBG$ (Feat. Big K.R.I.T., MIKNNA)" label="FBG$ (Feat. Big K.R.I.T., MIKNNA)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Double_Dip_Feat_Soulja_Boy_로꼬/</id><title>Far East Movement - Double Dip (Feat. Soulja Boy, 로꼬) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Double_Dip_Feat_Soulja_Boy_%EB%A1%9C%EA%BC%AC/" title="Far East Movement - Double Dip (Feat. Soulja Boy, 로꼬) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Soulja <br>Far East Movement <br>5 4 3 2 <br>Double down double lit <br>Muthafuckin’ double dip <br>Double down double lit <br>Muthafuckin’ double dip <br>Double down double lit <br>Muthafuckin’ double dip <br>Double down double lit <br>Muthafuckin’ double dip <br>Double dip <br>Double dip <br>Double dip <br>Double dip <br>Couple broads on three way <br>I’m give em’ both USDA <br>Skip the foreplay no delay <br>Bump to your heads <br>spins back CDJ <br>Double dutch down <br>I’m on the momo’ <br>I can han both y’all solo <br>Double my bizz that promo <br>I post this <br>got fomo <br>Double poppin it <br>double hittin’ it <br>Double shots <br>and we double sippin’ it <br>Double gwap <br>and we double fistin’ it <br>Way we livin it <br>double gettin’ it <br>Double bitches <br>that’s double gifted <br>I’m double parkin <br>and don’t use protection <br>That’s dumb enough <br>to be double dippin’ it <br>Double fuckin’ <br>i’m young n’ pimpin’ it <br>Double down double lit <br>Muthafuckin’ double dip <br>Double down double lit <br>Muthafuckin’ double dip <br>Double down double lit <br>Muthafuckin’ double dip <br>Double down double lit <br>Muthafuckin’ double dip <br>Double dip <br>Double dip <br>Double dip <br>Double dip <br>한개론 부족해 <br>4인분으로 두개 <br>매일 꿩 먹고 알도 먹어서 <br>난 포만감이 두배 <br>새삥에 중독됐어 <br>먼지 쌓여가는 구제 <br>면허 딴지 1년 된 <br>초보운전이 Porsche가 두대 <br>이제야 낼 수 있는 <br>추임새 skirrrr <br>좋은 뜻이야 내가 <br>안면을 구길 땐 <br>그냥 하던대로 할 거면 <br>넌 기대를 하지말어 <br>고개가 부러질 정도로 <br>Double down double lit <br>Muthafuckin’ double dip <br>Double down double lit <br>Muthafuckin’ double dip <br>Double down double lit <br>Muthafuckin’ double dip <br>Double down double lit <br>Muthafuckin’ double dip <br>Double dip <br>Double dip <br>Double dip <br>Double dip <br>Double dip <br>Double dip <br>Double dip <br>Double dip <br>]]></content><category term="Far East Movement" label="Far East Movement"/><category term="Double Dip (Feat. Soulja Boy, 로꼬)" label="Double Dip (Feat. Soulja Boy, 로꼬)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Umbrella_Feat_효린_Of_씨스타_Gill_Chang/</id><title>Far East Movement - Umbrella (Feat. 효린 Of 씨스타, Gill Chang) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Umbrella_Feat_%ED%9A%A8%EB%A6%B0_Of_%EC%94%A8%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80_Gill_Chang/" title="Far East Movement - Umbrella (Feat. 효린 Of 씨스타, Gill Chang) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby 널 올려줄게 우산처럼 <br>고개 들어 내가 있잖아 <br>영원히 사랑하길 약속해 <br>우산처럼 네 마음을 받아줄게 <br>외치고 싶어 <br>우리의 시간은 right now <br>내가 들리니 내 마음이 <br>너의 심장 소리 난 들려 <br>비 내리던 날들 있었지 <br>두려워 숨었던 날들도 <br>더 가까이 내가 꽉 안아줄게 <br>밝은 날 올 때까지 <br>Baby 널 올려줄게 우산처럼 <br>고개 들어 내가 있잖아 <br>영원히 사랑하길 약속해 <br>우산처럼 네 마음을 받아줄게 <br>Never ever <br>I'll never ever <br>I'll never let you <br>fall down <br>Oh no no <br>I'll never ever <br>I'll never ever <br>I'll never let you <br>fall down <br>비 내리던 날들 있었지 <br>두려워 숨었던 날들도 <br>더 가까이 내가 꽉 안아줄게 <br>밝은 날 올 때까지 <br>Baby 널 올려줄게 우산처럼 <br>고개 들어 내가 있잖아 <br>영원히 사랑하길 약속해 <br>우산처럼 네 마음을 받아줄게 <br>Baby 널 올려줄게 우산처럼 <br>고개 들어 내가 있잖아 <br>영원히 사랑하길 약속해 <br>우산처럼 네 마음을 받아줄게 <br>Never ever <br>I'll never ever <br>I'll never let you <br>fall down <br>Oh no no <br>I'll never ever <br>I'll never ever <br>I'll never let you <br>fall down <br>]]></content><category term="Far East Movement" label="Far East Movement"/><category term="Umbrella (Feat. 효린 Of 씨스타, Gill Chang)" label="Umbrella (Feat. 효린 Of 씨스타, Gill Chang)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/SXWME_Feat_박재범_Prod_By_MNEK/</id><title>Far East Movement - SXWME (Feat. 박재범) (Prod. By MNEK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/SXWME_Feat_%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94_Prod_By_MNEK/" title="Far East Movement - SXWME (Feat. 박재범) (Prod. By MNEK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby if you want me to be <br>I can be your new fantasy <br>Love me hard <br>and fulfill my needs <br>Don’t you want <br>to have sex with me <br>Baby if you want me to be <br>I can be your new fantasy <br>Love me hard <br>and fulfill my needs <br>Don’t you want <br>to have sex with me <br>I said my lady <br>Say yeah <br>Say ooooh yes <br>Yes yes <br>Sexiest thing I ever seen <br>No filter thighs smoking <br>like nicotine <br>Tryna stretch you out <br>like a limousine <br>Sex on fire <br>spread the lotion <br>like kerosene <br>Yea you I know I stay with it <br>wet up like bidet wit it <br>Ya body is my playground <br>time to 4play with it <br>Kill it get away with it <br>first 48 <br>She relate no escape <br>build a case still stay in it <br>Lady take off <br>High sex drive <br>got ya boy speeding <br>with the brakes off <br>Burn that cake off <br>Turn that thang raw <br>You my main line <br>give u FaceTime <br>bout to break it down <br>with my cape off <br>Bout to Pass it to the homie <br>like she down w Nate Dogg <br>Blowing up the hood <br>that lil mama napalm <br>Got me callin in the morning <br>til the til the break a dawn <br>Lil sip of henny and it’s on <br>Baby if you want me to be <br>I can be your new fantasy <br>Love me hard <br>and fulfill my needs <br>Don’t you want <br>to have sex with me <br>Baby if you want me to be <br>I can be your new fantasy <br>Love me hard <br>and fulfill my needs <br>Don’t you want <br>to have sex with me <br>I’ll love you harder <br>than a rock girl <br>The moon shining <br>like the diamonds <br>on my watch girl <br>I love your bottom <br>so let’s take it <br>from the top girl <br>Red light district <br>but don’t let that stop you <br>There ain’t nothin wrong <br>with a lil’ bump and grind <br>Yeah we be up all night fuckin’ <br>til’ the sun come up <br>Girl lemme break yo walls <br>like I was the juggernaut <br>Yeah it’s the renaissance <br>what I do is a work of art <br>Let’s get lit off the champagne <br>Turn off yo phone who cares <br>what yo man’s sayin’ <br>Get nasty like the old LL <br>We'll be doin’ it <br>and doin’ it <br>and doin’ it well <br>Play with it lemme watchya <br>Notorious when I’m <br>in the sauce <br>I gotta gun between my legs <br>bout to shoot up yo place <br>Cause I love it <br>when you call me Big Poppa <br>Baby if you want me to be <br>I can be your new fantasy <br>Love me hard <br>and fulfill my needs <br>Don’t you want <br>to have sex with me <br>Baby if you want me to be <br>I can be your new fantasy <br>Love me hard <br>and fulfill my needs <br>Don’t you want <br>to have sex with me <br>Baby if you want me to be <br>I can be your new fantasy <br>Love me hard <br>and fulfill my needs <br>Don’t you want <br>to have sex with me <br>Baby if you want me to be <br>I can be your new fantasy <br>Love me hard <br>and fulfill my needs <br>Don’t you want <br>to have sex with me <br>Now can i get nasty baby <br>I wanna spread <br>your legs open wide <br>And lick you up <br>And lick you down <br>I said lick you up <br>And lick you down <br>Now I’m gonna <br>turn your body over <br>Make you scream <br>over and over yeah <br>I can give it to you <br>I can give it to you <br>Give it to you <br>Give it to you baby <br>Baby if you want me to be <br>I can be your new fantasy <br>Love me hard <br>and fulfill my needs <br>Don’t you want <br>to have sex with me <br>Baby if you want me to be <br>I can be your new fantasy <br>Love me hard <br>and fulfill my needs <br>Don’t you want <br>to have sex with me <br>]]></content><category term="Far East Movement" label="Far East Movement"/><category term="SXWME (Feat. 박재범) (Prod. By MNEK)" label="SXWME (Feat. 박재범) (Prod. By MNEK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Dont_Speak_Feat_티파니_Of_소녀시대_King_Chain/</id><title>Far East Movement - Don`t Speak (Feat. 티파니 Of 소녀시대, King Chain) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Dont_Speak_Feat_%ED%8B%B0%ED%8C%8C%EB%8B%88_Of_%EC%86%8C%EB%85%80%EC%8B%9C%EB%8C%80_King_Chain/" title="Far East Movement - Don`t Speak (Feat. 티파니 Of 소녀시대, King Chain) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You’re playing shy <br>Don’t think that I don’t want to be <br>Treading around you carefully <br>I don’t play games <br>I don’t play <br>Don’t care to know your name <br>Just want you for tonight <br>I want to dance <br>All night in LA make your advance <br>We run like it’s payday <br>There’s crazy tension in the air <br>Think we should start a love affair <br>Breathe don’t speak <br>Why don’t you come and <br>dance with me <br>Get weak <br>The beat will leave you lost <br>just screamin’ oh <br>Someone help me oh <br>The people help me scream it <br>Breathe don’t speak <br>Why don’t you <br>come and dance with me <br>Get weak <br>The beat will leave you lost <br>just screamin’ oh <br>Someone help me oh <br>Someone help me <br>I’m alive <br>This love is bound to last past five <br>We won’t get out until the night <br>I want to play <br>Tonight ain’t over yet <br>Don’t know your name <br>Ain’t nothing to regret <br>I want to dance <br>All night in LA make your advance <br>We run like it’s payday <br>There’s crazy tension in the air <br>Think we should start a love affair <br>Breathe don’t speak <br>Why don’t you come and <br>dance with me <br>Get weak <br>The beat will leave you lost <br>just screamin’ oh <br>Someone help me oh <br>The people help me scream it <br>Breathe don’t speak <br>Why don’t you come and <br>dance with me <br>Get weak <br>The beat will leave you lost <br>just screamin’ oh <br>Someone help me oh <br>Someone help me <br>]]></content><category term="Far East Movement" label="Far East Movement"/><category term="Don`t Speak (Feat. 티파니 Of 소녀시대, King Chain)" label="Don`t Speak (Feat. 티파니 Of 소녀시대, King Chain)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Church_Feat_Elijah_Blake/</id><title>Far East Movement - Church (Feat. Elijah Blake) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Church_Feat_Elijah_Blake/" title="Far East Movement - Church (Feat. Elijah Blake) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[See I was raised by a preacher man <br>Who couldn’t wrap <br>my brain on religion <br>But I’ll follow you <br>through and through <br>My mother prayed for deliverance <br>Cause your touch is <br>far from innocent <br>But I’ll follow you <br>through and through <br>River water very low <br>Now ocean deep <br>Baby I’ll be holding on <br>You give me something to believe <br>Just like Church <br>There’s devotion in you <br>You’re just like <br>There’s devotion in you <br>You’re just like <br>Hallelujah <br>Baby ain’t a sin I wouldn’t do for you <br>Church <br>I’ll follow you through and through <br>Just like Church <br>Hallelujah <br>Baby ain’t a sin I wouldn’t do for you <br>Church <br>I’ll follow you through and through <br>Just like Church <br>See I was raised by a preacher man <br>Who couldn’t wrap <br>my brain on religion <br>But I’ll follow you <br>through and through <br>My mother prayed for deliverance <br>Cause your touch is <br>far from innocent <br>But I’ll follow you <br>through and through <br>River water very low <br>Now ocean deep <br>Baby I’ll be holding on <br>You give me something to believe <br>Just like Church <br>Hallelujah <br>Baby ain’t a sin I wouldn’t do for you <br>Church <br>I’ll follow you through and through <br>Just like Church <br>I heard em’ singing now <br>Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah <br>Baby ain’t a sin I wouldn’t do for you <br>]]></content><category term="Far East Movement" label="Far East Movement"/><category term="Church (Feat. Elijah Blake)" label="Church (Feat. Elijah Blake)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/F-VR_Feat_Candice_Pillay_No_Riddim/</id><title>Far East Movement - F-VR (Feat. Candice Pillay, No Riddim) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/F-VR_Feat_Candice_Pillay_No_Riddim/" title="Far East Movement - F-VR (Feat. Candice Pillay, No Riddim) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This atmosphere is even farther <br>Don’t know no one but you and me <br>we keep it undivided <br>Now if I ever feel a type of way <br>fold up and light it <br>We real about it We still about it <br>Forever and ever <br>We on this forever <br>We ridin’ forever <br>Cause we good forever <br>We own this forever <br>Yeah all this forever <br>We all in forever <br>Ever Ever ever <br>Ever ever We all in Ever ever We all in <br>Ever ever We all in Ever ever We all in <br>Ever ever We all in Ever ever We all in <br>Ever ever We all in <br>Ever and ever <br>We on this forever <br>Cause we good forever <br>We own this forever <br>We all in forever <br>Ever Ever ever <br>This atmosphere is hella vibin <br>Don’t know no one but you and me <br>we keep it undivided <br>Now if I ever feel a type of way <br>fold up and light it <br>We real about it We still about <br>Forever and ever <br>We on this forever <br>We ridin’ forever <br>Cause we good forever <br>We own this forever <br>Yeah all this forever <br>We all in forever <br>Ever Ever ever <br>Ever ever We all in Ever ever We all in <br>Ever ever We all in Ever ever We all in <br>Ever ever We all in Ever ever We all in <br>Ever ever We all in <br>Forever and ever <br>We on this forever <br>We ridin’ forever <br>Cause we good forever <br>We own this forever <br>Yeah all this forever <br>We all in forever <br>Ever Ever ever <br>Ever and ever <br>We on this forever <br>We ridin forever <br>Cause we good forever <br>We own this forever <br>Yeah all this forever <br>We all in forever <br>Ever Ever ever <br>]]></content><category term="Far East Movement" label="Far East Movement"/><category term="F-VR (Feat. Candice Pillay, No Riddim)" label="F-VR (Feat. Candice Pillay, No Riddim)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Freal_Luv_Feat_찬열_Of_EXO_Tinashe/</id><title>Far East Movement - Freal Luv (Feat. 찬열 Of EXO, Tinashe) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Freal_Luv_Feat_%EC%B0%AC%EC%97%B4_Of_EXO_Tinashe/" title="Far East Movement - Freal Luv (Feat. 찬열 Of EXO, Tinashe) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Freal luv <br>Freal luv <br>Freal luv <br>Freal luv <br>Know no limits <br>to feel the truth <br>When the world stops spinnin <br>I'll know it's you <br>Searching all night <br>like a spotlight <br>For the one to show <br>Could it be you <br>could it be me <br>Only way to know <br>I'm all yours <br>when you really want <br>to take me there <br>Don't let me go no where <br>I'd give it all up for you I swear <br>Only Freal luv <br>That love that keeps me shaking <br>So real there's no mistaking <br>I’d give it all up to you I swear <br>Only Freal luv <br>Lovin that real luv <br>something you feel luv <br>Turning me back to the old me <br>Ride for my realla <br>I die for my realla <br>I give you respect like the OGs <br>Lockin me down like the police <br>We ain't never be lonely <br>Protectin’ my love <br>like a goalie <br>You'll be the only one <br>next to me right with the homies <br>We got that empire mind <br>combine n’ steadily rise <br>That be freal <br>Moment of truth of has arrived <br>trust that forever you ride <br>That be freal <br>You be the bank on my side <br>you supervise <br>Lets make a deal <br>Let's get it sealed <br>let's make a trill <br>Let's rule the world <br>together freal <br>Freal luv <br>Freal luv <br>Freal luv <br>Freal luv <br>I'm all yours <br>when you really want <br>to take me there <br>Don't let me go no where <br>I'd give it all up for you I swear <br>Only Freal luv <br>I'm all yours <br>when you really want <br>to take me there <br>Don't let me go no where <br>I'd give it all up for you I swear <br>Only Freal luv <br>That love that keeps me shaking <br>So real there's no mistaking <br>I’d give it all up to you I swear <br>Only Freal luv <br>Love is a high <br>we feelin’ alive <br>you Lovin’ the size <br>이 흐름을 타 <br>I give you more <br>you feelin’ the flow <br>you never let none of them <br>bring down the vibe <br>Hustle to win <br>we be livin’ in sin <br>makin’ us two of a kind <br>새로운 길 <br>babe we got temples to build <br>ain't no haters can <br>step to our grind <br>We got that empire mind <br>함께 천천히 올라 <br>That be freal <br>진실이 닿는 순간 <br>느껴봐 눈을 감아 <br>That be freal <br>You be the bank on my side <br>nothing but dimes <br>Let’s make a deal <br>서서히 필 꿈과 현실 <br>내 손을 잡으면 <br>together freal <br>Freal luv <br>Freal luv <br>Freal luv <br>Freal luv <br>]]></content><category term="Far East Movement" label="Far East Movement"/><category term="Freal Luv (Feat. 찬열 Of EXO, Tinashe)" label="Freal Luv (Feat. 찬열 Of EXO, Tinashe)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Fighter_Feat_윤미래_Autolaser/</id><title>Far East Movement - Fighter (Feat. 윤미래, Autolaser) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:21:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:21:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Far_East_Movement/Fighter_Feat_%EC%9C%A4%EB%AF%B8%EB%9E%98_Autolaser/" title="Far East Movement - Fighter (Feat. 윤미래, Autolaser) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fighter <br>With my back against the wall <br>Said that you've had enough <br>But you still take my calls <br>I need to know I need to know <br>If there's any fight left <br>For us to make it all right <br>Tell me what's the next step <br>I’ma fighter <br>What do you wanna do now <br>You a fighter <br>Whatever you gotta go through <br>Fighter Baby it's up to you <br>Whatever you wanna do <br>I'm down with it <br>Ohhhhhh It's up to you <br>Whatever you goin through <br>I'm down with it <br>Fighter Knock me down <br>but I’ll keep fighting <br>For you til’ the end <br>we’ll keep on trying <br>Like a fighter <br>Knock us down <br>but we’re survivors <br>For love til’ the end <br>we’ll keep on fighting <br>Fighter Fighter Fighter Fighter <br>Ohhhhhhh It's up to you <br>Whatever you wanna do <br>I'm down with it <br>Ohhhhhh It's up to you <br>Whatever you goin through <br>I'm down with it <br>Fighter <br>With my back against the wall <br>Said that you've had enough <br>But you still take my calls <br>I need to know I need to know <br>If there's any fight left <br>For us to make it all right <br>Tell me what's the next step <br>I’ma fighter <br>What do you wanna do now <br>You a fighter <br>Whatever we gotta go through <br>Fighter Baby it's up to you <br>Whatever you wanna do <br>I'm down with it <br>It's up to you <br>Whatever you goin through <br>I'm down with it <br>It's up to you <br>Whatever you goin through <br>I'm down with it <br>]]></content><category term="Far East Movement" label="Far East Movement"/><category term="Fighter (Feat. 윤미래, Autolaser)" label="Fighter (Feat. 윤미래, Autolaser)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silla_실라/트루컬러/</id><title>Silla (실라) - 트루컬러 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:23:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:23:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silla_%EC%8B%A4%EB%9D%BC/%ED%8A%B8%EB%A3%A8%EC%BB%AC%EB%9F%AC/" title="Silla (실라) - 트루컬러 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Talk to the moon <br>Talk to the sky <br>노을진 하늘은 <br>노랗게 물들어 <br>오렌지색 구름사이로 <br>하루는 지나고 <br>까만 밤하늘 사이로 <br>지나는 별들 <br>지친 하루에 내맘은 <br>또 파랗게 변해 <br>새벽 공기 마시며 <br>무거운 맘으로 <br>하루를 열때 <br>세상 가진 모든것 <br>다 미워지기도 하네요 <br>무뎌진 순수함을 <br>잊고 있진 않은가요 <br>가끔 사랑하던 <br>그때를 떠올려봐요 <br>오늘밤 노란 <br>달빛으로 날아갈래 <br>은은한 별빛과 <br>은하수 사이로 <br>I see your true true color <br>I see your true true color <br>I see your true true color <br>Oh my baby <br>Maybe its red <br>Maybe its blue <br>Maybe its green or yellow <br>It doesn’t matter <br>It doesn’t matter <br>It doesn’t matter <br>It doesn’t matter <br>또 다시오겠죠 <br>새하얀 밝은 아침도 <br>파스텔로 채워진 꿈도 <br>다시 꾸게되겠죠 <br>또 내리겠죠 <br>투명한 비도 <br>내맘의 숲도 <br>녹색으로 물들거야 <br>지나간 연인과 <br>얘기하고싶은 순간들 <br>가슴속에 묻기 <br>쉽지않은 기억들 <br>어깨에 기대 <br>울고싶은 지난 얘기들 <br>깊은밤 잠이 오지 않는 <br>그런 생각들 <br>사랑했던 모든걸 <br>다 잃어버린 것처럼 <br>무너지는 세상속 앞을 <br>볼 수 없을때도 <br>넘어지고 쓰러지고 <br>아무도 내옆에 없을때 <br>잃어버린 순간은 <br>쉽진 않지만 웃어야되요 <br>Let’s swim into the blue sky <br>Let’s walk onto the blue ocean <br>새벽 공기 마시며 <br>무거운 맘으로 <br>하루를 열때 <br>세상 가진 모든것 <br>다 미워지기도 하네요 <br>무뎌진 순수함을 <br>잊고 있진 않은가요 <br>가끔 사랑하던 <br>그때를 떠올려봐요 <br>오늘밤 노란 <br>달빛으로 날아갈래 <br>은은한 별빛과 <br>은하수 사이로 <br>I see your true true color <br>I see your true true color <br>I see your true true color <br>Oh my baby <br>오늘밤 노란 <br>달빛으로 날아갈래 <br>은은한 별빛과 <br>은하수 사이로 <br>I see your true true color <br>I see your true true color <br>I see your true true color <br>Oh my baby <br>Maybe its red <br>Maybe its blue <br>Maybe its green or yellow <br>It doesn’t matter <br>It doesn’t matter <br>It doesn’t matter <br>It doesn’t matter <br>]]></content><category term="Silla (실라)" label="Silla (실라)"/><category term="트루컬러" label="트루컬러"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하이싱어즈/As_Time_Goes_By/</id><title>하이싱어즈 - As Time Goes By - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:25:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:25:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%EC%8B%B1%EC%96%B4%EC%A6%88/As_Time_Goes_By/" title="하이싱어즈 - As Time Goes By - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This day and age we're living in <br>Gives cause for apprehension <br>With speed and new invention <br>And things like fourth dimension <br>Yet we get a trifle weary <br>With Mr.Einstein's theory <br>So we must get down <br>to earth at times <br>Relax relieve the tension <br>And no matter what the progress <br>Or what may yet be proved <br>The simple facts of life are such <br>They cannot be removed <br>You must remember this <br>A kiss is just a kiss <br>a sigh is just a sigh <br>The fundamental things apply <br>As time goes by <br>And when two lovers woo <br>They still say I love you <br>On that you can rely <br>No matter what the future brings <br>As time goes by <br>Moonlight and love songs <br>Never out of date <br>Hearts full of passion <br>Jealousy and hate <br>Woman needs man <br>And man must have his mate <br>That no one can deny <br>It's still the same old story <br>A fight for love and glory <br>A case of do or die <br>The world will always <br>welcome lovers <br>As time goes by As time goes by <br>Moonlight and love songs <br>Moonlight and love songs <br>Never out of date <br>Hearts full of passion <br>Jealousy and hate <br>Woman needs man <br>And man must have his mate <br>That no one can deny <br>It's still the same old story <br>A fight for love and glory <br>A case of do or die <br>The world will always <br>welcome lovers <br>As time goes by As time goes by <br>As time goes by <br>]]></content><category term="하이싱어즈" label="하이싱어즈"/><category term="As Time Goes By" label="As Time Goes By"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하이싱어즈/Youd_Be_So_Nice_To_Come_Home_To/</id><title>하이싱어즈 - You`d Be So Nice To Come Home To - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:25:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:25:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%EC%8B%B1%EC%96%B4%EC%A6%88/Youd_Be_So_Nice_To_Come_Home_To/" title="하이싱어즈 - You`d Be So Nice To Come Home To - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You'd be so nice to come home to <br>You'd be so nice by the fire <br>While the breeze on high <br>sang a lullaby <br>You'd be all that I could desire <br>Under stars chilled by the winter <br>Under an August moon burning above <br>You'd be so nice you'd be paradise <br>To come home to and love <br>Under stars chilled by the winter <br>Under an August moon burning above <br>You'd be so nice you'd be paradise <br>To come home to <br>To come home to <br>To come home to and love <br>]]></content><category term="하이싱어즈" label="하이싱어즈"/><category term="You`d Be So Nice To Come Home To" label="You`d Be So Nice To Come Home To"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하이싱어즈/Lover_Come_Back_To_Me/</id><title>하이싱어즈 - Lover Come Back To Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:25:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:25:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%EC%8B%B1%EC%96%B4%EC%A6%88/Lover_Come_Back_To_Me/" title="하이싱어즈 - Lover Come Back To Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The sky was blue <br>And high above <br>The moon was new <br>And so was love <br>This eager heart of mine was <br>singing <br>Lover where can you be <br>You came at last <br>Love had its day <br>That day is past <br>You've gone away <br>This aching heart of mine is <br>singing <br>Lover come back to me <br>I remember every little thing <br>You used to do <br>I'm so lonely <br>Every road I walked along <br>I walked along with you <br>No wonder I feel lonely <br>The sky is blue <br>The night is cold <br>The moon is new <br>But love is old <br>And while I'm waiting here <br>This heart of mine is singing <br>Lover come back to me <br>This aching heart of mine is singing <br>Lover come back to me <br>I remember every little thing <br>You used to do <br>I’m so lonely <br>Every road I walked along <br>I walked along with you <br>no wonder I feel lonely <br>The sky is blue <br>The night is cold <br>The moon is new <br>But love is old <br>And while I'm waiting here <br>This heart of mine is singing <br>Lover come back to <br>Lover come back to <br>Lover come back to me <br>And while I'm waiting here <br>This heart of mine is singing <br>Lover come back to me <br>Lover lover lover come back to me <br>]]></content><category term="하이싱어즈" label="하이싱어즈"/><category term="Lover Come Back To Me" label="Lover Come Back To Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하이싱어즈/Route_66/</id><title>하이싱어즈 - Route 66 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:25:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:25:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%EC%8B%B1%EC%96%B4%EC%A6%88/Route_66/" title="하이싱어즈 - Route 66 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If you ever plan to motor west <br>Travel my way <br>take the highway that's best <br>Get your kicks on Route sixty six <br>It winds from Chicago to LA <br>More than two thousand miles <br>all the way <br>Get your kicks on Route sixty six <br>Now you go through Saint Louis <br>Joplin Missouri <br>And Oklahoma City is mighty pretty <br>You'll see Amarillo <br>Gallup New Mexico <br>Flagstaff Arizona <br>Don't forget Winona <br>Kingman Barstow <br>San Bernandino <br>Won't you get hip to this timely tip <br>When you make that California trip <br>Get your kicks on Route sixty six <br>Now you go through Saint Louis <br>Joplin Missouri <br>And Oklahoma City is mighty pretty <br>You'll see Amarillo <br>Gallup New Mexico <br>Flagstaff Arizona <br>Don't forget Winona <br>Kingman Barstow <br>San Bernandino <br>Won't you get hip to this timely tip <br>When you make that California trip <br>Get your kicks on Route sixty six <br>Get your kicks on Route sixty six <br>Get your kicks on Route sixty six <br>Get your kicks on Route sixty six <br>]]></content><category term="하이싱어즈" label="하이싱어즈"/><category term="Route 66" label="Route 66"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조민욱/퇴근버스/</id><title>조민욱 - 퇴근버스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:25:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:25:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EB%AF%BC%EC%9A%B1/%ED%87%B4%EA%B7%BC%EB%B2%84%EC%8A%A4/" title="조민욱 - 퇴근버스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이별 한지 한 달이 돼 <br>네 생각에 <br>잠 못 이루었어 <br>지친 몸을 이끌고 <br>퇴근 길에 <br>낯익은 버스에 <br>몸을 기울였었어 <br>텅빈 버스 안에서 <br>흘러나오는 노래 소리에 <br>내 마음이 내 심장이 <br>아직도 그댈 향해있나요 <br>얼마나 더 멀리가야 <br>너를 잊을까 <br>아직 남은 그대의 기억이 <br>혼자 서성이는 가요 <br>소리 없이 그댈 부르고 <br>불러 봤지만 <br>그댈 잊는 다는게 <br>아직 멀기만 하죠 <br>난 아직도 <br>시간이 지나 듣는 <br>너의 소식에 <br>나도 몰래 찾게되는 <br>너의 이름 <br>아직도 너를 <br>그리워 하나봐 <br>어떡해야 그대를 <br>잊을수 있나요 <br>너도 나처럼 <br>많이 힘이 드나요 <br>서성이던 내모습이 <br>간직해줘 나와 <br>함께 했던 시간들을 <br>너무 힘들겠지만 <br>많이 힘들겠지만 <br>잊어볼게 <br>]]></content><category term="조민욱" label="조민욱"/><category term="퇴근버스" label="퇴근버스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김영근/사랑_그렇게_보내네/</id><title>김영근 - 사랑 그렇게 보내네 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:25:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:25:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%98%81%EA%B7%BC/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A0%87%EA%B2%8C_%EB%B3%B4%EB%82%B4%EB%84%A4/" title="김영근 - 사랑 그렇게 보내네 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무 말도 <br>아무것도 안 했는데 <br>이름 하나만으로도 <br>마음이 아려와 <br>아주 멀리 가버릴 줄 <br>왜 몰랐을까 <br>사랑 그렇게 보내네 <br>이유 없이 <br>퉁명스럽던 그때를 <br>때론 모질고 소홀한 <br>그 순간들을 <br>미안하단 말도 <br>아직 하지 못한 채 <br>사랑 그렇게 보내네 <br>괜찮을 거라고 <br>내 마음을 알아줄 거라고 <br>스스로를 타일러봐도 <br>잊을 수도 없고 <br>잊혀지지 않는 추억이 <br>뒤늦게 <br>후회로 밀려와 <br>하루라도 <br>다시 만날 수 있다면 <br>오래오래 그대 앞에 <br>울고 싶은데 <br>바람소리 마저 <br>너무 조용한 하늘 <br>사랑 그렇게 보내네 <br>괜찮을 거라고 <br>내 마음을 알아줄 거라고 <br>스스로를 타일러봐도 <br>잊을 수도 없고 <br>잊혀지지 않는 추억이 <br>뒤늦게 <br>후회로 밀려와 <br>바라고 바라다 <br>다시 한번 <br>만날 수 있게 되면 <br>그땐 고맙다고 <br>늦지 않게 말하리 <br>사랑 그렇게 보내네 <br>사랑 그렇게 보내네 <br>]]></content><category term="김영근" label="김영근"/><category term="사랑 그렇게 보내네" label="사랑 그렇게 보내네"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/심집사/Amazing_Love_Feat_송지연/</id><title>심집사 - Amazing Love (Feat. 송지연) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:30:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:30:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%AC%EC%A7%91%EC%82%AC/Amazing_Love_Feat_%EC%86%A1%EC%A7%80%EC%97%B0/" title="심집사 - Amazing Love (Feat. 송지연) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 마음 깊은 곳에서 <br>남몰래 부르는 노래 <br>멈출수가 없는 걸 <br>성령의 손길이 나를 <br>만지네 만지네 <br>주체할 수 없는 기쁨이 넘치네 예 <br>작은자 한 영혼을 사랑하신 <br>나의 영원하신 <br>주님 낮은 곳에 내맘에 오신 예수 <br>사랑해 사랑하네 <br>크고 놀라우신 그의 사랑 <br>나를 살리신 amazing love <br>내 마음 깊은 곳에서 <br>남몰래 흐르는 눈물 <br>멈출수가 없는 걸 <br>사랑의 손길이 나를 <br>만지네 만지네 <br>표현할수 없는 감사가 넘치네 예 <br>작은자 한 영혼을 <br>구원하신 오직 하나뿐인 <br>주님 사망 권세 이기신 오직 예수 <br>찬양해 찬양하네 <br>크고 놀라우신 그의 사랑 <br>나를 살리신 amazing love <br>작은자 한 영혼을 <br>사랑하신 나의 영원하신 <br>주님 낮은 곳에 내맘에 오신 예수 <br>사랑해 사랑하네 <br>크고 놀라우신 그의 사랑 <br>나를 살리신 amazing love]]></content><category term="심집사" label="심집사"/><category term="Amazing Love (Feat. 송지연)" label="Amazing Love (Feat. 송지연)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/심집사/주님_만지시네_Feat_김지훈/</id><title>심집사 - 주님 만지시네 (Feat. 김지훈) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:31:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:31:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%AC%EC%A7%91%EC%82%AC/%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98_%EB%A7%8C%EC%A7%80%EC%8B%9C%EB%84%A4_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%80%ED%9B%88/" title="심집사 - 주님 만지시네 (Feat. 김지훈) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주님이 계시네 내 안에 계시네 <br>내 마음 깊은 곳 들어와 계시네 <br>어루만지시네 나의 모든 상처 <br>주님의 눈물로 씻어지네 <br>주님 만지시네 내 맘을 만지네 <br>더러운 몸과 맘 깨끗케 하시네 <br>내게 말씀하네 넌 내 아들이야 <br>내가 널 어떡해 포기하니 <br>그래요 주님은 항상 내 편이죠 <br>내가 외면해도 날 안아주었죠 <br>나 이렇게 눈물을 흘리며 <br>아버지의 손을 잡아요 <br>따뜻한 그 사랑을 느껴요 <br>주님 만지시네 내 맘을 만지네 <br>더러운 몸과 맘 깨끗케 하시네 <br>내게 말씀하네 넌 내 사랑이야 <br>내가 널 어떡해 미워하니 <br>그래요 주님은 항상 내 벗이죠 <br>깊은 방황에도 날 품어 주셨죠 <br>나 이렇게 두손을 모아요 <br>아버지 사랑 노래해요 <br>따뜻한 그 사랑을 <br>날 향한 주님의 그 사랑 <br>그래요 주님은 항상 내 편이죠 <br>내가 외면해도 날 안아주었죠 <br>나 이렇게 눈물을 흘리며 <br>아버지의 손을 잡아요 <br>따뜻한 그 사랑을 느껴요 <br>아버지의 그 사랑]]></content><category term="심집사" label="심집사"/><category term="주님 만지시네 (Feat. 김지훈)" label="주님 만지시네 (Feat. 김지훈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/반스_BANS/똑똑_Trick_Or_Treat_Dark_Ver/</id><title>반스 (BANS) - 똑똑 Trick Or Treat (Dark Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:31:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:31:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%98%EC%8A%A4_BANS/%EB%98%91%EB%98%91_Trick_Or_Treat_Dark_Ver/" title="반스 (BANS) - 똑똑 Trick Or Treat (Dark Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>똑똑 <br>이제까지 보지 못 했던 <br>나의 이면을 밝히리 oh <br>사실 누구보다 잔인하고 <br>못된 아이 Valkyrie oh <br>시시한 무용담이 아닌 <br>진짜 이야기를 들어보렴 <br>타협은 없을 거야 <br>군내 나는 배려는 <br>나와 안 어울려 <br>똑똑 <br>eh oh eh oh <br>순수히 있어줬던 <br>지난날에 oh <br>함부로 나를 대하는 <br>너의 모습은 재밌던 걸 <br>eh oh eh oh <br>따분히 지나가던 <br>지날 날에 oh <br>앞으로 계속 기억될 <br>하루를 만들자 <br>재밌을 걸 <br>똑똑 <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>둘 중에 하나는 <br>꼭 골라야 해 <br>sweety <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>둘 중에 뭘 골라도 <br>결과는 같을 거야 <br>sweety <br>낯을 많이 가리는 아인 <br>이젠 낮을 가려 <br>어두운 밤 <br>이 날만 기다렸어 <br>너에게 선사할 <br>너를 날릴 폭탄 <br>bomb <br>심심한 사자들이 <br>미리 와서 기다린다더군 <br>다시는 없을 거야 <br>나의 노크로 <br>쇼는 시작된단다 <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>둘 중에 하나는 <br>꼭 골라야 해 <br>sweety <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>둘 중에 뭘 골라도 <br>결과는 같을 거야 <br>sweety <br>매번 날 쓰게 했던 너도 <br>오늘은 내게 단 걸 줘야 해 <br>계속 반복한 매일 말고 <br>이제와는 달리 특별해야 해 <br>우리 우리 <br>우리의 D-day <br>eh oh eh oh <br>순수히 있어줬던 <br>지난날에 oh <br>함부로 나를 대하는 <br>너의 모습은 재밌던 걸 <br>eh oh eh oh <br>따분히 지나가던 <br>지난 날에 oh <br>앞으로 계속 기억될 <br>하루를 만들자 재밌을 걸 <br>쉿 <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>둘 중에 하나는 <br>꼭 골라야 해 <br>sweety <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>똑똑 Trick or Treat <br>둘 중에 뭘 골라도 <br>결과는 같을 거야 <br>sweety <br>]]></content><category term="반스 (BANS)" label="반스 (BANS)"/><category term="똑똑 Trick Or Treat (Dark Ver.)" label="똑똑 Trick Or Treat (Dark Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유엔젤_보이스/삶이_그대를_속일지라도_영어_Ver/</id><title>유엔젤 보이스 - 삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (영어 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:32:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:32:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EC%97%94%EC%A0%A4_%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4/%EC%82%B6%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%A5%BC_%EC%86%8D%EC%9D%BC%EC%A7%80%EB%9D%BC%EB%8F%84_%EC%98%81%EC%96%B4_Ver/" title="유엔젤 보이스 - 삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (영어 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What though life <br>conspire to cheat you <br>What though life <br>conspire to cheat you <br>Do not sorrow or complain <br>Lie still on the day of pain <br>Lie still on the time of rain <br>and the day of joy will greet you <br>What though life <br>conspire to cheat you <br>What though life <br>conspire to cheat you <br>Do not sorrow or complain <br>Lie still on the day of pain <br>Lie still on the time of rain <br>and the day of joy will greet you <br>Hearts live in the coming day <br>There's an end to passing sorrow <br>Suddenly all flies away <br>And delight returns tomorrow <br>What though life conspire <br>Though life conspire to cheat you <br>Do not sorrow or complain <br>Lie still on the day <br>still on the day of pain <br>And the day of joy will greet you <br>What though life <br>conspire to cheat you <br>What though life <br>conspire to cheat you <br>Do not sorrow or complain <br>Lie still on the day of pain <br>Lie still on the time of rain <br>and the day of joy will greet you <br>What though life <br>conspire to cheat you <br>What though life <br>conspire to cheat you <br>Do not sorrow or complain <br>Lie still on the day of pain <br>Lie still on the time of rain <br>And the day of joy will greet you <br>]]></content><category term="유엔젤 보이스" label="유엔젤 보이스"/><category term="삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (영어 Ver.)" label="삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (영어 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유엔젤_보이스/삶이_그대를_속일지라도_중국_Ver/</id><title>유엔젤 보이스 - 삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (중국 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:32:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:32:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EC%97%94%EC%A0%A4_%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4/%EC%82%B6%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%A5%BC_%EC%86%8D%EC%9D%BC%EC%A7%80%EB%9D%BC%EB%8F%84_%EC%A4%91%EA%B5%AD_Ver/" title="유엔젤 보이스 - 삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (중국 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ji shi sheng huo qi pian le ni <br>ye bu yao bei shang bu yao sheng qi <br>ren zhu jian chi <br>zong hui ying lai kuai le de ri zi <br>jiu suan shi jie pao qi le ni <br>ye bu yao bei shang bu yao sheng qi <br>ren zhu jian chi <br>zong hui ying lai gao xing de ri zi <br>zhi yao xin zhong xiang zhe wei lai <br>bei shang de jin tian hui zhuan shun er guo <br>dan you he dan xin dou jiang xiao shi <br>hui ying lai gao xing de ming tian <br>ji shi sheng huo qi pian le ni <br>ye bu yao bei shang bu yao sheng qi <br>zai jue wang de ri zi <br>ren zhu jian chi <br>gao xing zhi ri zhong jiang dao lai <br>ji shi sheng huo qi pian le ni <br>ye bu yao bei shang bu yao sheng qi <br>ren zhu jian chi <br>zong hui ying lai kuai le de ri zi <br>jiu suan shi jie pao qi le ni <br>ye bu yao bei shang bu yao sheng qi <br>ren zhu jian chi <br>zong hui ying lai gao xing de ri zi <br>]]></content><category term="유엔젤 보이스" label="유엔젤 보이스"/><category term="삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (중국 Ver.)" label="삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (중국 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유엔젤_보이스/삶이_그대를_속일지라도_한국어_Full_Ver/</id><title>유엔젤 보이스 - 삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (한국어 Full Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:32:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:32:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EC%97%94%EC%A0%A4_%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4/%EC%82%B6%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%A5%BC_%EC%86%8D%EC%9D%BC%EC%A7%80%EB%9D%BC%EB%8F%84_%ED%95%9C%EA%B5%AD%EC%96%B4_Full_Ver/" title="유엔젤 보이스 - 삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (한국어 Full Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[삶이 그대를 속일지라도 <br>슬퍼하거나 화내지마 <br>슬픈날들을 참고 견디면 <br>즐거운날들 오리니 <br>세상이 그대를 버릴지라도 <br>슬퍼하거나 화내지마 <br>힘든 날들을 참고 견디면 <br>기쁨의 날 꼭 올거야 <br>마음은 미래를 꿈꾸니 <br>슬픈 오늘은 곧 지나버리네 <br>걱정근심 모두 사라지고 <br>내일은 기쁨의 날 맞으라 <br>삶이 그대를 차마 속일지라도 <br>슬퍼하거나 화내지마 <br>절망의 날 그대 참고 견디면 <br>기쁨의 날 꼭 올거야 <br>삶이 그대를 속일지라도 <br>슬퍼하거나 화내지마 <br>힘든 날들을 참고 견디면 <br>기쁨의 날 꼭 올거야 <br>마음은 미래를 꿈꾸니 <br>슬픈 오늘은 곧 지나버리네 <br>걱정근심 모두 사라지고 <br>내일은 기쁨의 날 맞으라 <br>삶이 그대를 차마 속일지라도 <br>슬퍼하거나 화내지마 <br>절망의 날 그대 참고 견디면 <br>기쁨의 날 꼭 올거야 <br>삶이 그대를 속일지라도 <br>슬퍼하거나 화내지마 <br>슬픈 날들을 참고 견디면 <br>즐거운 날들 오리니 <br>세상이 그대를 버릴지라도 <br>슬퍼하거나 화내지마 <br>힘든 날들을 참고 견디면 <br>기쁨의 날 꼭 올거야 <br>]]></content><category term="유엔젤 보이스" label="유엔젤 보이스"/><category term="삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (한국어 Full Ver.)" label="삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (한국어 Full Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유엔젤_보이스/삶이_그대를_속일지라도_한국어_Ver/</id><title>유엔젤 보이스 - 삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (한국어 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:32:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:32:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EC%97%94%EC%A0%A4_%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4/%EC%82%B6%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%A5%BC_%EC%86%8D%EC%9D%BC%EC%A7%80%EB%9D%BC%EB%8F%84_%ED%95%9C%EA%B5%AD%EC%96%B4_Ver/" title="유엔젤 보이스 - 삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (한국어 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[삶이 그대를 속일지라도 <br>슬퍼하거나 화내지마 <br>슬픈 날들을 참고 견디면 <br>즐거운 날들 오리니 <br>세상이 그대를 버릴지라도 <br>슬퍼하거나 화내지마 <br>힘든 날들을 참고 견디면 <br>기쁨의 날 꼭 올거야 <br>마음은 미래를 꿈꾸니 <br>슬픈 오늘은 곧 지나버리네 <br>걱정 근심 모두 사라지고 <br>내일은 기쁨의 날 맞으라 <br>삶이 그대를 차마 속일지라도 <br>슬퍼하거나 화내지마 <br>절망의 날 그대 참고 견디면 <br>기쁨의 날 꼭 올거야 <br>삶이 그대를 속일지라도 <br>슬퍼하거나 화내지마 <br>슬픈 날들을 참고 견디면 <br>즐거운 날들 오리니 <br>세상이 그대를 버릴지라도 <br>슬퍼하거나 화내지마 <br>힘든 날들을 참고 견디면 <br>기쁨의 날 꼭 올거야 <br>]]></content><category term="유엔젤 보이스" label="유엔젤 보이스"/><category term="삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (한국어 Ver.)" label="삶이 그대를 속일지라도 (한국어 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리틀싸이_황민우/오키도키/</id><title>리틀싸이 황민우 - 오키도키 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:34:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:34:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%ED%8B%80%EC%8B%B8%EC%9D%B4_%ED%99%A9%EB%AF%BC%EC%9A%B0/%EC%98%A4%ED%82%A4%EB%8F%84%ED%82%A4/" title="리틀싸이 황민우 - 오키도키 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아침부터 시작된 엄마의 잔소리 <br>쓴소리 내가 하는 몇 년된 헛소리 <br>숙제 안 했다고 (Oh No) 시험을 왜 또 망쳤냐고 (Oh No) <br>넌 대체 누굴 닮았냐고 아이고 어딜 봐도 봐도 둘 다 투덜이 계속되는데 <br><br>투덜투덜투덜대며 넌 안돼 자꾸자꾸 인상 쓰며 넌 안돼 <br>언제나 I'm Fine And You? Thank You 좌절금지 모두 같이 <br><br>오키도키 뿅뿅 오키도키 Aye Aye 오키도키 뿅뿅 오키도키 오글오글 <br>오키도키 뿅뿅 오키도키 Aye Aye 오키도키 뿅뿅 오키도키 오글오글 오키도키 <br><br>OKAY! <br><br>버스에서 들려오는 잔액 부족소리 (잔액이 부족합니다) <br>쓴소리 난데없는 이건 왜 풋소리 (히트다 히트) <br>콜라마셨다고 (Oh No) 그런데 왜 간장이냐고 (Oh No) <br>왜 자꾸 배가 아프냐고 아이고 어딜 봐도 봐도 어서 휴지는 왜 없는 건데 <br><br>투덜투덜투덜대며 넌 안돼 자꾸자꾸 인상 쓰며 넌 안돼 <br>언제나 I'm Fine And You? Thank You 좌절금지 모두 같이 <br><br>오키도키 뿅뿅 오키도키 Aye Aye 오키도키 뿅뿅 오키도키 오글오글 <br>오키도키 뿅뿅 오키도키 Aye Aye 오키도키 뿅뿅 오키도키 오글오글 오키도키 <br><br>이걸 어찌 하오리 그냥 아싸 가오리 난 통통 너구리 모두 같이 OKAY! <br>이걸 어찌 하오리 그냥 아싸 가오리 내가 통통 너구리 이나저나 난 Sing <br><br>투덜투덜투덜대며 넌 안돼 자꾸자꾸 인상 쓰며 넌 안돼 <br>언제나 I'm Fine And You? Thank You 좌절금지 모두 같이 <br><br>오키도키 뿅뿅 오키도키 Aye Aye 오키도키 뿅뿅 오키도키 오글오글 <br>오키도키 뿅뿅 오키도키 Aye Aye 오키도키 뿅뿅 오키도키 오글오글 오키도키 <br><br>OKAY!]]></content><category term="리틀싸이 황민우" label="리틀싸이 황민우"/><category term="오키도키" label="오키도키"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도민/오직_Feat_예빈/</id><title>도민 - 오직 (Feat. 예빈) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:35:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:35:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%EB%AF%BC/%EC%98%A4%EC%A7%81_Feat_%EC%98%88%EB%B9%88/" title="도민 - 오직 (Feat. 예빈) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 나의 길을 택할지라도 <br>그 길 인도하는 나의 주인이신 <br>어떤것도 내 뜻대로 안되네 <br>나 그 분안에 구속됐네 <br>내 오직 주님만 <br>나의 만족이 되시고 <br>나의 삶의 위로자 되네 <br>내 오직 주님만 <br>나의 필요가 되시고 <br>나의 영원한 소망되네 <br>죄인중에 괴수같은 나인데 <br>끝까지 내 삶을 포기하지 않는 <br>어떤 삶도 주님안에 있으면 <br>헛된 인생은 될 수 없네 <br>내 오직 주님만 <br>나의 만족이 되시고 <br>나의 삶의 위로자 되네 <br>내 오직 주님만 <br>나의 필요가 되시고 <br>나의 영원한 소망되네 <br>내 오직 주님만 <br>나의 만족이 되시고 <br>나의 삶의 위로자 되네 <br>내 오직 주님만 <br>나의 필요가 되시고 <br>나의 영원한 소망되네 <br>영원한 나의 소망되네 <br>]]></content><category term="도민" label="도민"/><category term="오직 (Feat. 예빈)" label="오직 (Feat. 예빈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한아로/청소부/</id><title>한아로 - 청소부 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:40:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:40:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EC%95%84%EB%A1%9C/%EC%B2%AD%EC%86%8C%EB%B6%80/" title="한아로 - 청소부 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[안녕 내 이름은 아로 <br>빙시 새끼들 분리수거하러 <br>먼 길 왔다 <br>곧 죽어도 랩이라는 <br>겉 멋에 찌든 애들이 <br>왜 이리 많아 <br>인위적으로 미친척하는 <br>놈들도 <br>하나 둘 서이 너이 <br>잠시 훑어봐도 <br>씨발 존나게 많아 <br>지네끼리 누굴 아네 누가 <br>나를 알아봤네 <br>얼마 전에 대충 내놓은 <br>내 Mixtape 몇 명 <br>정도가 들었네 But <br>YDG 말 빌려 <br>그게 사실인지 <br>뻥인지 사실 <br>그 뻥이 뻥인 게 <br>사실인지는 아무도 <br>관심 없지 <br>그래 알았으니까 <br>니가 하고 있는 <br>좆 까는 소리 저기 <br>달나라 가서 마음껏 해라 <br>별 볼 일 없는 <br>빙시들 쓸어버려 <br>별 볼 일 없는 <br>빙시들 쓸어버려 <br>별 볼 일 없는 <br>빙시들 쓸어버려 <br>별 볼 일 없는 <br>빙시들 쓸어버려 <br>2011년 겨울 술 <br>마시고 Jordan bag <br>하나 들고 <br>윗 공기 마시러 <br>창원 떠나 서울까지 <br>홍대 길바닥에서 Mic <br>하나로 세상 <br>다 가진 듯 말하던 <br>용돈 받아쓰던 <br>새끼들이 첫 번째 Bro <br>Second Bro 247 정액 <br>마려워서 흐른데 <br>우린 공연하는데 <br>왜 구석에서 <br>여자 번호 물어 보는데 <br>그 외 언급하기 싫은 <br>다수의 쓰레기들 <br>공통점 하나 있어 <br>말해 줄게 <br>며칠 몇 개월 뒤는 <br>시궁창을 벗어나 있겠지 <br>지금은 말고 내일의 <br>멋진 내 모습을 얘기해 <br>오늘 해야 할 일 마저 <br>다음으로 미룬 놈이 <br>무슨 말이야 <br>조까라 마이싱 과대망상은 <br>저기 달 나라 가서 <br>마음껏 해라 <br>별 볼 일 없는 <br>빙시들 쓸어버려 <br>별 볼 일 없는 <br>빙시들 쓸어버려 <br>별 볼 일 없는 <br>빙시들 쓸어버려 <br>별 볼 일 없는 <br>빙시들 쓸어버려 <br>]]></content><category term="한아로" label="한아로"/><category term="청소부" label="청소부"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anouk/There_He_Goes/</id><title>Anouk - There He Goes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:40:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:40:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anouk/There_He_Goes/" title="Anouk - There He Goes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A perfect night in New York City <br>I feel alive and kinda pretty <br>On this sunny Sunday evening <br>Where no worse is being done <br>I put my feet here on the ground <br>You make me something turn around <br>As I pass where no one can see <br>Cause no one's there <br><br>But when you walk on by <br>Through city lights <br>I'm on fire <br>You're like dynamite <br><br>You walk like a lion, yellow mane <br>I see myself holding your hand <br>You mesmerize me as I come undone <br>You warm me like the sun <br>Even your walk has its own groove <br>That crawls me deeply into you <br>I don't know where you're coming from <br>You've got my heart beat like a drum <br><br>Cause when you walk on by <br>Through city lights <br>Baby, I'm on fire <br>You're like dynamite <br>Yeah when you walk on by <br>Through city lights <br>I'm on fire <br>'Til you're out of sight <br><br>There he goes, he walks <br>There he goes <br>There he goes <br>Follow you <br>There he goes, he walks <br>There he goes, there he goes <br>There he goes <br>'Til you're out of sight <br>Baby, I'm on fire <br><br>Baby, I'm on fire <br>When you walk on by <br>Through city lights, yeah <br>Baby, I'm on fire]]></content><category term="Anouk" label="Anouk"/><category term="There He Goes" label="There He Goes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/민기_MK/연리지/</id><title>민기 (MK) - 연리지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:40:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:40:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AF%BC%EA%B8%B0_MK/%EC%97%B0%EB%A6%AC%EC%A7%80/" title="민기 (MK) - 연리지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[있잖아 나는 니가 웃을때 <br>마냥 좋아 <br>있잖아 눈이 마주칠때 <br>나는 마냥 떨려 <br>그렇게 그냥 너무 좋아 <br>니가 함께 있고싶어 너와 <br>막차태워 보내는 일도 <br>이젠 싫어 <br>비가 오는 날엔 <br>너의 우산이 <br>무지 추운 날엔 <br>따뜻한 커피가 <br>눈물 나는 날엔 <br>너의 포근한 <br>어깨가 되어줄게 <br>이상같았던 니가 <br>내 일상이 되고 <br>우리 함께했던 <br>기억이 넘쳐 <br>너에게 물들어 <br>스며들어 <br>좋아하는 마음을 <br>이 곡에 멋지게 담아보고 <br>내 진심을 전하고 싶은데 <br>사랑하는 마음을 <br>이 곡에 예쁘게 포장해서 <br>지금 너에게 선물할게 <br>우연처럼 만나 <br>인연이 된 우리 <br>서롤 알아보던 <br>그 느낌처럼 <br>그 마음 하나로 <br>지금 너에게 <br>좋아하는 마음을 <br>이 곡에 멋지게 담아보고 <br>내 진심을 전하고 싶은데 <br>사랑하는 마음을 <br>이 곡에 예쁘게 포장해서 <br>지금 너에게 선물할게 <br>고마워 감사해 사랑해 <br>사랑하는 마음을 <br>이 곡에 예쁘게 포장해서 <br>지금 너에게 선물할게 <br>지금 너에게 <br>]]></content><category term="민기 (MK)" label="민기 (MK)"/><category term="연리지" label="연리지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이로운_Ronely/무료해_Boredom/</id><title>이로운 (Ronely) - 무료해 (Boredom) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:40:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:40:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B4_Ronely/%EB%AC%B4%EB%A3%8C%ED%95%B4_Boredom/" title="이로운 (Ronely) - 무료해 (Boredom) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[요즘은 밖이 싫어 <br>흥미가 생기질 않아 <br>침대가 내 곁에서 <br>떠나가지 않은 기분 <br>친구들이 불러도 <br>여자 없음 가기 싫어 <br>여자가 있어도 <br>뭐 그저 그렇고 <br>새로 나온 게임을 해도 <br>어디서 해본 것 같고 <br>인기 있는 영화를 봐도 <br>나에겐 뻔한 것 같고 <br>낮엔 자고 싶고 <br>밤엔 또 자기 싫고 <br>모두 내겐 의미 없나 봐 <br>무료해 무료해 무료해 <br>지루해 지루해 지루해 <br>주변의 일들이 다 무료해 <br>무료해 무료해 무료해 <br>지루해 지루해 지루해 <br>매일 일이 돌고 <br>돌 듯 지루해 <br>아마 난 Phone 중독 <br>집안에 숨어선 <br>핸드폰 속으로 <br>다이빙하기 직전 <br>월화수목금 <br>각자의 개성을 잃었어 <br>매일 매일 <br>멍 때리고 있어 <br>머리 위 말풍선 <br>속엔 점점점 <br>딱히 흥미로운 <br>것도 없어 어 어 <br>내일도 아마 <br>똑같겠지 뭐 어 어 <br>유난히 달콤한 빛 <br>나른한 오후네 <br>매일 같은 하룰 사는 게 <br>나만 힘든 건지 <br>내 주변만 뿌옇게 <br>안개가 낀 듯 보이는지 <br>외로워 외로워 나 홀로 <br>외로워 외로워 남긴듯해 <br>나만 혼자 무기력한듯해 <br>무료해 무료해 무료해 <br>지루해 지루해 지루해 <br>주변의 일들이 다 무료해 <br>무료해 무료해 무료해 <br>지루해 지루해 지루해 <br>매일 일이 돌고 <br>돌 듯 지루해 <br>너무나 무료해 <br>무료해 무료해 무료해 <br>지루해 지루해 지루해 <br>주변의 일들이 다 무료해 <br>Everything Just Make Me <br>Feel so sick <br>무료해 무료해 무료해 <br>지루해 지루해 지루해 <br>매일 일이 돌고 <br>돌 듯 지루해 <br>무료해 무료해 무료해 <br>지루해 지루해 지루해 <br>돈이 더 생기면 괜찮을지 <br>연애를 하면 좀 나아질지 <br>무료해 무료해 무료해 <br>지루해 지루해 지루해 <br>아마 내일 하루도 역시 <br>내게는 의미 없을 것 같아 <br>]]></content><category term="이로운 (Ronely)" label="이로운 (Ronely)"/><category term="무료해 (Boredom)" label="무료해 (Boredom)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ANEMOS_아네모스/단편집_SHORT_NOVEL_Feat_SALV/</id><title>ANEMOS (아네모스) - 단편집 (SHORT NOVEL) (Feat. SALV) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:41:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:41:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ANEMOS_%EC%95%84%EB%84%A4%EB%AA%A8%EC%8A%A4/%EB%8B%A8%ED%8E%B8%EC%A7%91_SHORT_NOVEL_Feat_SALV/" title="ANEMOS (아네모스) - 단편집 (SHORT NOVEL) (Feat. SALV) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This could be your story <br>인생은 짧은 <br>단편 소설 <br>그 속에 소년은 <br>울고 있어 <br>외롭게 걸었던 날들을 <br>한 글자씩 혼자서 <br>적어가고 있어 <br>오랜 시간 지나간 <br>후에 알게 됐지 <br>험한 파도에 밀려난 우린 <br>멀리 어미 품을 떠난 <br>새끼고래기에 <br>많은 지혜와 <br>인내가 필요해 <br>좁은 욕조 위에 해일을 <br>견뎌내던 작은 <br>태엽장치 고래는 <br>지금은 물기 없이 말랐네 <br>지금의 내 모습과 닮았네 <br>무표정한 얼굴 위로 <br>알 수 없는 눈물 <br>위로 받지 못한 슬픔 <br>그때로 갈 수 <br>없는 아쉬움이 <br>먼 훗날 내가 다신 <br>나를 찾지 못할까 <br>잊혀질까 봐 두려워서 <br>매일 날 그렸어 <br>길고 긴 터널 <br>어릴 적 순수함을 잃어 <br>어둠에서 빛은 <br>길을 잃어버린 세월 <br>멈춰 세울 수만 있다면 <br>난 마냥 좋겠어 <br>그때는 멈출 수 있다고 <br>그냥 믿었어 <br>당신도 지금 나와 같을까 <br>불 꺼진 방에 홀로 잠긴 밤 <br>인생은 원래 <br>혼자인 거야 바보야 <br>애써 위로해도 눈물 흘려 <br>베개를 적신다 <br>때론 모두 내려 놓았을 때 <br>빛이 나고 견고해지네 <br>가끔 혼자라고 느껴질 땐 <br>눈을 감아봐 <br>인생은 짧은 단편 소설 <br>그 속에 소년은 울고 있어 <br>외롭게 걸었던 날들을 <br>한 글자씩 혼자서 <br>적어가고 있어 <br>that your poor name <br>may have the glory <br>to live remembered <br>in your story <br>don't you cry <br>don't you cry <br>that your poor name <br>may have the glory <br>to live remembered <br>in your story <br>don't you cry <br>don't you cry <br>If I had a message <br>for my dreams <br>To be very simple <br>you are not allowed to die <br>until you have killed me <br>]]></content><category term="ANEMOS (아네모스)" label="ANEMOS (아네모스)"/><category term="단편집 (SHORT NOVEL) (Feat. SALV)" label="단편집 (SHORT NOVEL) (Feat. SALV)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ANEMOS_아네모스/MOON_WALKER/</id><title>ANEMOS (아네모스) - MOON WALKER - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:41:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:41:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ANEMOS_%EC%95%84%EB%84%A4%EB%AA%A8%EC%8A%A4/MOON_WALKER/" title="ANEMOS (아네모스) - MOON WALKER - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's Dream <br>Good Night <br>해져가는 노을 창 밖 <br>웃음 소리 가득 메운 밤 <br>in twilight <br>거미집을 치고 <br>사는 부랑자 <br>늦은 저녁 거리 <br>위로 붉은 바다 <br>오늘보다 더 나은 내일 <br>해수면의 오르내림 <br>달이 잠에서 깨고 나면 <br>또 다른 내가 되기 위한 <br>위대한 작업 <br>난 지금 변해가 <br>소설 속에 나온 <br>어린 왕자 사는 별에도 가 <br>사막여우 말에 눈이 아닌 <br>마음으로 보면 <br>진실을 알아볼 <br>수가 있다는 것 <br>세상에 나만 혼자 <br>남은 듯이 <br>가사를 쓰다 보면 <br>어느새 새벽 2시 <br>뭐가 대단하다고 <br>또 밤을 새지 <br>오늘은 그냥 걷자고 <br>참 달이 밝지 <br>It's Dream <br>Jackson Michael Jackson <br>Jackson Michael Jackson 의 <br>Moon Walker Moon Walker <br>거꾸로 밤을 걷는 <br>Moon Walker <br>Jackson Michael Jackson <br>Jackson Michael Jackson 의 <br>Moon Walker Moon Walker <br>거꾸로 밤을 걷는 <br>Moon Walker <br>왕복 우주선을 타고 <br>달나라로 떠나 <br>해가 잠에 들고나면 <br>말이야 <br>별처럼 쏟아지는 단어 <br>주머니에 가득 채워 <br>맘에 드는 걸로 담아 <br>새벽 이슬 아래 <br>흠뻑 젖었던 <br>나의 마음을 종이에다 <br>가득 채워 <br>잠에 들지 않는 <br>바람 위에 나를 태워 <br>어디로든 떠나 가보자구 <br>멀리 더 Oh <br>사막 같은 밤의 오아시스 <br>별 바다 위에 꿈을 <br>하나 던졌지 <br>어느새 저 하늘은 <br>내겐 검정 도화지 <br>수 많은 밤을 별로 <br>색칠해 놓았지 <br>이 밤이 새도록 <br>돌아가는 기차 <br>그 밤이 새도록 <br>부딪혔던 술잔 <br>그 소리마저 내겐 <br>좋은 가사거리야 <br>꿈을 꿀 수 있어 <br>행복한 시간이야 <br>정말 행복한 시간이야 <br>It's Dream <br>Jackson Michael Jackson <br>Jackson Michael Jackson 의 <br>Moon Walker Moon Walker <br>거꾸로 밤을 걷는 <br>Moon Walker <br>Jackson Michael Jackson <br>Jackson Michael Jackson 의 <br>Moon Walker Moon Walker <br>거꾸로 밤을 걷는 <br>Moon Walker <br>Jackson Michael Jackson <br>Jackson Michael Jackson 의 <br>Moon Walker Moon Walker <br>거꾸로 밤을 걷는 <br>Moon Walker <br>Good Night <br>]]></content><category term="ANEMOS (아네모스)" label="ANEMOS (아네모스)"/><category term="MOON WALKER" label="MOON WALKER"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ANEMOS_아네모스/변해가네_Feat_LONA/</id><title>ANEMOS (아네모스) - 변해가네 (Feat. LONA) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:41:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:41:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ANEMOS_%EC%95%84%EB%84%A4%EB%AA%A8%EC%8A%A4/%EB%B3%80%ED%95%B4%EA%B0%80%EB%84%A4_Feat_LONA/" title="ANEMOS (아네모스) - 변해가네 (Feat. LONA) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보이지 않아 앞이 <br>닫힌 문을 열고 <br>나가야 해 <br>어차피 잡을 수 <br>없는 날들을 <br>그리워 한들 뭐해 <br>지금의 나도 예전과는 <br>전혀 다른 사람이 됐네 <br>좀 더 나은 삶을 위해 <br>쉼 없이 걸어야 해 <br>나를 스쳐가는 바람처럼 <br>지나버린 시간 째깍 <br>언젠가 서른이 되면 뭔가 <br>어른이 되어 멋진 삶을 <br>살 줄 알았지 <br>정답이 없었지 <br>천천히 길을 걷지 <br>왜 계속 멀어지려 해 <br>내 옆에 있던 친구들에게 <br>전화를 걸어 <br>그리웠지 너의 목소리 <br>우리 같은 곳을 봤지만 <br>이제는 다른 길을 걷지 <br>늘 아쉬움이 남아 <br>이렇게 매일 <br>노래하는 내 모습 <br>혼자선 아무 것도 <br>아니라고 <br>나를 둘러싼 어둠이 <br>날 삼킬지라도 <br>우리만은 변치말자 약속 <br>다음에 소주 한잔 꼭 하자 <br>떠나온 뒤에 더 나은 미래 <br>oh <br>변해가네 <br>변해가네 <br>멀어져 가네 <br>oh <br>변해가네 <br>변해가네 <br>멀어져 가네 <br>친구야 <br>우린 정말 많이 <br>변했구나 <br>시간에 녹아버린 <br>케이크처럼 <br>주름만 쌓여가는구나 <br>그저 울고 웃던 <br>그때가 지금은 <br>너무 그리워 <br>이제 와서 자주 <br>연락 못한 내가 미워 <br>누군가 변하지 않는 <br>것은 없다 했지 <br>먼지처럼 너는 <br>자유를 갈망했지 <br>그것마저 변한다는 것은 <br>참 애석하지만 <br>원래 그런 거라고 <br>생각하면 속 편하지 <br>어릴 적 다툰 기억과 <br>철없이 웃던 그때가 <br>지나서 보니 모든 게 <br>추억이 되어 남아 <br>다 괜찮아 그때의 <br>미소만은 <br>영원히 간직하자 <br>우리의 우정만은 <br>절대로 변하지는 말자 <br>예정 없는 기차역에서 <br>무작정 표를 끊었지 <br>우린 약속 없는 <br>시간 속에서 사라지겠지 <br>그때도 술 한잔 건 내면서 <br>너스레 피워주겠니 <br>그래 그렇게 <br>우리의 모든 것이 <br>변해가겠지 <br>oh <br>변해가네 <br>변해가네 <br>멀어져 가네 <br>oh <br>변해가네 <br>변해가네 <br>멀어져 가네 <br>oh <br>변해가네 <br>변해가네 <br>멀어져 가네 <br>oh <br>변해가네 <br>변해가네 <br>멀어져 가네 <br>]]></content><category term="ANEMOS (아네모스)" label="ANEMOS (아네모스)"/><category term="변해가네 (Feat. LONA)" label="변해가네 (Feat. LONA)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ANEMOS_아네모스/FILM_Feat_이예인/</id><title>ANEMOS (아네모스) - FILM (Feat. 이예인) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:41:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:41:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ANEMOS_%EC%95%84%EB%84%A4%EB%AA%A8%EC%8A%A4/FILM_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%EC%98%88%EC%9D%B8/" title="ANEMOS (아네모스) - FILM (Feat. 이예인) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[네가 떠난 자리에 <br>난 항상 그대로 있지 <br>불 꺼진 기억이라 머리 속에 <br>스위치를 더듬거리며 <br>찾아 떠났네 <br>수 없이 부딪혔던 <br>너와 나는 깨져버린 유리 <br>죽을 것만 같던 이별 뒤의 날들이 <br>정신 없이 사는 법을 가르쳐줬지 <br>돌아보니 너는 <br>한참을 떠나 저 멀리에 <br>불 꺼진 신호등에 멈춰서 정지 <br>지금 나는 고장 난 lever <br>천장 위에 그려 <br>밤을 새워 너로 채워 <br>힘들게 지워냈던 <br>네가 다시 떠올라서 <br>오늘 딱 하루만 너를 <br>꺼내기로 했어 <br>뒤로 감는 필름 위로 걷는 우리 둘 <br>사이로 엉켜있는 <br>추억은 거미줄처럼 <br>복잡한 시간을 지나온 감정 <br>잊지 못할 장면들이 겹쳐져 <br>또 없을 짧은 상영 시간 <br>엔딩을 알기에 또 혼자 슬픈 걸까 <br>너로 인해 비롯된 <br>내 삶은 한편의 영화로써 기록돼 <br>시간을 걸어 기억에서 널 <br>다시 볼 수 있을까 <br>우린 닿을 수 있을까 <br>필름 위를 걸어 네 앞에 서면 <br>지난 추억에 잠겨 <br>슬픈 미소 짓고 말아 <br>오가는 대화는 주고받는 대사 <br>또 컷이 울리고 <br>카메라 불이 꺼지고 나면 <br>서로 다른 길로 헤어져 <br>이별 후엔 다음 Scene을 기다렸어 <br>허공 위에 띄운 우린 <br>담배연기 사라지듯 흩어지고 <br>영화에서 지운 장면처럼 <br>나는 잊혀져 <br>이 아픈 상황에서 벗어나야 살아 <br>아직도 너의 사랑에 <br>난 계속 매일 자라 <br>시간을 걸어 기억에서 널 <br>다시 볼 수 있을까 <br>우린 닿을 수 있을까 <br>필름 위를 걸어 네 앞에 서면 <br>지난 추억에 잠겨 <br>슬픈 미소 짓고 말아 <br>한때는 지독히도 사랑했던 사람 <br>깊이 가슴 속에 묻은 사람 <br>내 생에 명작으로 <br>영원히 넌 남겠지 <br>하나뿐인 너는 추억으로 남겠지 <br>한때는 지독히도 사랑했던 사람 <br>깊이 가슴 속에 묻은 사람 <br>내 생에 명작으로 <br>영원히 넌 남겠지 <br>하나뿐인 너는 추억으로 남겠지 <br>시간을 걸어 기억에서 널 <br>다시 볼 수 있을까 <br>우린 닿을 수 있을까 <br>필름 위를 걸어 네 앞에 서면 <br>지난 추억에 잠겨 <br>슬픈 미소 짓고 말아 <br>]]></content><category term="ANEMOS (아네모스)" label="ANEMOS (아네모스)"/><category term="FILM (Feat. 이예인)" label="FILM (Feat. 이예인)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ANEMOS_아네모스/흔들의자_Feat_LONA/</id><title>ANEMOS (아네모스) - 흔들의자 (Feat. LONA) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:41:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:41:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ANEMOS_%EC%95%84%EB%84%A4%EB%AA%A8%EC%8A%A4/%ED%9D%94%EB%93%A4%EC%9D%98%EC%9E%90_Feat_LONA/" title="ANEMOS (아네모스) - 흔들의자 (Feat. LONA) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[희미한 불빛의 꺼져가는 불씨 <br>언제부터 의자가 삐끗거린 건지 <br>부러진 연필처럼 삐뚤어진 글씨 <br>바람 불어 후하고 털어내면 <br>먼지 뒤덮인 세상 <br>그 안에 나의 모습 <br>너무나 처량하네 <br>나는 아주 작은 점에 지나지 않아 <br>박자를 맞춰야 해 난 <br>언제부터인지 <br>흔들리는 의자 같이 <br>같은 방향으로 움직여 <br>숨어 사는 외톨박이 <br>웃음 뒤로 애써 가려 울고 <br>낙엽 지고 얼어 버리고 <br>편히 잠에 들 수 없기에 <br>꿈을 꿀 수 조차 없네 <br>수 만가지의 감정에 부딪혀 <br>미리 짜여진 각본에 맞추어 <br>거짓으로 살아가며 감정을 숨겼던 <br>나는 가면을 쓴 채로 숨 쉬어 <br>날갤 펴고 다시 낮게라도 <br>나는 날고 싶어 <br>창문 열고 다시 바람 쐬며 <br>하늘을 보고 싶어 <br>또 해가 지네 흔들 의자기에 <br>모든 게 내 맘대로 되지가 않아 <br>나는 끌려가네 <br>돌아가는 시계바늘 잡고 울며 <br>나는 늘어지네 <br>꿈은 저 멀리에 다시 흔들리네 <br>터질듯한 한숨과 익숙해진 <br>눈물만 흘러 내리네 <br>흔들리는 불빛이 <br>희미해져만 가네 <br>흔들리는 게 난 익숙해지네 <br>아지랑이 피어나는 작은 소망은 <br>증발되어 사라지네 <br>퍼즐 조각을 끼워 맞춰 <br>살아봐도 안될 거라고 <br>자신에게 타일렀지 그만하라고 <br>덫에 걸린 듯이 <br>발버둥을 쳐도 제자리에 <br>상처를 지워내도 <br>다시 그대로 흉터지네 <br>가을이 지나고 겨울이 오겠지 <br>여밀 시간 없이 <br>파란 하늘마저 짧아 지겠지 <br>여유도 없이 약한 바람에도 <br>몸서리 치는 내가 미워 <br>그 손은 치워 난 내가 싫어 <br>달력을 찢어 내겐 미래는 없어 <br>하루가 지긋지긋해 <br>아픈 청춘의 시는 지금 <br>땀에 찌들어 시름 시름 <br>냄새만 피워내고 시든 꽃이 됐네 <br>내일의 내 거름이 될 거라 믿었던 <br>나도 벌써 어른이 됐네 <br>세월을 걷는데 불안한 마음과 <br>무감각 해지는 찰나 <br>방황은 날이 선 칼날처럼 <br>내리치며 승패를 갈라 <br>흔들리는 의자 위에 <br>앉아서 들어 고개를 <br>난 백색 연기만 하늘에 내뿜네 <br>터질듯한 한숨과 익숙해진 <br>눈물만 흘러 내리네 <br>흔들리는 불빛이 <br>희미해져만 가네 <br>흔들리는 게 난 익숙해지네 <br>터질듯한 한숨과 익숙해진 <br>눈물만 흘러 내리네 <br>흔들리는 불빛이 <br>희미해져만 가네 <br>흔들리는 게 난 익숙해지네 <br>]]></content><category term="ANEMOS (아네모스)" label="ANEMOS (아네모스)"/><category term="흔들의자 (Feat. LONA)" label="흔들의자 (Feat. LONA)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ClaD_클래디/Still_all_day_Feat_Heavy_Ray/</id><title>ClaD (클래디) - Still all day (Feat. Heavy Ray) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:41:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:41:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ClaD_%ED%81%B4%EB%9E%98%EB%94%94/Still_all_day_Feat_Heavy_Ray/" title="ClaD (클래디) - Still all day (Feat. Heavy Ray) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I need a Rais <br>너는 내게 오면 되 <br>and like a stars <br>feeling shine <br>나를 존재하게 해 <br>how was your day <br>If I ain't got you <br>난 너에게 <br>닿는 기분을 위한 날을 <br>꿀 꺼야 available <br>when I leave <br>when I leave <br>i'm waiting for The sky a <br>너만 따라 오면 되 baby <br>cuz I'm waiting <br>stars in <br>ho <br>crazy love <br>you don't have to fall <br>너를 잡게 될 테니 <br>where are you <br>you don't have to fall <br>when I was alive <br>without you <br>whenever never <br>All I got <br>너에게 난 가고 있어 <br>I'm still all day <br>still all day <br>still all day <br>널 갖고 싶어 <br>you don't have to fall <br>너를 잡게 될 테니 <br>where are you <br>you don't have to fall <br>when I was alive <br>without you <br>whenever never <br>All I got <br>너에게 난 가고 있어 <br>I'm still all day <br>still all day <br>still all day <br>널 갖고 싶어 <br>I need you baby <br>너를 지금 takin' <br>Girl 이젠 lay down <br>우리 둘의 feel game set <br>너는 뭘 원해 <br>tell me babe if you <br>'bout that love somethin' <br>So i'll give chance <br>계속 발 끝만 바라보네 no no <br>아무 말도 필요 없어 <br>그냥 따라오면 돼 babe <br>지금인 듯 해 <br>woo make it love <br>you don't have to fall <br>너를 잡게 될 테니 <br>where are you <br>you don't have to fall <br>when I was alive <br>without you <br>whenever never <br>All I got <br>너에게 난 가고 있어 <br>I'm still all day <br>still all day <br>still all day <br>널 갖고 싶어 <br>you don't have to fall <br>너를 잡게 될 테니 <br>where are you <br>you don't have to fall <br>when I was alive <br>without you <br>whenever never <br>All I got <br>너에게 난 가고 있어 <br>I'm still all day <br>still all day <br>still all day <br>널 갖고 싶어 <br>when I leave you crying <br>니가 우는 자리 <br>Some day I will send you <br>if you want to see it Rais <br>니 곁에서 <br>떨어져 있는게 <br>그 곳을 갈 수 있는 <br>불빛을 내리네 <br>너와 high away <br>you don't have to fall <br>너를 잡게 될 테니 <br>where are you <br>you don't have to fall <br>when I was alive <br>without you <br>whenever never <br>All I got <br>너에게 난 가고 있어 <br>I'm still all day <br>still all day <br>still all day <br>널 갖고 싶어 <br>you don't have to fall <br>너를 잡게 될 테니 <br>where are you <br>you don't have to fall <br>when I was alive <br>without you <br>whenever never <br>All I got <br>너에게 난 가고 있어 <br>I'm still all day <br>still all day <br>still all day <br>널 갖고 싶어 <br>]]></content><category term="ClaD (클래디)" label="ClaD (클래디)"/><category term="Still all day (Feat. Heavy Ray)" label="Still all day (Feat. Heavy Ray)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ClaD_클래디/In_a_Darkened/</id><title>ClaD (클래디) - In a Darkened - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:41:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:41:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ClaD_%ED%81%B4%EB%9E%98%EB%94%94/In_a_Darkened/" title="ClaD (클래디) - In a Darkened - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 삐끗할 마음 뿐 인것 같아 <br>내가 그래 왔듯이 <br>어쩌면 넌 다른 사람 같아 hey <br>기억을 잃어버린 사람 같지 <br>의미 없는 눈빛 사이로 <br>하얀 눈 내릴 듯이 <br>나는 가을 전에는 <br>이별을 말 할 것 같아 <br>너는 떠났지 <br>The Fallin season <br>Fallin season <br>Fallin season <br>Fallin season <br>Fallin season <br>너는 처음부터 <br>날 밟고 갈듯이 <br>말 거는 기분 <br>거는 기분 <br>거는 기분 <br>똑같은 가을이 오면 <br>어색해 <br>깊은 하늘이 너무 싫어 <br>우리 사이 같아 <br>난 지겹게도 <br>cuz I'm feeling fine <br>난 자기 전에 너에게 <br>lookin to you <br>crazy I mean crazy <br>I'm in <br>Rais <br>난 두려워 미쳐 가는 중이야 <br>나 홀로 Crying <br>trying for you stay there <br>trying for you Lady <br>Look at this <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>I'm still in here <br>my song is fine <br>how are you doin <br>난 아직은 가해자야 <br>널 버리고 가는 <br>궂이 이런 버릇 <br>안 버리고 살어 <br>넌 강인한 여자거든 <br>난 자비를 원해 <br>니 행동에 패여 <br>그 깊이를 재고 있어 <br>널 미워했거든 <br>울지마 돌아서겠다면 <br>나의 뒤에서 <br>더 차가운 소리로 <br>나를 위해서 <br>Faillin Faillin in crazy <br>눈 가리네 괜히 <br>사람들 사이에 <br>섞이려 하네 여전히 <br>I'll find The Rais <br>and Rais and <br>해일이 되고 안 보이는 <br>내일이 두려워 <br>깊이 잠기는 중이야 <br>in a darkened room <br>니가 빛이 되는 <br>꿈에서는 너와 나를 <br>이제 알아가는 중이지 <br>still find on me <br>무사히 넘기는 밤이 두려워 <br>reason to live In me <br>cuz I'm feeling fine <br>난 자기 전에 너에게 <br>looking to you <br>crazy I mean crazy <br>I'm in <br>Rais <br>난 두려워 미쳐 가는 중이야 <br>나 홀로 Crying <br>trying for you stay there <br>trying for you Lady <br>두번 다시 나를 <br>보지 않기를 <br>답한 그댄 너무 <br>멀리 갔고 나 홀로 <br>Prater <br>어쩌면 다 큰 나는 <br>어리광을 부리지 <br>내 방에선 <br>Creep I got pain <br>어둠을 잡은 채로 <br>놓지 않으려 해 <br>니가 주인이 되는 <br>밤을 맞이하려고 <br>Let it shine Little body <br>leave in high away <br>이미 죽은 나의 하루인걸 <br>when am I crazy daring <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>In a darkened <br>]]></content><category term="ClaD (클래디)" label="ClaD (클래디)"/><category term="In a Darkened" label="In a Darkened"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ClaD_클래디/별빛_사이/</id><title>ClaD (클래디) - 별빛 사이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:41:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:41:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ClaD_%ED%81%B4%EB%9E%98%EB%94%94/%EB%B3%84%EB%B9%9B_%EC%82%AC%EC%9D%B4/" title="ClaD (클래디) - 별빛 사이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[끝나는 너와의 어제 밤에 <br>이별한 내 가여운 자리 <br>지금 이 거리 위 너와 나 <br>늘어가는 불빛들 사이 <br>Feeling my Face ye <br>넌 거의 끝에 서있고 <br>머리는 비었어 나의 발밑에 <br>little my 케이스 <br>둘이 고른 그 반지가 <br>구르고 있어 너무 반듯해 <br>우리 사이처럼 미끄러진 <br>길을 따라가다 <br>보면 일그러진 <br>너의 표정이 너무 싫어서 <br>바라기전에 <br>이별하게 된 거지 <br>지금을 음미해 hm <br>돌아서겠다면 지금이야 <br>막바지로 접어들었지 음 <br>너의 말은 거짓말뿐이야 <br>날 붙잡아 <br>많이 구차해도 난 괜찮아 <br>요즘은 바람이 날카롭지 <br>내일은 껴입어 <br>내가 거기 없잖아 <br>Let's do it again <br>끝나는 너와의 어제 밤에 <br>이별한 내 가여운 자리 <br>지금 이 거리 위 너와 나 <br>늘어가는 불빛들 사이 <br>start day <br>넌 나의 밤에 들어와 <br>날 탐내 내 꿈에서만 <br>너와 건배해 자주 가던 그 <br>Hot place <br>거리가 멀어져 <br>나의 부름에도 <br>너는 보지 않지 <br>가로등은 아직 <br>노란 불을 켜고 있지 <br>해가 뜨고 나면 <br>집으로갔고 <br>아직도 니 방에 <br>불은 꺼져있지 <br>둘이었을 때는 모르던 Feelin <br>너의 뺨에 내 입맞춤 <br>나를 바라보는 이불 위에 <br>너의 그 skin이 <br>달갑지만은 않았던 거야 <br>너를 잊길 바래 <br>너의 팔에 작게 새겼던 나를 <br>다시 말해 너는 타투야 <br>나를 투영하는 그림 아래 <br>너의 체온이 베있지 <br>아무도 없는 거기 <br>just you and I <br>In passion <br>you and I <br>In passion <br>still a ray <br>In there <br>아끼던 둘의 Ring's <br>I'm just feelin you <br>In passion <br>feeling you In passion <br>cuz I really bad <br>불리한듯해 <br>니가 먼저 말한 건 <br>준비를 했던 거야 <br>그 이별에 관하여 <br>I can't leave you alone <br>believe me ye <br>난 적어도 내 기분에 <br>책임은 질 수 있어 <br>니가 뭔데 <br>니가 뭔데 <br>I'm leave in Away feelin me <br>나를 위해 걷네 <br>니가 뭔데 <br>니가 뭔데 <br>이젠 꿈에서도 <br>우린 다른 곳 <br>향해 돌아 서고 있어 <br>끝나는 너와의 어제 밤 <br>이별한 내 가여운 자리 <br>지금 이 거리 위 너와 나 <br>늘어가는 불빛들 사이 <br>]]></content><category term="ClaD (클래디)" label="ClaD (클래디)"/><category term="별빛 사이" label="별빛 사이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ClaD_클래디/허전함_Feat_Rick_Bridges/</id><title>ClaD (클래디) - 허전함 (Feat. Rick Bridges) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:41:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:41:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ClaD_%ED%81%B4%EB%9E%98%EB%94%94/%ED%97%88%EC%A0%84%ED%95%A8_Feat_Rick_Bridges/" title="ClaD (클래디) - 허전함 (Feat. Rick Bridges) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나의 허전함이 <br>우릴 만드네 <br>니가 질렸나봐 <br>나는 다른 사람이 <br>눈에 들어 올 꺼야 내가 <br>하늘에서 비춘 <br>달이 되면 너가 <br>우산을 쓰네 <br>그런 날이 됬나 봐 <br>니가 날 거부하는 날 <br>난 날 미워 할 꺼야 <br>너무 다른 사람 된 날 <br>매일 매일 지워 낼 꺼야 <br>time is run away run away <br>우리 다른 사람 될까 <br>너의 빈말이라면 다시 <br>우리 사이 저 멀리 <br>허전함이 둘 <br>허전함이 둘 <br>허전함이 둘 <br>을 바라보네 <br>허전함이 둘 <br>허전함이 둘 <br>허전함이 둘 <br>을 바라보네 <br>난 니 주변을 돌지 <br>내 맘을 들킬까 봐서 <br>내게 연락이 없는 <br>이걸 안심하며 한숨 쉬네 <br>하루를 벌며 사는 꼴이 <br>지겨울 뿐이야 <br>내가 가진 너의 맘이 <br>너무 작아졌네 <br>내가 널 거부하는 날 <br>넌 날 미워 할 꺼야 <br>너무 다른 사람 된 날 <br>매일 매일 지워 낼꺼야 <br>time is run away run away <br>우리 다른 사람 될까 <br>니가 정해준다면 <br>다시 우리 사이 저 멀리 <br>허전함이 둘 <br>허전함이 둘 <br>허전함이 둘 <br>을 바라보네 <br>허전함이 둘 <br>허전함이 둘 <br>허전함이 둘 <br>을 바라보네 <br>니가 없는 이 차가운 <br>밤이 나를 밀쳐 <br>너에게 가라고 하는 듯한데 <br>멀리 저 <br>허전함이 둘 <br>허전함이 둘 <br>허전함이 둘 <br>을 바라보네 <br>I don't know what it is <br>허전 하긴 해도 <br>I don't care <br>내 옆에 앉아있던 <br>너의 빈자리를 <br>메꾸는 일은 전혀 <br>어렵지 않아 <br>Oh well I'm fine <br>괜한 말이 아니라 <br>난 잘 살아 <br>너의 착각과는 달리 <br>잠이 들기 전에 드는 <br>생각 중 너가 차지하는 건 <br>nothin <br>네 머릿속엔 늘 <br>high price dresses <br>fuckin scandal <br>'I was abandoned' <br>그런 쓸데없는 생각들에 <br>You be the gold digger <br>friendo <br>여전히 기억하네 <br>새벽 두 시반 <br>웃기지도 않아 <br>잠을 자야겠다던 <br>너는 클럽 안에서 <br>fuck around and <br>'round and 'round and 'round <br>I know you got that <br>Beautiful face <br>I know you got that <br>Seductive ass <br>I know you got that <br>I know you got that <br>I know you got that <br>Nuthin <br>너가 손에 쥐고 있는 <br>것들은 모두 <br>껍데기 뿐이라는 걸 <br>알아채길 바래 그 때 <br>너의 표정을 보고 싶어 <br>애처로운 마음으로 <br>너에 대한 가사를 <br>써 내려가네 <br>So good ho <br>허전함이 <br>허전함이 <br>허전함이 <br>허전함이 <br>허전함이 <br>허전함이 <br>허전함이 <br>]]></content><category term="ClaD (클래디)" label="ClaD (클래디)"/><category term="허전함 (Feat. Rick Bridges)" label="허전함 (Feat. Rick Bridges)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ClaD_클래디/Yours/</id><title>ClaD (클래디) - Yours - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:41:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:41:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ClaD_%ED%81%B4%EB%9E%98%EB%94%94/Yours/" title="ClaD (클래디) - Yours - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>각자의 삶이 다르지 <br>우린 시한부 같은 <br>인생을 사네 <br>모두의 사명이 다르지 <br>늘 마른 우물을 파는 것 <br>그게 내 일이었다면 <br>지구를 뚫을 준비가 <br>되있 겠지 난 <br>어떠한 물음에 답하는 순간 <br>후회할 시간은 없지 <br>비탈길에 서있는 <br>것들에게 박수를 보내 난 <br>의미 없이 헛된 상처를 <br>밟고 가려는 그 마음 <br>또한 늘 부럽지 <br>낮선 땅을 밟으려는 삶 <br>그 안에 가고 싶어 <br>그들이 나보다 <br>나은 삶을 산다면 <br>인정 할 수도 있어 <br>난 틀에 박히지 않기 위해 <br>미래가 지지않기 위해 <br>넘어가는 숨 부여잡고 <br>싸웠지 매번 난 날 지지해 <br>이곳에 내가 <br>살아 남기 위해 <br>하고 싶은 걸 하지 <br>내 갈길 이네 <br>내가 태어난 <br>이유를 찾기 위해 <br>어머니가 주신 <br>하나뿐인 난 날 위해 <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>위기뿐인 나의 삶에 <br>걸리는 모든 것들이 <br>난 너무 좋아 <br>미련을 갖는 일 따위에 <br>내 시간을 할애 <br>할 순 없거니와 <br>이 자리를 비롯한 <br>내 이름을 믿으며 <br>신이 강요 하는 대로 <br>사는 건 나답지 않네 <br>멀리 물음이 닿지 <br>않는 곳 을 가려 할 때 <br>나의 가족한테 기도하지 <br>그가 나의 뒤로 oh <br>넌 너고 나는 다르니 <br>비교하지 아니하길 <br>나를 방해하고 싶다면 <br>음악으로 니 숨으로 <br>빛깔이 다른 색으로 <br>이야기하길 <br>난 하루살이 삶을 <br>사네 너의 바램 앞에 <br>음악을 하기 위해서 <br>이 감정을 토해 내려 <br>하네 나의 아버지인 <br>나의 드럼 <br>나의 존재를 위해서 <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>또 내게만 <br>들리는 소리들과함께 <br>또 내게만 <br>들어오네 음악이 나한테 <br>Oh Really Mind <br>I'm in here <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>Cuz All about <br>I'm yours <br>and now 너와 함께 <br>나를 벌 하여 두 눈을 <br>감지 못하게 하고 <br>팔을 뻗으면 닿을 거리에 <br>Mic하나 주어진다면 <br>노래를 하겠지 <br>나의 랩이 주문을 건다면 <br>팔이 가는 대로 무대를 걸으며 <br>내가 살아있다고 말해 <br>지금 이 기도를 <br>Just All about <br>I'm yours <br>Just All about <br>I'm yours <br>Just All about <br>I'm yours <br>Just All about <br>I'm yours <br>Just All about <br>I'm yours <br>Just All about <br>I'm yours <br>Just All about <br>I'm yours <br>Just All about <br>I'm yours <br>Just All about <br>I'm yours <br>Just All about <br>I'm yours <br>Just All about <br>I'm yours <br>]]></content><category term="ClaD (클래디)" label="ClaD (클래디)"/><category term="Yours" label="Yours"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ClaD_클래디/Flat_Feat_Stunna/</id><title>ClaD (클래디) - Flat (Feat. Stunna) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T23:41:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T23:41:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ClaD_%ED%81%B4%EB%9E%98%EB%94%94/Flat_Feat_Stunna/" title="ClaD (클래디) - Flat (Feat. Stunna) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[put'em down hand's up <br>h <br>put'em down hand's high <br>put'em down hand's high <br>talking about girl <br>I'm trying to what <br>너완 다른 나의 Mind <br>Leaving life girl <br>나의 향기가 베 <br>Cuz Doing I'm Fellow <br>Look at them crumble <br>그들은 내게 별로 <br>trying to away I'm flat <br>trying to away I'm flat road <br>trying to away I'm flat <br>trying to away I'm flat road <br>trying to away I'm flat <br>trying to away I'm flat road <br>난 반음 높아있지 <br>그들은 몰라 나의 위치 <br>너는 Flat <br>비가 내리겠지 <br>그대로 가라고 <br>난 길을 다 밟진 않어 <br>아마 다르게 취급되겠지 <br>넌 불리한 듯 두 귀를 막어 <br>너는 Stone 난 나무 <br>그늘이되어 <br>너를 가리고 내리는 <br>비를 막아 난 태연해 <br>때론 불을 바라지 날 태우길 바래 <br>재가되면 바람 따라 날아 <br>저 위로가 모두를 내려다봐 <br>마치 다른 행성에서 <br>온 듯이 눈이 커져 <br>doing I'm Falchion <br>베어내지 자라는 나무들 <br>어디를 밟아 니가 <br>자라 날 땅은 푹 꺼져 <br>going high high high <br>낙엽이 쌓인 자리 나의 발로 밟어 <br>비를 뿌리는 하늘에 불을 지르고 <br>타오르는 줄기를 타지 <br>아무도 시도 한적 없는 <br>put'em down hand's up <br>h <br>put'em down hand's high <br>put'em down hand's high <br>talking about girl <br>I'm trying to what <br>너완 다른 나의 Mind <br>Leaving life girl <br>나의 향기가 베 <br>Cuz Doing I'm Fellow <br>Look at them crumble <br>그들은 내게 별로 <br>trying to away I'm flat <br>trying to away I'm flat road <br>trying to away I'm flat <br>trying to away I'm flat road <br>trying to away I'm flat <br>trying to away I'm flat road <br>난 반음 높아있지 <br>그들은 몰라 나의 위치 <br>너는 Flat <br>같은 지반 아래 <br>뿌리부터 달라 넌 너무 짠해 <br>넌 반음 아래 h <br>발버둥 쳐도 나는 반응 안 해 <br>니들 씨는 말라가네 <br>깊어지는 절망감에 넌 더 깜깜해 <br>난 파멸하는 니 미래를 본 <br>몇 안 되는 신과 맞담배를 피는 놈 <br>I feel like a crack 수백억치 <br>g 내 삶은 그래 <br>등대 따윈 필요 없는 <br>특색 있는 홀로선 늑대 <br>난 이제 전혀 상관 안 해 <br>너와 나의 승패 <br>때로 몰려와도 학살을 당하지 <br>니 무덤은 쓰레기통 같은 광안리 <br>내앞에 무릎 꿇는게 <br>낫지 넌 차라리 <br>니가 안감힘을 써도 <br>널 짓밟는 나는 하나님 <br>put'em down hand's up <br>h <br>put'em down hand's high <br>put'em down hand's high <br>talking about girl <br>I'm trying to what <br>너완 다른 나의 Mind <br>Leaving life girl <br>나의 향기가 베 <br>Cuz Doing I'm Fellow <br>Look at them crumble <br>그들은 내게 별로 <br>trying to away I'm flat <br>trying to away I'm flat road <br>trying to away I'm flat <br>trying to away I'm flat road <br>trying to away I'm flat <br>trying to away I'm flat road <br>난 반음 높아있지 <br>그들은 몰라 나의 위치 <br>너는 Flat <br>]]></content><category term="ClaD (클래디)" label="ClaD (클래디)"/><category term="Flat (Feat. Stunna)" label="Flat (Feat. Stunna)"/></entry></feed>