<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:52:45+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Down_In_It_Live/</id><title>Nine_Inch_Nails - Down In It (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:04:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:04:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Down_In_It_Live/" title="Nine_Inch_Nails - Down In It (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wimp. Wimp. <br><br>Kinda like a cloud I was up way up in the sky. <br>And I was feeling some feelings you wouldn't believe. <br>Sometimes I don't believe them myself and I decided I was never coming down. <br><br>Just then a tiny little dot caught my eye. <br>It was just about too small to see. <br>But I watched it way too long. <br>It was pulling down. <br><br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>Now I'm down in it <br><br>Shut up. <br>So what what does it matter now. <br>I was swimming in the hate now I crawl on the ground. <br>And everything I never liked about you is kind of seeping into me. <br>I try to laugh about it now but isn't it funny how everything works out. <br>I guess the jokes on me, she said. <br><br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>Now I'm down in it <br><br>I used to be so big and strong. <br>I used to know my right from wrong. <br>I used to never be afraid. <br>I used to be somebody. <br><br>I used to have something inside. <br>Now just this hole it's open wide. <br>I used to want it all. <br>I used to be somebody. <br><br>I'll cross my heart and hope to die. <br>But the needle's already in my eye. <br>And all the world's weight is on my back and I don't even know why. <br>And what I used to think was me is just a fading memory. <br>I looked him right in the eye and said "goodbye." <br><br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>Now I'm down in it <br><br>Rain rain go away. <br>Rain rain go away. <br>Rain rain go away. <br>Come again some other day. <br><br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>Now I'm down in it <br><br>Na na na na na na na na.]]></content><category term="Nine Inch Nails" label="Nine Inch Nails"/><category term="Down In It (Live)" label="Down In It (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/The_Only_Time_Live/</id><title>Nine_Inch_Nails - The Only Time (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:04:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:04:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/The_Only_Time_Live/" title="Nine_Inch_Nails - The Only Time (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm drunk. <br>And right now I'm so in love with you. <br>And I don't want to think too much about what we should or shouldn't do. <br>Lay my hands on Heaven and the sun and the moon and the stars. <br>While the devil wants to fuck me in the back of his car. <br><br>Nothing quite like the feel of something new. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up in you. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up in you. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>This is the only time I really feel alive. <br>This is the only time I really feel alive. <br><br>I swear. <br>I just found everything I need. <br>The sweat in your eyes the blood in your veins are listening to me. <br>Well I want to wrap it up and swim in it until I drown. <br>My moral standing is lying down. <br><br>Nothing quite like the feel of something new. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up in you. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up in you. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>This is the only time I really feel alive. <br>This is the only time I really feel alive]]></content><category term="Nine Inch Nails" label="Nine Inch Nails"/><category term="The Only Time (Live)" label="The Only Time (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Burn_Live/</id><title>Nine_Inch_Nails - Burn (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:04:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:04:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Burn_Live/" title="Nine_Inch_Nails - Burn (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This world rejects me <br>This world threw me away <br>This world never gave me a chance <br>This world's gonna have to pay <br><br>I don't believe in your institutions <br>I did what you wanted me to <br>Like cancer in the system <br>I've got a little suprise for you <br><br>Something inside of me has opened up its eyes <br>Why did you put it there did you not realize <br>This thing inside of me it screams the loudest sound <br>Sometimes i think i could <br><br>Burn <br><br>I look down there where you're standing <br>Flock of sheep out on display <br>Saw your lives burned up around you <br>I can take it all away <br><br>Something inside of me has opened up its eyes <br>Why did you put it there did you not realize <br>This thing inside of me it screams the loudest sound <br>Sometimes i think i could <br><br>I'm gonna burn this whole world down <br><br>I never was a part of you burn <br><br>I am the agent i never was a part of you burn <br>I am corruption i never was a part of you burn <br>I am the angel i never was a part of you burn <br>Of your destruction i never was a part of you burn <br><br>I am subversion i never was a part of you burn <br>Secret desire i never was a part of you burn <br>I am your future i never was a part of you burn <br>Swallow down all that fire]]></content><category term="Nine Inch Nails" label="Nine Inch Nails"/><category term="Burn (Live)" label="Burn (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Reptile_Live/</id><title>Nine_Inch_Nails - Reptile (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:04:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:04:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Reptile_Live/" title="Nine_Inch_Nails - Reptile (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[she spread herself wide open to let the insects in <br>she leaves a trail of honey to show me where she's been <br>she has the blood of reptile just underneath her skin <br>seeds from a thousand others drip down from within <br><br>oh my beautiful liar <br>oh my precious whore <br>my disease my infection <br>I am so impure <br><br>get it <br><br>devils speak of the ways in which she'll manifest <br>angels bleed from the tainted touch of my caress <br>need to contaminate to alleviate this loneliness <br>I now know the depths I reach are limitless <br><br>oh my beautiful liar <br>oh my precious whore <br>my disease my infection <br>I am so impure]]></content><category term="Nine Inch Nails" label="Nine Inch Nails"/><category term="Reptile (Live)" label="Reptile (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Something_I_Can_Never_Have_Live/</id><title>Nine_Inch_Nails - Something I Can Never Have (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:04:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:04:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Something_I_Can_Never_Have_Live/" title="Nine_Inch_Nails - Something I Can Never Have (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I still recall the taste of your tears. <br>Echoing your voice just like the ringing in my ears. <br>My favorite dreams of you still wash ashore. <br>Scraping through my head 'till I don't want to sleep anymore. <br><br>You make this all go away. <br>You make this all go away. <br>I'm down to just one thing. <br>And I'm starting to scare myself. <br>You make this all go away. <br>You make this all go away. <br>I just want something. <br>I just want something I can never have <br><br>You always were the one to show me how <br>Back then I couldn't do the things that I can do now. <br>This thing is slowly taking me apart. <br>Grey would be the color if I had a heart. <br><br>Come on tell me <br><br>You make this all go away. <br>You make this all go away. <br>I'm down to just one thing. <br>And I'm starting to scare myself. <br>You make this all go away. <br>You make this all go away. <br>I just want something. <br>I just want something I can never have <br><br>In this place it seems like such a shame. <br>Though it all looks different now <br>I know it's still the same <br>Everywhere I look you're all I see. <br>Just a fading fucking reminder of who I used to be. <br><br>Come on tell me <br><br>You make this all go away. <br>You make this all go away. <br>I'm down to just one thing. <br>And I'm starting to scare myself. <br>You make this all go away. <br>You make this all go away. <br>I just want something. <br>I just want something I can never have <br><br>I just want something I can never have]]></content><category term="Nine Inch Nails" label="Nine Inch Nails"/><category term="Something I Can Never Have (Live)" label="Something I Can Never Have (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Tush_Live/</id><title>ZZ_Top - Tush (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Tush_Live/" title="ZZ_Top - Tush (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I been up, I been down. <br>Take my word, my way around. <br>I ain't askin' for much. <br>I said, Lord, take me downtown <br>I'm just lookin' for some tush. <br><br>I been bad, I been good <br>Dallas, Texas, Hollywood. <br>I ain't askin' for much. <br>I said, Lord, take me downtown <br>I'm just lookin' for some tush. <br><br>Take me back way back home <br>not by myself, not alone. <br>I ain't askin' for much. <br>I said, Lord, take me downtown <br>I'm just lookin' for some tush.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Tush (Live)" label="Tush (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Jailhouse_Rock_Live/</id><title>ZZ_Top - Jailhouse Rock (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Jailhouse_Rock_Live/" title="ZZ_Top - Jailhouse Rock (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Goin' to a party in the county jail <br>Prison band was there and they began to wail. <br>Kid is shakin' and began to sing; <br>You should've heard them knocked out jailbirds sing. <br>Let's rock! Everybody, let's rock! <br>Everybody in the whole cell block <br>Was dancin' to the jailhouse rock. <br><br>Spider Murphy sittin' on a block of stone; <br>Little Joey blowin' on a slide trombone. <br>Come on, Silly Willy, don't you be no square. <br>If you cannot find a partner, use a wooden chair. <br>Let's rock! Everybody, let's rock! <br>Everybody in the whole cell block <br>Was dancin' to the jailhouse rock. <br><br>Shifty Henry said to Bugs,"For heaven's sake <br>No one's lookin'; now's our chance to make a break." <br>Bugsy turned to Shifty and he said, "Nix nix. I <br>Wanna stick around awhile and get my kicks." <br>Let's rock! Everybody, let's rock! <br>Everybody in the whole cell block <br>Was dancin' to the jailhouse rock.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Jailhouse Rock (Live)" label="Jailhouse Rock (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Dust_My_Broom_Live/</id><title>ZZ_Top - Dust My Broom (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Dust_My_Broom_Live/" title="ZZ_Top - Dust My Broom (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm gonna get up in the morning <br>I believe I'll dust my broom. <br>I'm gonna get up in the morning <br>I believe I'll dust my broom. <br>Well my best gal I'll be leaving <br>So my friend, get out my room <br><br>I'm gonna write a letter to China <br>See if my baby's over there. <br>I'm gonna write a letter to China <br>See if my baby's over there. <br>If she ain't up in the Hawaiian Islands <br>Must be in Ethiopia somewhere <br><br>I believe believe my time alone <br>I believe believe my time alone <br>I've had to quit my baby and give up my happy home]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Dust My Broom (Live)" label="Dust My Broom (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Hi_Fi_Mama_Live/</id><title>ZZ_Top - Hi Fi Mama (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Hi_Fi_Mama_Live/" title="ZZ_Top - Hi Fi Mama (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want your hi fi mama, won't you let me play it tonight <br>I want your hi fi mama, won't you let me play it tonight <br>I put the needle in the groove, baby while you douse the lights. <br><br>I play it on your dresser, play it upside your wall <br>I play it in your kitchen, even play it in your hall <br>I play it anywhere you want it, any old time at all. <br><br>Hi fi lo fi no fi's just fine with me. <br>Hi fi lo fi no fi's just fine with me. <br>And if you want to give me stereo first give me vitamin E. <br>I got your name and your number.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Hi Fi Mama (Live)" label="Hi Fi Mama (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/She_Loves_My_Automobile_Live/</id><title>ZZ_Top - She Loves My Automobile (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/She_Loves_My_Automobile_Live/" title="ZZ_Top - She Loves My Automobile (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She don't love me, she love my automobile. <br>She don't love me, she love my automobile. <br>Well she would do anything just to slide behind the wheel. <br><br>She said what's it gonna take for you to lay your top on down? <br>She said what's it gonna take for you to lay your top on down? <br>I said honey why don't you ask me when we get to the outskirts of town. <br><br>Well now she don't care if I'm stoned or sloppy drunk. <br>Well she don't care if I'm stoned or sloppy drunk <br>Long as she got the keys and there's a spare wheel in her trunk.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="She Loves My Automobile (Live)" label="She Loves My Automobile (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Arrested_For_Driving_While_Blind_Live/</id><title>ZZ_Top - Arrested For Driving While Blind (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Arrested_For_Driving_While_Blind_Live/" title="ZZ_Top - Arrested For Driving While Blind (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you're driving down the highway at night <br>And you're feelin' that wild turkey's bite <br>Don't give Johnny Walker a ride <br>Cause Jack Black is right by your side <br>You might get taken to the jailhouse and find <br>You've been arrested for driving while blind <br><br>Now just the other night with nothin' to do <br>We broke a case of proof 102 <br>And started itchin' for that wonderful feel <br>Of rollin' in an automobile <br>You could say we was out of our mind <br>And let me tell you we were flyin' while blind <br><br>Then they had us up against the wall <br>Hey it's only blood grain alcohol <br>And there ain't no cause for alarm <br>We ain't out to do nobody no harm <br>How could anyone be so unkind <br>To arrest a man for drivin' while blind]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Arrested For Driving While Blind (Live)" label="Arrested For Driving While Blind (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Cheap_Sunglasses_Live/</id><title>ZZ_Top - Cheap Sunglasses (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Cheap_Sunglasses_Live/" title="ZZ_Top - Cheap Sunglasses (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you get up in the morning and the light is hurt your head <br>The first thing you do when you get up out of bed <br>Is hit that street a-runnin' and try to meet the masses <br>And go get yourself some cheap sunglasses <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah <br><br>Spied a little thing and I followed her all night <br>In a funky fine levis and her sweater's kind of tight <br>She had a west coast strut that was sweet as molases <br>But what really knocked me out was her cheap sunglasses <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah <br><br>Now go out and get yourself some thick black frames <br>With the glass so dark thay won't even know your name <br>And the choice is up to you cause they come in two classes <br>Rhinestone shades and cheap sunglasses <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Cheap Sunglasses (Live)" label="Cheap Sunglasses (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/A_Fool_For_Your_Stockings_Live/</id><title>ZZ_Top - A Fool For Your Stockings (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/A_Fool_For_Your_Stockings_Live/" title="ZZ_Top - A Fool For Your Stockings (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Is it you again outside <br>Just banging on the front door? <br>You say you had enough <br>Now you're coming' back for more <br>But that's alright. <br>I said that that's alright. <br>I may not want to admit it <br>I'm just a fool for your stockings I believe. <br><br>Now I don't mind when you send money <br>and bring your girlfriends with you <br>But how could one be so thoughtless to try <br>and handle less than two? <br>But that's alright. <br>I said that that's alright, baby. <br>I may not want to admit it <br>I'm just a fool for your stockings I believe. <br><br>Now I'm tellin' everybody <br>It seems too good to be true: <br>Sweet things can always get sweeter. <br>I know mine did, how about you? <br>Yes, it's alright. <br>I said, yes it is, that's alright. <br>I may not want to admit it <br>I'm just a fool for your stockings I believe.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="A Fool For Your Stockings (Live)" label="A Fool For Your Stockings (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Low_Down_In_The_Street_Live/</id><title>ZZ_Top - Low Down In The Street (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Low_Down_In_The_Street_Live/" title="ZZ_Top - Low Down In The Street (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well there comes Lola, out of control-a: <br>She just loves those rhythm and blues. <br>And miss Ivy will be arriving; <br>in leopard skin tights she's willing to cruise. <br><br>It's a fiend scene and it happens 'bout once a week. <br>So fork over some bread, it'll do your head to get low down in the street. <br><br>There's Jimmy and Jojo, there's Kim and Keith <br>Way outside the eyes of cool. <br>And sweet M.B., and there's little G.B. <br>Everybody wants to be their fool. <br><br>It's a fiend scene and it happens here ev'ry week. <br>Fork over some bread, it'll do your head to get low down in the street. <br><br>Some nights are lonely, some nights are lazy <br>but ain't nobody try and slip away. <br>They'll make you loose. They'll make you crazy. <br>Know what I mean, what you say, what you say. <br><br>It's a fiend scene and it happens 'bout once a week. <br>So roam on in, it ain't no sin to get low down in the street.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Low Down In The Street (Live)" label="Low Down In The Street (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Im_Bad_Im_Nationwide_Live/</id><title>ZZ_Top - I`m Bad I`m Nationwide (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Im_Bad_Im_Nationwide_Live/" title="ZZ_Top - I`m Bad I`m Nationwide (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well I was rollin' down the road in some cold blue steel <br>I had a bluesman in the back, and a beautician at the wheel. <br>We're going downtown in the middle of the night <br>We was laughing and I'm jokin' and we feelin' alright. <br>Oh I'm bad, I'm nationwide. <br>Yes I'm bad, I'm nationwide. <br><br>Easin' down the highway in a new Cadillac <br>I had a fine fox in front, I had three more in the back. <br>They sportin' short dresses, wearin' spike-heeled shoes <br>They smokin' Lucky Strikes, wearing nylon too. <br>Welcome back, we're nationwide. <br>Yeah we bad, we're nationwide. <br><br>Well I was movin' down the road in my V-8 Ford <br>I had a shine on my boots, I had my sideburns lowered. <br>With my New York brim and my gold tooth displayed <br>Nobody give me trouble cause they know I got it made. <br>I'm bad, I'm nationwide. <br>Girl I'm bad, bad, bad, bad, bad, I'm nationwide.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="I`m Bad I`m Nationwide (Live)" label="I`m Bad I`m Nationwide (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Jesus_Just_Left_Chicago_Live/</id><title>ZZ_Top - Jesus Just Left Chicago (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Jesus_Just_Left_Chicago_Live/" title="ZZ_Top - Jesus Just Left Chicago (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jesus just left Chicago and he's bound for New Orleans. <br>Well now, Jesus just left Chicago and he's bound for New Orleans. <br>Yeah, yeah. <br>Workin' from one end to the other and all points in between. <br><br>Took a jump through Mississippi, well, muddy water turned to wine. <br>Took a jump through Mississippi, muddy water turned to wine. <br>Yeah, yeah. <br>Then out to California through the forests and the pines. <br>Ah, take me with you, Jesus. <br><br>You might not see him in person but he'll see you just the same. <br>You might not see him in person but he'll see you just the same. <br>Yeah, yeah. <br>You don't have to worry 'cause takin' care of business is his name.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Jesus Just Left Chicago (Live)" label="Jesus Just Left Chicago (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Waitin_For_The_Bus_Live/</id><title>ZZ_Top - Waitin` For The Bus (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Waitin_For_The_Bus_Live/" title="ZZ_Top - Waitin` For The Bus (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Have mercy, been waitin' for the bus all day. <br>Have mercy, been waitin' for the bus all day. <br>I got my brown paper bag and my take-home pay. <br><br>Have mercy, old bus be packed up tight. <br>Have mercy, old bus be packed up tight. <br>Well, I'm glad just to get on and home tonight. <br><br>Right on, that bus done got me back. <br>Right on, that bus done got me back. <br>Well, I'll be ridin' on the bus till I Cadillac.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Waitin` For The Bus (Live)" label="Waitin` For The Bus (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/I_Thank_You_Live/</id><title>ZZ_Top - I Thank You (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/I_Thank_You_Live/" title="ZZ_Top - I Thank You (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You didn't have to love me like you did <br>But you did, but you did. <br>And I thank you. <br>You didn't have to love me like you did <br>But you did, but you did. <br>And I thank you. <br>But you took your love to someone else <br>I wouldn't know what it meant to be loved to death <br><br>You made me feel like I've never felt <br>Kisses so good I had to holler for help <br>You didn't have to squeeze it but you did <br>But you did but you did <br>And I thank you. <br>You didn't have to hold it but you did <br>But you did but you did <br>And I thank you. <br><br>Every day was something new <br>You put on your bag and your fine to-do <br>You got me trying new things too <br>Just so I can keep up with you. <br><br>You didn't have to shake it but you did <br>But you did but you did <br>And I thank you. <br>You didn't have to make it like you did <br>but you did but you did <br>And I thank you. <br><br>All my life I've been shortchanged <br>Without your love baby it's a crying shame <br>But now I know what the fellas talking about <br>Hear me say that they been turned out <br>I want to thank you <br>I want to thank you <br>I want to thank you <br>Yes, I want to thank you]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="I Thank You (Live)" label="I Thank You (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Hey_Hey_My_My_Out_Of_The_Black_Live/</id><title>Neil_Young - Hey Hey, My My (Out Of The Black) (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Hey_Hey_My_My_Out_Of_The_Black_Live/" title="Neil_Young - Hey Hey, My My (Out Of The Black) (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey hey, my my <br>Rock and roll can never die <br>There's more to the picture <br>Than meets the eye. <br>Hey hey, my my. <br><br>Out of the blue <br>and into the black <br>You pay for this <br>but they give you that <br>And once you're gone <br>you can't come back <br>When you're out of the blue <br>and into the black. <br><br>The king is gone <br>but he's not forgotten <br>Is this the story <br>of Johnny Rotten? <br>It's better to burn out <br>'cause rust never sleeps <br>The king is gone <br>but he's not forgotten. <br><br>Hey hey, my my <br>Rock and roll can never die <br>There's more to the picture <br>Than meets the eye.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Hey Hey, My My (Out Of The Black) (Live)" label="Hey Hey, My My (Out Of The Black) (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Like_A_Hurricane_Live/</id><title>Neil_Young - Like A Hurricane (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Like_A_Hurricane_Live/" title="Neil_Young - Like A Hurricane (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Once I thought I saw you <br>in a crowded hazy bar <br>Dancing on the light <br>from star to star. <br>Far across the moonbeam <br>I know that's who you are <br>I saw your brown eyes <br>turning once to fire. <br><br>You are like a hurricane <br>There's calm in your eye. <br>And I'm gettin' blown away <br>To somewhere safer <br>where the feeling stays. <br>I want to love you but <br>I'm getting blown away. <br><br>I am just a dreamer <br>but you are just a dream <br>You could have been <br>anyone to me. <br>Before that moment <br>you touched my lips <br>That perfect feeling <br>when time just slips <br>Away between us <br>on our foggy trip. <br><br>You are like a hurricane <br>There's calm in your eye. <br>And I'm gettin' blown away <br>To somewhere safer <br>where the feeling stays. <br>I want to love you but <br>I'm getting blown away. <br><br>You are just a dreamer <br>and I am just a dream. <br>You could have been <br>anyone to me. <br>Before that moment <br>you touched my lips <br>That perfect feeling <br>when time just slips <br>Away between us <br>on our foggy trip. <br><br>You are like a hurricane <br>There's calm in your eye. <br>And I'm gettin' blown away <br>To somewhere safer <br>where the feeling stays. <br>I want to love you but <br>I'm getting blown away.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Like A Hurricane (Live)" label="Like A Hurricane (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Violent_Side_Live/</id><title>Neil_Young - Violent Side (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Violent_Side_Live/" title="Neil_Young - Violent Side (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here comes the night <br>Here comes the anger <br>Hidden so deep inside <br>No one can see <br>Behind these eyes <br>There walks a stranger <br>Wandering through the dark <br>Following me. <br><br>Control the violent side <br>Control the violent side <br>Control the violent side <br>Control the violent side. <br><br>Electric light <br>Shining on your block <br>Sayin' to everyone <br>The power is on <br>While your alarm <br>Set up for safety <br>Keeps out invaders who come <br>But still can't control. <br><br>Control the violent side <br>Control the violent side <br>Control the violent side <br>Control the violent side. <br><br>Got to fight to control <br>the violent side <br>Every day and night <br>I've got to fight <br>to control it.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Violent Side (Live)" label="Violent Side (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Computer_Age_Live/</id><title>Neil_Young - Computer Age (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Computer_Age_Live/" title="Neil_Young - Computer Age (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cars and trucks <br>Fly by me on the corner <br>But I'm all right <br>Standin' proud <br>before the signal <br>When I see the light <br>I know I'm more <br>than just a number. <br>And I stand before you <br>Or else we <br>just don't see the other <br>Computer age computer age <br>Computer age. <br><br>Bikes and vans <br>Fly by me on the desert <br>But I'm all right <br>Standing out here <br>in the hot sun <br>When I see the light <br>I feel like <br>more than just a number <br>And I stand before you <br>Or else we <br>just don't see the other <br>Computer age computer age <br>Computer age. <br><br>Precious metal lines <br>Molded into highways <br>Running through me <br>So microscopically <br>Days and nights <br>Weeks and months and seasons <br>Rolling through me <br>So chronologically. <br>Computer age computer age <br>Computer age. <br><br>I need you <br>To let me know <br>that there's a heartbeat <br>Let it pound and pound <br>And I'll be <br>flying like a free bird <br>And you need me <br>Like ugly needs a mirror <br>And day by day <br>This horizon's getting clearer <br>Computer age computer age <br>Computer age.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Computer Age (Live)" label="Computer Age (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Sample__Hold_Live/</id><title>Neil_Young - Sample &amp; Hold (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Sample__Hold_Live/" title="Neil_Young - Sample &amp; Hold (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sample and Hold <br>Hair: Blonde <br>Eyes: Blue <br>Weight: 110 <br>Disposition: Even <br>Mood Code: Rotary Adjustable <br><br>I need a unit to sample and hold <br>But not the angry one <br>A new design, new design. <br><br>I need a unit to sample and hold <br>But not the lonely one <br>A new design, new design. <br><br>I need a unit to sample and hold <br>But not the lonely one <br>A new design, new design. <br><br>Sample and hold. <br><br>We'll send it out right away <br>Satisfaction guaranteed. <br>Please specify <br>The color of skin and eye <br>We know you'll be happy. <br><br>Don't hesitate to give us a call <br>We know you'll be satisfied <br>When you energize <br>And see your unit come alive <br>We know you'll be happy. <br><br>I need a unit to sample and hold <br>But not the lonely one <br>the lonely one <br>the lonely one <br>Sample and hold. <br>Weight: 110. <br><br>Perfection in every details <br>Fabricated from <br>the curl of the hair <br>To the tip of the nail <br>Because our units never fail <br>We know you'll be happy. <br><br>I need a unit to sample and hold. <br><br>Don't hesitate to give us a call <br>We know you'll be satisfied <br>When you energize <br>And see your unit come alive <br>We know you'll be happy. <br><br>I need a unit to sample and hold. <br><br>We know you'll be happy 110 <br>We know you'll be happy <br>We know you'll be happy. <br><br>But not the lonely one <br>A new design, new design <br>Perfection in every detail <br>new design <br>Sample and hold.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Sample &amp; Hold (Live)" label="Sample &amp; Hold (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/After_The_Goldrush_Live/</id><title>Neil_Young - After The Goldrush (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/After_The_Goldrush_Live/" title="Neil_Young - After The Goldrush (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, I dreamed I saw the knights <br>In armor coming <br>Saying something about a queen. <br>There were peasants singing and <br>Drummers drumming <br>And the archer split the tree. <br>There was a fanfare blowing <br>To the sun <br>That was floating on the breeze. <br>Look at Mother Nature on the run <br>In the nineteen seventies. <br>Look at Mother Nature on the run <br>In the nineteen seventies. <br><br>I was lying in a burned out basement <br>With the full moon in my eyes. <br>I was hoping for replacement <br>When the sun burst thru the sky. <br>There was a band playing in my head <br>And I felt like getting high. <br>I was thinking about what a <br>Friend had said <br>I was hoping it was a lie. <br>Thinking about what a <br>Friend had said <br>I was hoping it was a lie. <br><br>Well, I dreamed I saw the silver <br>Space ships flying <br>In the yellow haze of the sun <br>There were children crying <br>And colors flying <br>All around the chosen ones. <br>All in a dream, all in a dream <br>The loading had begun. <br>They were flying Mother Nature's <br>Silver seed to a new home in the sun. <br>Flying Mother Nature's <br>Silver seed to a new home.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="After The Goldrush (Live)" label="After The Goldrush (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/The_Needle__The_Damage_Done_Live/</id><title>Neil_Young - The Needle &amp; The Damage Done (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/The_Needle__The_Damage_Done_Live/" title="Neil_Young - The Needle &amp; The Damage Done (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I caught you knockin' <br>at my cellar door <br>I love you, baby <br>can I have some more <br>Ooh, ooh, the damage done. <br><br>I hit the city and <br>I lost my band <br>I watched the needle <br>take another man <br>Gone, gone, the damage done. <br><br>I sing the song <br>because I love the man <br>I know that some <br>of you don't understand <br>Milk-blood <br>to keep from running out. <br><br>I've seen the needle <br>and the damage done <br>A little part of it in everyone <br>But every junkie's <br>like a settin' sun.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="The Needle &amp; The Damage Done (Live)" label="The Needle &amp; The Damage Done (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Sugar_Mountain_Live/</id><title>Neil_Young - Sugar Mountain (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Sugar_Mountain_Live/" title="Neil_Young - Sugar Mountain (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, to live on Sugar Mountain <br>With the barkers and the colored balloons <br>You can't be twenty on Sugar Mountain <br>Though you're thinking that <br>you're leaving there too soon <br>You're leaving there too soon. <br><br>It's so noisy at the fair <br>But all your friends are there <br>And the candy floss you had <br>And your mother and your dad. <br><br>Oh, to live on Sugar Mountain <br>With the barkers and the colored balloons <br>You can't be twenty on Sugar Mountain <br>Though you're thinking that <br>you're leaving there too soon <br>You're leaving there too soon. <br><br>There's a girl just down the aisle <br>Oh, to turn and see her smile. <br>You can hear the words she wrote <br>As you read the hidden note. <br><br>Oh, to live on Sugar Mountain <br>With the barkers and the colored balloons <br>You can't be twenty on Sugar Mountain <br>Though you're thinking that <br>you're leaving there too soon <br>You're leaving there too soon. <br><br>Now you're underneath the stairs <br>And you're givin' back some glares <br>To the people who you met <br>And it's your first cigarette. <br><br>Oh, to live on Sugar Mountain <br>With the barkers and the colored balloons <br>You can't be twenty on Sugar Mountain <br>Though you're thinking that <br>you're leaving there too soon <br>You're leaving there too soon. <br><br>Now you say you're leavin' home <br>'Cause you want to be alone. <br>Ain't it funny how you feel <br>When you're findin' out it's real? <br><br>Oh, to live on Sugar Mountain <br>With the barkers and the colored balloons <br>You can't be twenty on Sugar Mountain <br>Though you're thinking that <br>you're leaving there too soon <br>You're leaving there too soon. <br><br>Oh, to live on Sugar Mountain <br>with the barkers and the colored balloons <br>You can't be twenty on Sugar Mountain <br>Though you're thinking that <br>you're leaving there too soon <br>You're leaving there too soon.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Sugar Mountain (Live)" label="Sugar Mountain (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Heart_Of_Gold_Live/</id><title>Neil_Young - Heart Of Gold (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Heart_Of_Gold_Live/" title="Neil_Young - Heart Of Gold (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want to live <br>I want to give <br>I've been a miner for a heart of gold. <br>It's these expressions <br>I never give <br>That keep me searching for a heart of gold. <br><br>And I'm getting old. <br>Keep me searching for a heart of gold <br>And I'm getting old. <br><br>I've been to Hollywood <br>I've been to Redwood <br>I crossed the ocean for a heart of gold. <br>I've been in my mind <br>It's such a fine line <br>That keeps me searching for a heart of gold. <br><br>And I'm getting old. <br>Keeps me searching for a heart of gold <br>And I'm getting old. <br><br>Keep me searching for a heart of gold. <br>You keep me searching and I'm growing old. <br>Keep me searching for a heart of gold <br>I've been a miner for a heart of gold.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Heart Of Gold (Live)" label="Heart Of Gold (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Opera_Star_Live/</id><title>Neil_Young - Opera Star (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Opera_Star_Live/" title="Neil_Young - Opera Star (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So your girlfriend <br>slammed the door shut <br>In your face tonight <br>but that's all right <br>Then she took off <br>to the opera <br>With some highbrow <br>from the city lights <br>Well, you grew up on a corner <br>You never missed a moonlit night. <br><br>Some things never change <br>they stay the way they are. <br>You were born to rock <br>you'll never be an opera star <br>Some things never change <br>they stay the way they are. <br><br>So you stay out all night <br>Gettin' fucked up <br>in that rock and roll bar <br>And you never get tired <br>'Cause your drugs <br>are in a little jar. <br><br>You were born to rock <br>you'll never be an opera star. <br>Some things never change <br>they stay the way they are. <br><br>I was born to rock! <br><br>So your girlfriend <br>slammed the door shut <br>In your face tonight <br>but that's all right <br>Then she took off <br>to the opera <br>With some highbrow <br>from the city lights <br>Well, you grew up on a corner <br>You never missed a moonlit night. <br><br>Some things never change <br>they stay the way they are. <br>You were born to rock <br>you'll never be an opera star.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Opera Star (Live)" label="Opera Star (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Drive_Back_Live/</id><title>Neil_Young - Drive Back (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Drive_Back_Live/" title="Neil_Young - Drive Back (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever gets you <br>through the night <br>That's all right with me <br>When it's time to say goodbye <br>I have to make you see <br><br>You won't know me <br>I won't call you <br>I won't be there <br>To remind you <br>What you told me <br>When I showed you <br>In the morning <br>Let me know you'll <br><br>Drive back to your old town <br>I wanna wake up <br>with no-one around <br>Drive back to your old town. <br><br>If somebody <br>Is haunting your mind <br>Look in my eyes <br>Let me hide you <br>From yourself and <br>All your old friends <br>Every good thing <br>Comes to an end. <br><br>Drive back <br>drive back <br>drive back. <br><br>Drive back to your old town <br>I wanna wake up with no-one around <br>Drive back to your old town.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Drive Back (Live)" label="Drive Back (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Down_By_The_River_Live/</id><title>Neil_Young - Down By The River (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Down_By_The_River_Live/" title="Neil_Young - Down By The River (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Be on my side <br>I'll be on your side <br>baby <br>There is no reason <br>for you to hide <br>It's so hard for me <br>staying here all alone <br>When you could be <br>taking me for a ride. <br><br>Yeah, she could drag me <br>over the rainbow <br>send me away <br>Down by the river <br>I shot my baby <br>Down by the river <br>Dead, oh, shot her dead. <br><br>You take my hand <br>I'll take your hand <br>Together we may get away <br>This much madness <br>is too much sorrow <br>It's impossible <br>to make it today. <br><br>Yeah, she could drag me <br>over the rainbow <br>send me away <br>Down by the river <br>I shot my baby <br>Down by the river <br>Dead, oh, shot her dead. <br><br>Be on my side <br>I'll be on your side <br>baby <br>There is no reason <br>for you to hide <br>It's so hard for me <br>staying here all alone <br>When you could be <br>taking me for a ride. <br><br>Yeah, she could drag me <br>over the rainbow <br>send me away <br>Down by the river <br>I shot my baby <br>Down by the river <br>Dead, oh, shot her dead.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Down By The River (Live)" label="Down By The River (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/When_You_Dance_I_Can_Really_Love_Live/</id><title>Neil_Young - When You Dance I Can Really Love (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/When_You_Dance_I_Can_Really_Love_Live/" title="Neil_Young - When You Dance I Can Really Love (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you dance <br>Do your senses tingle? <br>Then take a chance? <br>In a trance <br>While the lonely mingle <br>With circumstance? <br><br>I've got <br>something to tell you <br>you make it show. <br>Let me come over <br>I know you know <br>When you dance <br>I can really love. <br><br>I can love <br>I can really love <br>I can really love <br>I can love <br>I can really love <br>I can really love <br><br>Like a <br>mountain that's growing <br>a river that rolls <br>Let me come over <br>I know you know <br>When you dance <br>I can really love. <br><br>When you dance <br>Do your senses tingle? <br>Then take a chance? <br>In a trance <br>While the lonely mingle <br>With circumstance? <br><br>I've got <br>something to tell you <br>you make it show. <br>Let me come over <br>I know you know <br>When you dance <br>I can really love.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="When You Dance I Can Really Love (Live)" label="When You Dance I Can Really Love (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Cinnamon_Girl_Live/</id><title>Neil_Young - Cinnamon Girl (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Cinnamon_Girl_Live/" title="Neil_Young - Cinnamon Girl (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wanna live <br>with a cinnamon girl <br>I could be happy <br>the rest of my life <br>With a cinnamon girl. <br><br>A dreamer of pictures <br>I run in the night <br>You see us together <br>chasing the moonlight <br>My cinnamon girl. <br><br>Ten silver saxes <br>a bass with a bow <br>The drummer relaxes <br>and waits between shows <br>For his cinnamon girl. <br><br>A dreamer of pictures <br>I run in the night <br>You see us together <br>chasing the moonlight <br>My cinnamon girl. <br><br>Pa sent me money now <br>I'm gonna make it somehow <br>I need another chance <br>You see your baby loves to dance <br>Yeah... yeah... yeah.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Cinnamon Girl (Live)" label="Cinnamon Girl (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Mr_Soul_Live/</id><title>Neil_Young - Mr. Soul (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Mr_Soul_Live/" title="Neil_Young - Mr. Soul (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, hello Mr. Soul <br>I dropped by <br>to pick up a reason <br>For the thought that I caught <br>that my head <br>is the event of the season <br>Why in crowds just a trace <br>of my face <br>could seem so pleasin' <br>I'll cop out to the change <br>but a stranger <br>is putting the tease on. <br><br>I was down on a frown <br>when the messenger <br>brought me a letter <br>I was raised by the praise <br>of a fan <br>who said I upset her <br>Any girl in the world <br>could have easily <br>known me better <br>She said, You're strange <br>but don't change <br>and I let her. <br><br>In a while will the smile <br>on my face <br>turn to plaster? <br>Stick around while the clown <br>who is sick <br>does the trick of disaster <br>For the race of my head <br>and my face <br>is moving much faster <br>Is it strange I should change? <br>I don't know <br>why don't you ask her?]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Mr. Soul (Live)" label="Mr. Soul (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박정우/내마음_별과같이/</id><title>박정우 - 내마음 별과같이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:21:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:21:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A0%95%EC%9A%B0/%EB%82%B4%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C_%EB%B3%84%EA%B3%BC%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%B4/" title="박정우 - 내마음 별과같이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[산 노을에 두둥실 <br>홀로 가는 저 구름아 <br>너는 알리라 내 마음을 <br>부평초같은 마음을 <br>한송이 구름꽃을 <br>피우기위해 <br>떠도는 유랑별처럼 <br>내마음 별과 같이 <br>저 하늘 별이 되어 <br>영원히 빛나리 <br>강바람에 두둥실 <br>길을 잃은 저 구름아 <br>너는 알리라 내 갈길을 <br>나그네 떠나 갈길을 <br>찬란한 젊은 꿈을 <br>피우기위해 <br>떠도는 몸이라지만 <br>내마음 별과 같이 <br>저 하늘 별이 되어 <br>영원히 빛나리 <br>]]></content><category term="박정우" label="박정우"/><category term="내마음 별과같이" label="내마음 별과같이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박정우/사랑/</id><title>박정우 - 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:21:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:21:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A0%95%EC%9A%B0/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="박정우 - 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 세상에 하나밖에 <br>둘도 없는 내 여인아 <br>보고 또 보고 또 쳐다봐도 <br>싫지 않는 내 사람아 <br>비 내리는 여름날엔 <br>내 가슴은 우산이 되고 <br>눈 내리는 겨울날엔 <br>내 가슴은 불이 되리라 <br>온 세상을 다 준다 해도 <br>바꿀 수 없는 내 여인아 <br>잠시라도 떨어져서는 <br>못살 것 같은 내 사람아 <br>행여 당신 외로울 땐 <br>내가 당신 친구가 되고 <br>행여 당신 우울할 땐 <br>내가 당신 웃음 주리라 <br>이 세상에 하나밖에 <br>둘도 없는 내 여인아 <br>보고 또 보고 또 쳐다봐도 <br>싫지 않는 내 사람아 <br>]]></content><category term="박정우" label="박정우"/><category term="사랑" label="사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박정우/청춘_그시절/</id><title>박정우 - 청춘 그시절 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:21:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:21:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A0%95%EC%9A%B0/%EC%B2%AD%EC%B6%98_%EA%B7%B8%EC%8B%9C%EC%A0%88/" title="박정우 - 청춘 그시절 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이제 다시는 오지않겠지 <br>아름답던 청춘 그 시절 <br>그래도 나름대로 멋있게 살았다고 <br>미련도 후회도 없다 <br>인생길 울고 웃던 그고비마다 <br>사랑으로 꿈을 주던 고마운 당신 <br>나도 당신도 그청춘 <br>이렇게 빨리 갈 줄 몰랐다 <br>우리 이제 남은 인생 <br>아름다운 사람들과 정나누며 <br>한잔술에 추억으로 <br>그렇게 살아갑시다 <br>인생길 울고 웃던 그 고비마다 <br>사랑으로 꿈을 주던 고마운 당신 <br>나도 당신도 그청춘 <br>이렇게 빨리 갈 줄 몰랐다 <br>우리 이제 남은 인생 <br>아름다운 사람들과 정나누며 <br>한잔술에 추억으로 <br>그렇게 살아갑시다 <br>]]></content><category term="박정우" label="박정우"/><category term="청춘 그시절" label="청춘 그시절"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박정우/물레방아/</id><title>박정우 - 물레방아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:21:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:21:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A0%95%EC%9A%B0/%EB%AC%BC%EB%A0%88%EB%B0%A9%EC%95%84/" title="박정우 - 물레방아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[돌고 돌아가는 인생같은 물레방아 <br>너를 보고 있으면 옛생각이 난다 <br>내가 자란 고향에 돌아가던 물레방아 <br>철이 없던 그 시절 친구들과 뛰놀던 <br>그 추억이 그립다 <br>살다보면 하나둘씩 잊혀지지만 <br>너는 나의 마음에 고향 <br>강물같은 세월 돌고도는 세상 <br>물레방아 방아야 <br>돌고 돌아가는 인생같은 물레방아 <br>너를 보고 있으면 옛생각이 난다 <br>내가 자란 고향에 돌아가던 물레방아 <br>철이 없던 그 시절 친구들과 뛰놀던 <br>그 추억이 그립다 <br>살다보면 인생길이 힘겨울때면 <br>너는 나의 마음에 고향 <br>강물같은 세월 돌고도는 세상 <br>물레방아 방아야 <br>강물같은 세월 돌고도는 세상 <br>물레방아 방아야 <br>]]></content><category term="박정우" label="박정우"/><category term="물레방아" label="물레방아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lemonan_Studio/Ice_Cream/</id><title>Lemonan_Studio - Ice Cream - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:21:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:21:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lemonan_Studio/Ice_Cream/" title="Lemonan_Studio - Ice Cream - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[유난히 넌 내게 차갑고 <br>널보면 난 고개를 푹 숙여 <br>넌 누구에게나 달콤해 <br>왜 난 씁쓸하기만 해 <br>차갑게 굴어도 사실 oh <br>i know there is something <br>sweet in your mind <br>매일 널 향해 주문을 걸어 <br>매일 밤 내맘은 널 향해 걸어 <br>꾹 다문 입술 시크한 말투 <br>네 앞에서 난 정말 바보같지만 <br>어쩔 수 없어 네게로 자꾸만 <br>떨어지고 있는걸 <br>boy you are my ice cream <br>you are my ice cream <br>난 알아 무심한 척해도 <br>내게 머무른 시선 <br>반짝이는 your eyes <br>달콤한 whipped cream 처럼 녹아들어 <br>ice cream you are my ice cream <br>난 알아 넌 날 좋아한다는걸 <br>내게 다가와 손 잡아줄래 <br>약속해 넌 나만의 ice cream <br>네 앞에서면 빨갛게 익은 <br>내 뺨을 네게 들키긴 싫은데 <br>어쩔수 없어 네게로 자꾸만 <br>떨어지고있는걸 <br>boy you are my ice cream <br>you are my ice cream <br>난 알아 무심한 척해도 <br>내게 머무른 시선 <br>반짝이는 your eyes <br>달콤한 whipped cream처럼 녹아들어 <br>ice cream you are my ice cream <br>난 알아 넌 날 좋아한다는걸 <br>내게 다가와 손 잡아줄래 <br>약속해 넌 나만의 ice cream <br>bittersweet and strange <br>참 알 수 없는 네 맘 <br>do you know how i feel <br>Ice cream you are my ice cream <br>난 알아 무심한 척해도 <br>내게 머무른 시선 <br>반짝이는 your eyes <br>달콤한 whipped cream처럼 녹아들어 <br>ice cream you are my ice cream <br>난 알아 넌 날 좋아한다는걸 <br>내게 다가와 손 잡아줄래 <br>약속해 넌 나만의 ice cream <br>]]></content><category term="Lemonan Studio" label="Lemonan Studio"/><category term="Ice Cream" label="Ice Cream"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/은정은/국화/</id><title>은정은 - 국화 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:22:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:22:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%80%EC%A0%95%EC%9D%80/%EA%B5%AD%ED%99%94/" title="은정은 - 국화 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[일렁이는 촛불너머로 <br>고운 미소 아름다운데 <br>국화향기 그 안에서 당신은 <br>아무 말이 없구려 <br>친구들이 권하는 술을 <br>마다 않고 꽤나 마셨지만 <br>처음과 끝을 함께 하자던 <br>봄 날의 맹세는 더욱 또렷해 <br>그 곳에는 뭐가 그리 좋길래 <br>서둘러 나를 떠나 간단 말이요 <br>이 곳에는 당신의 노래가 <br>눈물 비로 내리고 있는데 <br>당신 없인 그 아무것도 <br>내게는 의미조차 없는데 <br>내 심장 안에 그대 빈자리 <br>주홍빛 자욱은 더욱 또렷해 <br>그 곳에는 뭐가 그리 좋길래 <br>서둘러 나를 떠나 간단 말이요 <br>이 곳에는 당신의 노래가 <br>눈물 비로 내리고 있는데 <br>그 곳에서 나를 기다려 주오 <br>서둘러 지워 버리시면 안되오 <br>이 곳에서 소풍 끝나는 날 <br>일곱 색 무지개가 될 테요 <br>잘 가시오 <br>내가 존재하는 이유가 돼준 사람 <br>잘 가시오 <br>오직 한 사람 오직 내 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="은정은" label="은정은"/><category term="국화" label="국화"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/은정은/고백해봐요/</id><title>은정은 - 고백해봐요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:22:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:22:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%80%EC%A0%95%EC%9D%80/%EA%B3%A0%EB%B0%B1%ED%95%B4%EB%B4%90%EC%9A%94/" title="은정은 - 고백해봐요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내게 관심있나요 말을 해봐요 <br>왜 자꾸 나만 보시나요 <br>어서어서와 고백을 해버려 <br>이런 기회 오늘 한번뿐 <br>나는 이미 눈치챘어 <br>당신 마음 들켜버렸어 <br>오늘은 그냥 모르는 척 <br>넘어가줄지 몰라 <br>지금 딱이야 고백해봐요 <br>내 여자가 되어 달라고 <br>나를 사랑하나요 말을 해봐요 <br>그렇게 망설이지 말고 <br>예쁜 여자는 기다리지 않아 <br>이런 기회 오늘 한번뿐 <br>나는 이미 눈치챘어 <br>당신 마음 들켜버렸어 <br>오늘은 그냥 모르는 척 <br>넘어가줄지 몰라 <br>지금 딱이야 고백해봐요 <br>내 여자가 되어 달라고 <br>나는 이미 눈치챘어 <br>당신 마음 들켜버렸어 <br>오늘은 그냥 모르는 척 <br>넘어가줄지 몰라 <br>지금 딱이야 고백해봐요 <br>내 여자가 되어 달라고 <br>내가 너를 사랑한다고 <br>]]></content><category term="은정은" label="은정은"/><category term="고백해봐요" label="고백해봐요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/은정은/한번쯤/</id><title>은정은 - 한번쯤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:22:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:22:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%80%EC%A0%95%EC%9D%80/%ED%95%9C%EB%B2%88%EC%AF%A4/" title="은정은 - 한번쯤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한번쯤 한번쯤 한번쯤 한번쯤 <br>누구나 한번쯤 한번쯤 <br>예쁜여자 지나가면 멍때리며 <br>바라보고 <br>마치 내 여자인 것처럼 상상도 하고 <br>누구나 한번쯤 한번쯤 <br>멋진남자 지나가면 슬그머니 <br>바라보고 <br>마치 내 남자인 것처럼 상상도 하고 <br>하지만 그건 나만의 나만의 <br>착각이었어 <br>제정신 차리고 나면 허탈한 것을 <br>그래도 난 또 다시 상상을 하지 <br>언젠가 정말 현실이 될지도 몰라 <br>누구나 한번쯤 한번쯤 될지도 몰라 <br>누구나 한번쯤 한번쯤 될지도 몰라 <br>누구나 한번쯤 <br>한번쯤 한번쯤 한번쯤 한번쯤 <br>누구나 한번쯤 한번쯤 <br>예쁜여자 지나가면 멍때리며 <br>바라보고 <br>마치 내 여자인 것처럼 상상도 하고 <br>누구나 한번쯤 한번쯤 <br>멋진남자 지나가면 슬그머니 <br>바라보고 <br>마치 내 남자인 것처럼 상상도 하고 <br>하지만 그건 나만의 나만의 <br>착각이었어 <br>제정신 차리고 나면 허탈한 것을 <br>그래도 난 또 다시 상상을 하지 <br>언젠가 정말 현실이 될지도 몰라 <br>누구나 한번쯤 한번쯤 될지도 몰라 <br>누구나 한번쯤 한번쯤 될지도 몰라 <br>누구나 한번쯤 <br>]]></content><category term="은정은" label="은정은"/><category term="한번쯤" label="한번쯤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Call_Me/</id><title>NAV - Call Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:23:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:23:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Call_Me/" title="NAV - Call Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro] <br>Metro Boomin want some more, nigga <br><br>[Verse 1] <br>They tell me, "Don't forget where you came from" <br>I regret what I came from <br>In my old hood moving like I got a vest on me <br>I'ma keep on winning, you should place your bets on me <br>I could open up a bakery, baguettes on me <br>Walking through the mall, I got a check on me <br>Designer look the best on me <br>I got lots of pressure, lotsa stress on me <br>Independent, I got people that depend on me <br>Knew you was a fake, you can't pretend on me <br>What I used to spend on you, I spend on me <br>Somehow all these problems keep on landing on me <br>I went on a mission with a bad bitch <br>3AM, I'm getting Backwoods like I'm average <br>All this money turned me to a savage <br>My life was better when I didn't have shit <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Do you know how it feel to feel alone? <br>Bought myself a house, still feel like I ain't home <br>Driving by myself, ain't got nowhere to go <br>I just took two 30s, now I'm in my zone <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>Me and Metro Boomin' want some more, yah <br>All this money made me bored, yah <br>But there's lots of drugs to explore, yah <br>I'm a boss, yeah, I could employ ya <br>Couldn't buy one, now I got four, yah <br>Used to pray feds don't kick down the door, yah <br>Running back the sack the trap feel like a sport, yah <br>Yeah I'm famous but I miss my life before, yah <br>Finally got some money, can't go to the store <br>I lose every girl I love when I'm on tour <br>My mama calling me and I ignore <br>Running from my problems 'til my feet get sore <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Do you know how it feel to feel alone? <br>Bought myself a house, still feel like I ain't home <br>Driving by myself, ain't got nowhere to go <br>I just took two 30s, now I'm in my zone <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br><br>[Verse 3] <br>I got what you need, you feeling lonely? <br>I need, I need you to hold me <br>I hope you mean everything that you told me <br>I'll try to come back to you, girl, I'm sorry <br>If you miss me just call me <br>You try to diss me 'cause you salty <br>Did this on my own, it's all me <br>I just wish that you would call me <br><br>[Outro] <br>Call me <br>I just wish that you would call me up <br>Wish that you would call me <br>I just wish that you would call me up <br>Wish that you would call me <br>I just wish that you would call me up <br>Wish that you would call me <br>I just wish that you would call me up <br>Me up <br>Just wish that you would call me up <br>Me up, me up <br>I just wish that you would call me up <br>(Me up, me up) <br>I just wish that you would call me up <br>Me up]]></content><category term="NAV" label="NAV"/><category term="Call Me" label="Call Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Both_Sides_Feat_21_Savage/</id><title>NAV - Both Sides (Feat. 21 Savage) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:23:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:23:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Both_Sides_Feat_21_Savage/" title="NAV - Both Sides (Feat. 21 Savage) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro: Future] <br>If Young Metro don't trust ya, I'm gon shoot ya <br><br>[Chorus: 21 Savage] <br>Get my Maybach washed at the studio <br>I'm passing out xans to the groupie hoes <br>I got five on a Lamb' like Coolio <br>Multi-millionaire, now I'm hanging with the shooters tho <br>Yeah, bust downs, got a few of those <br>Yeah, bitch stop calling my phone, I'm in the studio <br>Yeah, nigga we ain't doing no Twitter, lil nigga get supersoaked <br>Nigga we ain't playing both sides, lil nigga who you rooting for? <br><br>[Verse 1: NAV] <br>My life is a secret, everything confidential <br>Rollie presidential, working on my mental <br>Ready for the pressure (yeah) 38 special (yeah) <br>Aim it at your temple (yeah), shooters behind me driving in a rental <br>Told his mama, "Sorry for your loss, did you get the flowers that I sent you?" <br>Used to sell my beats for two bills, now you can't even get a sample <br>Mama found the work in a closet <br>I was making shoe box deposits <br>Ain't looking back, change the topic <br>Park a Bentley coupe in the projects <br>Told my ex bitch I'm doing great, yah <br>So much ice, I need some skates, yah <br>Playing two sides, my shooter put three in his face, yah <br>I just spent eleven on my waist, yah <br>I dress like a star, my closet running out of space, yah <br><br>[Chorus: 21 Savage] <br>Get my Maybach washed at the studio <br>I'm passing out xans to the groupie hoes <br>I got five on a Lamb' like Coolio <br>Multi-millionaire, now I'm hanging with the shooters tho <br>Yeah, bust downs, got a few of those <br>Yeah, bitch stop calling my phone, I'm in the studio <br>Yeah, nigga we ain't doing no Twitter, lil nigga get supersoaked <br>Nigga we ain't playing both sides, lil nigga who you rooting for? <br><br>[Verse 2: 21 Savage] <br>Woah, Gucci jacket, inside pocket hold the ratchet <br>OG kush I'm smoking on a potent package <br>Saint Laurent don on me <br>And I got a gun on me <br>Can't no infiltrators come around me <br>Told my son don't suck his thumb around me <br>Issa lotta bloodhounds around me <br>You could get gunned down around me <br>Yeah, all my friends bad guys <br>Search him at the door, he might be wearing a wire <br>In a foreign, drinking syrup, that's a DUI <br>Police ass nigga, you the FBI <br><br>[Chorus: 21 Savage] <br>Get my Maybach washed at the studio <br>I'm passing out xans to the groupie hoes <br>I got five on a Lamb' like Coolio <br>Multi-millionaire, now I'm hanging with the shooters tho <br>Yeah, bust downs, got a few of those <br>Yeah, bitch stop calling my phone, I'm in the studio <br>Yeah, nigga we ain't doing no Twitter, lil nigga get supersoaked <br>Nigga we ain't playing both sides, lil nigga who you rooting for? <br><br>[Outro: 21 Savage] <br>I'm sleeping where the killers at <br>I'm hanging on a fed block <br>Yeah, Glock 40 with a red dot <br>Ten racks for a hard shot]]></content><category term="NAV" label="NAV"/><category term="Both Sides (Feat. 21 Savage)" label="Both Sides (Feat. 21 Savage)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Held_Me_Down/</id><title>NAV - Held Me Down - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:23:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:23:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Held_Me_Down/" title="NAV - Held Me Down - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Metro Boomin want some more, nigga <br><br>I've been running from my problems <br>I've been running from you <br>Girl, all this money, all these things don't feel the same without you <br>I can't trust these others girls, I got a feeling 'bout you <br>Even though I'm doing well, I lose my touch without you <br>I hate to hurt you, cameras showing everything that I do <br>Piece of shit, I got a side bitch and I lie to her too <br>My mama asking 'bout you, and I'm finna lie to her too <br>I blew up and got lost in the sauce, and changed up on you <br><br>But when nobody else was around <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br>Way before I found my sound <br>She kept my feet on the ground <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br><br>I've been living life on the road <br>Feeling lonely, heart is turning cold <br>I be covered up in sold out clothes <br>Feeling empty, doing sold out shows <br>Use the drugs to cover up my emotions (abusing drugs) <br>Every time you see me, I'm either rolling or smoking (I'm rollin' up) <br>Everybody love me now, only you make me feel important <br>When we settle down, everything you buy gon' be imported <br>All of your friends, they told you, "Don't fuck with a artist" <br>When I tell you what my body count is, that gon hit you the hardest <br><br>I've been running from my problems <br>I've been running from you <br>Girl, all this money, all these things don't feel the same without you <br>I can't trust these others girls, I got a feeling 'bout you <br>Even though I'm doing well, I lose my touch without you <br>I hate to hurt you, cameras showing everything that I do <br>Piece of shit, I got a side bitch and I lie to her too <br>My mama asking 'bout you, and I'm finna lie to her too <br>I blew up and got lost in a sauce, and changed up on you <br><br>But when nobody else was around <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br>Way before I found my sound <br>She kept my feet on the ground <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br><br>Whenever they took my music for a joke <br>Whenever I ever had my back against the ropes <br>When I was down nand out with no hope <br>She was always down from the get-go <br>She was always down, stayed ten toes <br>Lost my girl, found a thousand hoes <br>She a good girl, don't work on a pole <br>If I need it, she would stash my pole <br>She paid for all the dinners when I was broke <br>If I needed, she would hide my dope <br>Girl, I know you still wearing my clothes <br>I know you think about me when you're alone <br>I know you think about texting my phone <br>I wish you would give in and just let go <br>I'm happy I found out you was at my show <br>You're more than my girl <br>You're part of my soul <br><br>I've been running from my problems <br>I've been running from you <br>Girl, all this money, all these things don't feel the same without you <br>I can't trust these others girls, I got a feeling 'bout you <br>Even though I'm doing well, I lose my touch without you <br>I hate to hurt you, cameras showing everything that I do <br>Piece of shit, I got a side bitch and I lie to her too <br>My mama asking 'bout you, and I'm finna lie to her too <br><br>I blew up and got lost in a sauce, and changed up on you <br><br>But when nobody else was around <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br>Way before I found my sound <br>She kept my feet on the ground <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down]]></content><category term="NAV" label="NAV"/><category term="Held Me Down" label="Held Me Down"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/AAP_Ferg_Feat_Lil_Uzi_Vert/</id><title>NAV - A$AP Ferg (Feat. Lil Uzi Vert) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:23:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:23:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/AAP_Ferg_Feat_Lil_Uzi_Vert/" title="NAV - A$AP Ferg (Feat. Lil Uzi Vert) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If Young Metro don't trust you, I'm gon' shoot you <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br><br>Tell me what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>I came from the dirt, know I put in work <br>Like I'm A$AP Ferg, like I'm A$AP Ferg <br>Know I put in work <br>Know I put in work <br>Know I put in, yeah <br>Know I put in, yeah <br>Know I put in work <br>Diamonds different colors, so my neck look like Starburst <br>Kicked it one time, with your girlfriend <br>And she fucked me for a purse <br>I could hit that thing forever, when I'm on the perc <br><br>I used to put in work <br>Now my young boys do the dirt (brown boy) <br>Fully automatic, pull up hit you with a burst <br>Put you on a shirt, you a lil' boy, you a smurf <br>She used to put me down, and now she lifting up her skirt <br>Pull up and I swerve, leave her feelings hurt <br>She fucked me for a purse, she fucked me for a XO shirt <br>I see you wearing Off-White, but you know, I bought it first <br>I seen you post a picture, and I had to change my shirt <br>I can't punch him in his face, he gonna sue me now <br>Took your bitch to Nobu, fuck me for some sushi now <br>I hit it once, and now I can't stand her now <br>They pay me fifty thousand, just to stand around <br><br>Yeah, what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>I came from the dirt, know I put in work <br>Like I'm A$AP Ferg, like I'm A$AP Ferg <br>Know I put in work <br>Know I put in work <br>Know I put in, yeah <br>Know I put in, yeah <br>Know I put in work <br>Diamonds different colors, so my neck look like Starburst <br>Kicked it one time, with your girlfriend <br>And she fucked me for a purse <br>I could hit that thing forever, when I'm on the perc <br><br>Heard you got that AP swerve, that was my watch first <br>Heard you got that Lambo', skrt, that was my drive first <br>Chopper beat that bitch to spurs, clip hang to the curb <br>That girl know, I put in work, like I'm A$AP Ferg <br>Your girlfriend say, I'm handsome <br>Fuck any girl, so random <br>Rock any clothes, I'm random <br>I rock that Demna right on my sandal <br>Don't give me the top then cancel <br>My momma said these niggas can't stand you <br>And I'm laughing right to the bank <br>All my chains on like I'm Shabba Ranks <br><br>Tell me what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>I came from the dirt, know I put in work <br>Like I'm A$AP Ferg, like I'm A$AP Ferg <br>Know I put in work <br>Know I put in work <br>Know I put in, yeah <br>Know I put in, yeah <br>Know I put in work <br>Diamonds different colors, so my neck look like Starburst <br>Kicked it one time, with your girlfriend <br>And she fucked me for a purse <br>I could hit that thing forever, when I'm on the perc <br><br>I came up from the dirt, yeah <br>I came up from the dirt, yeah <br>Put in work like A$AP Ferg, yeah <br>You're getting on my nerves, yeah <br>No pancakes, I want syrup, yeah <br>Mix some molly with the percs, yeah <br>Diss me take you off this earth, yeah <br>I came up from the dirt, yeah <br>I came up from the dirt, yeah <br>Came up from the dirt, yeah <br>Came up from the dirt, yeah <br>Put in work like A$AP Ferg, yeah <br>I got Vs on all my shirts, yeah <br>No pancakes, I want syrup, yeah <br>Mix some molly with the percs, yeah <br>Diss me take you off this earth, yeah <br>I came up from the dirt, yeah <br>I came up from the dirt, yeah]]></content><category term="NAV" label="NAV"/><category term="A$AP Ferg (Feat. Lil Uzi Vert)" label="A$AP Ferg (Feat. Lil Uzi Vert)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Hit/</id><title>NAV - Hit - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:23:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:23:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Hit/" title="NAV - Hit - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Southside <br>If Young Metro don't trust you, I'm gon shoot you <br><br>Smoke a lot, got a permanent cough <br>Popping them pills again <br>Used to think you was my dog, now you are not my friend <br>Turn myself into a boss, I was born to win <br>Still know how to handle a loss <br>Me and Metro going in <br>Everything hit <br>All my songs hits <br>All my chains hit <br>I look like a lick <br>Everything hit <br>Diss me, you get hit <br>Southside got the stick <br>Everything hit <br><br>My shooter gave me a promise, said he won't miss <br>I'm rich, I'm just being honest, look at my wrist <br>You ain't shit, you ain't piss <br>20k ain't shit, spent that on my bitch <br>Roll up I smoke by the zip <br>Got gorillas, a jungle with me <br>Snakes and bees on my feet <br>Bought a Range 'cause I don't want a Jeep <br>Fucking your bitch for a week <br>I fuck your bitch right where you sleep <br>Leaving my nut in your sheets <br>Molly turned me into a beast <br>Working four days, no sleep <br><br>Smoke a lot, got a permanent cough <br>Popping them pills again <br>Used to think you was my dog, now you are not my friend <br>Turn myself into a boss, I was born to win <br>Still know how to handle a loss <br>Me and Metro going in <br>Everything hit <br>All my songs hits <br>All my chains hit <br>I look like a lick <br>Everything hit <br>Diss me, you get hit <br>Southside got the stick <br>Everything hit <br><br>Water on my wrist <br>Codeine when I piss <br>Got pills in my shit <br>Don't think I could quit <br>Taking xannies to sleep <br>Wake up and I sip <br>There's a girl in my bed, and I don't know the bitch <br>I'm sipping juice, I make the yellow Fanta orange <br>I was stuck inside my house and now I'm touring <br>I couldn't do it, had to get it, life got boring <br>And now my clothes, my whip, and all my bitches foreign <br><br>Smoke a lot, got a permanent cough <br>Popping them pills again <br>Used to think you was my dog, now you are not my friend <br>Turn myself into a boss, I was born to win <br>Still know how to handle a loss <br>Me and Metro going in <br>Everything hit <br>All my songs hits <br>All my chains hit <br>I look like a lick <br>Everything hit <br>Diss me, you get hit <br>Southside got the stick <br>Everything hit <br><br>I'm sipping juice, I make the yellow Fanta orange <br>I was stuck inside my house and now I'm touring <br>I couldn't do it, had to get it, life got boring <br>And I might close my whip, and all my bitches foreign]]></content><category term="NAV" label="NAV"/><category term="Hit" label="Hit"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/I_Dont_Care/</id><title>NAV - I Don`t Care - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:23:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:23:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/I_Dont_Care/" title="NAV - I Don`t Care - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Metro Boomin' want some more nigga <br><br>Metro Boomin said he got me, yeah <br>All these rappers try to copy, yeah <br>Stick to ice, don't play no hockey, yeah <br>My strap is black and hot like coffee, yeah <br>I'm goin' fast, you can't stop me, yeah <br>Heard your album, break weed on a copy, yeah <br>I used to want her, now she sloppy, yeah <br>Compare 'em to me, they can't top me, yeah <br><br>Yeah, I'ma put the money up for broski's bail, yeah <br>I just spent $200 on my nails, yeah <br>You wasn't there and now I'm outta here, yeah <br>You call my phone, I ignore and I don't care, yeah <br>You say you goin' broke and I don't care <br>Got 10 Gucci shoes, I flex on you and buy another pair <br>When I had no hope you wasn't there <br>So when you ask for help, no I don't care <br><br>You say you can't pay your bills, no I don't care <br>I'ma go and spend your rent on underwear <br>I'm in Saks Fifth, used to shop at Sears <br>I've been poppin' pills and poppin' seals <br>I removed the fakes and shit got real <br>My shooter got tech fleece on <br>He don't train, but he trained to kill <br>Remember when Cash hit me up on the phone, I was broke as hell <br>'Member when I used to wake up, I ain't wanna check the mail <br>I know some bitches whorin' but I won't kiss and tell <br>The same bitches that put Body in a cell <br>All we knew is rob and steal and sell <br>I'm eatin' cajun salmon, used to eat Taco Bell <br><br>Metro Boomin said he got me, yeah <br>All these rappers try to copy, yeah <br>Stick to ice, don't play no hockey, yeah <br>My strap is black and hot like coffee, yeah <br>I'm goin' fast, you can't stop me, yeah <br>Heard your album, break weed on a copy, yeah <br>I used to want her, now she sloppy, yeah <br>Compare 'em to me, they can't top me, yeah <br><br>Yeah, I'ma put the money up for broski's bail, yeah <br>I just spent $200 on my nails, yeah <br>You wasn't there and now I'm outta here, yeah <br>You call my phone, I ignore and I don't care, yeah <br>You say you goin' broke and I don't care <br>Got 10 Gucci shoes, I flex on you and buy another pair <br>When I had no hope you wasn't there <br>So when you ask for help, no I don't care <br><br>You ain't drinkin' real Act, I can tell by the smell <br>Your girl just text me, said she hope I've been doin' well <br>They was cold, but now when they see me all these bitches melt <br>I'm a wizard, my dick game got her under a spell <br>I pop some molly, I just might go and shoot at myself <br>Frost just passed it to me, I put it under my belt <br>Still hide the work behind my hats on top of the shelf <br>Used to hide from my mom smokin' blunts in the back of the house <br>Why would I give you a half? I'll take it myself <br>You be the type to pop pills and go sit on the couch <br>I heard that your man is a rat and your OG's a mouse <br>You think I fucked on your bitch, I just nutted in her mouth <br><br>Metro Boomin said he got me, yeah <br>All these rappers try to copy, yeah <br>Stick to ice, don't play no hockey, yeah <br>My strap is black and hot like coffee, yeah <br>I'm goin' fast, you can't stop me, yeah <br>Heard your album, break weed on a copy, yeah <br>I used to want her, now she sloppy, yeah <br>Compare 'em to me, they can't top me, yeah <br><br>Yeah, I'ma put the money up for broski's bail, yeah <br>I just spent $200 on my nails, yeah <br>You wasn't there and now I'm outta here, yeah <br>You call my phone, I ignore and I don't care, yeah <br>You say you goin' broke and I don't care <br>Got 10 Gucci shoes, I flex on you and buy another pair <br>When I had no hope you wasn't there <br>So when you ask for help, no I don't care]]></content><category term="NAV" label="NAV"/><category term="I Don`t Care" label="I Don`t Care"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Perfect_Timing_Intro/</id><title>NAV - Perfect Timing (Intro) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:23:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:23:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Perfect_Timing_Intro/" title="NAV - Perfect Timing (Intro) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If Young Metro don't trust you, I'm gon' shoot you <br>Metro Boomin want some more, nigga <br><br>Me and Metro don't need help <br>Mail a pint to myself <br>Flew a pornstar to ATL <br>Louis Goyard belt <br>5 star hotels <br>Buy everything on the rack (cash) <br>Buy everything on the shelf (cash) <br>I make you mad, I can tell <br><br>Perfect timing, yeah <br>Watch full of diamonds, yeah (bling) <br>Chart climbing, yeah <br>Foreign car driving, yeah (skrt) <br>Perfect timing, yeah <br>Diamonds shining, yeah <br>Stars aligning, yeah <br>It's perfect timing, yeah <br><br>Double styrofoam cup (lean) <br>Big dog, you a pup <br>Since me and Metro made "Up" <br>All these bitches acting like sluts <br>You're not the type I can trust <br>Feel your energy through your touch <br>Follow feelings in my gut <br>Choppa turn your body into dust <br>She don't wanna listen to you <br>Your girlfriend listening to me <br>She on the phone with you <br>While she sucking on me <br>Off-white and Supreme <br>VLONE Vs, double Gs <br>Molly, liquor, bush, weed <br>These bitches so easy to please <br><br>Me and Metro don't need help <br>Mail a pint to myself <br>Flew a pornstar to ATL <br>Louis Goyard belt <br>5 star hotels <br>Buy everything on the rack (cash) <br>Buy everything on the shelf (cash) <br>I make you mad, I can tell <br><br>Perfect timing, yeah <br>Watch full of diamonds, yeah (bling) <br>Chart climbing, yeah <br>Foreign car driving, yeah (skrt) <br>Perfect timing, yeah <br>Diamonds shining, yeah <br>Stars aligning, yeah <br>It's perfect timing, yeah <br><br>Bust down rollie, flood it with diamonds <br>Can't tell what the time is, still know it's perfect timing <br>See it, want it, then I buy it, yeah <br>Lambo roar like a lion, yeah <br>Private jets is what I'm flying, yeah <br>Watching rap careers dying, yeah <br>Won't come to your wedding 'cause I don't want to wear a suit <br>Walking through the snow, I'm wearing YSL boots <br>9AM I'm off the Addys, still up in the booth <br>These other brown boys corny <br>They love me 'cause I'm the truth <br><br>Me and Metro don't need help <br>Mail a pint to myself <br>Flew a pornstar to ATL <br>Louis Goyard belt <br>5 star hotels <br>Buy everything on the rack (cash) <br>Buy everything on the shelf (cash) <br>I make you mad, I can tell <br><br>Perfect timing, yeah <br>Watch full of diamonds, yeah (bling) <br>Chart climbing, yeah <br>Foreign car driving, yeah (skrt) <br>Perfect timing, yeah <br>Diamonds shining, yeah <br>Stars aligning, yeah <br>It's perfect timing, yeah]]></content><category term="NAV" label="NAV"/><category term="Perfect Timing (Intro)" label="Perfect Timing (Intro)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/장유진/우둔남녀_Feat_김진아_김유태/</id><title>장유진 - 우둔남녀 (Feat. 김진아, 김유태) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:25:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:25:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%EC%9C%A0%EC%A7%84/%EC%9A%B0%EB%91%94%EB%82%A8%EB%85%80_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%84%EC%95%84_%EA%B9%80%EC%9C%A0%ED%83%9C/" title="장유진 - 우둔남녀 (Feat. 김진아, 김유태) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뒤에서만 바라보고 있는 나를 <br>한걸음 다가갈까 <br>망설이고 있는 나를 <br>언제쯤이면 뒤돌아봐 <br>나를 알아봐 줄까 <br>오늘도 오 난 기다린다 <br>멀리서 바라봐 너를 <br>나도 알아 네가 생각하는 나를 <br>들키진 않겠지 <br>넌 한 눈 팔고 있어 <br>넌 첫 만남부터 눈치가 없어 <br>기다리고 있어 <br>우리의 맘이 그림자처럼 <br>말없이 함께 할 수 있기를 <br>오늘도 기다린다 <br>내 하루가 너로 가득 채워지고 <br>조그마한 내 맘에 <br>들어온 너가 벅차서 <br>언제쯤이면 뒤돌아봐 <br>나를 알아봐 줄까 <br>오늘도 오 난 기다린다 <br>멀리서 바라봐 너를 <br>나도 알아 네가 생각하는 나를 <br>들키진 않겠지 넌 한눈팔고 있어 <br>넌 첫 만남부터 눈치가 없어 <br>기다리고 있어 우리의 맘이 <br>그림자처럼 말없이 <br>함께할 수 있기를 <br>오늘도 기다린다 <br>가끔 생각해 <br>혹시 너도 날 바라보고 있는지 <br>나 혼자서만 <br>나 혼자서만 <br>바라보는 게 <br>바라보는 게 <br>점점 힘들어지는데 <br>멀리서 바라봐 너를 <br>나도 알아 네가 생각하는 나를 <br>들키진 않겠지 넌 한눈팔고 있어 <br>넌 첫 만남부터 눈치가 없어 <br>기다리고 있어 <br>우리의 맘이 그림자처럼 <br>말없이 함께 할 수 있기를 <br>오늘도 기다린다 <br>]]></content><category term="장유진" label="장유진"/><category term="우둔남녀 (Feat. 김진아, 김유태)" label="우둔남녀 (Feat. 김진아, 김유태)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/문정원/인천항_차이나타운/</id><title>문정원 - 인천항 차이나타운 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:25:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:25:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B8%EC%A0%95%EC%9B%90/%EC%9D%B8%EC%B2%9C%ED%95%AD_%EC%B0%A8%EC%9D%B4%EB%82%98%ED%83%80%EC%9A%B4/" title="문정원 - 인천항 차이나타운 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[인천항 차이나타운 <br>그 거리에 가고 싶다 <br>만리장성 꿈틀 꿈틀 <br>화려한 꿈을 꾸네 <br>바람에 흔들 흔들 <br>홍등 불빛 빨간 기둥 <br>황금기와 자장면 미스 차이나 <br>미스 차이나 수줍던 첫사랑 <br>기다리네 기다리네 차이나 거리 <br>쭝꿔 짜이요 차이나 타운 <br>항꿔 짜이요 차이나 타운 <br>인천항 차이나 타운 <br>인천항 차이나타운 <br>그 언덕에 가고 싶다 <br>자유공원 바다건너 <br>고향의 꿈을 꾸네 <br>바람에 살랑살랑 <br>홍등 불빛 빨간 기둥 <br>화덕만두 공갈빵 미스 차이나 <br>미스 차이나 허무한 풋사랑 <br>가고 싶네 가고 싶네 차이나 거리 <br>쭝꿔 짜이요 차이나 타운 <br>항꿔 짜이요 차이나 타운 <br>인천항 차이나 타운 <br>기다리네 기다리네 차이나 거리 <br>쭝꿔 짜이요 차이나 타운 <br>항꿔 짜이요 차이나 타운 <br>인천항 차이나 타운 <br>]]></content><category term="문정원" label="문정원"/><category term="인천항 차이나타운" label="인천항 차이나타운"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전소현/Rain/</id><title>전소현 - Rain - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:25:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:25:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%86%8C%ED%98%84/Rain/" title="전소현 - Rain - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Rain 눅눅한 방안에 공기와 <br>Rain 창문 틈 사이 흐르는 냄새와 <br>잿빛 하늘과 젖은 땅 거친 차의 소리 <br>오늘 하루는 비 오는 날 <br>Rain 두 눈을 감으면 들리는 <br>Rain 조금씩 두드리는 빗방울 <br>거친 마음에 점점 다가오는 소리 <br>오늘 하루는 오늘 하루는 <br>비가 내리고 날이 저물고 <br>눈물이 흘러 어느새 밤이야 <br>텅 빈 마음에 흘러 들어와 <br>왜 날 괴롭히는 거니 <br>비가 내리고 날이 저물고 <br>눈물이 흘러 여전히 밤이야 <br>텅 빈 마음에 흘러 들어와 <br>자꾸 들어와 왜 내게 <br>비가 내리고 날이 저물고 <br>눈물이 흘러 어느새 밤이야 <br>텅 빈 마음에 흘러 들어와 <br>왜 날 괴롭히는 거니 <br>비가 내리고 날이 저물고 <br>눈물이 흘러 여전히 밤이야 <br>텅 빈 마음에 흘러 들어와 <br>자꾸 들어와 왜 내게 <br>Rain 두 눈을 감으면 들리는 <br>Rain 비 오는 오늘 밤이 지나네 <br>]]></content><category term="전소현" label="전소현"/><category term="Rain" label="Rain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박지효/Bon_Bon_With_김예린/</id><title>박지효 - Bon Bon (With 김예린) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:29:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:29:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A7%80%ED%9A%A8/Bon_Bon_With_%EA%B9%80%EC%98%88%EB%A6%B0/" title="박지효 - Bon Bon (With 김예린) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[톡 하면 터질 듯 뜨거운 두 볼 <br>너에게 취한 것도 아닌데 난 <br>두근거리는 소리에 들을 까봐 <br>겁나 이 순간 <br>색다른 느낌에 Just wanna chew <br>달콤 쌉싸름한 위스키 향기 <br>바람이 살랑 불어와 <br>내 입술을 스쳐갔죠 <br>Sweet and bitter 봉봉 <br>부드럽게 녹아 들죠 <br>Sweet and bitter 봉봉 <br>따스하게 안아줘요 <br>사랑에 빠진 것 같아 <br>I’m falling in Love <br>I’m falling for you <br>비누방울처럼 반짝이는 눈 <br>나를 바라보고만 있어도 <br>콩닥거리는 느낌에 <br>얼어버릴 것 만 같은데 <br>동그란 그 안에 뭐가 있을까 <br>달콤 쌉싸름한 초콜릿 향기 <br>넌 살금살금 다가와 <br>내 입술에 키스했죠 <br>Sweet and bitter 봉봉 <br>부드럽게 녹아 들죠 <br>Sweet and bitter 봉봉 <br>따스하게 안아줘요 <br>사랑에 빠진 것 같아 <br>I’m falling in Love <br>I’m falling for you <br>Would you love me oh baby <br>내 옆에 있어줄래 모른 척 웃어줄래 <br>Would you love me oh baby <br>나와 약속해줘 우리 둘만의 비밀 <br>Sweet and bitter 봉봉 <br>부드럽게 녹아 들죠 <br>Sweet and bitter 봉봉 <br>따스하게 안아줘요 <br>사랑에 빠진 거 같아 <br>I’m falling in Love <br>I’m falling for you <br>Sweet and bitter 봉봉 <br>부드럽게 녹아 들죠 <br>Sweet and bitter 봉봉 <br>따스하게 안아줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="박지효" label="박지효"/><category term="Bon Bon (With 김예린)" label="Bon Bon (With 김예린)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나비드_NAVID/아자아자_Inst/</id><title>나비드_NAVID - 아자아자 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:29:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:29:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84%EB%93%9C_NAVID/%EC%95%84%EC%9E%90%EC%95%84%EC%9E%90_Inst/" title="나비드_NAVID - 아자아자 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[웃자 크게 소리 내 웃어보자 <br>슬퍼할 여유도 없이 <br>땅만 보고 걷던 날은 잊자 <br>있는 힘껏 달려온 날들 <br>충분히 잘해왔잖아 <br>주저앉지 말자 <br>상쾌한 바람이 기분 좋게 불어와 <br>먼지 낀 커튼을 활짝 열고 <br>다시 힘을 내자 <br>아자 아자 원했던 일이 모두 다 <br>눈앞에 현실로 다가온다 <br>힘들었던 날의 보상이 온다 <br>아자 아자 더 못 견딜 것도 없다 <br>두 눈을 딱 감고 심기일전 <br>누구보다 찬란하게 빛나는 <br>단 한 번뿐인 Sweet My Life <br>잊자 어두운 생각은 떨쳐내 <br>무엇도 원망하지 마 <br>자책하지 말자 <br>갑자기 몰아친 소나기가 걷히면 <br>얼룩진 신발은 깨끗하게 털고 <br>다시 뛰자 <br>아자 아자 원했던 일이 모두 다 <br>눈앞에 현실로 다가온다 <br>힘들었던 날의 보상이 온다 <br>아자 아자 더 못 견딜 것도 없다 <br>두 눈을 딱 감고 심기일전 <br>누구보다 찬란하게 빛나게 <br>어느새 이만큼 멀리 왔어 <br>지난날은 후회하지 않아 <br>시간을 되돌린대도 선택은 같을걸 <br>끝까지 부딪쳐봐 <br>아자 아자 원했던 일이 모두 다 <br>눈앞에 현실로 다가온다 <br>힘들었던 날의 보상이 온다 <br>아자 아자 더 못 견딜 것도 없다 <br>두 눈을 딱 감고 심기일전 <br>누구보다 찬란하게 빛나는 <br>단 한 번뿐인 Sweet My Life <br>]]></content><category term="나비드 (NAVID)" label="나비드 (NAVID)"/><category term="아자아자 (Inst.)" label="아자아자 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나비드_NAVID/아자아자/</id><title>나비드_NAVID - 아자아자 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:29:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:29:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84%EB%93%9C_NAVID/%EC%95%84%EC%9E%90%EC%95%84%EC%9E%90/" title="나비드_NAVID - 아자아자 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[웃자 크게 소리 내 웃어보자 <br>슬퍼할 여유도 없이 <br>땅만 보고 걷던 날은 잊자 <br>있는 힘껏 달려온 날들 <br>충분히 잘해왔잖아 <br>주저앉지 말자 <br>상쾌한 바람이 기분 좋게 불어와 <br>먼지 낀 커튼을 활짝 열고 <br>다시 힘을 내자 <br>아자 아자 원했던 일이 모두 다 <br>눈앞에 현실로 다가온다 <br>힘들었던 날의 보상이 온다 <br>아자 아자 더 못 견딜 것도 없다 <br>두 눈을 딱 감고 심기일전 <br>누구보다 찬란하게 빛나는 <br>단 한 번뿐인 Sweet My Life <br>잊자 어두운 생각은 떨쳐내 <br>무엇도 원망하지 마 <br>자책하지 말자 <br>갑자기 몰아친 소나기가 걷히면 <br>얼룩진 신발은 깨끗하게 털고 <br>다시 뛰자 <br>아자 아자 원했던 일이 모두 다 <br>눈앞에 현실로 다가온다 <br>힘들었던 날의 보상이 온다 <br>아자 아자 더 못 견딜 것도 없다 <br>두 눈을 딱 감고 심기일전 <br>누구보다 찬란하게 빛나게 <br>어느새 이만큼 멀리 왔어 <br>지난날은 후회하지 않아 <br>시간을 되돌린대도 선택은 같을걸 <br>끝까지 부딪쳐봐 <br>아자 아자 원했던 일이 모두 다 <br>눈앞에 현실로 다가온다 <br>힘들었던 날의 보상이 온다 <br>아자 아자 더 못 견딜 것도 없다 <br>두 눈을 딱 감고 심기일전 <br>누구보다 찬란하게 빛나는 <br>단 한 번뿐인 Sweet My Life <br>]]></content><category term="나비드 (NAVID)" label="나비드 (NAVID)"/><category term="아자아자" label="아자아자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/함정/제주봉봉/</id><title>함정 - 제주봉봉 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:29:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:29:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%A8%EC%A0%95/%EC%A0%9C%EC%A3%BC%EB%B4%89%EB%B4%89/" title="함정 - 제주봉봉 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기분이 너무 꿀꿀하고 우울할 때 <br>사랑도 내 맘대로 되지 않을 땐 <br>힘든 일 궂은 일 모두 내려놓고 <br>제주도로 떠나요 Go <br>좋아 좋아 오렌지보다 더 귀여운 <br>한라봉 봉 봉 <br>새콤해 달콤해 <br>색깔도 너무너무 예쁜 <br>망고 쥬스 캬 <br>좋아 좋아 여름엔 고소 달콤 <br>우도 땅콩 아이스크림 음 <br>나는 제주도가 젤 좋아 <br>맛있는 음식 먹으며 쉬고플 때 <br>바다 향 싱싱한 해산물이 넘쳐나고 <br>시원한 바람과 설레임 시작되는 <br>제주도로 떠나요 Go <br>놀멍 쉬멍 시원한 바람 불어 <br>흰둥이도 멍멍멍 <br>좋아 좋아 푸르른 바다 향기 듬뿍 <br>성게 미역국 <br>저녁엔 싱싱한 뿔소라 <br>해삼 멍게 한 접시에 한잔 캬 <br>좋아 좋아 나 혼자서도 좋아 <br>저 연인들이 부럽지만 <br>다음엔 나도 함께라면 음 <br>나는 제주도가 젤 좋아 <br>제주도가 하와이보다 더 좋아 <br>]]></content><category term="함정" label="함정"/><category term="제주봉봉" label="제주봉봉"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최규/우리_이모_손님_Ver/</id><title>최규 - 우리 이모 (손님 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:32:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:32:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EA%B7%9C/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9D%B4%EB%AA%A8_%EC%86%90%EB%8B%98_Ver/" title="최규 - 우리 이모 (손님 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이모의 손맛 정말 치명적이야 <br>오늘도 어김없이 이모 보러 가네요 <br>고단한 하루 일을 훅 끝마치고서 <br>캬 오늘 잘 넘어가네 <br>대짜같은 소짜줘요 <br>오늘 따라 술이 달단 말은 말아요 <br>노가리먹태 친구들이 함께 있잖아 <br>이모의 손맛은 안주킬러 빵야 <br>국물 참 끝내줘요 이모 <br>외상은 안 된다 <br>요즘 세상 살이 지칠 때면 <br>이모가 해준 한마디 <br>당당해라 어깨 펴라 <br>못 먹어도 Go야 <br>이모야 우리 이모 <br>이모 이모 이모 우리 이모 최고야 <br>빨간 불 켜진 삶이지만 <br>이모 때문에 산다 <br>이모야 우리 이모 <br>이모 이모 이모 우리 이모 최고야 <br>파란 불 켜질 미래에는 <br>내가 다 팍팍 쏠게 <br>나로 말하자면 이모 단골 <br>이모만이 나의 진정한 멘토 <br>다른 손님이 껄떡거려도 <br>끄떡없이 날 지켜줄 이모 <br>난 이모의 영원한 포로 <br>절대로 안 해 가게 변경 <br>이모만 따라갈 거야 <br>잔 속에 비친 눈빛 치명적이야 <br>오늘도 어김없이 이모 보러 왔네요 <br>차가운 사랑이 훅 후벼 파고서 <br>캬 오늘 죽여주네요 <br>대짜같은 소짜줘요 <br>오늘 따라 술이 쓰단 말은 말아요 <br>사랑도 인생처럼 흘러가네요 <br>이모의 눈빛은 눈물킬러 빵야 <br>국물 참 끝내줘요 이모 <br>여자친구가 바낐네 <br>요즘 세상 살이 지칠 때면 <br>이모가 해준 한마디 <br>당당해라 어깨 펴라 <br>못 먹어도 Go야 <br>이모야 우리 이모 <br>이모 이모 이모 우리 이모 최고야 <br>빨간 불 켜진 삶이지만 <br>이모 때문에 산다 <br>이모야 우리 이모 <br>이모 이모 이모 우리 이모 최고야 <br>파란 불 켜질 미래에는 <br>내가 다 팍팍 쏠게 <br>이모야 우리 이모 <br>사랑해 나만의 우리 이모 <br>]]></content><category term="최규" label="최규"/><category term="우리 이모 (손님 Ver.)" label="우리 이모 (손님 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최규/우리_이모_주인_Ver/</id><title>최규 - 우리 이모 (주인 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:32:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:32:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EA%B7%9C/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9D%B4%EB%AA%A8_%EC%A3%BC%EC%9D%B8_Ver/" title="최규 - 우리 이모 (주인 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이모의 손맛 정말 치명적이야 <br>오늘도 어김없이 이모 보러 가네요 <br>고단한 하루 일을 훅 끝마치고서 <br>캬 오늘 잘 넘어가네 <br>대짜같은 소짜줘요 <br>오늘 따라 술이 달단 말은 말아요 <br>노가리먹태 친구들이 함께 있잖아 <br>이모의 손맛은 안주킬러 빵야 <br>국물 참 끝내줘요 이모 <br>외상은 안 된다 <br>요즘 세상 살이 지칠 때면 <br>이모가 해준 한마디 <br>당당해라 어깨 펴라 <br>못 먹어도 Go야 <br>이모야 우리 이모 <br>이모 이모 이모 우리 이모 최고야 <br>빨간 불 켜진 삶이지만 <br>이모 때문에 산다 <br>이모야 우리 이모 <br>이모 이모 이모 우리 이모 최고야 <br>파란 불 켜질 미래에는 <br>내가 다 팍팍 쏠게 <br>당당하게 살아라 <br>어깨 쭉 피고 <br>기분이다 이모가 서비스로 <br>주꾸미 주꾸마 <br>이모만 따라갈 거야 <br>잔 속에 비친 눈빛 치명적이야 <br>오늘도 어김없이 이모 보러 왔네요 <br>차가운 사랑이 훅 후벼 파고서 <br>캬 오늘 죽여주네요 <br>대짜같은 소짜줘요 <br>오늘 따라 술이 쓰단 말은 말아요 <br>사랑도 인생처럼 흘러가네요 <br>이모의 눈빛은 눈물킬러 빵야 <br>국물 참 끝내줘요 이모 <br>여자친구가 바낐네 <br>요즘 세상 살이 지칠 때면 <br>이모가 해준 한마디 <br>당당해라 어깨 펴라 <br>못 먹어도 Go야 <br>이모야 우리 이모 <br>이모 이모 이모 우리 이모 최고야 <br>빨간 불 켜진 삶이지만 <br>이모 때문에 산다 <br>이모야 우리 이모 <br>이모 이모 이모 우리 이모 최고야 <br>파란 불 켜질 미래에는 <br>내가 다 팍팍 쏠게 <br>이모야 우리 이모 <br>사랑해 나만의 우리 이모 <br>]]></content><category term="최규" label="최규"/><category term="우리 이모 (주인 Ver.)" label="우리 이모 (주인 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/환희_업텐션/사진_평창의_마스코트_나야나_수호랑_넌_내게_반했어_반다비/</id><title>환희_업텐션 - 사진 (평창의 마스코트 나야나 수호랑, 넌 내게 반했어 반다비) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:33:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:33:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%98%ED%9D%AC_%EC%97%85%ED%85%90%EC%85%98/%EC%82%AC%EC%A7%84_%ED%8F%89%EC%B0%BD%EC%9D%98_%EB%A7%88%EC%8A%A4%EC%BD%94%ED%8A%B8_%EB%82%98%EC%95%BC%EB%82%98_%EC%88%98%ED%98%B8%EB%9E%91_%EB%84%8C_%EB%82%B4%EA%B2%8C_%EB%B0%98%ED%96%88%EC%96%B4_%EB%B0%98%EB%8B%A4%EB%B9%84/" title="환희_업텐션 - 사진 (평창의 마스코트 나야나 수호랑, 넌 내게 반했어 반다비) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너와 내가 담기는 소리 찰칵 <br>둘이 만든 달달한 요리 찰칵 <br>너의 모든 순간을 다 간직하고 싶어 <br>언제나 로맨틱한 남자 주인공처럼 <br>지어봐 나를 위한 표정 <br>잡아봐 나를 향한 포즈 <br>웃어봐 나와 함께 치즈 <br>이 사진첩에 너와 나 우리 둘이 <br>가장 멋지게 예쁘게 담아봐 <br>사랑하며 닮아가는 우리 둘 사이 <br>내 추억 모두 너라서 난 행복해 <br>시간이 지나서 나약해진대도 <br>My love 나처럼 이렇게 웃자 <br>하나 둘씩 커져가는 우리 이야기 <br>일분일초가 정말 아깝지 않아 <br>내 두 눈엔 너만 보여 <br>찍혀진 사진처럼 언제나 웃자 <br>카메라 렌즈를 당겨 널 향하는 줌 <br>카메라 셔터를 눌러 널 채우는 중 <br>어쩜 이리도 예뻐 너의 모든 게 다 <br>언제나 한결 같아 정말 첫 만남처럼 <br>지어봐 나를 위한 표정 <br>잡아봐 나를 향한 포즈 <br>웃어봐 나와 함께 치즈 <br>이 사진첩에 너와 나 우리 둘이 <br>가장 멋지게 담아봐 <br>사랑하며 닮아가는 우리 둘 사이 <br>내 추억 모두 너라서 난 행복해 <br>시간이 지나서 나약해진대도 <br>My love 나처럼 이렇게 웃자 <br>하나 둘씩 커져가는 우리 이야기 <br>일분일초가 정말 아깝지 않아 <br>내 두 눈엔 너만 보여 <br>찍혀진 사진처럼 웃자 <br>아이스크림처럼 부드러운 너의 미소 <br>어떡해 너무 달콤해 <br>내 두 눈에 포커스는 <br>네게 맞춰져 있어 <br>내 두 눈에 포커스는 <br>오직 너뿐이야 <br>누가 봐도 예뻐 보여 우리 둘 사이 <br>내 곁에 너만 있으면 난 행복해 <br>시간이 지나도 너만 사랑할게 <br>My love 평생을 이렇게 웃자 <br>한 장 두 장 쌓여가는 우리 이야기 <br>설레는 내 맘 정말 감출 수 없어 <br>내 두 눈엔 너만 보여 <br>사진 속 우리처럼 <br>언제나 웃자 <br>]]></content><category term="환희 (업텐션)" label="환희 (업텐션)"/><category term="사진 (평창의 마스코트 나야나 수호랑, 넌 내게 반했어 반다비)" label="사진 (평창의 마스코트 나야나 수호랑, 넌 내게 반했어 반다비)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이소은/좋은_사람_과즙미_뿜뿜_과일빙수_태양을_피하고_싶어_파라솔/</id><title>이소은 - 좋은 사람 (과즙미 뿜뿜 과일빙수, 태양을 피하고 싶어 파라솔) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:33:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:33:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%80/%EC%A2%8B%EC%9D%80_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C_%EA%B3%BC%EC%A6%99%EB%AF%B8_%EB%BF%9C%EB%BF%9C_%EA%B3%BC%EC%9D%BC%EB%B9%99%EC%88%98_%ED%83%9C%EC%96%91%EC%9D%84_%ED%94%BC%ED%95%98%EA%B3%A0_%EC%8B%B6%EC%96%B4_%ED%8C%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%86%94/" title="이소은 - 좋은 사람 (과즙미 뿜뿜 과일빙수, 태양을 피하고 싶어 파라솔) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘은 무슨 일인 거니 <br>울었던 얼굴 같은걸 <br>그가 너의 마음을 아프게 했니 <br>나에겐 세상 제일 소중한 너인데 <br>자판기 커피를 내밀어 <br>그 속에 감춰온 내 맘을 담아 <br>고마워 오빤 너무 좋은 사람이야 <br>그 한마디에 난 웃을 뿐 <br>혹시 넌 기억하고 있을까 <br>내 친구 학교 앞에 놀러 왔던 날 <br>우리들 연인 같다 장난쳤을 때 <br>넌 웃었고 난 밤 지새웠지 <br>네가 웃으면 나도 좋아 <br>넌 장난이라 해도 <br>널 기다렸던 날 널 보고 싶던 밤 <br>내겐 벅찬 행복 가득한데 <br>나는 혼자여도 괜찮아 <br>널 볼 수만 있다면 <br>늘 너의 뒤에서 늘 널 바라보는 <br>그게 내가 가진 몫인 것만 같아 <br>친구들 지겹다 말하지 <br>늘 같은 노랠 부르는 나에게 <br>하지만 그게 바로 내 마음인걸 <br>그대 먼 곳만 보네요 <br>혹시 넌 그날 내 맘을 알까 <br>우리를 아는 친구 모두 모인 밤 <br>술 취한 널 데리러 온 그를 내게 <br>인사시켰던 나의 생일 날 <br>네가 좋으면 나도 좋아 <br>네 옆에 그를 보며 <br>나완 너무 다른 난 초라해지는 <br>그에게 널 부탁한다는 말 밖에 <br>널 울리는 사람과 <br>위로 밖에 못하는 나 <br>네가 웃으면 나도 좋아 <br>넌 장난이라 해도 <br>널 기다렸던 날 널 보고 싶던 밤 <br>내겐 벅찬 행복 가득한데 <br>나는 혼자여도 괜찮아 <br>널 볼 수만 있다면 <br>늘 너의 뒤에서 늘 널 바라보는 <br>그게 내가 가진 몫인 것만 같아 <br>]]></content><category term="이소은" label="이소은"/><category term="좋은 사람 (과즙미 뿜뿜 과일빙수, 태양을 피하고 싶어 파라솔)" label="좋은 사람 (과즙미 뿜뿜 과일빙수, 태양을 피하고 싶어 파라솔)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/톰톰/고맙다는_말보다는/</id><title>톰톰 - 고맙다는 말보다는 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:35:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:35:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%86%B0%ED%86%B0/%EA%B3%A0%EB%A7%99%EB%8B%A4%EB%8A%94_%EB%A7%90%EB%B3%B4%EB%8B%A4%EB%8A%94/" title="톰톰 - 고맙다는 말보다는 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언제나 똑같은 말만 <br>되풀이하는 당신 <br>모르는 건 아닐 텐데 <br>내가 무슨 말을 듣고 싶은지 <br>얄밉게 웃지 말아요 <br>아무것도 할 수 없이 <br>두 손이 묶인 나에게 <br>그 미소는 너무 치사하잖아 <br>내 손에 들린 패는 <br>이미 들켜 버린 지 오래됐고 <br>당신은 맞은 편에 앉아서 <br>날 가만히 쳐다보네 <br>숨길 수 없는 걸 숨기려 드니 <br>잘 될 리가 없겠지 <br>이젠 그만 내가 원하는 걸 <br>언제나 똑같은 말만 <br>되풀이하는 당신 <br>좋아해 줘서 고마워 <br>넌 나의 가장 소중한 친구야 <br>내 손에 들린 패는 <br>이미 들켜 버린 지 오래됐고 <br>당신은 맞은 편에 앉아서 <br>술만 홀짝대고 있네 <br>난 고맙단 말보단 <br>사랑한다는 말을 원해 <br>이런 제길 너무 비참한 걸 <br>언제나 똑같은 말만 <br>되풀이하는 당신 <br>고맙다 말할 거라면 <br>차라리 욕이라도 한 번 해줘요 <br>고맙다 말하지 말고 <br>고맙다는 말보다는 <br>사랑한다는 말을 내게 해줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="톰톰" label="톰톰"/><category term="고맙다는 말보다는" label="고맙다는 말보다는"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thanksgiving_band/주_예수_내_맘에_들어와_계신_후_Vocal_Ver/</id><title>Thanksgiving_band - 주 예수 내 맘에 들어와 계신 후 (Vocal Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:35:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:35:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thanksgiving_band/%EC%A3%BC_%EC%98%88%EC%88%98_%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%98%EC%97%90_%EB%93%A4%EC%96%B4%EC%99%80_%EA%B3%84%EC%8B%A0_%ED%9B%84_Vocal_Ver/" title="Thanksgiving_band - 주 예수 내 맘에 들어와 계신 후 (Vocal Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주 예수 내 맘에 들어와 계신 후 <br>변하여 새 사람 되고 <br>내가 늘 바라던 참 빛을 찾음도 <br>주 예수 내 맘에 오심 <br>주 예수 내 맘에 오심 <br>주 예수 내 맘에 오심 <br>물밀듯 내 맘에 기쁨이 넘침은 <br>주 예수 내 맘에 오심 <br>주 예수 내 맘에 오심 <br>주 예수 내 맘에 오심 <br>물밀듯 내 맘에 기쁨이 넘침은 <br>주 예수 내 맘에 오심 <br>주 예수 내 맘에 오심 <br>주 예수 내 맘에 오심 <br>물밀듯 내 맘에 기쁨이 넘침은 <br>주 예수 내 맘에 오심 <br>]]></content><category term="Thanksgiving band" label="Thanksgiving band"/><category term="주 예수 내 맘에 들어와 계신 후 (Vocal Ver.)" label="주 예수 내 맘에 들어와 계신 후 (Vocal Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/빈센트앤_로즈/Oh_Oh_Oh/</id><title>빈센트앤_로즈 - Oh Oh Oh - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:37:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:37:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%88%EC%84%BC%ED%8A%B8%EC%95%A4_%EB%A1%9C%EC%A6%88/Oh_Oh_Oh/" title="빈센트앤_로즈 - Oh Oh Oh - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh <br>아무렇게나 구겨신은 <br>신발에 기대 <br>노을 질 무렵 돌담길에서 <br>난 널 기다렸는데 <br>어지럽혀진 서랍 속을 <br>정리하다가 <br>노을 질 무렵 네가 준 편지에 <br>미소가 번지네 <br>오 이런 내가 <br>얼마나 기다렸는지 <br>오 이런 내가 <br>얼마나 널 기다린지 <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>I'm missing you <br>아름다운 커피같은 그대 모습 <br>I am sing of you <br>아름다운 커튼같은 너의 모습 <br>Oh you don't have to why <br>늘 그 자리에서 <br>날 기다리면 돼 oh baby <br>Oh you don't have to why <br>그냥 그 자리에서 <br>날 받아주면 돼 oh baby <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh <br>아무렇게나 걸쳐입은 <br>재킷에 기대 <br>노을 질 무렵 돌담길에서 <br>난 널 기다렸는데 <br>어지럽혀진 서랍 속을 <br>정리하다가 <br>노을 질 무렵 <br>네가 준 편지에 미소가 번지네 <br>오 이런 내가 <br>얼마나 기다렸는지 <br>오 이런 내가 <br>얼마나 널 기다린지 <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>I'm missing you <br>아름다운 커피같은 그대 모습 <br>I am sing of you <br>아름다운 커튼같은 너의 모습 <br>생각의 터널 끝에서 <br>미소 짓는 네가 서 있어 <br>오랜만이야 그치 <br>가끔은 너도 내 미소를 <br>떠올려 주었다면 <br>그걸로 됐어 Alright <br>I'm missing you <br>아름다운 커피같은 그대 모습 <br>I am sing of you <br>아름다운 커튼같은 너의 모습 <br>Oh you don't have to why <br>늘 그 자리에서 <br>날 기다리면 돼 oh baby <br>Oh you don't have to why <br>그냥 그 자리에서 <br>날 받아주면 돼 oh <br>]]></content><category term="빈센트앤 로즈" label="빈센트앤 로즈"/><category term="Oh Oh Oh" label="Oh Oh Oh"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/빈센트앤_로즈/안전벨트/</id><title>빈센트앤_로즈 - 안전벨트 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:37:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:37:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%88%EC%84%BC%ED%8A%B8%EC%95%A4_%EB%A1%9C%EC%A6%88/%EC%95%88%EC%A0%84%EB%B2%A8%ED%8A%B8/" title="빈센트앤_로즈 - 안전벨트 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아저씨 조금만 더 <br>빨리 달려주시죠 <br>그녀 맘이 날 더 <br>단단히 붙잡을 수 있게 <br>아저씨 신호는 살짝 무시해주시죠 <br>그녀의 가쁜 호흡 조차 <br>날 느낄 수 있게 <br>난 너의 안전벨트 <br>너의 푹 파인 Gossip에 날 묻고 <br>널 느끼는 Emotion <br>난 너의 안전벨트 <br>가끔 흔들릴 때면 어쩔 줄 몰라 <br>난 큰 바위 Motion <br>Fasten your seat belt Hoo- <br>Fasten your seat belt Hah- <br>Fasten your seat belt Hoo- <br>Fasten your seat belt <br>God bless you girl Uah <br>아저씨 조금만 더 <br>빨리 달려주시죠 <br>그녀 맘이 날 더 <br>단단히 붙잡을 수 있게 <br>아저씨 신호는 살짝 무시해주시죠 <br>그녀의 가쁜 호흡 조차 <br>날 느낄 수 있게 <br>Beautiful day Beautiful lady <br>Beautiful day Beautiful lady <br>Fasten your seat belt Hoo- <br>Fasten your seat belt Hah- <br>Fasten your seat belt Hoo- <br>Fasten your seat belt <br>God bless you girl Uah <br>난 너의 안전벨트 <br>너의 푹 파인 Gossip에 날 묻고 <br>널 느끼는 Emotion <br>난 너의 안전벨트 <br>가끔 흔들릴 때면 어쩔 줄 몰라 <br>난 큰 바위 Motion <br>]]></content><category term="빈센트앤 로즈" label="빈센트앤 로즈"/><category term="안전벨트" label="안전벨트"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_데이데이/올라야해_All_Day_Every_Day/</id><title>Dayday_데이데이 - 올라야해 (All Day Every Day) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:37:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:37:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4/%EC%98%AC%EB%9D%BC%EC%95%BC%ED%95%B4_All_Day_Every_Day/" title="Dayday_데이데이 - 올라야해 (All Day Every Day) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All Day Every Day <br>Ain’t no time to waste <br>Every second every minute <br>Don’t you let it fade <br>한 번 살 인생 계속 올라야해 <br>올라 올라야해 올라 올라야해 <br>Oh Oh 올라 올라야해 <br>Oh Oh 올라 올라야해 <br>All Day Every Day <br>Ain’t no time to waste <br>Every second every minute <br>Don’t you let it fade <br>Nineteen eighty three <br>장가가긴 아마 그른 아재 돼지띠 <br>Cuz I’m livin life <br>like I’m forever twenty three <br>MIC를 잡을 때 <br>다 졸던 놈들 Look at me <br>I'm high fivin 하나님 <br>로꼬처럼 난 늘 기분이 너무 높아 <br>내가 나이 먹어도 <br>목표는 영원히 오빠 <br>내 daily routine <br>작업실 gym 작업실 집 <br>작업 다 끝나면 club에 가도 <br>이젠 몸이 귀찮아 못해 작업질 <br>누가 하늘까지가 한계라 했어 <br>난 몸 좀 풀 겸 <br>우주 한 바퀴가 유산소 <br>기존 애들보다 앞서간 <br>내 끝판왕 flow <br>발전 없으면 발사 준비할게 <br>발정 난 이 중지로 <br>All Day Every Day <br>Ain’t no time to waste <br>Every second every minute <br>Don’t you let it fade <br>한 번 살 인생 계속 올라야해 <br>올라 올라야해 올라 올라야해 <br>Oh Oh 올라 올라야해 <br>Oh Oh 올라 올라야해 <br>All Day Every Day <br>Ain’t no time to waste <br>Every second every minute <br>Don’t you let it fade <br>Twenty four seven <br>Three six five <br>I’m above and beyond <br>bullshit just positive vibes <br>Still rap 먹이사슬의 꼭대기 <br>서른다섯에 첫 EP라니 <br>Yesterday든 내일은 안보기 <br>걍 Dayday는 매일 <br>like 하루살이 yolo <br>I said put some respect <br>on my 이름 uh oh <br>이젠 개나 소나 다 <br>데이데이라고 지음 no no <br>허나 절대로 빨리진 않아 내 기는 <br>앞만 보며 나의 갈 길은 없어 <br>No 꽃 No 지름 <br>Shout out to AOMG <br>Team Loco Jay Park <br>and GRAY Simon D <br>Holmes crew Dalmatian too <br>I got love for all of yall till I d i e <br>늘 향했던 정상 계속 올라가야 해 <br>For my fam for my friends <br>올라 올라야해 <br>All Day Every Day <br>Ain’t no time to waste <br>Every second every minute <br>Don’t you let it fade <br>한 번 살 인생 계속 올라야해 <br>올라 올라야해 올라 올라야해 <br>Oh Oh 올라 올라야해 <br>Oh Oh 올라 올라야해 <br>All Day Every Day <br>Ain’t no time to waste <br>Every second every minute <br>Don’t you let it fade <br>]]></content><category term="Dayday (데이데이)" label="Dayday (데이데이)"/><category term="올라야해 (All Day Every Day)" label="올라야해 (All Day Every Day)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_데이데이/돼지_저금통_remix_Feat_Hash_Swan_Shupie_Silly_Boot_Y1ee/</id><title>Dayday_데이데이 - 돼지 저금통 remix (Feat. Hash Swan, Shupie, Silly Boot, Y1ee) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:37:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:37:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4/%EB%8F%BC%EC%A7%80_%EC%A0%80%EA%B8%88%ED%86%B5_remix_Feat_Hash_Swan_Shupie_Silly_Boot_Y1ee/" title="Dayday_데이데이 - 돼지 저금통 remix (Feat. Hash Swan, Shupie, Silly Boot, Y1ee) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All Day Every Day <br>얼굴 좋아 보이지 <br>You know it’s my Dayday <br>똥국장이 통편집해도 <br>내 이름은 명곡이 됐네 <br>Oh yea hell yea <br>꼰대가리’s hate <br>when we gettin paid <br>내 앞길을 막아 봐도 <br>bulldozer로 박아 <br>Imma keep hustlin’ <br>이제 더 이상 누구 <br>그림자 뒤에서 <br>시다바리질은 안 해 <br>다시 밑바닥에 <br>나와 띠동갑들과 rookie <br>자세 restarted <br>Imma old boy with that young <br>감 멈추지가 않아 rap 성장 <br>내 나이만큼 늘어나는 실력은 <br>부정할 수 없어 <br>베테랑들도 공감 <br>오로지 good energy <br>시간은 금이라지 <br>열심히 일하면 <br>좋은 날 오니까 <br>금요일이라 하지 <br>And I be on my grinding mode <br>절대 금수저는 아니어도 <br>내 왼팔에 달린 건 <br>마이다스 손 게다가 <br>중지는 diamond <br>생각해보니까 <br>돼지저금통을 <br>꽉 채워본 적이 없는 것 같아 <br>어릴 적이니까 <br>그럴 수도 있다고 생각해 <br>근데 벌써 twenty five <br>돈 없는 통장 <br>근육 없는 몸처럼 힘이 없네 <br>If you know how I feel <br>You deserve to listen to my EP <br>Seoul city There is no hippy <br>나는 new hippy라고 <br>팔에 새긴 다음부터 <br>더 빡세게 살았던 것 같아 제길 <br>서른 살엔 순례 여행 떠날 거니까 <br>그땐 아무도 말리지 마라 <br>여든 살엔 풀업을 <br>삼십 번 하는 할아버지가 될 거야 <br>머슬매니아의 상을 탈 거야 <br>자식들아 말리지 마라 <br>나는 원숭이 잔나비띠 끼가 많네 <br>또 난 AB형 또라이가 맞네 <br>쿨하지 않아서 질척거리지만 <br>굴하지 않아 비바람에 <br>수다를 떨다가 비관하는 너에 비해 <br>조용한 나는 한 시간 안에 <br>이 가사를 다 쓰고 <br>녹음을 끝마치잖아 <br>Yeah right Silly Boot MZN <br>We work hard play hard <br>This rap game is a day job <br>넌 꿈꾸고 있을 때 <br>난 큰 Dream Chaser <br>스물네 시간 삼백육십오 <br>스물두 살이던 Thirty four <br>절실하면 절대 안될 건 없지 <br>Yo Get that 돼지 저금통 <br>돼지 저금통 <br>돼지 저금통 <br>Get that 돼지 저금통 <br>돼지 저금통 <br>Get that 돼지 저금 <br>사람들이 나의 스물둘에 반응해 <br>왜냐면 난 말보다 <br>행동이 더 빠르네 <br>싸가지가 없어도 <br>너무 없던 그 형들은 <br>요즘 들어 내게 <br>웬일로 예의가 바르네 <br>Oh Oh 근데 아직 멀었어 성공 <br>난 가야 해 홍콩 <br>그러려면 벗어야겠지 <br>내 뇌에 씌워진 만족이란 <br>두꺼운 콘돔 Yeah <br>그게 내 야망 근데 <br>야망에 비해 성공이 빨라 <br>내가 갖고 싶은 모든걸 <br>겨우 스물둘의 버킷리스트에 <br>다 눌러 담아 <br>난 귀찮아 이제 <br>너희 새까만 속에 <br>본능적인 거부감만 <br>왜냐면 내 10만원하는 <br>지갑엔 몇백만원어치 <br>명함이 너무 많아 <br>그런 내 옆엔 Dayday IMAC <br>그 저금통에 내가 <br>저금해 둔 텍스트들로 <br>새로 산 이불은 네이비 색 <br>Yeah 내 돼지 저금통은 <br>오늘도 버는 중이야 <br>여러 문장들을 <br>돼지 저금통의 배를 가르기 전까진 <br>뭐가 있을지는 모르지만 <br>keep just cut it <br>원하는 게 있음 뺏어와야 된단 말에 <br>어느 정도 동의하니까는 <br>keep just cut it <br>싸가지 없이 보이긴 해도 <br>난 내 형제들을 위해 살아 <br>문제들은 <br>keep just cut it <br>If you have to be our enemy <br>니 바지 벗길 거야 <br>and your lil dick <br>keep just cut it <br>데이는 내 친구 <br>또 난 얘의 친구 <br>한강에서 칠린하고 나온 우리 싱글 <br>누구의 실수 덕에 <br>홍보는 좀 막혔어도 <br>이 곡은 틀림없는 <br>턴업곡의 진수 <br>Don't worry bruh <br>We've got a lot of time <br>Always keep it real 우린 쩔어 <br>언젠가 개 잘될 거니깐 밀고 나가 <br>push it <br>실력 없는 fresh는 구려 상한 스시 <br>Let's make some money <br>Let's make some noise <br>아홉 시 뉴스 인터뷰가 나의 목표 <br>약 빨지 않으셨냔 말에 답은 no no <br>앨범이나 홍보해달라고 <br>새끼야 얼른 <br>이름이 뭐냔 말에 <br>나는 호기롭게 말해 <br>그냥 편하게 불러 슈형 <br>마지막으로 남기실 말에 답은 <br>그냥 솔직하게 말해 너희는 구려 <br>We work hard play hard <br>This rap game is a day job <br>넌 꿈꾸고 있을 때 <br>난 큰 Dream Chaser <br>스물네 시간 삼백육십오 <br>스물두 살이던 Thirty four <br>절실하면 절대 안될 건 없지 <br>Yo Get that 돼지 저금통 <br>돼지 저금통 <br>돼지 저금통 <br>Get that 돼지 저금통 <br>돼지 저금통 <br>Get that 돼지 저금 <br>Get that mula get that doe <br>Get that paper get that 돈 <br>배고파요 Ain't no diet for my <br>돼지 저금통 <br>우린 순서를 기다리지 <br>분명 된 거 같아 때가 <br>지금 깨고 싶진 않아 <br>왠지 될 거 같아 내가 <br>Get that mula get that doe <br>Get that paper get that 돈 <br>배고파요 Ain't no diet for my <br>돼지 저금통 <br>벌써 또 우린 하나를 하지 <br>알다가도 몰라 <br>배불러 누워서 High five with 하나님 <br>work hard play hard <br>rap game is a day job <br>꿈꾸고 있을 때 <br>큰 Dream Chaser <br>스물네 시간 삼백육십오 <br>스물두 살이던 Thirty four <br>절실하면 절대 안될 건 없지 <br>Yo Let’s get 돼지 저금통 <br>돼지 저금통 <br>돼지 저금통 <br>Get that 돼지 저금통 <br>돼지 저금통 <br>Get that 돼지 저금 <br>]]></content><category term="Dayday (데이데이)" label="Dayday (데이데이)"/><category term="돼지 저금통 remix (Feat. Hash Swan, Shupie, Silly Boot, Y1ee)" label="돼지 저금통 remix (Feat. Hash Swan, Shupie, Silly Boot, Y1ee)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_데이데이/No_Tomorrow_Feat_릴보이_of_긱스/</id><title>Dayday_데이데이 - No Tomorrow (Feat. 릴보이 of 긱스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:37:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:37:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4/No_Tomorrow_Feat_%EB%A6%B4%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4_of_%EA%B8%B1%EC%8A%A4/" title="Dayday_데이데이 - No Tomorrow (Feat. 릴보이 of 긱스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언젠간 오겠지 또 웃을 날이 <br>엄마가 기도해주실 때 꼭 눈물 나지 <br>Jay-z보단 Problem 수천 수만 가지 <br>Man I'm just workin <br>through this life <br>번창할 때까지 <br>어릴 적부터 꿈꿨어 <br>어릴 적부터 꿈꿨어 <br>남들이 바라볼 role model <br>겸 효도하는 것뿐이었어 <br>Chasin paper gotta make <br>doe like bakers <br>어리석거나 어김없이 난 <br>떳떳하게 배웠어 <br>포기라는 단어 내게는 <br>어울리지가 않아 <br>자존심은 조금 버렸어도 난 <br>영혼 안 팔아 <br>그래 난 끝도 보고 바로 <br>극복하고 바로 금방 일어섰지 <br>날 긁고 깎아내려 해봐도 <br>내게는 nothing <br>매일 매일 매일 적었었던 rhymes <br>좀 기발하던 내 punchlines <br>Dedication motivation <br>overcame tribulations <br>in my worst times <br>Writer's block <br>한 바퀴만 돌아보다가 다시 떠올라 난 <br>only only positive vibes <br>One day <br>Imma make it to the clouds and <br>One day <br>I'm gonna make my momma proud yea <br>Someday <br>I'll look back at this right now <br>But until then till then <br>Imma live like No Tomorrow <br>No No Tomorrow <br>No No Tomorrow <br>No No Tomorrow Tomorrow Tomorrow <br>I think that we'll be better tomorrow <br>I think that we'll be better tomorrow <br>There will be a better tomorrow <br>Now everything gone yea <br>No Tomorrow 넌 아무것도 <br>할 수 없다고 <br>내게 말하던 때가 있었지 <br>Like no tomorrow <br>그래 우린 어떨지 몰라 <br>내일이 But maybe <br>I feel <br>We can make it happen <br>yeah we can make it happen <br>아무 말도 하지 않았지 <br>그래도 넌 옆에 앉아있지 <br>우린 나이가 먹어도 prolly <br>똑같을 거야 너도 알듯이 <br>내일이 온대도 fuck apocalypse <br>우린 술을 먹고 과속하지 <br>Like we don't care bout rules boi <br>we don't care bout rules boi <br>아무것도 보이지 않았던 오늘이 지나 <br>매일이 좋기만 바라는 나의 욕심이 <br>과할지도 모르겠지만 너도 알잖아 <br>That's what we die for <br>마법이 혹 일어날 수도 <br>fuck that 공수래공수거 <br>우린 두 손 활짝 펴고 웃으며 <br>대답하지 Live like no tomorrow <br>옆 좌석엔 민식이 <br>뒤를 돌아보면 상운이 형 <br>우린 열심히 살아 no business here <br>너희는 상상도 못 해 What a family <br>사실은 명확히 보여 내일이 <br>하지만 만족할 일 없으니 <br>다시 떠올라 there's only <br>positive vibes <br>But you motherfucker <br>그저 그런 음악을 하는 애들 잘 들어 <br>너희들에게는 No Tomorrow <br>랩만 잘함 뭐해 정작 음악엔 관심 없지 <br>내가 볼 때 너흰 절대 못해 only one <br>Better keep that attitude <br>따라 하기만 바쁜 애들 <br>모아 놓고 Dayday 형과 <br>구경하러 갈 테니 준비해둬라 <br>Tommorow <br>One day <br>Imma make it to the clouds and <br>One day <br>I'm gonna make my momma proud yea <br>Someday <br>I'll look back at this right now <br>But until then till then <br>Imma live like No Tomorrow <br>No No Tomorrow <br>No No Tomorrow <br>No No Tomorrow Tomorrow Tomorrow <br>I think we'll have a better tomorrow <br>Think there'll be a better tomorrow yea <br>I think we'll have a better tomorrow <br>]]></content><category term="Dayday (데이데이)" label="Dayday (데이데이)"/><category term="No Tomorrow (Feat. 릴보이 of 긱스)" label="No Tomorrow (Feat. 릴보이 of 긱스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_데이데이/나를_불러_Feat_GRAY_박재범/</id><title>Dayday_데이데이 - 나를 불러 (Feat. GRAY, 박재범) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:37:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:37:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4/%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EB%B6%88%EB%9F%AC_Feat_GRAY_%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/" title="Dayday_데이데이 - 나를 불러 (Feat. GRAY, 박재범) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[외롭게 집에 혼자 있을 때 <br>그날따라 연락할 사람들이 없을 때도 <br>그땐 나를 불러 불러 불러 <br>그땐 나를 불러 불러 불러 <br>그땐 나를 불러 불러 불러도 돼 <br>Hey girl 지금 뭐 해 집에 있지마 <br>아직 이불 밖엔 안전해 이 시간 <br>너도 solo이니까 <br>party에 빠지면 안 되지 <br>What Just like 찌찌범 <br>Ay 챙길 건 그 몸매뿐 <br>dress code <br>자유니까 와도 돼 대충 <br>오늘은 너의 날이야 너의 날이야 <br>다시 떠오를 거야 <br>It's your Dayday-javu <br>You’re so bad and 부지런해 <br>한 주 너무 열심히 보냈으니 <br>한잔 일단 적시러 가자 <br>혼자 있기엔 너무 아깝잖아 <br>holla at me <br>Livin good feel hella great <br>오늘 밤 Celeb처럼 Celebrate <br>바쁘다던 친구들 부럽게 <br>ceremony에 훅 빠져 <br>Tell em GRAY <br>외롭게 집에 혼자 있을 때 <br>그날따라 연락할 사람들이 없을 때도 <br>그땐 나를 불러 불러 불러 <br>그땐 나를 불러 불러 불러 <br>그땐 나를 불러 불러 불러도 돼 <br>I'll be your personal hotline <br>다 털어봐 what's on your mind <br>No I ain’t a baller <br>허나 공들일 준비가 됐으니까 <br>널 모셔 VI보단 MVP로 <br>다 냅두고 와 너의 스트레스와 피로 <br>또 간 볼 필요 없이 흑기사는 기본 <br>그때 되면 날 불러 대신 같이 불 질러 <br>그때 나를 불러 <br>새벽쯤이면 I'm up in the club <br>그래도 달려갈게 어디든지 <br>Ready for love <br>So hit me on my line <br>hit me on my line <br>내 핸드폰이 빛이 나 <br>계속 빛이 나도 <br>네 메세지만 확인하지 <br>바쁘더라도 오늘 밤이 <br>우리의 날이 될 수 있게끔 <br>난 시간을 비워놓지 <br>느낌이 바로 오지 <br>For you the one and only <br>알코올이 나를 돕지 <br>yeah yeah yeah <br>I'm feelin good feelin hella great <br>Always on my grind <br>I do this shh like everyday <br>I'm your Big Sean you Jhene Aiko <br>우린 날라가는 새처럼 <br>언제나 자유로워 <br>외롭게 집에 혼자 있을 때 <br>그날따라 연락할 사람들이 없을 때도 <br>그땐 나를 불러 불러 불러 <br>그땐 나를 불러 불러 불러 <br>그땐 나를 불러 불러 불러도 돼 <br>내 별그램 아이디처럼 call me <br>전화해서 나를 불러 <br>when you want me <br>When you need me <br>whenever you call me <br>I'll be there oh <br>더 고민하지 마 망설일 것도 <br>없으니까 맡겨봐 네 몸과 마음도 <br>아름다운 밤은 너를 닮아가지고 <br>다음 날이 오지 않길 바라 빨리 불러 <br>외롭게 집에 혼자 있을 때 <br>그날따라 연락할 사람들이 없을 때도 <br>그땐 나를 불러 불러 불러 <br>그땐 나를 불러 불러 불러 <br>그땐 나를 불러 불러 불러도 돼 <br>Yo 아무 때나 불러도 돼 <br>걍 아무 때나 불러도 돼 <br>Cuz tonight we gon celebrate <br>I said 아무 때나 불러도 돼 <br>Call me any time or day <br>아무 때나 불러줘 Bae <br>]]></content><category term="Dayday (데이데이)" label="Dayday (데이데이)"/><category term="나를 불러 (Feat. GRAY, 박재범)" label="나를 불러 (Feat. GRAY, 박재범)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_데이데이/Better_Days_Feat_G2_ELO_DJ_Wegun/</id><title>Dayday_데이데이 - Better Days (Feat. G2, ELO, DJ Wegun) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:38:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:38:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4/Better_Days_Feat_G2_ELO_DJ_Wegun/" title="Dayday_데이데이 - Better Days (Feat. G2, ELO, DJ Wegun) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 목적지는 어딜까 <br>Is it the number 1 spot <br>욕심 아님 결심일까 <br>힙합은 밥벌이보단 나의 먹잇감 <br>Only the strong survive <br>얼마나 버틸까 <br>억지 감성팔이는 <br>I don’t do cuz you <br>only get one shot <br>but I don’t lose <br>내 목숨 하나만 달려있는 게 아니라 <br>그냥 장래희망 아냐 <br>nah that's my truth <br>and fact I proved <br>but 아직 바퀴벌레 <br>인생 한 바퀴 돈 맏형은 <br>당당하게 벌래 <br>쉬운 길은 많지만 절대 못 유혹해 <br>세상이 더럽혀도 성경책은 <br>내 소독제야 <br>알지 실패는 성공의 어머니 <br>훌륭히 키워주셨으니 <br>다윗의 길을 뒤 따르고 Imma keep <br>on doin my thing so yea <br>I'm gon be the king <br>Pray for better days <br>더 좋은 날 위해 두 손 모았지 <br>Guide me through evil ways <br>Oh please <br>Oh Oh Oh Better Days <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh I pray for better days <br>매일이 나의 Birthday day처럼 <br>기분 좋게 설렐래 <br>매일매일 눈을 떠 <br>내가 꿈을 꾸는 이유 <br>Gotta maintain <br>till everyday be my payday <br>지폐에 너무 매달리기 싫지만 <br>실패의 기준이 어느새 <br>가난함이 돼버렸어 <br>결국에는 나도 현실이라는 놈의 <br>노예가 돼 있네 <br>Dang <br>어쩔 수 없지 내게 주어진 <br>모든 기회에 <br>gotta take advantage <br>쟤네 부러워할 때 <br>더 세게 마이크를 잡아 <br>until every song <br>on my album gettin airplay <br>어릴 적 내가 생각했던 꽤 괜찮은 꿈 <br>누군 비웃으며 말을 했지 그건 개꿈 <br>그 개꿈이 지금 나를 먹여 살려 <br>가능성을 열면서 성공은 여러 방법 <br>Pray for better days <br>더 좋은 날 위해 두 손 모았지 <br>Guide me through evil ways <br>Oh please <br>Oh Oh Oh Better Days <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh I pray for better days <br>좋은 예감 좋은 예상 <br>마치 epiphany가 막 떠오른 마음 <br>마치 모두가 인정하는 존재감 <br>오직 좋은 기운만 쏟아 <br>body and mind <br>마치 real really recognize <br>positive vibes <br>너네 부정의 비린내 좀 풍기지 마 <br>Superstar 따라잡을 때가 왔으니까 <br>난 이제 boost 할 준비하지 No 맨발 <br>Oh Lordy I pray for the best <br>나의 행보를 응원하는 자들에게 <br>더 이상 짐이 아닌 힘이 될 수 있게 <br>그게 뭐가 됐든 간에 <br>money power respect <br>Finally oh Lord <br>I pray for the rest <br>나의 행복을 가로막는 자들에게 <br>눈에는 눈 이에는 이 <br>눈뜨고도 볼 수 없는 이 위해 <br>I’m turnin’ up and away <br>Pray for better days <br>더 좋은 날 위해 두 손 모았지 <br>Guide me through evil ways <br>Oh please <br>Oh Oh Oh Better Days <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh I pray for better days <br>]]></content><category term="Dayday (데이데이)" label="Dayday (데이데이)"/><category term="Better Days (Feat. G2, ELO, DJ Wegun)" label="Better Days (Feat. G2, ELO, DJ Wegun)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_데이데이/엎어_Feat_김효은_DJ_Wegun/</id><title>Dayday_데이데이 - 엎어 (Feat. 김효은, DJ Wegun) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:38:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:38:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4/%EC%97%8E%EC%96%B4_Feat_%EA%B9%80%ED%9A%A8%EC%9D%80_DJ_Wegun/" title="Dayday_데이데이 - 엎어 (Feat. 김효은, DJ Wegun) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I go by the name of Dayday <br>a.k.a rap쟁이 하루하루 <br>종일 매일매일 <br>다른 곡마다 다른 발음 flow 따라 <br>또 다른 내 style을 따라 할 수 없어 <br>no nada 보통 본토들과는 달라 <br>협박하는 복통을 담아 불러 <br>내 교포 혓바닥으로 <br>맛깔난 rap을 발라 노는 동안에 <br>너네는 겁나게 똥꼬 빠네 <br>그 혓바닥으로 <br>Smooth rapper boom <br>bapper swag too dapper <br>I get stupid <br>when I spit call me boom babo <br>and I don’t start battles <br>평화주의지만 <br>가끔 Benjamin Button과 <br>섞은 Bruce Banner <br>Imma beast 기광 아닌 광기 <br>네 달팽이관을 때려 박을 <br>King Kong shit <br>마치 rap crossfit 이 바닥은 빡세지 <br>인맥과 인지도 그 사이 <br>실력의 비대칭 <br>방송은 진리보단 분량 뽑기 <br>인정사정 볼 것 없이 show no mercy <br>강하게 나오든지 집에 돌아가든지 <br>내 flow는 heavy급 microdot 덩치 <br>텐션이 올라 포텐 높아 <br>competition보단 demolition 같아 <br>내 실력은 한계가 없는 신의 한 수 <br>내 나이 탓하는 건 <br>너네들의 십년감수 <br>I don’t give a fuck 로마의 법 <br>가짜들 아닌 척 깔 자격은 퍽 <br>그래 난 MR. Chu를 썼지만 <br>입술 위에 MIC로 씹어먹을 수 있으니 <br>run for ya life <br>It’s that beat knocker <br>head bopper <br>rap 적은 emcee들의 pen dropper <br>다 엎어 난장판이야 난장 <br>판 엎어 판 다 엎어 <br>It’s that beat knocker <br>head bopper <br>rap 적은 emcee들의 pen dropper <br>판을 다 엎어 난장판이야 난장 <br>판 엎어 다 판 다 엎어 <br>1년 전만 해도 걍 아는 애 <br>내 꿈을 늘어놓음 하나 같이 eh <br>근데 내가 지금 누구랑 같이해 <br>더 이상 너넨 아냐 내 대화 상대 <br>데이데이 형이든 <br>누구든 판을 엎어 놓음 <br>내가 다시 엎을 거야 판을 엎어 놓음 <br>다신 없을 거야 누가 판을 엎어 놓을 <br>그런 일은 그러니들 <br>잠이나 자 엎어져 <br>그런 일은 즉 니들 <br>꿈속에서나 있거든 <br>믿음을 믿으면 현실이고 나를 봐 <br>기분은 저 하늘 위 구름 <br>유지해 창밖은 하늘 위 구름 어느새 <br>여느 세월 여느 때처럼 <br>즐겁게 살고 있을 걸 <br>난 관심도 없지 사실 너네들 싸움엔 <br>너네들 싸울 동안 여잔 내가 쌈해 <br>생각해보니 방송판은 너무 싸 <br>난 바로 Vegas로 쏴 <br>Yea Kenny raw <br>We in this bitch <br>spittin raw raw shit <br>no specific topics only bars <br>that’s lit <br>only bars that’s lit <br>Molotov rap kids <br>no tolerance for wackness <br>so be gone vanish <br>always underrated <br>never outdated I’m just <br>patiently waitin <br>and no ain’t complainin <br>I stay elevated levitated <br>detonate to greatness <br>and I keep distance <br>from fuckboys <br>they contagious <br>만약에 판을 엎어 놓음 <br>그 판을 다시 엎을 놈들은 나와 효은 <br>Boy be ambitious <br>on these bustas man <br>bumrush'em to the floor <br>이건 힙합 anthem 아닌 <br>ambush for you hoes <br>It’s that beat knocker <br>head bopper <br>rap 적은 emcee들의 pen dropper <br>다 엎어 난장판이야 난장 <br>판 엎어 판 다 엎어 <br>It’s that beat knocker <br>head bopper <br>rap 적은 emcee들의 pen dropper <br>판을 다 엎어 난장판이야 난장 <br>판 엎어 다 판 다 엎어 <br>]]></content><category term="Dayday (데이데이)" label="Dayday (데이데이)"/><category term="엎어 (Feat. 김효은, DJ Wegun)" label="엎어 (Feat. 김효은, DJ Wegun)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joypark_조이파크/캘리포니아_오렌지/</id><title>Joypark_조이파크 - 캘리포니아 오렌지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:38:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:38:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joypark_%EC%A1%B0%EC%9D%B4%ED%8C%8C%ED%81%AC/%EC%BA%98%EB%A6%AC%ED%8F%AC%EB%8B%88%EC%95%84_%EC%98%A4%EB%A0%8C%EC%A7%80/" title="Joypark_조이파크 - 캘리포니아 오렌지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Say you love me <br>선명한 두 입술 그 사이로 <br>Drip it baby <br>떨어지는 juice 그 미소 <br>I'll squeeze it woo my lady <br>빛이 없는 오션 <br>그건 nothing to me honey so please <br>Kiss me for orange sky <br>Take a sip and surf to the top <br>지금 우린 <br>Drinking in orange sky <br>Come and find <br>What we are <br>I'm a map <br>And you are my golden compass <br>다가와 <br>Don't be shy <br>No more no more <br>Take it easy <br>아찔한 너의 beach wear <br>그 사이로 <br>떨어지는 <br>햇살은 눈부셔 <br>It drive me crazy lady <br>I'll be a farmer 웃는 <br>너는 해변 위의 오렌지 my baby <br>너의 입술은 내 손끝을 지나 <br>우린 춤을 춰 uh uh <br>빛이 없는 오션 <br>그건 nothing to me honey so please <br>Kiss me for orange sky <br>Take a sip and surf to the top <br>지금 우린 <br>Drinking in orange sky <br>Come and find <br>What we are <br>I'm a map <br>And you are my golden compass <br>다가와 <br>Don't be shy <br>No more no more <br>Come and find <br>Paradise <br>Here we are <br>Yeah we're in California <br>다가와 <br>Don't be shy <br>No more no more <br>]]></content><category term="Joypark (조이파크)" label="Joypark (조이파크)"/><category term="캘리포니아 오렌지" label="캘리포니아 오렌지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joypark_조이파크/Alive_Feat_지애린/</id><title>Joypark_조이파크 - Alive (Feat. 지애린) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:38:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:38:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joypark_%EC%A1%B0%EC%9D%B4%ED%8C%8C%ED%81%AC/Alive_Feat_%EC%A7%80%EC%95%A0%EB%A6%B0/" title="Joypark_조이파크 - Alive (Feat. 지애린) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want you to notice <br>오 이 순간 위에 <br>우린 함께 있어 <br>We've been panting runners <br>이 밤이 지나도 <br>We never surrender <br>We never get older <br>세상이 변해도 <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>We will be together <br>놓치지마 두 손 <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>Just sing on <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>Just sing on <br>이렇게 우린 young and alive <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>성글어진 별들 <br>저 사이로 우리 <br>이렇게 걷는 거야 <br>아침이 오면 <br>Sun will ignite us <br>And it will celebrate us <br>We never get older <br>세상이 변해도 <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>We will be together <br>놓치지마 두 손 <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>Just sing on <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>Just sing on <br>이렇게 우린 young and alive <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>Just sing on <br>Now Just sing on <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>Just sing on <br>Will be together now <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>Just sing on <br>Don't say no no no <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>]]></content><category term="Joypark (조이파크)" label="Joypark (조이파크)"/><category term="Alive (Feat. 지애린)" label="Alive (Feat. 지애린)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김영철/파도/</id><title>김영철 - 파도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:38:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:38:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%98%81%EC%B2%A0/%ED%8C%8C%EB%8F%84/" title="김영철 - 파도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[황치열 김영철 <br>One Two One Two Three Four <br>너를 보내고 나 또다시 찾은 바닷가 <br>하지만 이제 내 곁에 <br>다른 사람 있는 걸 <br>새롭게 시작하고 싶어 <br>그녀를 따라왔어 <br>하지만 내 맘 네 모습만 생각이 나 <br>그녀 머리에 쏟아진 별빛들 <br>그 별빛 아래 약속한 <br>지난날이 떠올라 <br>흔들리는 나의 마음을 <br>가눌 길 없는 내 눈빛 <br>너와 비슷한 사람마저 쫓고 있었어 <br>그 순간 내 두 눈 속에 <br>너무 익숙했던 너의 뒷모습 <br>그렇게 그리던 지난날 바로 너였어 <br>눈이 부시게 아름다운 바닷가 <br>나의 눈 속엔 그보다 고운 너였어 <br>하얀 내 맘에 지난날 <br>우리가 남긴 추억들 <br>파도가 안기듯 다시 <br>내게 돌아오는 걸 <br>따르릉 <br>오빠야 오빠 오빠야 네 오빠야 <br>오빠야 오빠 오빠야 네 오빠야 <br>이런 놈 저런 놈 만나봤겠지만 <br>즐거웠겠지만 너를 사랑해 사랑해 <br>따르릉 따르릉 내가 네 오빠야 <br>오 오 빠 빠 내가 네 오빠야 <br>오 오 빠 빠 내가 네 오빠야 <br>네 오빠야 <br>눈이 부시게 아름답던 바닷가 <br>나의 눈 속엔 그보다 고운 너였어 <br>너였어 <br>너였어 <br>다시 너에게 <br>달려가는 나를 봐 <br>찌는 태양도 내 사랑을 가릴 순 없어 <br>하얀 모래 위 우리의 사랑을 <br>다시 새겨봐 <br>이제는 내 사랑 <br>이제는 내 사랑 <br>이제는 내 사랑 <br>이제는 내 사랑 <br>이제는 내 사랑 <br>너를 놓지 않을 테니까 <br>]]></content><category term="김영철" label="김영철"/><category term="파도" label="파도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송재희/어쩌다_마주친_그대/</id><title>송재희 - 어쩌다 마주친 그대 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:38:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:38:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EC%9E%AC%ED%9D%AC/%EC%96%B4%EC%A9%8C%EB%8B%A4_%EB%A7%88%EC%A3%BC%EC%B9%9C_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80/" title="송재희 - 어쩌다 마주친 그대 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어쩌다 마주친 그대 모습에 <br>내 마음을 빼앗겨버렸네 <br>어쩌다 마주친 그대 두 눈이 <br>내 마음을 사로잡아버렸네 <br>내 마음을 사로잡아버렸네 <br>어쩌다 마주친 그대 모습에 <br>내 마음을 빼앗겨버렸네 <br>어쩌다 마주친 그대 두 눈이 <br>내 마음을 사로잡아버렸네 <br>그대에게 할 말이 있는데 <br>왜 이리 용기가 없을까 <br>말을 하고 싶지만 자신이 없어 <br>내 가슴만 두근두근 <br>답답한 이 내 마음 <br>바람 속에 날려보내리 <br>피어나는 꽃처럼 아름다운 그녀가 <br>내 마음을 빼앗아버렸네 <br>이슬처럼 영롱한 그대 고운 두 눈이 <br>내 마음을 사로잡아버렸네 <br>그대에게 할 말이 있는데 <br>왜 이리 용기가 없을까 <br>말을 하고 싶지만 자신이 없어 <br>내 가슴만 두근두근 <br>바보 바보 나는 바보인가 봐 <br>그대에게 할 말이 있는데 <br>왜 이리 용기가 없을까 <br>말을 하고 싶지만 자신이 없어 <br>내 가슴만 두근두근 <br>바보 바보 나는 바보인가 봐 <br>바보 바보 나도 바보인가 봐 <br>우린 바보인가 봐 <br>저기요 저 이번에 내려요 <br>전 이미 두 정거장이나 지났는걸요 <br>우린 사랑인가 봐 <br>]]></content><category term="송재희" label="송재희"/><category term="어쩌다 마주친 그대" label="어쩌다 마주친 그대"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Twelve24/The_Book/</id><title>Twelve24 - The Book - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:40:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:40:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Twelve24/The_Book/" title="Twelve24 - The Book - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You got me going <br>you got me going crazy <br>Something about you <br>your love is so amazing <br>I know that you’ll be <br>everything I need <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Your word brings me to life <br>No matter where I go <br>I give you control <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Like a cloud by day <br>like a fire by night <br>You’re with me all the way <br>You’re with me all the way <br>Like a cloud by day <br>like a fire by night <br>You’re with me all the way <br>You’re with me all the way <br>They say nothing lasts forever <br>but that aint true <br>You can change the weather <br>but they can’t change you <br>And I love it when you speak <br>coz you speak the truth <br>Your words bring me to life <br>and make me brand new <br>So oh my I know <br>you been there my whole life <br>And you got me acting <br>to crazy right now <br>You saved me right now <br>aint that the truth <br>I know that you’ll be <br>everything I need <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Your word brings me to life <br>No matter where I go <br>I give you control <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Like a cloud by day <br>like a fire by night <br>You’re with me all the way <br>You’re with me all the way <br>Like a cloud by day <br>like a fire by night <br>You’re with me all the way <br>You’re with me all the way <br>When I don’t know what to say <br>and I don’t know what to do <br>Everything is falling down <br>I know you’ll get me through <br>Even with my broken heart <br>when every bit is torn apart <br>I know I can look to you <br>I know that you’ll be <br>everything I need <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Your word brings me to life <br>No matter where I go <br>I give you control <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Your word brings me to life <br>You’re with me all the way <br>You’re with me all the way <br>]]></content><category term="Twelve24" label="Twelve24"/><category term="The Book" label="The Book"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/요조/두근두근_여름날_Inst/</id><title>요조 - 두근두근 여름날 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:41:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:41:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9A%94%EC%A1%B0/%EB%91%90%EA%B7%BC%EB%91%90%EA%B7%BC_%EC%97%AC%EB%A6%84%EB%82%A0_Inst/" title="요조 - 두근두근 여름날 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리들의 여름날이 스쳐가 <br>쏟아지는 햇살 사이로 <br>너를 생각하면 가슴이 막 뛰어 나는 <br>눈이 부시게 파란 하늘과 <br>창문 밖으로 춤추는 나무들 <br>니 옆 모습을 바라보다 웃음이 나 <br>다 이뤄지길 바래 원하는 모든 것 <br>더 영원하길 바래 소중한 것 <br>하늘처럼 푸르른 이 여름을 <br>먼 훗날 우린 기억할까 <br>온 세상이 다 반짝 빛나고 있잖아 <br>날 바라보던 너의 눈빛처럼 <br>하루 종일 두근두근 내 마음은 <br>내일을 꿈꾸고 있는 걸 <br>이유 없이 열이 나고 아플 때 <br>알 수 없이 숨이 찰 때도 <br>너를 생각하면 괜찮아져 신기 하지 <br>주저 앉아서 울고 싶을 때 <br>바보처럼 그리워 질 때도 <br>날 믿어주는 니 가 있어 그거면 돼 <br>다 이뤄지길 바래 원하는 모든 것 <br>더 영원하길 바래 소중한 것 <br>하늘처럼 푸르른 이 여름을 <br>먼 훗날 우린 기억 할 까 <br>온 세상이 다 반짝 빛나고 있잖아 <br>날 바라보는 너의 눈 빛처럼 <br>하루 종일 두근두근 내 마음은 <br>내일을 꿈꾸고 있는 거 <br>]]></content><category term="요조" label="요조"/><category term="두근두근 여름날 (Inst.)" label="두근두근 여름날 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/요조/두근두근_여름날/</id><title>요조 - 두근두근 여름날 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:41:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:41:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9A%94%EC%A1%B0/%EB%91%90%EA%B7%BC%EB%91%90%EA%B7%BC_%EC%97%AC%EB%A6%84%EB%82%A0/" title="요조 - 두근두근 여름날 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리들의 여름날이 스쳐가 <br>쏟아지는 햇살 사이로 <br>너를 생각하면 가슴이 막 뛰어 나는 <br>눈이 부시게 파란 하늘과 <br>창문 밖으로 춤추는 나무들 <br>니 옆 모습을 바라보다 웃음이 나 <br>다 이뤄지길 바래 원하는 모든 것 <br>더 영원하길 바래 소중한 것 <br>하늘처럼 푸르른 이 여름을 <br>먼 훗날 우린 기억할까 <br>온 세상이 다 반짝 빛나고 있잖아 <br>날 바라보던 너의 눈빛처럼 <br>하루 종일 두근두근 내 마음은 <br>내일을 꿈꾸고 있는 걸 <br>이유 없이 열이 나고 아플 때 <br>알 수 없이 숨이 찰 때도 <br>너를 생각하면 괜찮아져 신기 하지 <br>주저 앉아서 울고 싶을 때 <br>바보처럼 그리워 질 때도 <br>날 믿어주는 니 가 있어 그거면 돼 <br>다 이뤄지길 바래 원하는 모든 것 <br>더 영원하길 바래 소중한 것 <br>하늘처럼 푸르른 이 여름을 <br>먼 훗날 우린 기억 할 까 <br>온 세상이 다 반짝 빛나고 있잖아 <br>날 바라보는 너의 눈 빛처럼 <br>하루 종일 두근두근 내 마음은 <br>내일을 꿈꾸고 있는 거 <br>]]></content><category term="요조" label="요조"/><category term="두근두근 여름날" label="두근두근 여름날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루노/널_기다려/</id><title>루노 - 널 기다려 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:41:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:41:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%EB%85%B8/%EB%84%90_%EA%B8%B0%EB%8B%A4%EB%A0%A4/" title="루노 - 널 기다려 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보고 싶다 안 보고 싶다 <br>꽃잎을 세며 오늘도 <br>그 자리에 앉아 <br>널 기다리고 있어 <br>어제처럼 <br>한참을 바라보고 서있다 <br>다시 집으로 돌아 가야 해 <br>내일 또 오지 않을 <br>널 기다려야 하니까 <br>오지 않을 너를 한없이 <br>기다리며 꽃잎이 <br>떨어질 때마다 내 눈물 <br>또 흘러 내가 그만 울 수 있게 <br>그만 돌아와 <br>한참을 바라보고 서있다 <br>다시 집으로 돌아 가야 해 <br>내일 또 오지 않을 <br>널 기다려야 하니까 <br>오지 않을 너를 한없이 <br>기다리며 꽃잎이 <br>떨어질 때마다 내 눈물 <br>또 흘러 내가 그만 울 수 있게 <br>그만 돌아와 <br>]]></content><category term="루노" label="루노"/><category term="널 기다려" label="널 기다려"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/찬_ChAN/너를_보낸다/</id><title>찬_ChAN - 너를 보낸다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:41:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:41:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B0%AC_ChAN/%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC_%EB%B3%B4%EB%82%B8%EB%8B%A4/" title="찬_ChAN - 너를 보낸다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈부신 그대가 온다 <br>아무 말을 못하는 난 또 운다 <br>무슨 말을 할지 다 알아 <br>가슴이 먹먹해와 <br>떨리는 목소리가 이젠 <br>굳은 표정이 이젠 <br>다 끝이 났다고 <br>이제 떠난다고 <br>보내달라 말을 해 <br>멀어져만 가는 뒷모습 <br>남자답게 보내줘야만 한다 <br>아파도 난 행복했는데 <br>자꾸만 멀어지는 그대 안녕 <br>떨리는 목소리가 이젠 <br>굳은 표정이 이젠 <br>다 끝이 났다고 <br>이제 떠난다고 <br>보내달라 말을 해 <br>멀어져만 가는 뒷모습 <br>남자답게 보내줘야만 한다 <br>아파도 난 행복했는데 <br>자꾸만 멀어지는 그대 <br>멀어져만 가는 뒷모습 <br>남자답게 보내줘야만 한다 <br>아파도 난 행복했는데 <br>자꾸만 멀어지는 그대 안녕 <br>눈부신 그대가 온다 <br>아무 말을 못하는 난 또 운다 <br>무슨 말을 할지 다 알아 <br>가슴이 먹먹해와 <br>]]></content><category term="찬 (ChAN)" label="찬 (ChAN)"/><category term="너를 보낸다" label="너를 보낸다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한성/지지고볶고/</id><title>한성 - 지지고볶고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:42:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:42:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EC%84%B1/%EC%A7%80%EC%A7%80%EA%B3%A0%EB%B3%B6%EA%B3%A0/" title="한성 - 지지고볶고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지지고 볶고 지지고 볶고 <br>지지고 볶고 <br>지지고 볶고 지지고 볶고 <br>지지고 볶고 <br>사는 게 인생 살이지 <br>잘난 맛에 사는 사람들 <br>남 탓하며 우는 사람들 <br>지지고 볶고 사는 것이 세상 살이지 <br>덧없는 인생 세월 따라 살아갈 텐데 <br>흙수저야 탄식하면 금 나오더냐 <br>인생을 지지고 사랑을 볶아봐 <br>지지고 볶고 크게 한번 웃어봐 얼쑤 <br>지지고 볶고 지지고 볶고 <br>지지고 볶고 <br>지지고 볶고 지지고 볶고 <br>지지고 볶고 <br>사는 게 인생 살이지 <br>떵떵대며 사는 사람들 <br>아등바등 사는 사람들 <br>지지고 볶고 사는 것이 세상 살이지 <br>덧없는 인생 돌아갈 땐 마찬가진데 <br>금수저야 폼 잡으면 달라지더냐 <br>인생을 지지고 사랑을 볶아봐 <br>지지고 볶고 두리둥실 살아봐 <br>지지고 볶고 지지고 볶고 <br>지지고 볶고 <br>얼싸 안고 굴러봐 얼쑤 <br>]]></content><category term="한성" label="한성"/><category term="지지고볶고" label="지지고볶고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한성/넋두리/</id><title>한성 - 넋두리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:42:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:42:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EC%84%B1/%EB%84%8B%EB%91%90%EB%A6%AC/" title="한성 - 넋두리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넋두리 하소연 가슴에 담고 <br>떠돌고 돌며 살았소 <br>정처 없는 구름처럼 헝클어진 몸 <br>안 가슴엔 멍이 들었소 <br>한도 많은 세상살이 눈물 훔치며 <br>모진 세월 어찌 살았나 <br>생각 할수록 애달픈 마음 <br>마디마디 설움 찬 사연 <br>한껏 울었소 마냥 웃었소 <br>인생사가 넋두리라오 <br>넋두리 하소연 가슴에 담고 <br>떠돌고 돌며 살았소 <br>정처 없는 구름처럼 헝클어진 몸 <br>안 가슴엔 멍이 들었소 <br>한도 많은 세상살이 눈물 훔치며 <br>모진 세월 어찌 살았나 <br>보면 볼수록 애달픈 마음 <br>세상만사 다 그런 것을 <br>잘난 사람도 못난 사람도 <br>인생사가 넋두리라오 <br>돌고 돌아가는 세월 장단에 <br>울고 웃는 넋두리라오 <br>]]></content><category term="한성" label="한성"/><category term="넋두리" label="넋두리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하이투힘_Hi_to_him/저기_Duet_Ver/</id><title>하이투힘_Hi_to_him - 저기 (Duet Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:42:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:42:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%ED%88%AC%ED%9E%98_Hi_to_him/%EC%A0%80%EA%B8%B0_Duet_Ver/" title="하이투힘_Hi_to_him - 저기 (Duet Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[저기 우리 만난 적이 있던가요 <br>어디서 본 듯한데 <br>기억이 잘 나지 않아요 <br>저기 차 한 잔 하고 가도 되나요 <br>바쁘면 괜찮아요 <br>그냥 한 번 물어봤어요 <br>흔들흔들 갈팡질팡 하는 나의 마음을 <br>알면서 아무렇지 않은 듯 한 <br>망설이지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>부담 갖지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>내숭 떨지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>혹시 나와 같다면 <br>날 기다리게 하지 말아줄래요 <br>긴가 민가 알쏭달쏭하는 너의 마음을 <br>알면서 아무렇지 않은 척 한 <br>망설이지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>부담 갖지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>내숭 떨지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>혹시 거절한다면 <br>날 기다리게 하지 마 <br>망설이지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>부담 갖지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>내숭 떨지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>혹시 나와 같다면 <br>날 기다리게 하지 말아줄래요 <br>]]></content><category term="하이투힘 (Hi to him)" label="하이투힘 (Hi to him)"/><category term="저기 (Duet Ver.)" label="저기 (Duet Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하이투힘_Hi_to_him/짝사랑_왈츠/</id><title>하이투힘_Hi_to_him - 짝사랑 왈츠 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:42:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:42:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%ED%88%AC%ED%9E%98_Hi_to_him/%EC%A7%9D%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_%EC%99%88%EC%B8%A0/" title="하이투힘_Hi_to_him - 짝사랑 왈츠 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[항상 니 옆에 서 있었잖아 <br>익숙해져 모른다 해도 <br>연애 상담도 이젠 지겨워 <br>시무룩한 내 표정 좀 봐 <br>우울한 얼굴로 나타난 너 <br>짝사랑은 힘들다고 <br>언젠가 니 옆에 날 보겠지 <br>아무리 기다려 봐도 <br>이젠 너에게 내 맘을 말할게 <br>오랫동안 망설였던 <br>이젠 더 이상 숨기지 않을게 <br>너를 향한 나의 마음들을 <br>어색해질까 봐 두려웠지 <br>친구에서 연인이 되면 <br>하지만 커지는 기대감을 <br>더 이상 숨길 수 없어 <br>이젠 너에게 내 맘을 말할게 <br>오랫동안 망설였던 <br>이젠 더 이상 숨기지 않을게 <br>너를 향한 나의 마음들을 <br>말하지 못한 내 마음들을 <br>너를 향한 나의 짝사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="하이투힘 (Hi to him)" label="하이투힘 (Hi to him)"/><category term="짝사랑 왈츠" label="짝사랑 왈츠"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하이투힘_Hi_to_him/순간의_감정/</id><title>하이투힘_Hi_to_him - 순간의 감정 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:42:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:42:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%ED%88%AC%ED%9E%98_Hi_to_him/%EC%88%9C%EA%B0%84%EC%9D%98_%EA%B0%90%EC%A0%95/" title="하이투힘_Hi_to_him - 순간의 감정 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기다리다 지친 나의 마음이 조금은 <br>무채색 공기처럼 익숙해져만 가는데 <br>아무 의미 없는 너의 문자에 어느새 <br>뭐라고 답을 할까 <br>고민만 깊어 가는데 <br>조금은 아주 조금은 나 <br>떨려도 내색 안 했어 <br>너와의 시간 <br>가끔은 조금 어색해도 <br>괜찮아 솔직히 말이야 <br>순간의 감정 <br>이미 지나버린 너의 생일에 아직도 <br>연락을 할까 말까 망설이기만 하는데 <br>언제부터인지 나조차도 모르지만 <br>무슨 생각을 할까 <br>자꾸 신경 쓰이는데 <br>조금은 아주 조금은 나 <br>떨려도 내색 안 했어 <br>너와의 시간 <br>가끔은 조금 어색해도 <br>괜찮아 솔직히 말이야 <br>순간의 감정 <br>조금은 <br>떨려도 <br>너와의 시간 <br>가끔은 조금 어색해도 <br>괜찮아 솔직히 말이야 <br>순간의 감정 <br>순간의 감정 <br>순간의 감정 <br>]]></content><category term="하이투힘 (Hi to him)" label="하이투힘 (Hi to him)"/><category term="순간의 감정" label="순간의 감정"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하이투힘_Hi_to_him/저기/</id><title>하이투힘_Hi_to_him - 저기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:42:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:42:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%ED%88%AC%ED%9E%98_Hi_to_him/%EC%A0%80%EA%B8%B0/" title="하이투힘_Hi_to_him - 저기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[저기 우리 만난 적이 있던가요 <br>어디서 본 듯한데 <br>기억이 잘 나지 않아요 <br>저기 차 한 잔 하고 가도 되나요 <br>바쁘면 괜찮아요 <br>그냥 한 번 물어봤어요 <br>흔들흔들 갈팡질팡 하는 나의 마음을 <br>알면서 아무렇지 않은 듯 한 <br>망설이지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>부담 갖지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>내숭 떨지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>혹시 나와 같다면 <br>날 기다리게 하지 말아줄래요 <br>저기 아직도 고민하고 있나요 <br>이것도 인연인데 <br>그냥 한 번 만나볼래요 <br>긴가민가 알쏭달쏭하는 너의 마음을 <br>알면서 아무렇지 않은 척 한 <br>망설이지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>부담 갖지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>내숭 떨지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>혹시 거절한다면 <br>날 기다리게 하지 마 <br>망설이지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>부담 갖지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>내숭 떨지 말고 지금 여기 가까이 <br>혹시 나와 같다면 <br>날 기다리게 하지 말아줄래요 <br>]]></content><category term="하이투힘 (Hi to him)" label="하이투힘 (Hi to him)"/><category term="저기" label="저기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/프라이드밴드/안녕/</id><title>프라이드밴드 - 안녕 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:43:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:43:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%84%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EB%93%9C%EB%B0%B4%EB%93%9C/%EC%95%88%EB%85%95/" title="프라이드밴드 - 안녕 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오 피어났다 또 시들었다 <br>숨어버린 내 하루 <br>오 다짐을 한다 또 잠을 잔다 <br>반복된 내 모습 <br>하늘을 날고 싶었던 <br>구름을 안고 싶었던 <br>난 이렇게 어른이 되네 <br>안녕 안녕 안녕 <br>문자가 왔어 넌 잘 지내니 <br>안녕 안녕 나도 안녕 <br>궁금했었어 모든 게 <br>시간이 흘러 많이 변해도 그래도 <br>내 꿈이 항상 가득 차있길 믿어 <br>안녕 안녕 I believe your dream <br>오 나를 깨운다 나를 부른다 <br>기억나는 목소리 <br>오 날 찾아본다 날 느껴본다 <br>내가 아닌 내 모습 <br>하늘을 날고 싶었던 <br>구름을 안고 싶었던 <br>난 이렇게 어른이 되네 <br>안녕 안녕 안녕 <br>문자가 왔어 넌 잘 지내니 <br>안녕 안녕 나도 안녕 <br>궁금했었어 모든 게 <br>시간이 흘러 많이 변해도 그래도 <br>내 꿈이 항상 가득 차있길 믿어 <br>안녕 안녕 I believe your dream <br>My dream is to be with you <br>My dream is to be with you <br>My dream is to be with you <br>My dream is to be with you <br>우연히 아닌데 <br>나를 깨우는 목소리가 <br>분명히 아는데 <br>나를 부르는 목소리 <br>나보다 나를 더 잘 알아주는 <br>너에게 고마워 <br>지금처럼 끝까지 믿어줘 <br>이제 난 어른인가 봐 <br>안녕 안녕 안녕 <br>이제는 알고 있어 <br>이 모습이 나인걸 <br>실수는 많아도 <br>실패는 하지 않을게 안녕 <br>안녕 안녕 안녕 <br>기다렸었던 그 목소리가 <br>안녕 안녕 어두웠던 <br>나를 밝혀줬어 모든 게 <br>시간이 흘러 많이 변해도 그래도 <br>내 꿈이 항상 가득 차있길 믿어 <br>안녕 안녕 I believe my dream <br>]]></content><category term="프라이드밴드" label="프라이드밴드"/><category term="안녕" label="안녕"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임아란/선한_목자되신_나의_주_Band_Ver/</id><title>임아란 - 선한 목자되신 나의 주 (Band Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:43:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:43:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EC%84%A0%ED%95%9C_%EB%AA%A9%EC%9E%90%EB%90%98%EC%8B%A0_%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%A3%BC_Band_Ver/" title="임아란 - 선한 목자되신 나의 주 (Band Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[선한 목자 되신 나의 주 항상 인도해 <br>푸른 초장 쉴만한 물가로 <br>인도하시네 <br>선한 목자 되신 나의 주 날 지키시네 <br>사망의 음침한 골짜기도 <br>두렵지 않네 <br>선한 목자 되신 나의 주 항상 인도해 <br>푸른 초장 쉴만한 물가로 <br>인도하시네 <br>선한 목자 되신 나의 주 날 지키시네 <br>사망의 음침한 골짜기도 <br>두렵지 않네 <br>난 길을 잃었지 방황하며 두려웠지 <br>큰 죄에 빠져 벗어날 수 없었지 <br>한 치 앞도 안보여 <br>돌아갈 길조차 없어 <br>두려워 주님을 불렀을 때 <br>주님은 기꺼이 <br>내 삶 속에 뛰어 들어와 <br>나의 손 잡아주셨네 <br>주님은 기꺼이 <br>내 삶 속에 뛰어 들어와 <br>나의 손 잡아주셨네 <br>난 길을 잃었지 방황하며 두려웠지 <br>큰 죄에 빠져 벗어날 수 없었지 <br>한 치 앞도 안보여 <br>돌아갈 길조차 없어 <br>두려워 주님을 불렀을 때 <br>주님은 기꺼이 <br>내 삶 속에 뛰어 들어와 <br>나의 손 잡아주셨네 <br>주님은 기꺼이 <br>내 삶 속에 뛰어 들어와 <br>나의 손 잡아주셨네 <br>주님은 기꺼이 <br>내 삶 속에 뛰어 들어와 <br>나의 손 잡아주셨네 <br>주님은 기꺼이 <br>내 삶 속에 뛰어 들어와 <br>나의 손 잡아주셨네 <br>선한 목자 되신 나의 주 <br>선한 목자 되신 나의 주 <br>선한 목자 되신 나의 주 항상 인도해 <br>선한 목자 되신 나의 주 <br>선한 목자 되신 나의 주 <br>선한 목자 되신 나의 주 날 지키시네 <br>]]></content><category term="임아란" label="임아란"/><category term="선한 목자되신 나의 주 (Band Ver.)" label="선한 목자되신 나의 주 (Band Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임아란/간음한_여인의_노래/</id><title>임아란 - 간음한 여인의 노래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:43:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:43:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EA%B0%84%EC%9D%8C%ED%95%9C_%EC%97%AC%EC%9D%B8%EC%9D%98_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="임아란 - 간음한 여인의 노래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사람들은 나의 삶을 보지만 <br>주는 내 맘 보시네 <br>사람들은 보이는 대로 보지만 <br>주는 내 맘 아시네 <br>사람들은 나의 삶을 보지만 <br>주는 내 맘 보시네 <br>사람들은 보이는 대로 보지만 <br>주는 내 맘 아시네 <br>주님 나를 찾아오셨네 <br>상처 입은 나의 맘을 아시네 <br>주님 나의 맘을 아시네 <br>상한 나의 맘을 안아주시네 <br>주님 나를 찾아오셨네 <br>상처 입은 나의 맘을 아시네 <br>주님 나의 맘을 아시네 <br>상한 나의 맘을 안아주시네 <br>주님 나를 찾아오셨네 <br>상처 입은 나의 맘을 아시네 <br>주님 나의 맘을 아시네 <br>상한 나의 맘을 안아주시네 <br>사람들은 나의 삶을 보지만 <br>주는 내 맘 보시네 <br>사람들은 보이는 대로 보지만 <br>주는 내 맘 아시네 <br>]]></content><category term="임아란" label="임아란"/><category term="간음한 여인의 노래" label="간음한 여인의 노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임아란/아_내_맘_속에/</id><title>임아란 - 아 내 맘 속에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:43:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:43:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EC%95%84_%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%98_%EC%86%8D%EC%97%90/" title="임아란 - 아 내 맘 속에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아 내 맘 속에 참된 평화 있네 <br>주 예수가 주신 평화 <br>시험 닥쳐와도 흔들리지 않아 <br>아 귀하다 이 평안함 <br>주가 항상 계셔 내 맘 속에 <br>주가 항상 계셔 아 기쁘다 <br>주 나의 맘에 계셔 위로하시네 <br>어찌 내가 주를 떠나 살까 <br>주 날개 아래 내가 사는 동안 <br>이 보배를 빛내리라 <br>주가 항상 계셔 내 맘속에 <br>주가 항상 계셔 아 기쁘다 <br>주가 나의 맘에 계셔 위로하시네 <br>어찌 내가 주를 떠나 살까 <br>주가 항상 계셔 내 맘속에 <br>주가 항상 계셔 아 기쁘다 <br>주가 나의 맘에 계셔 <br>내 맘을 위로하시네 <br>어찌 내가 주를 떠나 살까 <br>어찌 내가 주를 떠나 살까 <br>]]></content><category term="임아란" label="임아란"/><category term="아 내 맘 속에" label="아 내 맘 속에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임아란/짐이_무거우냐_Reach_Out_To_Jesus/</id><title>임아란 - 짐이 무거우냐 (Reach Out To Jesus) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:43:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:43:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EC%A7%90%EC%9D%B4_%EB%AC%B4%EA%B1%B0%EC%9A%B0%EB%83%90_Reach_Out_To_Jesus/" title="임아란 - 짐이 무거우냐 (Reach Out To Jesus) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[짐이 무거우냐 홀로 지고 가기엔 <br>험한 데로 갈까 두렵지는 않느냐 <br>온갖 일에 매여 고달프지 않느냐 <br>주가 도우시리 요청만 하면 <br>우리 기도를 언제 어디나 들으시고 <br>큰 사랑으로 감싸주시며 동행하니 <br>내가 실망할 때 기억해야 할 것은 <br>예수께 가면 주 내게 오시리 <br>우리 기도를 언제 어디나 들으시고 <br>큰 사랑으로 감싸주시며 동행하니 <br>우리 기도를 언제 어디나 들으시고 <br>큰 사랑으로 감싸주시며 동행하니 <br>내가 실망할 때 기억해야 할 것은 <br>예수께 가면 예수께 가면 <br>예수께 가면 주 <br>주 내게 오시리 <br>]]></content><category term="임아란" label="임아란"/><category term="짐이 무거우냐 (Reach Out To Jesus)" label="짐이 무거우냐 (Reach Out To Jesus)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임아란/여러분에게_하고_싶은_말/</id><title>임아란 - 여러분에게 하고 싶은 말 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:43:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:43:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EC%97%AC%EB%9F%AC%EB%B6%84%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_%ED%95%98%EA%B3%A0_%EC%8B%B6%EC%9D%80_%EB%A7%90/" title="임아란 - 여러분에게 하고 싶은 말 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 여러분에게 <br>하고 싶은 말 있는데 <br>나의 삶이 끝나는 날까지 <br>전하고 싶은 말 있는데 <br>예수가 나를 살렸네 <br>예수가 나의 길 되셨네 <br>예수가 나의 새 생명 되네 <br>어두운 과거를 뚫고 <br>난 새로워졌네 <br>난 새 인생을 얻었네 <br>어두운 슬픔의 벽을 뚫고 나와 <br>나 이제 소리치네 <br>난 노래하네 주를 <br>예수가 나를 살렸네 <br>예수가 나를 살렸네 <br>예수가 나를 살렸네 예수가 <br>예수를 말하고 싶네 <br>예수를 노래하고 싶네 <br>예수만 전하고 싶네 예수만 <br>오 오 오 오 오 오 <br>오 오 오 오 오 오 <br>예수가 나를 살렸네 <br>예수가 나를 살렸네 <br>예수가 나를 살렸네 예수가 <br>예수를 말하고 싶네 <br>예수를 노래하고 싶네 <br>예수만 전하고 싶네 예수만 <br>내 인생 끝나는 날까지 <br>난 이것만 전하다 가고 싶네 <br>내가 말하고픈 것 <br>내가 노래하고픈 것 <br>이것뿐이네 <br>]]></content><category term="임아란" label="임아란"/><category term="여러분에게 하고 싶은 말" label="여러분에게 하고 싶은 말"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임아란/여호와_이레/</id><title>임아란 - 여호와 이레 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:44:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:44:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EC%97%AC%ED%98%B8%EC%99%80_%EC%9D%B4%EB%A0%88/" title="임아란 - 여호와 이레 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여호와 이레 채우시네 <br>여호와 이레 채우시네 <br>여호와 라파 치료하시네 <br>여호와 라파 치료하시네 <br>여호와 닛시 이기시네 <br>여호와 닛시 이기시네 <br>여호와 샬롬 평안주시네 <br>여호와 샬롬 평안주시네 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 <br>여호와 이레 채우시네 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 <br>여호와 라파 치료하시네 <br>여호와 삼마 거하시네 <br>여호와 삼마 거하시네 <br>여호와 로이 인도하시네 <br>여호와 로이 인도하시네 <br>갈 길을 잃어 두렵니 <br>몸과 맘 다 지쳤니 <br>답도 없고 용기도 없니 <br>그럼 이제 그만 헤매고 <br>하나님 믿어봐 <br>아무리 가져도 공허하니 <br>실컷 놀아도 행복하지 않니 <br>평생 채워지지 않을거야 공허 <br>그건 하나님만 채울수 있단다 <br>난 아무것도 없지만 다 가졌지 <br>난 겁쟁이 맞지만 쫄지 않지 <br>난 믿음밖에 없지만 위풍당당 <br>왜냐 하나님이 내편이니까 <br>믿고싶지 너도 믿고싶지 <br>하나님 믿어봐 믿어봐 <br>너도 한번 믿어봐 <br>후회할 일 없을걸 내말좀 믿어봐 <br>믿어봐 믿어봐 너도 한번 믿어봐 <br>우리하나님 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 여호와 <br>이레 채우시네 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 여호와 <br>이레 채우시네 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 여호와 <br>이레 채우시네 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 여호와 <br>이레 채우시네 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 여호와 <br>이레 채우시네 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 여호와 <br>이레 채우시네 <br>]]></content><category term="임아란" label="임아란"/><category term="여호와 이레" label="여호와 이레"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임아란/착각/</id><title>임아란 - 착각 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:44:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:44:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EC%B0%A9%EA%B0%81/" title="임아란 - 착각 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나님 능력인데 <br>마치 내 능력인 것처럼 <br>하나님 은혜인데 <br>마치 내 노력인 것처럼 <br>하나님 선물인데 <br>마치 다 내것인 것처럼 <br>착각하며 그렇게 살아왔구나 <br>하나님 없으면 <br>난 아무 것도 아닙니다 <br>하나님 없으면 <br>난 아무 것도 못합니다 <br>하나님 없으면 <br>난 아무 의미도 없습니다 <br>나를 기대하지 마세요 <br>하나님을 기대하세요 <br>오 모두 다 내가 이룬 것처럼 <br>하나님 영광을 다 가로챘고 <br>사람들 칭찬에 으쓱해졌지 <br>오 모든 걸 다 잃고 난 깨달았지 <br>난 아무 것도 할 수 없단걸 <br>하나님 은혜인걸 <br>하나님 능력인데 <br>마치 내 능력인 것처럼 <br>하나님 은혜인데 <br>마치 내 노력인 것처럼 <br>하나님 선물인데 <br>마치 다 내것인 것처럼 <br>착각하며 그렇게 살아왔구나 <br>오 모두 다 내가 이룬 것처럼 <br>하나님 영광을 다 가로챘고 <br>사람들 칭찬에 으쓱해졌지 <br>오 모든 걸 다 잃고 난 깨달았지 <br>난 아무 것도 할 수 없단걸 <br>하나님 은혜인걸 <br>하나님 능력인걸 기억하기 <br>하나님 은혜인걸 잊지않기 <br>하나님 선물인걸 인정하기 <br>착각하며 살지않기 <br>하나님 능력인걸 기억하기 <br>하나님 은혜인걸 잊지않기 <br>하나님 선물인걸 인정하기 <br>착각하며 살지않기 <br>하나님 능력인걸 기억하기 <br>하나님 은혜인걸 잊지않기 <br>하나님 선물인걸 인정하기 <br>착각하며 살지않기 <br>하나님 능력인걸 기억하기 <br>하나님 은혜인걸 잊지않기 <br>하나님 선물인걸 인정하기 <br>착각하며 살지않기 <br>]]></content><category term="임아란" label="임아란"/><category term="착각" label="착각"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임아란/선한_목자되신_나의_주_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>임아란 - 선한 목자되신 나의 주 (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:44:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:44:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EC%84%A0%ED%95%9C_%EB%AA%A9%EC%9E%90%EB%90%98%EC%8B%A0_%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%A3%BC_Acoustic_Ver/" title="임아란 - 선한 목자되신 나의 주 (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[선한 목자되신 나의 주 항상 인도해 <br>푸른 초장 쉴 만한 <br>물가로 인도하시네 <br>선한 목자되신 나의 주 날 지키시네 <br>사망의 음침한 골짜기도 두렵지 않네 <br>선한 목자되신 나의 주 항상 인도해 <br>푸른 초장 쉴 만한 <br>물가로 인도하시네 <br>선한 목자되신 나의 주 날 지키시네 <br>사망의 음침한 골짜기도 두렵지 않네 <br>난 길을 잃었지 방황하며 두려웠지 <br>큰 죄에 빠져 벗어날 수 없었지 <br>한 치 앞도 안보여 <br>돌아갈 길조차 없어 <br>두려워 주님을 불렀을 때 <br>주님은 기꺼이 <br>내 삶 속에 뛰어 들어와 <br>나의 손 잡아주셨네 <br>주님은 기꺼이 <br>내 삶 속에 뛰어 들어와 <br>나의 손 잡아주셨네 <br>난 길을 잃었지 방황하며 두려웠지 <br>큰 죄에 빠져 벗어날 수 없었지 <br>한 치 앞도 안보여 <br>돌아갈 길조차 없어 <br>두려워 주님을 불렀을 때 <br>주님은 기꺼이 <br>내 삶 속에 뛰어 들어와 <br>나의 손 잡아주셨네 <br>주님은 기꺼이 <br>내 삶 속에 뛰어 들어와 <br>나의 손 잡아주셨네 <br>주님은 기꺼이 <br>내 삶 속에 뛰어 들어와 <br>나의 손 잡아주셨네 <br>주님은 기꺼이 <br>내 삶 속에 뛰어 들어와 <br>나의 손 잡아주셨네 <br>선한 목자되신 나의 주 <br>선한 목자되신 나의 주 <br>선한 목자되신 나의 주 항상 인도해 <br>선한 목자되신 나의 주 <br>선한 목자되신 나의 주 <br>선한 목자되신 나의 주 항상 인도해 <br>]]></content><category term="임아란" label="임아란"/><category term="선한 목자되신 나의 주 (Acoustic Ver.)" label="선한 목자되신 나의 주 (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/대한예수교장로회총회/내_맘_가득한/</id><title>대한예수교장로회총회 - 내 맘 가득한 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:44:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:44:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8C%80%ED%95%9C%EC%98%88%EC%88%98%EA%B5%90%EC%9E%A5%EB%A1%9C%ED%9A%8C%EC%B4%9D%ED%9A%8C/%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%98_%EA%B0%80%EB%93%9D%ED%95%9C/" title="대한예수교장로회총회 - 내 맘 가득한 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 맘 가득한 하나님의 사랑 <br>나 어떻게 표현할까 <br>내 맘 가득한 하나님의 사랑 <br>나 어떻게 표현할까 <br>하나님 감사해요 <br>하나님 찬양해요 <br>하나님 사랑해요 <br>내 마음 받아 주세요. <br><br>친구야 교회가자 <br>친구야 도와줄게 <br>친구야 우린 하나 <br>예수님 사랑 나눠줄래요]]></content><category term="대한예수교장로회총회" label="대한예수교장로회총회"/><category term="내 맘 가득한" label="내 맘 가득한"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/대한예수교장로회총회/Jump_Jump/</id><title>대한예수교장로회총회 - Jump Jump - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:44:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:44:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8C%80%ED%95%9C%EC%98%88%EC%88%98%EA%B5%90%EC%9E%A5%EB%A1%9C%ED%9A%8C%EC%B4%9D%ED%9A%8C/Jump_Jump/" title="대한예수교장로회총회 - Jump Jump - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하늘을 향해 두 팔을 펴고 <br>쿵쿵쾅쾅 발을 구르며 <br>기쁨으로 jump 사랑으로 jump <br>우린 달라졌네 우린 변화됐네 <br>친구를 향해 jump jump <br>교회를 향해 jump jump <br>세상을 향해 jump jump <br>예수님의 사랑으로 jump jump jump <br><br>하늘을 향해 두 팔을 펴고 <br>쿵쿵쾅쾅 발을 구르며 <br>기쁨으로 jump 사랑으로 jump <br>우린 달라졌네 우린 변화됐네 <br>친구를 향해 jump jump <br>교회를 향해 jump jump <br>세상을 향해 jump jump <br>예수님의 사랑으로 jump jump jump <br><br>친구를 향해 jump jump <br>교회를 향해 jump jump <br>세상을 향해 jump jump <br>예수님의 사랑으로 jump jump jump jump <br>]]></content><category term="대한예수교장로회총회" label="대한예수교장로회총회"/><category term="Jump Jump" label="Jump Jump"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/대한예수교장로회총회/믿음에서_사랑까지부제：바람의_소리를_들어보아요_2016년_여름성경학교_총주제가/</id><title>대한예수교장로회총회 - 믿음에서 사랑까지(부제：바람의 소리를 들어보아요) (2016년 여름성경학교 총주제가) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:44:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:44:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8C%80%ED%95%9C%EC%98%88%EC%88%98%EA%B5%90%EC%9E%A5%EB%A1%9C%ED%9A%8C%EC%B4%9D%ED%9A%8C/%EB%AF%BF%EC%9D%8C%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EA%B9%8C%EC%A7%80%EB%B6%80%EC%A0%9C%EF%BC%9A%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C%EC%9D%98_%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC%EB%A5%BC_%EB%93%A4%EC%96%B4%EB%B3%B4%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94_2016%EB%85%84_%EC%97%AC%EB%A6%84%EC%84%B1%EA%B2%BD%ED%95%99%EA%B5%90_%EC%B4%9D%EC%A3%BC%EC%A0%9C%EA%B0%80/" title="대한예수교장로회총회 - 믿음에서 사랑까지(부제：바람의 소리를 들어보아요) (2016년 여름성경학교 총주제가) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람의 소리를 들어보아요 <br>흐르는 물소리 들어보아요 <br>푸른 나무와 들꽃의 춤을 보아요 <br>우리에게 노래하고 있지 않나요 <br>마음 활짝 열고 세상을 봐요 <br>얼마나 아름다운 세상인지 <br>주님의 마음 내 안에 계시잖아요 <br>세상을 사랑으로 안아주세요 <br>우린 한 마음으로 노래할 수 있어요 <br>서로 다르지만 하나가 될 수 있죠 <br>하나님 우릴 한 몸으로 부르셨어요 <br>믿음으로 시작해서 사랑까지 살아가요 X2 <br><br>우린 한 마음으로 노래할 수 있어요 <br>서로 다르지만 하나가 될 수 있죠 <br>하나님 우릴 한 몸으로 부르셨어요 <br>믿음으로 시작해서 사랑까지 살아가요]]></content><category term="대한예수교장로회총회" label="대한예수교장로회총회"/><category term="믿음에서 사랑까지(부제：바람의 소리를 들어보아요) (2016년 여름성경학교 총주제가)" label="믿음에서 사랑까지(부제：바람의 소리를 들어보아요) (2016년 여름성경학교 총주제가)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/온유/이러지_말아요/</id><title>온유 - 이러지 말아요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:47:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:47:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A8%EC%9C%A0/%EC%9D%B4%EB%9F%AC%EC%A7%80_%EB%A7%90%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94/" title="온유 - 이러지 말아요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[참 어려웠었죠 많이 서투른 내가 <br>기다린단 말도 못하고 <br>차가운 척 돌아섰죠 <br>그대 나를 보내지 말아요 <br>그대에게 나 많이 부족하지만 <br>그래요 지금도 울고 있어요 <br>다시 나를 찾을까 봐 <br>내 이름 불러줄까 봐 <br>이대로는 안 될 것 같아요 <br>내 사랑이 너무 초라해 보여서 <br>우리 눈물이 흐르지 않도록 <br>그렇게 다시 사랑해요 <br>이젠 내 마음 알까요 <br>흘러가는 시간만 보며 <br>돌아서지도 못하는 날 <br>조금은 이해할까요 <br>그대 나를 보내지 말아요 <br>그대에게 나 많이 부족하지만 <br>그래요 지금도 울고 있어요 <br>다시 나를 찾을까 봐 <br>내 이름 불러줄까 봐 <br>이대로는 안 될 것 같아요 <br>내 사랑이 너무 초라해 보여서 <br>우리 눈물이 흐르지 않도록 <br>그렇게 다시 사랑해요 <br>나 이렇게 노래를 불러보아요 <br>힘에 겨운 이 맘이 저 별에 닿기를 <br>이곳에서 나 기다릴게요 <br>이토록 아파한 내가 정말 미워지지만 <br>아직도 사랑하는 마음뿐이라서 <br>하염없이 그댈 바라보고 있어요 <br>이렇게는 떠나지 말아줘요 <br>내 사랑이 너무 초라해 보여서 <br>우리 눈물이 흐르지 않도록 <br>그렇게 다시 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="온유" label="온유"/><category term="이러지 말아요" label="이러지 말아요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/다리아/그럼에도/</id><title>다리아 - 그럼에도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:49:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:49:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EB%A6%AC%EC%95%84/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%BC%EC%97%90%EB%8F%84/" title="다리아 - 그럼에도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[미련한 사랑이 또 <br>나를 울게 만들어 <br>그렇게 다신 안 할 거라 <br>다짐했는데 <br>이유도 모른 채 또 <br>나는 홀로 이 자리에 남겨져 <br>이렇게 <br>아무 말 없이 가면 난 <br>어떻게 하라는 건데 <br>도대체 왜 나를 <br>떠나가 버린 거니 <br>나에게도 조금은 <br>시간이 필요하잖아 <br>네가 그렇게 가버리면 <br>이제 혼자 남겨질 내가 <br>난 두려워 <br>그럼에도 <br>끝나버렸어 <br>흩어질 추억이 또 <br>나를 울게 만들어 <br>그렇게 다 잊을 거라 <br>다짐했는데 <br>시간이 약이라고 <br>다들 잊혀질 거라고 말해도 <br>이렇게 <br>나는 아무것도 못해 <br>어떻게 하라는 건데 <br>도대체 왜 나를 <br>떠나가 버린 거니 <br>나에게도 조금은 <br>시간이 필요하잖아 <br>네가 그렇게 가버리면 <br>이제 혼자 남겨질 내가 <br>난 두려워 <br>그럼에도 끝나버렸어 <br>]]></content><category term="다리아" label="다리아"/><category term="그럼에도" label="그럼에도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나보나/어쿠스틱_사랑/</id><title>나보나 - 어쿠스틱 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:49:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:49:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%B3%B4%EB%82%98/%EC%96%B4%EC%BF%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B1_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="나보나 - 어쿠스틱 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈부신 햇살이 내리는 날 <br>그대를 만나러 가는 길이야 <br>달려갈 거야 아니 날아갈 거야 <br>처음 느낌 그대로 심 쿵 <br>좋아하는 걸 사랑하는 걸 <br>기분이 너무 좋아서 날아갈 듯 <br>온 세상이 너랑 나 둘뿐인 듯 <br>So beautiful day <br>I feel so happy with you <br>우리사랑은 꾸밈 없는 화음 <br>순수하고 따뜻한 멜로디 <br>눈부신 햇살이 내리는 날 <br>그대를 만나러 가는 길이야 <br>달려갈 거야 아니 날아갈 거야 <br>처음 느낌 그대로 심 쿵 <br>좋아하는 걸 사랑하는 걸 <br>기분이 너무 좋아서 날아갈 듯 <br>온 세상이 너랑 나 둘뿐인 듯 <br>So beautiful day <br>I feel so happy with you <br>우리사랑은 꾸밈 없는 화음 <br>순수하고 따뜻한 멜로디 <br>so beautiful day <br>I feel so happy with you <br>서투르지만 솔직한 사랑 <br>우리는 어쿠스틱 사랑 <br>좋아하는 걸 사랑하는 걸 <br>]]></content><category term="나보나" label="나보나"/><category term="어쿠스틱 사랑" label="어쿠스틱 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Talking_Heads/No_Compassion_Live/</id><title>Talking_Heads - No Compassion (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:52:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:52:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Talking_Heads/No_Compassion_Live/" title="Talking_Heads - No Compassion (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In a world <br>where people have problems <br>In this world <br>where decisions are a way of life <br>Other people's problems they overwhelm my mind <br>They say compassion is a virtue, but I don't have the time <br><br>So many peoplehave their problems <br>I'm not interestedin their problems <br>I guess I'veexperienced some problems <br>But now I'vemade some decisions <br>Takes a lot of time to push away the nonsense <br>Take my compassionPush it as far as it goes <br>My interest level's dropping, my interest level is dropping <br>I've heard all I want to, I don't want to hear any more <br><br>What are you, in love with your problems <br>I think you take ita little too far <br>It'snot so cool to have so many problems <br>But don't expect me to explain your indecisions <br>Gotalk to your analyst, isn't that what they're paid for <br>You walk, you talkYou still function like you used to <br>It's not a questionOf your personality or style <br>Be a little more selfish, it might do you some good <br><br>In a world where people have problems <br>In this world where decisions are a way of life <br>Other people's problems, they overwhelm my mind <br>They say compassion is a virtue, but I don't have the time <br>Here we go again]]></content><category term="Talking Heads" label="Talking Heads"/><category term="No Compassion (Live)" label="No Compassion (Live)"/></entry></feed>