<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:55:19+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/빌리어코스티/보이나요/</id><title>빌리어코스티 - 보이나요 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:55:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:55:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%8C%EB%A6%AC%EC%96%B4%EC%BD%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B0/%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4%EB%82%98%EC%9A%94/" title="빌리어코스티 - 보이나요 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보이나요 그댈 향한 내 맘을 <br>느끼나요 이게 사랑이란 걸 <br>모르나요 그댈 바라보는 난 <br>어떡하죠 그댄 알고 있나요 <br>내 맘이 우후후 별빛 가득한 <br>우후후 눈부신 날에 <br>둘이서 함께 같은 곳을 <br>바라볼 수 있다면 <br>I love you <br>내게 말해 줄 순 없나요 <br>커져버린 내 사랑이 <br>표현하고 싶어 <br>나 이곳에서 기다리는데 <br>그댄 알까요 <br>Say I love you 미소 짓는 <br>그대 눈빛이 <br>내게 말해줄 것 같아 <br>나 그대 곁에서 <br>항상 맴도는 내 맘을 <br>그대는 알까요 <br>언제나 말없이 기다려줘서 <br>긴 시간 함께 해줘서 <br>약속할게요 이제는 <br>내가 지켜줄게요 <br>I love you <br>내게 말해 줄 순 없나요 <br>커져버린 내 사랑이 <br>표현하고 싶어 <br>나 이곳에서 기다리는데 <br>그댄 알까요 <br>Say I love you 미소 짓는 <br>그대 눈빛이 <br>내게 말해줄 것 같아 <br>나 그대 곁에서 <br>항상 맴도는 내 맘을 <br>그대는 알까요 <br>내 하루는 <br>그대 때문에 시작되고 <br>사랑이라면 나와 같다면 <br>그대에게 하고 싶은 말 <br>I love you <br>]]></content><category term="빌리어코스티" label="빌리어코스티"/><category term="보이나요" label="보이나요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제미니/어쩌다_우리가/</id><title>제미니 - 어쩌다 우리가 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:55:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:55:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EB%AF%B8%EB%8B%88/%EC%96%B4%EC%A9%8C%EB%8B%A4_%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EA%B0%80/" title="제미니 - 어쩌다 우리가 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어제는 뭘 했었는지 <br>오늘은 뭘 해야 할지 <br>이상해 도무지 모르겠어 <br>너와 함께했던 날들은 <br>정말 잘 지냈는데 <br>니가 안 보여서 <br>불안한가 봐 <br>가끔은 널 미워했고 <br>가끔은 원망도 했던 <br>사소한 그날들이 <br>다 그리워 <br>손에 잡힐듯 추억들이 <br>자꾸 생각이 나서 <br>아무것도 못하잖아 <br>날 어떻게 지워낸 거야 <br>넌 어떻게 멀쩡한 거야 <br>그땐 나만큼 많이 <br>사랑했잖아 나빠 <br>널 위해 다 써버렸잖아 <br>뭐 하나 남은 게 없잖아 <br>매일 이렇게 <br>지쳐가고 있잖아 나만 <br>어쩌다 우리가 <br>남이 돼버린 거야 <br>널 보면 참 따뜻했고 <br>널 보면 참 행복했어 <br>널 보며 이게 <br>사랑이라 믿었어 <br>내게 전부였던 사랑이 <br>멀어져만 가는 게 <br>죽을 만큼 그만큼 아파 <br>날 어떻게 지워낸 거야 <br>넌 어떻게 멀쩡한 거야 <br>그땐 나만큼 <br>많이 사랑했잖아 나빠 <br>널 위해 다 써버렸잖아 <br>뭐 하나 남은 게 없잖아 <br>매일 이렇게 <br>지쳐 가고 있잖아 나만 <br>어쩌다 우리가 <br>남이 돼버린 거야 <br>너와 나 쌓았던 <br>모든 순간에 <br>너 없이 나 혼자 <br>남아 서있어 <br>너 아니면 안 될 것 같아 <br>이별까진 못 갈 것 같아 <br>누굴 만나도 <br>너만 생각나잖아 너만 <br>어떤 말도 들리지 않아 <br>애를 써도 결국엔 너야 <br>떠나가도 돼 <br>나만 홀로 이대로 남아 <br>우리 사랑했던 <br>추억에 더 머물게 <br>]]></content><category term="제미니" label="제미니"/><category term="어쩌다 우리가" label="어쩌다 우리가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오윤혜/그래_그랬어/</id><title>오윤혜 - 그래 그랬어 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:55:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:55:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%98_%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%AC%EC%96%B4/" title="오윤혜 - 그래 그랬어 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[담담히 맘을 정리하고 있어 <br>여전히 그대로인 것도 있어 <br>한 켠에 두고 잊던 건 <br>진심이 아니란 걸 <br>잔잔히 바람이 불어올 때도 <br>촉촉이 비가 오는 날도 있어 <br>계절이 지나도 난 시간이 지나도 <br>너만 생각했나 봐 <br>사랑이라 말을 한 건 그때는 그랬어 <br>이별이라 말한 건 그래 그땐 그랬어 <br>이제는 너를 지워가고 있어 <br>가끔씩 떠오를 때면 울었어 <br>한 켠에 두고 떠나간 기억의 <br>저편에서 <br>오늘도 너를 정리하고 있어 <br>가끔씩 너를 생각하고 있어 <br>울음이 터지던 날 아픔이 터지던 <br>그때 기억 나나 봐 <br>사랑이라 말을 한 건 그때는 그랬어 <br>이별이라 말한 건 그래 그땐 그랬어 <br>라리라 라랄 라라 <br>꿈결같던 시간을 이제는 <br>너를 보내야만 할까 봐 <br>사랑이라 말을 한 건 그때는 그랬어 <br>이별이라 말한 건 그래 그땐 그랬어 <br>]]></content><category term="오윤혜" label="오윤혜"/><category term="그래 그랬어" label="그래 그랬어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/컨트리공방/나도_엄마있다/</id><title>컨트리공방 - 나도 엄마있다 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:55:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:55:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BB%A8%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AC%EA%B3%B5%EB%B0%A9/%EB%82%98%EB%8F%84_%EC%97%84%EB%A7%88%EC%9E%88%EB%8B%A4/" title="컨트리공방 - 나도 엄마있다 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오랜만에 나 홀로 명동길 <br>앞에 걷는 두 사람 <br>누구보다 편안해 보이는 <br>똑 닮은 두 미소 <br>팔짱 끼고 이것저것 보며 <br>귓속말도 소근소근 <br>호떡 가게 긴 줄 기다려 <br>하나 사서 서로 한입 <br>내가 만약 서울이 아니라면 <br>내가 살던 울동네면 <br>키가 작고 얼굴도 동그란 <br>똑 나 닮은 엄마랑 걸을 텐데 <br>팔짱 끼고 앞서 걷고 있는 <br>두 사람을 볼 때마다 <br>나에게도 엄마가 있다 <br>멀리 있어 애만 탈 뿐 <br>보고 싶어 눈물만 날 뿐 <br>]]></content><category term="컨트리공방" label="컨트리공방"/><category term="나도 엄마있다" label="나도 엄마있다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/효린/BLUE_MOON_Prod_GroovyRoom/</id><title>효린 - BLUE MOON (Prod. GroovyRoom) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:56:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:56:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9A%A8%EB%A6%B0/BLUE_MOON_Prod_GroovyRoom/" title="효린 - BLUE MOON (Prod. GroovyRoom) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어서 날 알아보길 바래 <br>나 없는 넌 안 되겠다고 말해 <br>깨고 또 깨어나도 <br>반복되는 깊고 슬픈 꿈 <br>내 머릴 쓰다듬고 <br>이제 괜찮다고 말해 <br>메마른 너의 눈빛은 <br>make me crazy <br>둘 사이 파랗고 위태로운 <br>다리를 건너 <br>나밖에 몰랐었던 너 <br>사랑이 전부였던 나 <br>그곳으로 난 돌아가길 바래 <br>날 끌어당겨 작은 틈도 없게 해줘 <br>네게 안겨 지친 맘을 쉬고 싶어 <br>발이 땅에 닿지 않는 이별 위를 <br>혼자 허우적대며 걷지 않게 해줘 <br>I walk on the moon in the air <br>I walk on the moon in the air <br>바닥 출신의 신사가 널 원해 <br>이 신사는 never leave you lonely <br>오늘 낮 오늘 밤 아 오늘 다 <br>너한테 내줄래 무료로 다 전세 <br>내 동네로 와 도시를 나와줘 <br>도시의 공주님 나에게 맡겨 널 <br>걱정 마 돈 벌어 구매할래 니 시간 <br>말 안 할랬는데 <br>내가 스타래 서울시가 <br>널 탐하는 남자는 villain <br>영웅은 단번에 악당을 killin <br>야망이 가득한 난 그 후 널 안고 <br>총 모양 오른손을 한 채로 1llin <br>Baby girl 나와 그댄 어려 <br>시간은 많잖아 <br>나와 몇 억 초를 세버려 <br>Mooooah 오늘뿐여도 yes <br>죽을 때까지라면 더 yes princess <br>날 끌어당겨 작은 틈도 없게 해줘 <br>네게 안겨 지친 맘을 쉬고 싶어 <br>발이 땅에 닿지 않는 이별 위를 <br>혼자 허우적대며 걷지 않게 해줘 <br>I walk on the moon in the air <br>I walk on the moon in the air <br>I walk on the moon in the air <br>I walk on the moon in the air <br>]]></content><category term="효린" label="효린"/><category term="BLUE MOON (Prod. GroovyRoom)" label="BLUE MOON (Prod. GroovyRoom)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공민지/니나노_English_Rap_Ver_Feat_플로우식_Flowsik/</id><title>공민지 - 니나노 (English Rap Ver.) (Feat. 플로우식 (Flowsik)) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%EB%AF%BC%EC%A7%80/%EB%8B%88%EB%82%98%EB%85%B8_English_Rap_Ver_Feat_%ED%94%8C%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B0%EC%8B%9D_Flowsik/" title="공민지 - 니나노 (English Rap Ver.) (Feat. 플로우식 (Flowsik)) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어머나 나 참 원 <br>처음 듣는 멜로디 <br>Turn up the lights <br>시선은 내 차지 <br>요란한 My drum <br>새로운 Fantasy <br>누가 어쩌던 <br>나는 Handle it <br>Show me show me what you got <br>오늘 밤 가식은 없지 <br>Come on come on 바로 너 <br>리듬에 맞춰서 step을 <br>흥이 나면 네버 엔딩 <br>감각적인 내 feeling <br>소스라치게 놀라긴 <br>이게 난데 <br>꿈에 그린 파라다이스 <br>멈출 수 없는 춤을 춰 <br>구름 위로 파라다이스 <br>두 손을 올리고 Let’s dance <br>너와 나의 파라다이스 <br>닿을 수 없는 곳까지 <br>하늘 위로 파라다이스 <br>두 손을 올리고 Let’s dance <br>니나노 니나노 <br>니나노 니나노 <br>니나노 니나노 <br>뭘 원하던 <br>기대 이상이지 <br>Won’t you burn it up <br>아직도 멀었니 <br>모두 내겐 yes <br>전부 끝내주지 <br>아무도 못 할 걸 <br>따라올 수 없지 <br>Show me show me what you got <br>오늘 밤 가식은 없지 <br>Come on come on 바로 너 <br>리듬에 맞춰서 Step을 <br>신이 나면 네버 엔딩 <br>창의적인 내 Feeling <br>소스라치게 놀라긴 <br>이게 난데 <br>꿈에 그린 파라다이스 <br>멈출 수 없는 춤을 춰 <br>구름 위로 파라다이스 <br>두 손을 올리고 Let’s dance <br>너와 나의 파라다이스 <br>닿을 수 없는 곳까지 <br>하늘 위로 파라다이스 <br>두 손을 올리고 Let’s dance <br>니나노 니나노 <br>니나노 니나노 <br>니나노 니나노 <br>I got that NINANO <br>make you reach high notes <br>Ghetto superstar <br>living the vida low <br>All I know you knee high <br>I’m fee-fi-fo with that <br>han flow take this game <br>both eyes closed man I’m <br>blessed signing off with the <br>checks whole squad on set <br>cross on my neck <br>going off like a jet <br>last ace lost in the decks <br>Started so I finish I'm the <br>cause and effect Yes <br>Can I see some of that <br>NINANO NINANO Yup <br>While I’m spittin that <br>figaro figaro Yah <br>Gone with the whirlwind the <br>rest gettin dizzy <br>50/50 I’m with Minzy <br>in the building getting busy <br>Come on <br>꿈에 그린 파라다이스 <br>멈출 수 없는 춤을 춰 <br>구름 위로 파라다이스 <br>두 손을 올리고 Let’s dance <br>너와 나의 파라다이스 <br>닿을 수 없는 곳까지 <br>하늘 위로 파라다이스 <br>두 손을 올리고 Let’s dance <br>]]></content><category term="공민지" label="공민지"/><category term="니나노 (English Rap Ver.) (Feat. 플로우식 (Flowsik))" label="니나노 (English Rap Ver.) (Feat. 플로우식 (Flowsik))"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공민지/Beautiful_Lie/</id><title>공민지 - Beautiful Lie - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%EB%AF%BC%EC%A7%80/Beautiful_Lie/" title="공민지 - Beautiful Lie - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우스갯소리로 넘기지 마 <br>이번만큼은 참지 못해 <br>You know 알고 있잖아 <br>거짓말에 속아준 내 맘도 <br>너를 위해 흘리던 눈물도 <br>이젠 쓸데없는 것들 <br>우두두두 떨어지는 이 비처럼 <br>뚜루루루 멀어지는 네 목소리 <br>Don’t call me baby <br>다신 찾지 마 묻지 마 <br>추억으로 살아가 <br>Don’t call me baby <br>날 잊어버려 영원히 안녕 <br>인정할게 나 항상 너만을 <br>바라보고 살아왔었어 <br>You know 더 잘 알잖아 <br>가끔 또다시 네가 생각나 <br>붙잡는다면 날 바라봐 줄까 <br>이젠 되돌릴 수 없는 것들 <br>우두두두 떨어지는 이 비처럼 <br>뚜루루루 멀어지는 네 목소리 <br>Don’t call me baby <br>다신 찾지 마 묻지 마 <br>추억으로 살아가 <br>Don’t call me baby <br>날 잊어버려 영원히 안녕 <br>가지 마 가지 마 <br>제발 내 곁을 떠나가지 마 <br>내 마음속에 남겨둔 <br>이 말 좀 들어봐 <br>시간이 멈춘다면 <br>너에게로 돌아가 <br>내 남은 사랑 모두 줄게 <br>Don’t call me baby <br>다신 찾지 마 묻지 마 <br>추억으로 살아가 <br>Don’t call me baby <br>날 잊어버려 영원히 안녕 <br>]]></content><category term="공민지" label="공민지"/><category term="Beautiful Lie" label="Beautiful Lie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공민지/Flashlight_Feat_박재범/</id><title>공민지 - Flashlight (Feat. 박재범) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%EB%AF%BC%EC%A7%80/Flashlight_Feat_%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/" title="공민지 - Flashlight (Feat. 박재범) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈이 마주친 그 순간 순간 <br>짜릿한 전율이 올라 올라 <br>이 마음은 Never ever <br>처음 느껴 Baby <br>웃음이 자꾸만 나 왠지 <br>널 생각하면 난 Yeah <br>너에게 점점 더 빠져드니까 <br>Been waiting and waiting <br>and waiting for you to make a move <br>내게 다가와 줄래 <br>이제 네 어깨에 내가 기댈 수 있게 <br>Been thinking and thinking <br>and thinking about you all day <br>내 곁에 머물러 줄래 <br>언제든 너와 함께하고 <br>있단 걸 느낄 수 있게 <br>Can you hear me 내 심장소리 <br>떨리는 나의 목소리 <br>너에게 닿을 수 있게 <br>조금 더 가까이 갈래 <br>보기만 해도 만족해 <br>오직 난 너 하나면 돼 <br>누가 뭐라든 상관없어 <br>‘Cause baby I’m always for you <br>Alright yeah 우리가 약속 잡은 <br>그날부터 Baby 지금까지 <br>얼마나 설레었는지 집 나오기 전에 <br>모자를 썼다 벗었지 <br>한 백 번이나 완벽해 <br>보이고 싶었지 Baby <br>너를 위해라면 <br>이쯤이면 나한테는 당연해 <br>Girl there ain’t no problem <br>I could do this everyday <br>고민은 다 내려놔 <br>이제부터 걱정 마 <br>나는 보스니까 다 해결해줄게 Oh <br>오 네 눈빛은 내게 말해 <br>어디서든 날 지켜주겠다고 <br>오늘도 난 Thinking and thinking <br>about you all day <br>내 곁에 머물러 줄래 <br>시간이 멈춰버린 듯이 <br>Ooh Yeah Yeah <br>Can you hear me 내 심장소리 <br>떨리는 나의 목소리 <br>너에게 닿을 수 있게 <br>조금 더 가까이 갈래 <br>보기만 해도 만족해 <br>오직 난 너 하나면 돼 <br>누가 뭐라든 상관없어 <br>‘Cause baby I’m always for you <br>Woo wah wah <br>너는 나 하나만을 비추는 Flashlight <br>어디든지 그댈 비춰줄게 <br>이젠 I can’t help falling in <br>love with you <br>you are my baby Yeah <br>Can you hear me 내 심장소리 <br>떨리는 나의 목소리 <br>너에게 닿을 수 있게 <br>조금 더 가까이 갈래 <br>보기만 해도 만족해 <br>오직 난 너 하나면 돼 <br>누가 뭐라든 상관없어 <br>‘Cause baby I’m always for you <br>]]></content><category term="공민지" label="공민지"/><category term="Flashlight (Feat. 박재범)" label="Flashlight (Feat. 박재범)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공민지/ING_알쏭달쏭/</id><title>공민지 - ING (알쏭달쏭) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%EB%AF%BC%EC%A7%80/ING_%EC%95%8C%EC%8F%AD%EB%8B%AC%EC%8F%AD/" title="공민지 - ING (알쏭달쏭) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 눈을 떠 <br>메시지를 확인 중 <br>이상하게 네 연락을 <br>자꾸 기다려 왜일까 <br>설마마마마 Yeah <br>설마마마마 Yeah <br>어설픈 사이 <br>만들고 싶지 않아 그러나 <br>내 맘은 계속 ING 쭉 진행중 <br>어머머머머 Yeah <br>어머머머머 Yeah <br>어느샌가 너를 바라볼 때면 <br>특별한 감정을 느껴 너는 모를거야 <br>Oh No No No No <br>No No No No <br>Don’t tell him <br>that I love him No No <br>심장아 나대지 좀 마 그냥 내버려 둬 <br>맘은 아직은 ING <br>Oh No No No No <br>No No No No <br>Just tell him <br>that I love him Yeah Yeah <br>그냥 확 말해 볼까 슬쩍 다가갈까 <br>내 맘은 여전히 ING <br>What’s Love Love <br>맘을 보여줘 네 맘을 보여줘 <br>진짜 사랑이란 <br>우정이란 <br>참 알쏭달쏭이야 <br>What’s Love Love <br>맘을 보여줘 네 맘을 보여줘 <br>이게 사랑이야 <br>뭐가 사랑이야 <br>참 알쏭달쏭이야 <br>또 연기해 <br>무심한 듯 힐끗 <br>어버버버 네 앞에선 <br>말도 못해 왜 이럴까 <br>설마마마마 Yeah <br>설마마마마 Yeah <br>음 잠깐 혹시 너도 내 맘과 <br>같다면 그땐 진짜 우리 어떡해 <br>어머머머머 Yeah <br>어쩜 좋아 <br>어머머머머 Yeah <br>어느샌가 너를 바라볼 때면 <br>특별한 감정을 느껴 너는 모를거야 <br>Oh No No No No <br>No No No No <br>Just tell him <br>that I love him Yeah Yeah <br>그냥 확 말해 볼까 슬쩍 다가갈까 <br>내 맘은 여전히 ING <br>What’s Love Love <br>맘을 보여줘 네 맘을 보여줘 <br>진짜 사랑이란 <br>우정이란 <br>참 알쏭달쏭이야 <br>What’s Love Love <br>맘을 보여줘 네 맘을 보여줘 <br>이게 사랑이야 <br>뭐가 사랑이야 <br>참 알쏭달쏭이야 <br>느끼는 대로 보는 그대로 솔직한 <br>대로 곁에 그대로 <br>느끼는 대로 보는 그대로 솔직한 <br>대로 나의 그대로 <br>Oh No No No No <br>No No No No <br>Just tell him <br>that I love him Yeah Yeah <br>그냥 확 말해 볼까 슬쩍 다가갈까 <br>내 맘은 여전히 ING <br>What’s Love Love <br>맘을 보여줘 네 맘을 보여줘 <br>진짜 사랑이란 <br>우정이란 <br>참 알쏭달쏭이야 <br>What’s Love Love <br>맘을 보여줘 네 맘을 보여줘 <br>이게 사랑이야 <br>뭐가 사랑이야 <br>참 알쏭달쏭이야 <br>]]></content><category term="공민지" label="공민지"/><category term="ING (알쏭달쏭)" label="ING (알쏭달쏭)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공민지/Superwoman_수퍼우먼/</id><title>공민지 - Superwoman (수퍼우먼) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%EB%AF%BC%EC%A7%80/Superwoman_%EC%88%98%ED%8D%BC%EC%9A%B0%EB%A8%BC/" title="공민지 - Superwoman (수퍼우먼) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 하루도 힘들다 <br>정신 없이 지내다 <br>걷고 걷다 본 유리 속 모습 <br>아픈 시간들은 늘고 <br>그래서 단단해지고 <br>굳세게 버틴 지난 시간 <br>넘어질 뻔한 적도 많아 <br>울고 싶을 때마다 난 다시 일어나 <br>내 곁에서 너 멀리 떠나가도 <br>I don't care I'm gonna go my way <br>약해지지 않아 두렵지도 않아 <br>뜨겁게 소리쳐 <br>I'm Superwoman <br>나약하지 않아 슬퍼하지 않아 <br>뜨겁게 소리쳐 <br>I'm Superwoman <br>Ooooooo Ooooooo Ooooooo <br>I'm Superwoman <br>Ooooooo Ooooooo Ooooooo <br>I'm Superwoman <br>오늘 하루도 한숨만 <br>쉴 틈 없이 일하다 <br>지쳐있던 거울 속 내 얼굴 <br>고민 거리들은 늘고 <br>그래도 이겨내려고 <br>당당히 버틴 많은 날들 <br>포기하려고 한 적도 많아 <br>쓰러지려고 할 때 난 다시 일어나 <br>내 곁에서 너 멀리 떠나가도 <br>I don't care I'm gonna go my way <br>약해지지 않아 두렵지도 않아 <br>뜨겁게 소리쳐 <br>I'm Superwoman <br>나약하지 않아 슬퍼하지 않아 <br>뜨겁게 소리쳐 <br>I'm Superwoman <br>Ooooooo Ooooooo Ooooooo <br>I'm Superwoman <br>Ooooooo Ooooooo Ooooooo <br>I'm Superwoman <br>깨지고 부서져도 <br>넌 그대로 눈부셔 <br>Love yourself you're so beautiful <br>깨지고 부서져도 <br>넌 그대로 눈부셔 <br>Love yourself you're so beautiful <br>약해지지 않아 두렵지도 않아 <br>뜨겁게 소리쳐 <br>I'm Superwoman <br>나약하지 않아 슬퍼하지 않아 <br>뜨겁게 소리쳐 <br>I'm Superwoman <br>넘어질 뻔한 적도 많아 <br>울고 싶을 때마다 난 다시 일어나 <br>내 곁에서 너 멀리 떠나가도 <br>I don't care I'm gonna go my way <br>Ooooooo Ooooooo Ooooooo <br>I'm Superwoman <br>]]></content><category term="공민지" label="공민지"/><category term="Superwoman (수퍼우먼)" label="Superwoman (수퍼우먼)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공민지/니나노_Feat_플로우식_Flowsik/</id><title>공민지 - 니나노 (Feat. 플로우식 (Flowsik)) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%EB%AF%BC%EC%A7%80/%EB%8B%88%EB%82%98%EB%85%B8_Feat_%ED%94%8C%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B0%EC%8B%9D_Flowsik/" title="공민지 - 니나노 (Feat. 플로우식 (Flowsik)) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어머나 나 참 원 <br>처음 듣는 멜로디 <br>Turn up the lights <br>시선은 내 차지 <br>요란한 My drum <br>새로운 Fantasy <br>누가 어쩌던 <br>나는 Handle it <br>Show me show me <br>what you got <br>오늘 밤 가식은 없지 <br>Come on come on 바로 너 <br>리듬에 맞춰서 step을 <br>흥이 나면 네버 엔딩 <br>감각적인 내 feeling <br>소스라치게 놀라긴 <br>이게 난데 <br>꿈에 그린 파라다이스 <br>멈출 수 없는 춤을 춰 <br>구름 위로 파라다이스 <br>두 손을 올리고 <br>Let's dance <br>너와 나의 파라다이스 <br>닿을 수 없는 곳까지 <br>하늘 위로 파라다이스 <br>두 손을 올리고 <br>Let's dance <br>니나노 니나노 니나노 <br>니나노 니나노 니나노 <br>뭘 원하던 <br>기대이상이지 <br>Won't you burn it up <br>아직도 멀었니 <br>모두 내겐 yes <br>전부 끝내주지 <br>아무도 못 할 걸 <br>따라올 수 없지 <br>Show me show me <br>what you got <br>오늘 밤 가식은 없지 <br>Come on come on 바로 너 <br>리듬에 맞춰서 Step을 <br>신이 나면 네버 엔딩 <br>창의적인 내 Feeling <br>소스라치게 놀라긴 <br>이게 난데 <br>꿈에 그린 파라다이스 <br>멈출 수 없는 춤을 춰 <br>구름 위로 파라다이스 <br>두 손을 올리고 <br>Let's dance <br>너와 나의 파라다이스 <br>닿을 수 없는 곳까지 <br>하늘 위로 파라다이스 <br>두 손을 올리고 <br>Let's dance <br>니나노 니나노 니나노 <br>니나노 니나노 니나노 <br>Yo Fresh out the 이발소 <br>깔끔한 치아 터져가는 지갑 속 <br>내 힙합 flow 위인들의 집합소 <br>톡 씹는 이유 지나치게 <br>바뻐 가만히 있어 <br>시작 내가 들어오면 <br>누워있던 놈들의 자세는 <br>직각으로 인사 <br>I got it from my 아버지가 <br>그러셨지 제시간에 도착했다는 <br>자체부터가 인마 지각 지각 <br>몸으로 니나노 니나노 Yah <br>입술로 Figaro Figaro Yah <br>민지 Not MC 하지만 난 진지 <br>게임오버 밥 먹자 GG Bae <br>꿈에 그린 파라다이스 <br>멈출 수 없는 춤을 춰 <br>구름 위로 파라다이스 <br>두 손을 올리고 <br>Let's dance <br>너와 나의 파라다이스 <br>닿을 수 없는 곳까지 <br>하늘 위로 파라다이스 <br>두 손을 올리고 <br>Let's dance <br>]]></content><category term="공민지" label="공민지"/><category term="니나노 (Feat. 플로우식 (Flowsik))" label="니나노 (Feat. 플로우식 (Flowsik))"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Logic/Black_SpiderMan_Feat_Damian_Lemar_Hudson/</id><title>Logic - Black SpiderMan (Feat. Damian Lemar Hudson) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Logic/Black_SpiderMan_Feat_Damian_Lemar_Hudson/" title="Logic - Black SpiderMan (Feat. Damian Lemar Hudson) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jesus Black Jesus <br>Jesus Black Jesus <br>I been feeling so down <br>I think they should know now <br>I think they should know what's up <br>That's that road I been down <br>I know how it go down <br>I know how it go now what's up <br>I feel like I don’t belong <br>I feel like my life is wrong <br>I feel like I don’t know <br>what's up <br>What's up what's up <br>Yeah yeah <br>Ayy <br>I ain’t here to pick and choose <br>I ain't here to sing the blues <br>I’m just here to spread the clues <br>I’m just here to spread the news <br>Everybody know I do <br>Listen <br>I ain’t ashamed to be white <br>I ain’t ashamed to be Black <br>I ain’t ashamed of my beautiful <br>Mexican wife as a matter of fact <br>I know you fucking with that <br>And I’m not scared of the <br>people who tell me I should be <br>Do what you love and don’t ever <br>wonder what it could be <br>Everybody from my hood <br>everybody know I’m good <br>Sometimes I’m misunderstood <br>But that's just the uneducated <br>that never related and feel <br>like I'm fading off <br>They feel like I'm fading <br>I'm right out my mind <br>Tell 'em <br>Momma don't love me <br>Daddy don't love me <br>Wonder why I drown in the bubbly <br>You could be anything you wanna be <br>'Cept the person <br>you don’t wanna be <br>Let him hate let em love <br>Wondering if everybody <br>still like this up above <br>When that push come to shove <br>Make me wanna pull up with the <br>with the gat in the glove like <br>I just wanna be free <br>Not a slave to the stereotype <br>All alone in my room <br>in the middle of the night <br>I don’t have the words <br>but my stereo might <br>I don't wanna be black <br>I don’t wanna be white <br>I just wanna be a man today <br>I don't wanna be a Christian <br>Muslim gay straight or bi <br>see you later bye <br>Not perceived by the things <br>I believe or the color of my skin <br>Or the fact I’m attracted <br>to her maybe him <br>Or the fact I’m a single mother <br>living all alone <br>Looking for a man <br>and a home to call my own <br>But I already have one <br>The only man I’ma ever need is <br>my son my son my son my son <br>Son say <br>Black is beautiful <br>Be black and proud <br>Fuck everybody hatin' on me <br>right now I’m black and proud <br>I’m just as white <br>as that Mona Lisa <br>I’m just as black <br>as my cousin Keisha <br>I’m biracial so bye Felicia <br>Praise Black Jesus <br>now call the preacher <br>Maybe Jesus was black <br>Maybe Jesus had dreads <br>Spiderman should be black <br>I vote for Glover instead <br>Glover instead <br>Like what's up <br>I vote for more and more <br>and more and more <br>and more and more <br>and more and more and more <br>I vote for so much more <br>I been feeling so down <br>I think they should know now <br>I think they should know what's up <br>That's that road I been down <br>I know how it go down <br>I know how it go now what's up <br>I feel like I don’t belong <br>I feel like my life is wrong <br>I feel like I don’t know <br>what's up <br>What's up what's up <br>Go on and let your soul glow <br>Let your soul glow <br>Glow <br>Shine and glow <br>Let it glow <br>Glow <br>Let let it <br>Black Spiderman can <br>he save a brother now <br>Black Spiderman can <br>he save a brother now <br>Yeah <br>Let your soul glow <br>Let your soul glow <br>Glow <br>Yeah <br>Ayy man <br>What's up bro <br>Spiderman should be Black <br>Yeah I mean Spiderman <br>should be Black <br>Fuck yeah <br>Yeah man <br>Black Spiderman <br>Black Superman <br>Black Santa Claus <br>Shit Black Seinfeld <br>Black Seinfeld <br>Nigga that's Martin <br>Damn you're right <br>Shit I'm fuckin' high <br>]]></content><category term="Logic" label="Logic"/><category term="Black SpiderMan (Feat. Damian Lemar Hudson)" label="Black SpiderMan (Feat. Damian Lemar Hudson)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Unbeats/Area_Steps/</id><title>Unbeats - Area Steps - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Unbeats/Area_Steps/" title="Unbeats - Area Steps - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아직도 날 설레게 하는 건 <br>펜촉의 감촉 <br>습관이 된 권태는 <br>그저 하루를 망쳐 <br>쌓인 욕구를 풀어 <br>마이크는 내 딜도 <br>두 마리 토끼를 다 잡아 <br>쾌락과 삶의 본질도 <br>조금 바쁜 삶에서 <br>이상과 현실 분배를 해 <br>시대는 변했지만 <br>아직도 난 붐뱁을 해 <br>이 더러운 바닥에서 <br>15년째 걸레질 <br>난 필요 없어 꼰대 질 앞장세워 <br>경력 보다는 실력 <br>내 가사는 거진 <br>말장난 보다는 필력 <br>날로 먹는 새끼들도 <br>내 언어로 다 익혀 <br>난 절대로 지지 않지 <br>항상 이 게임에서 이겨 <br>내게 필요한 건 <br>약간의 돈과 섹스 <br>종이와 펜슬 <br>날 부정하는 말들 신경 안 써 <br>만족해 내 삶의 방식 <br>행복이 없는 가치는 <br>그저 이 삶의 장식일 뿐 <br>어차피 나와 다른 <br>인간들은 날 비켜가 <br>변한 건 없지 <br>오늘도 어제와 똑같은 새벽 <br>All my steps for my BigDay <br>Just keep going <br>on &amp; One &amp; Only <br>검게만 느껴졌던 <br>도시의 밤을 Overcome <br>Steps for my BigDay <br>Steps for my BigDay <br>All my steps for my BigDay <br>Just keep going <br>on &amp; One &amp; Only <br>검게만 느껴졌던 <br>도시의 밤을 Overcome <br>Steps for my BigDay <br>Steps for my BigDay <br>All the caution it begins <br>even more we couldn`t digging` <br>i try to get my sight <br>true sight gone along time ago <br>how we wrong <br>how we do won`t be easy <br>I’m 26 <br>i see the limit but i faced it <br>feedback from the street <br>man got a BIGMAC <br>hit again shine`s show up <br>it`s time to be me <br>더러워진 길바닥에서도 <br>가길 바라 항상 지켜왔던 <br>내 가슴속 Ego <br>선택은 미래 기로에 서 <br>who can be me and deal <br>Ain`t got nothing <br>가진 것 없이 왔지 <br>Neighborhood doesn’t`t <br>care about my shouting <br>but their kids pay for about <br>my new tracks 깨닫길 부디 <br>도심 속 빌딩에 가려진 노을 <br>구름 위를 타 올라 타 <br>marching my days <br>초침은 나와 걸어 시간도 <br>Ain`t got nothing <br>Caught up on my BigDay <br>All my steps for my BigDay <br>Just keep going <br>on &amp; One &amp; Only <br>검게만 느껴졌던 <br>도시의 밤을 Overcome <br>Steps for my BigDay <br>Steps for my BigDay <br>All my steps for my BigDay <br>Just keep going <br>on &amp; One &amp; Only <br>검게만 느껴졌던 <br>도시의 밤을 Overcome <br>Steps for my BigDay <br>Steps for my BigDay <br>Steps for my BigDay <br>]]></content><category term="Unbeats" label="Unbeats"/><category term="Area Steps" label="Area Steps"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/14U_원포유/Good_Girl/</id><title>14U (원포유) - Good Girl - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/14U_%EC%9B%90%ED%8F%AC%EC%9C%A0/Good_Girl/" title="14U (원포유) - Good Girl - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ah bring it on girl Here we go <br>알듯 말듯 짜릿해 <br>네 맘은 그렇게 woo yaha <br>Fallin’ fallin’ 빠졌네 <br>이미 내 맘은 woo yaha <br>i’m in love with you baby <br>투명한 그 눈 <br>나를 바라 바라 봐줘요 girl <br>마주친 우리 시선 <br>심장이 터진다 bang <br>빨간 그 입술 <br>내게 말을 건다 <br>oh oh oh oh 어지러워 <br>You are my Good Girl <br>피할 수 없는 감정인걸 아찔해 <br>You are my are my Good Girl <br>너도 나와 같길 바라는걸 Good Girl <br>너를 위한 노래를 Be my girl <br>넌 듣자 마자 빠질 거야 <br>너를 위한 이 춤을 Oh my girl <br>너를 향한 고백을 받아줘요 Woo Ah <br>이 버스 안에 있는 버스 2개 <br>색깔이 같아 데스티니야 니뭐니 <br>Woo Yaha <br>I got you baby <br>모든 여자 중에 베스트 너 같아 <br>아니 제발 이건 진짜 데스티니야 해 <br>Woo Yaha <br>i’m in love with you baby <br>투명한 그 눈 <br>나를 바라 바라 봐줘요 Girl <br>마주친 우리 시선 <br>심장이 터진다 Bang <br>빨간 그 입술 <br>내게 말을 건다 <br>oh oh oh oh 어지러워 <br>You are my Good Girl <br>피할 수 없는 감정인걸 아찔해 <br>You are my are my Good Girl <br>너도 나와 같길 바라는걸 Good Girl <br>너를 위한 노래를 Be my girl <br>넌 듣자 마자 빠질 거야 <br>너를 위한 이 춤을 Oh my girl <br>너를 향한 고백을 받아줘요 Woo Ah <br>사탕처럼 상큼해 <br>초콜릿 당처럼 달달해 <br>찍어먹는 탕수육 보다 흥미로워 <br>망치 텅 맞은 기분 like 수류탄 팡 <br>A 이건 무기징역 쾅쾅쾅 <br>심장 속에 가두겠어 펌핑팡 <br>문자를 보내 시간은 뻐꾹 <br>어장관리 난 붕어 뻐끔 <br>You are my Good Girl <br>피할 수 없는 감정인걸 아찔해 <br>You are my are my Good Girl <br>너도 나와 같길 바라는걸 Good Girl <br>너를 위한 노래를 Be my girl <br>넌 듣자 마자 빠질 거야 <br>너를 위한 이 춤을 Oh my girl <br>너를 향한 고백을 받아줘요 Woo Ah <br>Good Girl <br>]]></content><category term="14U (원포유)" label="14U (원포유)"/><category term="Good Girl" label="Good Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/14U_원포유/VVV/</id><title>14U (원포유) - VVV - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/14U_%EC%9B%90%ED%8F%AC%EC%9C%A0/VVV/" title="14U (원포유) - VVV - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Very Very Very Hey GIrl <br>빠빠빠라 빰 <br>Very Very Very So Good <br>예뻐 빠라바라빠라 빰 <br>Very Very Very <br>14U Everybody <br>심장이 두근두근 하지 말야 Hey <br>너 때문에 내가 미쳐 갈지 몰라 <br>하루 종일 내가 이상해 <br>이럴 줄 몰랐어 <br>빠질 수밖에 없어 <br>너무 Very Very 예쁘잖아 <br>내꺼 할래 너 오늘부터 유혹시작 <br>내겐 너무나도 아름다운 널 <br>갖고 싶어 미치겠어 <br>너에게 빠져드는 걸 <br>Always see U <br>곁에 있을게 난 오직 You <br>너를 위해 난 <br>꽃길로 안내해줄게 따라와 <br>보여줄게 실사판 sunflower <br>내 맘의 반을 줄게 <br>With you know <br>This is <br>미치도록 네가 갖고 싶어 <br>Every Tonight <br>괜찮아 긴장하지 말고 서두르지 마 <br>왠지 이런 내 맘 들킨다면 그렇잖아 <br>솔직히 아름다워 미치겠어 <br>갖고 싶은 걸 <br>Very Very Very Hey girl <br>어서 이리와 빠라빠빠라 <br>Very Very Very 내가 <br>어쩔 줄 몰라 빠라빠라 빠라빰 <br>Very Very Very So Good <br>두근거려요 눈을 바라 볼 때면 <br>Very Very Very Right Now <br>내 손 잡아요 나랑 같이 놀아요 <br>그래 이게 나야 Sweet Girl Hey <br>넌 그래 이제 내게 빠져들 걸 <br>걱정 말고 그냥 그렇게 <br>내 손을 꼭 잡아 <br>Oh 어색한 네 미소가 <br>Very Very 예쁘잖아 <br>오늘부터 넌 내꺼하자 이제 시작 <br>텐션 up 함성 yeah <br>내 고개가 돌아가기 직전 <br>이건 내가 고백하기 위한 작전 <br>네 옆에는 내가 있게 될 거라는 비전 <br>Right 보조개가 보여 이뻐 보여 <br>Left 저기 저 사람들도 반했어 <br>정했어 너와 뚜루뚜루뚜한 사이 <br>그 사이가 돼서 우리 둘이 뚜윗뚜윗 <br>미치도록 네가 갖고 싶어 <br>Every Tonight <br>괜찮아 긴장하지 말고 서두르지 마 <br>왠지 이런 내 맘 들킨다면 그렇잖아 <br>솔직히 아름다워 미치겠어 <br>갖고 싶은 걸 <br>Very Very Very Hey Girl <br>어서 이리와 빠라빠빠라 <br>Very Very Very 내가 <br>어쩔 줄 몰라 빠라빠라 빠라빰 <br>Very Very Very <br>멈출 수가 없어 이 느낌 이대로 <br>그냥 달려가는 거야 babe <br>처음이야 왜 이러는 건지 나의 맘 <br>지금 이 순간 <br>미치도록 네가 갖고 싶어 <br>Every Tonigh <br>괜찮아 긴장하지 말고 서두르지 마 <br>왠지 이런 내 맘 들킨다면 그렇잖아 <br>솔직히 아름다워 미치겠어 <br>갖고 싶은걸 <br>Very Very Very Hey GIrl <br>어서 이리와 빠라빠빠라 <br>Very Very Very 내가 <br>어쩔 줄 몰라 빠라빠라 빠라빰 <br>Very Very Very so good <br>눈부셔 아름다워 빠라빠빠라 <br>Very Very Very right now <br>어쩔 줄 몰라 빠라빠라 빠라빰 <br>Very Very Very So Good <br>]]></content><category term="14U (원포유)" label="14U (원포유)"/><category term="VVV" label="VVV"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/잠비나이/담담히_적시고나_Inst/</id><title>잠비나이 - 담담히 적시고나 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A0%EB%B9%84%EB%82%98%EC%9D%B4/%EB%8B%B4%EB%8B%B4%ED%9E%88_%EC%A0%81%EC%8B%9C%EA%B3%A0%EB%82%98_Inst/" title="잠비나이 - 담담히 적시고나 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[긴긴날 보아도 못 보아 <br>그 향기 손에 남아 <br>고운 달빛 따라 <br>가는 비라도 되어 <br>가시는 그대 옷자락을 <br>담담히 적시고나 <br>문득 깨어보면 <br>이름 부를 사람 하나 <br>어두운 하늘 아래 <br>가만히 그대를 그리네 <br>보고파 보고파도 <br>돌아보진 마오 <br>보고파 보고파 <br>또 우리 만날 테니 <br>]]></content><category term="잠비나이" label="잠비나이"/><category term="담담히 적시고나 (Inst.)" label="담담히 적시고나 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/잠비나이/담담히_적시고나_Feat_박민희/</id><title>잠비나이 - 담담히 적시고나 (Feat. 박민희) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A0%EB%B9%84%EB%82%98%EC%9D%B4/%EB%8B%B4%EB%8B%B4%ED%9E%88_%EC%A0%81%EC%8B%9C%EA%B3%A0%EB%82%98_Feat_%EB%B0%95%EB%AF%BC%ED%9D%AC/" title="잠비나이 - 담담히 적시고나 (Feat. 박민희) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[긴긴날 보아도 못 보아 <br>그 향기 손에 남아 <br>고운 달빛 따라 <br>가는 비라도 되어 <br>가시는 그대 옷자락을 <br>담담히 적시고나 <br>문득 깨어보면 <br>이름 부를 사람 하나 <br>어두운 하늘 아래 <br>가만히 그대를 그리네 <br>보고파 보고파도 <br>돌아보진 마오 <br>보고파 보고파 <br>또 우리 만날 테니 <br>]]></content><category term="잠비나이" label="잠비나이"/><category term="담담히 적시고나 (Feat. 박민희)" label="담담히 적시고나 (Feat. 박민희)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비아_Via/Lonely_Inst/</id><title>비아 (Via) - Lonely (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%EC%95%84_Via/Lonely_Inst/" title="비아 (Via) - Lonely (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[손이 떨려서 꽉 잡았어 니가 모르게 <br>가슴이 무너져 아파도 너 모르게 <br>수 없이 박혀 있는 너 인데 <br>참 나쁜 사람을 만나 사랑한거지 <br>하늘을 보면 니가 <br>내 곁에서 아른거려 <br>이러다 숨이 막혀 나 죽겠어 <br>니가 보고 싶단 말야 제발 <br>더 멀어지지 않게 거기서 돌아봐 <br>언제나 여기 서 있을게 <br>눈물 흘려선 안되잖아 니가 볼까봐 <br>가슴이 아파 멍들어도 <br>너 모르게 수 없이 <br>박혀 있는 너 인데 <br>참 못된 사람을 만나 사랑을 한거야 <br>하늘을 보면 니가 <br>내 곁에서 아른거려 <br>이러다 숨이 막혀 나 죽겠어 <br>니가 보고 싶단 말야 제발 <br>더 멀어지지 않게 거기서 돌아봐 <br>언제나 여기 서 있을게 <br>믿을 수 없어서 두 눈으로 다 봤잖아 <br>떠났잖아 다시 돌아올 수 없겠니 <br>날 사랑하던 날처럼 <br>하늘을 보면 니가 <br>내 곁에서 아른거려 <br>이러다 나 미쳐가 죽겠어 <br>니가 보고 싶단 말야 제발 <br>더 멀어지지 않게 거기서 돌아봐 <br>언제나 여기 서 있을게 <br>]]></content><category term="비아 (Via)" label="비아 (Via)"/><category term="Lonely (Inst.)" label="Lonely (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비아_Via/Lonely/</id><title>비아 (Via) - Lonely - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%EC%95%84_Via/Lonely/" title="비아 (Via) - Lonely - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[손이 떨려서 꽉 잡았어 니가 모르게 <br>가슴이 무너져 아파도 너 모르게 <br>수 없이 박혀 있는 너 인데 <br>참 나쁜 사람을 만나 사랑한거지 <br>하늘을 보면 니가 <br>내 곁에서 아른거려 <br>이러다 숨이 막혀 나 죽겠어 <br>니가 보고 싶단 말야 제발 <br>더 멀어지지 않게 거기서 돌아봐 <br>언제나 여기 서 있을게 <br>눈물 흘려선 안되잖아 니가 볼까봐 <br>가슴이 아파 멍들어도 <br>너 모르게 수 없이 <br>박혀 있는 너 인데 <br>참 못된 사람을 만나 사랑을 한거야 <br>하늘을 보면 니가 <br>내 곁에서 아른거려 <br>이러다 숨이 막혀 나 죽겠어 <br>니가 보고 싶단 말야 제발 <br>더 멀어지지 않게 거기서 돌아봐 <br>언제나 여기 서 있을게 <br>믿을 수 없어서 두 눈으로 다 봤잖아 <br>떠났잖아 다시 돌아올 수 없겠니 <br>날 사랑하던 날처럼 <br>하늘을 보면 니가 <br>내 곁에서 아른거려 <br>이러다 나 미쳐가 죽겠어 <br>니가 보고 싶단 말야 제발 <br>더 멀어지지 않게 거기서 돌아봐 <br>언제나 여기 서 있을게 <br>]]></content><category term="비아 (Via)" label="비아 (Via)"/><category term="Lonely" label="Lonely"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/DUCKWORTH/</id><title>Kendrick Lamar - DUCKWORTH. - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/DUCKWORTH/" title="Kendrick Lamar - DUCKWORTH. - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It was always me vs the world <br>Until I found it's me vs me <br>Why why why why <br>Why why why why <br>Just remember <br>what happens on Earth <br>stays on Earth <br>We gon' put it in reverse <br>Darling I told you many times <br>And I am telling you once again <br>Just to remind you sweetheart <br>That my <br>Oh Lamar <br>Hail Mary and marijuana <br>times is hard <br>Pray with the hooligans <br>shadows all in the dark <br>Fellowship with demons <br>and relatives <br>I'm a star <br>Life is one funny mothafucka <br>A true comedian <br>you gotta love him <br>you gotta trust him <br>I might be buggin' <br>infomercials and no sleep <br>Introverted by my thoughts <br>Children listen it gets deep <br>See once upon a time inside the <br>Nickerson Garden projects <br>The object was to process <br>and digest poverty's dialect <br>Adaptation inevitable <br>gun violence crack spot <br>Federal policies raid buildings <br>and drug professionals <br>Anthony was the oldest of seven <br>Well-respected <br>calm and collected <br>Laughin' and jokin' made life easier <br>Hard times <br>Momma on crack <br>A four-year-old tellin' <br>his nanny he needed her <br>His family history <br>pimpin' and bangin' <br>He was meant to be dangerous <br>Clocked him a grip and start slangin' <br>Fifteen <br>scrapin' up his jeans <br>with quarter pieces <br>Even got some head <br>from a smoker last weekend <br>Dodged a policeman <br>workin' for his big homie <br>Small-time hustler <br>graduated to a brick on him <br>10000 dollars out of a project housing <br>that's on the daily <br>Seen his first mil twenty years old <br>had a couple of babies <br>Had a couple of shooters <br>Caught a murder case <br>fingerprints on the gun <br>they assumin' <br>But witnesses couldn't prove it <br>That was back <br>when he turned his back <br>And they killed his cousin <br>He beat the case and <br>went back to hustlin' <br>Bird-shufflin' <br>Anthony rang <br>The first in the projects <br>with the two-tone Mustang <br>That 5.0 thing <br>they say 5-0 came <br>Circlin' parking lots and parking spots <br>And hoppin' out while harrassin' <br>the corner blocks <br>Crooked cops told Anthony <br>he should kick it <br>He brushed them off <br>And walked back <br>to the Kentucky Fried Chicken <br>See at this chicken spot <br>There was a light-skinned <br>nigga that talked a lot <br>With a curly top <br>and a gap in his teeth <br>He worked the window <br>his name was Ducky <br>He came from the streets <br>the Robert Taylor Homes <br>Southside Projects <br>Chiraq the Terror Dome <br>Drove to California with a woman <br>on him and 500 dollars <br>They had a son <br>hopin' that he'd see college <br>Hustlin' on the side <br>with a nine-to-five to freak it <br>Cadillac Seville <br>he'd ride his son around <br>on weekends <br>Three-piece special with his name <br>on the shirt pocket <br>'Cross the street from the projects <br>Anthony planned to rob it <br>Stuck up the place before <br>back in '84 <br>That's when affiliation <br>was really eight gears of war <br>So many relatives tellin' us <br>sellin' us devilish works <br>Killin' us crime <br>intelligent felonious <br>Prevalent proposition with 9's <br>Ducky was well-aware <br>They robbed the manager <br>and shot a customer last year <br>He figured he'd get <br>on these niggas' good sides <br>Free chicken every time <br>Anthony posted in line <br>Two extra biscuits <br>Anthony liked him <br>And then let him slide <br>they didn't kill him <br>In fact <br>it look like they're the last to survive <br>Pay attention <br>that one decision changed <br>both of they lives <br>One curse at a time <br>Reverse the manifest <br>and good karma <br>and I'll tell you why <br>You take two strangers <br>and put 'em in random predicaments <br>give 'em a soul <br>So they can make their own <br>choices and live with it <br>Twenty years later <br>them same strangers <br>you make 'em meet again <br>Inside recording studios <br>where they reapin' their benefits <br>Then you start remindin' them <br>about that chicken incident <br>Whoever thought the greatest <br>rapper would be from coincidence <br>Because if Anthony killed Ducky <br>Top Dawg could be servin' life <br>While I grew up without a <br>father and die in a gunfight <br>So I was takin' a walk the other day <br>]]></content><category term="Kendrick Lamar" label="Kendrick Lamar"/><category term="DUCKWORTH." label="DUCKWORTH."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/GOD/</id><title>Kendrick Lamar - GOD. - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/GOD/" title="Kendrick Lamar - GOD. - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This what God feel like huh yeah <br>Laughin' to the bank like <br>A-ha huh yeah <br>Flex on swole like <br>A-ha huh yeah <br>You feel some type of way <br>then a-ha <br>Huh yeah <br>a-ha-ha a-ha-ha <br>Ever since a young man <br>All I wanted to be was a gunman <br>Shootin' up the charts <br>better run man <br>Y'all gotta see that I won man <br>Slick as El DeBarge <br>with the finger waves <br>work it JT <br>Handle bars like a fade <br>watch me work it JT <br>I'm at large <br>runnin' plays like a circuit JT <br>I'm sellin' verses Jay Z <br>watch me work it JT <br>Look look hol' up <br>Don't judge me <br>my mama caught me with a strap <br>Don't judge me <br>I was young fuckin' all the rats <br>Don't judge me <br>aimin' at your head for a stack <br>Don't judge me <br>Don't judge me <br>Now my home got a Valley peak <br>Don't judge me <br>if I press your line you a freak <br>Don't judge me <br>won't you tell a friend <br>y'all gon' see <br>This what God feel like huh yeah <br>Laughin' to the bank like <br>A-ha huh yeah <br>Flex on swole like <br>A-ha huh yeah <br>You feel some type of way <br>then a-ha <br>Huh yeah <br>a-ha-ha a-ha-ha <br>Fuck is you talkin' to <br>Aye do you know <br>who you talkin' to <br>Slide on you like fallen drapes <br>God toss full of carnivals <br>I kill 'em with kindness <br>Or I kill 'em with diamonds <br>Or I put up like fifteen hundred <br>Get yo' ass killed by the finest <br>Everything in life is a gamble <br>Nothin' in life I can't handle <br>Seen it all done it all <br>felt pain more <br>For the cars <br>I done put blood on sword <br>Everything I do is to embrace y'all <br>Everything I write is a damn <br>eight ball <br>Everything I touch is a damn <br>gold mine <br>Everything I say is from an angel <br>I don't rush shit fuck shit <br>Always your shit my shit <br>Cannonballs to ignite shit <br>Morning to the night shift <br>I'm on I ain't sorry for it <br>Ask for a piece of mine <br>you charged me for it <br>I wanna see sometimes <br>if you ignore it <br>I'm in the streets sometimes <br>and can't afford it <br>I got a bad habit <br>Levitate duckin' haters <br>Oh my My heart is rich <br>my heart is famous <br>This what God feel like <br>Huh yeah <br>this what God feel like <br>Laughin' to the bank like A-ha <br>This what God feel like <br>Huh yeah <br>this what God feel like <br>Flex on swole like A-ha <br>This what God feel like <br>Huh yeah <br>this what God feel like <br>You feel some type of way <br>then a-ha <br>This what God feel like <br>Huh yeah <br>this what God feel like <br>This what God feel like <br>]]></content><category term="Kendrick Lamar" label="Kendrick Lamar"/><category term="GOD." label="GOD."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/FEAR/</id><title>Kendrick Lamar - FEAR. - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/FEAR/" title="Kendrick Lamar - FEAR. - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't think I could find a way <br>to make it on this earth <br>What's up family <br>Yeah it's yo cousin Carl man <br>just givin' you a call man <br>I know you been havin' a lot <br>on yo mind lately <br>and I know you feel like you know <br>people ain't been prayin' for you <br>But you have to understand this man <br>that we are a cursed people <br>Deuteronomy 28 28 says <br>The Lord shall smite <br>thee with madness <br>and blindness <br>and astonishment of heart <br>See family <br>that's why you feel like you feel like <br>you got a chip on your shoulder <br>Until you finally get the memo <br>Why God <br>why God do I gotta suffer <br>Pain in my heart carry <br>burdens full of struggle <br>Why God <br>why God do I gotta bleed <br>Every stone thrown at you <br>restin' at my feet <br>Why God <br>why God do I gotta suffer <br>Earth is no more <br>won't you burn this muh'fucka <br>I don't think I could find a way <br>to make it on this earth <br>I beat yo ass <br>keep talkin' back <br>I beat yo ass <br>who bought you that <br>You stole it <br>I beat yo ass if you say that <br>game is broken <br>I beat yo ass if you jump <br>on my couch <br>I beat yo ass if you walk <br>in this house <br>With tears in your eyes <br>runnin' from Poo Poo and Prentice <br>Go back outside I beat yo ass <br>lil nigga <br>That homework better be finished <br>I beat yo ass <br>Your teachers better not be <br>bitchin' 'bout you in class <br>That pizza better not be wasted <br>you eat it all <br>That TV better not be loud <br>if you got it on <br>Them Jordans better not get dirty <br>when I just bought 'em <br>Better not hear 'bout you humpin' <br>on Keisha's daughter <br>Better not hear you got caught up <br>I beat yo ass <br>you better not run to your father <br>I beat yo ass <br>you know my patience runnin' thin <br>I got beaucoup payments to make <br>County building's on my ass <br>Tryna take my food stamps away <br>I beat yo ass if you tell them <br>social workers he live here <br>I beat yo ass if I beat yo ass <br>twice and you still here <br>Seven years old <br>think you run this house by yourself <br>Nigga <br>you gon' fear me <br>if you don't fear no one else <br>If I could smoke fear away <br>I'd roll that mothafucka up <br>And then I'd take two puffs <br>I'm high now I'm high now <br>I'm high now I'm high now <br>Life's a bitch <br>pull them panties to the side now <br>I don't think I could find a way <br>to make it on this earth <br>I'll prolly die anonymous <br>I'll prolly die with promises <br>I'll prolly die walkin' back home <br>from the candy house <br>I'll prolly die because these <br>colors are standin' out <br>I'll prolly die because I ain't know <br>Demarcus was snitchin' <br>I'll prolly die at these house parties <br>fuckin' with bitches <br>I'll prolly die from witnesses <br>leavin' me falsed accused <br>I'll prolly die from thinkin' that <br>me and your hood was cool <br>Or maybe die from pressin' the line <br>actin' too extra <br>Or maybe die <br>because these smokers <br>Are more than desperate <br>I'll prolly die from one of <br>these bats and blue badges <br>Body slammed on black and <br>white paint <br>my bones snappin' <br>Or maybe die from panic <br>or die from bein' too lax <br>Or die from waitin' on it <br>die 'cause I'm movin' too fast <br>I'll prolly die tryna buy <br>weed at the apartments <br>I'll prolly die tryna diffuse <br>two homies arguin' <br>I'll prolly die 'cause that's <br>what you do when you're 17 <br>All worries in a hurry <br>I wish I controlled things <br>If I could smoke fear away <br>I'd roll that mothafucka up <br>And then I'd take two puffs <br>I've been hungry all my life <br>I'm high now I'm high now <br>I'm high now I'm high now <br>Life's a bitch <br>pull them panties to the side now <br>Now <br>When I was 27 <br>I grew accustomed to more fear <br>Accumulated 10 times <br>over throughout the years <br>My newfound life made <br>all of me magnified <br>How many accolades do <br>I need to block denial <br>The shock value of my success <br>put bolts in me <br>All this money <br>is God playin' a joke on me <br>Is it for the moment <br>and will he see me as Job <br>Take it from me and leave me <br>worse than I was before <br>At 27 my biggest fear <br>was losin' it all <br>Scared to spend money <br>had me sleepin' from hall to hall <br>Scared to go back to Section <br>8 with my mama stressin' <br>30 shows a month and <br>I still won't buy me no Lexus <br>What is an advisor <br>Somebody that's holdin' <br>my checks <br>Just to fuck me over and <br>put my finances in debt <br>I read a case about Rihanna's <br>accountant and wondered <br>How did the bad girl feel <br>when she looked at them numbers <br>The type of shit'll <br>make me flip out <br>And just kill somethin' <br>drill somethin' <br>Get ill and fill ratchets <br>with a lil' somethin' <br>I practiced runnin' from fear <br>guess I had some good luck <br>At 27 years old <br>my biggest fear was bein' judged <br>How they look at me reflect <br>on myself my family my city <br>What they say 'bout me reveal <br>If my reputation would miss me <br>What they see from me <br>Would trickle down generations <br>in time <br>What they hear from me <br>Would make 'em highlight <br>my simplest lines <br>I'm talkin' fear <br>fear of losin' creativity <br>I'm talkin' fear <br>fear of missin' out on you and me <br>I'm talkin' fear <br>fear of losin' loyalty from pride <br>'Cause my DNA won't let me <br>involve in the light of God <br>I'm talkin' fear <br>fear that my humbleness is gone <br>I'm talkin' fear fear that love <br>ain't livin' here no more <br>I'm talkin' fear fear that it's <br>wickedness or weakness <br>Fear whatever it is <br>both is distinctive <br>Fear <br>what happens on Earth stays on Earth <br>And I can't take these <br>feelings with me <br>So hopefully they disperse <br>Within fourteen tracks <br>carried out over wax <br>Searchin' for resolutions <br>until somebody get back <br>Fear <br>what happens on Earth stays on Earth <br>And I can't take these <br>feelings with me <br>So hopefully they disperse <br>Within fourteen tracks <br>carried out over wax <br>Wonderin' if I'm livin' <br>through fear or livin' through rap <br>Damn <br>Goddamn you <br>Goddamn me <br>Goddamn us <br>Goddamn we <br>Goddamn us all <br>Verse two says you only <br>have I known of all the <br>families of the Earth <br>therefore I will punish you <br>for all your iniquities <br>So until we come back <br>to these commandments <br>until you come back <br>to these commandments <br>we're gonna feel this way <br>we're gonna be under this curse <br>Because he said <br>he's gonna punish us <br>the so-called Blacks Hispanics <br>and Native American Indians <br>are the true children of Israel <br>We are the Israelites <br>according to the Bible <br>The children of Israel <br>he's gonna punish us <br>for our iniquities <br>for our disobedience <br>because we chose to follow <br>other gods that aren't his son <br>so the Lord thy God chasten thee <br>So just like you chasten your own son <br>he's gonna chastise you <br>because he loves you <br>So that's why we get chastised <br>that's why we're <br>in the position we're in <br>Until we come back to these laws <br>statutes and commandments <br>and do what the Lord said <br>these curses are gonna be upon us <br>We're gonna be at a lower state <br>in this life that we live here in today <br>in the United States of America <br>I love you son <br>and I pray for you <br>God bless you shalom <br>]]></content><category term="Kendrick Lamar" label="Kendrick Lamar"/><category term="FEAR." label="FEAR."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/XXX_Feat_U2/</id><title>Kendrick Lamar - XXX. (Feat. U2) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:57:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:57:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/XXX_Feat_U2/" title="Kendrick Lamar - XXX. (Feat. U2) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[America <br>God bless you if it's good to you <br>America please take my hand <br>Can you help me underst <br>New Kung Fu Kenny <br>Throw a steak off the ark <br>To a pool full of sharks <br>he'll take it <br>Leave him in the wilderness <br>With a sworn nemesis <br>he'll make it <br>Take the gratitude from him <br>I bet he'll show you somethin' whoa <br>I'll chip a nigga little bit of nothin' <br>I'll chip a nigga little bit of nothin' <br>I'll chip a nigga little bit of nothin' <br>I'll chip a nigga <br>then throw the blower in his lap <br>Walk myself to the court like <br>Bitch I did that X-rated <br>Johnny don't wanna <br>go to school no mo' <br>no mo' <br>Johnny said books <br>ain't cool no mo' <br>Johnny wanna be a rapper <br>like his big cousin <br>Johnny caught a body <br>yesterday out hustlin' <br>God bless America <br>you know we all love him <br>Yesterday I got a call like <br>from my dog like 101 <br>Said they killed his only son <br>because of insufficient funds <br>He was sobbin' he was mobbin' <br>way belligerent and drunk <br>Talkin' out his head <br>philosphin' on <br>what the Lord had done <br>He said K-Dot can you pray for me <br>It's been a fucked up day for me <br>I know that you anointed <br>show me how to overcome <br>He was lookin' for some closure <br>Hopin' I could bring him closer <br>To the spiritual <br>my spirit do no better <br>but I told him <br>I can't sugarcoat the answer for you <br>this is how I feel <br>If somebody kill my son <br>that mean somebody gettin' killed <br>Tell me what you do for love <br>loyalty and passion of <br>All the memories collected <br>moments you could never touch <br>I'll wait in front a niggas spot <br>and watch him hit his block <br>I'll catch a nigga leavin' service <br>if that's all I got <br>I'll chip a nigga <br>then throw the blower in his lap <br>Walk myself to the court like <br>Bitch I did that <br>Ain't no Black Power when your baby <br>killed by a coward <br>I can't even keep the peace <br>don't you fuck with one of ours <br>It be murder in the street <br>it be bodies in the hour <br>Ghetto bird be on the street <br>paramedics on the dial <br>Let somebody touch my mama <br>Touch my sister <br>touch my woman <br>Touch my daddy <br>touch my niece <br>Touch my nephew <br>touch my brother <br>You should chip a nigga <br>then throw the blower in his lap <br>Matter fact <br>I'm 'bout to speak at this convention <br>Call you back <br>Alright kids <br>we're gonna talk about gun control <br>Pray for me Damn <br>It's not a place <br>This country is to be a sound <br>of drum and bass <br>You close your eyes to look around <br>Hail Mary Jesus and Joseph <br>The great American flag <br>Is wrapped and dragged <br>with explosives <br>Compulsive disorder <br>sons and daughters <br>Barricaded blocks and borders <br>Look what you taught us <br>It's murder on my street <br>your street back streets <br>Wall Street corporate offices <br>Banks employees and bosses with <br>Homicidal thoughts <br>Donald Trump's in office <br>We lost Barack and promised <br>to never doubt him again <br>But is America honest <br>or do we bask in sin <br>Pass the gin <br>I mix it with American blood <br>Then bash him in you Crippin' <br>or you married to blood <br>I'll ask again oops accident <br>It's nasty when you set us up <br>Then roll the dice <br>then bet us up <br>You overnight the big rifles <br>then tell Fox to be scared of us <br>Gang members or terrorists <br>et cetera et cetera <br>America's reflections of me <br>that's what a mirror does <br>It's not a place <br>This country is to be a sound <br>of drum and bass <br>You close your eyes to look ar <br>]]></content><category term="Kendrick Lamar" label="Kendrick Lamar"/><category term="XXX. (Feat. U2)" label="XXX. (Feat. U2)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/LOVE_Feat_Zacari/</id><title>Kendrick Lamar - LOVE. (Feat. Zacari) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/LOVE_Feat_Zacari/" title="Kendrick Lamar - LOVE. (Feat. Zacari) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Damn love or lust <br>Damn all of us <br>Give me a run for my money <br>There is nobody <br>no one to outrun me <br>Another world premier <br>So give me a run for my money <br>Sippin' bubbly feelin’ lovely <br>livin' lovely <br>Just love me <br>I wanna be with you ayy <br>I wanna be with <br>I wanna be with you ayy <br>I wanna be with <br>I wanna be with you <br>If I didn't ride blade on curb <br>would you still love me <br>If I minimize my net worth <br>would you still love me <br>Keep it a hundred <br>I’d rather you trust me <br>than to love me <br>Keep it a whole one hund' <br>don't got you I got nothin' <br>Ayy I got somethin' <br>Hol' up we gon' function <br>no assumptions <br>Feelin' like Tyson with it <br>Knock it out twice I’m with it <br>Only for the night I’m kiddin' <br>Only for life <br>you’re a homie for life <br>You're a homie for life <br>let's get it <br>Hit that shoulder lean <br>I know what comin' over mean <br>Backstroke oversea <br>I know what you need <br>Already on ten <br>our money come in <br>All feeling go out <br>this feeling don’t drought <br>This party won't end <br>If I didn't ride blade on curb <br>would you still love me <br>If I minimize my net worth <br>would you still love me <br>Keep it a hundred <br>I'd rather you trust me <br>than to love me <br>Keep it a whole one hund' <br>don't got you I got nothin' <br>Give me a run for my money <br>There is nobody <br>no one to outrun me <br>So give me a run for my money <br>Sippin' bubbly feelin' lovely <br>livin' lovely <br>Just love me <br>I wanna be with you ayy <br>I wanna be with <br>I wanna be with you ayy <br>I wanna be with <br>I wanna be with you <br>I'm on the way <br>We ain't got no time to waste <br>Poppin' your gum on the way <br>Am I in the way <br>I don't wan' pressure you none <br>I want your blessing today <br>Oh by the way <br>open the door by the way <br>Told you that I'm on the way <br>I'm on the way <br>I know connection is vague <br>Pick up the phone for me babe <br>Damn it we jammin' <br>Bad attitude from yo' nanny <br>Curves and your hips <br>from yo' mammy <br>Remember Gardena <br>I took the studio camry <br>I know Top will be mad at me <br>I had to do it I want your body <br>your music <br>I bought the big one to prove it <br>Look what you made <br>Told you that I'm on the way <br>I'm like an exit away yep <br>If I didn't ride blade on curb <br>would you still love me <br>If I minimize my net worth <br>would you still love me <br>Keep it a hundred <br>I'd rather you trust me <br>than to love me <br>Keep it a whole one hund' <br>don't got you I got nothin' <br>Give me a run for my money <br>There is nobody <br>no one to outrun me <br>So give me a run for my money <br>Sippin' bubbly feelin' lovely <br>livin' lovely <br>Just love me <br>I wanna be with you ayy <br>I wanna be with <br>I wanna be with you ayy <br>I wanna be with <br>I wanna be with you <br>]]></content><category term="Kendrick Lamar" label="Kendrick Lamar"/><category term="LOVE. (Feat. Zacari)" label="LOVE. (Feat. Zacari)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/LUST/</id><title>Kendrick Lamar - LUST. - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/LUST/" title="Kendrick Lamar - LUST. - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I need some water <br>Somethin' came over me <br>Way too hot to simmer down <br>Might as well overheat <br>Too close to comfort <br>As blood rush my favorite vein <br>Heartbeat racin' like a junkie's <br>I just need you to want me <br>Am I askin' too much <br>Let me put the head in <br>Ooh I don't want more than that <br>Girl I respect the get <br>I promise just a touch <br>Let me put the head in <br>If it's okay <br>She said It's okay <br>Yeah I need everybody's <br>motherfuckin' hands up right now <br>I need everybody's motherfuckin' <br>Door and his Nike Air Rattles <br>Rush the fire exit <br>no time for battles <br>Well I I never expected <br>This that new shit <br>This that new new shit <br>Wake up in the mornin' <br>Thinkin' 'bout money <br>kick your feet up <br>Watch you a comedy take a shit <br>then roll some weed up <br>Go hit you a lick <br>go fuck on a bitch <br>Don't go to work today <br>cop you a fit <br>Or maybe some kicks <br>and make you <br>Door in his Nike Air Rattles <br>Rush the fire exit <br>no time for battles <br>Well I I never expected <br>Wake up in the mornin' <br>Thinkin' 'bout money <br>kick your feet up <br>Watch you a comedy hol' up <br>Wake up in the mornin' <br>Thinkin' 'bout money <br>kick your feet up <br>Watch you a comedy take a shit <br>then roll some weed up <br>Go hit you a lick <br>go fuck on a bitch <br>don't go to work today <br>Cop you a fit or maybe some <br>kicks and make it work today <br>Hang with your homies <br>stunt on your baby mama <br>Sip some lean go get a pistol <br>shoot out the window <br>Bet your favorite team <br>play you some Madden <br>Go to the club or your mama house <br>Whatever you doin' <br>just make it count <br>I need some water <br>Wake up in the mornin' <br>Thinkin' 'bout money <br>kick your feet up <br>Hop in the shower <br>put on your makeup <br>lace your weave up <br>Touch on yourself <br>call up your nigga <br>tell him he ain't shit <br>Credit card scam <br>get you a Visa <br>make him pay your rent <br>Hop on the 'Gram <br>flex on the bitches <br>that be hatin' on you <br>Pop you a pill <br>call up your bitches <br>have 'em waitin' on you <br>Go to the club <br>have you some fun <br>make that ass bounce <br>It's whatever just make it count <br>I need some water <br>Somethin' came over me <br>Way too hot to simmer down <br>Might as well overheat <br>Too close to comfort <br>As blood rush my favorite vein <br>Heartbeat racin' like a junkie's <br>I just need you to want me <br>Am I askin' too much <br>Let me put the head in <br>Ooh I don't want more than that <br>Girl I respect the get <br>I promise just a touch <br>Let me put the head in <br>If it's okay <br>She said It's okay <br>I wake in the mornin' <br>my head spinnin' <br>from the last night <br>Both in the trance <br>feelings I did what a fast life <br>Manager called <br>the lobby called <br>it's 11:30 <br>Did this before <br>promised myself <br>I'd be a hour early <br>Room full of clothes <br>bag full of money <br>call it loose change <br>Fumbled my jewelry 100k <br>I lost a new chain <br>Hop on the bird <br>hit the next city for another M <br>Take me a nap and do it again <br>We all woke up <br>tryna tune to the daily news <br>Lookin' for confirmation <br>hopin' election wasn't true <br>All of us worried <br>all of us buried <br>and our feeling's deep <br>None of us married <br>to his proposal <br>make us feel cheap <br>Still and sad <br>distraught and mad <br>tell the neighbor 'bout it <br>Bet they agree <br>parade the streets <br>with your voice proudly <br>Time passin' things change <br>Revertin' back <br>to our daily programs <br>stuck in our ways Lust <br>Lately I feel like I been <br>lustin' over the fame <br>Lately we lust on the same <br>routine of shame <br>Lately lately lately <br>my lust been hidin' Lately <br>Lately it’s all contradiction <br>Lately I’m not here <br>Lately I lust over self <br>Lust turn into fear <br>Lately in James 4:4 says <br>Friend of the world <br>is enemy of the Lord <br>Brace yourself lust is all yours <br>I need some water <br>Somethin' came over me <br>Way too high to simmer down <br>Might as well overheat <br>Too close to comfort <br>As blood rush my favorite vein <br>Heartbeat racin' like a junkie's <br>I just need you to want me <br>Am I askin' too much <br>Let me put the head in <br>Ooh I don't want more than that <br>Girl I respect the get <br>I promise just a touch <br>Let me put the head in <br>If it's okay <br>She said It's okay <br>]]></content><category term="Kendrick Lamar" label="Kendrick Lamar"/><category term="LUST." label="LUST."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/Youre_Gonna_Live_Forever_in_Me/</id><title>John Mayer - You`re Gonna Live Forever in Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/Youre_Gonna_Live_Forever_in_Me/" title="John Mayer - You`re Gonna Live Forever in Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A great big bang and dinosaurs <br>Fiery raining meteors <br>It all ends unfortunately <br>But you're gonna live forever in me <br>I guarantee, just wait and see <br>Parts of me were made by you <br>And planets keep their distance too <br>The moon's got a grip on the sea <br>And you're gonna live forever in me <br>I guarantee, it's your destiny <br>Life is full of sweet mistakes <br>And love's an honest one to make <br>Time leaves no fruit on the tree <br>But you're gonna live forever in me <br>I guarantee, it's just meant to be <br>And when the pastor asks the pews <br>For reasons he can't marry you <br>I'll keep my word in my seat <br>But you're gonna live forever in me <br>I guarantee, just wait and see]]></content><category term="John Mayer" label="John Mayer"/><category term="You`re Gonna Live Forever in Me" label="You`re Gonna Live Forever in Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/PRIDE/</id><title>Kendrick Lamar - PRIDE. - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/PRIDE/" title="Kendrick Lamar - PRIDE. - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love's gonna get you killed <br>But pride’s gonna be the death <br>of you and you and me <br>And you and you and you and me <br>And you and you and you and me <br>And you and you and you and me <br>and <br>It wasn't all to share but there <br>In another life <br>I surely was there <br>It wasn't all to share but there <br>I care I care <br>Hell raising wheel chasing <br>new worldy possessions <br>Flesh making spirit breaking <br>which one would you lessen <br>The better part the human heart <br>You love ’em or dissect 'em <br>Happiness or flashiness <br>How do you serve the question <br>See in the perfect world <br>I would be perfect world <br>I don't trust people enough <br>beyond they surface world <br>I don't love people enough <br>to put my faith in men <br>I put my faith in these lyrics <br>hoping I make amend <br>I understand I ain't perfect <br>I probably won't come around <br>This time I might put you down <br>Last time I ain't give a fuck <br>I still feel the same now <br>My feelings might go numb <br>you're dealing with cold thumb <br>I’m willing to give up a leg <br>and arm and show empathy from <br>Pity parties and functions <br>and you and yours <br>A perfect world <br>you probably live another 24 <br>I can’t fake humble just <br>'cause your ass is insecure <br>I can’t fake humble just <br>'cause your ass is insecure <br>It wasn't all to share but there <br>In another life <br>I surely was there <br>It wasn't all to share but there <br>I care I care <br>Maybe I wasn’t there <br>Maybe I wasn't there <br>Maybe I wasn't there <br>Maybe I wasn't there <br>Now in a perfect world <br>I probably won't be insensitive <br>Cold as December <br>but never remember <br>what Winter did <br>I wouldn't blame you <br>for mistakes I made <br>or the bed I laid <br>Seems like I point the finger <br>just to make a point nowadays <br>Smiles and cold stares <br>the temperature goes there <br>Indigenous disposition <br>feel like we belong here <br>I know the walls <br>they can listen <br>I wish they could talk back <br>The hurt becomes repetition <br>the love almost lost that <br>Sick venom in men and women <br>overcome with pride <br>A perfect world is never <br>perfect only filled with lies <br>Promises are broken and more <br>resentment come alive <br>Race barriers make inferior <br>of you and I <br>See in a perfect world <br>I'll choose faith over riches <br>I'll choose work over bitches <br>I'll make schools out of prison <br>I'll take all the religions <br>and put 'em all in one service <br>Just to tell 'em we ain't shit <br>but He's been perfect world <br>It wasn't all to share but there <br>In another life <br>I surely was there <br>It wasn't all to share but there <br>I care I care <br>Maybe I wasn't there <br>Maybe I wasn't there <br>Maybe I wasn't there <br>Maybe I wasn't there <br>]]></content><category term="Kendrick Lamar" label="Kendrick Lamar"/><category term="PRIDE." label="PRIDE."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/Rosie/</id><title>John Mayer - Rosie - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/Rosie/" title="John Mayer - Rosie - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Rosie <br>Come down and get the door for me <br>I'm drunk again, remember when we used to be? <br>Rosie <br>I know you said no more for me <br>But that was all before this dream that just came to me <br>Don't leave me here <br>Under the January rain <br>Come let me in <br>Take my heart by the hand <br>And lead me back to your room <br>And sing me your tune <br>Rosie <br>You don't have to hide his things <br>I'm fine with all the sorrow that tomorrow brings <br>Whoa-oh-oh, Rosie <br>Don't you know my love is true <br>'Perdon' and 'lo siento', see, <br>I learned those words for you <br>Don't leave me here <br>Under the January rain <br>Come let me in <br>Take my heart by the hand <br>And lead me back to your room <br>And sing me your tune <br>Don't leave me here <br>Under the January rain <br>Come let me in <br>Take my heart by the hand <br>And lead me back to your room <br>And sing me your tune]]></content><category term="John Mayer" label="John Mayer"/><category term="Rosie" label="Rosie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/LOYALTY_Feat_Rihanna/</id><title>Kendrick Lamar - LOYALTY. (Feat. Rihanna) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/LOYALTY_Feat_Rihanna/" title="Kendrick Lamar - LOYALTY. (Feat. Rihanna) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I said I'm geeked <br>and I’m fired up fired fire <br>All I want tonight is <br>just to get high up <br>high high high <br>Girl you look so good <br>it's to die for die for <br>Ooh that pussy good <br>it's to die for on fire <br>It’s a secret society <br>All we ask is trust <br>All we ask is trust <br>All we got is us <br>Loyalty loyalty loyalty <br>Loyalty loyalty loyalty <br>Kung Fu Kenny now <br>My resume is real enough <br>for two millenniums <br>A better way to make a wave <br>stop defendin' them <br>I meditate and moderate <br>all of my wins again <br>I'm hangin' on the fence again <br>I'm always on your mind <br>I put my lyric <br>and my lifeline on the line <br>And ain't no limit <br>when I might shine might grind <br>You rollin' with it <br>at the right time right now <br>Only for the dollar sign <br>Bad gyal RiRi now <br>Swerve swerve swerve <br>swerve deeper now <br>On your pulse like it's EDM <br>Gas in the bitch <br>like it’s premium <br>Haul ass on a bitch <br>all in the fast lane <br>Been a bad bitch way <br>before any cash came <br>I’m established <br>Hundred carats on my name <br>Run the atlas <br>I'm a natural I’m alright <br>I'm a savage I'm a asshole <br>I'm a king <br>Shimmy yeah shimmy yeah <br>shimmy yeah rock yeah <br>You can tell your nigga <br>he can meet me outside yeah <br>You can babysit him <br>when I leave him outside <br>Ain’t no other love <br>like the one I know <br>I done been down <br>so long I slowed <br>I done came down <br>so hard I slowed <br>I don't sleep forever <br>all a real nigga want <br>I said I'm geeked <br>and I'm fired up fired fire <br>All I want tonight is <br>just to get high up yeah <br>All I want is all I want is <br>Loyalty loyalty loyalty <br>Loyalty loyalty loyalty <br>10 4 no switchin' sides <br>Feel somethin' wrong <br>You actin' shifty you don't ride <br>With me no more I need <br>Loyalty loyalty loyalty <br>Loyalty loyalty loyalty <br>Tell me who you loyal to <br>Is it money Is it fame <br>Is it weed Is it drink <br>Is it comin' down <br>with the loud pipes <br>and the rain <br>Big chillin' only <br>for the power in your name <br>Tell me who you loyal to <br>Is it love for the streets <br>when the lights get dark <br>Is it unconditional <br>when the 'Rari don't start <br>Tell me when your loyalty <br>is comin' from the heart <br>Tell me who you loyal to <br>Do it start with your woman <br>or your man Mmm <br>Do it end with your family <br>and friends Mmm <br>Or you're loyal to yourself <br>in advance <br>I said tell me <br>who you loyal to <br>Is it anybody <br>that you would lie for <br>Anybody you would slide for <br>Anybody you would die for <br>That's what God for <br>I said I'm geeked <br>and I'm fired up fired fire <br>All I want tonight is <br>just to get high up <br>All I want is all I want is <br>Loyalty loyalty loyalty <br>Loyalty loyalty loyalty <br>10 4 no switchin' sides <br>Feel somethin' wrong <br>You actin' shifty you don't ride <br>With me no more I need <br>Loyalty loyalty loyalty <br>Loyalty loyalty loyalty <br>It's so hard to be humble <br>It's so hard to be <br>Lord knows I'm tryin' <br>Lord knows I'm dyin' baby <br>]]></content><category term="Kendrick Lamar" label="Kendrick Lamar"/><category term="LOYALTY. (Feat. Rihanna)" label="LOYALTY. (Feat. Rihanna)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/Never_on_the_Day_You_Leave/</id><title>John Mayer - Never on the Day You Leave - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/Never_on_the_Day_You_Leave/" title="John Mayer - Never on the Day You Leave - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No it's never on the day you leave <br>That you wonder what you still believe in <br>And you can't remember why you said goodbye <br>You'll hear an old familiar sound <br>and hope it's her when you turn around <br>But never, never on the day you leave <br>Love grows in the time it's been <br>Since you last heard her sing <br>She'll cut her hair and move somewhere <br>She don't owe you anything <br>No it's never on the day you leave <br>You can tell how it's gonna be <br>To watch a girl become a ghost before your eyes <br>You wish you'd given her one more kiss <br>To put away for a night like this <br>But never, never on the day you leave <br>Love grows in the time it's been <br>Since you last held her hand <br>She'll fight for you like hell <br>Then force herself to like some other man <br>No it's never on the day you leave <br>That you remember Christmas Eve <br>And all the things you miss about her crazy family <br>You'll know how lonely it is to see <br>a little drug store Christmas tree <br>But never, never on the day you leave <br>No never, never on the day you leave <br>So maybe it'd be better off to write her <br>And leave a little note right there beside her <br>That says maybe we're not perfect <br>But I'll be damned if I ever leave <br>Damned if I ever leave <br>Damned if I ever leave]]></content><category term="John Mayer" label="John Mayer"/><category term="Never on the Day You Leave" label="Never on the Day You Leave"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/Moving_On_and_Getting_Over/</id><title>John Mayer - Moving On and Getting Over - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/Moving_On_and_Getting_Over/" title="John Mayer - Moving On and Getting Over - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Moving on and getting over <br>Are not the same, it seems to me <br>Cause you've been gone, I'm growing older <br>But I still can't seem to get you off my mind <br>And I do believe I feel you all the time <br>Moving on and getting over <br>Are not the friends they used to be <br>It's been so long since I got to hold you <br>But I still can't seem to get you off my mind <br>And I do believe I feel you all the time, all the time <br>Tell me I can have the fact you've loved me to hold onto <br>Tell me I can keep the door cracked open, to let light through <br>For all my running, I can understand <br>I'm one text away from being back again <br>But I'm moving on and I'm getting over <br>I'm-a getting over, I'm getting over <br>I got to get over <br>Moving on and getting over <br>It's been so long; it just goes to show you <br>That I still can't seem to get you off my mind (get you off my mind) <br>And I sure would like to see you one more time <br>It's taken me so long just to say "so long" <br>Maybe it's all wrong, but I'm moving on <br>I'm gonna get a new girl <br>It's something I can do, girl <br>To try to get me through, girl <br>Cause I'm moving on <br>I'm moving on <br>And I'm moving on <br>I'm moving on <br>And I'm moving on <br>Consider me as good as gone <br>Cause I'm moving on <br>I'm moving on <br>Moving on, baby <br>Moving on <br>Moving on]]></content><category term="John Mayer" label="John Mayer"/><category term="Moving On and Getting Over" label="Moving On and Getting Over"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/FEEL/</id><title>Kendrick Lamar - FEEL. - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/FEEL/" title="Kendrick Lamar - FEEL. - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ain't nobody prayin' for me <br>Ain't nobody prayin' for me <br>Ain't nobody prayin' for me <br>Ain't nobody prayin' for me <br>I feel like a chip on my shoulders <br>I feel like I'm losin' my focus <br>I feel like I'm losin' my patience <br>I feel like my thoughts <br>in the basement <br>Feel like <br>I feel like you're miseducated <br>Feel like I don't wanna <br>be bothered <br>I feel like you may be the problem <br>I feel like it ain't no <br>tomorrow fuck the world <br>The world is endin' <br>I'm done pretendin' <br>And fuck you if you get offended <br>I feel like friends been overrated <br>I feel like the family been fakin' <br>I feel like the feelings <br>are changin' <br>Feel like my daughter <br>compromised and jaded <br>Feel like you wanna <br>scrutinize how I made it <br>Feel like I ain't feelin' you all <br>Feel like removin' myself <br>no feelings involved <br>I feel for you I've been <br>in the field for you <br>It's real for you right <br>Shit I feel like <br>Ain't nobody prayin' for me <br>Ain't nobody prayin' for me <br>Ain't nobody prayin' for me <br>Ain't nobody prayin' <br>I feel niggas been out of pocket <br>I feel niggas tappin' they pockets <br>I feel like debating on <br>who the greatest can stop it <br>I am legend I feel like <br>all of y'all is peasants <br>I feel like all <br>of y'all is desperate <br>I feel like all it take <br>is a second to feel like <br>Mike Jordan <br>whenever holdin' a real mic <br>I ain't feelin' your presence <br>Feel like I'ma learn you a lesson <br>Feel like only me <br>and the music though <br>I feel like your feelin' <br>ain't mutual <br>I feel like the enemy <br>you should know <br>Feel like the feelin' of no hope <br>The feelin' of bad dope <br>A quarter ounce manipulated <br>from soap <br>The feelin' <br>the feelin' of false freedom <br>I'll force-feed 'em the poison <br>that fill 'em up in the prison <br>I feel like it's just me <br>Look I feel like I can't breathe <br>Look I feel like I can't sleep <br>Look I feel heartless <br>often off this <br>Feelin' of fallin' <br>of fallin' apart with <br>Darkest hours lost it <br>Fillin' the void of bein' <br>employed with ballin' <br>Streets is talkin' <br>fill in the blanks with coffins <br>Fill up the banks with dollars <br>Fill up the graves with fathers <br>Fill up the babies with bullshit <br>Internet blogs and pulpit <br>fill 'em with gossip <br>I feel like this gotta <br>be the feelin' what 'Pac was <br>The feelin' of an <br>apocalypse happenin' <br>But nothin' is awkward <br>the feelin' won't prosper <br>The feelin' is toxic <br>I feel like I'm boxin' demons <br>Monsters false prophets schemin' <br>Sponsors industry promises <br>Niggas bitches honkies <br>crackers Compton <br>Church religion token blacks <br>and bondage <br>Lawsuit visits subpoena <br>served in concert <br>Fuck your feelings <br>I mean this for imposters <br>I can feel it <br>the phoenix sure to watch us <br>I can feel it <br>the dream is more than process <br>I can put a regime <br>that forms a Loch Ness <br>I can feel it the scream <br>that haunts our logic <br>I feel like say somethin' <br>I feel like take somethin' <br>I feel like skatin' off <br>I feel like waitin' for 'em <br>Maybe it's too late for 'em <br>I feel like the whole world <br>want me to pray for 'em <br>But who the fuck prayin' for me <br>Ain't nobody prayin' for me <br>Who prayin' for me <br>Ain't nobody prayin' <br>]]></content><category term="Kendrick Lamar" label="Kendrick Lamar"/><category term="FEEL." label="FEEL."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/ELEMENT/</id><title>Kendrick Lamar - ELEMENT. - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/ELEMENT/" title="Kendrick Lamar - ELEMENT. - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[New Kung Fu Kenny <br>Ain't nobody prayin' for me <br>Y'all know what happens <br>on Earth stays on Earth <br>Here we go <br>I don't give a fuck <br>I don't give a fuck <br>I don't give a I don't give a <br>I don't give a fuck <br>I'm willin' to die for this shit <br>I done cried for this shit <br>might take a life for this shit <br>Put the Bible down <br>and go eye for an eye <br>for this shit <br>D O T my enemy <br>won't catch a vibe <br>for this shit ayy <br>I been stomped out <br>in front of my mama <br>My daddy commissary <br>made it to commas <br>Bitch all my grandmas dead <br>So ain't nobody prayin' for me <br>I'm on your head ayy <br>Thirty millions later <br>know the feds watchin' <br>Auntie on my telegram <br>like Be cautious <br>I be hangin' out at Tam's <br>I be on Stockton <br>I don't do it for the 'Gram <br>I do it for Compton <br>I'm willin' to die <br>for this shit nigga <br>I'll take your fuckin' life <br>for this shit nigga <br>We ain't goin' back to broke <br>family sellin' dope <br>That's why you maney ass <br>rap niggas better know <br>If I gotta slap a pussy ass nigga <br>I'ma make it look sexy <br>If I gotta go hard on a bitch <br>I'ma make it look sexy <br>I pull up hop out air out <br>made it look sexy <br>They won't take me out my element <br>Nah take me out my element <br>I'm allergic to a bitch nigga ayy <br>An imaginary rich nigga ayy <br>Seven figures hoe <br>that slimmer <br>than my bitch figure ayy <br>Goin' digital and physical <br>on all y'all ayy <br>Bunch of criminals <br>and money in my phone calls ayy <br>We okay we let the A1 fly <br>Relocate jump on the same G5 <br>Checkin' for me heavy <br>'cause I go yeah I go yeah <br>They never been ready yeah <br>I know yeah know yeah <br>100K spread across the floor <br>'cross the floor yeah <br>None of y'all fuckin' <br>with the flow yeah the flow yeah <br>Years in the makin' <br>and don't y'all mistake it <br>I got 'em by a landslide <br>we talkin' about races <br>You know this'll never be a tie <br>just look at their laces <br>You know careers take off <br>just gotta be patient <br>Mr One through Five <br>that's the only logic <br>Fake my death go to Cuba <br>that's the only option <br>If I gotta slap a pussy ass nigga <br>I'ma make it look sexy <br>If I gotta go hard on a bitch <br>I'ma make it look sexy <br>I pull up hop out air out <br>made it look sexy <br>They won't take me out my element <br>Nah take me out my element <br>Damned if I do if I don't yuhhh <br>Goddamn us all if you won't <br>yuhhh <br>Damn damn damn <br>it's a goddamn shame <br>You ain't frontline <br>get out the goddamn way <br>Niggas thought they wasn't <br>gonna see me huh <br>Niggas thought <br>that K-Dot real life <br>Was the same life <br>they see on TV huh <br>Niggas wanna flex on me <br>and be in LA for free huh <br>Next time they hit the 10 freeway <br>we need receipt huh <br>'Cause most of y'all ain't real <br>Most of y'all gon' squeal <br>Most of y'all just envy <br>but jealousy get you killed <br>Most of y'all throw rocks <br>and try to hide your hand <br>Just say his name <br>and I promise <br>that you'll see Candyman <br>Because it's all in your eyes <br>most of y'all tell lies <br>Most of y'all don't fade <br>most of y'all been advised <br>Last LP I tried <br>to lift the black artists <br>But it's a difference <br>between black artists <br>and wack artists <br>If I gotta slap a pussy ass nigga <br>I'ma make it look sexy <br>It's the one and only <br>the world's greatest <br>the Kid Capri <br>If I gotta go hard on a bitch <br>I'ma make it look sexy <br>I pull up hop out air out <br>made it look sexy <br>They won't take me out my element <br>Nah take me out my element <br>]]></content><category term="Kendrick Lamar" label="Kendrick Lamar"/><category term="ELEMENT." label="ELEMENT."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/Changing/</id><title>John Mayer - Changing - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/Changing/" title="John Mayer - Changing - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I am not done changing <br>Out on the run, changing <br>I may be old and I may be young <br>But I am not done changing <br>I met me someone changing <br>We had some fun changing <br>Sometimes I wonder if she'll be the one <br>When I am done changing <br>Some of us stopped running <br>Some of us went home <br>Some of us don’t got one <br>So we'll build one of our own <br>Friends behind their fences <br>Looking at me strange <br>Wondering when <br>I’m gonna come to my senses <br>But I'm still changing <br>And I can’t change my ways <br>I see the sky changing <br>Reminds me of my changing <br>Wish I could tie me a rope 'round the sun <br>'Cause I am not done changing <br>Time's been talking to me <br>Whispering in my ear <br>Saying “Follow your heart <br>'Til it tears you apart” <br>But hearts keep changing <br>Hearts keep changing <br>Hearts keep changing <br>Hearts keep changing <br>I am not done changing <br>Out on the run, changing <br>I may be old and I may be young <br>But I am not done changing <br>Changing <br>Changing]]></content><category term="John Mayer" label="John Mayer"/><category term="Changing" label="Changing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/YAH/</id><title>Kendrick Lamar - YAH. - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/YAH/" title="Kendrick Lamar - YAH. - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[New shit new Kung Fu Kenny <br>I got so many theories <br>and suspicions <br>I'm diagnosed <br>with real nigga conditions <br>Today is the day <br>I follow my intuition <br>Keep the family close <br>get money fuck bitches <br>I double parked the Aston in the red <br>My mama told me <br>that I'ma work myself to death <br>My girl told me <br>don't let these hoes <br>get in my head <br>My world been ecstatic <br>I checked the signal that read <br>Buzzin' radars is buzzin' <br>Yah yah yah yah <br>Yah yah yah yah yah yah <br>Buzzin' radars is buzzin' <br>Yah yah yah yah <br>Yah yah yah yah yah yah <br>Interviews wanna know <br>my thoughts and opinions <br>Fox News wanna use <br>my name for percentage <br>My latest muse is my niece <br>she worth livin' <br>See me on the TV and scream <br>That's Uncle Kendrick <br>Yeah that's the business <br>Somebody tell Geraldo <br>this nigga got some ambition <br>I'm not a politician <br>I'm not 'bout a religion <br>I'm a Israelite <br>don't call me Black no mo' <br>That word is only a color <br>it ain't facts no mo' <br>My cousin called <br>my cousin Carl Duckworth <br>Said know my worth <br>And Deuteronomy <br>say that we all been cursed <br>I know he walks the Earth <br>But it's money to get <br>bitches to hit yah <br>Zeroes to flip temptation is yah <br>First on my list I can't resist yah <br>Everyone together now <br>know that we forever <br>Buzzin' radars is buzzin' <br>Yah yah yah yah <br>Yah yah yah yah yah yah <br>Buzzin' radars is buzzin' <br>Yah yah yah yah <br>Yah yah yah yah yah yah <br>]]></content><category term="Kendrick Lamar" label="Kendrick Lamar"/><category term="YAH." label="YAH."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Boyz_II_Men/Ill_Make_Love_To_You/</id><title>Boyz II Men - I`ll Make Love To You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Boyz_II_Men/Ill_Make_Love_To_You/" title="Boyz II Men - I`ll Make Love To You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Close your eyes make a wish <br>And blow out the candlelight <br>For tonight is just your night <br>We're gonna celebrate <br>all thru the night <br>Pour the wine light the fire <br>Girl your wish is my command <br>I submit to your demands <br>I'll do anything <br>girl you need only ask <br>I'll make love to you <br>Like you want me to <br>And I'll hold you tight <br>Baby all thru the night <br>I'll make love to you <br>When you want me to <br>And I will not let go <br>Till you tell me to <br>Girl relax let's go slow <br>I ain't got nowhere to go <br>I'm just gonna concentrate on you <br>Girl are you ready <br>it's gonna be a long night <br>Throw your clothes on the floor <br>I'm gonna take my clothes off too <br>I made plans to be with you <br>Girl whatever you <br>ask me you know I'll do <br>I'll make love to you <br>Like you want me to <br>And I'll hold you tight <br>Baby all thru the night <br>I'll make love to you <br>When you want me to <br>And I will not let go <br>Till you tell me to <br>Baby tonight is just your night <br>And I will do you right <br>Just make a wish on your night <br>Anything that you ask <br>I will give you <br>the love of your life <br>your life your life <br>I'll make love to you <br>Like you want me to <br>And I'll hold you tight <br>Baby all thru the night <br>I'll make love to you <br>When you want me to <br>And I will not let go <br>Till you tell me to <br>I'll make love to you <br>Like you want me to <br>And I'll hold you tight <br>Baby all thru the night <br>I'll make love to you <br>When you want me to <br>And I will not let go <br>Till you tell me to]]></content><category term="Boyz II Men" label="Boyz II Men"/><category term="I`ll Make Love To You" label="I`ll Make Love To You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/In_the_Blood/</id><title>John Mayer - In the Blood - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/In_the_Blood/" title="John Mayer - In the Blood - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How much of my mother has my mother left in me? <br>How much of my love will be insane to some degree? <br>And what about this feeling that I'm never good enough? <br>Will it wash out in the water, or is it always in the blood? <br>How much of my father am I destined to become? <br>Will I dim the lights inside me just to satisfy someone? <br>Will I let this woman kill me, or do away with jealous love? <br>Will it wash out in the water, or is it always in the blood? <br>I can feel love the I want, I can feel the love I need <br>But it's never gonna calm the way I am <br>Could I change it if I wanted, can I rise above the flood? <br>Will it wash out in the water, or is it always in the blood? <br>How much like my brothers, do my brothers wanna be? <br>Does a broken home become another broken family? <br>Or will we be there for each other, like nobody ever could? <br>Will it wash out in the water, or is it always in the blood? <br>I can feel love the I want, I can feel the love I need <br>But it's never gonna calm the way I am <br>Could I change it if I wanted, can I rise above the flood? <br>Will it wash out in the water, or is it always in the blood? <br>I can feel love the I want, I can feel the love I need <br>But it's never gonna calm the way I am <br>Could I change it if I wanted, can I rise above the flood? <br>Will it wash out in the water, or is it always in the blood?]]></content><category term="John Mayer" label="John Mayer"/><category term="In the Blood" label="In the Blood"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/DNA/</id><title>Kendrick Lamar - DNA. - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/DNA/" title="Kendrick Lamar - DNA. - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I got I got I got I got <br>Loyalty got royalty inside my DNA <br>Cocaine quarter piece <br>got war and peace inside my DNA <br>I got power poison <br>pain and joy inside my DNA <br>I got hustle though ambition flow <br>inside my DNA <br>I was born like this <br>since one like this <br>Immaculate conception <br>I transform like this <br>perform like this <br>Was Yeshua's new weapon <br>I don’t contemplate I meditate <br>then off your fucking head <br>This that put-the-kids-to-bed <br>This that I got I got I got I got <br>Realness I just kill shit <br>'cause it's in my DNA <br>I got millions I got riches <br>buildin’ in my DNA <br>I got dark I got evil <br>that rot inside my DNA <br>I got off I got troublesome <br>heart inside my DNA <br>I just win again then win again <br>like Wimbledon I serve <br>Yeah that's him again <br>the sound that engine <br>in is like a bird <br>You see fireworks <br>and Corvette tire <br>skrrt the boulevard <br>I know how you work <br>I know just who you are <br>See you's a you's a you's a <br>Bitch your hormones prolly switch <br>inside your DNA <br>Problem is all that sucker shit <br>inside your DNA <br>Daddy prolly snitched heritage <br>inside your DNA <br>Backbone don't exist <br>born outside a jellyfish I gauge <br>See my pedigree most definitely <br>don't tolerate the front <br>Shit I've been through <br>prolly offend you <br>This is Paula’s oldest son <br>I know murder conviction <br>Burners boosters burglars ballers <br>dead redemption <br>Scholars fathers dead with kids <br>And I wish I was fed forgiveness <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah soldier’s DNA <br>Born inside the beast <br>My expertise checked out <br>in second grade <br>When I was 9 on cell motel <br>we didn't have nowhere to stay <br>At 29 I’ve done so well <br>hit cartwheel in my estate <br>And I'm gon' shine <br>like I'm supposed to <br>Antisocial extrovert <br>And excellent mean the extra work <br>And absentness <br>what the fuck you heard <br>And pessimists <br>never struck my nerve <br>And that’s a riff <br>gonna plead this case <br>The reason my power's <br>here on earth <br>Salute the truth <br>when the prophet say <br>I I got loyalty got royalty <br>This is why I say <br>that hip hop has done <br>more damage to young <br>African Americans <br>than racism in recent years <br>inside my DNA <br>This is my heritage <br>all I'm inheritin' <br>Money and power <br>the makin' of marriages <br>Tell me somethin' <br>You mothafuckas <br>can't tell me nothin' <br>I'd rather die than to listen to you <br>My DNA not for imitation <br>Your DNA an abomination <br>This how it is <br>when you're in the Matrix <br>Dodgin' bullets <br>reapin' what you sow <br>And stackin' up the footage <br>livin' on the go <br>And sleepin' in a villa <br>Sippin' from a Grammy <br>and walkin' in the buildin' <br>Diamond in the ceilin' <br>marble on the floors <br>Beach inside the window <br>peekin' out the window <br>Baby in the pool godfather goals <br>Only Lord knows <br>I've been goin' hammer <br>Dodgin' paparazzi <br>freakin' through the cameras <br>Eat at Four Daughters <br>Brock wearin' sandals <br>Yoga on a Monday <br>stretchin' to Nirvana <br>Watchin' all the snakes <br>curvin' all the fakes <br>Phone never on <br>I don't conversate <br>I don't compromise <br>I just penetrate <br>Sex money murder <br>these are the breaks <br>These are the times <br>level number 9 <br>Look up in the sky <br>10 is on the way <br>Sentence on the way <br>killings on the way <br>Motherfucker <br>I got winners on the way <br>You ain't shit <br>without a body on your belt <br>You ain't shit <br>without a ticket on your plate <br>You ain't sick enough to <br>pull it on yourself <br>You ain't rich enough to <br>hit the lot and skate <br>Tell me when destruction <br>gonna be my fate <br>Gonna be your fate <br>gonna be our faith <br>Peace to the world let it rotate <br>Sex money murder our DNA <br>]]></content><category term="Kendrick Lamar" label="Kendrick Lamar"/><category term="DNA." label="DNA."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/Love_On_The_Weekend/</id><title>John Mayer - Love On The Weekend - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:58:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:58:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/Love_On_The_Weekend/" title="John Mayer - Love On The Weekend - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's a Friday, we finally made it <br>I can't believe I get to see your face <br>You've been working and I've been waiting <br>To pick you up and take you from this place <br>Love on the weekend <br>Love on the weekend <br>Like only we can <br>Like only we can <br>Love on the weekend <br>Love on the weekend <br>I'm coming up and I'm loving every minute of it <br>You be the DJ, I'll be the driver <br>You put your feet up in the getaway car <br>I'm flying fast like a, a wanted man <br>I want you, baby, like you can't understand <br>Oh, love on the weekend <br>Love on the weekend <br>We found a message in a bottle we were drinking <br>Love on the weekend <br>Love on the weekend <br>I hate your guts 'cause I'm loving every minute of it <br>Oh, oh <br>Oh, oh <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>I gotta leave ya, it's gonna hurt me <br>My clothes are dirty and my friends are getting worried <br>Down there below us, under the clouds <br>Baby, take my hand and pull me down, down, down, down <br>And I'll be dreamin' of the next time we can go <br>Into another serotonin overflow <br>Love on the weekend <br>Love on the weekend <br>I'm busted up but I'm loving every minute of it <br>(Love on the weekend) <br>(Love on the weekend) <br>I'm looking for a little love <br>I'm looking for a little love, oh yeah <br>(Love on the weekend) <br>(Love on the weekend) <br>(Love on the weekend)]]></content><category term="John Mayer" label="John Mayer"/><category term="Love On The Weekend" label="Love On The Weekend"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/BLOOD/</id><title>Kendrick Lamar - BLOOD. - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:59:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:59:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kendrick_Lamar/BLOOD/" title="Kendrick Lamar - BLOOD. - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Is it wickedness <br>Is it weakness <br>You decide <br>Are we gonna live or die <br>So I was takin' a walk the other day <br>and I seen a woman <br>a blind woman <br>pacin' up and down the sidewalk <br>She seemed to be a bit frustrated <br>as if she had dropped somethin' and <br>havin' a hard time findin' it <br>So after watchin' her <br>struggle for a while <br>I decide to go over <br>and lend a helping hand you know <br>Hello ma'am <br>can I be of any assistance <br>It seems to me <br>that you have lost something <br>I would like to help you find it <br>She replied Oh yes <br>you have lost something <br>You've lost your life <br>Is it wickedness <br>Lamar stated his views <br>on police brutality <br>with that line in the song quote <br>And we hate the popo <br>wanna kill us in the street fo' sho' <br>Oh please ugh I don't like it <br>]]></content><category term="Kendrick Lamar" label="Kendrick Lamar"/><category term="BLOOD." label="BLOOD."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bachman-Turner_Overdrive/Takin_Care_Of_Business/</id><title>Bachman-Turner Overdrive - Takin` Care Of Business - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:59:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:59:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bachman-Turner_Overdrive/Takin_Care_Of_Business/" title="Bachman-Turner Overdrive - Takin` Care Of Business - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You get up every morning from your alarm clock's warning <br>Take the 815 into the city <br>There's a whistle up above and people pushin', people shovin' <br>And the girls who try to look pretty <br>And if your train's on time, you can get to work by nine <br>And start your slaving job to get your pay <br>If you ever get annoyed, look at me I'm self employed <br>I love to work at nothing all day <br><br>And I'll be taking care of business every day <br>Taking care of business every way <br>I've been taking care of business it's all mine <br>Taking care of business and working overtime, work out <br><br>If it were easy as fishin' you could be a musician <br>If you could make sounds loud or mellow <br>Get a second hand guitar, chances are you'll go far <br>If you get in with the right bunch of fellows <br>People see you having fun just a lying in the sun <br>Tell them that you like it this way <br>It's the work that we avoid, and we're all self employed <br>We love to work at nothing all day <br><br>And we be taking care of business every day <br>Taking care of business every way <br>We be been taking care of business it's all mine <br>Taking care of business and working overtime <br><br>Mercy <br>Whoo <br>All right <br><br>Take good care of my business <br>When I'm away, every day <br>Whoo <br><br>You get up every morning from your alarm clock's warning <br>Take the 815 into the city <br>There's a whistle up above and people pushin', people shovin' <br>And the girls who try to look pretty <br>And if your train's on time, you can get to work by nine <br>And start your slaving job to get your pay <br>If you ever get annoyed, look at me I'm self employed <br>I love to work at nothing all day <br><br>And I be taking care of business every day <br>Taking care of business every way <br>I've been taking care of business it's all mine <br>Taking care of business and working overtime, take care <br><br>Takin' care of business, whoo <br>Takin' care of business <br>Takin' care of business <br>Takin' care of business <br>Takin' care of business every day <br>Takin' care of business every way <br>Takin' care of business it's all mine <br>Takin' care of business and working overtime, whoo <br><br>Takin' care of business <br>Takin' care of business <br>We be takin' care of business <br>We be takin' care of business <br>Takin' care of business <br>Takin' care of business <br>Takin' care of business]]></content><category term="Bachman-Turner Overdrive" label="Bachman-Turner Overdrive"/><category term="Takin` Care Of Business" label="Takin` Care Of Business"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gino_Vannelli/I_Just_Wanna_Stop/</id><title>Gino Vannelli - I Just Wanna Stop - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:59:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:59:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gino_Vannelli/I_Just_Wanna_Stop/" title="Gino Vannelli - I Just Wanna Stop - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[For your love <br>When I think about those nights in Montreal <br>I get the sweetest thoughts of you and me <br>Memories of love above the city lights <br>Ooh, I tried so hard to take it <br>But oh lord my heart won't make it <br><br>I just wanna stop <br>And tell you what I feel about you babe <br>I just wanna stop <br>I never wanna live without you babe <br>I just gotta stop <br>For your love <br><br>When I think about the way the world must turn <br>I get the saddest thoughts for you and me <br>Memories of life and times go on and on <br>Ooh, Ive tried hard to forget it <br>But of lord my mind won't let it <br><br>I just wanna stop <br>And tell you what I feel about you babe <br>I just wanna stop <br>I never wanna live without you babe <br>I just gotta stop <br>For your love <br><br>Ooo, Ive tried so hard to take it <br>But oh lord my heart won't make it <br><br>I just wanna stop <br>And tell you what I feel about you babe <br>I just wanna stop <br>I never wanna live without you babe <br>I just gotta stop <br>For your love]]></content><category term="Gino Vannelli" label="Gino Vannelli"/><category term="I Just Wanna Stop" label="I Just Wanna Stop"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Poco/Crazy_Love/</id><title>Poco - Crazy Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:59:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:59:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Poco/Crazy_Love/" title="Poco - Crazy Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tonight I'm gonna break away <br>Just you wait and see <br>I'll never be imprisoned by <br>A faded memory <br><br>Just when I think I'm over her <br>This broken heart will mend <br>I hear her name and I have to cry <br>The tears come down again <br><br>It happens all the time <br>This crazy love of mine <br>Wraps around my heart <br>Refusin' to unwind <br>Ooh hoo, crazy love <br>Ah ha <br><br>Count the stars in a summer sky <br>That fall without a sound <br>And then pretend that you can't hear <br>These teardrops comin' down <br><br>It happens all the time <br>This crazy love of mine <br>Wraps around my heart <br>Refusin' to unwind <br>Ooh hoo, crazy love <br>Ah ha <br><br>Tonight I'm gonna break away <br>Just you wait and see <br>I'll never be imprisoned by <br>A faded memory <br><br>It happens all the time <br>This crazy love of mine <br>Wraps around my heart <br>Refusin' to unwind <br>Ooh hoo, crazy love <br>Ah ha <br><br>Tonight I'm gonna break away]]></content><category term="Poco" label="Poco"/><category term="Crazy Love" label="Crazy Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Mothers_Son/Come_On_Down_To_My_Boat/</id><title>Every Mother`s Son - Come On Down To My Boat - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:59:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:59:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Mothers_Son/Come_On_Down_To_My_Boat/" title="Every Mother`s Son - Come On Down To My Boat - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She sits on the dock a fishin' in the water uh, huh <br>I don't know her name she's the fisherman's daughter uh, huh <br>Come on down to my boat baby <br>Come on down where we can play <br><br>Come on down to my boat baby <br>Come on down we'll sail away <br>She smiled so nice like she wants to come with me uh, huh <br>But she's tied to the dock and she can't get free <br><br>Come on down to my boat baby <br>Fish all day sleep all night <br>Father never lets her out of his sight <br>Soon I'm gonna have to get my knife and cut that rope, cut that rope <br><br>Then we can go fishin' in my little red boat <br>Make you happy in my little red boat <br>so come on down to my boat baby]]></content><category term="Every Mother`s Son" label="Every Mother`s Son"/><category term="Come On Down To My Boat" label="Come On Down To My Boat"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Lewis__The_Playboys/Save_Your_Heart_For_Me/</id><title>Gary Lewis &amp; The Playboys - Save Your Heart For Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:59:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:59:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gary_Lewis__The_Playboys/Save_Your_Heart_For_Me/" title="Gary Lewis &amp; The Playboys - Save Your Heart For Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Walk along the lake with someone new <br>Have yourself a summer fling or two <br>But remember I'm in love with you and <br>Save your heart for me <br><br>When the summer moon is on the rise <br>And you're dancin' under starlit skies <br>Please don't let stars get in your eyes, just <br>Save your heart for me <br><br>When you're all alone, far away from home <br>Someone's gonna flirt with you ou <br>I won't think it's wrong if you play along <br>Just don't fall for someone new <br><br>When the autumn winds begin to blow <br>And the summertime is long ago <br>You'll be in my arms again I know, so <br>Save your heart for me <br>Darlin', save your heart for me <br><br>Brief instrumental with whistling first two lines of a verse <br>Please remember I'm in love with you so <br>Save your heart for me <br>Darlin', save your heart for me]]></content><category term="Gary Lewis &amp; The Playboys" label="Gary Lewis &amp; The Playboys"/><category term="Save Your Heart For Me" label="Save Your Heart For Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Grass_Roots/Heaven_Knows/</id><title>The Grass Roots - Heaven Knows - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:59:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:59:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Grass_Roots/Heaven_Knows/" title="The Grass Roots - Heaven Knows - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[With a song in my heart <br>And a chance to be yours forever <br>I couldn't feel more secure <br>I know I couldn't feel any better <br>Oh Lord, Heaven knows <br>How much I love you and <br>How much it shows <br>Oh Lord, Heaven <br>Heaven knows <br><br>Every time we're together <br>Your love is moving like lightning through me <br>It's such a beautiful feeling <br>Never hearing good bye said to me <br><br>Oh Lord, Heaven knows <br>How much I love you and <br>How much it shows <br>Oh Lord, Heaven <br>Heaven knows <br><br>I was living without you <br>Trying to make it alone <br>But there is something about you <br>Now your heart is my home <br><br>With a song in my heart <br>And a chance to be yours forever <br>I couldn't feel more secure <br>I know I couldn't feel any better <br>Oh Lord, Heaven knows <br>How much I love you and <br>How much it shows <br>Oh Lord, Heaven <br>Heaven knows <br><br>Oh Lord, Heaven knows <br>How much I love you and <br>How much it shows <br>Oh Lord, Heaven <br>Heaven knows]]></content><category term="The Grass Roots" label="The Grass Roots"/><category term="Heaven Knows" label="Heaven Knows"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Raspberries/Go_All_The_Way/</id><title>The Raspberries - Go All The Way - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:59:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:59:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Raspberries/Go_All_The_Way/" title="The Raspberries - Go All The Way - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I never knew, never knew how complete love could be <br>Till she kissed me and said <br><br>Baby, please, go all the way <br>It feels so right being with you, here, tonight <br>Please, go all the way <br>Just hold 'me close don't ever let me go <br><br>I couldn't say what I wanted to say <br>Till she whispered <br>I love you so, please, go all the way <br><br>It feels so right being with you, here, tonight <br>Please go all the way <br>Just hold me close <br>Don't ever let me go <br><br>Before her love I was cruel and mean <br>I had a hole in the place where my heart should have been <br>But now I've changed and it feels so strange <br>I come alive when she does all those things to me <br>And she says <br>Come on, come on, come on <br>I need you, I love you, I need you <br><br>Baby, please, go all the way <br>It feels so right being with you, here, tonight <br>Please, go all the way <br>Just hold 'me close don't ever let me go]]></content><category term="The Raspberries" label="The Raspberries"/><category term="Go All The Way" label="Go All The Way"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hamilton_Joe_Frank__Reynolds/Dont_Pull_Your_Love/</id><title>Hamilton, Joe Frank &amp; Reynolds - Don`t Pull Your Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:59:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:59:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hamilton_Joe_Frank__Reynolds/Dont_Pull_Your_Love/" title="Hamilton, Joe Frank &amp; Reynolds - Don`t Pull Your Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't pull your love out on me baby <br>If you do then I think that maybe <br>I'll just lay me down and cry for a hundred years <br>Don't pull your love out on me honey <br>Take my heart, my soul, my money <br>But don't leave me drownin' in my tears <br><br>You say you're gonna leave <br>Gonna take that big white bird <br>Gonna fly right out of here <br>Without a single word <br>Don't you know you'll break my heart <br>When I watch you close that door <br>'Cause I know I won't see you anymore <br><br>Don't pull your love out on me baby <br>If you do then I think that maybe <br>I'll just lay me down and cry for a hundred years <br>Don't pull your love out on me honey <br>Take my heart, my soul, my money <br>But don't leave me drownin' in my tears <br><br>Haven't I been good to you <br>What about that brand new ring <br>Doesn't that mean love to you <br>Doesn't that mean anything <br>If I threw away my pride <br>And I got down on my knees <br>Would I have to beg you, pretty please <br><br>Don't pull your love out on me baby <br>If you do then I think that maybe <br>I'll just lay me down and cry for a hundred years <br>Don't pull your love out on me honey <br>Take my heart, my soul, my money <br>But don't leave me drownin' in my tears <br><br>There's so much I wanna do <br>I've got love enough for two <br>But I'll never use it girl if I don't have you <br><br>Don't pull your love out on me baby <br>If you do then I think that maybe <br>I'll just lay me down and cry for a hundred years <br>Don't pull your love out on me honey <br>Take my heart, my soul, my money <br>But don't leave me drownin' in my tears]]></content><category term="Hamilton, Joe Frank &amp; Reynolds" label="Hamilton, Joe Frank &amp; Reynolds"/><category term="Don`t Pull Your Love" label="Don`t Pull Your Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Mamas__Papas/Words_Of_Love/</id><title>The Mamas &amp; Papas - Words Of Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:59:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:59:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Mamas__Papas/Words_Of_Love/" title="The Mamas &amp; Papas - Words Of Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Words of love, so soft and tender <br>Won't win a girl's heart anymore <br>If you love her then you must send her <br>Somewhere where she's never been before <br>Worn out phrases and longin' gazes <br>Won't get you where you want to go, no <br>Words of love, soft and tender <br>Won't win her <br><br>You oughta know by now <br>You oughta know, you oughta know by now <br><br>Words of love, soft and tender <br>Won't win her anymore <br><br>You oughta know by now <br>You oughta know, you oughta know by now <br><br>Words of love, soft and tender <br>Won't win a girl's heart anymore <br>If you love her then you must send her <br>Somewhere where she's never been before <br>Worn out phrases and longin' gazes <br>Won't get you where you want to go <br><br>Words of love, soft and tender <br>Won't win her anymore, anymore]]></content><category term="The Mamas &amp; Papas" label="The Mamas &amp; Papas"/><category term="Words Of Love" label="Words Of Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Righteous_Brothers/Youre_My_Soul_And_Inspiration/</id><title>The Righteous Brothers - (You`re My) Soul And Inspiration - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T07:59:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T07:59:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Righteous_Brothers/Youre_My_Soul_And_Inspiration/" title="The Righteous Brothers - (You`re My) Soul And Inspiration - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Girl, I can't let you do this <br>Let you walk away <br>Girl, how can I live through this <br>When you're all I wake up for each day <br><br>Baby, you're my soul and my heart's inspiration <br>You're all I've got to get me by <br>You're my soul and my heart's inspiration <br>Without you baby, what good am I <br><br>I never had much goin' <br>But at least I had you <br>How can you walk out knowin' <br>I ain't got nothin' left if you do <br><br>Baby, you're my soul and my heart's inspiration <br>You're all I've got to get me by <br>You're my soul and my heart's inspiration <br>Without you baby, what good am I, oh what good am I <br><br>Baby, I can't make it withoutcha <br>And I'm, I'm tellin' ya, honey you're my <br>reason for laughin', for cryin', for livin', and for dyin' <br><br>Baby, I can't make it without you <br>Please, I'm begging you baby <br>If you go it will kill me <br>I swear it, Dear, my love can't bear it <br><br>You're my soul and my heart's inspiration <br>You're all I've got to get me by <br>You're my soul and my heart's inspiration <br>Without you baby, what good am I, what good am I <br><br>Mm mm mm Mm mm mm <br>Mm mm mm]]></content><category term="The Righteous Brothers" label="The Righteous Brothers"/><category term="(You`re My) Soul And Inspiration" label="(You`re My) Soul And Inspiration"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NeedleGem/34N125E/</id><title>Needle&amp;Gem - 34N125E - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:00:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:00:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NeedleGem/34N125E/" title="Needle&amp;Gem - 34N125E - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This ship is going to sink <br>I can feel it <br>I tried to tell them <br>But no one would listen <br>This ship is on its toes <br>I can see it <br>I'll hold my breath <br>For as long as I could <br>The light is paling <br>And the boat stopped sailing <br>Then I thought of you <br>And our little garden <br>Where you and I used to walk along <br>The water's flowing in <br>I can feel it <br>I drew my hand <br>And put it on my cheek <br>The light is paling <br>And the boat stopped sailing <br>Then I thought of you <br>And our little garden <br>The light is paling <br>And the boat stopped sailing <br>Then I thought of you <br>And our little garden <br>Where you and I used to walk along <br>The sky is failing <br>And I stopped trying <br>When I opened my eyes <br>You came along <br>And walked me to home <br>]]></content><category term="Needle&amp;Gem" label="Needle&amp;Gem"/><category term="34N125E" label="34N125E"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Andup_앤덥/뭐_어쩔꺼/</id><title>Andup (앤덥) - 뭐 어쩔꺼 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:00:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:00:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Andup_%EC%95%A4%EB%8D%A5/%EB%AD%90_%EC%96%B4%EC%A9%94%EA%BA%BC/" title="Andup (앤덥) - 뭐 어쩔꺼 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지들이 뒷담까면 뭐 뭐 어쩔꺼 <br>니가 인정 못해도 뭐 뭐 어쩔꺼 <br>got my people on my side <br>only my people on my mind <br>I'll be sippin Jack n 쏘맥 <br>쏠게 친구야 올라타 <br>조만간 꼬나봤던 애 <br>조지겠다는 가사 안써 <br>마주칠 일도 없거니와 <br>굳이 신경 안써 <br>어울리는 대로 어울리는 삶 <br>떠올리기 싫어 쏠리는 면상 <br>좋고 싶어 난 기분이 규칙의 기본이 <br>no teacher allowed <br>갈길 갈게 가르치려 마 걍 뒷담까줘 <br>같이 가는 사람 많아 이미 귀찮아 넌 <br>항상 바삐 살어 <br>창작 hookin' poppin' bottles <br>안사 lotto 거 뭐하러 <br>하나 모자른 게 없어 나는 ay <br>지들이 인정 못하면 뭐 뭐 어쩔꺼 ya <br>털끝도 손 못 대 huh 뭐 어쩔꺼 ya <br>livin' well and prosper <br>즐길 게 많아 바뻐 <br>젤 쓸데 없는 걱정 bout me <br>넣어둬 넣어둬 <br>뭐 어쩔꺼야 yayayaya <br>뭐 어쩔꺼야 yayayaya <br>뭐 어쩔꺼야 yayayaya <br>뭐 어쩔꺼야 yayaya <br>입는 옷 일상 뱉는 말 <br>괴리감 없어 내 음악 <br>누가 캐 더 뜰 필요 있어 <br>um 몇 년 쓸 돈이 있어 <br>ridin' no rarri ridin' Sonata <br>엄마 빽 하나 사지 <br>나머진 통장안에다 쳐 박아둬 <br>club에서 party 재밌지만 <br>club 노래 부르는 건 별로 <br>평소에 진지충이라 <br>주말의 광기는 별도야 <br>배틀 로얄 쎄게 겪고서 <br>평화로운 상태 <br>인도네시아 유럽 <br>이쁨 받고 왔어 sante <br>사랑하는 우리 엄마 눈치 안본 내가 <br>너거 말을 듣겠나 생각해봐 빠가들아 <br>니가 인정하든 말든 livin good <br>다들 빨리 안정 찾길 비는 중 <br>지들이 인정 못하면 뭐 뭐 어쩔꺼 ya <br>털끝도 손 못 대 huh 뭐 어쩔꺼 ya <br>livin' well and prosper <br>즐길 게 많아 바뻐 <br>젤 쓸데 없는 걱정 bout me <br>넣어둬 넣어둬 <br>뭐 어쩔꺼야 yayayaya <br>뭐 어쩔꺼야 yayayaya <br>뭐 어쩔꺼야 yayayaya <br>뭐 어쩔꺼야 yaya <br>]]></content><category term="Andup (앤덥)" label="Andup (앤덥)"/><category term="뭐 어쩔꺼" label="뭐 어쩔꺼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정찬미/너의_마음/</id><title>정찬미 - 너의 마음 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:01:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:01:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%B0%AC%EB%AF%B8/%EB%84%88%EC%9D%98_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C/" title="정찬미 - 너의 마음 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어떻게 넌 내 마음을 조금도 모르니 <br>아닌 척 나 무심한 듯 <br>모른 척 해봐도 음 <br>어제도 생각해 오늘도 생각해 <br>온통 네 생각뿐인데 <br>굳이 내가 먼저 말해야 알겠니 <br>나 정말 답답해 <br>보여줄래 나를 향한 네 마음을 <br>말해줄래 오랫동안 지켜온 믿음을 <br>우 우 우우 <br>바로 지금 너의 마음을 <br>오늘도 생각해 내일도 생각해 <br>온통 네 생각뿐인데 <br>굳이 내가 먼저 말해야 알겠니 <br>나 정말 속상해 <br>보여줄래 나를 향한 네 마음을 <br>말해줄래 오랫동안 지켜온 믿음을 <br>우 우 우우 <br>바로 지금 너의 마음을 <br>사실은 나 말야 <br>다른 사람에게도 친절한 <br>너의 그 미소 정말 미웠어 <br>예민해진 나도 내가 미워 <br>보여줄래 나를 향한 네 마음을 <br>말해줄래 오랫동안 지켜온 믿음을 <br>우 우 우우 <br>바로 지금 너의 마음을 <br>널 사랑해 변하지 않는 이 마음 <br>두근대던 우리 설레었던 그 마음을 <br>약속해 우리의 사랑을 <br>약속해 우리의 사랑을 <br>약속해 우리의 사랑을 <br>]]></content><category term="정찬미" label="정찬미"/><category term="너의 마음" label="너의 마음"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김보희/가던길_간다/</id><title>김보희 - 가던길 간다 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:01:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:01:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%B3%B4%ED%9D%AC/%EA%B0%80%EB%8D%98%EA%B8%B8_%EA%B0%84%EB%8B%A4/" title="김보희 - 가던길 간다 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다시 생각해 <br>왜 니가 그렇게 사는지 <br>세상 걱정 혼자 하고 있잖아 <br>바뀌지 않아 밤새워 고민을 해도 <br>그냥 시작해 니 뜻대로 <br>모든 일들이 쉽진 않아 <br>포기하고 싶을 때도 있지 <br>앞만 보고 걷다가 보면 <br>원했던 모든 걸 가질거야 <br>바람 같은 인생 <br>돌아보지 말고 <br>이 길 그냥 가자 가던 대로 <br>햇살 밝은 날에 <br>매일 행복하자 <br>언젠간 좋은 날 올 테니까 <br>모든 일들이 쉽진 않아 <br>포기하고 싶을 때도 있지 <br>앞만 보고 걷다가 보면 <br>원했던 모든 걸 가질거야 <br>바람 같은 인생 <br>돌아보지 말고 <br>이 길 그냥 가자 가던 대로 <br>햇살 밝은 날에 <br>매일 행복하자 <br>언젠간 좋은 날 올 테니까 <br>태양처럼 빛나게 서 있을 거야 <br>지금 어두운 시간이 다 지나고 <br>끝난 후에 우워 <br>바람 같은 인생 <br>돌아보지 말고 <br>이 길 그냥 가자 가던 대로 <br>햇살 밝은 날에 <br>매일 행복하자 <br>언젠간 좋은 날 올 테니까 <br>바람 같은 인생 <br>돌아보지 말고 <br>이 길 그냥 가자 가던 대로 <br>햇살 밝은 날에 <br>매일 행복하자 <br>언젠간 좋은 날 올 테니까 <br>]]></content><category term="김보희" label="김보희"/><category term="가던길 간다" label="가던길 간다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김보희/딸바보_Feat_김지안/</id><title>김보희 - 딸바보 (Feat. 김지안) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:01:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:01:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%B3%B4%ED%9D%AC/%EB%94%B8%EB%B0%94%EB%B3%B4_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%80%EC%95%88/" title="김보희 - 딸바보 (Feat. 김지안) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지금 잡은 손 놓지 마요 <br>언제나 내 곁에서 <br>기억 하나요 눈 뜬 순간 <br>날 바라보던 그 봄날을 <br>처음 웃던 날 걸음 뗀 날 <br>바달 보고 놀랐던 날 <br>너의 그 많은 처음인 날들 <br>함께 해 행복했다 <br>잊을 수 없지 나의 전부는 <br>늘 언제나 너뿐인데 <br>쉽지 않았던 내 인생을 <br>지킬 수 있었던 건 <br>날 볼 때마다 웃어주던 너 <br>그래서 고마웠다 <br>하얀 드레스 너무 예뻐서 <br>남모르게 눈물 흘리네 <br>내 손 놓고 걸어가는 길에 <br>행복을 빌어줄게 <br>이제 내 품을 떠나가지만 <br>늘 마음은 너의 곁에 <br>언제나 너의 곁에 <br>]]></content><category term="김보희" label="김보희"/><category term="딸바보 (Feat. 김지안)" label="딸바보 (Feat. 김지안)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/케이_KEI/흔들흔들_Feat_수연3/</id><title>케이 (KEI) - 흔들흔들 (Feat. 수연3) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:01:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:01:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4_KEI/%ED%9D%94%EB%93%A4%ED%9D%94%EB%93%A4_Feat_%EC%88%98%EC%97%B03/" title="케이 (KEI) - 흔들흔들 (Feat. 수연3) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흔들흔들 내 마음 나도 몰라요 <br>어쩜어쩜 내 마음 나도 몰라요 <br>오빠의 사랑에 나를 맡기고 <br>오늘밤 추억 속으로 <br>내 마음 흔들어 놓고 <br>내 사랑 몰라 주나요 <br>밤새워 당신만 기다리는데 <br>님은 오질 않네요 <br>무정한 사람 무심한 사랑 <br>내 마음 어쩌면 좋아 <br>그래도 당신을 기다릴게요 <br>뜨거운 사랑을 위해 <br>흔들흔들 내 마음 나도 몰라요 <br>어쩜어쩜 내 마음 나도 몰라요 <br>오빠의 사랑에 나를 담그고 <br>영원히 잠들고 싶어 <br>흔들흔들 내 마음 나도 몰라요 <br>어쩜어쩜 내 마음 나도 몰라요 <br>오빠의 사랑에 나를 맡기고 <br>오늘밤 추억 속으로 <br>무정한 사람 무심한 사랑 <br>내 마음 어쩌면 좋아 <br>그래도 당신을 기다릴게요 <br>뜨거운 사랑을 위해 <br>흔들흔들 내 마음 나도 몰라요 <br>어쩜어쩜 내 마음 나도 몰라요 <br>오빠의 사랑에 나를 담그고 <br>영원히 잠들고 싶어 <br>흔들흔들 내 마음 나도 몰라요 <br>어쩜어쩜 내 마음 나도 몰라요 <br>오빠의 사랑에 나를 맡기고 <br>오늘밤 추억 속으로 <br>흔들흔들 내 마음 나도 몰라요 <br>어쩜어쩜 내 마음 나도 몰라요 <br>오빠의 사랑에 나를 담그고 <br>영원히 잠들고 싶어 <br>흔들흔들 내 마음 나도 몰라요 <br>어쩜어쩜 내 마음 나도 몰라요 <br>오빠의 사랑에 나를 맡기고 <br>오늘밤 추억 속으로 <br>오늘밤 추억 속으로 <br>]]></content><category term="케이 (KEI)" label="케이 (KEI)"/><category term="흔들흔들 (Feat. 수연3)" label="흔들흔들 (Feat. 수연3)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KennyJ/그냥_너_Feat_랑쑈/</id><title>Kenny.J - 그냥 너 (Feat. 랑쑈) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:01:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:01:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KennyJ/%EA%B7%B8%EB%83%A5_%EB%84%88_Feat_%EB%9E%91%EC%91%88/" title="Kenny.J - 그냥 너 (Feat. 랑쑈) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모든 게 다 달라졌어 <br>너를 만난 순간부터 <br>하얀 구름에 걸린 해처럼 <br>네 생각이 날 따라다녀 <br>있잖아 사실 말야 <br>바보처럼 그냥 좋은걸 <br>넌 짙은 밤 하늘 빛나는 <br>날 비추는 달빛 같아 <br>내 방식대로 내 느낌대로 <br>네 눈빛만 봐도 사랑할 내가 있잖아 <br>내 안에 너 하나 들어와서 <br>모든 걸 바꿔놨어 <br>널 사랑할래 널 지켜줄래 <br>왜 네 미소 나를 온종일 웃게 하니 <br>내게 마지막 사랑이 <br>너라면 좋겠어 <br>고마워 믿어줘서 <br>항상 곁엔 내가 있어 <br>지친 하루 숨소리 마저도 <br>네 행복이 나였으면 <br>내 방식대로 내 느낌대로 <br>네 눈빛만 봐도 사랑할 내가 있잖아 <br>내 안에 너 하나 들어와서 <br>모든 걸 바꿔놨어 <br>널 사랑할래 널 지켜줄래 <br>왜 네 미소 나를 온종일 웃게 하니 <br>내게 마지막 사랑이 <br>너라면 좋을텐데 <br>하루하루가 너의 생일이라면 <br>주고 싶은 선물 모두 다 줄 텐데 <br>내게 보여준 네 사랑 <br>그걸로 나는 행복한 걸 <br>난 그냥 너야 그래도 너야 <br>하루 종일 너만 그리고 보고 싶은걸 <br>언제나 내 옆에 두고 싶어 <br>Forever my love I’m with you <br>난 그냥 너야 난 너만 할래 <br>내 모든 걸 줘도 아깝지 않을 넌데 <br>내게 마지막 사랑이 <br>너라면 좋겠어 <br>]]></content><category term="Kenny.J" label="Kenny.J"/><category term="그냥 너 (Feat. 랑쑈)" label="그냥 너 (Feat. 랑쑈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이혁진/주가_일하시네/</id><title>이혁진 - 주가 일하시네 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:02:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:02:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%98%81%EC%A7%84/%EC%A3%BC%EA%B0%80_%EC%9D%BC%ED%95%98%EC%8B%9C%EB%84%A4/" title="이혁진 - 주가 일하시네 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날이 저물어 갈 때 빈들에서 걸을 때 <br>그때가 하나님의 때 <br>내 힘으로 안될 때 빈손으로 걸을 때 <br>내가 고백해 여호와이레 <br>주가 일하시네 주가 일하시네 <br>주께 아끼지 않는 자에게 <br>주가 일하시네 주가 일하시네 <br>신뢰하며 걷는 자에게 <br>우리 모인 이곳에 주님 함께 계시네 <br>누리네 아버지 은혜 <br>적은 떡과 물고기 내 모든 걸 드릴 때 <br>모두 고백해 여호와이레 <br>주가 일하시네 주가 일하시네 <br>주께 아끼지 않는 자에게 <br>주가 일하시네 주가 일하시네 <br>신뢰하며 걷는 자에게 <br>주가 일하시네 주가 일하시네 <br>주께 아끼지 않는 자에게 <br>주가 일하시네 주가 일하시네 <br>신뢰하며 걷는 자에게 <br>주가 일하시네 주가 일하시네 <br>주께 아끼지 않는 자에게 <br>주가 일하시네 주가 일하시네 <br>신뢰하며 걷는 자에게 <br>신뢰하며 걷는 자에게 <br>]]></content><category term="이혁진" label="이혁진"/><category term="주가 일하시네" label="주가 일하시네"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임재형/한때/</id><title>임재형 - 한때 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:02:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:02:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9E%AC%ED%98%95/%ED%95%9C%EB%95%8C/" title="임재형 - 한때 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한때 <br>우리 함께 했었다는 걸 <br>기억하지 못할 거야 <br>서로를 볼 때마다 <br>다른 사람 떠올렸단 걸 <br>우린 알지 못할 거야 <br>이제는 믿지 않을래 <br>어지러운 마음 속에서 <br>떠다니는 너의 말들 <br>우리 함께 했었다는 걸 <br>기억하지 못할 거야 <br>우리 한때 함께였단 기억을 <br>믿을 수 없을 거야 <br>나는 너의 사소한 손짓까지 <br>잊을 수 없을 거야 <br>떠나는 순간까지 <br>나를 맴돌던 너의 말들 <br>지울 수 없을 거야 <br>아직은 잊지 않을래 <br>지나버린 우리 시간들 <br>이제는 늦었지만 <br>되돌아갈 순 없겠지만 <br>기억하고 있을 거야 <br>한때 우리 함께였단 기억을 <br>지울 수 없을 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="임재형" label="임재형"/><category term="한때" label="한때"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임재형/후달달달/</id><title>임재형 - 후달달달 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:02:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:02:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9E%AC%ED%98%95/%ED%9B%84%EB%8B%AC%EB%8B%AC%EB%8B%AC/" title="임재형 - 후달달달 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다리 떠는 게 멋있어 <br>너는 복이 없는 사람 <br>유난히 재수가 없는 사람 <br>음 그래도 넌 다리 <br>다리 떠는 게 멋있어 <br>절뚝거리는 걸음도 <br>난 다 이해할거야 <br>너는 마지막까지 거만하게 <br>다리를 떠는 게 멋있어 <br>까딱대는 게 멋있어 <br>너는 개념 없는 사람 <br>유난히 집중 못하는 사람 <br>음 그래도 넌 고개 <br>까딱대는 게 멋있어 <br>찌질이 같은 모습도 <br>난 다 이해할거야 <br>너는 마지막까지 개념 없게 <br>고개를 까딱대는 게 멋있어 <br>고개를 까딱대는 게 멋있어 <br>]]></content><category term="임재형" label="임재형"/><category term="후달달달" label="후달달달"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임재형/자고싶어/</id><title>임재형 - 자고싶어 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:02:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:02:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9E%AC%ED%98%95/%EC%9E%90%EA%B3%A0%EC%8B%B6%EC%96%B4/" title="임재형 - 자고싶어 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[솔직하게 말할 테니 <br>욕하지 말아줘 <br>너랑 자고 싶어 <br>손도 안 잡고 그냥 <br>자고 싶어 <br>나 땀도 별로 안 나 <br>냄새도 안 나 <br>코 고는 건 고칠 테니 <br>우리 자자 <br>그렇게 하자 <br>우리 자자 <br>그렇게 하자 <br>거짓말로 말할 테니 <br>믿지 말아줘 <br>너랑 자고 싶어 <br>너의 엉덩이 <br>부여잡고 싶어 <br>나 능숙하지는 않아 <br>하지만 노력은 할게 <br>2세는 걱정하지 마 <br>우리 자자 <br>그렇게 하자 <br>우리 자자 <br>그렇게 하자 <br>우리 자자 <br>그렇게 하자 <br>우리 자자 <br>그렇게 하자 <br>]]></content><category term="임재형" label="임재형"/><category term="자고싶어" label="자고싶어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임재형/교양있게/</id><title>임재형 - 교양있게 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:02:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:02:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9E%AC%ED%98%95/%EA%B5%90%EC%96%91%EC%9E%88%EA%B2%8C/" title="임재형 - 교양있게 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘은 얌전하게 놀고 싶은 날 <br>이상한 농담도 하지 않고 <br>누군가 무릎에 앉힐 일 없이 <br>조용히 술만 마시고 싶어 <br>교양 있게 <br>다리에 손이 가지 않게 <br>가슴에 손이 가지 않게 <br>얌전한 얼굴로 있고 싶은 날 <br>교양 있게 <br>공부하고 싶지는 않아 <br>책 읽는 건 더 지쳤어 <br>오늘은 가만히 얌전하게 <br>오늘은 얌전하게 놀고 싶은 난 <br>하물며 술잔도 높이 들지 않네 <br>교양 있게 <br>교양 있게 <br>]]></content><category term="임재형" label="임재형"/><category term="교양있게" label="교양있게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임재형/붕어빵/</id><title>임재형 - 붕어빵 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:02:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:02:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9E%AC%ED%98%95/%EB%B6%95%EC%96%B4%EB%B9%B5/" title="임재형 - 붕어빵 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밤마다 어두웠어 <br>당연하지 밤이니까 <br>밤마다 배고팠어 <br>당연해 굶었으니까 <br>오늘은 군인도 집어 치울래 <br>난 지금 너무 배고파 <br>너의 목덜미를 움켜잡을 때 <br>김 나는 너의 눈빛을 볼 때 <br>겁이 나 뜨거울까 봐 <br>하지만 용기 내볼래 <br>나는 지금 너무 배고파 <br>오늘은 어른도 집어 치울래 <br>난 지금 너무 배고파 <br>너의 목덜미를 움켜잡을 때 <br>김 나는 너의 눈빛을 볼 때 <br>겁이 나 뜨거울까 봐 <br>하지만 용기 내볼래 <br>나는 지금 너무 배고파 <br>]]></content><category term="임재형" label="임재형"/><category term="붕어빵" label="붕어빵"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임재형/사이다_그_사이/</id><title>임재형 - 사이다 그 사이 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:02:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:02:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9E%AC%ED%98%95/%EC%82%AC%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%A4_%EA%B7%B8_%EC%82%AC%EC%9D%B4/" title="임재형 - 사이다 그 사이 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[목이 말라서 사이다를 샀어 <br>너무 목이 마른데 <br>한 번에 다 마실 수 없어 <br>목이 따끔거리니까 <br>참을 수 없을 때가 있으니까 <br>헤어진 너를 떠올렸어 <br>너무 보고 싶은데 <br>이젠 만날 수 없을 거야 <br>눈이 따끔거리니까 <br>참을 수 없을 때가 있으니까 <br>지금도 가끔 어지러워져 <br>흔들리던 기억이 떠오르면 <br>사이다를 사곤 해 <br>한 번에 비울 수 없는 <br>사이다를 마시곤 해 <br>사이다를 마시곤 해 <br>]]></content><category term="임재형" label="임재형"/><category term="사이다 그 사이" label="사이다 그 사이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/에즈피_ASP/이불_Vocal_도라희/</id><title>에즈피 (ASP) - 이불 (Vocal. 도라희) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:02:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:02:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%90%EC%A6%88%ED%94%BC_ASP/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B6%88_Vocal_%EB%8F%84%EB%9D%BC%ED%9D%AC/" title="에즈피 (ASP) - 이불 (Vocal. 도라희) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잘 자요 내사랑 <br>오늘도 수고 많이 했어요 <br>잘 자요 내사랑 <br>오늘도 내 옆에 있어 고마워요 <br>속상한 일에 지쳐 <br>맘껏 울고 싶을 때 <br>내가 너를 감싸 안아줄게 <br>나를 뒤집어쓰고 편히 울어요 <br>창피한 일이 있는데 <br>누구에게도 말 못할 땐 <br>나를 걷어 차도 돼요 <br>그대 맘이 조금 편해진다면 <br>위로 받고 싶을 때 <br>외롭다고 느낄 때 <br>난 언제나 같은 자리에 있어 <br>언제든 내게 와 안겨도 돼요 <br>너가 잠이 드는 매일 밤 <br>니 이불이 되고 싶어 <br>너를 빈틈없이 안아 <br>좋은 꿈꾸게 해줄 거야 <br>잘 자요 내사랑 <br>오늘도 수고 많이 했어요 <br>잘 자요 내사랑 <br>오늘도 내 옆에 있어 고마워요 <br>힘들었던 하룰 노래하는 <br>코골이도 <br>내겐 어떤 노래보다 이쁜 <br>멜로디죠 <br>밝은 보름달 아래 <br>곤히 잠든 넌 화보 같아 <br>달빛은 니 조명 난 사진작가 <br>안 좋은 꿈을 꾸는 듯 <br>앓는 소리를 내고 <br>인상을 찡그리고 <br>뒤척이며 나 밀쳐도 <br>다시 네게 가서 널 더 꽉 안아 <br>괜찮아 내가 지켜줄게 푹 자 my love <br>이유 없이 불안하고 <br>잡생각이 많아질 땐 <br>아무 고민 말고 내게 와 <br>내가 안아줄게 <br>생각보다 난 더 따뜻할 거야 <br>너가 잠이 드는 매일 밤 <br>니 이불이 되고 싶어 <br>너를 빈틈없이 안아 <br>좋은 꿈꾸게 해줄 거야 <br>잘 자요 내사랑 <br>오늘도 수고 많이 했어요 <br>잘 자요 내사랑 <br>오늘도 내 옆에 있어 고마워요 <br>잘자 <br>]]></content><category term="에즈피 (ASP)" label="에즈피 (ASP)"/><category term="이불 (Vocal. 도라희)" label="이불 (Vocal. 도라희)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Overflow/Killed_Myself/</id><title>Overflow - Killed Myself - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:02:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:02:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Overflow/Killed_Myself/" title="Overflow - Killed Myself - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 하루도 어제와 같다 <br>똑같은 고민 속에서 살아나간다 <br>오늘 하루도 어제와 같다 <br>똑같은 고민 속에서 살아나간다 <br>나의 하루하루가 <br>여전히 바쁜 일로 가득해 <br>난 걸어가다가 <br>붉은 신호등에 멈춰 서 <br>참 빨리 달리는 트럭이 <br>내 앞을 지나갈 때쯤 <br>그냥 뛰어들까나 <br>한심한 생각들을 하곤 해 <br>사람들 눈엔 어떻게 보일지 <br>무참히 찢겨진 내 모습이 <br>날 아는 사람들은 말을 하겠지 <br>밝은 아이라고 생각했는데 <br>나의 하루하루가 <br>여전히 바쁜 일로 가득해 <br>너무 아름다운 밤 <br>스스럼없이 나는 <br>killed myself <br>오늘 하루도 어제와 같다 <br>똑같은 고민 속에서 살아나간다 <br>오늘 하루도 어제와 같다 <br>똑같은 고민 속에서 살아나간다 <br>나의 하루하루가 <br>여전히 바쁜 일로 가득해 <br>난 걸어가다가 <br>작은 공사장에 멈춰 서 <br>얼굴을 가린 채로 <br>조심히 용접하는 아저씨 <br>가까이 다가가 <br>맨눈으로 보고 싶어 <br>수많은 감각들이 살아나겠지 <br>스티비 원더 레이 찰스처럼 <br>사람을 겉만 보는 삶은 없겠지 <br>니가 내게 짓던 표정도 <br>나의 하루하루가 <br>여전히 바쁜 일로 가득해 <br>너무 아름다운 밤 <br>스스럼없이 나는 <br>killed myself <br>오늘 하루도 어제와 같아 <br>똑같은 고민 속에서 살아나간다 <br>오늘 하루도 어제와 같아 <br>똑같은 고민 속에서 살아나간다 <br>오늘 하루도 어제와 같아 <br>똑같은 고민 속에서 살아나간다 <br>오늘 하루도 어제와 같아 <br>똑같은 고민 속에서 살아나간다 <br>오늘 하루도 어제와 같아 <br>똑같은 고민 속에서 살아나간다 <br>]]></content><category term="Overflow" label="Overflow"/><category term="Killed Myself" label="Killed Myself"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백현_BAEKHYUN/바래다줄게_Take_You_Home_Inst/</id><title>백현 (BAEKHYUN) - 바래다줄게 (Take You Home) (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:02:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:02:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%ED%98%84_BAEKHYUN/%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%98%EB%8B%A4%EC%A4%84%EA%B2%8C_Take_You_Home_Inst/" title="백현 (BAEKHYUN) - 바래다줄게 (Take You Home) (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[알아 <br>아무렇지도 않은 척해 봐도 <br>기다린단 걸 애써 웃어 보는 <br>눈가에 묻은 슬픔 <br>내가 어쩔 수 없단 걸 <br>느낄 수 있어 <br>괜찮아 미안하단 말 <br>곁에 있는 것만으로 <br>충분해 하지 마 <br>아냐 됐다 그냥 네 맘 <br>편하면 들어줄게 <br>네 남자 아니지만 <br>조금만 지켜봐 줘 <br>I need you girl <br>너의 그 사람 아니지만 <br>너를 안아줄 순 없어도 <br>널 집에 데려갈 <br>넓은 등을 가진 그런 남자야 <br>바래다줄게 <br>내게 기대 <br>아무렇지도 않은 척해 봐도 <br>기다린단 걸 애써 미소 짓는 <br>입가에 묻은 슬픔 <br>네가 어쩔 수 없단 걸 <br>느낄 수 있어 <br>괜찮아 미안하단 말 <br>곁에 있는 것만으로 <br>충분해 하지 마 <br>아냐 됐다 그냥 네 맘 <br>편하면 들어줄게 <br>네 남자 아니지만 <br>조금만 지켜봐 줘 <br>I need you girl <br>너의 그 사람 아니지만 <br>너를 안아줄 순 없어도 <br>널 집에 데려갈 <br>넓은 등을 가진 그런 남자야 <br>바래다줄게 <br>내게 기대 <br>이 말도 안 되는 <br>어설픈 위로만으로 <br>힘이 되었단 걸 그때의 난 <br>널 웃게 할 수 있단 걸 <br>그 앤 왜 모르는지 <br>내 모습 그대로를 <br>조금만 지켜봐 줘 <br>I love you girl <br>너의 그 사람 아니지만 <br>지금 안아볼 순 없대도 <br>네 곁을 지켜줄 <br>넓은 맘을 가진 그런 남자야 <br>바래다줄게 <br>내게 기대]]></content><category term="백현 (BAEKHYUN)" label="백현 (BAEKHYUN)"/><category term="바래다줄게 (Take You Home) (Inst.)" label="바래다줄게 (Take You Home) (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백현_BAEKHYUN/바래다줄게_Take_You_Home/</id><title>백현 (BAEKHYUN) - 바래다줄게 (Take You Home) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:03:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:03:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%ED%98%84_BAEKHYUN/%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%98%EB%8B%A4%EC%A4%84%EA%B2%8C_Take_You_Home/" title="백현 (BAEKHYUN) - 바래다줄게 (Take You Home) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[알아 <br>아무렇지도 않은 척해 봐도 <br>기다린단 걸 애써 웃어 보는 <br>눈가에 묻은 슬픔 <br>내가 어쩔 수 없단 걸 <br>느낄 수 있어 <br>괜찮아 미안하단 말 <br>곁에 있는 것만으로 <br>충분해 하지 마 <br>아냐 됐다 그냥 네 맘 <br>편하면 들어줄게 <br>네 남자 아니지만 <br>조금만 지켜봐 줘 <br>I need you girl <br>너의 그 사람 아니지만 <br>너를 안아줄 순 없어도 <br>널 집에 데려갈 <br>넓은 등을 가진 그런 남자야 <br>바래다줄게 <br>내게 기대 <br>아무렇지도 않은 척해 봐도 <br>기다린단 걸 애써 미소 짓는 <br>입가에 묻은 슬픔 <br>네가 어쩔 수 없단 걸 <br>느낄 수 있어 <br>괜찮아 미안하단 말 <br>곁에 있는 것만으로 <br>충분해 하지 마 <br>아냐 됐다 그냥 네 맘 <br>편하면 들어줄게 <br>네 남자 아니지만 <br>조금만 지켜봐 줘 <br>I need you girl <br>너의 그 사람 아니지만 <br>너를 안아줄 순 없어도 <br>널 집에 데려갈 <br>넓은 등을 가진 그런 남자야 <br>바래다줄게 <br>내게 기대 <br>이 말도 안 되는 <br>어설픈 위로만으로 <br>힘이 되었단 걸 그때의 난 <br>널 웃게 할 수 있단 걸 <br>그 앤 왜 모르는지 <br>내 모습 그대로를 <br>조금만 지켜봐 줘 <br>I love you girl <br>너의 그 사람 아니지만 <br>지금 안아볼 순 없대도 <br>네 곁을 지켜줄 <br>넓은 맘을 가진 그런 남자야 <br>바래다줄게 <br>내게 기대 <br>]]></content><category term="백현 (BAEKHYUN)" label="백현 (BAEKHYUN)"/><category term="바래다줄게 (Take You Home)" label="바래다줄게 (Take You Home)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인모스트/Reunion_동창회/</id><title>인모스트 - Reunion (동창회) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:03:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:03:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EB%AA%A8%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/Reunion_%EB%8F%99%EC%B0%BD%ED%9A%8C/" title="인모스트 - Reunion (동창회) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 담배를 물면 조금 나았을까 <br>그 때 진짜 나 혼자만 떨렸을까 <br>술 한 잔에 고백하면 나았을까 <br>그 때 손을 잡았다면 달랐을까 <br>오랜만이야 내 폰에 <br>네 번호가 찍힌게 <br>연락 안하고 산 지 <br>몇 년 된거 같은데 <br>간만에 만나 우리 커피나 한 잔 해 <br>술은 잘 못해 대충 걸치고 나갈게 <br>당연하듯 흡연실 옆 자리잡은 너 <br>쑥쓰럽게 담배갑을 테이블에 올려 <br>그걸 싫어하는 나인걸 알면서도 <br>불편하다거나 하는 건 못 느껴 <br>많은게 변했어 대화를 하면서 <br>안부를 물으며 잘 지내고 있냐고 <br>자연스레 물어 보다가도 <br>전화가 울리면 담배갑을 들고 <br>일어서는 너 <br>한 개비 물고 애뜻한 표정을 하는 <br>그 모습이 딱히 걱정되진 않아 <br>그냥 내 여자는 아니겠구나 하는 <br>속물된 생각에 다시 커피잔만 핥아 <br>내가 담배를 물면 조금 나았을까 <br>그 때 진짜 나 혼자만 떨렸을까 <br>술 한 잔에 고백하면 나았을까 <br>그 때 손을 잡았다면 달랐을까 <br>바래다 주고 나서 다시 돌아오는 길 <br>다른 방향의 집 가는 길에 나눈 <br>이야기 뒤에 혼자 오던 <br>길을 돌아가며 <br>아 나와 다른 방향을 다녔지 <br>생각에 잠기며 서있는 가로등 밑에 <br>담배와 커피가 뒤섞인 향기에 <br>순간 속이 메스껍다가도 안 그래 <br>그런 것 만큼이나 내 기분도 신기해 <br>전에는 꿈에 자주 나온 얼굴이 <br>이젠 눈꼽만큼도 보이지도 않아 <br>억지로 기억해보려 해보니 <br>자다깨니 새벽 짜증만이 남아 <br>질투인걸까 체념인걸까 <br>헌데 이제와 그건 중요하지 않아 <br>한 시간이라도 자려는 생각에 <br>기억을 더듬어 꿈 속을 다시 찾아 <br>내가 담배를 물면 조금 나았을까 <br>그 때 진짜 나 혼자만 떨렸을까 <br>술 한 잔에 고백하면 나았을까 <br>그 때 손을 잡았다면 달랐을까 <br>내가 담배를 물면 조금 나았을까 <br>아니면 술자리였다면 <br>차라리 편했을까 <br>모르겠어라며 이젠 덮어놓고 싶어도 <br>맴돌아 그 날 마신 커피의 메슥함 <br>내가 담배를 물면 조금 나았을까 <br>아니면 술자리였다면 <br>차라리 편했을까 <br>모르겠어라며 이젠 덮어놓고 싶어도 <br>맴돌아 그 날 마신 담배 연기의 매캐함 <br>내가 담배를 물면 조금 나았을까 <br>그 때 진짜 나 혼자만 떨렸을까 <br>술 한 잔에 고백하면 나았을까 <br>그 때 손을 잡았다면 달랐을까 <br>내가 담배를 물면 조금 나았을까 <br>그 때 진짜 나 혼자만 떨렸을까 <br>술 한 잔에 고백하면 나았을까 <br>그 때 손을 잡았다면 달랐을까 <br>]]></content><category term="인모스트" label="인모스트"/><category term="Reunion (동창회)" label="Reunion (동창회)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/데이브니어_Dave_Near/하늘과_바다/</id><title>데이브니어 (Dave Near) - 하늘과 바다 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:09:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:09:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%B8%8C%EB%8B%88%EC%96%B4_Dave_Near/%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98%EA%B3%BC_%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%A4/" title="데이브니어 (Dave Near) - 하늘과 바다 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[저 하늘을 바라볼 때면 <br>저 바다를 바라볼 때면 <br>너의 이름 살며시 불러본다 <br>그 무엇이 그토록 붙들었나 <br>그대여 나는 더 이상 <br>외면하고 도망치고 싶진 않아 <br>저 바다 위를 걸어가보자 <br>거칠 것도 두려울 것도 없이 <br>저 하늘 위로 날아가보자 <br>거칠 것도 두려울 것도 없이 <br>그 무엇이 그토록 붙들었나 <br>그대여 나는 더 이상 <br>외면하고 도망치고 싶진 않아 <br>저 바다 위를 걸어가보자 <br>거칠 것도 두려울 것도 없이 <br>저 하늘 위로 날아가보자 <br>거칠 것도 두려울 것도 없이 <br>이제 일어나서 두 눈을 뜨고 <br>새롭게 맞아야 할 시간이 왔어 <br>어깻죽지에 난 날개를 펴고 <br>우리가 바라던 그 세계로 <br>저 바다 위를 걸어가보자 <br>거칠 것도 두려울 것도 없이 <br>저 하늘 위로 날아가보자 <br>거칠 것도 두려울 것도 <br>저 바다 위를 걸어가보자 <br>거칠 것도 두려울 것도 없이 <br>저 하늘 위로 날아가보자 <br>거칠 것도 두려울 것도 <br>거칠 것도 두려울 것도 <br>거칠 것도 두려울 것도 없이 <br>]]></content><category term="데이브니어 (Dave Near)" label="데이브니어 (Dave Near)"/><category term="하늘과 바다" label="하늘과 바다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/에스토_Esto/되걸음_Feat_최정원/</id><title>에스토 (Esto) - 되걸음 (Feat. 최정원) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:09:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:09:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%90%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0_Esto/%EB%90%98%EA%B1%B8%EC%9D%8C_Feat_%EC%B5%9C%EC%A0%95%EC%9B%90/" title="에스토 (Esto) - 되걸음 (Feat. 최정원) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너와 함께했던 우리 그저 안녕 <br>가끔 생각이나 지금 우리 우린 왜 <br>oh 내 맘 어떡하나요 <br>이별이 쉽지 않아 <br>oh 그댈 잊어보아도 <br>어느새 선명해져 <br>그대 오 그대 나만 이렇게 아픈가요 <br>그대 오 그대 정말 이렇게 끝인가요 <br>oh 함께 걷던 이 길도 <br>나누던 추억하나 <br>다 모두 여기 있는데 <br>내 곁에 그대 하나만 없는 거죠 <br>그대 오 그대 정말 이렇게 끝인가요 <br>그대 오 그대 난 안되죠 난 못하죠 <br>그댈 지워내는 거 <br>그대 오 그대 내게 다시 돌아와요 <br>그대 오 그대 우린 정말 끝난 거죠 <br>]]></content><category term="에스토 (Esto)" label="에스토 (Esto)"/><category term="되걸음 (Feat. 최정원)" label="되걸음 (Feat. 최정원)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/A-CHESS/그녀는/</id><title>A-CHESS - 그녀는 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:10:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:10:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/A-CHESS/%EA%B7%B8%EB%85%80%EB%8A%94/" title="A-CHESS - 그녀는 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 솔직한 거니 <br>내겐 진심인 거니 <br>눈앞에 니가 있단 게 <br>좀 두려워 <br>깨끗이 정리된 거니 <br>정말 믿어도 되니 <br>이렇게 한 번씩 두 번씩 <br>믿음을 깨면 No <br>아프다는 핑계 대고 <br>핸드폰은 연락 두절 <br>정말 이럴 땐 어떡해야 해 <br>죽 싸들고 약 사들고 <br>집 앞으로 찾아가서 <br>나 왔어 라고 말해도 <br>아무런 기척조차 나지 않아 <br>믿어도 될지 <br>끝도 없이 반복될런지 <br>너라는 사람에게는 <br>확신이 서지 않아 <br>내일이면 잊을까 <br>이게 집착인 걸까 <br>언제까지 내가 버틸 수 있을지 <br>어디 갔었니 <br>내겐 연락도 없이 <br>정말 솔직하게 얘기 좀 해봐 <br>납득할 수 있게 <br>너 원래 이 정도였니 <br>이것 밖에 안됐니 <br>이렇게 대답도 변명도 <br>아무 말없이 No <br>하루 종일 전화해도 <br>핸드폰은 연락 두절 <br>정말 이럴 땐 어떡해야 해 <br>기다리고 기다리다 <br>친구 놈의 연락 한 통 <br>니 애인 어떤 남자랑 <br>지금 사이 좋게 놀고 있어 <br>믿어도 될지 <br>끝도 없이 반복될런지 <br>너라는 사람에게는 <br>확신이 서지 않아 <br>내일이면 잊을까 <br>이게 집착인 걸까 <br>언제까지 내가 버틸 수 있을지 <br>술에 취해 마중 가면 <br>모르는 놈의 어깨에 기대 <br>정말 이럴 땐 어떡해야 해 <br>괜찮다고 술 깼다고 <br>내일 낮에 만나자고 말하고 <br>하루 지나면 아무런 <br>기억조차 하지 못해 <br>믿어도 될지 <br>끝도 없이 반복될런지 <br>너라는 사람에게는 <br>확신이 서지 않아 <br>내일이면 잊을까 <br>이게 집착인 걸까 <br>언제까지 내가 버틸 수 있을지 <br>]]></content><category term="A-CHESS" label="A-CHESS"/><category term="그녀는" label="그녀는"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박정현/나_가거든/</id><title>박정현 - 나 가거든 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:11:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:11:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A0%95%ED%98%84/%EB%82%98_%EA%B0%80%EA%B1%B0%EB%93%A0/" title="박정현 - 나 가거든 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쓸쓸한 달빛 아래 <br>내 그림자 하나 생기거든 <br>그땐 말해볼까요 이 마음 <br>들어나 주라고 <br>문득 새벽을 알리는 <br>그 바람 하나가 지나거든 <br>그저 한숨 쉬듯 물어 볼까요 <br>난 왜 살고 있는지 <br>나 슬퍼도 살아야 하네 <br>나 슬퍼서 살아야 하네 <br>이 삶이 다하고 나야 알 텐데 <br>내가 이 세상을 다녀간 그 이유 <br>나가고 기억 하는 이 <br>나 슬픔까지도 <br>사랑했다 말해주길 <br>흩어진 노을처럼 <br>내 아픈 기억도 바래지면 <br>그땐 웃어줄까요 이 마음 <br>그리운 옛일로 <br>저기 홀로 선 별 하나 <br>나의 외로움을 아는 건지 <br>차마 날 두고는 떠나지 못해 <br>밤새 그 자리에만 <br>나 슬퍼도 살아야 하네 <br>나 슬퍼서 살아야 하네 <br>이 삶이 다하고 나야 알 텐데 <br>내가 이 세상을 다녀간 그 이유 <br>나가고 기억 하는 이 <br>내 슬픔까지도 사랑하길 <br>나가고 슬퍼하는 이 <br>나 슬픔 속에도 <br>행복했다 믿게 해 <br>]]></content><category term="박정현" label="박정현"/><category term="나 가거든" label="나 가거든"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박정현/꿈에/</id><title>박정현 - 꿈에 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:11:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:11:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A0%95%ED%98%84/%EA%BF%88%EC%97%90/" title="박정현 - 꿈에 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어떤 말을 해야 하는지 <br>난 너무 가슴이 떨려서 <br>우리 옛날 그대로의 <br>모습으로 만나고 있네요 <br>이건 꿈인 걸 알지만 <br>지금 이대로 깨지 않고서 <br>영원히 잠 잘 수 있다면 <br>날 안아 주네요 예전 모습처럼 <br>그 동안 힘들었지 <br>나를 보며 위로하네요 <br>내 손을 잡네요 <br>지친 맘 이젠 쉬라며 <br>지금도 그대 손은 <br>그때처럼 따뜻하네요 <br>혹시 이게 꿈이란 걸 <br>그대가 알게 하진 않을 거야 <br>내가 정말 잘 할거야 <br>그대 다른 생각 못하도록 <br>그대 이젠 가지 마요 <br>그냥 여기서 나와 있어줘요 <br>나도 깨지 않을 게요 <br>이젠 보내지 않을 거예요 <br>계속 나를 안아 주세요 <br>예전 모습처럼 <br>그 동안 힘들었지 <br>나를 보며 위로하네요 <br>내 손을 잡네요 <br>지친 맘 이젠 쉬라며 <br>지금도 그대 손은 <br>그때처럼 따뜻하네요 <br>대답해줘요 그대도 <br>나를 나만큼 그리워했다고 <br>바보같이 즐거워만 하는 <br>날 보며 <br>날 보면 <br>안쓰런 미소로 <br>슬픈 미소로 <br>이제 나 먼저 갈게 <br>미안한 듯 얘길 하네요 <br>나처럼 그대도 <br>그대도 <br>알고 있었군요 <br>꿈이라는걸 <br>그래도 고마워요 <br>이렇게라도 만나줘서 <br>날 안아 주네요 작별인사라며 <br>나 웃어 줄게요 <br>이렇게 보내긴 싫은데 <br>뒤돌아 서네요 다시 그 때처럼 <br>나 잠 깨고 나면 <br>또 다시 혼자 있겠네요 <br>저 멀리 가네요 이젠 익숙하죠 <br>나 이제 울게요 <br>또 다시 보내기 싫은데 <br>보이지 않아요 <br>이제 다시 눈을 떴는데 <br>가슴이 많이 시리네요 <br>고마워요 <br>사랑해요 <br>난 괜찮아요 다신 오지 말아요 <br>]]></content><category term="박정현" label="박정현"/><category term="꿈에" label="꿈에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김범수/하루/</id><title>김범수 - 하루 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:11:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:11:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%B2%94%EC%88%98/%ED%95%98%EB%A3%A8/" title="김범수 - 하루 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑이 날 또 아프게 해요 <br>사랑이 날 또 울게 하네요 <br>그렇게 사랑했던 추억마저 <br>잊어달라며 <br>사랑은 잔인하게 떠나가네요 <br>정말 내가 괜찮을까요 <br>그대가 한 그 인사처럼 <br>그래도 이 세상에 살고 싶단 <br>행복을 주는 건 <br>너무나도 고마웠어요 <br>사랑이 날 또 아프게 해요 <br>사랑이 날 또 울게 하네요 <br>그렇게 사랑했던 추억마저 <br>잊어달라며 <br>사랑은 잔인하게 떠나가네요 <br>잊을 수도 있을 거예요 <br>그대처럼 나도 변하겠죠 <br>하지만 그날까지 내가 <br>어찌 살아낼까요 <br>벌써 그댈 보고 싶어요 <br>사랑이 날 또 아프게 해요 <br>사랑이 날 또 울게 하네요 <br>그렇게 사랑했던 추억마저 <br>잊어달라며 <br>사랑은 잔인하게 떠나가네요 <br>이렇게 또 하루가 지나가네요 <br>남겨진 모든 걸 가져가줘요 <br>참을 수가 없는 아픔도 기억도 <br>사랑이 날 또 아프게 해요 <br>사랑이 날 또 울게 하네요 <br>그렇게 사랑했던 추억마저 <br>잊어달라며 <br>사랑은 잔인하게 떠나가네요 <br>사랑이 사랑이 사랑이 날 <br>다시는 못 쓰게 된 내 가슴은 <br>이렇게 아픈데 <br>사랑은 꿈을 깨듯 허무하네요 <br>이렇게 또 하루가 지나 <br>이렇게 또 하루가 지나 <br>이렇게 또 하루가 지나가네요 <br>]]></content><category term="김범수" label="김범수"/><category term="하루" label="하루"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박형식/그_사람이_너라서_Inst/</id><title>박형식 - 그 사람이 너라서 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:13:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:13:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%98%95%EC%8B%9D/%EA%B7%B8_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C%EC%9D%B4_%EB%84%88%EB%9D%BC%EC%84%9C_Inst/" title="박형식 - 그 사람이 너라서 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 안에 작은 떨림이 있어요 <br>나조차 모르던 낯선 모습이죠 <br>숨 쉴때 마다 숨겨둔 내 마음 <br>조금씩 깨어나 자꾸만 차올라 <br>내 안은 너의 빛으로 물들어요 <br>눈을 감아도 비처럼 스며든 <br>그 사람이 너라서 그 사람이 너라서 <br>머리 속엔 떠오르지만 <br>마음 속에 숨겨 둔 <br>내 입술 끝에 걸린 이 말 널 사랑해 <br>너를 볼때면 미소가 번져요 <br>예전엔 모르던 낯선 모습이죠 <br>사랑에 서툰 내 모습이지만 <br>이제는 용기내 조금씩 다가가 <br>니 안을 나의 빛으로 물들일래 <br>눈을 감아도 비처럼 스며든 <br>그 사람이 너라서 그 사람이 너라서 <br>머리 속엔 떠오르지만 <br>마음 속에 숨겨 둔 <br>내 입술 끝에 걸린 이 말 널 사랑해 <br>늦지 않길 바래요 <br>지금 내가 달려가 <br>너를 품에 꼭 안고서 고백할게 <br>눈을 감아도 비처럼 스며든 <br>단 한사람 너라서 나의 끝은 너라서 <br>더이상 숨길 수 없어서 <br>결국 너여야 해서 <br>내입술 끝내 고백한 말 널 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="박형식" label="박형식"/><category term="그 사람이 너라서 (Inst.)" label="그 사람이 너라서 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박형식/그_사람이_너라서/</id><title>박형식 - 그 사람이 너라서 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:13:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:13:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%98%95%EC%8B%9D/%EA%B7%B8_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C%EC%9D%B4_%EB%84%88%EB%9D%BC%EC%84%9C/" title="박형식 - 그 사람이 너라서 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 안에 작은 떨림이 있어요 <br>나조차 모르던 낯선 모습이죠 <br>숨 쉴때 마다 숨겨둔 내 마음 <br>조금씩 깨어나 자꾸만 차올라 <br>내 안은 너의 빛으로 물들어요 <br>눈을 감아도 비처럼 스며든 <br>그 사람이 너라서 그 사람이 너라서 <br>머리 속엔 떠오르지만 <br>마음 속에 숨겨 둔 <br>내 입술 끝에 걸린 이 말 널 사랑해 <br>너를 볼때면 미소가 번져요 <br>예전엔 모르던 낯선 모습이죠 <br>사랑에 서툰 내 모습이지만 <br>이제는 용기내 조금씩 다가가 <br>니 안을 나의 빛으로 물들일래 <br>눈을 감아도 비처럼 스며든 <br>그 사람이 너라서 그 사람이 너라서 <br>머리 속엔 떠오르지만 <br>마음 속에 숨겨 둔 <br>내 입술 끝에 걸린 이 말 널 사랑해 <br>늦지 않길 바래요 <br>지금 내가 달려가 <br>너를 품에 꼭 안고서 고백할게 <br>눈을 감아도 비처럼 스며든 <br>단 한사람 너라서 나의 끝은 너라서 <br>더이상 숨길 수 없어서 <br>결국 너여야 해서 <br>내입술 끝내 고백한 말 널 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="박형식" label="박형식"/><category term="그 사람이 너라서" label="그 사람이 너라서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강경철/한걸음_Feat_성민/</id><title>강경철 - 한걸음 (Feat. 성민) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:16:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:16:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EA%B2%BD%EC%B2%A0/%ED%95%9C%EA%B1%B8%EC%9D%8C_Feat_%EC%84%B1%EB%AF%BC/" title="강경철 - 한걸음 (Feat. 성민) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한걸음 한걸음 너에게 한걸음 <br>이제 말할게 너에게 내 마음을 <br>나의 간절한 마음이 네게 닿길 <br>한걸음 너에게 한걸음 <br>한걸음 네 마음에 한 걸음 <br>너의 마음속에 내가 <br>한걸음 더 가면 안되니 <br>한걸음 너에게 한걸음 <br>가는 날 받아줄 수는 없니 <br>이런 마음이 네게 전해 지길 <br>이젠 말해줘 나에게 니 마음을 <br>나의 간절한 마음이 네게 닿았다고 <br>네 마음으로 가는 길을 <br>내게 알려 줄 수 없겠니 <br>네 마음에 한걸음 더 갈 수 있게 <br>한걸음 너에게 한걸음 <br>한걸음 네 마음에 한걸음 <br>너의 마음속에 내가 <br>한걸음 더 가면 안되니 <br>한걸음 너에게 한걸음 <br>가는 날 받아줄 수는 없니 <br>이런 마음이 네게 전해 지길 <br>]]></content><category term="강경철" label="강경철"/><category term="한걸음 (Feat. 성민)" label="한걸음 (Feat. 성민)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동그란/비행청소년/</id><title>동그란 - 비행청소년 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:16:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:16:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%80/%EB%B9%84%ED%96%89%EC%B2%AD%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84/" title="동그란 - 비행청소년 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가끔 창 밖을 보면 <br>날아가는 비행기를 잡고 싶어 <br>가끔 창 밖을 보면 <br>구름인지 얼룩인지 <br>누가 날 이렇게 만들었나 <br>아무도 그러지 않았어 <br>나는 널 데리고 하늘높이 <br>자유롭게 날아갈 거야 <br>가끔 창 밖을 보면 <br>날아가는 비행기를 잡고 싶어 <br>가끔 창 밖을 보면 <br>구름인지 얼룩인지 <br>누가 날 이렇게 만들었나 <br>아무도 그러지 않았어 <br>나는 널 데리고 하늘높이 <br>자유롭게 날아갈 거야 <br>가끔 창 밖을 보면 <br>창 밖을 보면 <br>날아가는 비행기를 잡고 싶어 <br>잡고 싶어 <br>가끔 창 밖을 보면 <br>창 밖을 보면 <br>구름인지 얼룩인지 <br>가끔 창 밖을 보면 <br>날아가는 비행기를 잡고 싶어 <br>가끔 창 밖을 보면 <br>구름인지 얼룩인지 <br>가끔 창 밖을 보면 <br>날아가는 비행기를 잡고 싶어 <br>가끔 창 밖을 보면 <br>구름인지 얼룩인지 <br>]]></content><category term="동그란" label="동그란"/><category term="비행청소년" label="비행청소년"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동그란/위로가_필요한_날/</id><title>동그란 - 위로가 필요한 날 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:16:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:16:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%80/%EC%9C%84%EB%A1%9C%EA%B0%80_%ED%95%84%EC%9A%94%ED%95%9C_%EB%82%A0/" title="동그란 - 위로가 필요한 날 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[멍이 들어서 스치는 바람에 <br>혹시 들킬까 상처를 감추는 <br>너는 그렇게 <br>약하지 않았는데 <br>우리들 일 때 <br>빛나던 너였는데 <br>너는 아마도 <br>두려운 거겠죠 <br>혼자라는 게 <br>혹시 위로가 필요하면 <br>이 노랠 듣고 여기로 와줘 <br>우는 널 위해 같이 노래를 부를게 <br>그 순간만큼은 가장 행복했던 <br>우리의 목소리만 들릴 거야 <br>사실 누구도 지금은 힘들고 <br>다시 내일을 지키긴 어려워 <br>그날 그때로 <br>돌아갈 수는 없어 <br>아마도 너는 <br>향기를 잃었지 <br>그래도 같이 <br>한다면 너는 <br>빛나겠지 <br>혹시 위로가 필요하면 <br>이 노랠 듣고 여기로 와줘 <br>우는 널 위해 같이 노래를 부를게 <br>그 순간만큼은 가장 행복했던 <br>우리의 목소리만 들릴 거야 <br>너 혼자 울지 않아도 돼 <br>너 혼자 버티지 않아도 돼 <br>언제나 힘들면 다시 돌아와 <br>내가 여기 있을 테니 <br>혹시 위로가 필요하면 <br>]]></content><category term="동그란" label="동그란"/><category term="위로가 필요한 날" label="위로가 필요한 날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월31일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월31일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:16:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:16:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9431%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월31일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월31일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월31일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월31일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월31일 생일축하노래" label="5월31일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월30일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월30일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:16:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:16:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9430%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월30일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월30일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월30일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월30일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월30일 생일축하노래" label="5월30일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월29일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월29일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:16:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:16:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9429%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월29일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월29일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월29일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월29일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월29일 생일축하노래" label="5월29일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월28일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월28일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:16:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:16:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9428%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월28일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월28일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월28일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월28일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월28일 생일축하노래" label="5월28일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월27일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월27일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:16:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:16:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9427%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월27일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월27일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월27일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월27일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월27일 생일축하노래" label="5월27일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월26일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월26일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:17:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:17:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9426%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월26일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월26일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월26일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월26일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월26일 생일축하노래" label="5월26일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월25일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월25일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:17:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:17:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9425%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월25일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월25일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월25일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월25일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월25일 생일축하노래" label="5월25일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월24일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월24일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:17:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:17:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9424%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월24일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월24일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월24일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월24일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월24일 생일축하노래" label="5월24일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월23일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월23일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:17:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:17:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9423%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월23일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월23일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월23일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월23일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월23일 생일축하노래" label="5월23일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월22일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월22일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:17:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:17:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9422%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월22일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월22일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월22일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월22일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월22일 생일축하노래" label="5월22일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월21일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월21일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:17:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:17:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9421%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월21일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월21일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월21일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월21일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월21일 생일축하노래" label="5월21일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월20일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월20일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:17:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:17:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9420%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월20일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월20일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월20일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월20일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월20일 생일축하노래" label="5월20일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월19일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월19일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:17:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:17:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9419%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월19일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월19일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월19일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월19일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월19일 생일축하노래" label="5월19일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월18일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월18일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:17:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:17:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9418%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월18일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월18일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월18일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월18일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월18일 생일축하노래" label="5월18일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월17일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월17일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:17:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:17:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9417%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월17일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월17일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월17일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월17일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월17일 생일축하노래" label="5월17일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월16일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월16일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:17:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:17:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9416%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월16일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월16일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월16일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월16일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월16일 생일축하노래" label="5월16일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월15일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월15일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:17:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:17:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9415%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월15일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월15일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월15일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월15일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월15일 생일축하노래" label="5월15일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월14일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월14일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:17:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:17:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9414%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월14일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월14일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월14일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월14일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월14일 생일축하노래" label="5월14일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월13일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월13일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:17:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:17:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9413%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월13일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월13일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월13일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월13일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월13일 생일축하노래" label="5월13일 생일축하노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/축하사절단/5월12일_생일축하노래/</id><title>축하사절단 - 5월12일 생일축하노래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T08:17:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T08:17:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%88%EB%8B%A8/5%EC%9B%9412%EC%9D%BC_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC%EC%B6%95%ED%95%98%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="축하사절단 - 5월12일 생일축하노래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 5월12일 당신의 생일을 축하합니다 <br><br>오늘은 5월12일 당신의 생일이죠 <br>아름다운 5월 저 푸른 하늘만큼 <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>케이크에 촛불을 켜고 <br>생일축하노래를 불러요 <br>두눈을 감고 두손모아 기도해요 <br>그대 언제나 행복하기를 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>봄바람도 살랑살랑 그대의 생일을 축하해 <br>내 마음도 살랑살랑 그대에게 마음이 향하네 <br>친구의 인스타를 보고 블로그 페이스북 보고 <br>오늘 생일 여러분들을 위한 노래, 5월12일 생일축하노래 <br>1, 2, 3, Let's Go <br><br>생일 축하해요 <br>생일 축하해요 <br>당신의 생일을 정말 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br><br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>Happy Happy Birthday To You <br>당신의 생일을 축하해요 <br>]]></content><category term="축하사절단" label="축하사절단"/><category term="5월12일 생일축하노래" label="5월12일 생일축하노래"/></entry></feed>