<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:15:41+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나비/59-10/</id><title>나비 - 59-10 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:54:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:54:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84/59-10/" title="나비 - 59-10 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Green grass Cloudy sky <br>And Wide spread grass lands <br>Step on the grass barefoot <br>Step on the grass barefoot <br>Step on the grass barefoot <br>Step on the grass barefoot <br>Step on the grass barefoot <br>Step on the grass barefoot <br>Step on the grass barefoot <br>I do not get tired <br>It is still lying <br>In the grass just like you <br>It is still lying <br>In the grass just like you <br>Green grass Cloudy sky <br>And wide spread grass lands <br>Moist grass moist eyes <br>Moist feet Suddenly the night <br>Suddenly the night <br>]]></content><category term="나비" label="나비"/><category term="59-10" label="59-10"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/젊은이/제자리/</id><title>젊은이 - 제자리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:55:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:55:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%8A%EC%9D%80%EC%9D%B4/%EC%A0%9C%EC%9E%90%EB%A6%AC/" title="젊은이 - 제자리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[대답하지도 못했던 말들은 <br>돌아오는 걸음에 밟히고 <br>질문은 차갑게 바람에 실려가 <br>스치는 사람들 모두 같은 얼굴 <br>거리를 가득 채운 들뜬 걸음 <br>짓누르는 것 같은 공기에 <br>마른 기침 속에 섞여 버린 마음 <br>하나 둘 켜지는 불빛 따라가네 <br>어디까지 왔을까 <br>얼만큼 떠나 버렸나 <br>애써 떨치며 괜찮다 <br>추스려 보지만 <br>어느 곳에 있을까 <br>조금 가까워진 걸까 <br>걷고 걸어도 <br>오늘도 제자리 같은데 <br>질문은 차갑게 바람에 실려가 <br>스치는 사람들 모두 같은 얼굴 <br>마른 기침 속에 섞여 버린 마음 <br>하나 둘 켜지는 불빛 따라가네 <br>어디까지 왔을까 <br>얼만큼 떠나 버렸나 <br>애써 떨치며 괜찮다 <br>추스려 보지만 <br>어느 곳에 있을까 <br>조금 가까워진 걸까 <br>걷고 걸어도 <br>오늘도 제자리 같은데 <br>]]></content><category term="젊은이" label="젊은이"/><category term="제자리" label="제자리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이석훈/오늘은_어제보다_괜찮았지/</id><title>이석훈 - 오늘은 어제보다 괜찮았지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:55:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:55:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%9D%ED%9B%88/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98%EC%9D%80_%EC%96%B4%EC%A0%9C%EB%B3%B4%EB%8B%A4_%EA%B4%9C%EC%B0%AE%EC%95%98%EC%A7%80/" title="이석훈 - 오늘은 어제보다 괜찮았지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다음은 어디쯤일까 <br>가끔씩 생각을 해봐 <br>하루가 오늘따라 참 길었지 <br>지친 내 몸을 뉘이고 <br>아직은 아니겠지만 <br>어쩐지 서운하지만 <br>오늘은 어제보다 괜찮았지 <br>누군가 말해주기를 <br>가끔은 내가 짊어진 <br>어깨에 짐이 무거워 <br>그래도 아직 여기에 <br>곁에 있으니 <br>그대 내 곁에 있으니 <br>아직은 아니겠지만 <br>어쩐지 서운하지만 <br>오늘은 어제보다 괜찮았지 <br>누군가 말해주기를 <br>가끔은 내가 짊어진 <br>어깨에 짐이 무거워 <br>그래도 아직 여기에 <br>곁에 있으니 <br>그대 내 곁에 있으니 <br>아직은 아니겠지만 <br>어쩐지 서운하지만 <br>오늘은 어제보다 괜찮았지 <br>누군가 말해주기를 <br>]]></content><category term="이석훈" label="이석훈"/><category term="오늘은 어제보다 괜찮았지" label="오늘은 어제보다 괜찮았지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/데이브레이크_DAYBREAK/Mellow_Drama_Ver/</id><title>데이브레이크_DAYBREAK - Mellow (Drama Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:55:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:55:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%B8%8C%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%ED%81%AC_DAYBREAK/Mellow_Drama_Ver/" title="데이브레이크_DAYBREAK - Mellow (Drama Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[두 눈을 깜박거리면 나는 어떡해 <br>그렇게 피식 웃으면 나는 어떡해 <br>애써 분위기를 잡고 <br>입술은 눈 앞에 있고 <br>나 지금 장난 아닌데 <br>일단 눈은 감았는데 <br>이 다음엔 어떡해 <br>심장이 왜 이래 숨소리 어떡해 <br>고개를 오른쪽으로 <br>왜 너도 같은쪽으로 <br>서툴게 샤랄라랄라 <br>Mellow mellow mellow <br>드라마 같지는 않지만 <br>Mellow mellow <br>우린 그런 걸로 <br>마시멜로우 같은 <br>달콤한 너의 입술에 <br>샤랄라 <br>춥다고 집에 가자고 하면 어떡해 <br>혼자 가도 괜찮다고 하면 어떡해 <br>너의 손을 꼭 붙잡고 <br>난 좀 더 걷고 싶었고 <br>헤어질 때 또 샤랄라라라 <br>Mellow mellow mellow <br>드라마 같지는 않지만 <br>Mellow mellow <br>우린 그런 걸로 <br>마시멜로우 같은 <br>달콤한 너의 입술에 <br>샤랄라 <br>지금 이 순간을 한 번 더 어때 <br>오늘 이 장면을 한 번 더 어때 <br>이대로 끝이길 <br>바라는 해피엔딩처럼 <br>샤랄라 샤랄라 샤랄라 <br>Mellow mellow mellow <br>드라마 같지는 않지만 <br>Mellow mellow <br>우린 그런 걸로 <br>마시멜로우 같은 <br>달콤한 너의 입술에 <br>샤랄라 <br>Mellow mellow mellow <br>드라마 같지는 않아도 <br>Mellow mellow <br>우린 사랑의 <br>마시멜로우 같은 <br>달콤한 우리 사이에 <br>샤랄라 <br>]]></content><category term="데이브레이크 (DAYBREAK)" label="데이브레이크 (DAYBREAK)"/><category term="Mellow (Drama Ver.)" label="Mellow (Drama Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/해빈_구구단/Forever_Love/</id><title>해빈_구구단 - Forever Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:55:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:55:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%B4%EB%B9%88_%EA%B5%AC%EA%B5%AC%EB%8B%A8/Forever_Love/" title="해빈_구구단 - Forever Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아직 네겐 말할 수 없죠 <br>그대였다는 걸 <br>난 알고 있지만 <br>조금 더 널 느낄 수 있게 <br>내 곁에 내 맘에 있어요 <br>I Will love with you <br>forever love <br>아직 내 마음 <br>네 안에 남아 널 <br>I Will love with you <br>forever love <br>아직도 난 못 잊어 <br>아직도 난 그리워 <br>처음 본 너의 모습 <br>상처 위에 상처가 나도 <br>아픈 줄 모르고 <br>날 다그쳤었던 <br>미련하게 바보 같던 날 <br>예쁘다 안아 준 한 사람 <br>I Will love with you <br>forever love <br>아직 내 마음 <br>네 안에 남아 널 <br>I Will love with you <br>forever love <br>내 곁을 떠나지 마 <br>눈을 감아도 그대와 난 <br>사랑이었을거야 <br>수없이 끊어져도 <br>이어질 얘길거야 <br>다시 내게 돌아온 <br>너의 그 따뜻한 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="해빈 (구구단)" label="해빈 (구구단)"/><category term="Forever Love" label="Forever Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이현/그대라서/</id><title>이현 - 그대라서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:55:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:55:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%98%84/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%9D%BC%EC%84%9C/" title="이현 - 그대라서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한번 날 바라봐요 <br>미소 가득한 얼굴 보여요 <br>그대 맘이 내 맘에 보여요 <br>또 내 안에 <br>그대를 향한 사랑 있죠 <br>다시 날 밀어내도 <br>그댈 포기할 수가 없네요 <br>힘들었던 지나온 시간이 <br>또 그리운 사랑이 <br>아직 내 안에 남아 <br>다시 널 기다리는데 <br>그대라서 그대라서 <br>내 운명이죠 <br>그 무엇과도 <br>바꿀 수가 없네요 <br>you are my life <br>내 안에 품은 <br>그대 얼굴이 <br>환히 웃도록 <br>미소 짓도록 그대 <br>이젠 난 깨달아요 <br>내가 살아갈 이유 그대가 <br>내 손을 잡고 <br>같이 숨 쉬고 <br>또 내 안의 심장이 <br>그댈 향하는 것은 <br>내 사랑 하나뿐임을 <br>그대라서 그대라서 <br>내 운명이죠 <br>그 무엇과도 <br>바꿀 수가 없네요 <br>you are my life <br>내 안에 품은 <br>그대 얼굴이 <br>환히 웃도록 <br>미소 짓도록 그대 <br>I'll be there for you <br>단 한순간도 그댈 <br>잊지 않을거라 믿어요 <br>그대라서 그대라서 <br>내 운명이죠 <br>그 무엇과도 <br>바꿀 수가 없네요 <br>you are my life <br>내 안에 품은 <br>그대 얼굴이 <br>환히 웃도록 <br>미소 짓도록 <br>그대 <br>]]></content><category term="이현" label="이현"/><category term="그대라서" label="그대라서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전인권/걷고_걷고_New_Ver/</id><title>전인권 - 걷고, 걷고 (New Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:55:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:55:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%9D%B8%EA%B6%8C/%EA%B1%B7%EA%B3%A0_%EA%B1%B7%EA%B3%A0_New_Ver/" title="전인권 - 걷고, 걷고 (New Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[걷고 걷고 또 걷는다 <br>새벽 그대 떠난 길 지나 <br>아침은 다시 밝아오겠지 <br>푸르른 새벽 길 <br>꽃이 피고 또 지고 <br>산 위로 돌멩이길 지나 <br>아픔은 다시 잊혀지겠지 <br>끝없는 생각들 <br>내가 세상에 태어난 것 <br>모두 어쩌면 축복일지 몰라 <br>걷고 걷고 걷는다 <br>멀리 반짝이는 별지나 <br>걷고 걷고 걷는다 <br>새벽 그대 떠난 길지나 <br>아침은 다시 밝아오겠지 <br>푸르른 새벽 길 <br>내가 세상에 태어난 것 <br>모두 어쩌면 축복일지 몰라 <br>걷고 걷고 걷는다 <br>멀리 반짝이는 별지나 <br>걷고 걷고 걷는다 <br>새벽 그대 떠난 길지나 <br>아침은 다시 밝아오겠지 <br>푸르른 새벽 길 <br>꽃이 피고 꽃이 지고 <br>꽃이 피고 또 지고 <br>아픔은 다시 잊혀지겠지 <br>]]></content><category term="전인권" label="전인권"/><category term="걷고, 걷고 (New Ver.)" label="걷고, 걷고 (New Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신용재_포맨/언제나_괜찮아/</id><title>신용재_포맨 - 언제나 괜찮아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:55:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:55:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9A%A9%EC%9E%AC_%ED%8F%AC%EB%A7%A8/%EC%96%B8%EC%A0%9C%EB%82%98_%EA%B4%9C%EC%B0%AE%EC%95%84/" title="신용재_포맨 - 언제나 괜찮아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지나간 날이 밉지는 않아 <br>세상을 만나 어른이 됐고 <br>그대를 보면 아팠던 내가 <br>자꾸 보여서 <br>어떤 위로라도 <br>할 수 있으니 <br>들리지 않는 <br>노랠 부르고 <br>보이지 않는 <br>그림을 그리던 나 <br>누군가 내 오랜 <br>슬픈 꿈을 <br>깨운 것처럼 <br>나도 그대의 맘 <br>깨우고 싶어 <br>바람이 부는 어느 날 <br>흔들려도 좋아 <br>뒷걸음쳐도 돼 <br>쓰러질 수 있어 <br>하지만 그대여 <br>언제나 괜찮아 <br>휘청이던 하루 <br>우두커니 서있는 <br>내게로 와 <br>얼마나 많은 <br>눈물을 쏟고 <br>얼마나 깊은 <br>한숨을 뱉었는지 <br>그댄 아무 말 하지 않아도 <br>난 듣고 있어 <br>이젠 그대 맘이 <br>내 맘 같아서 <br>바람이 부는 어느 날 <br>흔들려도 좋아 <br>뒷걸음쳐도 돼 <br>쓰러질 수 있어 <br>하지만 그대여 <br>언제나 괜찮아 <br>휘청이던 하루 <br>우두커니 서있는 <br>내게로 와 <br>세상 어딘가엔 <br>우리가 찾던 <br>그 정답이 있는 걸 <br>나 달려온 그 이유 <br>나보다 더 나를 <br>많이 믿어 준 <br>그 사람 만나면 <br>난 아이처럼 울겠지 <br>눈물이 나면 그렇게 <br>다 젖어도 좋아 <br>소리 내 울어도 <br>바보여도 좋아 <br>사랑해 그대여 <br>영원히 괜찮아 <br>바람이 멎는 곳 <br>풍경처럼 서있는 <br>내게로 와 <br>]]></content><category term="신용재 (포맨)" label="신용재 (포맨)"/><category term="언제나 괜찮아" label="언제나 괜찮아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아이오아이_IOI/소나기/</id><title>아이오아이_IOI - 소나기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:55:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:55:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%98%A4%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4_IOI/%EC%86%8C%EB%82%98%EA%B8%B0/" title="아이오아이_IOI - 소나기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 비가 <br>머리 위로 쏟아지면 <br>흠뻑 젖고 말겠죠 <br>내 마음도 <br>머물러줘요 <br>아직까진 그대 없이 나 혼자 <br>이 비를 맞기엔 <br>아직 어리고 <br>조금 무서워 <br>금방 그칠 거란걸 <br>뻔히 다 알면서도 <br>그댈 찾네요 <br>이제 그만 <br>다 그칠까 <br>이 빗물도 <br>내 눈물도 <br>비에 젖어 추위에 <br>떨고 싶진 않아요 <br>정말 언젠간 <br>너무 차디찼던 빗물이 <br>따뜻한 눈물이 되어 <br>흘러내리겠죠 <br>괜찮아요 <br>금방 지나갈 소나기죠 <br>그냥 스쳐 <br>지나가는 소나기죠 <br>그런 감정이죠 <br>나 정말 <br>그대를 만나 <br>행복했던 많은 추억들을 <br>빗물에 잃지 않아요 <br>내리는 비가 <br>그칠 때쯤에 <br>그때 다시 만나요 <br>우리 다시 웃으며 <br>함께 있을게요 <br>이제 그만 <br>다 그칠까 <br>이 빗물도 <br>내 눈물도 <br>비에 젖어 추위에 <br>떨고 싶진 않아요 <br>정말 언젠간 <br>너무 차디찼던 빗물이 <br>따뜻한 눈물이 되어 <br>흘러내리겠죠 <br>괜찮아요 <br>금방 지나갈 소나기죠 <br>지금은 흠뻑 젖어가고만 있죠 <br>우산을 필 힘조차 없네요 <br>하지만 우린 알아요 <br>잠시만 울게요 <br>빗물에 기대어 <br>우리의 슬픈 눈물을 <br>그대가 보지 못하게 <br>우리 이제 안녕 <br>이제 그만 <br>다 그칠까 <br>이 빗물도 <br>내 눈물도 <br>비에 젖어 추위에 <br>떨고 싶진 않아요 <br>정말 언젠간 <br>너무 차디찼던 빗물이 <br>따뜻한 눈물이 되어 <br>흘러내리겠죠 <br>괜찮아요 <br>금방 지나갈 소나기죠 <br>]]></content><category term="아이오아이 (I.O.I)" label="아이오아이 (I.O.I)"/><category term="소나기" label="소나기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/캐스퍼_KASPER/Lean_On_Me/</id><title>캐스퍼_KASPER - Lean On Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:55:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:55:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%A4%ED%8D%BC_KASPER/Lean_On_Me/" title="캐스퍼_KASPER - Lean On Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby just lean on me and <br>언제든 전화해 <br>누가 기다려도 난 항상 너밖에 <br>Baby just lean on me and <br>언제든 전화해 <br>오늘도 나의 밤은 <br>너에게 다 줘버릴 테니 <br>살짝 졸리네 <br>난 앞으론 밖으로 <br>나갈 일이 없어졌지 <br>네가 더 이상 <br>나와 함께할 일이 <br>없을 거라 말했어 It's <br>okay it's fine I understand <br>하지만 언제든 전화해 <br>미안하다거나 죄책감이 들어 <br>네 정신을 괴롭힐 때면 Lean that <br>Clean that erase it just erase it <br>없던 일로 하자는 건 아냐 잠시 <br>묻어둘 뿐 그러면 <br>좋잖아 How sweet 아직 <br>난 움직이지 않고 그 자리에 서서 <br>추억들을 모아두고 있어 어쩜 <br>너도 그럴 거란 생각에 벌써 <br>가던 길을 멈춰 <br>Baby just lean on me and <br>언제든 전화해 <br>누가 기다려도 난 항상 너밖에 <br>Baby just lean on me and <br>언제든 전화해 <br>오늘도 나의 밤은 <br>너에게 다 줘버릴 테니 <br>Ring ring ring <br>The telephone sings to me <br>I pick up pick up <br>전화를 들고 나는 또 널 <br>오늘 밤 하루 나와 함께할만한 <br>이유를 만들어 꼭 <br>이쯤 되면 마음 약해지는 <br>너와 계속되는 통화 <br>언제쯤 끊을 수 있을까 나는 널 <br>Baby just lean on me and <br>언제든 전화해 <br>누가 기다려도 난 항상 너밖에 <br>Baby just lean on me and <br>언제든 전화해 <br>오늘도 나의 밤은 <br>너에게 다 줘버릴 테니 <br>노랠 만들어도 <br>손에 잡히질 않네 <br>밤새 내 꿈은 아직도 <br>널 기억해 <br>잔을 채워 이걸 마셔 봐도 너밖에 <br>그냥 TV를 봐도 다 너 같아 <br>네가 알리 없지 <br>You have no idea how much so <br>Lean on me call up my cell phone <br>Drinks are free 여긴 다 니 꺼 <br>We were meant to be together <br>Don't go home don't go home <br>Lean on me call up my cell phone <br>Drinks are free 여긴 다 니 꺼 <br>We were meant to be together <br>Don't go home don't go home <br>]]></content><category term="캐스퍼 (KASPER)" label="캐스퍼 (KASPER)"/><category term="Lean On Me" label="Lean On Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JQK_제이최성준오현민/씹어_먹어/</id><title>JQK_제이최성준오현민 - 씹어 먹어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:55:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:55:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JQK_%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%EC%B5%9C%EC%84%B1%EC%A4%80%EC%98%A4%ED%98%84%EB%AF%BC/%EC%94%B9%EC%96%B4_%EB%A8%B9%EC%96%B4/" title="JQK_제이최성준오현민 - 씹어 먹어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Uh 진짜 배기들이 왔어 <br>Uh sm 출신 actor rocker <br>Ya 나도 알아 떨어졌어 <br>근데 니들보다 랩 잘하니까 <br>전부 shut the fuck up <br>니들 언제부터 힙합 좋아했어 <br>Maybe show me the money <br>인정 어 인정 <br>But I'm jigga nas biggie pac <br>시절부터 힙합을 아꼈어 <br>I got the real one real shit <br>real flow real hoe <br>내가 마이크를 잡으면 <br>풀려 니들 동공 <br>West coast east coast <br>경계선이 없는 내 랩에 <br>무릎 꿇고 모두 복종 <br>역시 내 rap은 너무 쩔어 <br>여자들은 내가 <br>지나가면 전부 얼어 <br>이젠 나도 하고 싶어 <br>바닥에서 turn up <br>이 무대에서 내가 <br>니들 다 씹어 먹어 <br>누구든지 그냥 다 들어오라 해 <br>누구든지 그냥 다 들어보라 해 <br>누구든지 그냥 다 읊어보라 해 <br>누구든지 우리 앞에서 하라 해 <br>누구든지 그냥 다 들어오라 해 <br>누구든지 그냥 다 들어보라 해 <br>아무리 해도 <br>못 따라오는 건 네 잘못 <br>누가 누구를 탓해 <br>그러니깐 넌 힙알못 <br>내가 너네들 모두를 전부 씹어 ya <br>mo’fuckin 가짜들 전부 다 먹어 ya <br>내가 너네들 모두를 전부 씹어 ya <br>뱉어 내서 내 것을 귀에다 먹여 ya <br>내가 너네들 모두를 전부 씹어 ya <br>mo’fuckin 가짜들 전부 다 먹어 ya <br>내가 너네들 모두를 전부 씹어 ya <br>뱉어 내서 내 것을 귀에다 먹여 ya <br>날 봐 신기하지 <br>배운 적도 없는 랩 완전 쩔지 <br>지나가던 누가 봐도 좆도 간지 <br>머리부터 발끝까지 <br>나는 하드 캐리 wo <br>I don't care <br>even if you don't understand <br>what I'm talkin <br>내가 씹어 먹어버릴 거라고 <br>선택해 Eeny meeny miny moe <br>지난 한 해의 <br>병신년은 아래로 가고 <br>새로운 년을 위해 <br>짠해 잔을 말아 원샷 <br>인생은 원래 <br>그렇게 아름답진 않아 <br>그러니까 put your hands up <br>하고 앞으로 또 달려 나가 <br>나도 느껴 너의 시선 <br>know you care about me <br>나쁜 선택 아냐 내가 가는 길이지 <br>절대 사라지지 않는 <br>칼을 뽑아 얇게 썰어버려 스시 wo <br>누구든지 그냥 다 들어오라 해 <br>누구든지 그냥 다 들어보라 해 <br>누구든지 그냥 다 읊어보라 해 <br>누구든지 우리 앞에서 하라해 <br>누구든지 그냥 다 들어오라 해 <br>누구든지 그냥 다 들어보라 해 <br>아무리 해도 <br>못 따라오는 건 네 잘못 <br>누가 누구를 탓해 <br>그러니깐 넌 힙알못 <br>내가 너네들 모두를 전부 씹어 ya <br>mo’fuckin 가짜들 전부 다 먹어 ya <br>내가 너네들 모두를 전부 씹어 ya <br>뱉어 내서 내 것을 귀에다 먹여 ya <br>내가 너네들 모두를 전부 씹어 ya <br>mo’fuckin 가짜들 전부 다 먹어 ya <br>내가 너네들 모두를 전부 씹어 ya <br>뱉어 내서 내 것을 귀에다 먹여 ya <br>wo 마지막에 등장했지 <br>습관적으로 주인공 역을 맡아 <br>wo uh 태양도 아니면서 지구가 <br>내 위주로 돌아가는 듯 <br>느낌이 들어 <br>항상 어른들이 말했어 <br>잘하는 일을 해야 <br>돈을 벌어먹고 살아 <br>근데 못하는 일이 없어서 <br>나이는 어린데 <br>돈을 아주 우습게만 알아 wo <br>god damn <br>신은 원래 불공평해 <br>증거를 원한다면 <br>입 닥치고 가서 빨리 거울을 봐 <br>나는 다 가졌어 <br>키는 내가 반납했어 <br>일을 더하기 위해서 <br>귀요미가 돼버렸어 <br>eh eh eh eh <br>난 랩을 해도 존나 멋있어 <br>나도 놀라지만 <br>내 박자감 uh 미쳤어 <br>계속 해서 내 속에서 <br>구속 됐던 flow로 <br>이젠 모두에게 보여 <br>이젠 even make it rain yo <br>누구든지 그냥 다 들어오라 해 <br>누구든지 그냥 다 들어보라 해 <br>누구든지 그냥 다 읊어보라 해 <br>누구든지 우리 앞에서 하라 해 <br>누구든지 그냥 다 들어오라 해 <br>누구든지 그냥 다 들어보라 해 <br>아무리 해도 <br>못 따라오는 건 네 잘못 <br>누가 누구를 탓해 <br>그러니깐 넌 힙알못 <br>내가 너네들 모두를 전부 씹어 ya <br>mo’fuckin 가짜들 전부 다 먹어 ya <br>내가 너네들 모두를 전부 씹어 ya <br>뱉어 내서 내 것을 귀에다 먹여 ya <br>내가 너네들 모두를 전부 씹어 ya <br>mo’fuckin 가짜들 전부 다 먹어 ya <br>내가 너네들 모두를 전부 씹어 ya <br>뱉어 내서 내 것을 귀에다 먹여 ya <br>]]></content><category term="JQK (제이&amp;최성준&amp;오현민)" label="JQK (제이&amp;최성준&amp;오현민)"/><category term="씹어 먹어" label="씹어 먹어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레디_Reddy/Complicated/</id><title>레디_Reddy - Complicated - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:55:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:55:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EB%94%94_Reddy/Complicated/" title="레디_Reddy - Complicated - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[u are too complicated <br>u are too complicated <br>단순하게 생각해 <br>복잡한 세상은 변하지 매일 <br>u are too complicated <br>u are too complicated <br>벗어나고 싶어 <br>복잡한 세상 속에서 나는 매일 <br>단순하게 살고 싶어 마치 acne <br>복잡한 건 싫어 난 <br>hate that shit <br>남자는 1이고 여자는 10 <br>but 지금 내 상태는 <br>서울시내의 퇴근길 <br>좋은 앨범을 만들고 싶어 <br>그래서 그런지 <br>나답지 않게 예민해져 있어 <br>그래도 그녀는 <br>이런 나를 안아주지 <br>내 투정도 외야수처럼 <br>다 받아주지 <br>밖은 복잡해 생각들 쫓아내 <br>내 공간엔 좋은 <br>에너지들로만 꽉 차게 <br>할 거고 거기서 나온 내 음악들은 <br>단순하게 만들 거야 <br>듣는 너네들을 <br>인생은 아침마다 가는 화장실 <br>처럼 비워 내야 돼 무슨 말들이 <br>그렇게들 많은지 <br>부러우면 네가 하든지 <br>용기 없으면 닥치고 가 <br>네가 가던 <br>길 예 길 예 <br>복잡하지 않은 my way yea <br>인생은 복잡해 <br>but I will do what I wanna do <br>내 길을 가야 돼 <br>u are too complicated <br>u are too complicated <br>단순하게 생각해 <br>복잡한 세상은 변하지 매일 <br>u are too complicated <br>u are too complicated <br>벗어나고 싶어 <br>복잡한 세상 속에서 나는 매일 <br>complex <br>complex <br>complex <br>complex <br>난 뭐 하나에 꽂히면 <br>다른 건 못 봐 <br>어릴 때부터 그랬지 <br>다른 길 못 봐 <br>Nobody is a somebody now <br>노래가 날 그렇게 <br>만들었지 돈도 많이 <br>벌었겠네 내 속도 모르고 <br>얘기하지 내 삶의 속도는 오르고 <br>머릿속 불빛들은 slo-mo <br>의미 없는 고민들과 감정 소모 <br>노래만 하면 막 뭐라도 <br>될 것 같았지 내가 뭐라고 <br>얽히고 설킨 채 사는 게 <br>사는 게 아냐 날 제발 좀 도와줘 <br>내가 사랑하는 게 날 미치도록 해 <br>어느새 내가 아닌 <br>남을 위해 노력해 <br>답답해 갑갑해 저 바깥에 <br>날 데리고 가 여긴 너무 삭막해 <br>u are too complicated <br>u are too complicated <br>단순하게 생각해 <br>복잡한 세상은 변하지 매일 <br>u are too complicated <br>u are too complicated <br>벗어나고 싶어 <br>복잡한 세상 속에서 나는 매일 <br>u are too complicated <br>u are too complicated <br>단순하게 생각해 <br>복잡한 세상은 변하지 매일 <br>u are too complicated <br>u are too complicated <br>벗어나고 싶어 <br>복잡한 세상 속에서 나는 매일 <br>complex <br>complex <br>complex <br>complex <br>]]></content><category term="레디 (Reddy)" label="레디 (Reddy)"/><category term="Complicated" label="Complicated"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/딘딘/기리와_디니_Feat_뮤지/</id><title>딘딘 - 기리와 디니 (Feat. 뮤지) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:55:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:55:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%94%98%EB%94%98/%EA%B8%B0%EB%A6%AC%EC%99%80_%EB%94%94%EB%8B%88_Feat_%EB%AE%A4%EC%A7%80/" title="딘딘 - 기리와 디니 (Feat. 뮤지) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[결승 무대까지 왔지 <br>don’t you know im 로꼬 <br>셀 수도 없이 마이크 폰과 뽀뽀 <br>실컷 했어 내 노래도 뽑고 <br>이제 개콘 갈래 다이아 갖고 <br>나밖에 경연 1등 했고 <br>훅 그거 바로 내가 짰고 <br>방송 분량 다 챙겼고 <br>이제 김기리와 다이아 갖고 <br>무대 올라가면 <br>내가 다 부실 거야 <br>이제 클럽 가서 <br>마구 들이 부을 거야 <br>여자들의 마음 다 훔칠 거야 <br>김기리기리 와 디니디니 <br>힙합 클럽은 나 안 갈 거야 <br>진짜 멋진 힙합 <br>아니면 안 들을 거야 <br>힙합의 민족 다신 안 할 거야 <br>김기리기리 와 디니디니 <br>티켓 챙겨 let’s ride with us <br>일단 땡겨 모두 여기로 <br>네 친구 내 친구 다 불러 <br>let’s party all night <br>티켓 챙겨 let’s ride with us <br>일단 땡겨 모두 여기로 <br>네 친구 내 친구 다 불러 <br>let’s party all night <br>시작은 이태원 소방서 옆 <br>사거리에서 하려고 <br>gotta move <br>마무리는 신사역 <br>사거리에서 gotta move <br>hey 탐욕돼지 피타입이라고 <br>딘딘이 시켰어요 피타입 짱 <br>랩 인간형 그 수식어 <br>김기리한테 붙여 마이노스 <br>너넨 쎄쎄쎄나 해 <br>내가 하이라이트 <br>어디 갔어 핫칙스 <br>붙자 다이다이 <br>브랜뉴 이제 너넨 기리안보여 <br>준비된 hot ladies 다 여기 모여 <br>무대 올라가면 <br>내가 다 부실 거야 <br>이제 클럽 가서 <br>마구 들이 부을 거야 <br>여자들의 마음 다 훔칠 거야 <br>김기리기리 와 디니디니 <br>힙합 클럽은 나 안 갈 거야 <br>진짜 멋진 힙합 <br>아니면 안 들을 거야 <br>힙합의 민족 다신 안 할 거야 <br>김기리기리 와 디니디니 <br>티켓 챙겨 let’s ride with us <br>일단 땡겨 모두 여기로 <br>네 친구 내 친구 다 불러 <br>let’s party all night <br>티켓 챙겨 let’s ride with us <br>일단 땡겨 모두 여기로 <br>네 친구 내 친구 다 불러 <br>let’s party all night <br>시작은 이태원 소방서 옆 <br>사거리에서 하려고 <br>gotta move <br>마무리는 신사역 <br>사거리에서 gotta move <br>all night <br>let’s ride with us <br>all night <br>let’s ride with us <br>김기리기리 와 디니디니 <br>우리 끼리끼리 we party party <br>all night <br>let’s ride with us <br>all night <br>let’s ride with us <br>come on baby party tonight <br>제가 지금까지 랩 한다고 <br>까불고 있는데 <br>사실 제가 존경하는 <br>사람들은 래퍼들이 아니에요 <br>진짜 김기리 respect <br>신동엽 유재석 강호동 <br>남희석과 컬투 박수홍 <br>김준호 박성호 임하룡 <br>김수용 장용 그리고 정성호 <br>남철 남성남 봉선 박성광 <br>조세호 김구라 김병만 노우진 <br>옹알스 야누스 옹달샘까지 <br>이성동 임우일 나 김기리 <br>we party we party <br>we like to party babe <br>we party we party <br>we like to party babe <br>we party we party <br>we like to party babe <br>come on babe party tonight <br>la la la la la la la <br>la la la la la la la <br>la la la la la la la <br>김기리기리 와 디니디니 <br>la la la la la la la <br>la la la la la la la <br>la la la la la la la <br>우리 끼리 끼리 <br>we party party <br>]]></content><category term="딘딘" label="딘딘"/><category term="기리와 디니 (Feat. 뮤지)" label="기리와 디니 (Feat. 뮤지)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마이노스_MINOS/킥킥/</id><title>마이노스_MINOS - 킥킥 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:55:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:55:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8%EC%8A%A4_MINOS/%ED%82%A5%ED%82%A5/" title="마이노스_MINOS - 킥킥 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Introduce myself <br>Can I 킥킥 <br>Yes we can <br>Introduce myself <br>침 뱉듯이 살다가 죽을 거야 난 <br>담배가 더 맛있어지는 계절이야 <br>덮어쓴 후드패션 <br>관심 없는 거에 대해선 <br>No more question <br>꾹 닫은 입 <br>새벽처럼 냉정해졌지 <br>X신 새끼 왈왈 <br>Fly with me <br>뭐 래퍼들의 무덤에 <br>줄 서서 목매라네 <br>X까 쫙 찢어 네 유서 <br>서까지 다 <br>내 열정의 불쏘시개 <br>정도나 될까 <br>담배 연기 더 있네 <br>예술성 성 <br>Uh 귀엔 Penny형의 <br>비트 손엔 담배 <br>This weather and This place <br>Two some <br>나까지 하면 <br>Nasty Three some <br>돗대까지 탁탁 <br>털지 터지는 허풍선 <br>Hey you get off my clouds <br>You don't know me <br>and You don't know my style <br>서로 빨아주는 <br>Wack 파티 너나 가셔 <br>HIPHOP 걔도 거기 <br>싫단다 냄새나서 <br>Introduce myself <br>Can I 킥킥 <br>Yes we can <br>Introduce myself <br>침 뱉듯이 살다가 죽을 거야 난 <br>밑 빠진 독에다가 <br>물 부어 부어 <br>좀 새면 어때 <br>들이부어 부어 <br>재충전 그 호사는 <br>너나 가지든가 <br>저 개나 줘 <br>끄덕끄덕 when i flow <br>밑 빠진 독에다가 <br>물 부어 부어 <br>좀 새면 어때 <br>들이부어 부어 <br>재충전 그 호사는 <br>너나 가지든가 <br>저 개나 줘 <br>끄덕끄덕 when i flow <br>이제는 지겨워 <br>주인공 친구 쩌리 <br>볼 캡 눌러써 <br>내 눈빛 이 거리 <br>춤을 추듯 뱉는 거야 <br>내 Flow so curry <br>인도적인 말투 <br>고수의 향긴 피처링 <br>요즘엔 개나 소나 엔터테이너 <br>연기한답시고 밥그릇 <br>기웃거리는 게 트렌드 <br>Thank you 그 덕에 <br>내 손에 MIC <br>무대는 애초에 내 것이니까 <br>이건 Killing in the name <br>난 존재가 반칙 <br>Blazin' Half man <br>Half amazin' 딱 반씩 <br>엿 바꿔먹어 네 자의식 <br>SNS 거지들 애정결핍 <br>구걸하는 관심 <br>자 여기 *uck you 먹어 <br>1차는 내가 사 <br>배불러 뱉는 <br>헛소리들 찢는 내 가사 <br>하늘은 높고 말은 살쪄 <br>내게도 가을은 오고 <br>내 말이 또 살쪄 <br>Introduce myself <br>Can I 킥킥 <br>Yes we can <br>Introduce myself <br>침 뱉듯이 살다가 죽을 거야 난 <br>밑 빠진 독에다가 <br>물 부어 부어 <br>좀 새면 어때 <br>들이부어 부어 <br>재충전 그 호사는 <br>너나 가지든가 <br>저 개나 줘 <br>끄덕끄덕 when i flow <br>밑 빠진 독에다가 <br>물 부어 부어 <br>좀 새면 어때 <br>들이부어 부어 <br>재충전 그 호사는 <br>너나 가지든가 <br>저 개나 줘 <br>끄덕끄덕 when i flow <br>침 뱉듯이 살다가 죽을 거야 난 <br>]]></content><category term="마이노스 (MINOS)" label="마이노스 (MINOS)"/><category term="킥킥" label="킥킥"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피타입/트라우마/</id><title>피타입 - 트라우마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:55:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:55:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%ED%83%80%EC%9E%85/%ED%8A%B8%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B0%EB%A7%88/" title="피타입 - 트라우마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 가끔 <br>전부 다 꿈 <br>같아 울랄라 밖은 <br>내게 낯설었지 맞바꾼 <br>황금과 꿈 가끔 <br>들이 들이 <br>들이대 빨아먹을 생각뿐 <br>먹튀들 뒤를 이어 찾아온 공백 <br>마이크 쥐고 돌아왔지 <br>나 홀로 컴백 <br>두 손 모아 빌어 <br>빌어 <br>빌어먹을 <br>비록 이렇게 다시 여기로 <br>무대에 남기는 기록 위로 <br>whut <br>사람들이 내게 돌아와 줄까 <br>예전처럼 내 몸이 <br>날 따라와 줄까 <br>우리 엄마 드린 내 신장 <br>얼마나 버틸까 <br>회식 다음 회복 <br>왜 이리도 더딜까 <br>괴로워 <br>get on up get on up <br>괴로우면 어깨 빌리죠 hey <br>노래를 불러줘 piano man <br>billy joel <br>지나간 상처는 과연 아물까 <br>오늘 이 가사도 <br>날려 먹진 않을까 <br>Get on up up up jump <br>the boogie to the boogie to the <br>boogie the beat <br>hit it hit it <br>Get on up up up jump <br>the boogie to the boogie to the <br>boogie the beat <br>hit it hit it <br>무대라는 게임 위의 <br>케미에 관한 건 <br>묻지도 마 괜히 왜 <br>힙민2 우리 둘이 하드캐리 해 <br>oh excuse me ready yet <br>내가 이 바닥에서 <br>얼마나 삐 댈까 <br>올해는 어떤 아이들이 <br>랩스타 될까 <br>나도 그들처럼 타협하며 <br>살게 될까 <br>딱 행복 하나 원해 <br>괜한 기대일까 <br>출근하는 아내 축 늘어진 어깨 <br>매일 매일을 걱정하네 <br>늘 어지럽게 <br>돌아가는 걸 이 바닥 <br>희망 한 가닥 <br>잡기 위해 파닥거려 <br>너도 나도 까닭 <br>모르고 다 존버 <br>세상은 과정보다 결과 <br>오늘도 내 주변엔 다 john doe <br>바 등대다 군데군데 까져 <br>아픈데 다시 까져 <br>근데 안 죽어 누가 관둔데 <br>짠한 거 원해 미안해 <br>내 안의 얘긴 이 안에 <br>다 담을 수가 없거든 <br>위로라면 이미 아내에게 <br>다 받았으니까 됐고 <br>이제 내려갈래 훅 하나 더 뱉고 <br>Get on up up up jump <br>the boogie to the boogie to the <br>boogie the beat <br>hit it hit it <br>Get on up up up jump <br>the boogie to the boogie to the <br>boogie the beat <br>hit it hit it <br>무대라는 게임 위의 <br>케미에 관한 건 <br>묻지도 마 괜히 왜 <br>힙민2 우리 둘이 하드캐리 해 <br>oh excuse me <br>ready yet <br>Get on up up up jump <br>the boogie to the boogie to the <br>boogie the beat <br>hit it hit it <br>Get on up up up jump <br>the boogie to the boogie to the <br>boogie the beat <br>hit it hit it <br>무대라는 게임 위의 <br>케미에 관한 건 <br>묻지도 마 괜히 왜 <br>힙민2 우리 둘이 하드캐리 해 <br>oh excuse me ready yet <br>Throw your hands up <br>Throw your hands up <br>Throw your hands up <br>Throw your hands up <br>Throw your hands up <br>Throw your hands up <br>Throw your hands up <br>Throw your hands up <br>Throw your hands up <br>Throw your hands up <br>Throw your hands up <br>Throw your hands up <br>]]></content><category term="피타입" label="피타입"/><category term="트라우마" label="트라우마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LE_EXID/내_맴/</id><title>LE_EXID - 내 맴 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LE_EXID/%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%B4/" title="LE_EXID - 내 맴 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아 쫌 날 그냥 <br>이대로 냅둬 줘 제발 <br>Fuck you <br>나 싸가지 원래 없으니까 <br>내가 뭘 하던 다 내 맴 맴 맴 <br>내가 뭘 하던 다 내 맴 맴 맴 <br>야 진짜 솔직히 말해봐 <br>우리 만난 적도 없었잖아 <br>친구 코스프레 <br>그만하고 말해봐 <br>누가 네 친구야 이 썅년아 <br>내가 한 적도 없는 말을 <br>그럴싸하게 네가 지어냈다고 <br>거짓이 사실이 되지는 않아 <br>그럴 시간에 네 더러워진 <br>입이나 닦어 <br>Uh Uh 할 줄 아는 게 뭐야 <br>진짜 궁금해서 <br>물어 보는 거야 <br>아니 사실 비꼬는 거야 <br>부정하지 말아 <br>그냥 그게 너야 <br>근데 혹시 님 직업이 <br>키보드 워리어 이신가요 <br>내 기사에 싸지른 댓글이 <br>유일한 커리어 이신가요 <br>내가 상냥하든 혹은 막나가든 <br>욕은 나 가 거든 해 <br>내가 기부를 하든 길에 <br>똥을 싸든 내가 다 알아서 해 <br>내가 뭘 하든 다 내 맴맴맴 <br>너도 들어봤지 <br>WE BAD BAD BAD <br>다 꺼져 제발 니들 일이나 해 <br>오지라퍼들은 입 다물라 해 <br>아 쫌 날 그냥 <br>이대로 냅둬 줘 제발 <br>Fuck you <br>나 싸가지 원래 없으니까 <br>내가 뭘 하던 다 내 맴 맴 맴 <br>내가 뭘 하던 다 내 맴 맴 맴 <br>아 쫌 날 그냥 <br>이대로 냅둬 줘 제발 <br>Fuck you <br>나 싸가지 원래 없으니까 <br>내가 뭘 하던 다 내 맴 맴 맴 <br>내가 뭘 하던 다 내 맴 맴 맴 <br>그만 훔쳐봐 내 INSTAGRAM <br>왜 자꾸 내 인성에 대해 <br>니들이 논할라 그래 <br>그래 내가 니들에게 <br>좆 같이 구는 거 <br>난 그냥 똑같이 구는 거 <br>왜 애꿎은 내게 화를 푸는 거 <br>조심해 데일라 어서 불을 꺼 <br>I JUST WANNA SAY <br>FUCK U GO FUCK YOURSELF <br>나에게 떤 가식은 벗고 <br>GO SUCK YOURSELF <br>내가 착한 척 또는 예쁜 척 <br>한다는 말 많은 병신년 <br>이미 져버린 년 이겨 뭐해 <br>이거 내가 봐도 내가 너무해 <br>내가 상냥하든 혹은 막나가든 <br>욕은 나 가 거든 해 <br>내가 기부를 하든 길에 <br>똥을 싸든 내가 다 알아서 해 <br>내가 뭘 하든 다 내 맴맴맴 <br>너도 들어봤지 <br>WE BAD BAD BAD <br>다 꺼져 제발 니들 일이나 해 <br>오지라퍼들은 입 다물라 해 <br>아 쫌 날 그냥 <br>이대로 냅둬 줘 제발 <br>Fuck you <br>나 싸가지 원래 없으니까 <br>내가 뭘 하던 다 내 맴 맴 맴 <br>내가 뭘 하던 다 내 맴 맴 맴 <br>아 쫌 날 <br>그냥 이대로 냅둬줘 제발 <br>Fuck you <br>나 싸가지 원래 없으니까 <br>내가 뭘 하던 다 내 맴 맴 맴 <br>내가 뭘 하던 다 내 맴 맴 맴 <br>내 맴 맴 맴 <br>내 맴 맴 맴 <br>내 맴 맴 맴 <br>내 맴 맴 맴 <br>]]></content><category term="LE (EXID)" label="LE (EXID)"/><category term="내 맴" label="내 맴"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인메이/버섯전골/</id><title>인메이 - 버섯전골 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4/%EB%B2%84%EC%84%AF%EC%A0%84%EA%B3%A8/" title="인메이 - 버섯전골 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쏘아붙임에 변명할 <br>몇 가지 논리를 <br>머리 속으로 되뇌었다 <br>조금 피곤한 표정을 <br>일부러 만들고는 <br>문 손잡이를 돌렸다 <br>그이는 현관에 서 있었다 <br>내 얼굴을 조용히 쳐다보고는 <br>잘 돌아왔다고 말했다 <br>부엌에는 버섯전골이 <br>보글보글 끓고 있었다 <br>]]></content><category term="인메이" label="인메이"/><category term="버섯전골" label="버섯전골"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인메이/모르겠어/</id><title>인메이 - 모르겠어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4/%EB%AA%A8%EB%A5%B4%EA%B2%A0%EC%96%B4/" title="인메이 - 모르겠어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[좋아한다 말할 수 없어 <br>용기가 없어서가 아니라 <br>끝이 너무 명백해서야 <br>넌 지금도 <br>날 슬금슬금 피하고 있는걸 <br>내가 사랑하는 사람이 <br>나를 사랑하는 기적은 <br>언제쯤 일어나는 거야 <br>그런 게 있기는 한 거야 <br>내가 이상한 걸까 <br>인연을 못 만난 걸까 <br>아니면 사랑이란 게 <br>원래 그런 걸까 <br>아무도 안 만난 건 아냐 <br>그 애가 좋아한다 말했고 <br>나도 좋다고 그랬었어 <br>그리 오래가진 못했어 <br>생각해보면은 그때에 <br>내가 고개를 끄덕였던 건 <br>그 애를 사랑한다는 말이 아니라 <br>그냥 승낙이었었나 봐 <br>뭐라고 말할까 우울하고 외로워 <br>나는 그런 감각밖에 <br>느껴본 적 없는걸 <br>세상이 아름답고 즐거운 거라고 <br>나도 생각할 수 있게 <br>그 증거를 보여줘 <br>니가 날 좋아하는지 아닌지 <br>거기에 내 목숨이 달렸었어 <br>요즘은 니가 뭘 하는지 <br>어디 있는지도 몰라 <br>사랑은 원래 식는 거야 <br>아니면 내가 잘못한 거야 <br>성격차이라고 하기엔 <br>사람은 모두 달라 <br>사랑해서 만나는 거야 <br>만나서 사랑하게 된 거야 <br>나는 뭘 어떻게 해야 해 <br>어디로 누굴 찾아가 <br>내가 이상한 걸까 <br>인연을 못 만난 걸까 <br>아니면 사랑이란 게 <br>원래 그런 걸까 <br>뭐라고 말할까 우울하고 외로워 <br>나는 그런 감각밖에 <br>느껴본 적 없는걸 <br>세상이 아름답고 즐거운 거라고 <br>나도 생각할 수 있게 <br>그 증거를 보여줘 <br>]]></content><category term="인메이" label="인메이"/><category term="모르겠어" label="모르겠어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인메이/힘내지_마/</id><title>인메이 - 힘내지 마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4/%ED%9E%98%EB%82%B4%EC%A7%80_%EB%A7%88/" title="인메이 - 힘내지 마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[힘내지마 <br>어깨도 마음도 무거워서 <br>웃으려 해도 웃어지지 않으면 <br>그냥 아직 힘내지마 <br>지쳤으면 <br>그건 그냥 될 대로 되게 내버려둬 <br>모든 게 다 싫어질 만큼 <br>마지막 힘까지 쏟아 붓지는 마 <br>정말 애썼던 일도 <br>아무리 중요한 일도 <br>너라는 사람만큼 중요하진 않아 <br>한심하게 느껴도 <br>바보같이 느껴도 <br>너는 그냥 너인 채로 좋아 <br>정말 애썼던 일도 <br>아무리 중요한 일도 <br>너라는 사람만큼 중요하진 않아 <br>한심하게 느껴도 <br>바보같이 느껴도 <br>너는 그냥 너인 채로 좋아 <br>]]></content><category term="인메이" label="인메이"/><category term="힘내지 마" label="힘내지 마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인메이/합리화/</id><title>인메이 - 합리화 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4/%ED%95%A9%EB%A6%AC%ED%99%94/" title="인메이 - 합리화 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 그렇게 해서까지 <br>얻고 싶은 게 뭐였을까 <br>난 얼마나 대단한 <br>사람이 되고픈 걸까 <br>그곳에 닿으면 <br>또 그 다음 걸 욕심 낼 텐데 <br>난 그냥 만족하는 <br>방법을 배우고 싶어 <br>소소한 것들이 얼마나 소중한지 <br>알게 되는 건 비교할 필요 없는 <br>꽤 행복한 일인 것 같아 <br>그런데 난 지금 <br>나약하고 의지 없는 나를 <br>단지 합리화 하는 걸까 <br>아니면 진짜 일상에 만족하는 <br>소소한 행복을 찾고 싶은 걸까 <br>무엇도 고정된 사실이기 보다는 <br>누군가의 개인적인 믿음일 뿐야 <br>그런 거면 오래도록 <br>불안해 하지 않을 <br>단단한 믿음을 가지고 싶어 <br>왜들 그렇게 해서까지 <br>연인을 만드는 걸까 <br>완벽해 보이는 그 사람도 <br>곧 단점이 폭발할 텐데 <br>구속과 오해 속에 보냈던 <br>시간과 돈이 아까울걸 <br>아무도 신경 쓸 필요 없는 <br>자유로움이 그리울 텐데 <br>그런데 난 지금 <br>노력도 용기도 없는 나를 <br>단지 합리화 하는 걸까 <br>아니면 진짜 느긋하고 자유로운 <br>나만의 시간을 즐기고 싶은 걸까 <br>무엇도 고정된 사실이기 보다는 <br>누군가의 개인적인 믿음일 뿐야 <br>그런 거면 오래도록 <br>불안해 하지 않을 <br>단단한 믿음을 가지고 싶어 <br>]]></content><category term="인메이" label="인메이"/><category term="합리화" label="합리화"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인메이/아무에게도_아무도_아니다/</id><title>인메이 - 아무에게도 아무도 아니다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4/%EC%95%84%EB%AC%B4%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C%EB%8F%84_%EC%95%84%EB%AC%B4%EB%8F%84_%EC%95%84%EB%8B%88%EB%8B%A4/" title="인메이 - 아무에게도 아무도 아니다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그래 그사람 <br>괜찮은 것같아 <br>하지만 나에게 <br>관심 없으면 <br>나도 관둘래 <br>먼저 말걸어 줄 사람 <br>어딘가 있을테니까 <br>뭔가 조금 내키지않으면 <br>금방 다른 사람 찾아 <br>사람 이렇게 많은데 <br>더 좋은사람도 <br>어딘가 있을테니까 <br>조금만 자존심 건드린다면 <br>처음부터 그 사람 싫었단듯 <br>외모 말투 습관 이상했다고 <br>기억을 조작하면 돼 <br>누군가 정말 싫어하려해도 <br>자세히 그 사람 알아야 해 <br>요샌 누군가 그럴만큼 <br>깊게 만날 일도 없어 <br>사람이라는건 아름답고 <br>소중하고 사랑스럽기보다 <br>너무 많아서 되도록은 <br>없었으면하는 <br>거추장스런 존재 <br>환상은 절대 버려지지않고 <br>어떻게 해도 만족할 수 없어 <br>사람이 아무리 많아도 <br>외로움은 해결되지 않고 <br>내가 이렇게 생각한단 건 <br>다른사람들도 그렇단것 <br>누구에게나 적당히 <br>대꾸하고 돌아서 <br>소심한 상냥함 겉으론 <br>친절한 언제나 <br>늘 그러고 마는데 <br>운명의 사랑이 눈앞에와도 <br>어떻게 알아봐 <br>사람이라는건 아름답고 <br>소중하고 사랑스럽기보다 <br>너무 많아서 되도록은 <br>없었으면하는 <br>거추장스런 존재 <br>환상은 절대 버려지지않고 <br>어떻게 해도 만족할 수 없어 <br>사람이 아무리 많아도 <br>외로움은 해결되지 않고 <br>여전히 아무에게도 <br>아무도 아니다 <br>]]></content><category term="인메이" label="인메이"/><category term="아무에게도 아무도 아니다" label="아무에게도 아무도 아니다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인메이/사랑스러운_아침feat_원동환/</id><title>인메이 - 사랑스러운 아침(feat. 원동환) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%8A%A4%EB%9F%AC%EC%9A%B4_%EC%95%84%EC%B9%A8feat_%EC%9B%90%EB%8F%99%ED%99%98/" title="인메이 - 사랑스러운 아침(feat. 원동환) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[알람없이 느긋한 아침 <br>멀리들리는 새소리 <br>방안가득 들어온 햇살 <br>일어나지 않아도 <br>된다는 게 정말 <br>조금은 배가 고프고 <br>화장실도 가고 싶지만 <br>마냥 누워만 있고파 <br>밀린 웹툰보고 <br>타임라인 당기며 <br>그때 울리는 초인종 <br>왜 날 내버려 두지않아 <br>작은 주말의 여유조차 <br>내겐 허락되지않았나 <br>]]></content><category term="인메이" label="인메이"/><category term="사랑스러운 아침(feat. 원동환)" label="사랑스러운 아침(feat. 원동환)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인메이/이해해_달라는_게_아니고/</id><title>인메이 - 이해해 달라는 게 아니고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4/%EC%9D%B4%ED%95%B4%ED%95%B4_%EB%8B%AC%EB%9D%BC%EB%8A%94_%EA%B2%8C_%EC%95%84%EB%8B%88%EA%B3%A0/" title="인메이 - 이해해 달라는 게 아니고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이해해 달라는 게 아니고 <br>이해할 수 없다는 걸 <br>인정하라는 거야 <br>너와 나는 다른 사람이고 <br>어떡해도 넌 내가 <br>돼볼 수 없는 거야 <br>니가 천년만년을 살았든 <br>그래봤자 니 좁은 <br>몸 속이었을뿐야 <br>니가 날 알 수 <br>있다는 생각은 <br>꿈에서라도 감히 <br>하지말라는 거야 <br>이해해 달라는 게 아니고 <br>이해할 수 없다는 걸 <br>인정하라는 거야 <br>너와 나는 다른 사람이고 <br>어떡해도 넌 내가 <br>돼볼 수 없는 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="인메이" label="인메이"/><category term="이해해 달라는 게 아니고" label="이해해 달라는 게 아니고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인메이/그래도_나를_불러줘/</id><title>인메이 - 그래도 나를 불러줘 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%98%EB%8F%84_%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EB%B6%88%EB%9F%AC%EC%A4%98/" title="인메이 - 그래도 나를 불러줘 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너랑있는 게 난 좋아 <br>4시간까지만 <br>너랑있는 게 난 좋아 <br>일주일에 한번만 <br>예고도없이 너의 <br>밑바닥을 모두 보이고 <br>자 이제 니 차례야 <br>나에게 턴을 넘기지 마 <br>사람들 만나는 게 좋아 <br>해뜨기 전까지만 <br>이야길 듣는 게 좋아 <br>반복되기 전까지만 <br>나에 대한 모든 걸 <br>알아내려 취조하지마 <br>동의 강요 마 모든 면에서 <br>니 편은 아닌걸 <br>그래도 날 잊지 말고 <br>그곳에 나를 불러줘 <br>체력이 조금 적을 뿐 <br>평생 혼자고 싶지 않아 <br>그래도 날 잊지 말고 <br>그곳에 나를 불러줘 <br>모두가 즐거운 곳에 <br>나만 없고 싶지 않아 <br>여행얘기 듣는 게 <br>좋아 가고 싶진 않지만 <br>뒷담화도 가끔은 좋아 <br>내친구만 아니면 <br>예고도없이 너의 <br>밑바닥을 모두 보이고 <br>자 이제 니 차례야 <br>나에게 턴을 넘기지 마 <br>그래도 날 잊지 말고 <br>그곳에 나를 불러줘 <br>체력이 조금 적을 뿐 <br>평생 혼자고 싶지 않아 <br>그래도 날 잊지 말고 <br>그곳에 나를 불러줘 <br>모두가 즐거운 곳에 <br>나만 없고 싶지 않아 <br>어디에나 잘 어울리고 <br>무슨말이든 잘하는 <br>그런 나는 아니라도 <br>그래도 나를 불러줘 <br>]]></content><category term="인메이" label="인메이"/><category term="그래도 나를 불러줘" label="그래도 나를 불러줘"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인메이/미안하기_싫어요/</id><title>인메이 - 미안하기 싫어요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4/%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%88%ED%95%98%EA%B8%B0_%EC%8B%AB%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="인메이 - 미안하기 싫어요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우린 자주 만났어요 <br>당신은 친절해요 <br>날 이렇게 대해준 <br>사람 없었어요 <br>하지만 당신을 <br>사랑할 수 없어요 <br>불편하고 부담스런 <br>마음이 더 짙어져 <br>내가 거의 당신 꺼라 <br>생각할지 몰라요 <br>항상 곁에 있었고 <br>내 시간을 알았죠 <br>빠져나갈 수 없게 <br>하는 방법까지 <br>그대는 너무 잘 <br>알고 있는 것 같아 <br>이제는 미안하기 싫어요 <br>그대가 원하는 게 <br>미안해서 돌려주는 <br>친절은 아니잖아 <br>나도 모르는 나를 <br>나라고 생각하는걸 <br>나라는 이름에 새긴 <br>그대의 환상인걸 <br>자신감을 잃어버린 <br>당신께 미안해요 <br>좋은 사람이었단 건 <br>변하지 않아요 <br>당신을 잃게 될 <br>나도 너무 가여워 <br>하지만 이제는 <br>그만 해야만 해요 <br>이제는 미안하기 싫어요 <br>그대가 원하는 게 <br>미안해서 돌려주는 <br>친절은 아니잖아 <br>그대는 나도 모르는 나를 <br>나라고 생각하는걸 <br>나라는 이름에 새긴 <br>그대의 환상인걸 <br>당신은 너무나 외로웠고 <br>너무 많은 사랑을 원해 <br>무섭게 쏟아지는 열정 <br>그 안에 난 어느날 <br>배신감 느낄까요 <br>나쁜 사람인가요 <br>말도 꺼내기 전에 <br>거절했어야 하나요 <br>]]></content><category term="인메이" label="인메이"/><category term="미안하기 싫어요" label="미안하기 싫어요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인메이/맛있는_저녁을_먹어요/</id><title>인메이 - 맛있는 저녁을 먹어요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4/%EB%A7%9B%EC%9E%88%EB%8A%94_%EC%A0%80%EB%85%81%EC%9D%84_%EB%A8%B9%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="인메이 - 맛있는 저녁을 먹어요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밥보다 잠이 좋아서 <br>5분이라도 잠을 택해요 <br>배고프다고 느껴볼 <br>시간도 사실 없었어요 <br>좋아하지 않는 사람과 <br>좋아하지 않는 메뉴를 <br>허겁지겁 마시듯 훌훌 <br>그렇게 점심을 때웠죠 <br>아침은 생략 <br>점심은 대충 <br>그러니까 우리 <br>맛있는 저녁을 먹어요 <br>오늘 하루는 <br>정말 힘들었죠 <br>우린 자격 있어요 <br>근사한 저녁을 먹어요 <br>너무 비싸지 않냐니 그런 건 <br>걱정하지 말아요 <br>당신과 맛있는 저녁 <br>그보다 더 좋은 건 없으니 <br>다이어트라니 그런 건 <br>걱정하지 말아요 <br>조금 더 찌면 그대 <br>조금 더 이쁠테니까 <br>아침은 생략 <br>점심은 대충 <br>그러니까 우리 <br>맛있는 저녁을 먹어요 <br>오늘 하루는 <br>정말 힘들었죠 <br>우린 자격 있어요 <br>근사한 저녁을 먹어요 <br>인생이라는 게 <br>마음대로 되지 않고 <br>마음대로 되지 않고 <br>마음대로 되지 않고 <br>마음대로 되는 건 <br>마음대로 되는 건 <br>마음대로 되는 건 <br>저녁메뉴 <br>아침은 생략 <br>점심은 대충 <br>그러니까 우리 <br>맛있는 저녁을 먹어요 <br>오늘 하루는 <br>정말 힘들었죠 <br>빰빰 <br>우린 자격 있어요 <br>근사한 저녁을 먹어요 <br>빰 <br>]]></content><category term="인메이" label="인메이"/><category term="맛있는 저녁을 먹어요" label="맛있는 저녁을 먹어요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인메이/그대는_그대로_아름다워요/</id><title>인메이 - 그대는 그대로 아름다워요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%8A%94_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%A1%9C_%EC%95%84%EB%A6%84%EB%8B%A4%EC%9B%8C%EC%9A%94/" title="인메이 - 그대는 그대로 아름다워요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[누군가 그대를 바라봐 <br>주기 전에도 <br>그대에게 이름을 붙여 <br>주기 전에도 <br>자신을 소개할 말이 <br>하나도 없어도 <br>그대는 그대로 아름다워요 <br>어제 다짐하고 오늘 <br>지키지 못해도 <br>해놓은 게 없고 <br>하고 싶은 게 없어도 <br>의욕이 없고 가만히 누워있어도 <br>그대는 그대로 아름다워요 <br>아무 말도 하지 마요 <br>아무 것도 증명할 필요 없어요 <br>어떤 모습이라 해도 <br>그대는 그대로 아름다우니까요 <br>열심히 고민하고 결국엔 <br>엉뚱한 걸 골라도 <br>똑같은 실수를 바보같이 <br>계속 반복해도 <br>나아지지 않는 자신이 <br>한심해 보여도 <br>그대는 그대로 아름다워요 <br>어디서도 미움 받지 않으려 <br>노력했는데 <br>모나지 않게 둥글어지려 했는데 <br>오해만 남기고 실패 해버렸대도 <br>그대는 그대로 아름다워요 <br>아무 말도 하지 마요 <br>아무 것도 증명할 필요 없어요 <br>어떤 모습이라 해도 <br>그대는 그대로 아름다우니까요 <br>당신의 가치는 행동으로 <br>증명해야 할 게 아니라 <br>존재로 이미 증명되어 있는 것 <br>]]></content><category term="인메이" label="인메이"/><category term="그대는 그대로 아름다워요" label="그대는 그대로 아름다워요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인메이/내릴_역을_놓친_김에_여행을_가야지/</id><title>인메이 - 내릴 역을 놓친 김에 여행을 가야지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4/%EB%82%B4%EB%A6%B4_%EC%97%AD%EC%9D%84_%EB%86%93%EC%B9%9C_%EA%B9%80%EC%97%90_%EC%97%AC%ED%96%89%EC%9D%84_%EA%B0%80%EC%95%BC%EC%A7%80/" title="인메이 - 내릴 역을 놓친 김에 여행을 가야지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잠들려고 귀에 꽂은 <br>팟캐스트가 <br>너무 재밌어 버려서 <br>늦잠을 잤나 봐 <br>사람 많은 지하철에 <br>몸을 구겨 넣고 <br>문득 정신 차려보니 <br>내려야 할 역이야 <br>문은 열렸는데 <br>내 앞 길을 <br>가로 막는 사람이 <br>너무 많아 <br>힘을 써서 밀쳐내면 <br>어떻게든 <br>내릴 수는 있을 거지만 <br>오늘은 왠지 <br>그러고 싶지 않아 <br>내릴 역을 놓친 김에 <br>여행을 가야지 <br>즐겨찾기 해놓고 <br>백 번 열어본 그 곳 <br>파도소리 들으면서 <br>짠 냄새를 맡으며 <br>해가 지면 쏟아지는 <br>별을 봐야지 <br>낚시를 못해도 <br>사 먹으면 되겠지 <br>화면으로 보면서 <br>침만 삼키던 그거 <br>야들야들 짭조름한 <br>담백함을 맛보며 <br>살 안 쪄서 돌아가면 <br>예의가 아니겠지 <br>알람을 끈 기억이 <br>없는데 꺼져있네 <br>몸을 일으키려는데 <br>느낌이 싸해 <br>뜬금없는 타이밍에 <br>대자연이 나를 덮치네 <br>사규에 있는 대로 <br>생리휴가 쓰려해도 <br>지랄을 하겠지 <br>오늘은 왠지 <br>그러고 싶지 않아 <br>내릴 역을 놓친 김에 <br>여행을 가야지 <br>아무 호텔 잡은 뒤에 <br>방 안에 있어야지 <br>포슬포슬 이불 속에 <br>스팀 냄새 맡으며 <br>배가 고파지면 <br>룸서비스를 달라해야지 <br>낚시를 못해도 <br>사 먹으면 되겠지 <br>화면으로 보면서 <br>침만 삼키던 그거 <br>야들야들 짭조름한 <br>담백함을 맛보며 <br>살 안 쪄서 돌아가면 <br>예의가 아니겠지 <br>나를 위한 나 <br>미래를 위한 미래 <br>나를 위한 나 <br>미래를 위한 미래 <br>내릴 역을 놓친 김에 <br>여행을 가야지 <br>즐겨찾기 해놓고 <br>백 번 열어본 그 곳 <br>파도소리 들으면서 <br>짠 냄새를 맡으며 <br>해가 지면 쏟아지는 <br>별을 봐야지 <br>낚시를 못해도 <br>사 먹으면 되겠지 <br>화면으로 보면서 <br>침만 삼키던 그거 <br>야들야들 짭조름한 <br>담백함을 맛보며 <br>살 안 쪄서 돌아가면 <br>예의가 아니겠지 <br>내릴 역을 놓친 김에 <br>여행을 가야지 <br>]]></content><category term="인메이" label="인메이"/><category term="내릴 역을 놓친 김에 여행을 가야지" label="내릴 역을 놓친 김에 여행을 가야지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인메이/화를_못내/</id><title>인메이 - 화를 못내 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4/%ED%99%94%EB%A5%BC_%EB%AA%BB%EB%82%B4/" title="인메이 - 화를 못내 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[분명히 저쪽이 잘못했는데 <br>그걸 지적하기가 좀 곤란해 <br>민폐 끼치고 있는 저쪽인데 <br>내가 화를 내기가 좀 애매해 <br>이 정도까진 <br>항상 용서된다는 걸 <br>알고 있는지 <br>아니면 아예 <br>뭐가 잘못됐다는 것도 <br>모르는지 <br>다 부셔버리고 싶어 <br>다 엎어버리고 싶어 <br>무슨 부귀영화를 <br>누릴 것도 아닌데 <br>왜 난 이러고 사나 <br>다 부셔버리고 싶어 <br>다 엎어버리고 싶어 <br>화가 나는 데도 <br>아무 말도 못하는 <br>멍청이 호구 같은 나 <br>고개 끄덕이고 예예 한다고 <br>아무 일 없는 게 절대 아닌데 <br>내가 그냥 실실 웃어준다고 <br>속이 안 썩고 있는 게 아닌데 <br>계속된 호의 <br>이젠 당연하다고 <br>느껴지는 건지 <br>화낼 수 없는 <br>나의 위치를 알고 <br>이용하는 건지 <br>다 부셔버리고 싶어 <br>다 엎어버리고 싶어 <br>무슨 부귀영화를 <br>누릴 것도 아닌데 <br>왜 난 이러고 사나 <br>다 부셔버리고 싶어 <br>다 엎어버리고 싶어 <br>화가 나는 데도 <br>아무 말도 못하는 <br>멍청이 호구 같은 나 <br>왜 이 스트레스는 항상 <br>나의 몫이어야 해 <br>왜 이 스트레스는 항상 <br>나의 몫이어야 해 <br>왜 이 스트레스는 항상 <br>나의 몫이어야 해 <br>왜 이 스트레스는 항상 <br>다 부셔버리고 싶어 <br>다 엎어버리고 싶어 <br>무슨 부귀영화를 <br>누릴 것도 아닌데 <br>왜 난 이러고 사나 <br>다 부셔버리고 싶어 <br>다 엎어버리고 싶어 <br>화가 나는 데도 <br>아무 말도 못하는 <br>멍청이 호구 같은 나 <br>]]></content><category term="인메이" label="인메이"/><category term="화를 못내" label="화를 못내"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김종윤/겨울_Prod_By_타린/</id><title>김종윤 - 겨울 (Prod By. 타린) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A2%85%EC%9C%A4/%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8_Prod_By_%ED%83%80%EB%A6%B0/" title="김종윤 - 겨울 (Prod By. 타린) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가녀린 어깨로 날 감싸 안던 <br>그 밤 그 겨울이 생각이 나면 난 <br>또 웃지 그런 기억이 <br>내게 있었단 걸 감사히 여기는 <br>그 멜로디 속에서 <br>살아온 너와의 기억 <br>아프지 않아 살아 숨쉬던 밤도 <br>이야기를 내게 건네주던 겨울도 <br>다 녹아버리고 <br>또 없어진 데도 남아있는 <br>가버린 날 <br>이젠 다시 돌아올 수 없는 <br>그때 그 밤이 <br>내게 너무도 선명한데 <br>춤추던 겨울에 <br>남아있는 녹슬어버린 마음 <br>아프지 않아 살아 숨쉬던 밤도 <br>이야기를 내게 건네주던 겨울도 <br>다 녹아버리고 <br>또 없어진 데도 남아있는 <br>]]></content><category term="김종윤" label="김종윤"/><category term="겨울 (Prod By. 타린)" label="겨울 (Prod By. 타린)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/H-Line/웃음이나_Feat_박주완/</id><title>H-Line - 웃음이나 (Feat. 박주완) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/H-Line/%EC%9B%83%EC%9D%8C%EC%9D%B4%EB%82%98_Feat_%EB%B0%95%EC%A3%BC%EC%99%84/" title="H-Line - 웃음이나 (Feat. 박주완) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어느 순간 둘이 남아 <br>서로가 뻘줌해져 <br>그런 나를 쳐다보면 <br>내가 부끄러워져 <br>어색한 기운이 <br>온몸을 감싸며 <br>어떻게 해볼까 <br>농담을 던져 <br>썰렁한 농담도 <br>웃긴 얘기가 돼 <br>너와 나의 거리가 <br>점점 가까워져 <br>자꾸만 웃음이나 <br>너의 웃음이 보여 <br>어떻게 하면 너와 <br>가까워 질까 생각해 <br>단둘이 남아있어도 <br>전혀 어색하지 않아 <br>즐거운 기운이 <br>온몸을 감싸며 <br>더 다가가볼까 <br>얘기를 던져 <br>평범한 얘기도 <br>웃긴 얘기가 돼 <br>너와 나의 거리가 <br>점점 가까워져 <br>자꾸만 웃음이나 <br>너의 웃음이 보여 <br>어떻게 하면 너와 <br>가까워 질까 생각해 <br>자꾸만 웃음이나 <br>너의 웃음이 보여 <br>어떻게 하면 너와 <br>가까워 질까 생각해 <br>]]></content><category term="H-Line" label="H-Line"/><category term="웃음이나 (Feat. 박주완)" label="웃음이나 (Feat. 박주완)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/플로우식_Flowsik/Go_Hard/</id><title>플로우식_Flowsik - Go Hard - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%8C%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B0%EC%8B%9D_Flowsik/Go_Hard/" title="플로우식_Flowsik - Go Hard - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흙 crumbs in my 옷 <br>clappin ur 총 <br>입맞추는 꽃 <br>피묻은 주먹밥 꽉쥐고 <br>높은 하늘에 <br>바 바치는 몸 <br>clenching my fist <br>tight vice grip <br>yeah day night shift <br>lock and loaded <br>내리쬐는 햇빛 <br>망치는 sleep <br>taking a leap back to my 집 <br>yeah back to my home <br>i need a throne <br>깍지를 껴 <br>어두운 세상에 불가진건 나 <br>폐기처리해 이 핵쟁이 <br>click away POTG flick away <br>gg 치지 너와나 한끝차이 <br>한눈파는 사이 <br>더 멀어지는 날은 <br>더 가까이 <br>책장위 단 한권의 책 <br>내 책상위 펜자국 <br>액자뒤 숨겨논 가족 <br>aiming my frame <br>근데 나는 <br>태생부터 <br>맹수의 blood <br>지금도 피가 돌아 <br>기죽은채 전부 쫄아 <br>휘슬이 불릴때까지 <br>I go hard <br>강처럼 흐르는 마음 <br>산처럼 오르는 길 <br>땅처럼 낮은 자세 <br>거꾸로 피가 솟구치길 <br>강처럼 흐르는 마음 <br>산처럼 오르는 길 <br>땅처럼 낮은 자세 <br>거꾸로 피가 솟구치길 <br>sick flow 포격 <br>bout to blow up <br>빨리대피 가드내림 <br>언제나 squad is heavy <br>mmmm oppa 야가 <br>HARD CARRY <br>This ain't a 문제 yeah <br>You be the 술래 <br>누가 이 bullet의 <br>내 첫 주인공 될래 <br>생존 of fittest <br>상자 u fit in <br>의미없는 이름 <br>i ain’t got pity for y’all <br>다 엎드려 뻗쳐 <br>서로 다른 업적 <br>가는 길이 겹쳐 <br>하늘에 손을 벌려 <br>내 영역에 대문이 열려 열려 <br>때문에 시선을 무시해 <br>오로지 한길에 <br>모든걸 전념 <br>환호와 무대위 <br>일어선 사람들 <br>귀에서 흐르는 정적 <br>짐바구니속에 마지막 <br>부품을 조립 <br>Quest에 나선 거인 <br>무거운 사슬풀린 poet I <br>니들이 휘두른 채찍 <br>you better be ready <br>내 맷집 쎄지 <br>내 맥박 steady <br>휘발류 적신 성냥개비 <br>sick flow 포격 <br>bout to blow up <br>빨리대피 가드내림 <br>언제나 squad is heavy <br>오빠야가 HARD CARRY <br>my third eye <br>see through your mental <br>third eye <br>철사에 감긴채로 <br>망상은 계속 <br>철사에 감긴채로 <br>wish dirt on my name <br>catch a sneeze God bless you <br>내 가족 i got God <br>imma go hard <br>내 가족 내 squad을 위해 <br>I plot <br>god imma go hard <br>]]></content><category term="플로우식 (Flowsik)" label="플로우식 (Flowsik)"/><category term="Go Hard" label="Go Hard"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Siboy/Mula_Feat_Booba/</id><title>Siboy - Mula (Feat. Booba) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Siboy/Mula_Feat_Booba/" title="Siboy - Mula (Feat. Booba) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tout est noir demande a Alox <br>Ai je bre som Rue des Prairies <br>J'ai pas feate mais j'ai baise Katy Perry <br>J'ecoute beaucoup d'Alain Souchon <br>Cagoule avec des chaussons <br>J'fais plus du trap mais du poison <br>C'est pas que j't'aime plus mais disons qu't'etais plus bonne auparavant <br>Salope sache le, c'est dans ta chatte que ma queue va se baigner fais pas chier <br>Si tu n'peux pas te raser la chatte, au moins va la peigner <br>92i dans le trou noir de leur meres <br>etre gentil, je l'etais avant hier <br>Tu parles beaucoup, on a qu'une parole <br>On t'calcule pas comme un pays sans petrole <br>600 larmes, pas XXX <br>Te faire confiance, ca sent pas bon <br>Tu dis qu't'es fort, on repond ah bon <br>J'te tape pas sans que t'aies ton pardon <br>De l'univers, les meilleures gestuelles <br>La curiosite cree des homosexuels <br>Ils cherchent la guerre mais ils ont guere de talent <br>J'arrive en retard car ils ont perdu d'avance <br><br>La mula mula, la mula mula <br>La mula mula, taga dans les poumons <br>Faut qu'on fe ta fe ta pour cette mula mula <br>Faut d'la mula mula, d'la mula mula <br>D'la mula mula, taga dans les poumons <br>Faut qu'on fe ta fe ta pour cette mula mula <br>Faut d'la mula mula, d'la mula mula <br>D'la mula mula, taga dans les poumons <br>Faut qu'on fe ta fe ta pour cette mula mula <br>Faut d'la mula mula, d'la mula mula <br>D'la mula mula, taga dans les poumons <br>Faut qu'on fe ta fe ta pour cette mula mula <br><br>Art de rue comme la FF <br>Ferrari F12, week end a Marrakech <br>Pas de maladresse tu bouges, tu meurs, donne moi la caisse <br>Me demande pas comment je vais <br>Ne vois tu pas, ennemi n'peut pas se relever <br>Diamant Cuban Link'zer, plaque sur col V <br>Ils m'ouvrent la porte, j'ai deja casse la tre vi <br>Une rotule au sol, j'fais les lacets d'mon se fi <br>DUC, Siboy, pas de maladresse <br>Tu cherches l'echec, tu sais qui a l'adresse <br>J'baise une pute d'Chateau Rouge, je lui crache dans les tresses <br>J't'allumerai negro avec allegresse <br>T'es sur les Buttes Chaumont avec Jena Lee <br>J'suis sur mont de Tallac avec grizzli <br>Faut d'la mula mula, d'la mula mula <br>Ils n'aiment pas le mafe, ils n'aiment pas la burqa <br>Fier de mes origines comme la bouille a Luna <br>J'ai cru voir un rappeur twerker chez Hanouna <br>On a decele cocaine dans ta khanouna <br>Laisse les croire que je n'sais dire que ounga ounga <br>Feuille de marijuana dans le gloubi boulga <br>Tout est noi noir <br><br>La mula mula, la mula mula <br>La mula mula, taga dans les poumons <br>Faut qu'on fe ta fe ta pour cette mula mula <br>Faut d'la mula mula, d'la mula mula <br>D'la mula mula, taga dans les poumons <br>Faut qu'on fe ta fe ta pour cette mula mula <br>Faut d'la mula mula, d'la mula mula <br>D'la mula mula, taga dans les poumons <br>Faut qu'on fe ta fe ta pour cette mula mula <br>Faut d'la mula mula, d'la mula mula <br>D'la mula mula, taga dans les poumons <br>Faut qu'on fe ta fe ta pour cette mula mula <br><br>D'aucune pitie, je m'sens saisi <br>Je les encule avec plaisir <br>Fuck les flagrants delits <br>Ferme la et peut etre ta mort va s'embellir sache le <br>Tu pousses 100 kil' en salle, tu meurs d'une balle de quelques grammes <br>J'suis sorti capuche le soir, j'suis d'humeur a baiser quelques dames <br>J'suis comme la mort, j'peux surprendre au prochain carrefour <br>Laisse moi faire mon parcours, ta vie sera le Darfour <br>Faut qu'tu saches petit negre, t'es ma proie petit negre <br>Tu m'suceras jusqu'a en perdre la voix petit negre <br>Faut qu'j'te vois negro pour que j'te crois petit negre <br>Faut qu'j'te croise petasse pour que j'te broie, salope <br>C'qui est fait est fait, negro fuck les regrets <br>Regarde moi bien si tu veux voir ta mort d'plus pres <br>Negro c'est terrible, c'est pas les tuer mais cacher l'corps qui est penible <br>J'suis que de passage, j'vais les dresser comme enfants de bas age <br><br>La mula mula, la mula mula <br>La mula mula, taga dans les poumons <br>Faut qu'on fe ta fe ta pour cette mula mula <br>Faut d'la mula mula, d'la mula mula <br>D'la mula mula, taga dans les poumons <br>Faut qu'on fe ta fe ta pour cette mula mula <br>Faut d'la mula mula, d'la mula mula <br>D'la mula mula, taga dans les poumons <br>Faut qu'on fe ta fe ta pour cette mula mula <br>Faut d'la mula mula, d'la mula mula <br>D'la mula mula, taga dans les poumons <br>Faut qu'on fe ta fe ta pour cette mula mula]]></content><category term="Siboy" label="Siboy"/><category term="Mula (Feat. Booba)" label="Mula (Feat. Booba)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Save_Myself/</id><title>Ed_Sheeran - Save Myself - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:56:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:56:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Save_Myself/" title="Ed_Sheeran - Save Myself - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I gave all my oxygen <br>to people that could breath <br>I gave away my money and <br>now we don’t even speak <br>I drove miles and miles <br>but would you do the same for me <br>Oh honestly <br>Offered up my shoulder just <br>for you to cry upon <br>Gave you constant shelter and <br>a bed to keep you warm <br>They gave me the heartache <br>and in return I gave a song <br>It goes on and on <br>Life can get you down <br>so I just numb the way it feels <br>I drown it with a drink <br>and out of date prescription pills <br>And all the ones that love me <br>they just left me on the shelf <br>no farewell <br>So before I save someone else <br>I’ve got to save myself <br>I gave you all my energy <br>and I took away your pain <br>Cause human beings <br>are destined to radiate or drain <br>What line do we stand upon <br>cause from here it looks the same <br>And only scars remain <br>Life can get you down <br>so I just numb the way it feels <br>I drown it with a drink <br>and out of date prescription pills <br>And all the ones that love me <br>they just left me on the shelf <br>no farewell <br>So before I save someone else <br>I’ve got to save myself <br>But if I don’t <br>then I’ll go back <br>to where I’m rescuing a stranger <br>Just because they needed saving <br>just like that <br>Oh I’m here again <br>between the devil and the danger <br>But I guess it’s just my nature <br>My dad was wrong <br>cause I’m not like my mum <br>Cause she’d just smile <br>and I’m complaining in a song <br>but it helps <br>So before I save someone else <br>I’ve got to save myself <br>Life can get you down <br>so I just numb the way it feels <br>Or drown it with a drink <br>and out of date prescription pills <br>And all the ones that love me <br>they just left me on the shelf <br>no farewell <br>So before I save someone else <br>I’ve got to save myself <br>And before I blame someone else <br>I’ve got to save myself <br>And before I love someone else <br>I’ve got to love myself <br>]]></content><category term="Ed Sheeran" label="Ed Sheeran"/><category term="Save Myself" label="Save Myself"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Nancy_Mulligan/</id><title>Ed_Sheeran - Nancy Mulligan - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:57:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:57:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Nancy_Mulligan/" title="Ed_Sheeran - Nancy Mulligan - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was twenty four years old <br>when I met the woman <br>I would call my own <br>Twenty two grand <br>kids now growing old <br>in the house that your <br>brother brought ya <br>On the summer day <br>when I proposed <br>I made that wedding ring <br>from dentist gold <br>And I asked her father <br>but her daddy said no <br>You can’t marry my daughter <br>She and I went on the run <br>Don’t care about religion <br>I’m gonna marry the woman I love <br>Down by the Wexford border <br>She was Nancy Mulligan <br>and I was William Sheeran <br>She took my name <br>and then we were one <br>Down by the Wexford border <br>Well I met at her Guys <br>in the second world war <br>She was working on a soldier’s ward <br>Never had I seen such beauty before <br>The moment that I saw her <br>Nancy was my yellow rose <br>And we got married wearing <br>borrowed clothes <br>We got eight children now <br>growing old <br>Five sons and three daughters <br>She and I went on the run <br>Don’t care about religion <br>I’m gonna marry the woman I love <br>Down by the Wexford border <br>She was Nancy Mulligan <br>and I was William Sheeran <br>She took my name <br>and then we were one <br>Down by the Wexford border <br>From her snow white <br>streak in her jet black hair <br>Over sixty years <br>I’ve been loving her <br>Now we’re sat by the fire <br>in our old armchairs <br>You know Nancy I adore ya <br>From a farm boy <br>born near Belfast town <br>I never worried about the <br>king and crown <br>Cause I found my heart upon the <br>southern ground <br>There’s no difference I assure ya <br>She and I went on the run <br>Don’t care about religion <br>I’m gonna marry the woman I love <br>Down by the Wexford border <br>She was Nancy Mulligan <br>and I was William Sheeran <br>She took my name <br>and then we were one <br>Down by the Wexford border <br>]]></content><category term="Ed Sheeran" label="Ed Sheeran"/><category term="Nancy Mulligan" label="Nancy Mulligan"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Bibia_Be_Ye_Ye/</id><title>Ed_Sheeran - Bibia Be Ye Ye - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:57:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:57:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Bibia_Be_Ye_Ye/" title="Ed_Sheeran - Bibia Be Ye Ye - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bibia Be Ye Ye <br>I lost my shoes last night <br>I don’t know <br>where I put my keys <br>I was tired and fell asleep <br>beneath an oak tree <br>I bet my mother’s proud of me <br>from each scar upon my knuckle <br>And each graze upon my knee <br>and all I know <br>is I got a cab and then threw up <br>on his car seat <br>He kicked me out <br>and then I walked in the rain <br>I tell myself in every way <br>I won’t be doing this again <br>And tomorrow’s a brand new day <br>Someone told me <br>always say what’s on your mind <br>And I am only <br>being honest with you <br>I I get lonely <br>And make mistakes <br>from time to time <br>Se enioma enko ye <br>Bibia Be Ye Ye <br>Bibia Be Ye Ye Ye Ye Ye Ye Ye <br>Bibia Be Ye Ye <br>I remember less and less <br>and mostly things that I regret <br>In my phone are several texts <br>from girls I’ve never met <br>And in the pocket of my jeans <br>are only coins and broken dreams <br>My heart is breaking at the seams <br>And I’m coming apart now <br>Now things are looking up <br>I’ll find my shoes <br>right next to the oak tree <br>And I’ll get a bus straight into town <br>And spend the afternoon <br>looking around <br>for the things that I left <br>on the ground <br>And say you’re with me <br>tomorrow’s a brand new day <br>Someone told me <br>always say what’s on your mind <br>And I am only <br>being honest with you <br>I I get lonely <br>And make mistakes <br>from time to time <br>Se enioma enko ye <br>Bibia Be Ye Ye <br>Wo nooma Be Ye Ye <br>Wo nooma maaaa ye <br>Wo nooma Be Ye Ye <br>Wo nooma maaaa ye <br>Wo nooma Be Ye Ye <br>Wo nooma maaaa ye <br>Wo nooma Be Ye Ye <br>Wo nooma maaaa ye <br>Someone told me <br>always say what’s on your mind <br>And I am only <br>being honest with you <br>I I get lonely <br>And make mistakes <br>from time to time <br>Se enioma enko ye <br>Bibia Be Ye Ye <br>Bibia Be Ye Ye Ye Ye Ye Ye Ye <br>Bibia Be Ye Ye <br>Wo nooma Be Ye Ye <br>Wo nooma maaaa ye <br>Wo nooma Be Ye Ye <br>Bibia Be Ye Ye <br>Wo nooma Be Ye Ye <br>Wo nooma maaaa ye <br>Wo nooma Be Ye Ye <br>Wo nooma maaaa ye <br>]]></content><category term="Ed Sheeran" label="Ed Sheeran"/><category term="Bibia Be Ye Ye" label="Bibia Be Ye Ye"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Barcelona/</id><title>Ed_Sheeran - Barcelona - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:57:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:57:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Barcelona/" title="Ed_Sheeran - Barcelona - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well get up up on the <br>dancefloor tonight <br>I’ve got two left feet <br>and a bottle of red wine <br>Making me feel <br>like the beat and the bassline <br>Are in my blood both <br>hands upon her waistline <br>Get on up baby dance to the <br>rhythm of the music <br>Don’t care what the DJ chooses <br>Get lost in the rhythm of me <br>Place don’t close <br>until we wanna leave it <br>You and I we’re flying <br>on an aeroplane tonight <br>We’re going somewhere <br>where the sun is shining bright <br>Just close your eyes <br>and let’s pretend <br>we’re dancing in the street <br>In Barcelona <br>Barcelona <br>Barcelona <br>Barcelona <br>Well get up up on the <br>dancefloor move <br>it’s a Saturday night <br>I fell in love <br>with the sparkle in the moonlight <br>Reflected in your beautiful eyes <br>I guess that is destiny <br>doing it right <br>And dance like they do <br>in the Mediterranean <br>Spin you around me <br>again and again <br>You’re like something that <br>God has sent me <br>I want you baby solamente <br>You and I we’re flying <br>on an aeroplane tonight <br>We’re going somewhere <br>where the sun is shining bright <br>Just close your eyes <br>and let’s pretend <br>we’re dancing in the street <br>In Barcelona <br>Barcelona <br>Barcelona <br>Barcelona <br>Barcelona <br>Barcelona <br>Oh Barcelona <br>So let’s pretend <br>we’re dancing in the street <br>In Barcelona <br>Las Ramblas <br>I’ll meet you <br>we’ll dance around <br>La Sagrada Familia <br>Drinking Sangria <br>mi nina te amo mi carino <br>Mamacita rica <br>si tu te adoro senorita <br>Los otros viva la vida <br>Come on <br>let’s be free in Barcelona <br>Las Ramblas <br>I’ll meet ya <br>come on and dance with me <br>in Barcelona <br>Drinking Sangria <br>I just want to be <br>in Barcelona <br>Mamacita rica <br>feel that summer breeze <br>in Barcelona <br>Los otros viva la vida <br>siempre vida <br>Barcelona <br>]]></content><category term="Ed Sheeran" label="Ed Sheeran"/><category term="Barcelona" label="Barcelona"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Supermarket_Flowers/</id><title>Ed_Sheeran - Supermarket Flowers - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:57:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:57:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Supermarket_Flowers/" title="Ed_Sheeran - Supermarket Flowers - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I took the supermarket flowers <br>from the windowsill <br>Threw the day old tea from the cup <br>Packed up the photo album <br>Matthew had made <br>Memories of a life <br>that’s been loved <br>Took the get well soon cards <br>and stuffed animals <br>Poured the old ginger beer <br>down the sink <br>Dad always told me <br>don’t you cry when you’re down <br>But mum there’s a tear <br>every time that I blink <br>Oh I’m in pieces <br>it’s tearing me up but I know <br>A heart that’s broke <br>is a heart that’s been loved <br>So I’ll sing Hallelujah <br>you were an angel <br>in the shape of my mum <br>When I fell down you’d be there <br>holding me up <br>Spread your wings as you go <br>And when God takes you back <br>He’ll say Hallelujah you’re home <br>I fluffed the pillows <br>made the beds <br>stacked the chairs up <br>Folded your nightgowns <br>neatly in a case <br>John said he’d drive then <br>put his hand on my cheek <br>And wiped a tear from the side <br>of my face <br>I hope that I see the world <br>as you did cause I know <br>A life with love is a life <br>that’s been lived <br>So I’ll sing Hallelujah <br>you were an angel <br>in the shape of my mum <br>When I fell down you’d be there <br>holding me up <br>Spread your wings as you go <br>when God takes you back <br>He’ll say Hallelujah you’re home <br>Hallelujah <br>you were an angel <br>in the shape of my mum <br>You got to see the person <br>that I have become <br>Spread your wings and I know <br>That when God took you back <br>he said Hallelujah you’re home <br>]]></content><category term="Ed Sheeran" label="Ed Sheeran"/><category term="Supermarket Flowers" label="Supermarket Flowers"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/How_Would_You_Feel_Paean/</id><title>Ed_Sheeran - How Would You Feel (Paean) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:57:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:57:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/How_Would_You_Feel_Paean/" title="Ed_Sheeran - How Would You Feel (Paean) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You are the one girl <br>and you know that it's true <br>I'm feeling younger <br>every time that I'm alone with you <br>We were sitting in a parked car <br>stealing kisses in the front yard <br>We got questions <br>we should not ask but <br>How would you feel <br>if I told you I loved you <br>It's just something <br>that I want to do <br>I'll be taking my time <br>spending my life <br>Falling deeper in love with you <br>So tell me that you love me too <br>In the summer <br>as the lilacs bloom <br>Love flows deeper than the river <br>every moment that I spend with you <br>We were sat upon <br>our best friend's roof <br>I had both of my arms round you <br>Watching the sunrise <br>replace the moon <br>How would you feel <br>if I told you I loved you <br>It's just something <br>that I want to do <br>I'll be taking my time <br>spending my life <br>Falling deeper in love with you <br>So tell me that you love me too <br>We were sitting in a parked car <br>stealing kisses in the front yard <br>We got questions <br>we should not ask but <br>How would you feel <br>if I told you I loved you <br>It's just something <br>that I want to do <br>I'll be taking my time <br>spending my life <br>Falling deeper in love with you <br>So tell me that you love me too <br>Tell me that you love me too <br>Tell me that you love me too <br>]]></content><category term="Ed Sheeran" label="Ed Sheeran"/><category term="How Would You Feel (Paean)" label="How Would You Feel (Paean)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/What_Do_I_Know_/</id><title>Ed_Sheeran - What Do I Know? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:57:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:57:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/What_Do_I_Know_/" title="Ed_Sheeran - What Do I Know? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ain't got a soapbox <br>I can stand upon <br>But god gave me a stage <br>a guitar and a song <br>My daddy told me <br>son don't you get involved <br>in politics religions <br>other peoples' quarrels <br>I'll paint the picture <br>let me set the scene <br>I know when I have children <br>they will know what it means <br>And I'll pass on the things <br>my family's given to me <br>Just love and understanding <br>positivity <br>We could change this whole <br>world with a piano <br>Add a bass some guitar <br>grab a beat and away we go <br>I'm just a boy <br>with a one man show <br>No university no degree <br>but lord knows <br>Everybody's talking about <br>exponential growth <br>And the stock market crashing <br>and their portfolios <br>While I'll be sitting here <br>with a song that I wrote <br>Saying love could change <br>the world in a moment <br>But what do I know <br>Love can change the world in a moment <br>But what do I know <br>Love can change the world in a moment <br>The revolution's coming <br>it's a minute away <br>I saw people marching <br>in the streets today <br>You know we are made up <br>of love and hate <br>But both of them are balanced <br>on a razor blade <br>I'll paint the picture <br>let me set the scene <br>I know <br>I'm all for people following <br>their dreams <br>Just remember life is more than <br>fitting in your jeans <br>It's love and understanding <br>positivity <br>We could change this whole <br>world with a piano <br>Add a bass some guitar <br>grab a beat and away we go <br>I'm just a boy <br>with a one man show <br>No university no degree <br>but lord knows <br>Everybody's talking about <br>exponential growth <br>And the stock market crashing <br>and their portfolios <br>While I'll be sitting here <br>with a song that I wrote <br>Saying love could change <br>the world in a moment <br>But what do I know <br>Love can change the world in a moment <br>But what do I know <br>Love can change the world in a moment <br>I'll paint the picture <br>let me set the scene <br>You know the future's <br>in the hands of you and me <br>So let's all get together <br>we can all be free <br>Spread love and understanding <br>positivity <br>We could change this whole <br>world with a piano <br>Add a bass some guitar <br>grab a beat and away we go <br>I'm just a boy with a one man show <br>No university no degree <br>but lord knows <br>Everybody's talking about <br>exponential growth <br>And the stock market crashing <br>and their portfolios <br>While I'll be sitting here <br>with a song that I wrote <br>Saying love could change <br>the world in a moment <br>But what do I know <br>Love can change the world in a moment <br>But what do I know <br>Love can change the world in a moment <br>But what do I know <br>]]></content><category term="Ed Sheeran" label="Ed Sheeran"/><category term="What Do I Know?" label="What Do I Know?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Hearts_Dont_Break_Around_Here/</id><title>Ed_Sheeran - Hearts Don`t Break Around Here - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:57:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:57:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Hearts_Dont_Break_Around_Here/" title="Ed_Sheeran - Hearts Don`t Break Around Here - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She is the sweetest thing <br>that I know <br>You should see the way <br>she holds me <br>when the lights go low <br>Shakes my soul like a pot hole <br>every time <br>Took my heart upon <br>a one way trip <br>Guess she went wandering <br>off with it <br>Unlike most women I know <br>This one will bring it back whole <br>Daisies daisies perched upon <br>your forehead <br>Oh my baby lately I know <br>That every night <br>I'll kiss you you'll say in my ear <br>Oh we're in love aren't we <br>Hands in your hair <br>fingers and thumbs baby <br>I feel safe when you're <br>holding me near <br>Love the way that you <br>conquer your fear <br>You know hearts don't <br>break around here <br>Oh yeah yeah yeah <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>She is the river flow in Orwell <br>And tin wind chimes <br>used for doorbells <br>Fields and trees and her smell <br>fill my lungs <br>Spent my summer time <br>beside her <br>And the rest of the year <br>the same <br>She is the flint that <br>sparks the lighter <br>And the fuel that will <br>hold the flame <br>Oh roses roses laid upon <br>your bed spread <br>Oh my hold this <br>oh this I know <br>That every night <br>I'll kiss you you'll say in my ear <br>Oh we're in love aren't we <br>Hands in your hair <br>fingers and thumbs baby <br>I feel safe when you're <br>holding me near <br>Love the way that you <br>conquer your fear <br>You know hearts don't <br>break around here <br>Oh yeah yeah yeah <br>Well I found love in the inside <br>The arms of a woman I know <br>She is the lighthouse in the night <br>that will safely guide me home <br>And I'm not scared of passing over <br>Or the thought of growing old <br>Because from now until I go <br>Every night <br>I'll kiss you you'll say in my ear <br>Oh we're in love aren't we <br>Hands in your hair <br>fingers and thumbs baby <br>I feel safe when you're <br>holding me near <br>Love the way that you <br>conquer your fear <br>You know hearts don't <br>break around here <br>Oh yeah yeah <br>Every night <br>I'll kiss you you'll say in my ear <br>Oh we're in love aren't we <br>Hands in your hair <br>fingers and thumbs baby <br>I feel safe when you're <br>holding me near <br>Love the way that you <br>conquer your fear <br>You know hearts don't <br>break around here <br>Yeah yeah yeah <br>You know hearts don't <br>break around here <br>Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>]]></content><category term="Ed Sheeran" label="Ed Sheeran"/><category term="Hearts Don`t Break Around Here" label="Hearts Don`t Break Around Here"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/New_Man/</id><title>Ed_Sheeran - New Man - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:57:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:57:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/New_Man/" title="Ed_Sheeran - New Man - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I heard he spent five hundred <br>pounds on jeans <br>Goes to the gym at least <br>six times a week <br>Wears boat shoes with no socks <br>on his feet <br>And I heard he's on a new diet <br>and watches what he eats <br>He's got his eyebrows plucked <br>and his arsehole bleached <br>Owns every single Ministry CD <br>Tribal tattoos and he don't know <br>what it means <br>But I heard he makes you happy <br>so that's fine by me <br>But still I'm just keeping it real <br>still looking at your Instagram <br>and I'll be creeping a little <br>I'll be trying not to double tap <br>from way back <br>cause I know that's <br>where the trouble's at <br>Let me remind of the days <br>when you used to hold my hand <br>And when we sipped <br>champagne out of cider cans <br>I guess if you were Lois Lane <br>I wasn't superman <br>just a young boy <br>trying to be loved <br>So let me give it to you <br>I don't wanna know about <br>your new man <br>cause if it was meant to be <br>You wouldn't be calling me <br>up trying to <br>Cause I'm positive that <br>he don't wanna know about me <br>I don't wanna know about <br>your new man <br>we'll get there eventually <br>I know you're missing <br>all this kind of love <br>But I'm positive that <br>he don't wanna know about me <br>Your new man rents a house <br>in the burb <br>and wears a man bag <br>on his shoulder <br>but I call it a purse <br>Every year he goes to Malaga <br>with all the fellas <br>drinks beer but has a six pack <br>I'm kind of jealous <br>He wears sunglasses indoors <br>in winter at nighttime <br>and every time a rap song <br>comes on <br>He makes a gun sign <br>says chune <br>bwoydem light up the room <br>But enough about him <br>girl let's talk about you <br>You were the type of girl <br>that sat beside the water reading <br>Eating a packet of crisps <br>but you will never find you cheating <br>Now you're eating kale <br>hitting the gym <br>keeping up with Kylie &amp; Kim <br>In the back of the club kissing <br>a boy that ain't him <br>Ok you need to be alone <br>and if you wanna talk about it <br>you can call my phone <br>I just thought that I would tell you <br>cause you oughta know <br>You're still a young girl <br>trying to be loved <br>So let me give it to you <br>I don't wanna know about <br>your new man <br>cause if it was meant to be <br>You wouldn't be calling me <br>up trying to <br>Cause I'm positive that <br>he don't wanna know about me <br>I don't wanna know about <br>your new man <br>we'll get there eventually <br>I know you're missing <br>all this kind of love <br>But I'm positive that <br>he don't wanna know about me <br>Baby <br>I'm not trying to ruin your week <br>But you act so differently <br>When you're with him <br>I know you're lonely <br>Please <br>remember you're still free <br>to make the choice and leave <br>And don't call me up <br>you need to show me <br>I don't wanna know about <br>your new man <br>cause if it was meant to be <br>You wouldn't be calling me <br>up trying to <br>Cause I'm positive that <br>he don't wanna know about me <br>I don't wanna know about <br>your new man <br>we'll get there eventually <br>I know you're missing <br>all this kind of love <br>But I'm positive that <br>he don't wanna know about me <br>Know about me know <br>know about me <br>I don't wanna know <br>about your new man <br>]]></content><category term="Ed Sheeran" label="Ed Sheeran"/><category term="New Man" label="New Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Happier/</id><title>Ed_Sheeran - Happier - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:57:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:57:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Happier/" title="Ed_Sheeran - Happier - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Walking down 29th and park <br>I saw you in another's arms <br>Only a month we've been apart <br>You look happier <br>Saw you walk inside a bar <br>He said something to <br>make you laugh <br>I saw that both your smiles <br>were twice as wide as ours <br>Yeah you look happier you do <br>Ain't nobody hurt you like <br>I hurt you <br>But ain't nobody love you like I do <br>Promise that I will not take it <br>personal baby <br>If you're moving on <br>with someone new <br>Cause baby you look happier you do <br>My friends told me one day <br>I'll feel it too <br>And until then I'll smile to <br>hide the truth <br>But I know I was happier with you <br>Sat in the corner of the room <br>Everything's reminding me of you <br>Nursing an empty bottle and <br>telling myself you're happier <br>Aren't you <br>Ain't nobody hurt you like <br>I hurt you <br>But ain't nobody need you <br>like I do <br>I know that there's others <br>that deserve you <br>But my darling I am still <br>in love with you <br>But I guess you look happier you do <br>My friends told me one day <br>I'll feel it too <br>I could try to smile to <br>hide the truth <br>But I know I was happier with you <br>Baby you look happier you do <br>I knew one day <br>you'd fall for someone new <br>But if he breaks <br>your heart like lovers do <br>Just know that <br>I'll be waiting here for you <br>]]></content><category term="Ed Sheeran" label="Ed Sheeran"/><category term="Happier" label="Happier"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Galway_Girl/</id><title>Ed_Sheeran - Galway Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:57:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:57:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Galway_Girl/" title="Ed_Sheeran - Galway Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She played the fiddle <br>in an Irish band <br>But she fell in love <br>with an English man <br>Kissed her on the neck <br>and then I took her by the hand <br>Said baby I just want to dance <br>I met her on Grafton street right <br>outside of the bar <br>She shared a cigarette <br>with me while her brother <br>played the guitar <br>She asked me <br>what does it mean the Gaelic ink <br>on your arm <br>Said it was one <br>of my friend’s songs <br>do you want to drink on <br>She took Jamie as a chaser <br>Jack for the fun <br>She got Arthur on the table <br>with Johnny riding as shot gun <br>Chatted some more <br>one more drink at the bar <br>Then put Van on the jukebox <br>got up to dance you know <br>She played the fiddle <br>in an Irish band <br>But she fell in love <br>with an English man <br>Kissed her on the neck <br>and then I took her by the hand <br>Said baby I just want to dance <br>With my pretty little Galway Girl <br>You’re my pretty <br>little Galway Girl <br>You know she beat me at darts <br>and then she beat me at pool <br>And then she kissed me like <br>there was nobody else in the room <br>As last orders were called <br>was when she stood on the stool <br>After dancing to ceili <br>singing to trad tunes <br>I never heard Carrickfergus <br>ever sung so sweet <br>Acapella in the bar <br>using her feet for a beat <br>Oh I could have that voice playing <br>on repeat for a week <br>And in this packed out room <br>swear she was singing to me <br>She played the fiddle <br>in an Irish band <br>But she fell in love <br>with an English man <br>Kissed her on the neck <br>and then I took her by the hand <br>Said baby I just want to dance <br>My pretty little Galway girl <br>My my my my my my my Galway girl <br>My my my my my my my Galway girl <br>My my my my my my my Galway girl <br>Now we’ve outstayed our welcome <br>and it’s closing time <br>I was holding her hand <br>her hand was holding mine <br>Our coats both smell of smoke <br>whisky and wine <br>As we fill up our lungs <br>with the cold air of the night <br>I walked her home <br>then she took me inside <br>Finish some Doritos <br>and another bottle of wine <br>I swear I’m going to put you <br>in a song that I write <br>About a Galway girl <br>and a perfect night <br>She played the fiddle <br>in an Irish band <br>But she fell in love <br>with an English man <br>Kissed her on the neck <br>and then I took her by the hand <br>Said baby I just want to dance <br>My pretty little Galway girl <br>My my my my my my my Galway girl <br>My my my my my my my Galway girl <br>My my my my my my my Galway girl <br>]]></content><category term="Ed Sheeran" label="Ed Sheeran"/><category term="Galway Girl" label="Galway Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Perfect/</id><title>Ed_Sheeran - Perfect - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:57:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:57:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Perfect/" title="Ed_Sheeran - Perfect - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I found a love for me <br>Darling just dive right in <br>and follow my lead <br>Well I found a girl <br>beautiful and sweet <br>I never knew you were <br>the someone waiting for me <br>Cause we were just kids <br>when we fell in love <br>Not knowing what it was <br>I will not give you up this time <br>But darling just kiss me slow <br>your heart is all I own <br>And in your eyes <br>you’re holding mine <br>Baby I’m dancing in the dark <br>with you between my arms <br>Barefoot on the grass <br>listening to our favourite song <br>When you said you looked a mess <br>I whispered underneath my breath <br>But you heard it <br>darling you look perfect tonight <br>Well I found a woman <br>stronger than anyone I know <br>She shares my dreams <br>I hope that someday <br>I’ll share her home <br>I found a love <br>to carry more than just my secrets <br>To carry love <br>to carry children of our own <br>We are still kids <br>but we’re so in love <br>fighting against all odds <br>I know we’ll be alright this time <br>Darling just hold my hand <br>be my girl <br>I’ll be your man <br>I see my future in your eyes <br>Baby I’m dancing in the dark <br>with you between my arms <br>Barefoot on the grass <br>listening to our favourite song <br>When I saw you in that dress <br>looking so beautiful <br>I don’t deserve this <br>darling you look perfect tonight <br>Baby I’m dancing in the dark <br>with you between my arms <br>Barefoot on the grass <br>listening to our favourite song <br>I have faith in what I see <br>Now I know I have met <br>an angel in person <br>And she looks perfect <br>no I don’t deserve this <br>You look perfect tonight <br>]]></content><category term="Ed Sheeran" label="Ed Sheeran"/><category term="Perfect" label="Perfect"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Castle_on_the_Hill/</id><title>Ed_Sheeran - Castle on the Hill - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:57:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:57:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Castle_on_the_Hill/" title="Ed_Sheeran - Castle on the Hill - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I was six years old <br>I broke my leg <br>I was running from my brother <br>and his friends <br>tasted the sweet perfume <br>of the mountain grass <br>I rolled down <br>I was younger then <br>take me back to when I <br>Found my heart and broke it here <br>made friends and lost them <br>through the years <br>And I’ve not seen <br>the roaring fields in so long <br>I know I’ve grown <br>but I can’t wait to go home <br>I’m on my way driving at 90 <br>down those country lanes <br>Singing to Tiny Dancer <br>And I miss the way <br>you make me feel <br>and it’s real <br>When we watched the sunset <br>over the castle on the hill <br>Fifteen years old <br>and smoking hand rolled cigarettes <br>Running from the law <br>through the backfields <br>and getting drunk with my friends <br>Had my first kiss <br>on a Friday night <br>I don’t reckon I did it right <br>I was younger then <br>take me back to when we found <br>Weekend jobs when we got paid <br>and buy cheap spirits <br>and drink them straight <br>Me and my friends have <br>not thrown up in so long <br>oh how we’ve grown <br>I can’t wait to go home <br>I’m on my way <br>driving at 90 down <br>those country lanes <br>Singing to Tiny Dancer <br>And I miss the way <br>you make me feel <br>it’s real <br>When we watched the sunset <br>over the castle on the hill <br>Over the castle on the hill <br>Over the castle on the hill <br>One friend left to sell clothes <br>One works down by the coast <br>One had two kids but lives alone <br>One’s brother overdosed <br>Ones already on his second wife <br>Ones just barely getting by <br>But these people raised me <br>And I can’t wait to go home <br>And I’m on my way <br>and I still remember <br>those country lanes <br>When we did not know the answers <br>And I miss the way <br>you make me feel <br>it’s real <br>When we watched the sunset <br>over the castle on the hill <br>Over the castle on the hill <br>Over the castle on the hill <br>]]></content><category term="Ed Sheeran" label="Ed Sheeran"/><category term="Castle on the Hill" label="Castle on the Hill"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_C_The_Slide_Man/Cha_Cha_Slide_Radio_Edit/</id><title>Mr_C_The_Slide_Man - Cha Cha Slide (Radio Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:57:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:57:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_C_The_Slide_Man/Cha_Cha_Slide_Radio_Edit/" title="Mr_C_The_Slide_Man - Cha Cha Slide (Radio Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This is something new <br>The Casper slide part two <br>Featuring the platinum band <br>And this time <br>We're going to get Funky <br>Funky <br><br>Everybody clap your hands <br>Clap Clap Clap Clap your hands <br>Clap Clap Clap Clap your hands <br>Alright now, we're going to do the basic step <br><br>To the left <br>Take it back now, y'all <br>One hop this time <br>Right foot, let's stomp <br>Left foot, let's stomp <br>Cha Cha real smooth <br><br>Turn it out <br>To the left <br>Take it back now y'all <br>One hop this time <br>Right foot, let's stomp <br>Left foot, let's stomp <br>Cha Cha now y'all <br>Last time we're getting funky <br><br>To the right now <br>To the left <br>Take it back now y'all <br>One hop this time <br>One hop this time <br>Right foot two stomps <br>Left foot two stomps <br>Slide to the left <br>Slide to the right <br>Criss Cross <br>Criss Cross <br>Cha Cha real smooth <br><br>Let's go to work <br>To the left <br>Take it back now y'all <br>Two hops this time <br>Two hops this time <br>Right foot two stomps <br>Left foot two stomps <br>Hands on you knees Hands on your knees <br>Keep funking it All yeah <br>Cha Cha now y'all <br>Turn it out <br><br>To the left <br>Take it back now y'all <br>Five hops this time <br>Hop it out now <br>Right foot let's stomp <br>Left foot let's stomp <br>Right foot again <br>Left foot again <br>Right foot let's stomp <br>Left foot let's stomp <br>FREEZE <br>Everybody clap your hands <br><br>Come on y'all Check it out y'all <br>How low can you go <br>Can you go down low <br>All the way to the floor <br>How low can you go <br>Can you bring it to the top <br>Like it never never stop <br>Can you bring it to the top <br>One hop <br>Right foot now <br>Left foot now y'all <br>Cha Cha real smooth <br><br>Turn it out <br>To the left <br>Take it back now y'all <br>One hop this time <br>One hop this time <br>Reverse <br>Reverse <br>Slide to the left <br>Slide to the right <br>Reverse reverse <br>Reverse reverse <br>Cha Cha now y'all <br>Cha Cha again <br>Cha Cha now y'all <br>Cha Cha again <br><br>Turn it out <br>To the left <br>Take it back now y'all <br>Two hops Two hops <br>Two hops Two hops <br>Right foot let's stomp <br>Left foot let's stomp <br>Charlie brown <br>Hop it out now <br>Slide to the right <br>Slide to the left <br>Take it back now y'all <br>Cha Cha now y'all <br><br>Ah, yeah <br>Yeah Do that stuff <br>Ah yeah <br><br>I'm out of here y'all Peace]]></content><category term="Mr. C The Slide Man" label="Mr. C The Slide Man"/><category term="Cha Cha Slide (Radio Edit)" label="Cha Cha Slide (Radio Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Dive/</id><title>Ed_Sheeran - Dive - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:57:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:57:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Dive/" title="Ed_Sheeran - Dive - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe I came on too strong <br>Maybe I waited too long <br>Maybe I played my cards wrong <br>Oh just a little bit wrong <br>Baby I apologise for it <br>I could fall or I could fly <br>Here in your aeroplane <br>I could live I could die <br>Hanging on the words you say <br>I’ve been known to give my all <br>And jumping in harder than <br>10000 rocks on the lake <br>So don’t call me baby <br>Unless you mean it <br>Don’t tell me you need me <br>If you don’t believe it <br>So let me know the truth <br>Before I dive right into you <br>You’re a mystery <br>I have travelled the world <br>And there’s no other girl <br>like you no one <br>What’s your history <br>Do you have a tendency <br>to lead some people on <br>Cause I heard you do <br>I could fall or I could fly <br>Here in your aeroplane <br>I could live I could die <br>Hanging on the words you say <br>I’ve been known to give my all <br>And lie awake every day <br>Don’t know how much I can take <br>So don’t call me baby <br>Unless you mean it <br>Don’t tell me you need me <br>If you don’t believe it <br>So let me know the truth <br>Before I dive right into you <br>I could fall or I could fly <br>Here in your aeroplane <br>I could live I could die <br>Hanging on the words you say <br>I’ve been known to give my all <br>Sitting back looking at <br>Every mess that I made <br>So don’t call me baby <br>Unless you mean it <br>Don’t tell me you need me <br>If you don’t believe it <br>So let me know the truth <br>Before I dive right into you <br>Before I dive right into you <br>Before I dive right into you <br>]]></content><category term="Ed Sheeran" label="Ed Sheeran"/><category term="Dive" label="Dive"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Eraser/</id><title>Ed_Sheeran - Eraser - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T12:57:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T12:57:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ed_Sheeran/Eraser/" title="Ed_Sheeran - Eraser - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was born inside a small town <br>I lost that state of mind <br>Learned to sing inside the <br>lord’s house <br>But stopped at the age of nine <br>I forget when I get awards now <br>the wave I had to ride <br>The paving stones I played upon <br>that kept me on the grind <br>So blame it on the pain <br>that blessed me with the life <br>Friends and family filled <br>with envy <br>when they should be filled <br>with pride <br>And when the world’s against me <br>is when I really come alive <br>And every day that Satan tempts me <br>I try to take it in my stride <br>You know that I’ve got whisky <br>with white lies <br>and smoke in my lungs <br>I think life has got to the point <br>I know without it’s no fun <br>I need to get in the right mind <br>and clear myself up <br>Instead I look in the mirror <br>questioning what I’ve become <br>Guess it’s a stereotypical day <br>for someone like me <br>Without a nine to five job <br>or a uni degree <br>To be caught up <br>in the trappings of the industry <br>Show me the locked doors <br>I’ll find another use for the key <br>and you’ll see <br>I’m well aware of certain things <br>that can destroy a man like me <br>But with that said give me <br>one more <br>I am another one <br>to take the sting away <br>I am happy on my own so here <br>I’ll stay <br>Save your loving arms for a <br>rainy day <br>And I’ll find comfort in my <br>pain eraser <br>I used to think that nothing <br>could be better than touring <br>the world <br>with my songs <br>I chased the picture perfect life <br>I think they painted it wrong <br>I think that money <br>is the route of all evil <br>and fame is hell <br>Relationships and hearts you fix <br>they break as well <br>And ain’t nobody <br>want to see you down <br>in the dumps <br>Because you’re living your dream <br>and this should be fun <br>Please know <br>that I’m not trying to preach <br>like I’m reverend run <br>I beg you don’t be disappointed <br>with the man I’ve become <br>Conversations with my father <br>on the A14 <br>Age 12 telling me <br>I’ve gotta chase those dreams <br>Now I’m playing <br>for the people dad <br>and they know me <br>With my beaten small guitar <br>wearing the same old jeans <br>Wembley stadium crowds <br>two hundred and forty thou <br>I may have grown up <br>but I hope that Damian’s proud <br>And to the next generation <br>inspiration’s allowed <br>The world may be filled with hate <br>but keep erasing it now somehow <br>I’m well aware of certain things <br>that will befall a man like me <br>But with that said give me <br>one more <br>I am another one <br>to take the sting away <br>Oh I am happy on my own <br>so here I’ll stay <br>Well save your loving arms <br>for a rainy day <br>And I’ll find comfort in my <br>pain eraser <br>And I’ll find comfort in my <br>pain eraser <br>And I’ll find comfort in my <br>pain eraser <br>Welcome to the new show <br>I guess you know I’ve been away <br>Where I'm heading who knows <br>My heart will stay the same <br>Welcome to the new show <br>I guess you know I’ve been away <br>Where I'm heading who knows <br>My pain eraser <br>And I’ll find comfort <br>in my pain eraser <br>And I’ll find comfort <br>in my pain eraser <br>And I’ll find comfort <br>in my pain eraser <br>And I’ll find comfort <br>in my pain eraser <br>]]></content><category term="Ed Sheeran" label="Ed Sheeran"/><category term="Eraser" label="Eraser"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Os_Almondegas/Piquete_Do_Caveira/</id><title>Os_Almondegas - Piquete Do Caveira - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:01:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:01:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Os_Almondegas/Piquete_Do_Caveira/" title="Os_Almondegas - Piquete Do Caveira - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[LANcAS ERGUIDAS ESPADAS NO AR <br>eO PIQUETE DO CAVEIRA que CHEGOU PRA ESPANTAR <br>PRA ESPALHAR OS INIMIGOS <br>PRA MANDAR E DESMANDAR <br><br>e PONTA DE FACA e RELHO NA MaO <br>CAVALHADA EM DISPARADA <br>VEM DEIXANDO PELO CHaO <br>A MARCA DO PIQUETE <br>DO CAVEIRA O VALENTaO <br><br>VEM CHEGANDO VEM CHEGANDO <br>VEM CHEGANDO CAVEIRA <br>VEM CHEGANDO VEM CHEGANDO <br>VEM CHEGANDO CAVEIRA <br>CAVALO NEGRO A ESCURIDAO <br>O LENcO PRETO e ASSOMBRAcaO <br>BOTANDO GENTE PRA CORRER]]></content><category term="Os Almondegas" label="Os Almondegas"/><category term="Piquete Do Caveira" label="Piquete Do Caveira"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Os_Almondegas/Feiticeira/</id><title>Os_Almondegas - Feiticeira - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:01:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:01:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Os_Almondegas/Feiticeira/" title="Os_Almondegas - Feiticeira - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Uma negra mulher <br>Com dois olhos de Satanas <br>Cobras, macas, temporais <br>Infernizou minha paz <br><br>Esta linda mulher <br>Poucos gestos e mil aneis <br>Cheiro de flor, rouca voz <br>Enfeiticou me a seus pes <br><br>Unhas e dentes de amor <br>Abracadabra, felina feiticeira <br>Como te posso parar <br>Mata me logo, perversa feiticeira <br>Como e terrivel morrer de prazer <br><br>Esta louca mulher <br>Com seus sonhos de fada ma <br>Soube sonhar o que eu sei <br>E o que ninguem sabera <br><br>Esta ave mulher <br>Com seus cantos de sabia <br>Soube cantar o que eu sei <br>E o que eu nao sei se sera <br><br>Louco e esoterico amor <br>Abracabala, felina feiticeira <br>Quanto te posso parar <br>Mata me aos poucos, perversa feiticeira <br>Como e incrivel morrer de prazer <br><br>Luminosa mulher <br>Ja nao quero me controlar <br>Teu fogo azul, seducao <br>Queimou o meu coracao]]></content><category term="Os Almondegas" label="Os Almondegas"/><category term="Feiticeira" label="Feiticeira"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Os_Almondegas/Alhos_Com_Bugalhos/</id><title>Os_Almondegas - Alhos Com Bugalhos - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:01:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:01:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Os_Almondegas/Alhos_Com_Bugalhos/" title="Os_Almondegas - Alhos Com Bugalhos - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Quantos anos tem a sua cara <br>Nao confunda alhos com bugalho <br><br>O sol nasce quente, as seis da manha <br>No meio do dia, ele queima que doi <br>Ele queima que doi <br><br>Quantos olhos tem a sua cara <br>Quanto mais me queimo, mais me amarro <br><br>O amor nasce quente, acende a manha <br>Nomeio do quarto, ele queima que doi <br>Ele queima que doi <br><br>Quantas pregas tem a sua saia <br>Nao confunda alhos com bugalhos]]></content><category term="Os Almondegas" label="Os Almondegas"/><category term="Alhos Com Bugalhos" label="Alhos Com Bugalhos"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Os_Almondegas/Futurismo/</id><title>Os_Almondegas - Futurismo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:01:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:01:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Os_Almondegas/Futurismo/" title="Os_Almondegas - Futurismo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Voar e com os astros, Zodiaco <br>Com buzios maos e cartas, horoscopo <br>E eu, navegador aquariano <br>Deste ceu de previsoes <br>Dias cheios de supersticoes <br>Um mar de desilusoes e ambicoes <br>Zumbido na cabeca <br>A voz de um futuro fatal <br>Largue minhas maos <br>Meiga cigana com olhos de jaguar <br>Largue minhas maos <br>De seus felinos <br>Saberes nao farei a paz <br>Dias cheios de supersticoes <br>Um mar de desilusoes e ambicoes <br>Zumbido na cabeca <br>A voz de um futuro fatal <br>Largue minhas maos <br>Meiga cigana com olhos de jaguar <br>Largue minhas maos <br>De seus felinos <br>Saberes nao farei a paz]]></content><category term="Os Almondegas" label="Os Almondegas"/><category term="Futurismo" label="Futurismo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Os_Almondegas/Gaucho_Do_Passo_Fundo/</id><title>Os_Almondegas - Gaucho Do Passo Fundo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:01:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:01:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Os_Almondegas/Gaucho_Do_Passo_Fundo/" title="Os_Almondegas - Gaucho Do Passo Fundo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Me perguntaram se eu sou gaucho <br>Esta na cara, repare o meu jeito <br>Eu sou gaucho la de Passo Fundo <br>E trato todo mundo, com muito respeito <br>Mas se alguem me pisar no pala <br>Meu revolver fala <br>E o bochincho ta feito <br><br>Me perguntaram qual era a razao <br>De eu ter orgulho em ser passofundense <br>Eu respondi sou da terra do trigo <br>Tenho um povo amigo, que quando luta vence <br>e um pedaco do Rio Grande amado <br>Orgulha o Estado <br>E o povo Riograndense <br><br>Nao sou nervoso nem carrego medo <br>Eu me criei sem conhecer remedio <br>Eu meto o peito em qualquer fandango <br>Mas quando eu me zango, ate derrubo o predio <br>Eu sou gaucho e se me agride eu fundo <br>Sou de Passo Fundo <br>Do planalto medio <br><br>Ja respondi a pergunta, seu moco <br>Me da licenca, vou encilhar o cavalo <br>Brasil afora atravessei os Estado <br>Troteando apressado, eu fui tirando talo <br>Pra ver as prenda mais lindas do mundo <br>Chego em passo fundo, no cantar do galo]]></content><category term="Os Almondegas" label="Os Almondegas"/><category term="Gaucho Do Passo Fundo" label="Gaucho Do Passo Fundo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Os_Almondegas/No_Meu_Coracao/</id><title>Os_Almondegas - No Meu Coracao - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:01:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:01:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Os_Almondegas/No_Meu_Coracao/" title="Os_Almondegas - No Meu Coracao - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Voar e com as borboletas <br>Que sabem como bem voar <br>E cada voo colorido <br>Borboleta setas no meu coracao <br><br>Beijar e com os beija flores <br>Que sabem como bem beijar <br>E cada beijo colorido <br>Beija flora flores no meu coracao <br><br>Cantar e com os passarinhos <br>Que sabem como bem cantar <br>E cada canto colorido <br>Passarinha ninhos no meu coracao]]></content><category term="Os Almondegas" label="Os Almondegas"/><category term="No Meu Coracao" label="No Meu Coracao"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Os_Almondegas/Em_Palpos_De_Aranha/</id><title>Os_Almondegas - Em Palpos De Aranha - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:01:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:01:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Os_Almondegas/Em_Palpos_De_Aranha/" title="Os_Almondegas - Em Palpos De Aranha - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Este apartamento me sufoca <br>As paredes me calam a voz <br>A lingua ao lado, eu sei <br>Reclama se a minha guitarra <br>Espanta as moscas do ar <br>Nao e facil respirar <br>Apesar dos dois pulmoes que eu tenho <br>Eu ja nao posso mais cantar o rock que fiz <br>No ultimo dia tres de primavera <br>Sob este ceu suburbano, so me resta chorar <br>Realmente estou em palpos de aranha <br>Moco, venha me ajudar <br>Seja voce o Super Homem <br>Kit Carson ou ate mesmo Bufalo Bill <br>Me tire do aperto, alivie o cerco <br>Deixe o ar entrar <br>Mesmo que o meu rock sirva so pra espantar]]></content><category term="Os Almondegas" label="Os Almondegas"/><category term="Em Palpos De Aranha" label="Em Palpos De Aranha"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Flo_Morrissey/Look_At_What_The_Light_Did_Now/</id><title>Flo_Morrissey - Look At What The Light Did Now - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:02:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:02:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Flo_Morrissey/Look_At_What_The_Light_Did_Now/" title="Flo_Morrissey - Look At What The Light Did Now - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hear it like a pounce upon a peak, oh <br>Look at what the light did now <br>Bear it like a bounce upon the beak, oh <br><br>Look at what the light did now <br>Land and water and bird or beast, oh <br>Look at what the light did now <br>Shiny little band or golden fleece, oh <br>Look at what the light did now <br><br>Look at what the light did now <br><br>In my will I went 'till it's wasted <br>Look at what the light did now <br>Taste the taste I taste 'till it's tasted <br>Look at what the light did now <br><br>Bought it like a boast that burly beaming <br>Look at what the light did now <br>Got it like a ghost that girly gleaming <br>Look at what the light did now <br><br>Like a dead tree that's dry and leaving <br>Look at what the light did now <br>Play it on me with grief and grieving <br>Look at what the light did now <br>I would finally fall to pieces <br>Look at what the light did now <br>We'll meet soon as newphew's nieces <br>Look at what the light did now]]></content><category term="Flo Morrissey" label="Flo Morrissey"/><category term="Look At What The Light Did Now" label="Look At What The Light Did Now"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이지영_빅마마/어떻게_된거야/</id><title>이지영_빅마마 - 어떻게 된거야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:02:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:02:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80%EC%98%81_%EB%B9%85%EB%A7%88%EB%A7%88/%EC%96%B4%EB%96%BB%EA%B2%8C_%EB%90%9C%EA%B1%B0%EC%95%BC/" title="이지영_빅마마 - 어떻게 된거야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어떻게 된 거야 <br>어디부터 잘못된 거야 <br>너에게 묻고 싶지만 <br>하지만 난 이제 <br>네게서 멀어진 사람 <br>그러면 안 된다는 걸 알아 <br>하지만 난 볼 수 있어 <br>너의 차가운 가면 <br>누구보다 여린 너의 <br>너의 진짜 모습 <br>나만이 볼 수 있어 <br>아름다운 너의 모습 <br>널 안을 수만 있다면 <br>나는 들을 수 있어 <br>아름다운 너의 노래 <br>아직 그대로인데 <br>사람들은 쉽게 말하곤 하지 <br>그렇게 변해간다고 <br>하지만 널 첨 만났던 그때 <br>그 느낌을 믿어 <br>나만이 볼 수 있어 <br>아름다운 너의 모습 <br>널 안을 수만 있다면 <br>나는 들을 수 있어 <br>아름다운 너의 노래 <br>아직 그대로인데 <br>아무리 외쳐도 들리지 않는 <br>너 없는 공간에 숨 쉬고 있는 <br>내가 원망스러워 <br>고독과 외로움 없는 곳에서 <br>너만은 아프지 않길 <br>오늘도 기도해 <br>나만이 볼 수 있어 <br>아름다운 너의 모습 <br>널 안을 수만 있다면 <br>나는 들을 수 있어 <br>아름다운 너의 노래 <br>아직 그대로인데 <br>그곳에서 널 데려올 텐데 <br>아직 그대로인데 <br>]]></content><category term="이지영 (빅마마)" label="이지영 (빅마마)"/><category term="어떻게 된거야" label="어떻게 된거야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하엘비/친구의_주님/</id><title>하엘비 - 친구의 주님 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:03:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:03:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%97%98%EB%B9%84/%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC%EC%9D%98_%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98/" title="하엘비 - 친구의 주님 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너를 사랑하는 마음에 <br>주님을 만났었네 <br>혼자라는 생각 속에서 <br>힘들고 지쳐 쓰러질 때 <br>너를 사랑하는 주님을 <br>한 번 만나고 싶어 <br>그 분의 사랑을 느끼며 <br>나의 마음 변하고 싶어 <br>진정으로 주님께 <br>눈물로 고백할 때 <br>너의 마음 잡아주셨어 <br>한번만 그분의 사랑을 <br>나에게 보여줄 순 없겠니 <br>나의 생활 속에 용기를 <br>주시는 주님의 사랑을 <br>친구의 주님을 만났네 <br>눈물을 감출 순 없었네 <br>언제나 내 맘 속에 <br>함께 계셨네 <br>사랑하는 주님 <br>진정으로 주님께 <br>눈물로 고백할 때 <br>너의 마음 잡아주셔서 <br>한번만 그분의 사랑을 <br>나에게 보여줄 순 없겠니 <br>나의 생활 속에 용기를 <br>주시는 주님의 사랑을 <br>친구의 주님을 만났네 <br>눈물을 감출 순 없었네 <br>언제나 내 맘 속에 <br>함께 계셨네 <br>사랑하는 주님 <br>]]></content><category term="하엘비" label="하엘비"/><category term="친구의 주님" label="친구의 주님"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Samuli_Putro/Matkamuistot/</id><title>Samuli_Putro - Matkamuistot - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:03:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:03:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Samuli_Putro/Matkamuistot/" title="Samuli_Putro - Matkamuistot - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Se nero joka luulee <br>Etta onnellinen mies on <br>Onnellinen aina <br>On tavattoman tyhma <br>Elama on sarja <br>Surujenkin sarja <br>Ja joka sita pelkaa <br>Jaa hyllylle ja polyyntyy <br>Niin kuin matkamuistot <br>Niin kuin matkamuistot <br>Jaa hyllylle ja polyyntyy <br>Niin kuin matkamuistot <br>Se valpas joka loytaa <br>Arvettoman naisen <br>On loytanyt koneen <br>Ja mita silla tekee <br>Sen voi laittaa paalle <br>Ja katsoa sen tekevan <br>Naiselliset jutut <br>Ja sit kun siihen kyllastyy <br>Sen voi sulkee <br>Sen voi sulkea <br>Se viisas joka keksii <br>Rakkaudelle kaavan <br>On huomattavan rikas <br>Ja turhautunut pian <br>Elama on sarja <br>Yllatysten sarja <br>Se joka sita pelkaa <br>Jaa sisalle ja polyyntyy <br>Niin kuin matkamuistot <br>Niin kuin matkamuistot <br>Jaa sisalle ja polyyntyy <br>Niin kuin matkamuistot <br>Sun taipumaton luonne <br>On voinut olla este <br>Menestyksen tiella <br>On pyrkyreiden juhlat <br>Sun jaarapainen luonne <br>On voinut olla riesa <br>Mutta se on lahja <br>Sita ei voi palauttaa <br>Se on kuin matkamuistot <br>Se viisas joka keksii <br>Rakkaudelle kaavan <br>On huomattavan rikas <br>Ja turhautunut pian <br>Elama on sarja <br>Yllatysten sarja <br>Se joka sita pelkaa <br>Jaa sisalle ja polyyntyy <br>Niin kuin matkamuistot <br>Niin kuin matkamuistot <br>Jaa sisalle ja polyyntyy <br>Niin kuin matkamuistot <br>Niin kuin matkamuistot <br>Jaa sisalle ja polyyntyy <br>Niin kuin matkamuistot]]></content><category term="Samuli Putro" label="Samuli Putro"/><category term="Matkamuistot" label="Matkamuistot"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/희원/한숨만/</id><title>희원 - 한숨만 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:03:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:03:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9D%AC%EC%9B%90/%ED%95%9C%EC%88%A8%EB%A7%8C/" title="희원 - 한숨만 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그저 옆에만 있어줘 <br>너무 많은 걸 바란 거니 <br>아무 기대 안 할게 <br>모두 잃을 것 같아 <br>두려워 나 약속해 <br>부담주지 않을 게 <br>널 놓치고 난 뒤에 <br>이제야 알게 된 거야 <br>생각보다 많이 사랑했어 <br>넌 이제까지 만나온 <br>다른 사람들과는 달라 <br>오 난 이제는 말할게 <br>한숨만 커다랗게 나왔어 <br>너를 보낸 기억에 <br>이젠 네가 없인 <br>안 된단 걸 알아 <br>괜찮아 그냥 <br>지금처럼만 곁에 있어 <br>그 이상은 바라지 않아 <br>왜 지금은 안되니 <br>다른 여자가 생긴 거니 <br>아무 기대 안 할게 <br>모두 잃을 것 같아 <br>두려워 나 약속해 <br>부담주지 않을 게 <br>널 놓치고 난 뒤에 <br>이제야 알게 된 거야 <br>생각보다 많이 사랑했어 <br>넌 이제까지 만나온 <br>다른 사람들과는 달라 <br>오 난 이제는 말할게 <br>한숨만 커다랗게 나왔어 <br>너를 보낸 기억에 <br>이젠 네가 없인 <br>안 된단 걸 알아 <br>괜찮아 그냥 <br>지금처럼만 곁에 있어 <br>그 이상은 바라지 않아 <br>]]></content><category term="희원" label="희원"/><category term="한숨만" label="한숨만"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레베카/안아줄_테니까/</id><title>레베카 - 안아줄 테니까 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:03:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:03:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EB%B2%A0%EC%B9%B4/%EC%95%88%EC%95%84%EC%A4%84_%ED%85%8C%EB%8B%88%EA%B9%8C/" title="레베카 - 안아줄 테니까 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 널 잊어도 되겠니 <br>아니 나 널 잃어 버려도 <br>괜찮은 거니 <br>있잖아 나는 조금도 널 <br>놓을 수 없어 <br>근데 아무렇지 않게 <br>넌 떠나간다 <br>날 놓치마 후회할거잖아 <br>분명 너도 아파 할거면서 <br>왜 그렇게 모질게 그래 <br>아무리 밀어내도 <br>나는 여기 있을 테니까 <br>언제라도 나를 찾아와 <br>마치 아무일 없었던 듯이 <br>어제 만나고 또 만난 듯이 <br>아무렇지 않게 <br>너를 바라보며 <br>안아줄 테니까 <br>너 화내는 그 모습이 <br>하나도 <br>어울리지 않아서 웃었어 <br>언제나 웃으면서 하던 <br>장난들까지 생각나 그것 봐 <br>너도 웃잖아 <br>그래 참 유치하잖아 <br>너도 어색하잖아 그러니까 <br>그런 말 하지마 <br>아무리 밀어내도 <br>나는 여기 있을 테니까 <br>언제라도 나를 찾아와 <br>마치 아무일 없었던 듯이 <br>어제 만나고 또 만난 듯이 <br>아무렇지 않게 <br>너를 바라보며 <br>안아줄 테니까 <br>]]></content><category term="레베카" label="레베카"/><category term="안아줄 테니까" label="안아줄 테니까"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Doing_Good/</id><title>Milky_Chance - Doing Good - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:04:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:04:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Milky_Chance/Doing_Good/" title="Milky_Chance - Doing Good - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Calling you lovable <br>How are you feeling now <br>Making it all above <br>Falling for you somehow <br><br>I can't refuse you walking along the lonely way <br>Wish I could leave you everytime but all you say <br><br>'Cause I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing so good <br><br>Calling you lovable <br>How are you feeling now <br>Making it all above <br>Falling for you somehow <br><br>I can't refuse you walking along the lonely way <br>Wish I could leave you everytime but all you say <br><br>'Cause I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing, I'm doing so good <br><br>Calling you lovable <br>How are you feeling now <br>Making it all above <br>Falling for you somehow <br><br>I can't refuse you walking along the lonely way <br>Wish I could leave you everytime but all you say <br><br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good <br>I'm doing so good]]></content><category term="Milky Chance" label="Milky Chance"/><category term="Doing Good" label="Doing Good"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Judith_Durham/I_Am_Australian_Single_Ver_Feat_Russell_Hitchcock__Mandawuy_Yunupingu/</id><title>Judith_Durham - I Am Australian (Single Ver.) (Feat. Russell Hitchcock &amp; Mandawuy Yunupingu) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:05:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:05:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Judith_Durham/I_Am_Australian_Single_Ver_Feat_Russell_Hitchcock__Mandawuy_Yunupingu/" title="Judith_Durham - I Am Australian (Single Ver.) (Feat. Russell Hitchcock &amp; Mandawuy Yunupingu) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I came upon the prison ship <br>Bound down by iron chains <br>I fought the land, endured the lash <br>And waited for the rains <br>I'm a settler, I'm a farmer's wife <br>On a dry and barren run <br>A convict then a free man <br>I became Australian <br><br>I'm the daughter of a digger <br>Who sought the mother lode <br>The girl became a woman <br>on the long and dusty road <br>I'm a child of the depression <br>I saw the good times come <br>I'm a bushy I'm a battler <br>I am Australian <br><br>We are one <br>But we are many <br>And from all the lands on earth we come <br>We'll share a dream <br>And sing with one voice <br>I am, you are, we are Australian <br><br>I'm a teller of stories <br>I'm a singer of songs <br>I am Albert Namatjira <br>And I paint the ghostly gums <br>I'm Clancy on his horse <br>I'm Ned Kelly on the run <br>I'm the one who waltzed Matilda <br>I am Australian <br><br>I'm the hot wind from the desert <br>I'm the black soil of the plains <br>I'm the mountains and the valleys <br>I'm the drought and flooding rains <br>I am the rock, I am the sky <br>The rivers when they run <br>The spirit of this great land <br>I am Australian <br><br>We are one <br>But we are many <br>And from all the lands on earth we come <br>We'll share a dream <br>And sing with one voice <br>I am, you are, we are Australian <br><br>I came from the dreaming <br>From the dusty red soil plains <br>I am the ancient heart <br>The keeper of the flame <br>I stood upon the rocky shores <br>I watched the tall ships come <br>For forty thousand years I've been <br>The first Australian <br><br>We are one but we are many <br>And from all the lands on earth we come <br>We'll share a dream <br>And sing with one voice <br>I am, you are, we are Australian <br><br>We are one but we are many <br>And from all the lands on earth we come <br>We'll share a dream <br>And sing with one voice <br>I am, you are, we are Australian <br><br>I am, you are, we are Australian]]></content><category term="Judith Durham" label="Judith Durham"/><category term="I Am Australian (Single Ver.) (Feat. Russell Hitchcock &amp; Mandawuy Yunupingu)" label="I Am Australian (Single Ver.) (Feat. Russell Hitchcock &amp; Mandawuy Yunupingu)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비하트_BHEART/필요없어/</id><title>비하트_BHEART - 필요없어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:05:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:05:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%95%98%ED%8A%B8_BHEART/%ED%95%84%EC%9A%94%EC%97%86%EC%96%B4/" title="비하트_BHEART - 필요없어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[화려한 불빛 아래 서있는 <br>너와 나 이제는 니가 <br>손을 놓으려 해 <br>그저 쳐다보는 나 <br>눈빛도 안 주는 너 Yeah <br>이제 모든 건 끝난 거 같아 <br>믿기 힘들 정도로 말이야 <br>끝이 없다 생각했었던 <br>내가 너무 바보 같아 하 <br>내 손을 잡고 아무 생각 마 <br>두려울 때 난 네가 생각나 <br>분명 힘들어하고 <br>후회가 남아 Oh Babe <br>I Gave You Everything <br>But 넌 더 원하나 봐 <br>I Got No Everything <br>난 아직 널 잘 몰라 <br>차가운 인사말로 안녕 <br>시간을 되돌릴 수만 있다면 <br>I Gave You Everything <br>but 넌 더 원하나 봐 <br>I Got No Eveything <br>난 아직 널 잘 몰라 <br>아무것도 필요 없어 <br>너만 있으면 필요 없어 <br>매일같이 널 또 울려 <br>마치 마지막인 것처럼 <br>늘 다그치던 나였지만 <br>오늘은 못 참아 걸 <br>사랑에 좋은 이별 <br>따위 없다면서 <br>날 밀어내는 널 보는 <br>내 맘은 어떻겠어 <br>좋았었던 기억이 <br>안 나는지 <br>그런데 왜 넌 <br>아파하고만 있는지 <br>이미 끝난 듯이 <br>우리 사이 끝이 없는 <br>로코 드라마 <br>감정이 다 무너져도 <br>날 보면 웃게 되잖아 <br>내 손을 잡고 아무 생각 마 <br>두려울 때 난 네가 생각나 <br>분명 힘들어하고 <br>후회가 남아 Oh Babe <br>I Gave You Everything <br>But 넌 더 원하나 봐 <br>I Got No Everything <br>난 아직 널 잘 몰라 <br>차가운 인사말로 안녕 <br>시간을 되돌릴 수만 있다면 <br>I Gave You Everything <br>but 넌 더 원하나 봐 <br>I Got No Eveything <br>난 아직 널 잘 몰라 <br>아무것도 필요 없어 <br>너만 있으면 필요 없어 <br>내 방안에 모든 <br>것이 멈춘듯해 <br>내 중심은 온통 <br>너였었는데 Girl <br>영원하자고 믿으라고 <br>운명이라 넌 말했었지 <br>이제 그만하자는 널 <br>끝내기엔 아직 <br>사랑하는데 <br>I Gave You Everything <br>But 넌 더 원하나 봐 <br>I Got No Everything <br>난 아직 널 잘 몰라 <br>차가운 인사말로 안녕 <br>시간을 되돌릴 수만 있다면 <br>I Gave You Everything <br>but 넌 더 원하나 봐 <br>I Got No Eveything <br>난 아직 널 잘 몰라 <br>아무것도 필요 없어 <br>너만 있으면 필요 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="비하트 (B.HEART)" label="비하트 (B.HEART)"/><category term="필요없어" label="필요없어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mighty_Oaks/Be_With_You_Always/</id><title>Mighty_Oaks - Be With You Always - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:05:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:05:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mighty_Oaks/Be_With_You_Always/" title="Mighty_Oaks - Be With You Always - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I am standing by your side <br>and you know this is the final time <br>as you every thing will change <br>i will never forget this day <br><br>i see so much in my life <br>brightest dawn and darkest night <br>every moment lead me to this place <br><br>and i never be the same <br>no i'll never be the same again <br><br>give me that love <br>give me that soul <br>give me your fire and i'll give you my own <br>all of my life <br>i never let go <br>and i'll be with you always <br><br>burst the silence than shock <br>all we ready or all we night <br>i remeber how we talk <br>like the world we were something we forgot <br><br>be my home an nothing safe <br>we'll get lost along the way <br>there will be peace after the hurricane <br><br>and we will never be the same <br>no we'll never be the same again <br><br>give me that love <br>give me that soul <br>give me your fire and i'll give you my own <br>all of my life <br>i never let go <br>and i'll be with you always <br><br>for the rest of my days <br>i won't let you down <br>but your were on my shoulders <br>i'll be with you always <br>i won't let you down <br>and i won't let go <br><br>give me that love <br>give me that soul <br>give me your fire and i'll give you my own <br>all my life <br>i of never let go <br>and i'll be with you always]]></content><category term="Mighty Oaks" label="Mighty Oaks"/><category term="Be With You Always" label="Be With You Always"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박경_블락비/잔상_Feat_윤현상/</id><title>박경_블락비 - 잔상 (Feat. 윤현상) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:05:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:05:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EA%B2%BD_%EB%B8%94%EB%9D%BD%EB%B9%84/%EC%9E%94%EC%83%81_Feat_%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%84%EC%83%81/" title="박경_블락비 - 잔상 (Feat. 윤현상) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈을 감아서 <br>어둠을 만들고 <br>반짝였던 기억들을 <br>띄워놓아요 <br>긴 시간이 지나 <br>잔상으로 변해가도 <br>지워지진 않을 거예요 <br>사랑해 그리고 미안해 <br>점차 서로의 삶에 <br>녹아들자 말했던 <br>처음부터 끝까지 <br>넌 날 깨닫게 하네 <br>감정의 일교차가 심해지고 <br>익숙함은 감기처럼 찾아와 <br>세상 행복했던 날 <br>순간 헷갈리게 하더니 <br>이제야 날 아프게 하나 봐 <br>너무나 많이 후회하고 있어 <br>후회하고 있어 <br>특별했던 너와 나 <br>날 귀찮게 하던 너가 <br>무척이나 보고 싶은 날이야 <br>눈을 감아서 <br>어둠을 만들고 <br>반짝였던 기억들을 <br>띄워놓아요 <br>긴 시간이 지나 <br>잔상으로 변해가도 <br>지워지진 않을 거예요 <br>입버릇처럼 했던 말 <br>내 우선순위는 일이라고 <br>요즘 힘든 시기라고 <br>그렇게 너를 미루고 <br>기다림이 당연해진 널 <br>당연히 여겨 사지 못할 <br>너의 감정을 <br>난 값싸게 여겨 <br>버거운 사랑을 원했으면서 <br>막상 받으니 버거워했고 <br>감당하지 못 했던 난 <br>후회하고 있어 <br>후회하고 있어 <br>잔상이 되긴커녕 <br>더 또렷해지고 있어 <br>후회하고 있어 <br>후회하고 있어 <br>잔상이 되긴커녕 <br>더 선명해지고 있어 <br>후회하고 있어 <br>후회하고 있어 <br>널 잊긴커녕 <br>더 사랑하고 있어 <br>눈을 감아서 <br>어둠을 만들고 <br>반짝였던 기억들을 <br>띄워놓아요 <br>긴 시간이 지나 <br>잔상으로 변해가도 <br>지워지진 않을 거예요 <br>]]></content><category term="박경 (블락비)" label="박경 (블락비)"/><category term="잔상 (Feat. 윤현상)" label="잔상 (Feat. 윤현상)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박경_블락비/자격지심_Feat_은하_Of_여자친구/</id><title>박경_블락비 - 자격지심 (Feat. 은하 Of 여자친구) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:05:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:05:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EA%B2%BD_%EB%B8%94%EB%9D%BD%EB%B9%84/%EC%9E%90%EA%B2%A9%EC%A7%80%EC%8B%AC_Feat_%EC%9D%80%ED%95%98_Of_%EC%97%AC%EC%9E%90%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC/" title="박경_블락비 - 자격지심 (Feat. 은하 Of 여자친구) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You 도대체 문제가 <br>뭐야 말 좀 해봐 <br>Hey You 질투하는 거야 <br>자격지심인 거야 boy <br>몇 번이나 말했잖아 <br>나에겐 한 사람밖에 없다고 <br>귀여워 너답지 않은 너가 <br><br>빠라바빠빠 <br>빠라바빠빠빠 <br>빠라바빠빠 <br>넌 모를 거야 내 맘을 <br><br>너 지금 어딜 보는 건지 <br>지나가는 쟤 쳐다봤지 <br>쇼윈도를 보는 척하면서 <br>눈은 왜 그리 돌아가니 <br>그래 나보다 키 크고 <br>어깨도 넓은 거 나도 보이는데 <br>너가 그래버리면 더 <br>비참해지잖아 <br><br>왜 그리 자신 없어 <br>어딜 보긴 뭘 어딜 봐 <br>어느 누구와도 너를 비교한 적 없어 <br>소심하게 굴지 마 <br>어제 카페 그 알바생 <br>앞에서 왜 그리 웃는데 <br>내가 이상한 건지 너가 이상한 건지 <br>몰라 궁금해 머릿속이 <br><br>You 도대체 문제가 <br>뭐야 말 좀 해봐 <br>Hey You 질투하는 거야 <br>자격지심인 거야 boy <br>몇 번이나 말했잖아 <br>나에겐 한 사람밖에 없다고 <br>귀여워 너답지 않은 너가 <br><br>빠라바빠빠 <br>빠라바빠빠빠 <br>빠라바빠빠 <br>넌 모를 거야 내 맘을 <br><br>하나만 물어볼게 차 있단 <br>그 오빠 얘긴 왜 자꾸 해 <br>뚜벅이가 뭐 어때서 어디든 가줄게 <br>너 친구들 남자 친구 놈들 <br>딱 들어보니 가식덩어리들 <br>I told ya 남잔 늑대 순하디 <br>순한 너에겐 위험해 yo <br>숨어 있어 내 울타리 안에 <br>우리 사진으로 메신져 프사해 <br><br>왜 그리 자신 없어 <br>아무것도 필요 없어 <br>내겐 누구보다 큰 너 <br>나도 알고 있어 <br>남자는 다 똑같애 <br><br>그걸 아는 사람이 그래 <br>밀고 당길 땐 벌써 지났는데 <br>내가 이상한 건지 너가 이상한 건지 <br>몰라 궁금해 머릿속이 <br><br>You 도대체 문제가 <br>뭐야 말 좀 해봐 <br>Hey You 질투하는 거야 <br>자격지심인 거야 boy <br>몇 번이나 말했잖아 <br>나에겐 한 사람밖에 없다고 <br>귀여워 너답지 않은 너가 <br><br>빠라바빠빠 <br>빠라바빠빠빠 <br>빠라바빠빠 <br>넌 모를 거야 내 맘을 <br><br>빠라바빠빠 <br>빠라바빠빠빠 <br>빠라바빠빠 <br>넌 모를 거야 내 맘을 <br><br>혹시나 해서 말인데 <br>오해할까 걱정인데 <br>이거 절대 자격지심 아냐 아냐 <br><br>혹시나 해서 말인데 <br>난 아무 상관없는데 <br>그러는 거 자격지심 맞아 맞아]]></content><category term="박경 (블락비)" label="박경 (블락비)"/><category term="자격지심 (Feat. 은하 Of 여자친구)" label="자격지심 (Feat. 은하 Of 여자친구)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박경_블락비/오글오글/</id><title>박경_블락비 - 오글오글 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:05:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:05:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EA%B2%BD_%EB%B8%94%EB%9D%BD%EB%B9%84/%EC%98%A4%EA%B8%80%EC%98%A4%EA%B8%80/" title="박경_블락비 - 오글오글 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I got you I got you you you <br>Umm OK <br>I got you and i love you <br>I got you and i love you <br>I got you <br>Ay go back to 22 <br>I wanna tell ya <br><br>두 볼에 입 맞추고 또 <br> 두 손을 꼭 잡죠 <br>이런 오글거림 없었죠 <br>Nobody knows it <br>문자도 예쁘게 쓰고 <br>기념일을 기다리죠 <br>하늘을 나는 기분 <br>Fly ah ah ah ah yeah <br><br>Baby girl you make <br>me fall in love <br>조금은 부끄럽긴 <br>하지만 이젠 말할래 <br>더 이상은 못 참아 <br>I can make it slowly <br><br>이 노래를 듣고 있니 <br>너 하나를 위해 내는 목소리 <br>가만히만 있어도 좋아 <br>나를 보고만 있다면 <br><br>야 너 진짜 씹덕 터져 <br>보고만 있어도 너무 귀여워 <br>I’ll be your big fan <br>널 담을 때만큼은 <br>내 눈은 무엇보다 좋은 캠 <br><br>싸인해줘 내 볼에 너의 <br>빨간 입술이 볼펜 <br>알아 알아 오글거리는 거 <br>그래도 좋으니까 할래 <br>I’m in love with you girl <br><br>두 볼에 입 맞추고 또 <br>두 손을 꼭 잡죠 <br>이런 오글거림 없었죠 <br>Nobody knows it <br>문자도 예쁘게 쓰고 <br>기념일을 기다리죠 <br>하늘을 나는 기분 <br>Fly ah ah ah ah yeah <br><br>내가 일만 한다고 <br>밤에 일찍 자러 간다고 <br>답장 빨리 안 한다고 <br>너 또 괜히 알면서도 그래 <br><br>But It's OK! Are you OK? <br>비위 맞춰줄 수 있어 <br>낮은 목소리가 좋다면 <br>낮춰줄 수 있어 Yeah <br><br>명동에서 스티커 사진 찍고 <br>잠깐 쉬고 밥 먹을 때도 찍고 <br>그 다음 집에 와선 비트윈에 <br>또 추억 하나를 추가 시키고 <br><br>너와 함께라면 스킨십이 <br>아니더라도 뭐든 좋아 <br>I don't know what <br>should I do for you <br>One more time baby <br><br>두 볼에 입 맞추고 <br>또 두 손을 꼭 잡죠 <br>이런 오글거림 없었죠 <br>Nobody knows it <br>문자도 예쁘게 쓰고 <br>기념일을 기다리죠 <br>하늘을 나는 기분 <br>Fly ah ah ah ah yeah <br><br>I got you and I love you <br>I got you and I love you <br>I got you and I love you <br>영원히 둘이서 <br><br>I got you and I love you <br>I got you and I love you <br>I got you and I love you <br>영원히 둘이서]]></content><category term="박경 (블락비)" label="박경 (블락비)"/><category term="오글오글" label="오글오글"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박경_블락비/너_앞에서_나는_Feat_브라더수/</id><title>박경_블락비 - 너 앞에서 나는 (Feat. 브라더수) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:05:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:05:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EA%B2%BD_%EB%B8%94%EB%9D%BD%EB%B9%84/%EB%84%88_%EC%95%9E%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C_%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_Feat_%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EB%8D%94%EC%88%98/" title="박경_블락비 - 너 앞에서 나는 (Feat. 브라더수) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너 앞에서 나는 (Feat. 브라더수) <br><br>너 앞에서 나는 <br>사춘기인 것처럼 <br>너 앞에서 나는 <br>새벽 감성처럼 <br>너 앞에서 나는 <br>크리스마스이브처럼 <br>너 앞에서의 난 <br>너 앞에서 나는 <br>늘 첫 만남처럼 <br>너 앞에서 나는 <br>들뜬 아이처럼 <br>너 앞에서 나는 <br>롤러코스터처럼 <br>너의 행동 하나하나가 <br>날 반응하게 해 <br>Right girl <br>이건 가식도 아니고 다 <br>들통날 연기하는 <br>것도 아니야 <br>근데 다만 어쩔 줄 <br>모르게 돼 <br>다리만 동동 구르게 돼 <br>I wanna talk to you <br>I wanna talk to you <br>내게 기대 절대로 <br>널 무거워하지 않을게 <br>뜨거워져도 <br>무더워하지 않을게 <br>나를 따뜻하다가도 <br>식기도 얼기도 <br>하게 만든 너라서 <br>그런 너 앞에서 나는 <br>말을 꺼내려다가도 <br>다시 또 삼키고 있잖아 <br>너 앞에서 나는 이상해 <br>너 앞에서 나는 <br>겁쟁이였다가 <br>너 앞에서 나는 <br>또 용감해지고 <br>너 앞에서 나는 <br>내가 아닌 것처럼 <br>아무 일도 없는 듯이 <br>날 감춰 <br>너 앞에서 나는 <br>너무 설레어서 <br>너 앞에서 <br>내 맘은 들떠져 <br>혼자만 이런 걸까 <br>그 맘 궁금할 때 <br>한마디만 해줘 <br>나도 너와 똑같다고 <br>나를 따뜻하다가도 <br>식기도 얼기도 <br>하게 만든 너라서 <br>그런 너 앞에서 나는 <br>말을 꺼내려다가도 <br>다시 또 삼키고 있잖아 <br>너 앞에서 나는 이상해 <br>In love in love in love <br>In love I fall in love <br>In love in love in love <br>걱정 안 해도 돼 <br>진작에 내 속엔 <br>너란 색으로 물들여져서 <br>아름다운 걸 <br>단지 거기면 돼 <br>있어 주기만 해 <br>너 그대로 <br>]]></content><category term="박경 (블락비)" label="박경 (블락비)"/><category term="너 앞에서 나는 (Feat. 브라더수)" label="너 앞에서 나는 (Feat. 브라더수)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박경_블락비/보통연애_Feat_박보람/</id><title>박경_블락비 - 보통연애 (Feat. 박보람) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:05:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:05:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EA%B2%BD_%EB%B8%94%EB%9D%BD%EB%B9%84/%EB%B3%B4%ED%86%B5%EC%97%B0%EC%95%A0_Feat_%EB%B0%95%EB%B3%B4%EB%9E%8C/" title="박경_블락비 - 보통연애 (Feat. 박보람) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새로운 사람, 흥미가 생기고 <br>뻔하디 뻔한 말들을 주고받다. <br>서로 눈치채고 있는 타이밍에 <br>용기 내 하는 취중고백 <br><br>끼워 맞추듯 취미를 공유하고 <br>‘야!’라 부르던 네가 자기가 되어도 <br>너무나 익숙한 장면 같아 반복되는 Dejavu <br><br>너도 느끼잖아 이거 좀 웃기잖아 <br>소설 속의 발단, 전개, 위기, 절정, 결말처럼 언제나 <br>같은 Process 딱 그 정도 <br>뜨거웠다 식는 연애의 온도 <br>항상 그래 왔기에 함부로 치지도 못하는 설레발 <br><br>근데 이상해 좀 잘못된 듯 해 <br>더 설레고 조급해 <br><br>평소처럼 또 머물다 가는 순간의 감정일까 <br>아님 혹시 이번엔 다를까 <br><br>Baby I gotta go <br>나 반복의 반복이더라도 <br>다시 제자리로 온대도 <br>I don't give up (aye!) <br>날 들었다 놨다 하는 너 보통이 아닌걸 <br><br>Oh boy <br>너의 행동 말투나 표정 <br>이상형과는 달라도 자꾸 끌리는데 <br>어쩌겠어 (baam!) <br>날 들었다 놨다 <br>하는 너 보통이 아닌걸 <br>I can feel it <br><br>아잇 <br><br>새로운 사랑 초반의 설렘 <br>뻔하디 뻔한 애칭도 붙여주고 <br>온종일 붙잡고 있는 핸드폰 속엔 <br>끊기지 않는 문자들 <br><br>끼워 맞췄던 것이 좋아지고 <br>무의식 중 자연스레 널 자기라 부르는 모습들이 <br>어딘가 익숙해 반복되는 Dejavu <br><br>저 맞은편에서 보인 <br>너의 모습 so beautiful <br>나는 분명 네가 좋은데 <br>이상하게 걱정이 돼 <br><br>내가 걱정이 돼? <br>그러다 사랑이 정이 돼 <br>어떻게 사람 마음이 하루아침에 정의돼 but <br><br>이번엔 달라 좀 잘못된듯해 <br>더 커지고 조급해 <br><br>평소처럼 또 머물다 가는 순간의 감정일까 <br>아님 혹시 (different) <br><br>Baby I gotta go <br>나 반복의 반복이더라도 <br>다시 제자리로 온대도 <br>I don't give up (aye!) <br>날 들었다 놨다 하는 너 보통이 아닌걸 <br><br>Oh boy <br>너의 행동 말투나 표정 <br>이상형관 달라도 자꾸 끌리는데 <br>어쩌겠어 (baam!) <br>날 들었다 놨다 <br>하는 너 보통이 아닌걸 <br>I can feel it <br><br>Yo, I’m confused girl <br>Hey, I’m confused boy <br><br>이런 걱정 바보 같은 거 알아 <br>근데 사실은 말이야 <br>이건 너 변할까 봐 혼자 먼저 하는 자기방어 <br>같은 거야 그러니 나와 같을 거라고 말해줘 <br>어린애같이 유치한 날 달래줘 <br><br>Baby I gotta go <br>나 반복의 반복이더라도 <br>다시 제자리로 온대도 <br>I don't give up (aye!) <br>날 들었다 놨다 하는 너 보통이 아닌걸 <br><br>Oh boy <br>너의 행동 말투나 표정 <br>이상형관 달라도 자꾸 끌리는데 <br>어쩌겠어 (baam!) <br>날 들었다 놨다 <br>하는 너 보통이 아닌걸 <br>I can feel it]]></content><category term="박경 (블락비)" label="박경 (블락비)"/><category term="보통연애 (Feat. 박보람)" label="보통연애 (Feat. 박보람)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Retro_Youth/Hometown_Homesick/</id><title>Retro_Youth - Hometown Homesick - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:07:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:07:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Retro_Youth/Hometown_Homesick/" title="Retro_Youth - Hometown Homesick - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do you remember when our lives were simple, not a cloud in our skies <br>Didn't work for nothing, didn't care to struggle, we'd just sit and laugh and smoke and drink our <br><br>Money down the drain, just sit and while away our days, till we're numb and feeling no pain <br>Blurred face, feeling spaced, hazy lazing 'bout the place Oh ain't it such a crying shame <br><br>Run away, with me, this town will drown us if we let it can't you see <br>Run away, I'm sure, I can't keep feeling oh so homesick in my hometown anymore <br><br>I know we've got no money, it doesn't matter As long as I've still got you <br>It'd be such a waste to stay and die in this place, take my hand I'll hold your heart with every step that we take <br><br>Yet our moneys down the drain, can't wait and while away our days, till we're numb and feeling no pain <br>Blurred face, feeling spaced, hazy lazing 'bout the place Oh ain't it such a crying shame <br><br>Run away, with me, this town will drown us if we let it can't you see <br>Run away, I'm sure, I can't keep feeling oh so homesick in my hometown anymore <br><br>It's only for a little while, have hope, have heart Give an inch we'll run a mile This time is ours <br><br>Run away, with me, this town will drown us if we let it can't you see <br>Run away, I'm sure, I can't keep feeling oh so homesick in my hometown anymoreCHORUS <br>Run away, with me, this town will drown us if we let it can't you see <br>Run away, I'm sure, I can't keep sick to death of my hometown anymore]]></content><category term="Retro Youth" label="Retro Youth"/><category term="Hometown Homesick" label="Hometown Homesick"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/RimK/Hitch_Feat_Sadek/</id><title>RimK - Hitch (Feat. Sadek) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:08:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:08:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/RimK/Hitch_Feat_Sadek/" title="RimK - Hitch (Feat. Sadek) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[J'suis dans l'carre VIP, j'envoie les bouteilles a la Meech <br>M'prends pas pour une dinde, mon lapin parce que j'suis riche <br>evi evidemment j'ai l'droit d'allumer mon spliff Bob Marley <br>T'arrive dans un Uber, mon lapin tu repars en Heetch <br>J'suis dans l'carre VIP, j'envoie les bouteilles a la Meech <br>J'suis dans l'carre VIP, j'envoie les bouteilles a la Meech <br>M'prends pas pour une dinde, mon lapin parce que j'suis riche <br>J'arrive dans un Uber, mon lapin tu repars en Heetch <br><br>J'gagne au poker a Las Vegas <br>Chivas Regal, regard de glace <br>Ta meuf est bonne qu'a cuisiner des pates <br>Elle voit les copains, direct elle ecarte <br>Lamborghini superleggera, j'fume toute la reserve federale <br>J'pese lourd comme un scorpion, on m'craint comme la Scampia <br>J'enregistre un delit, montagnes de Kabylie comme les couilles a Broly <br>Addition de taulier, des bouteilles de six litres <br>J'me ravitaille chez rifi <br>A la Big Meech a la Wiz <br>Le cigare remplit de weed <br>Avec mes associes du crime, gros bzez dans la piscine <br>Big fumee dans la piece, j'tire j'tire sur la peuf' <br>Avec une Selena Gomez, grosse claque sur ses fesses <br>Tu repars en Heetch, je repars en i <br>Qu'en moto japonaise, la marque de mon arme ecrit en polonais <br>Cellophane, on a grandi dans la bibi <br>Tu peux pas dormir entre moi et mon calibre <br>J'remplis les sacs Louis V et on s'barre en velib <br>J'pourrais rouler jusqu'a Medellin <br><br>J'suis dans l'carre VIP, j'envoie les bouteilles a la Meech <br>M'prends pas pour une dinde mon lapin parce que j'suis rich' <br>evi evidemment j'ai l'droit d'allumer mon spliff Bob Marley <br>T'arrive dans un Uber, mon lapin tu repars en Heetch <br>J'suis dans l'carre VIP, j'envoie les bouteilles a la Meech <br>J'suis dans l'carre VIP, j'envoie les bouteilles a la Meech <br>M'prends pas pour une dinde mon lapin parce que j'suis rich <br>J'arrive dans un Uber, mon lapin tu repars en Heetch <br><br>Oublie pas qu'on revait du dessert sans gouter l'entree <br>T'inquiete pas, on fait qu'manger khey tu me parle de me ranger <br>J'ai pas d'frein arriere, aucun amour pour l'armistice <br>Qui va nous racketter J'vais les tuer des le service <br>Profite de mon corps, ne crois pas qu'on se reverra <br>J'veux que mes petits passent du Gilera au Carrera <br>Et la sipette c'est le redma <br>Paye sur le benef' de la MD <br>Ta aucun trou dans le tail de <br>On meurt aujourd'hui, on revit redwa <br>Tomber,belve,bebe,je suis deconnecte <br>Bisous, mandat pour ceux qui tourneront tout l'ete <br>Tonton Karim, on les baise <br>Le terma rempli de mayonnaise <br>Je n'ecoute pas, j'fais c'qu'il me plait <br>Venez me passer les bracelets <br>Han j'etait bourre j'ai oublie de rappeler <br>On compte les billets, laisse les compter les abonnes <br>En gilet 'venchy mais j'peux vite remettre le K Way <br>On a toujours fait c'qu'il fallait <br><br>J'suis dans l'carre VIP, j'envoie les bouteilles a la Meech <br>M'prends pas pour une dinde mon lapin parce que j'suis rich' <br>evi evidemment j'ai l'droit d'allumer mon spliff Bob Marley <br>T'arrive dans un Uber, mon lapin tu repars en Heetch <br>J'suis dans l'carre VIP, j'envoie les bouteilles a la Meech <br>J'suis dans l'carre VIP, j'envoie les bouteilles a la Meech <br>M'prends pas pour une dinde mon lapin parce que j'suis rich <br>J'arrive dans un Uber, mon lapin tu repars en Hitch]]></content><category term="Rim`K" label="Rim`K"/><category term="Hitch (Feat. Sadek)" label="Hitch (Feat. Sadek)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Revolver_Freestyle/</id><title>Tedua - Revolver Freestyle - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:09:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:09:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Revolver_Freestyle/" title="Tedua - Revolver Freestyle - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, yaeah <br>Yaaoohh <br>Uuuh, uuuh, uuuh <br><br>Mamacita, mamacita <br>T'es mon well, t'es ma bella <br>Gucci, Cartier, Fendi, Prada <br>Beaucoup de business beaucoup de coupable <br>J'suis dans les wesh j'suis dans tes bras <br>Beaucoup de billets, j'suis plus dans les temps <br>Le business rapporte ca devient allechant <br>J'veux les Merco et les plus belles jambes <br>Ma femme se les soigne aux telethons <br>J'suis dans cette tout en Louis Vitton <br>Beaucoup de monnaie, de sac de vigon dom perignon <br>Donc mes reunions, j'suis plus elegant <br>J'suis refait dans le temps des ancens peupons <br>Ouh lala tu Milano <br>Me mon ma razir far' a ciro <br>Les blems pour les gars dm'appeler ''Giro'' <br>Des Zorro Des Zorro Des Zorro <br>Ye ancor inta biendo <br>C'est effet italiano <br><br>Uuuh uuh <br>Non so perche odiano baby, no <br>Pensi che mi importi No <br>Sto soltanto provando a fare sto cash <br>A farmi da solo e scappare da qua, yeh <br><br>Tedua, le strade si sono riunite <br>Come disse Nader <br>Parigi e a Milano e Milano e a Parigi <br>Ma il mare e di Cogo, e ti colgo in un covo di pare <br>E mi pare sto drill stia suonando Revolver <br>O parli di soldi o qui chi ti risponde <br>Se la vita e la G, Z4 nel cazzo di business <br>Homie con buste al buffet in suisse <br>A giornate tocca a far soldi <br>Sto battendo un cinque <br>Con cinque diverse combinazioni <br>Lei fa fitness che fa bene alla circolazione <br>Non capisce il mio slang perche e dei palazzoni <br>E ora guardaci in tele <br>Questa giungla non mi turba, no <br>Da qua i fra' si tuffano <br>Poi stamane lei e maledettamente in mente <br>Matematicamente attrae a se <br>E magicamente appare <br><br>Uuuh uuh <br>Non so perche odiano baby, no <br>Pensi che mi importi No <br>Sto soltanto provando a fare sto cash <br>A farmi da solo e scappare da qua, yeh <br><br>Tu mi pari un bel clown, lei ti vuole per se <br>Il piano e farmi casa, quale BMW <br>La squadra stava ad Hogwarts, ora e magia <br>E mangia meglio di quanto sognavamo un tempo <br>La tua roba penso non puo andare <br>Come penso questa donna non mi possa amare <br>Non cago le tue frecciate perche porta lema <br>Tu sei poca cosa perche hai troppa fretta <br>Da Parigi fanno Bang Bang Bang <br>'Sti ragazzini sono bestie, yeah <br>Flow apre porte come un passepartout <br>Calvairate con due marcie in piu <br>Il culo e bello grosso, copre gli spari <br>Infame mi parli alle spalle, infatti li stai <br>Se vuoi dieci ti do dieci, credi hai sempre ragione <br>Amore non funziona, non ripeto l'errore <br>Questa roba ci mangia e ci punge <br>Al ritorno le vomiti tutte <br>Penso Massi ora mastico appena <br>A me basta una penna, l'avresti mai detto <br>E il polso di Falco ne ha tre o quattro <br>Il tempo passa cosi svelto <br>E l'ho visto il tuo tipo, che bel clown <br>Non sembra ti stia divertendo <br><br>Uuuh uuh <br>Non so perche odiano baby, no <br>Pensi che mi importi No <br>Sto soltanto provando a fare sto cash <br>A farmi da solo e scappare da qua, yeh <br><br>Rappo da quando e iniziato il tempo <br>Che cazzo ridi Pure te le vivi <br>Siamo primitivi come sto vinello <br>Ho accettato tutto, e stato un fallimento <br>Fumo 'sto frutto e il demone che ho dentro <br>No, non c'e trucco, dipende chi sento <br>Faccio due sbuffi e la lascio al vento, al cielo <br>Faccio sacrificio di sangue <br>E verso un litro, due litri di flow <br>Che ci porta attraverso, mi specchi <br>Non guardo te, non faccio il vecchio <br>Non faccio cash e non faccio l'escort <br>Ti mollo il peso si, in un fazzoletto <br>Perche sai che pesa, l'hai tenuta in grembo <br>Perche non c'e chiesa fra' per quest'obbrobbrio <br>Perche i miei fratelli non lo fanno sobrio, no <br>Mamacita, mamacita <br>Paris, Genova, Milano e una gita di metrica calda <br>Flow locomotiva, un malloppo emotivo <br>Ogni volta che sfida <br>Il contratto del film quando ho fatto vent'anni <br>Come se fosse fra' il mio compleanno <br>Solo che non son figlio del pa <br>Billion Headz, Jungle, WildB, Zona 4 <br><br>No, no <br>Pensi che mi importi No <br>Sto soltanto provando a fare sto cash <br>A farmi da solo e scappare da qua, yeh <br>Non so perche odiano baby, no <br>Pensi che mi importi No <br>Sto soltanto provando a fare sto cash <br>A farmi da solo e scappare da qua, yeh]]></content><category term="Tedua" label="Tedua"/><category term="Revolver Freestyle" label="Revolver Freestyle"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Pensa_Se_Piove_Rmx/</id><title>Tedua - Pensa Se Piove (Rmx) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:09:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:09:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Pensa_Se_Piove_Rmx/" title="Tedua - Pensa Se Piove (Rmx) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Teeeduaaa <br><br>Se mi manchi mandi in orbita la testa <br>Senza buona opinione d'altra parte <br>Non c'e partner nell'intesa <br>e tesa la strada intrapresa e pesa <br>Pero in preda al panico tappe al bagno, fumiamo sgamo <br>E torniamo al tavolo <br>Il mio foglio delle rime e volato <br>A causa del vento, avverso, avverto <br>Sto provando rincorrendolo a riprenderlo <br>Altrimenti, ti arriverebbero rime d'altre menti <br>Oggi menti bensi, i tuoi nuovi indumenti <br>Il cielo e cieco per lo smog e Dio ostruito <br>Ed io istruito a Dio non credo ma ci convivo <br><br>Una cravatta non distingue un uomo, neanche se muore <br>Una farfalla vive un giorno solo, pensa se piove <br>Non penso vorrai fare tardi anche stasera <br>Baby abbiamo fatto pace, il passato si azzera <br>E se mi pensi le notti nel sonno <br>Capisco perche ti agiti in quel modo <br>A tratti siamo simili, attratti come siamesi <br><br>Stavo cercando te perche per me <br>Eri una da conquistare, una con cui stare <br>Ti vedo che studi teatro ma con me non ci sai recitare <br>E bevi quei drink, al venerdi, invece di <br>Stare ferma in piazza tu vai pazza per viaggiare <br>A cena fuori cosa vuoi ordinare <br>Siamo gelosi ma non mi ordinare <br>Eh sti cazzi, ho preso i tuoi pregi <br>Tu hai preso i miei difetti, e di fatti <br>Siamo diversi e divelsi, te dal terreno, temevo <br>Un fiore colto fosse morto, ma <br>Ho travasato il vaso e dato spago al tronco <br><br>Una cravatta non distingue un uomo, neanche se muore <br>Una farfalla vive un giorno solo, pensa se piove <br>Non penso vorrai fare tardi anche stasera <br>Baby abbiamo fatto pace, il passato si azzera <br>E se mi pensi le notti nel sonno <br>Capisco perche ti agiti in quel modo <br>A tratti siamo simili, attratti come siamesi <br><br>Sai che non e un'allucinazione in avvicinamento <br>Pagano a provvigione per un approvvigionamento <br>Per noi che sembra una scialuppa di salvataggio <br>In un mare di cemento, saluta, un naufragato al nubifragio <br>Faccio finche le rime si fanno cotte, pronte <br>Le esco dal forno, le metto a contorno <br>Avevo il flow in frigo e un figo contenuto <br>Contenuto nel microonde ma e radioattivo e il micro, mi si scioglie <br>Qualsiasi cosa fai, fai in modo che ci sia passione <br>L'ambizione smuove, ma vuole ammirazione e non da <br>Quest'ultima, misericordia a chi non ricorda o scordera il tuo nome <br><br>Una cravatta non distingue un uomo, neanche se muore <br>Una farfalla vive un giorno solo, pensa se piove <br>Non penso vorrai fare tardi anche stasera <br>Baby abbiamo fatto pace, il passato si azzera <br>E se mi pensi le notti nel sonno <br>Capisco perche ti agiti in quel modo <br>A tratti siamo simili, attratti come siamesi]]></content><category term="Tedua" label="Tedua"/><category term="Pensa Se Piove (Rmx)" label="Pensa Se Piove (Rmx)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Pegaso/</id><title>Tedua - Pegaso - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:09:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:09:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Pegaso/" title="Tedua - Pegaso - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Adele, Atene la vediamo assieme <br>La tele, in ferie non tiene, mi preme <br>Bicchiere di pere, intere <br>Mischiato al Jack Daniel's <br>Gesta, in Gescal, testa a testa <br>Se te fra l'hai persa, gazzelle e pantere <br>Per le gazze ladre il quartiere si crede foresta <br>Quest'auto mi sfugge di mano <br>Ubriaco baby sto ubicato in un posto lontano <br>Stai all'occhio al posto di blocco <br>Posto proprio dal benzinaio <br><br>Eh sembra che questo calamaio mi dica Calma, Mario <br>Ogni volta che credevi fosse tutto pilotato <br>Non e il primo caso <br>Ordina due fritture come un calamaro <br>Ti porterei un anello con un gioiello incastonato <br>Ma senza soldi e tutto cosi incasinato <br><br>No che non vedo no, e tutto cosi scuro <br>Tuffi dall'arcipelago <br>Sembra se pensiamo al nostro futuro Ooh oh, ooh oh <br>Cazzo se pesano i cazzotti al fegato <br>Non e piu un cartoon di Pegasus <br>Quando i fra menano tornano e aspettano l'ultimo bus <br><br>Tedua attenta se stai in attesa <br>Baby sto a trenta piedi da terra <br>Mira i cieli e la terra <br>Per il mio crew io Kirikou <br>Chi di piu la vive meglio <br>Fra caldo e freddo in un igloo <br>O le case fatte in canne di bambu <br>La gravita e un ostacolo per le mie rime <br>Certi spettri fanno Oktagon <br>Optano per non dormire <br>Svoltano o slogano il mio avvenire <br><br>No che non vedo no, e tutto cosi scuro <br>Tuffi dall'arcipelago <br>Sembra se pensiamo al nostro futuro Ooh oh, ooh oh <br>Cazzo se pesano i cazzotti al fegato <br>Non e piu un cartoon di Pegasus <br>Quando i fra' menano tornano e aspettano l'ultimo bus]]></content><category term="Tedua" label="Tedua"/><category term="Pegaso" label="Pegaso"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Telefonate_Feat_Izi/</id><title>Tedua - Telefonate (Feat. Izi) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:09:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:09:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Telefonate_Feat_Izi/" title="Tedua - Telefonate (Feat. Izi) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Uh, uh <br>Gang, gang, gang <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>Gang, gang, gang, gang <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>Oh, oh, oh <br><br>Baby non ho perso un pezzo di me <br>Ben piu, di piu, pero ho piu da dire <br>Il dolore avvolge, a volte <br>E porge l'altra guancia, no ai porci della finanza <br>Sai quanta Acqua sotto ai ponti deve ancora venire <br>Roccia per scalfire, una roccia occorre una tempesta <br>Che sia funesta, come l'ira di Achille <br>Chi si e espresso ha reso un'idea <br>Sono riemerso in superficie, finendo l'apnea <br>No, non appena avro una motocross, la usero <br>Su di una duna della luna <br>Chi trova la zona non trova un tesoro <br>Chi trova un tesoro, se non torna in zona <br>Non trova perdono <br><br>So che siamo nati dalle costole ma di conseguenza non so <br>Come mai venga l'odio e l'istinto <br>Di far di tutta l'erba un fascio <br>O cercare il pelo nell'uovo per quello che faccio <br>Mi chiamano a fare soldi, good mornin' <br>Tedua tu corri via dagli infami <br>Fammi fare le mie telefonate <br>A te che ne rimane <br>Retate per delle ettate <br><br>Eh, Izeh, Izeh <br>No, no, no <br><br>Da noi mancava sempre il pane <br>Mancava dentro al piatto e lo dovevo disegnare <br>Matite, fogli A4 davo forma alla mia vita, si <br>Si, come sul palco, come quando si e felici, si <br>Sto con la mia Gang Shit, sto con la mia Gang Shit <br>Sopra quell'Enjoy rossa che sfreccia ai centoventi <br>Con Tedua, Bresh e Nolan sorvoliamo le correnti <br>Sei giu con i miei testi da un pochino e te li segni <br>Come soldi da dare, come assegni, come impegni che non hai <br>Te l'inventi li sul momento, non dire cose se poi non sai <br>Non far lo stronzo no, non ti sento <br>Non ho sentito mani dall'alto, si, fino a quando non ero pronto <br>Non stavo sobrio, manco un secondo <br>E che ero troppo pronto gia al pronto soccorso <br><br>So che siamo nati dalle costole ma di conseguenza non so <br>Come mai venga l'odio e l'istinto <br>Di far di tutta l'erba un fascio <br>O cercare il pelo nell'uovo per quello che faccio <br>Mi chiamano a fare soldi, good mornin' <br>Tedua tu corri via dagli infami <br>Fammi fare le mie telefonate <br>A te che ne rimane <br>Retate per delle ettate]]></content><category term="Tedua" label="Tedua"/><category term="Telefonate (Feat. Izi)" label="Telefonate (Feat. Izi)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Pugile/</id><title>Tedua - Pugile - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:09:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:09:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Pugile/" title="Tedua - Pugile - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Te du uh uh ah <br>Gang, Tedua, ok <br>Chris, Charlie <br>Ehy oh <br><br>Finche il gioco regge faccio finta che non mi manchi <br>Sotto il semaforo all'incrocio dei nostri sguardi <br>Se sei nel panico copriti e goditi il tuo cappotto nuovo <br>Un ragazzo in strada sta studiando per diventare un uomo <br>Sfumo con il dito la tempera <br>E servira per creare un colore nuovo <br>Tedua tempera il tuo caratterino <br>Verso la stessa direzione ma all'opposto di due lati Io e te <br>Come le ali degli aeroplani <br>Un bravo pugile e soprattutto bravo ad incassare <br>You know lo sai no, in questa merda per incassare <br>Eh, eh, eh, ehi <br>Per briciole di pane, MC's qui ci muoiono di fame <br>E mangiano chinati, infatti si danno testate <br>Mi piace se ti piace spogliarti e non solo d'estate <br><br>E no, non essere scontrosa <br>Che cosa ci siamo detti ieri <br>Avevo perso la bussola lungo i sentieri e se tieni a me <br>No, no, non mi mancare di rispetto mai <br>No, no, non perder la fiducia in noi <br>E stiamo sdraiati nel blocco ascoltandoci a malapena <br>Scordati per il ritorno di esser la stessa persona <br>Te va in cielo e coprici se getto l'ascia <br>Quando, quanto gelo lascia, la scialuppa mia <br>Vita di P squali nell'acqua <br><br>Ladies and gentlemen <br>Tre, due <br><br>Per farmi ste scene ancora, sei un po' grandicella <br>Da bimbi pensavamo noi da grandi in cella <br>Chi ha il rello in piazza porta gli altri in sella <br>Non mi sottovalutare, non sai cosa ho in serbo <br>Resto fermo no o vedro generazioni passare tipo il bidello <br>Se attraverso il tuo universo verso whisky <br>Undici dissing ti dissi, non basterebbero ad unirci, mai <br>Quanti chili hai perso Sei dimagrito <br>Quanti chili a puffo e poi sei sparito <br>Non si fa cosi, no <br>May day, dei bei Swarovski su quei lobi e polsi porti vorrei <br>L'amore e un motore per cui consumiamo <br>Un autore o un attore, non toglie mai il pathos <br>Non tollera altro che collera e alcol <br><br>E no, non essere scontrosa <br>Che cosa ci siamo detti ieri <br>Avevo perso la bussola lungo i sentieri e se tieni a me <br>No, no, non mi mancare di rispetto mai <br>No, no, non perder la fiducia in noi <br>E stiamo sdraiati nel blocco ascoltandoci a malapena <br>Scordati per il ritorno di esser la stessa persona <br>Te va in cielo e coprici se getto l'ascia <br>Quando, quanto gelo lascia, la scialuppa mia <br>Vita di P squali nell'acqua]]></content><category term="Tedua" label="Tedua"/><category term="Pugile" label="Pugile"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Ci_Vuole_Poco_Feat_Laioung/</id><title>Tedua - Ci Vuole Poco (Feat. Laioung) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:09:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:09:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Ci_Vuole_Poco_Feat_Laioung/" title="Tedua - Ci Vuole Poco (Feat. Laioung) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tedua Tedua <br>Chris Nolan Nolan <br>Laioung Laioung <br>Gang gang <br>Ehi, ehi ehi, ehi <br><br>Su quest'astronave ascoltare i nostri pezzi trap e un piacere <br>Non facciam le faide, toglie tempo al business, vi serve un paciere <br>Il mio fra mi fa ≪Non torno a dar pezzi o far pezzi col tornio≫ <br>Stiamo chiudendo dei pezzi giu in studio, in pieno agosto, si, il caldo non lo calcolo proprio <br>Tedua per la mia squad, giu la kefia, come a COD, da pivelli Carl Cox, bella Laioung <br>Due dritte sul canto, se stai accanto il flow e d'incanto <br>Non permettero mai che quest'hype mi dia alla testa <br>Sto rincorrendo dei sogni, quei soldi son conseguenza <br>Per questa vita siamo fissi, in salita, rischi <br>Di schiantarti, dischi, volanti, sbirri <br>Corri ai ripari <br>In tanti finti stanno ficcando i nasi <br><br>Finche poi se vuoi con noi tu puoi <br>Non esser piu la stessa l'indomani rispetto a stasera <br>Perche sai, a perdersi nei guai <br>Puoi prenderti degl'anni ma l'anima non si anima mai <br><br>Ho fatto da me, che chi fa da se fa per tre, perche ci vuole poco <br>Ho rincorso del cash freddo dentro al Moncler <br>Sempre con un mon frere perche ci vuole poco <br>Sono gia in tempo per fallire <br>Un negro dal retro stara per uscire <br>Cercava giustizia brandendo un fucile <br>Brrr ehi <br>Cercava giustizia brandendo un fucile <br>Cercava giustizia brandendo un fucile <br>Un negro da dentro stara per uscire <br>Cercava giustizia brandendo un fucile <br>Bam bam brrr ehi <br><br>D'estate rinchiuso in studio a fare i capolavori <br>Lei puo restare se vuole, io ricomincio da capo al lavoro <br>Anche vestito con vestiti vintage, mi chiamano capo al lavoro fresh <br>Non siamo di turno, ormai e il mio turno e ora dal game non mi muovo <br>Voglio la pace nel mondo, riconciliare le anime <br>Attento che l'odio distrugge e li continuerai senza di me <br>Guidiamo le Bentley all'estero, solamente con gente che merita <br>In Italia portiamo l'America, pure su una trappata angelica <br>Pure quando toniamo in pubblico purtroppo devo partire subito <br>Sai che restero quando c'ho i soldi, io non voglio i miei fratelli sciolti <br>Porto Roma con me come Cesare, ora mi chiamano Giulio <br>Se restiamo connessi vinciamo, se il nemico attacca linciamo <br><br>Finche poi se vuoi con noi tu puoi <br>Non esser piu la stessa l'indomani rispetto a stasera <br>Perche sai, a perdersi nei guai <br>Puoi prenderti degl'anni ma l'anima si anima mai <br><br>Ho fatto da me, che chi fa da se fa per tre, perche ci vuole poco <br>Ho rincorso del cash freddo dentro al Moncler <br>Sempre con un mon frere perche ci vuole poco <br>Sono gia in tempo per fallire <br>Un negro da dentro stara per uscire <br>Cercava giustizia brandendo un fucile <br>Brrr ehi <br>Cercava giustizia brandendo un fucile <br>Cercava giustizia brandendo un fucile <br>Un negro da dentro stara per uscire <br>Cercava giustizia brandendo un fucile <br>Bam bam brrr ehi]]></content><category term="Tedua" label="Tedua"/><category term="Ci Vuole Poco (Feat. Laioung)" label="Ci Vuole Poco (Feat. Laioung)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/OC_California/</id><title>Tedua - OC (California) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:09:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:09:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/OC_California/" title="Tedua - OC (California) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tedua, 15 anni, i panni del mercato regalati <br>La mia mami, sbatti tra debiti e mesi in ospedali <br>I miei fra come me, con problemi peggio o uguali <br>E stesse storie di sbatti collegiali <br>No no, non tribulare in tribunale a <br>Titubare di rubare tipo tentennare o tentare <br>Ed eravamo poveri per le belle a bei concerti <br>Eppure contenti di vederli dai tetti <br>E facevamo a gara a chi rigava l'auto degli sbirri <br>Fuori dal panificio, si, per puro sfizio <br>Tedua alle risse fra quartieri <br>Quando appartenevi a cio che non eri <br><br>Baby devi dirmi lo provi solo per me, Tedua <br>Nottate a Dicembre in preda, corse fra la neve <br>Spera non ti venga la febbre, lo sai <br>Siamo di nuovo in gioco noi <br>Non ti terro mai d'occhio, vai <br>So che mi porti dentro e intanto <br>Tento un altro intervento di trapianto <br><br>I miei fra dall'orfanotrofio alle case al mare <br>Alle ville alle vie del centro <br>Da un ranch popolare o in case in affido <br>Dalla comunita od il collegio <br><br>Tedua la mia banda e fuori <br>Sbanda carreggiata calpestata <br>Dalla mia nuova scarpa Skater coi i Carrhart <br>No cara, non ci far caso a sto caos in casa <br>Mangiamo steak house a Corsico con i bro <br>Piu di Pharrel cosa faresti <br>Piu che farfalle nello stomaco ne senti i versi se muoiono <br>Perche lo stomaco non e posto per vivere, pieno di viscere <br>Seppur Pinocchio versa un occhio della testa d'affitto <br>Afflitto nella balena in balia della marea <br>Tra la barriera corallina inganna l'attesa <br>Versa amarena e Codeina <br><br>Baby devi dirmi lo provi solo per me, Tedua <br>Nottate a Dicembre in preda, corse fra la neve <br>Spera non ti venga la febbre, lo sai <br>Siamo di nuovo in gioco noi <br>Non ti terro mai d'occhio, vai <br>So che mi porti dentro e intanto <br>Tento un altro intervento di trapianto]]></content><category term="Tedua" label="Tedua"/><category term="OC (California)" label="OC (California)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Step_By_Step_Feat_Bresh/</id><title>Tedua - Step By Step (Feat. Bresh) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:09:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:09:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Step_By_Step_Feat_Bresh/" title="Tedua - Step By Step (Feat. Bresh) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sto contando i giri che la terra compie <br>Nell'arco di un anno <br>Mentre passa il tempo filtrano gli amici <br>Scarto quelli a babbo <br>Non e novita, se dal basso fra poi nasce un bastardo <br>Questa polvere non migliora ma vola come a maggio <br>Come in moto corro, come treno torno <br>Ma non mi aspettare che non ti riprendo <br>Muri di cemento dalle parti <br>Questo amaro freddo mi ha ghiacciato il petto <br>La mia civilta fa pubblicita <br>Con gli occhi coperti della bella vita <br>Non conosco fra solidarieta <br>Assieme agli anticorpi sgamo un parassita <br>Temo sia finito il tempo, pure 'sta canna e finita <br>Fermo a motore spento, tengo il mio girovita <br><br>Non hai parole per distrarci <br>Non basterebbe neanche il meglio che hai <br>Fra tutti i posti in cui potevo finire a cacciarmi <br>Fare i normali non ci e piaciuto mai <br><br>Perche quando mi chiama lei <br>Sento dei presentimenti <br>E per certi versi io pretendo apprezzi <br>Beh, che fare <br>Non ho un re di cuori <br>Con te che mi pare <br>A guardie fai nomi <br>Loro non hanno capito che sopra al set <br>Questo spartito cosa direbbe <br>Beh, vedi te <br>Non servirebbe deridere <br>Fuori dal gregge correre che <br>Non ci potranno correggere <br><br>Tedua, fuori siamo fiori <br>Non ho fori sul muro <br>Se mi curo il culo, paraculi <br>Avete scudi, scusi <br>Siamo qg, stiamo cuci nando curvi <br>E la schiena ci si piega in QT <br>Danna ad altrui <br>Appunti, scritte ed ardui ahh <br>Risarcisca il danno fatto <br>La perquisa trae in inganno <br>Mentre me la fa il mio fra la sta spargendo <br>Fuori peso in pieno autunno <br>L'uso delle parole e essenziale, sensuale <br>Senza un senso sensoriale <br>E' tentare di internare in te il male <br>Per un test intenzionale, ah beh <br>La mia gang sta volando, cazzo <br>Dobbiamo passare un'altro step by step <br>O ai re dei re saro l'erede del drepa mio pazzo <br>A te che nella scena fai il boss <br>Ma non hai scomodato il culo <br>So che vuoi un po' del mio flow <br>Ma non e in comodato d'uso <br><br>Perche quando mi chiama lei <br>Sento dei presentimenti <br>E per certi versi io pretendo apprezzi <br>Beh, che fare <br>Non ho un re di cuori <br>Con te che mi pare <br>A guardie fai nomi <br>Loro non hanno capito che sopra al set <br>Questo spartito cosa direbbe <br>Beh, vedi te <br>Non servirebbe deridere <br>Fuori dal gregge correre che <br>Non ci potranno correggere]]></content><category term="Tedua" label="Tedua"/><category term="Step By Step (Feat. Bresh)" label="Step By Step (Feat. Bresh)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Fifty_Fifty_Feat_Ghali/</id><title>Tedua - Fifty Fifty (Feat. Ghali) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:09:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:09:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Fifty_Fifty_Feat_Ghali/" title="Tedua - Fifty Fifty (Feat. Ghali) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Io e Ghali <br>Tedua roccia quanta pioggia puo scalfirmi <br>Can you hear me <br>La mia coccia, costa, costa, nostra, e NOS fra <br>Non ti mettere a scannare <br>Sporchi accordi presi in cortile <br>Per i miei, non perdonare <br>Vale a dire perseguire <br>Sul beat il pit non sta al canile <br>Quanto tempo passa e si insabbiano le notizie <br>Scarcerano fra cancellano le ingiustizie <br>Non sei me, no, nemmeno in 100 vite <br>Hai voglia di stare a fare nomi <br>Snitchi i miei commenti, homies <br>No, mi onori <br>Tefra non mentir poi <br>Ancora forti fuori coi miei folli tori <br>Tra la giungla la mia ciurma fa da pescatori per gli alligatori <br>Sono a riva al mare <br>Tu non scimmiottare Mowgli o muori <br>Money money so che li vuoi li vuoi <br>Orange County vola al Schiphol Detroit <br>Flow una tigre come ti riesce, ri esce non t'intimidire <br>Tedua <br><br>A letto vado sempre tardi <br>I soldi in tasca mi durano poco <br>Non so ancora come comportarmi <br>Per me e come se fosse un gioco <br>Roccia scusa se ti incazzi <br>Questi bianchi lo fanno a loro modo <br>E io non mi ritrovo <br><br>Tedua ogni weekend <br>Alza un K d'idee <br>A K servite <br>Assaggia le rime <br>Se sei uno snitcher non mi si addice <br>Lei mi sorride a te non lo dice <br><br>Hello Puoi sentirmi <br>Non sai quante cose ora avrei da dirti <br>Fumo io, fumi te <br>Fifty fifty <br>Si credon dei ma noi siamo monoteisti <br>Sono usciti i sogni dal cassetto <br>Perche l'ho tenuto aperto <br>Mamma mi dice stai attento <br>A mettere il seme la dentro <br>e presto ma certo <br>Guarda come si sta adesso <br>Noi volevamo si questo <br>Parlo di te in ogni testo <br>Quando usciamo fra e cinema <br>Anche sotto i palazzi di chi ne ha <br>Il cielo no, non mi delinea <br>Scendo sempre al capolinea <br>Non vedi la squadra che si allinea <br>Zombie stasera ho casa libera <br>Veneziano fai il bravo dai girala <br>Fumo e canto come Jigglypuff <br><br>A letto vado sempre tardi <br>I soldi in tasca mi durano poco <br>Non so ancora come comportarmi <br>Per me e come se fosse un gioco <br>Roccia scusa se ti incazzi <br>Questi bianchi lo fanno a loro modo <br>E io non mi ritrovo <br><br>Tedua ogni weekend <br>Alza un K d'idee <br>A K servite <br>Assaggia le rime <br>Se sei uno snitcher non mi si addice <br>Lei mi sorride a te non lo dice]]></content><category term="Tedua" label="Tedua"/><category term="Fifty Fifty (Feat. Ghali)" label="Fifty Fifty (Feat. Ghali)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/No_Snitch_Freestyle/</id><title>Tedua - No Snitch Freestyle - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:09:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:09:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/No_Snitch_Freestyle/" title="Tedua - No Snitch Freestyle - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No homie, che cazzo hai in testa <br>No snitch, non farlo ancora <br>Sul beat il Pit e sciolto <br>Non bisticci con noi, nah <br>C'ho il flow, c'ho include che e il mio shooter <br>Alture le misure <br>A due passi dal blocco <br>A fuoco le pattuglie <br><br>Perche homie, che cazzo hai in testa <br>No snitch, non farlo ancora <br>Sul beat il Pit e sciolto <br>Non bisticci con noi, nah <br>C'ho il flow, c'ho il Krueger che e il mio shooter <br>Alture le misure <br>A due passi dal blocco <br>A fuoco le pattuglie <br><br>Tedua no, non mettermi MD <br>Devi informarti, informati <br>Queste cene fre e un catering di camerieri <br>Dai tavoli non lavori <br>Gli anni dentro al disagio <br>Pesano piu da minorenni <br>Perche mi comprendi <br>Non hai vitto, affetti <br>Tipo al Fleming <br>La mia squad ha quotato in borsa <br>Perche certi ricicli son ciclici shhh, cimici <br>Volo, piu in alto <br>Cosi tu non mi afferri, Fendi <br>Questa cinta, ci sta <br><br>No homie, che cazzo hai in testa <br>No snitch, non farlo ancora <br>Sul beat il Pit e sciolto <br>Non bisticci con noi, nah <br>C'ho il flow, c'ho il Krueger che e il mio shooter <br>Alture le misure <br>A due passi dal blocco <br>A fuoco le pattuglie <br><br>Perche homie, che cazzo hai in testa <br>No snitch, non farlo ancora <br>Sul beat il Pit e sciolto <br>Non bisticci con noi, nah <br>C'ho il flow, c'ho include che e il mio shooter <br>Alture le misure <br>A due passi dal blocco <br>A fuoco le pattuglie]]></content><category term="Tedua" label="Tedua"/><category term="No Snitch Freestyle" label="No Snitch Freestyle"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Buste_Della_Spesa/</id><title>Tedua - Buste Della Spesa - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:09:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:09:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Buste_Della_Spesa/" title="Tedua - Buste Della Spesa - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, Orange, Orange <br>Ehi ehi ehi, Charlie Charlie <br>Orange County, County Ahah <br>Skuuu, Skrt skrt <br>Tedua, gang gang <br><br>Stai cercando di fottere Tedua <br>Verranno a farti brutto entro stasera <br>Mo pensi che ne valga la pena <br>Chico tranquillo e tutta scena <br>Hip Hop e poi ma che cantilena <br>I tuoi solo cattiveria <br>Se vuoi puoi portarci <br>Le buste nella busta della spesa <br>Con pure la pesa <br><br>Se mi ricordo quando fottevate Tedua, beh <br>Ne e passato di tempo <br>Oggi tu hai l'ansia, fallimento <br>Il flow fa fare a tutti voi da esempio <br>Non so se sai che a noi fa senso, questo posto <br>Il podio e nel nostro studio <br>Faccio un porno, musical <br>Noi al bar, Genoa Doria <br>Con lo shha della zona <br>Volo perso, verso l'universo <br>Oggi che mi credo grande <br>Sono nato e continuato a coltivarle kush, 'ste doti <br>I miei fra con l'eastpak pieni di tocchi <br><br>Stai cercando di fottere Tedua <br>Verranno a farti brutto entro stasera <br>Mo pensi che ne valga la pena <br>Chico tranquillo e tutta scena <br>Hip Hop e poi ma che cantilena <br>I tuoi solo cattiveria <br>Se vuoi puoi portarci <br>Le buste nella busta della spesa <br>Con pure la pesa <br><br>I can't fear nobody <br>Fai che fino a domani ci rimanga dell'erba <br>Il mio fra che vuole afferra <br>Oh ti diro, solo solo litigo <br>Se mi manchi brindero il vino in taverna <br>Appena faccio questa roba <br>La mia testa in calotta artica <br>Dalla calotta cranica si cerna <br>Flow in vetta vieta di fare breccia <br>Lei mi pensava, il cuore le batteva <br>Sto prendendo quota <br>Homie ora che gli altri perdono quota <br>Homie qualche malcapitato stara augurando <br>Sia un giro dell'oca <br>O un cane che si morde la coda <br>Ma cosa, ho saltato la coda <br>e soltanto la nostra ora quindi <br><br>Stai cercando di fottere Tedua <br>Verranno a farti brutto entro stasera <br>Mo pensi che ne valga la pena <br>Chico tranquillo e tutta scena <br>Hip Hop e poi ma che cantilena <br>I tuoi solo cattiveria <br>Se vuoi puoi portarci <br>Le buste nella busta della spesa <br>Con pure la pesa <br><br>Orange County <br>Orange County <br>Orange County <br>Orange County <br>Orange County]]></content><category term="Tedua" label="Tedua"/><category term="Buste Della Spesa" label="Buste Della Spesa"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Lezione/</id><title>Tedua - Lezione - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:09:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:09:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Lezione/" title="Tedua - Lezione - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tedua, due ragazzi fuori dal blocco <br>Mi ero nascosto, le volanti e ricordo <br>Le urla, Uomo di merda <br>E ti serva come lezione <br>Presero a calci il mio amico <br>Cosi uscimmo di corsa, e di forza spingemmo lo sbirro <br>No beef no, non farlo <br>Ho fifa, si fra <br>Ma canto solo sui beat io <br>Io homie no, non ti invidio <br>Ti invio il video in Ovidio di Mirko <br>Cosi lo guardi prima di entrare <br>Mesi a Marassi o vestiti e parti <br>Cazzo che caldo che provo <br>Dico a ogni modo, non mi commuovo <br>Perche di un uomo non e suo ruolo <br>Detto per gioco, pero ci provo <br>Tedua in terapia d'urgenza incendia l'anima sempre prima di fare musica <br><br>Roccia conta anche me <br>Porta in borsa del cash <br>Non mi importa di te <br>Che ti credi re <br>Roccia conta anche me <br>Porta in borsa del cash <br>Non mi importa di te <br>Che ti credi re <br><br>Da quando parli composto <br>Spacca casa in affido <br>Grido Mamma la voglio <br>Un pippotto poi ti porta all'asilo <br>Corri bambino, co copriti il viso <br>E cresci da solo <br>Tu fuggi al destino <br>Le forze verranno a mancare in un monolocale <br>Col CAP che mi cambia se cambio la stanza <br>Ho un sacco di sabbia <br>I miei homie fuggono dall'ipocrisia, seppur per pochi sia <br>Essere un uomo ed avere onore e diverso dall'essere un uomo d'onore in periferia <br>La mia via e Jihad CIA <br>La mia scuola e la Diaz <br>La mia storia e la FIAT, e magia, a Scampia <br>E 'sta troia, un'arpia <br>E m'ingoia in apnea <br>E va in gola e fa la la trap dalla trachea <br><br>Roccia conta anche me <br>Porta in borsa del cash <br>Non mi importa di te <br>Che ti credi re <br>Roccia conta anche me <br>Porta in borsa del cash <br>Non mi importa di te <br>Che ti credi re]]></content><category term="Tedua" label="Tedua"/><category term="Lezione" label="Lezione"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Wasabi_Freestyle/</id><title>Tedua - Wasabi Freestyle - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:09:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:09:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Wasabi_Freestyle/" title="Tedua - Wasabi Freestyle - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Guarda che cadi <br>Fra, salsa wasabi <br>Il tuo pucciotto puzza <br>Mi spuntano i cani <br>Mi cali le braghe <br>Dei baggy per strada <br>Siam rocce scalfite dal mare, dal male <br>Da madre puttana <br>Puntata di serie di Shameless <br>Di ferie a dicembre <br>Ho accettato il freddo <br>Fra gettato al gelo <br>Ti regalo un petalo d'ero <br>Il mio homie mi chiama, arrestato <br>Svuotami la casa dal retro <br>D'arredo ho uno stereo <br>Se acceso e un aereo <br>Che ho un flow pilotato <br>Toro Scatenato <br>Stiamo contando soldi <br>Tanti da dover fare a turni <br>State facendo i bulli <br>Voi che rappate bullshit <br>Non c'e pace per Cucchi <br>Odiate Duate che rappa, che trappa, che canta, che balla, che parla <br>Che barba, che noia che siete <br>Un mio fre quando ha sete <br>Non e mai di sapere <br>Nel locale, la locale, non puo starmi addosso <br>Nel prive i Figgeu di Cogo <br>Ma di che, liriche, direi che e di fuoco <br>Odi me, ottime pretese nel gioco <br>Nei tuoi panni non ci metti Tedua <br>Non mi parli, come hai detto, scusa <br>Che cura e kush fra <br>Vai a cercare la siga per la kunda <br>Tu ah <br><br>Tedua, Chris Nolan <br><br>No no, non mi mettere <br>No no, non ti permettere <br>Non ti vorrai far prendere <br>A chi ti infama non vendere <br>Lo so che hai <br>Molto piu ma mai <br>Tu vuoi ma non dai <br>Quanto subirai <br>Vorrei farti entrare un minuto nel mio mondo <br>Baby non e carnevale, maschere non ne porto ai piedi <br>Pero, Milano sembra Chicago <br>Vacci piano]]></content><category term="Tedua" label="Tedua"/><category term="Wasabi Freestyle" label="Wasabi Freestyle"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Lingerie_Feat_Sfera_Ebbasta/</id><title>Tedua - Lingerie (Feat. Sfera Ebbasta) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:10:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:10:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Lingerie_Feat_Sfera_Ebbasta/" title="Tedua - Lingerie (Feat. Sfera Ebbasta) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Non fottere il mio squad <br>Da COGO <br>Non fottere il mio squad <br>Da COGO <br><br>Roccia sto col Rkomi <br>Segna Calvairate <br>Faccio un salto a Nord est che Ciny e ospitale <br>I miei fra fumano Northern affacciati in Aler <br>Un fumo cosi crema <br>No fre non scaldare <br>Roccia ho portato il mare a Milano <br>Ho ancora il rispetto di dove abitavo <br>La tua squad varra si e no 7 carati <br>Scendo in Drilliguria mi sembran Caraibi <br>Falco offre cena che ha vinto ai cavalli <br>Neuro SerT all'EuroBet <br>Per me no, non puntare il pari <br>Quando parli a Tedua devi moderare <br>Tu vuoi un beat di Charlie ma non lo sai usare <br><br>Non fottere il mio squad <br>No, no, Non lo fare <br>Da COGO, dacci oggi il pane <br>La mia pussy gira in casa in Lingerie Orientale <br>Ha big booty jeans e inala droghe ricettate <br>E non lo sanno che faccio da solo <br>No no loro non lo sanno <br>'Sta strada e un tesoro <br>Se chiedi perche lo faccio <br>Rispondo per loro <br>Prima era tutto uno scherzo <br>Mo per Vito e un lavoro <br><br>I tuoi con le Canon <br>I miei coi cannoni <br>Zero cinta, soldi in tasca <br>Casca il pantalone <br>Dimmi tu come li fai <br>O se li hai e non li sudi mai <br>Giri in quartiere con Manu e con Vito <br>Tu punti il dito <br>Stiamo vincendo fra' <br>Mi sa sei il solo che non l'ha capito <br>Stiamo provando a scappare dai guai <br>Cambiare vita non l'ho fatto mai <br>L'unica cosa che cambia col tempo <br>E' la tipa che scopi e i modelli di Nike <br>In zona non pompano i pezzi d'amore <br>Si pompano la tua tipa <br>Che si fa scopare in cambio di un raglione <br>Chiaro che non vuoi piu avere ragione <br>Quando c'e Ureke in mezzo alla faccenda <br>Guardo la tua giacca e in finto montone <br>Pensa alla tua finta vita di merda <br><br>Non fottere il mio squad <br>No, no, Non lo fare <br>Da COGO, dacci oggi il pane <br>La mia pussy gira in casa in Lingerie Orientale <br>Ha big booty jeans e inala droghe ricettate <br>E non lo sanno che faccio da solo <br>No no loro non lo sanno <br>'Sta strada e un tesoro <br>Se chiedi perche lo faccio <br>Rispondo per loro <br>Prima era tutto uno scherzo <br>Mo per Vito e un lavoro]]></content><category term="Tedua" label="Tedua"/><category term="Lingerie (Feat. Sfera Ebbasta)" label="Lingerie (Feat. Sfera Ebbasta)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Circonvalley_Feat_Izi/</id><title>Tedua - Circonvalley (Feat. Izi) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:10:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:10:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tedua/Circonvalley_Feat_Izi/" title="Tedua - Circonvalley (Feat. Izi) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Orange County <br>Wild Bandana <br>Cogo, Cogo <br><br>Tedua, Tedua, cazzo <br>Astro nauta in Circonvalley <br>La via Lattea sembra gia qui, yo <br>Ok, fai la guerra con Tedua e vuole molto di piu <br>Ma non mi cerca e mi da tregua <br>Non te la do vinta <br>Ogni rima su tela e dipinta <br>Sono fiero se un tefra mi tifa <br>E non e vero che Tedua t'invidia <br>Perche ho piu di cosi <br>Non puoi piu dirmi che sei tu <br>Quella che sbaglia per crescere <br>Tu mi ripari quando fuori c'e tempesta <br>Baby benvenuta al party <br>Casa mia e una festa <br><br>Ho gia chiamato il taxi <br>Presto scendi di casa <br>Almeno prima che m'incazzi <br>Passiamo in tangenziale <br>Guarda in giro che palazzi <br>Guarda i palazzi Ma che palazzi <br>Guarda i palazzi, i palazzi <br><br>Appena mi alzo la mattina frate' grido UeUe <br>Stendo la lavatrice e dopo grido UeUe <br>Boh non lo so, mi fa sentire bene UeUe <br>Scendo giu dai commercianti in centro e grido UeUe <br>Qualcuno c'e ma qualcun'altro e in ferie <br>Saluto zie e saluto le famiglie <br>Saluto i figli in strada grido UeUe <br>C'e qualche amico che si e maturato <br>E qualche amico che e dentro da anni <br>Io voglio poter dire che ho fatturato <br>E non voglio mentire quindi dovro farli <br><br>Ho gia chiamato il taxi <br>Presto scendi di casa <br>Almeno prima che m'incazzi <br>Passiamo in tangenziale <br>Guarda in giro che palazzi <br>Guarda i palazzi Ma che palazzi <br>Guarda i palazzi, i palazzi]]></content><category term="Tedua" label="Tedua"/><category term="Circonvalley (Feat. Izi)" label="Circonvalley (Feat. Izi)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/Lac_Motion/</id><title>Cashis - Lac Motion - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:10:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:10:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/Lac_Motion/" title="Cashis - Lac Motion - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Screech out, yeah <br>That's what I'm talkin 'bout bzzt <br>Ca$his, Shady bzzt <br>Good lookin Em <br><br>We in the Cadillac Cartel and Snoop DeVilles <br>Ridin on Treys like Barksdale, I'm movin steel <br>Step out and see the new Car mellos you would steal <br>But you ain't runnin around here cause dude is real <br>You dub for fifteen minutes sayin they shoot and steal <br>I would tell you more, but I think, you would squeal <br>I'm ridin at the wheel, lean back, poppin pills <br>I make a lil' side money plus I got a deal <br>I'm nine kids deep see, why I gotta deal <br>And serve so the government, can't touch my skrill <br>Before I'm sittin in my big, house, on the hill <br>Dark, not in HB, Hall go, have a meal <br>I am the bogus boy, that was in my uncle's will <br>You figured that out, and see that I'm a G for real <br>And fear man is one thing that he don't feel <br>Knock a nigga out, while his gun on him still <br><br>'Llac 'Llac motion motion drop drop top top <br>West West coast coast beatin down yo' block <br>That's how we do it out here, out here folk <br>That's how we do it out here, back forth folk <br>Back on the 'Llac 'Llac motion motion drop drop top top <br>West West coast coast beatin down yo' block <br>That's how we do it out here, out here folk <br>That's how we do it out here, back forth folk <br>Back screech out <br><br>New Makaveli jeans, five Vicks, Blue Leaf <br>Tall tee, hang to my motherfuckin knees nigga <br>I got a gang of my partners from OC, figure <br>If it's some drama they all, ridin with me if ya <br>Recognize a situation that you can't win <br>You may feel like a marked mellow but you can live <br>Still you tryin to be hard, yellin out stupid shit <br>I just look at you laughin, say that you a bitch <br>I got somethin from class despite my truant seers <br>But I can whoop on yo' ass homie if you in Sears <br>It's better not to be brash and come with foolishness <br>Talkin 'bout my county 'til you see how true it is <br>Come to the 7 1 fo', Glizzy could get you rich <br>Some of the homies got dough, the rest is militant <br>We got goons that's loon tootin them wicked sticks <br>My whole set to end, Shady that's what the bid'ness is <br><br>'Llac 'Llac motion motion drop drop top top <br>West West coast coast beatin down yo' block <br>That's how we do it out here, out here folk <br>That's how we do it out here, back forth folk <br>Back on the 'Llac 'Llac motion motion drop drop top top <br>West West coast coast beatin down yo' block <br>That's how we do it out here, out here folk <br>That's how we do it out here, back forth folk <br>Back screech out <br><br>We switchin lanes and candy paints on 22's <br>And '83s and '88s, in grammar schools <br>Different names of the 'Llac, I hear the hundred crews <br>Miss the exit, that's all from gettin blunted fool <br>Flick the tussin, a couple buzzards is comin through <br>Soon as they see me say Ca$h, I wanna fuck wit'chu <br>So many niggas is lamed out, and gullible <br>We make 'em lookouts in fog eyes for copper moves <br>I was livin the life, of sellin rocks to dudes <br>When I got to a block, I was unstoppable <br>I had to serve out the 'Llac, cause they was watchin moves <br>But bein poor was just, somethin I couldn't do <br>I wanna roll in a six hundred and stunt on you <br>Next time I see you and yours, I'll pull a gun on you <br>Through every stage of my life, I been that fuckin dude <br>You should be glad I took, time to fuck wit'chu <br><br>'Llac 'Llac motion motion drop drop top top <br>West West coast coast beatin down yo' block <br>That's how we do it out here, out here folk <br>That's how we do it out here, back forth folk <br>Back on the 'Llac 'Llac motion motion drop drop top top <br>West West coast coast beatin down yo' block <br>That's how we do it out here, out here folk <br>That's how we do it out here, back forth folk <br>Back screech out]]></content><category term="Cashis" label="Cashis"/><category term="Lac Motion" label="Lac Motion"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/Thoughts_Of_Suicide/</id><title>Cashis - Thoughts Of Suicide - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:10:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:10:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/Thoughts_Of_Suicide/" title="Cashis - Thoughts Of Suicide - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lies in the game, how I entertain <br>The last lines of the next Kurt Cobain <br>Standin in the mirror with a 9 at my brain <br>Most rap guys wanna die for the fame <br>Supposed to die young cause, I'm in the gang <br>And I can't change cause, I entertain <br>Can sniff three verses through lines of 'caine <br>You just realized that, I'm insane <br>I'm enraged, engaged in a war with ways <br>They can have me spray shots off the stage <br>If I die like Malcolm will you feel my pain <br>Or just cry like a bitch while I lay in my grave <br>If I die like 'Pac, cause I yearn to bang <br>You discredit me, like I never learned a thang <br>If I die like Big would you praise my rhymes <br>And give me the spot, Best of All Time <br>If I die in NY will the West Coast ride <br>And the beef not stop 'til, hip hop die <br>Will a nigga who don't, understand that line <br>Try and damage my safety, in NY <br>Will the rap game embrace me cause I got skill <br>Or for the lies of that man, will I get killed nigga <br><br>I'm just gettin high, gettin high <br>Think of suicide, suicide <br>I'm just gettin high, gettin high <br>Think of suicide, suicide <br>I'm just gettin high, gettin high <br>I think of suicide, suicide <br><br>Will the crimes of my youth, come back to haunt me <br>By the time I shoot, will my father want me <br>When I tour will my girl be come a whore <br>And I come back home and can't fuck her raw <br>If I walked on stage like, FUCK the law <br>Will the hip hop cops try and kill my squad <br>Will the niggas on my team really ride like they say <br>Or push me in the shots, he gon' die anyway <br>Is niggas really jealous, cause I got shine <br>Is it envy from the fellas, cause I got signed <br>Will the whole hood hate, cause I speak my mind <br>Will I die for a rhyme before I reach my prime <br>If I kill my bitch like Robert Blake <br>Do I got enough money, to beat the case <br>If I crash out, right before I end the race <br>And die, 'fore I come out, would you feel my pain <br>I'm almost to a point, where I can't be saved <br>My mindstate, at a place, where it can't be changed <br>Laws got a nigga stuck like he can't get break <br>But I gotta back up, all the shit I say <br>It's lies in the game, how I entertain <br>The last lines of the next Kurt Cobain <br>Standin in the mirror with a 9 at my brain <br>Most rap guys wanna die for the fame <br><br>I'm just gettin high, gettin high <br>Think of suicide, suicide <br>I'm just gettin high, gettin high <br>Think of suicide, suicide <br>I'm just gettin high, gettin high <br>I think of suicide, suicide]]></content><category term="Cashis" label="Cashis"/><category term="Thoughts Of Suicide" label="Thoughts Of Suicide"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/Pistol_Poppin_Feat_Eminem/</id><title>Cashis - Pistol Poppin` (Feat. Eminem) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:10:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:10:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/Pistol_Poppin_Feat_Eminem/" title="Cashis - Pistol Poppin` (Feat. Eminem) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Haha <br>Ca$his, Ca$his <br>Yeah <br>King Mathers <br>C'MON <br>Pistol poppin, come get me nigga <br><br>Pistol poppin, bodies droppin, layin all around <br>You thought it was a game, now the neighbors callin out <br>The police find that, what's that sound <br>While you layin on the ground with your fuckin brain out <br><br>Walk through the door with my hands on a gun <br>Cause niggas 'round here wanna ask where I'm from <br>I throw up my signs, step back and pop one <br>'fore you throw up your sign if you even got one <br>I used to bust niggas heads open for fun <br>Chase him down, stomp him out, if he tried to run <br>I could flip packs, get stacks, big straps, where it at <br>Slung crack, real cat, you ain't never did that <br>Go hard, no peace, I gotta keep, chrome heat <br>I don't sleep, homie I'm watched by the police <br>Cops out patrolling, grab a Glock 40 <br>Sniper at the squad car, story noting <br>Fuck it if you want beef, click clack, wack rap <br>Tossed straps before, I'm out of here, homie <br>Militant in a sense, I don't really give a shit <br>Call up, Eminem, I gotta plead innocent <br><br>Pistol poppin, bodies droppin, layin all around <br>You thought it was a game, now the neighbors callin out <br>The police find that, what's that sound <br>While you layin on the ground with your fuckin brain out <br><br>Sixteenth in my sneakers, I ain't listen to my teachers <br>I'm the most hated nigga alive, since Jesus <br>Maybe in the afterlife they'll reveal my Christ like abilities <br>Come back, then ride on my enemies <br>Never been afraid of beef, metals of my bravery <br>War situations got you sayin he, crazy G <br>And emerge with the beat, I can serve anything <br>Especially anybody tryin to diss my team Shady <br>*blam* G Unit, Aftermath the same thing <br>So if you say them punk nigga you say me <br>I be in LA G, get at me when you see me <br>Catch you in OC, and in the bag you'll be leaving <br>I ain't worried 'bout my freedom cause for me to get even <br>Is worth e'rything, it's on BBGN <br>I son'd you folk, I'm lookin at your pinkie <br>You a fake ass gangsta, what a waste of my scenery <br><br>Pistol poppin, bodies droppin, layin all around <br>You thought it was a game, now the neighbors callin out <br>The police find that, what's that sound <br>While you layin on the ground with your fuckin brain out <br>Pistol poppin, bodies droppin, layin all around <br>You thought it was a game, now the neighbors callin out <br>The police find that, what's that sound <br>While you layin on the ground with your fuckin brain out <br><br>Maybe I just feel like there's too many pussies in rap <br>Shady Ca$his we gotta push 'em to the back <br>Move 'em along, push 'em aside, don't get me wrong <br>I love the finger snaps and the claps into the song <br>It's got a catch but come on man, the raps <br>We all gotta step our game up especially these lame fucks <br>Who walk around with their chest out <br>Just tryin to be down with anybody who's left now <br>Better be down with them, huh <br>But I dare some bitch to say somethin about, Eminem <br>Cause I'm not in the mood to be playin around with dudes <br>I already seen two friends get shot in the head <br>And lay on the ground this year and, one didn't make it <br>Proof, you are the truth <br>Please don't let us come face to face with these boo boo hoo <br>Fake ass tattooed havin <br>Fif' please tell 'em right now how hard it has been <br>For me to try and, stay out it <br>But they just won't quit runnin their mouth <br>At least 'til there's a gun in it son of a bitch <br>We all got shooters, yeah these days who doesn't <br>And as far as the snaps and claps, I wasn't <br>Dissin the South, that isn't what this is about <br>I just so sick of the beef, I don't even wanna see anymore <br><br>Pistol poppin, bodies droppin, layin all around <br>You thought it was a game, now the neighbors callin out <br>The police find that, what's that sound <br>While you layin on the ground with your fuckin brain out <br>Pistol poppin, bodies droppin, layin all around <br>You thought it was a game, now the neighbors callin out <br>The police find that, what's that sound <br>While you layin on the ground with your fuckin brain out]]></content><category term="Cashis" label="Cashis"/><category term="Pistol Poppin` (Feat. Eminem)" label="Pistol Poppin` (Feat. Eminem)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/Just_Like_Me/</id><title>Cashis - Just Like Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:10:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:10:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/Just_Like_Me/" title="Cashis - Just Like Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, Blocc Boy on the beat <br>It's Cashis, spend some real shit <br>It's for my, it's for my seeds, nigga <br>It's still Shady though <br><br>Sit back right, all night spot post <br>Do the same thang, killing off black folks <br>Selling on the side, string save a mean more <br>To anything I own, watch crack being smoke <br>Got the picture of the seven little reasons <br>That keep, any nigga disrespecting me breathing <br>Still I be high, every time I see them <br>My babies, my angels and they are my freedom <br>I know I'm on the grind, lately I ain't coming home <br>They keep you in my life, I never leave your mom alone <br>You know I'm whyling out, straying strapped, ride or dying <br>You hear the stories 'bout your daddy floating 'round town <br>But you call me up like, Daddy I been finding out <br>That you caught Rico slipping, beat him up and stomped him out <br>So when you go to school, you wanna do it too <br>You just like me, how can I be mad at you <br><br>You ain't had to live like I did and still you are just like me <br>Hell I even did a bid and came back to see you are just like me <br>The only reason I ain't kill myself is for fear you'll be just like be <br>You got the demons that's within myself, now I see, you are just like me <br><br>Standin on the block, tryna make my money clock <br>Servin situations, my nuts about a cock <br>I wanna stop but, y'all gotta have a lot <br>Even if it means sacrificing the life of your pops <br>I'm the breadwinner, I don't fear nann nigga <br>I don't trust nobody, I'm a man <br>Liquor, running through my veins, you running through my brain <br>I start to see your heart, we feel each other's pain <br>I talk to all of y'all when I say I love you mayne <br>One day we'll ball and I'll never have to leave again <br>Until that day comes, shorty be a G <br>I ride with y'all everywhere cause y'all are part of me <br>Here go my hugs and kisses, never give you up for bitches <br>Promise to give you riches, all of my little niggas <br>Here go my hugs and kisses, never give you up for bitches <br>Promise to give you riches, all of my little niggas <br><br>You ain't had to live like I did and still you are just like me <br>Hell I even did a bid and came back to see you are just like me <br>The only reason I ain't kill myself is for fear you'll be just like be <br>You got the demons that's within myself, now I see, you are just like me <br><br>Look how they talking shit, twice a year I drop a key <br>I bet nobody ever love 'em like they daddy did <br>I teach 'em young, don't be rolling on no scary shit <br>Long as you love each other, you'll be very rich <br>Everybody question how I be affording this <br>I make my money off of dicks and spend it on my kids <br>I'm sending messages in bottles of imagination <br>So they can feel my presence, though they at home just waiting <br>My soldiers still in training, throwing up forks like they banging <br>Know how to bogart, and never trust a stranger <br>They the ones I look to whenever I'm in danger <br>We walking holding hands, interlocking trigger fingers <br>This is my record to my kids, I'm a banger <br>And a father so my conversation must remain gangsta <br>This is my record to my kids, I'm a banger <br>And a father so my conversation must remain gangsta <br><br>You ain't had to live like I did and still you are just like me <br>Hell I even did a bid and came back to see you are just like me <br>The only reason I ain't kill myself is for fear you'll be just like be <br>You got the demons that's within myself, now I see, you are just like me <br><br>Yeah, it don't get much realer than that, Shady, Cashis, nigga <br>Be a man, take care of yours that don't make you no less gangsta <br>My nigga not take care of his, I take care of mine homie <br>I'mma give a individual shoutout to 'em, Miana, Jasmine, Ramani <br>Rashanti, Lil' Mone and Rah Monique, Tavian, they are just like me]]></content><category term="Cashis" label="Cashis"/><category term="Just Like Me" label="Just Like Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/Ms_Jenkins/</id><title>Cashis - Ms. Jenkins - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:10:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:10:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/Ms_Jenkins/" title="Cashis - Ms. Jenkins - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Momma, just killed a man <br>Put a gun against his head <br>Pulled my trigger, now he's dead <br>Momma, life had just begun <br>But now I've gone and thrown it all away <br><br>Geah, it's Ca$his, Shady Records <br>Real music, not fool music <br><br>There was just a lot tears shed over what you been through <br>A mother's pain pays, for what her kid do <br>As Brian light fades, in the rearview <br>You enslaved to her, but gotta skid through <br>We was both bangin, Brian and I <br>Different neighborhoods so we chose different sides <br>Confrontaton in the street, so we had to ride <br>I won the fight, his pride felt I had to die <br>He screamed 1 8 7 I say, I never hide <br>You know where I'm at boy, I ain't hard to find <br>A couple weeks went by, we passin time <br>He seen me in the alley with his niggas, I <br>Was just dealin off Cavi then I seen the 9 <br>Then I, heard a shot, he just kept firin <br>I started runnin, duckin, now I'm hidin <br>The whole time conscious of my own homicide and <br>I got away, click click in the nick of time <br>His clip dropped down, he start signifyin <br>You a bitch Ca$h, run with your bitch ass <br>Heard sirens, then I heard him hit the gas <br>Right then, I knew your son wouldn't last <br>I said to myself, Folk, I gotta kill his ass <br>Roll through my apartment, hit the buildin fast <br>Gun out of my closet, hit the stick and dash <br>Put the, strap in my pocket, on my mission I saw him <br>Down the block sittin back, sippin 'gnac <br>I walked up like, What's the business fam <br>He stared death in the eyes, then he shook his head <br>The broad he was with, shook as fuck <br>Put the barrel to his head, buck buck buck <br>He fell to the ground, grass covered with blood <br>I probably go to hell for what I did to your son <br>I walked off slowly bugged, I ain't run <br>It's been five years, and no it's never over <br>He left me no choice, I offer you closure <br>He left me no choice, I offer you closure <br><br>Momma, just killed a man <br>Put a gun against his head <br>Pulled my trigger, now he's dead <br>Momma, life had just begun <br>But now I've gone and thrown it all away <br><br>Dear Ms Jenkins, I send you my love <br>Hi, I'm Ca$his, I murdered your son <br>I'm closin the chapter, on what has begun <br>Dear Ms Jenkins, I murdered your son <br>Dear Ms Jenkins, I send you my love <br>Hi, I'm Ca$his, I murdered your son <br>I'm closin the chapter, on what has begun <br>Dear Ms Jenkins, I murdered your son <br><br>Dear momma, if you gettin this letter <br>I'm dead, I'm sorry if you gettin this letter <br>Wait I'm sorry I ain't live a lil' better <br>My own selfish will wouldn't send you this letter <br>See I had my hat cocked on the wrong spot <br>I threw the right sign up, on the wrong block <br>Blaow, blaow, bloaw Ramone shot <br>Fuck a Ca$his momma Ramone shot <br>It started as a fight, on a distant night <br>But far off the homicide, pistols tight <br>We still grieve over your brother <br>Now you, grieve over your son what the fuck <br>He squabbed me up, this my hood <br>Some nigga named Ca$his from Chris' hood <br>He supposed to come back with iron, I ain't scared <br>Yes I am momma, I don't wanna be dead <br>But I can't run too late, to try and change it <br>Born as your son but dyin as a banger <br>When my name gets discussed for entertainment <br>Never share this letter with a stranger <br>Please, please <br><br>Momma, just killed a man <br>Put a gun against his head <br>Pulled my trigger, now he's dead <br>Momma, life had just begun <br>But now I've gone and thrown it all away <br><br>Dear Ms Jenkins, I send you my love <br>Hi, I'm Ca$his, I murdered your son <br>I'm closin the chapter, on what has begun <br>Dear Ms Jenkins, I murdered your son <br>Dear Ms Jenkins, I send you my love <br>Hi, I'm Ca$his, I murdered your son <br>I'm closin the chapter, on what has begun <br>Dear Ms Jenkins, I murdered your son <br><br>Dear Brian, it's Ca$his, I can't sleep <br>I had to bang you, before you bang me <br>Just like I blame you, you could blame me <br>We both gave up our lives for banging yeah <br>We didn't know each other but we share the same hate <br>Your death is my life, so we share the same fate <br>This ain't what bangin was for, killin for nothin <br>Your death gave karma for the death of my woman Monique <br>I'm tryin to make amends cause within I'm croak <br>But outside I'm hard, my friends don't know <br>I'm sorry that I killed you, I know it don't mean shit <br>We both could've stopped it, if we only seen shit <br>Happens for a reason we don't even know it <br>When you leave here, do you know where you goin <br>I'm sendin my apologies through a song <br>Maybe we can reconcile when I'm gone <br><br>Momma, just killed a man <br>Put a gun against his head <br>Pulled my trigger, now he's dead <br>Momma, life had just begun <br>But now I've gone and thrown it all away <br><br>Dear Ms Jenkins, I send you my love <br>Hi, I'm Ca$his, I murdered your son <br>I'm closin the chapter, on what has begun <br>Dear Ms Jenkins, I murdered your son <br>Dear Ms Jenkins, I send you my love <br>Hi, I'm Ca$his, I murdered your son <br>I'm closin the chapter, on what has begun <br>Dear Ms Jenkins, I murdered your son]]></content><category term="Cashis" label="Cashis"/><category term="Ms. Jenkins" label="Ms. Jenkins"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/Gun_Rule/</id><title>Cashis - Gun Rule - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:10:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:10:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/Gun_Rule/" title="Cashis - Gun Rule - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>It's Ca$his, I'm comin, uhh <br>Shady Records niggas, GO <br><br>Walkin, with a semi cocked, flip down any block <br>Get cash, plenty guap, talk hard gettin shot <br>Went to war with the cops, you reach for what I got <br>Treat you like Singapore, swing a sword, you are chopped <br>Picture me pistol free, Look at me, look at me <br>And realizing none of y'all is hood as me <br>That's on e'rythang, take six to your frame <br>Your son caught in strays, he gon' die any day <br>Try and act brave, tell the law my name <br>I bet your family won't live to see another day <br>There is no other way, you hearin what I say <br>I got paper now, I can fight the case <br><br>I'm walkin through this concrete jungle <br>Plenty niggas here, ready to mug you, attitude of Fuck you <br>Nigga you ain't been where I'm from fool <br>The lames over here, will dump too, we live by gun rule <br>Walkin through this concrete jungle <br>Plenty niggas here, ready to mug you, attitude of Fuck you <br>Nigga you ain't been where I'm from fool <br>The lames over here, will dump too, we live by gun rule <br><br>Like Iraq, C 4 in backpacks <br>You can pull straps but you can't match that <br>Thought you was lord of shit bitch, why you let him snitch <br>Put the gun in your hand, now we can settle it <br>Put it up, to his head, I can't do it for ya <br>You, be the trigger man, kill your own brother <br>See, how it feels when he drops, and he bleeds <br>I handed you heat, it was your op tion to squeeze <br>Drop, to your knees, look at me, and believe <br>There's only one way to get out of this thing <br>Barrel aimed at your face, cock back, fire straight <br>Now at least neither one of us'll catch a murder case <br><br>I'm walkin through this concrete jungle <br>Plenty niggas here, ready to mug you, attitude of Fuck you <br>Nigga you ain't been where I'm from fool <br>The lames over here, will dump too, we live by gun rule <br>Walkin through this concrete jungle <br>Plenty niggas here, ready to mug you, attitude of Fuck you <br>Nigga you ain't been where I'm from fool <br>The lames over here, will dump too, we live by gun rule <br><br>Flyin down the 5, flicked out, gettin high <br>Jump off on Lincoln, roll through, Anaheim <br>Rush, of a homicide, races, through my mind <br>Not commit, any crime anywhere, anytime <br>Stick, niggas for they shine, yeah, you been on the grind <br>Yeah, take your jewelry off and pass it to me, it's mine <br>Cohort, me and my cohorts on codeine <br>Conspire and rioting, robbin niggas for more cream <br>Step on work, eighth by eighth <br>Six points off a quarter nigga, stretch that cake <br>I ain't chillin on the corner, you fall in your order <br>For eightballs and nope, I ain't holdin nothin short, yeah <br><br>I'm walkin through this concrete jungle <br>Plenty niggas here, ready to mug you, attitude of Fuck you <br>Nigga you ain't been where I'm from fool <br>The lames over here, will dump too, we live by gun rule <br>Walkin through this concrete jungle <br>Plenty niggas here, ready to mug you, attitude of Fuck you <br>Nigga you ain't been where I'm from fool <br>The lames over here, will dump too, we live by gun rule <br><br>We live by gun rule <br>Shady Records nigga <br>I'm ridin through to Annis <br>With my forks up folk, G's up]]></content><category term="Cashis" label="Cashis"/><category term="Gun Rule" label="Gun Rule"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/That_N__ga_A_Gangsta/</id><title>Cashis - That N**ga A Gangsta - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:10:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:10:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/That_N__ga_A_Gangsta/" title="Cashis - That N**ga A Gangsta - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lies in the game, how I entertain <br>The last lines of the next Kurt Cobain <br>Standin in the mirror with a 9 at my brain <br>Most rap guys wanna die for the fame <br>Supposed to die young cause, I'm in the gang <br>And I can't change cause, I entertain <br>Can sniff three verses through lines of 'caine <br>You just realized that, I'm insane <br>I'm enraged, engaged in a war with ways <br>They can have me spray shots off the stage <br>If I die like Malcolm will you feel my pain <br>Or just cry like a bitch while I lay in my grave <br>If I die like 'Pac, cause I yearn to bang <br>You discredit me, like I never learned a thang <br>If I die like Big would you praise my rhymes <br>And give me the spot, Best of All Time <br>If I die in NY will the West Coast ride <br>And the beef not stop 'til, hip hop die <br>Will a nigga who don't, understand that line <br>Try and damage my safety, in NY <br>Will the rap game embrace me cause I got skill <br>Or for the lies of that man, will I get killed nigga <br><br>I'm just gettin high, gettin high <br>Think of suicide, suicide <br>I'm just gettin high, gettin high <br>Think of suicide, suicide <br>I'm just gettin high, gettin high <br>I think of suicide, suicide <br><br>Will the crimes of my youth, come back to haunt me <br>By the time I shoot, will my father want me <br>When I tour will my girl be come a whore <br>And I come back home and can't fuck her raw <br>If I walked on stage like, FUCK the law <br>Will the hip hop cops try and kill my squad <br>Will the niggas on my team really ride like they say <br>Or push me in the shots, he gon' die anyway <br>Is niggas really jealous, cause I got shine <br>Is it envy from the fellas, cause I got signed <br>Will the whole hood hate, cause I speak my mind <br>Will I die for a rhyme before I reach my prime <br>If I kill my bitch like Robert Blake <br>Do I got enough money, to beat the case <br>If I crash out, right before I end the race <br>And die, 'fore I come out, would you feel my pain <br>I'm almost to a point, where I can't be saved <br>My mindstate, at a place, where it can't be changed <br>Laws got a nigga stuck like he can't get break <br>But I gotta back up, all the shit I say <br>It's lies in the game, how I entertain <br>The last lines of the next Kurt Cobain <br>Standin in the mirror with a 9 at my brain <br>Most rap guys wanna die for the fame <br><br>I'm just gettin high, gettin high <br>Think of suicide, suicide <br>I'm just gettin high, gettin high <br>Think of suicide, suicide <br>I'm just gettin high, gettin high <br>I think of suicide, suicide]]></content><category term="Cashis" label="Cashis"/><category term="That N**ga A Gangsta" label="That N**ga A Gangsta"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/County_Hound_Intro/</id><title>Cashis - County Hound (Intro) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:10:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:10:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cashis/County_Hound_Intro/" title="Cashis - County Hound (Intro) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ay, what up man <br><br>You came back quick as fuck <br><br>Yo, you got that bomb though <br><br>Yeah that's right, I know <br><br>Hey how much you need What you working with <br><br>Eighty Aight cool, I'ma hook you up I'ma give you a <br><br>But you need to keep coming back now, ya hear <br><br>Aight fo' sure <br><br>Aight <br><br>Man, look at that nigga Ca$his <br><br>He out here tryna get our money <br><br>Ca$his The rap nigga From fucking Orange County <br><br>Fuck that shit nigga,this our block <br><br>Man let's run this nigga off the block Is you ready <br><br>Hell yeah <br><br>Gangsters get out of their car and walk towards Ca$his <br><br>What the business is fo' <br><br>Ay nigga, what the fuck you doing on our block What <br><br>Ya look like ya ready to die or some something <br><br>Man, fuck you <br><br>Both gangsters talking at the same time <br><br>Ya mad cuz I'm getting all the bread around here,huh <br><br>Its whatever then, homie <br><br>There's only one way to handle it then,nigga <br><br>And what's that <br><br>Ca$his pulls out gun, and cocks it back <br><br>Oh shit <br><br>Both Gangsters run away]]></content><category term="Cashis" label="Cashis"/><category term="County Hound (Intro)" label="County Hound (Intro)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/준하/따르리/</id><title>준하 - 따르리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:10:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:10:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A4%80%ED%95%98/%EB%94%B0%EB%A5%B4%EB%A6%AC/" title="준하 - 따르리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[일 분 일 초도 <br>당신이 없이 <br>살아 갈 수 없어요 <br>나의 전부 목숨 이니까 <br>당신을 알고부터 <br>삶의 의미를 <br>조금씩 알게 됐어요 <br>따릅니다 따릅니다 <br>어디든지 따라 갑니다 <br>당신이 원하시면 <br>나는 따르리 <br>세상 끝까지 <br>따라 갑니다 <br>일년이 가고 <br>십년이 가도 <br>변치 않을 겁니다 <br>나의 사랑 하나 이니까 <br>당신을 알고부터 <br>나의 마음엔 <br>사랑의 꽃이 폈어요 <br>따르리오 따르리오 <br>어디든지 따라가리오 <br>당신이 원하시면 <br>나는 따르리 <br>세상 끝까지 따라가리오 <br>따릅니다 따릅니다 <br>어디든지 따라 갑니다 <br>당신이 원하시면 <br>나는 따르리 <br>세상 끝까지 따라 갑니다 <br>당신 하나만 따르렵니다 <br>]]></content><category term="준하" label="준하"/><category term="따르리" label="따르리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mannarino/Le_Rane/</id><title>Mannarino - Le Rane - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:15:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:15:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mannarino/Le_Rane/" title="Mannarino - Le Rane - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Le navi son partite <br>La vita e sulla luna <br>Ma nel cielo d'acqua vite <br>Navigare e cosa dura <br>Hai detto me ne vado <br>Per la mia avventura <br>Ma dove sei arrivato <br>C'e solo spazzatura <br>Ti scaldi con il fiato <br>E c'e d'aver paura <br><br>Le rane stanno sul como <br>Mi bevo quello che non ho <br>Da quando sei andato via <br>Ho allagato casa mia <br>E a Natale dove andro <br>Non trovo una fotografia <br>Magari mi ricordero <br><br>Per le tue cannonate <br>Lei s'e messa l'armatura <br>E niente piu la tocca <br>Ma e piena di paura <br>Hai sognato il sole <br><br>Di far l'amore in volo <br>Vorresti non svegliarti <br>Non ritrovarti solo <br>Divertiti a morire <br>Ma non ci rimanere <br><br>Le rane stanno sul como <br>Mi bevo quello che non ho <br>Da quando sei andato via <br>Ho allagato casa mia <br>E a Natale dove andro <br><br>Ho visto i migliori, pollini al vento <br>Cadere al cemento]]></content><category term="Mannarino" label="Mannarino"/><category term="Le Rane" label="Le Rane"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mannarino/Arca_Di_Noe/</id><title>Mannarino - Arca Di Noe - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:15:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:15:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mannarino/Arca_Di_Noe/" title="Mannarino - Arca Di Noe - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Questa e una storia <br>da raccontare <br>Puo andare bene, puo andare male <br>Ma non si qual e il finale <br>Bisogna andare, comunque andare <br>a camminare <br>sulla terrazza con vista mondo <br>dove ogni alba e anche un tramonto <br><br>Il mondo e un' Arca di Noe <br>che va perduta alla deriva <br>Ma se sei qui con me <br>il mondo non c'e <br>c'e solo pioggia estiva <br><br>Perso dentro te <br>come nel mare una sardina <br>Vago nell'eternita <br>e sto qua giu, dentro una stradina <br><br>Si va si va, ma dove si va <br>Chissa chissa, paura non ho <br>e questa vita mia <br>e tutto quel che ho <br>Piu breve lei sara <br>e piu forte cantero <br><br>Questa e una storia <br>da raccordare <br>t'ho vista urlare piccola vita <br>Poi ritornare con una vita <br>Lasciare al mondo un nuovo nome <br>Una vendetta, una speranza <br>O forse solo un po' d'amore <br>E il curbarante del motore <br>dell'astronave <br><br>Il mondo e un' Arca di Noe <br>che va perduta alla deriva <br>Ma se sei qui con me <br>il mondo non c'e <br>c'e una galassia estiva <br><br>Si va si va, ma dove si va <br>Chissa chissa, paura non ho <br>e questa vita mia <br>e tutto quel che ho <br>Piu breve lei sara <br>e piu forte cantero]]></content><category term="Mannarino" label="Mannarino"/><category term="Arca Di Noe" label="Arca Di Noe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mannarino/Apriti_Cielo/</id><title>Mannarino - Apriti Cielo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T13:15:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T13:15:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mannarino/Apriti_Cielo/" title="Mannarino - Apriti Cielo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Apriti cielo <br>E manda un po' di sole <br>A tutte le persone <br>Che vivono da sole <br><br>Apriti cielo <br>E fa luce per davvero <br>Su quando sono stato <br>Quello che non ero <br><br>Trovammo questa vita fra le stelle <br>Poi lasciammo le caverne <br>Arrivammo alle transenne <br><br>Lasciateme passa che non ho tempo <br>Ho gia dormito tanto <br>Adesso ho un grande appuntamento <br><br>Il vento che passa <br>Il cielo che vola <br>E una vita sola <br>E una vita sola <br><br>Apriti cielo <br>Sulla frontiera <br>Sulla rotta nera <br>Una vita intera <br><br>Apriti cielo <br>Per chi non ha bandiera <br>Per chi non ha preghiera <br>Per chi cammina dondolando nella sera <br><br>Apriti mare <br>E lasciami passare <br>Non hanno fatto niente <br>Niente di male <br><br>C'e un cartello appeso in mezzo al cielo <br>Se vuoi vivere alla grande <br>Devi stare con l'impero <br>Ma una ragazza un giorno m'ha spiegato <br>Che il mare ha tante onde <br>E non finisce all'orizzonte <br><br>Allora andiamo <br>Signore hanno scoperto con la lente <br>Che dietro al cielo non c'e niente <br>E ci sta solo un telo nero <br>Se lo scoprira la gente <br><br>Apriti cielo <br>Il cielo che vola <br>E una vita sola <br>E una vita sola <br><br>Apriti cielo <br>Sulla frontiera <br>Sulla rotta nera <br>Una vita intera <br><br>Apriti cielo <br>Per chi non ha bandiera <br>Per chi non ha preghiera <br>Per chi cammina dondolando nella sera <br><br>Vento di guerra <br>e un uragano <br>Amore mio non ho la forza <br>Camminiamo <br>Non aver paura <br>E damme la mano <br>La notte e scura <br>Ma io e te ci ripariamo <br><br>Apriti cielo <br>Sulla frontiera <br>Sulla rotta nera <br><br>Apriti cielo <br>Per chi non ha bandiera <br>Per chi non ha preghiera <br>Per chi cammina dondolando nella sera <br><br>Apriti cielo <br>E manda un po' di sole <br>Su chi non c'ha nulla <br>Su chi non ha ragione <br><br>Apriti cielo <br>E manda un po' di sole <br>Su chi cammina solo <br>Fra milioni di persone]]></content><category term="Mannarino" label="Mannarino"/><category term="Apriti Cielo" label="Apriti Cielo"/></entry></feed>