<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:11:31+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/세비야/충분히_힘들어/</id><title>세비야 - 충분히 힘들어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:11:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:11:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%B8%EB%B9%84%EC%95%BC/%EC%B6%A9%EB%B6%84%ED%9E%88_%ED%9E%98%EB%93%A4%EC%96%B4/" title="세비야 - 충분히 힘들어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다 괜찮을 거야 <br>좀 더 나아질 거야 <br>매일 하는 다짐인데도 <br>왜 안돼 <br>전혀 그렇지 않아 <br>아니 전보다도 더 커지는 <br>널 향한 그리움 <br>안 해본 게 없을 정도로 <br>별 짓 다 해봤는데 <br>왜 이러는 건지 눈물이 앞서 <br>미친 듯이 달려도 <br>넌 어느새 바로 옆에 <br>니가 와있네 저리 가 <br>소리쳐도 넌 그대로 <br>아니 점점 더 커져 오늘도 <br>지워지지가 않아 <br>아니 전보다도 더 진해져 <br>더 선명해져 가 <br>이제 그만하면 됐다고 <br>충분히 힘들어 <br>떠나가줘 제발 <br>미친 듯이 달려도 넌 <br>어느새 바로 옆에 <br>니가 와있네 저리 가 <br>소리쳐도 넌 그대로 <br>아니 점점 더 커져 오늘도 <br>]]></content><category term="세비야" label="세비야"/><category term="충분히 힘들어" label="충분히 힘들어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서진/작은_길/</id><title>서진 - 작은 길 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:11:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:11:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EC%A7%84/%EC%9E%91%EC%9D%80_%EA%B8%B8/" title="서진 - 작은 길 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아침 밝은 햇살 비추고 <br>그댈 만나는 날이 되면 <br>나만 그런 건지 나만 이렇게 <br>가슴속이 설레 오는지 <br>작은 길을 걷다가 보면 <br>괜스레 숨이 더 차올라 <br>날 기다리는 그대 생각에 <br>발걸음 더 빨라져 <br>길모퉁이를 지나고 나면 <br>빨간 상점을 지나고 나면 <br>그대 모습이 다가와 <br>환한 미소를 번져와 <br>고개를 낮추고 걸어가 <br>조그만 길들을 따라가 <br>나를 바라볼까 혹시 보일까 봐 <br>내 표정 숨길 수가 없잖아 <br>살며시 그댈 불러볼까 <br>또 그대 눈을 한번 바라볼까 <br>그냥 웃어봐 한번 말해봐 <br>처음 만났던 그날 <br>조그만 이 길을 <br>작은 길을 걷다가 보면 <br>괜스레 그대가 떠올라 <br>날 불러주는 그대 모습에 <br>발걸음 더 빨라져 <br>길모퉁이를 지나고 나면 <br>빨간 상점을 지나고 나면 <br>그대 모습이 다가와 <br>환한 미소를 번져와 <br>고개를 낮추고 걸어가 <br>조그만 길들을 따라가 <br>나를 바라볼까 혹시 보일까 봐 <br>내 표정 숨길 수가 없잖아 <br>살며시 그댈 불러볼까 <br>또 그대 눈을 한번 바라볼까 <br>그냥 웃어봐 한번 말해봐 <br>처음 만났던 그날 <br>조그만 이 길을 <br>돌아오는 혼자인 길은 <br>너무 허전해 <br>또 그댈 기다리는 게 <br>조금은 힘들 거 같아 <br>고개를 한번 더 들어봐 <br>그대의 얼굴을 바라봐 <br>나를 바라보는 그대 눈빛에 <br>내 마음 숨길 수가 없잖아 <br>살며시 손을 잡아볼까 <br>또 그대 품에 힘껏 안겨볼까 <br>그냥 웃어봐 한번 말해봐 <br>처음 만났던 그날 <br>조그만 이 길을 <br>]]></content><category term="서진" label="서진"/><category term="작은 길" label="작은 길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/황치열/잠시나마_Inst/</id><title>황치열 - 잠시나마 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:11:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:11:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%A9%EC%B9%98%EC%97%B4/%EC%9E%A0%EC%8B%9C%EB%82%98%EB%A7%88_Inst/" title="황치열 - 잠시나마 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가슴 끝이 시려온다 바람 한 점 없는데 <br>하루하룰 산다는 건 아픈 통증 같아 <br>그런 내게 다가온다 그녀란 한 사람이 <br>지난 아픔 다 모두 잊을 만큼 <br>내 머릿속은 백지처럼 <br>고통 속의 하루를 살아도 <br>불길 속의 그 길을 걸어도 <br>붉게 데인 상처가 눈에 보이지 않아 <br>너만을 바라보면 <br>잠시나마 내 가슴에 <br>쏟아지던 비가 그쳐진다 <br>내 삶의 끝에서 그대에게 전할 말 <br>내 전부였다 <br>소리 없이 웃어진다 그늘이진 마음에 <br>죽을 만큼 살고 싶단 이유를 <br>찾은 것 같아 <br>햇살처럼 스며든다 그녀란 한 사람이 <br>두 뺨에 흐른 눈물 자국들이 <br>어느 샌가 모두 사라져 <br>고통 속의 하루를 살아도 <br>불길 속의 그 길을 걸어도 <br>붉게 데인 상처가 눈에 보이지 않아 <br>너만을 바라보면 잠시나마 <br>울지마 날 위해 제발 울지마 <br>꿈속에라도 날 떠나지 말아요 <br>내 사랑하는 그대여 <br>잊지마 잊지마 나의 사랑아 <br>널 붙잡고 말하지 못한 건 <br>다시 너를 볼 수 없을까 봐 <br>내게 남긴 사랑은 다시 나를 울려도 <br>피할 수 없는 사랑 <br>오늘 밤 난 꿈을 꾼다 <br>곤히 잠든 어린 아이처럼 <br>내 삶의 끝에서 그대에게 전할 말 <br>그대는 내 사랑의 내 전부였다 <br>]]></content><category term="황치열" label="황치열"/><category term="잠시나마 (Inst.)" label="잠시나마 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Il_Cile/La_Fate_Facile/</id><title>Il Cile - La Fate Facile - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:12:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:12:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Il_Cile/La_Fate_Facile/" title="Il Cile - La Fate Facile - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nato negli anni ’80 come la disco music <br>Ricordi dell’infanzia sporadici e confusi <br>Giocattoli e ospedali, mia madre che piangeva <br>Lorenzo come stai” ogni ora mi chiedeva <br>Cresciuto in una stanza, pane e medicinali <br>Vedevo il mondo fuori con i telegiornali <br>A dodici anni cento chili a tredici cinquanta <br>Nessuno da quel giorno mi chiam pi pastasciutta <br>Adolescenza isterica da incubi e deliri <br>Mangiavo dentifricio per non prendere pi chili <br>I tagli sulle braccia, sognavo una ragazza <br>Sputavo mille demoni suonando una chitarra <br>Poi l’universita non mi ricordo niente <br>Andare e poi convivere  stato da incosciente <br>Gia mi vedevo morto, coi sogni dentro al naso <br>Un uso alternativo dei prodotti Proraso <br><br>La fate facile <br>Per voi  facile <br>Prendere un lupo <br>E renderlo docile <br><br>Amore <br>Ti prego torna a casa questa sera <br>I mostri sono fuori ed  gia buio <br>Ti giuro ti preparo anche la cena <br>Amore <br>Ti prego torna a casa questa sera <br>I mostri sono fuori ed  gia buio <br>Ma dormi nel mio letto per piacere <br><br>Adesso sono qui, il solito coglione <br>Ho perso donne e soldi, amici di finzione <br>Ho un cuore imbizzarrito che preoccupa i dottori <br>Un amico immaginario che non da consigli buoni <br>E penso alla mia vita trangugiata come il whisky <br>Che gira a 360 come in un giradischi <br>Mi piacerebbe solo ritornare a quel tempo <br>In cui sapevo fingere di essere contento <br>Non voglio che mi aiuti, non cerco compassione <br>Non cerco nuovi abbracci, non cerco un’illusione <br>Ho come la certezza che nella mia coscienza <br>Ancora sono in guerra con la mia dipendenza <br>Ma  questa societa a volerci tutti schiavi <br>Amanti di veleni barattati coi denari <br>Se mai avr il coraggio di salutarvi tutti <br>Sar il pi silenzioso tra i serpenti maledetti <br><br>La fate facile <br>Per voi  facile <br>Prendere un lupo <br>E renderlo docile <br><br>Amore <br>Ti prego torna a casa questa sera <br>I mostri sono fuori ed  gia buio <br>Ti giuro ti preparo anche la cena <br>Amore <br>Ti prego torna a casa questa sera <br>I mostri sono fuori ed  gia buio <br>Ma dormi nel mio letto per piacere <br><br>Amore <br>Ti prego torna a casa questa sera <br>I mostri sono fuori ed  gia buio <br>Ti giuro ti preparo anche la cena <br><br>Amore <br>Ti prego torna a casa questa sera <br>I mostri sono fuori ed  gia buio <br>Ma dormi nel mio letto per piacere]]></content><category term="Il Cile" label="Il Cile"/><category term="La Fate Facile" label="La Fate Facile"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kei_러블리즈/별과_해/</id><title>Kei (러블리즈) - 별과 해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:13:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:13:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kei_%EB%9F%AC%EB%B8%94%EB%A6%AC%EC%A6%88/%EB%B3%84%EA%B3%BC_%ED%95%B4/" title="Kei (러블리즈) - 별과 해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[별과 해는 결코 <br>만날 수가 없어요 <br>같은 시간 같은 공간 <br>늘 항상 그 자리인데 <br>우린 낮과 밤처럼 <br>마치 물과 불처럼 <br>끝내 함께 할 수 없어서 <br>속이 타들어가고 <br>맘에 멍이 들어도 <br>또다시 그댈 부르네요 <br>그대를 원하고 원하다 보면 <br>애타게 기도하면 <br>볼 수가 있을까요 <br>오늘도 흔들리는 이 내 마음 <br>어찌해야 하나요 <br>갈 곳을 잃었네요 <br>잠 못 드는 밤 밤 밤 <br>사무치는 맘 맘 맘 <br>슬픈 오늘 밤 밤 밤 <br>부서지는 맘 맘 맘 <br>슬픈 표정으로 <br>늘 그 자리에 있네요 <br>같은 생각 같은 눈빛 <br>다 내 것인 것 같은데 <br>우린 함께 있어도 <br>외롭기만 하죠 <br>한 겨울의 가지처럼 <br>늘 메말라있고 <br>너무 앙상하여서 <br>안아줄 힘이 없나 봐요 <br>그대를 원하고 원하다 보면 <br>애타게 기도하면 <br>볼 수가 있을까요 <br>오늘도 흔들리는 이 내 마음 <br>어찌해야 하나요 <br>갈 곳을 잃었네요 <br>내 마음 그리움들 가득 채워 <br>하늘에 기도하면 <br>볼 수가 있을까요 <br>사랑하는 사람에게 <br>사랑 받는 일이 <br>이리도 힘든가요 <br>아무것도 가질 욕심 <br>없는 나예요 <br>작은 소원 그대 하나 <br>들어주세요 내 삶에 <br>그대를 원하고 원하다 보면 <br>애타게 기도하면 <br>볼 수가 있을까요 <br>오늘도 흔들리는 이 내 마음 <br>어찌해야 하나요 <br>갈 곳을 잃었네요 <br>내 마음 그리움들 가득 채워 <br>하늘에 기도하면 <br>볼 수가 있을까요 <br>사랑하는 사람에게 <br>사랑 받는 일이 <br>이리도 힘든가요 <br>잠 못 드는 밤 밤 밤 <br>사무치는 맘 맘 맘 <br>슬픈 오늘 밤 밤 밤 <br>부서지는 맘 맘 맘 <br>]]></content><category term="Kei (러블리즈)" label="Kei (러블리즈)"/><category term="별과 해" label="별과 해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서영도_일렉트릭_앙상블/난_별_Feat_YUL/</id><title>서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블 - 난 별 (Feat. YUL) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:14:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:14:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EC%98%81%EB%8F%84_%EC%9D%BC%EB%A0%89%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AD_%EC%95%99%EC%83%81%EB%B8%94/%EB%82%9C_%EB%B3%84_Feat_YUL/" title="서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블 - 난 별 (Feat. YUL) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모든 일의 처음에 시작된 <br>정직한 마음을 잃어갈 때 <br>포기했던 일들을 <br>신념으로 날 세울 때 <br>별처럼 저 별처럼 <br>삶과 죽음의 답 없는 <br>끝없는 질문에 휩싸인 채 또 <br>아무것도 하지 않는 일에 빠져 <br>혼자 괴로울 때조차 <br>별처럼 저 별처럼 <br>난 별 <br>넌 별 <br>먼 별 <br>빛나는 별 <br>살아가며 하는 서로의 말들 <br>그 오해들 속에 <br>좀 참아가며 이해해야 하는 <br>시간들 속에 <br>원하든 원치 않든 <br>나와 다른 많은 사람들 속에 <br>저 별처럼 <br>우주의 한 부분으로 살며 <br>믿는 대로 생긴다는 <br>믿음을 잃지 않았을 때 오는 <br>빛나는 결과들에 감사하며 <br>별처럼 저 별처럼 <br>난 별 <br>빛나는 별 <br>살아가며 하는 서로의 말들 <br>그 오해들 속에 <br>좀 참아가며 이해해야 하는 <br>시간들 속에 <br>살아가며 하는 서로의 말들 <br>그 오해들 속에 <br>좀 참아가며 이해해야 하는 <br>시간들 속에 <br>원하든 원치 않든 <br>나와 다른 많은 사람들 속에 <br>사는 별처럼 <br>나 너 지금 이곳 다시 <br>별처럼 <br>저 별처럼 <br>별처럼 <br>저 별처럼 <br>]]></content><category term="서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블" label="서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블"/><category term="난 별 (Feat. YUL)" label="난 별 (Feat. YUL)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서영도_일렉트릭_앙상블/어둠_Feat_백현진/</id><title>서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블 - 어둠 (Feat. 백현진) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:14:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:14:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EC%98%81%EB%8F%84_%EC%9D%BC%EB%A0%89%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AD_%EC%95%99%EC%83%81%EB%B8%94/%EC%96%B4%EB%91%A0_Feat_%EB%B0%B1%ED%98%84%EC%A7%84/" title="서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블 - 어둠 (Feat. 백현진) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어둠 속에서 나 홀로 <br>부엉이 소리만 듣다가 왔지 <br>어둠 속에서 나 홀로 <br>부엉이 소리만 듣다가 왔지 <br>저 어둠 속에서 나 홀로 <br>부엉이 소리만 듣다가 왔지 <br>그 어둠 속에서 나 홀로 <br>나 홀로 <br>어둠 속에서 둘이서 <br>부엉이 소리만 듣다가 왔지 <br>어둠 속에서 둘이서 <br>부엉이 소리만 듣다가 왔지 <br>그 어둠 속에서 둘이서 <br>종달새 소리도 듣다가 왔지 <br>그 어둠 속에서 둘이서 <br>둘이서 둘이서 둘이서 둘이서 <br>]]></content><category term="서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블" label="서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블"/><category term="어둠 (Feat. 백현진)" label="어둠 (Feat. 백현진)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서영도_일렉트릭_앙상블/그래도_희망_Feat_나찰_Of_가리온_Always_There_박주원/</id><title>서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블 - 그래도 희망 (Feat. 나찰 Of 가리온, Always There, 박주원) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:14:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:14:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EC%98%81%EB%8F%84_%EC%9D%BC%EB%A0%89%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AD_%EC%95%99%EC%83%81%EB%B8%94/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%98%EB%8F%84_%ED%9D%AC%EB%A7%9D_Feat_%EB%82%98%EC%B0%B0_Of_%EA%B0%80%EB%A6%AC%EC%98%A8_Always_There_%EB%B0%95%EC%A3%BC%EC%9B%90/" title="서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블 - 그래도 희망 (Feat. 나찰 Of 가리온, Always There, 박주원) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[막지 마 내 앞길은 내가 챙겨 <br>갈 길은 정해 놓은 걸 됐어 <br>횃불이 시작된 하나의 <br>작은 불씨 큰 그림 <br>거짓말과 고난 겪어내 보자 <br>자자 드러나 진실 <br>매몰 현장은 너와 나의 소망 <br>계속 이겨 내야 해 답은 <br>나아가는 것밖에 <br>내 안 부정적인 것들이 방해 못 하게 <br>내 인생을 누가 책임져 <br>이제 믿음을 줘 넌 난 준비돼있어 <br>있어 있어 이 시대의 값어치 <br>실패에 가려진 것 <br>우리들 손안에 잣대를 가졌지 <br>촛불 하나둘셋 <br>다시 일어난다면 그건 실패가 아니지 <br>우리가 가져야 할 건 <br>믿음과 확신이지 <br>다시 볼 태양은 하나 <br>믿음과 사랑 전부 다 <br>삐걱거린 세상은 <br>이 시대의 가치야 겁 없지 <br>Never give up 절대 포기하지 마 <br>모든 건 시간이 해결해 줄 테니까 <br>타협은 지나가는 것들 <br>거짓들을 우려하는 것뿐 <br>거친 의지는 더욱더 <br>내 앞길에 깃든 무너지는 거품 <br>여전히 여전해 always there right <br>어리다고 할 수 없는 나이 <br>상식과 정의라는 것들 무겁고도 중해 <br>나인 숫자에 불과하니 변함없겠지 <br>밑줄 친 시간들이 너무 많어 <br>기억할 페이지 역사의 순간 걸었잖어 <br>한순간 풀어진 문제집 <br>무너진 그때 니 <br>이름은 여기서 다시 <br>써 보내란 말이잖어 <br>끝까지 두들긴다면 언젠가 열려 <br>모두 꽃피우는 과정 당장은 멀어 <br>보여도 놓여진 상황에 끝까지 열심히 <br>자신을 속이는 일 없이 움직이길 <br>주파수는 다름을 인정하지 그 다름은 <br>잘못된 결과 틀린 건 아니었어 <br>그 다음은 <br>우린 계속 가야지 늘 그랬듯이 <br>이제는 확신하니 절대로 안 숨지 <br>같이 같이 가자고 <br>그래 맞지 다시 말하고 <br>그 말이 가진 역사고 <br>그날에 우린 하나고 <br>여태 잘해왔어 그대로 가면 돼 <br>내가 받은 모든 믿음 <br>포기 안 해 약속해 <br>]]></content><category term="서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블" label="서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블"/><category term="그래도 희망 (Feat. 나찰 Of 가리온, Always There, 박주원)" label="그래도 희망 (Feat. 나찰 Of 가리온, Always There, 박주원)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서영도_일렉트릭_앙상블/무사고_Feat_조정희/</id><title>서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블 - 무사고 (Feat. 조정희) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:14:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:14:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EC%98%81%EB%8F%84_%EC%9D%BC%EB%A0%89%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AD_%EC%95%99%EC%83%81%EB%B8%94/%EB%AC%B4%EC%82%AC%EA%B3%A0_Feat_%EC%A1%B0%EC%A0%95%ED%9D%AC/" title="서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블 - 무사고 (Feat. 조정희) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그동안 살아오면서 지나온 많은 <br>슬프고 아픈 사연들 잊지 못합니다 <br>매일매일 빌어요 무사하자고 <br>내 가족 친구 모두들 안녕하자고 <br>하지만 오늘도 어제처럼 그렇네요 <br>힘들게 하루하루 버텨가면서 <br>제발 아무 일도 생기지 않길 바래요 <br>행복은 큰 것에 <br>있지 않다는 걸 알잖아요 <br>작은 것에 있어요 <br>약속 하나만 해요 우리 모두가 <br>사랑하며 살아요 그렇게 살아요 <br>누군가 말했죠 사는 게 중요해요 <br>포기하지 말고 살아가야 해요 <br>이 악물고 우리의 삶의 끈 놓지 마요 <br>그대여 아무 걱정 말라는 노랫말처럼 <br>이겨내고 살아요 <br>약속 하나만 해요 우리 모두가 <br>사랑하며 살아요 그렇게 살아요 <br>잊진 말아요 가슴에 묻어요 <br>결코 잊을 순 없잖아요 <br>해가 지네요 내일이 와요 <br>무사하게 살길 바래요 <br>]]></content><category term="서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블" label="서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블"/><category term="무사고 (Feat. 조정희)" label="무사고 (Feat. 조정희)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서영도_일렉트릭_앙상블/가물거리는_세상_Feat_백현진/</id><title>서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블 - 가물거리는 세상 (Feat. 백현진) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:14:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:14:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EC%98%81%EB%8F%84_%EC%9D%BC%EB%A0%89%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AD_%EC%95%99%EC%83%81%EB%B8%94/%EA%B0%80%EB%AC%BC%EA%B1%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81_Feat_%EB%B0%B1%ED%98%84%EC%A7%84/" title="서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블 - 가물거리는 세상 (Feat. 백현진) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새벽 아침 점심 저녁 그리고 밤 <br>빛 어둠 찰나 우리가 <br>갑자기 받은 무거운 소식 <br>너와 내가 겪는 일들 <br>누군 떠나고 누구는 죽어서 <br>기억이 계속 헛돈다 <br>볕이 좋은 날에는 <br>볕을 찾아 앉아서 <br>기억을 멈춰본다 <br>가능한 한 아무것도 <br>생각하지 않도록 <br>순간을 살아본다 <br>어둡고 하얗고 노랗고 푸르고 <br>희미한 선명한 가물거리는 세상 <br>골목길에서 꽤 오랫동안 <br>부서진 계단에 앉아 <br>며칠 전 오후 산에서 본 <br>꿩 한 마릴 생각한다 <br>풀숲으로 사라지는 <br>꿩을 가만 보다가 <br>석양을 맞이한 난 <br>가능한 한 아무 것도 <br>생각하지 않도록 <br>순간을 살아본다 <br>어둡고 하얗고 노랗고 푸르고 <br>희미한 선명한 가물거리는 세상 <br>어둡고 하얗고 노랗고 푸르고 <br>희미한 선명한 가물거리는 세상 <br>어둡고 하얗고 노랗고 푸르고 <br>희미한 선명한 가물거리는 세상 <br>]]></content><category term="서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블" label="서영도 일렉트릭 앙상블"/><category term="가물거리는 세상 (Feat. 백현진)" label="가물거리는 세상 (Feat. 백현진)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/손선/작은거울/</id><title>손선 - 작은거울 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:14:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:14:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%90%EC%84%A0/%EC%9E%91%EC%9D%80%EA%B1%B0%EC%9A%B8/" title="손선 - 작은거울 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[작은 거울속엔 희미하게 웃으며 <br>애써 미소를 짓는 <br>한 여자 얼굴이 있네 <br>자신을 바라 보는 이 순간 <br>모든 걸 잊고 눈앞에 보이는 모습엔 <br>조금 전 절망이 무색해 <br>여자의 얼굴에 조금씩 번지는 <br>곧 맺혀버린 물방울 <br>손톱에 물든 진한 분홍색 <br>슥 얼굴을 훑네 <br>다시 또렷해진 얼굴엔 <br>지나간 세월 또 니 그림자 <br>천천히 천천히 미소를 짓네 <br>아무에게 보일 수 없는 <br>슬픈 모습을 모두다 감추고 <br>천천히 천천히 미소를 짓네 <br>엹은 먼지가 묻고 손자국 난 거울은 <br>아직 쓸만한 지 여과없이 <br>여자의 얼굴 비추네 <br>다시는 없을 작은 거울 속 <br>여자의 모습 눈앞에 보이는 모습엔 <br>조금전 절망이 무색해 <br>여자의 얼굴에 조금씩 번지는 <br>곧 맺혀버린 물방울 <br>손톱에 물든 진한 분홍색 <br>슥 얼굴을 훑네 <br>다시 또렷해진 얼굴엔 <br>지나간 세월 또 니 그림자 <br>천천히 천천히 미소를 짓네 <br>아무에게 보일 수 없는 <br>슬픈 모습을 모두다 감추고 <br>천천히 천천히 미소를 짓네 <br>천천히 천천히 천천히 <br>미소를 짓네 <br>]]></content><category term="손선" label="손선"/><category term="작은거울" label="작은거울"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/그리다/Im_in_Love_with_You_Feat_구현모/</id><title>그리다 - I`m in Love with You (Feat. 구현모) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:14:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:14:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EB%8B%A4/Im_in_Love_with_You_Feat_%EA%B5%AC%ED%98%84%EB%AA%A8/" title="그리다 - I`m in Love with You (Feat. 구현모) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 시간되나요 <br>별일은 아니지만 <br>애매했던 우리 사이도 <br>이젠 끝내고 싶어요 <br>그댈 위해 준비해요 <br>그토록 기다린 오늘 <br>매일 그대 생각에 나 <br>아무것도 할 수 없었죠 <br>그댈 잃을 까봐 <br>밤새 고민했죠 <br>내 맘 어떻게 전해야 할지 <br>나 바보 같아도 <br>그대만 있으면 <br>I'm in love with you <br>Fall in love with you <br>난 그대만 있으면 좋아요 <br>만나 볼래요 <br>심장이 떨리네요 그대 <br>my love <br>나 이런 감정 처음이에요 <br>이렇게 떨린 적 없죠 <br>순간의 떨림 아니에요 나 <br>오랫동안 지켜온 거죠 <br>그댈 잃을 까봐 <br>밤새 고민했죠 <br>내 맘 어떻게 전해야 할지 <br>나 바보 같아도 <br>그대만 있다면 <br>I'm in love with you <br>Fall in love with you <br>난 그대만 있으면 좋아요 <br>만나 볼래요 <br>심장이 떨리네요 그대 <br>I'm in love with you <br>Fall in love with you <br>난 그대만 있으면 행복해 <br>사귀어 봐요 우리 시작해요 <br>그대만 좋다면 <br>my love <br>]]></content><category term="그리다" label="그리다"/><category term="I`m in Love with You (Feat. 구현모)" label="I`m in Love with You (Feat. 구현모)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/그리다/아이야_Feat_구현모/</id><title>그리다 - 아이야 (Feat. 구현모) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:14:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:14:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EB%8B%A4/%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC_Feat_%EA%B5%AC%ED%98%84%EB%AA%A8/" title="그리다 - 아이야 (Feat. 구현모) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무 것도 할 수가 없어 <br>너의 아픔 그 고통 <br>가슴이 뛰고 숨이 가빠져 <br>그저 멍하니 <br>널 만나지도 못했는데 널 <br>너무 보고 싶은데 <br>기다려야 하는 그 시간들 <br>내겐 너무 힘겨워 <br>아이야 널 사랑해 <br>너의 그 모든 것을 <br>아이야 널 사랑해 <br>두려움 없는 사랑 <br>널 만나지도 못했는데 널 <br>너무 보고 싶은데 <br>기다려야 하는 그 시간들 <br>내겐 너무 힘들어 <br>어쩜 이 세상이 더 힘들지 몰라 <br>그래 알아 조금만 기운을 내 <br>널 기다리는 친구들이 있잖아 <br>함께 하자 우리 함께 <br>아이야 널 사랑해 <br>아이야 널 사랑해 <br>너의 그 모든 것을 <br>아이야 널 사랑해 <br>두려움 없는 사랑 <br>아이야 널 사랑해 <br>너의 그 모든 것을 <br>아이야 널 사랑해 <br>두려움 없는 사랑 <br>두려움 없는 사랑 <br>두려움 없는 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="그리다" label="그리다"/><category term="아이야 (Feat. 구현모)" label="아이야 (Feat. 구현모)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Serengeti/Cracks_And_Creases/</id><title>Serengeti - Cracks And Creases - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:15:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:15:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Serengeti/Cracks_And_Creases/" title="Serengeti - Cracks And Creases - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Show me where the sun stands to the dark <br>Show me where to find my buried heart <br>Cause I can the traces in the faces that you left <br>And I can see your colors, they're faded, faded, faded <br>In cracks and creases, these little pieces of my mind <br><br>Bits and pieces of you everywhere <br>And everything I've ever known <br>I feel , saturated <br>You come and go, you come and go, you come and go <br>Like a shadow in the shadow <br><br>We walked on the beach at midnight <br>I remember we went to a theme park <br>Storms did not hide the harvest moon <br>Matching clothes and matching shoes <br>We didn't think about the lightning <br>We got home well after midnight <br>I dragged your body into the sea <br><br>I let you be there's bass <br>In cracks and there's snares creases there's rhythm <br>These little there's drums pieces on my mind there's love <br><br>Bits and pieces of you everywhere <br>And everything I've ever known <br>I feel , saturated <br>You come and go, you come and go, you come and go <br>Like a shadow in the shadow <br><br>Do you mind <br><br>There's bass in cracks and there's snares creases there's rhythm <br>These little there's drums pieces on my mind there's love <br><br>Bits and pieces of you everywhere <br>And everything I've ever known <br>I feel , saturated <br>You come and go, you come and go, you come and go <br>Like a shadow in the shadow <br>In cracks and creases <br>These little pieces]]></content><category term="Serengeti" label="Serengeti"/><category term="Cracks And Creases" label="Cracks And Creases"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Serengeti/Good_Guy/</id><title>Serengeti - Good Guy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:15:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:15:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Serengeti/Good_Guy/" title="Serengeti - Good Guy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I will never call you back <br>So I wouldn't hold your breath <br>But I think that you're a good guy <br>There will always be a goodbye <br>Maybe I'll see you round <br>Maybe I won't <br>But I think that you're a good guy <br>So you don't have to say goodbye <br><br>I see lovers in love, speaking in sign language <br>Scurry to the crib cause they be bangin' <br>And I'm hanging but not a vagrant <br>Beard on my face cause I go through changes <br>I thought it would be contagious <br>Look it's been love all through the ages <br>How come I can't even say shit <br>Can't tell why I even say this <br>Can it just be basic Face it <br>Faces, hard embraces <br>Lovers in love fixing up they places <br>Patience they say, it ain't races <br>Left behind they pick up the paces <br>When I look at you all I see is aces <br>Please babydoll don't make me chase you <br>Please babydoll I need something to stay true <br><br>I will never call you back <br>So I wouldn't hold your breath <br>But I think that you're a good guy <br>There will always be a goodbye <br>Maybe I'll see you round <br>Maybe I won't <br>But I think that you're a good guy <br>So you don't have to say goodbye <br><br>Oh oh oh oh Hey x2 <br>But I think that you're a good guy <br>I hate saying goodbye <br><br>I see lovers in love going to a concert <br>Scurry to the crib cause they 'bout to get work <br>Take off they shirt, live and direct <br>Please don't make me stay for the whole set <br>Beard on my face don't want the raincheck <br>My life's been shit back, I'm sound and complex <br>Asked me to change and I'm feeling reflect that <br>Go for pizza, maybe a pita <br>Margarita, bought you a cat look like a cheetah <br>If you smoke weed then I'll get you reefer <br>Just want to meet you <br>Pizza pizza, feed your cheetah <br>See you're cheap but I'm a believer <br>Buy you Tivas, go to Ibiza <br>Maybe St Lucia maybe St Riza <br>See momma mia <br>Have some sangrias <br><br>Love is just a crazy kind of motion <br>Never ending tale oh I suppose <br>That it's sometimes worth all the commotion <br>I'll get it right next time I promise get it right next time <br>Love is just a crazy kind of feeling <br>I know the water's warm but it feels cold <br>And everybody says that this gets easier <br>But that gets old <br><br>Yeah <br>I will never call you back <br>uh oh uh oh uh oh uh oh <br>So I wouldn't hold your breath <br>But I think that you're a good guy <br>I'm a good guy, good <br>There will always be a goodbye <br>Maybe I'll see you round <br>uh oh uh oh uh oh uh oh <br>A nice day, a beautiful day we'll have it <br>Maybe I won't <br>But I think that you're a good guy <br>So you don't have to say goodbye <br><br>Oh oh oh oh hey x2 <br>But I think that you're a good guy <br>I hate saying goodbye <br>Oh oh oh oh hey x2 <br>Then why does it have to be a goodbye <br>But I think that you're a good guy <br>Just give me one try]]></content><category term="Serengeti" label="Serengeti"/><category term="Good Guy" label="Good Guy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/천주교_수원교구_청소년국_초등부_어부들/아름다운_마음들이_모여서/</id><title>천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들 - 아름다운 마음들이 모여서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:15:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:15:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%9C%EC%A3%BC%EA%B5%90_%EC%88%98%EC%9B%90%EA%B5%90%EA%B5%AC_%EC%B2%AD%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84%EA%B5%AD_%EC%B4%88%EB%93%B1%EB%B6%80_%EC%96%B4%EB%B6%80%EB%93%A4/%EC%95%84%EB%A6%84%EB%8B%A4%EC%9A%B4_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C%EB%93%A4%EC%9D%B4_%EB%AA%A8%EC%97%AC%EC%84%9C/" title="천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들 - 아름다운 마음들이 모여서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아름다운 마음들이 모여서 <br>주의 은혜 나누며 <br>예수님을 따라 사랑 해야지 <br>우리 서로 사랑해 <br>하느님이 가르쳐준 한가지 <br>네 이웃을 네 몸과 같이 <br>미움 다툼 시기 질투 버리고 <br>우리 서로 사랑해 <br>이 다음에 예수님을 만나면 <br>우린 뭐라 말할까 <br>그때에는 부끄러움 없어야지 <br>우리 서로 사랑해 <br>하느님이 가르쳐준 한가지 <br>네 이웃을 네 몸과 같이 <br>미움 다툼 시기 질투 버리고 <br>우리 서로 사랑해 <br>내가 너희를 사랑한 것처럼 <br>서로 사랑하여라 <br>예수님을 닮아 살아가야지 <br>우리 서로 사랑해 <br>하느님이 가르쳐준 한가지 <br>네 이웃을 네 몸과 같이 <br>미움 다툼 시기 질투 버리고 <br>우리 서로 사랑해 <br>우리 서로 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들" label="천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들"/><category term="아름다운 마음들이 모여서" label="아름다운 마음들이 모여서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/천주교_수원교구_청소년국_초등부_어부들/성모송/</id><title>천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들 - 성모송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:15:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:15:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%9C%EC%A3%BC%EA%B5%90_%EC%88%98%EC%9B%90%EA%B5%90%EA%B5%AC_%EC%B2%AD%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84%EA%B5%AD_%EC%B4%88%EB%93%B1%EB%B6%80_%EC%96%B4%EB%B6%80%EB%93%A4/%EC%84%B1%EB%AA%A8%EC%86%A1/" title="천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들 - 성모송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[은총이 가득하신 <br>마리아님 기뻐하소서 <br>주님께서 함께 계시니 <br>여인 중에 복되시며 <br>태중의 아들 예수님 또한 <br>복되시나이다 <br>천주의 성모 마리아님 <br>이제와 저희 죽을 때에 <br>저희 죄인을 위하여 <br>빌어주소서 <br>은총이 가득하신 <br>마리아님 기뻐하소서 <br>주님께서 함께 계시니 <br>여인 중에 복되시며 <br>태중의 아들 예수님 또한 <br>복되시나이다 <br>천주의 성모 마리아님 <br>이제와 저희 죽을 때에 <br>저희 죄인을 위하여 <br>빌어주소서 <br>빌어주소서 <br>]]></content><category term="천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들" label="천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들"/><category term="성모송" label="성모송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/천주교_수원교구_청소년국_초등부_어부들/너와_나/</id><title>천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들 - 너와 나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:15:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:15:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%9C%EC%A3%BC%EA%B5%90_%EC%88%98%EC%9B%90%EA%B5%90%EA%B5%AC_%EC%B2%AD%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84%EA%B5%AD_%EC%B4%88%EB%93%B1%EB%B6%80_%EC%96%B4%EB%B6%80%EB%93%A4/%EB%84%88%EC%99%80_%EB%82%98/" title="천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들 - 너와 나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[랄랄라 <br>우리 여기 다같이 모여 <br>반가운 인사 안녕 <br>떨리는 두 손 잡고 서로를 보며 <br>미소를 지어봐요 <br>랄랄라 <br>지금 우리 하나 둘 셋 넷 <br>음악에 맞추어 <br>머리를 흔들흔들 <br>어깨를 으쓱으쓱 <br>신나게 즐겨요 함께 춤춰요 <br>예수님 손 꼭 잡고 <br>살짝 눈 맞춤 할까요 <br>빙글빙글 주님과 함께 춤춰요 <br>예수님 손 꼭 잡고 <br>살짝 눈 맞춤 할까요 <br>빙글빙글 주님과 춤춰요 <br>랄랄라 <br>우리 여기 다같이 모여 <br>반가운 인사 안녕 <br>떨리는 두 손 잡고 서로를 보며 <br>미소를 지어봐요 <br>랄랄라 <br>지금 우리 하나 둘 셋 넷 <br>음악에 맞추어 <br>머리를 흔들흔들 <br>어깨를 으쓱으쓱 <br>신나게 즐겨요 함께 춤춰요 <br>예수님 손 꼭 잡고 <br>살짝 눈 맞춤 할까요 <br>빙글빙글 주님과 함께 춤춰요 <br>예수님 손 꼭 잡고 <br>살짝 눈 맞춤 할까요 <br>빙글빙글 주님과 춤춰요 <br>]]></content><category term="천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들" label="천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들"/><category term="너와 나" label="너와 나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/천주교_수원교구_청소년국_초등부_어부들/우리_마음/</id><title>천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들 - 우리 마음 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:15:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:15:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%9C%EC%A3%BC%EA%B5%90_%EC%88%98%EC%9B%90%EA%B5%90%EA%B5%AC_%EC%B2%AD%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84%EA%B5%AD_%EC%B4%88%EB%93%B1%EB%B6%80_%EC%96%B4%EB%B6%80%EB%93%A4/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C/" title="천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들 - 우리 마음 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 서로 두 손을 잡고 <br>한발 두발 걸어가면 <br>하느님 말씀 ON 하느님 사랑 IN <br>우리 마음에 <br>우리 맘속에 내려온 <br>하느님 말씀이 큰 빛이 되어 <br>너와나 걷는 이 길을 <br>가득히 채워 비춰주시네 <br>랄랄라 <br>그 빛을 따라 걸어나가면 Ye <br>하느님 사랑 만나게 되리 <br>우리 서로 두 손을 잡고 <br>한발 두발 걸어가면 <br>하느님 말씀 ON 하느님 사랑 IN <br>우리 마음에 <br>우리 맘속에 내려온 <br>하느님 말씀이 큰 빛이 되어 <br>너와나 걷는 이 길을 <br>가득히 채워 비춰주시네 <br>랄랄라 <br>그 빛을 따라 걸어나가면 Ye <br>하느님 사랑 만나게 되리 <br>우리 서로 두 손을 잡고 <br>한발 두발 걸어가면 <br>하느님 말씀 ON 하느님 사랑 IN <br>우리 마음에 <br>우리 마음에 <br>]]></content><category term="천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들" label="천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들"/><category term="우리 마음" label="우리 마음"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/천주교_수원교구_청소년국_초등부_어부들/내_마음_그_사랑/</id><title>천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들 - 내 마음 그 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:15:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:15:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%9C%EC%A3%BC%EA%B5%90_%EC%88%98%EC%9B%90%EA%B5%90%EA%B5%AC_%EC%B2%AD%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84%EA%B5%AD_%EC%B4%88%EB%93%B1%EB%B6%80_%EC%96%B4%EB%B6%80%EB%93%A4/%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C_%EA%B7%B8_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들 - 내 마음 그 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나를 감싸는 주님 따스한 손길 <br>사랑으로 내 맘 채워 주시네 <br>마음 가득히 피어난 주의 향기 <br>한아름 안겨진 주님 사랑 <br>때론 힘들고 외로울 때에 <br>마음이 너무 아플 때 <br>두 손 모아 기도해 <br>인자한 주님 나를 위로해주시니 <br>내 마음은 기쁨으로 가득 차 <br>그 사랑 나누고 싶어 <br>때론 힘들고 외로울 때에 <br>마음이 너무 아플 때 <br>두 손 모아 기도해 <br>인자한 주님 나를 위로해주시니 <br>내 마음은 기쁨으로 가득 차 <br>그 사랑 나누고 싶어 <br>나를 감싸는 주님 따스한 손길 <br>사랑으로 내 맘 채워 주시네 <br>마음 가득히 피어난 주의 향기 <br>한아름 안겨진 주님 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들" label="천주교 수원교구 청소년국 초등부 어부들"/><category term="내 마음 그 사랑" label="내 마음 그 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소년공화국_Boys_Republic/流れる星に花束を___Nagareru_Hoshini_Hanatabao_흐르는_별에_꽃다발을_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>소년공화국 (Boys Republic) - 流れる星に花束を / Nagareru Hoshini Hanatabao (흐르는 별에 꽃다발을) (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:15:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:15:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84%EA%B3%B5%ED%99%94%EA%B5%AD_Boys_Republic/%E6%B5%81%E3%82%8C%E3%82%8B%E6%98%9F%E3%81%AB%E8%8A%B1%E6%9D%9F%E3%82%92___Nagareru_Hoshini_Hanatabao_%ED%9D%90%EB%A5%B4%EB%8A%94_%EB%B3%84%EC%97%90_%EA%BD%83%EB%8B%A4%EB%B0%9C%EC%9D%84_Acoustic_Ver/" title="소년공화국 (Boys Republic) - 流れる星に花束を / Nagareru Hoshini Hanatabao (흐르는 별에 꽃다발을) (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Moshimo anata no nani ka o hitotsu <br>wakeaeru to shi tara <br>boku wa itami o erabu daro u <br>kakaesugiteru nimotsu o boku ni <br>azuke te kure ta nara <br>kitto kokoro goto karuku naru kara <br>sekai ga anata o <br>kizutsukeru yoru mo aru <br>soredemo mae o mui te iru anata ni <br>boku ga dekiru koto <br>sono kotae wa tada hitotsu <br>anata o omou koto <br>tada sore shika deki nai kedo <br>nagareru hoshi ni <br>kasaneru omoi <br>anata no sono negai ga <br>kanai masu yo ni <br>anata no yume wa <br>anata dake no mono <br>tatoe toku hanare te mo <br>itsumo gawa ni iru <br>boku no omoi wa ima <br>koko ni oi te oko u <br>hanataba totomoni <br>dare ka no koe ni <br>fui ni kizutsuki <br>kanashiku natta toki <br>boku ga tonari de sasae te ageru kara <br>sekai ga bokura o <br>hikihanasu yoru mo aru <br>miage ta sora ga <br>ni nin o tsunage te <br>ashibaya ni mata <br>anata no moto e mukau <br>yatto kizui ta kono omoi ga <br>honmono da kara <br>tatoeba ai mo sono yasashi sa mo <br>amarini utsukushiku te <br>me ni wa mie nai <br>anata ga boku ni oshie te kure ta <br>aisuru koto no imi mo itami mo subete <br>sonna anata no koto <br>mamorinuku koto o <br>ima koko de chikao u <br>moshimo anata no namida <br>ame no yo ni <br>hakanaku hike te mo <br>nan do mo tsutsumikomi <br>kokoro aru sonna basho <br>atatameru dakara <br>moichido waratte iyo u <br>furidashi ta ame yagate nakiyami <br>tsukiakari ga terashidasu <br>bokura ni nin o <br>doko made mo arui te iko u <br>nagareru hoshi ni kasaneru omoi <br>anata no sono negai ga <br>kanai masu yo ni <br>anata no yume wa anata dake no mono <br>tatoe toku hanare te mo <br>itsumo gawa ni iru <br>boku no omoi wa ima <br>koko ni oi te oko u <br>tsubomi datta bokura mo itsuka <br>konna kaze ni kirei ni sake ru koto o <br>wasure nai de hoshii kara <br>hanataba totomoni <br>]]></content><category term="소년공화국 (Boys Republic)" label="소년공화국 (Boys Republic)"/><category term="流れる星に花束を / Nagareru Hoshini Hanatabao (흐르는 별에 꽃다발을) (Acoustic Ver.)" label="流れる星に花束を / Nagareru Hoshini Hanatabao (흐르는 별에 꽃다발을) (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소년공화국_Boys_Republic/Beautiful/</id><title>소년공화국 (Boys Republic) - Beautiful - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:15:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:15:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84%EA%B3%B5%ED%99%94%EA%B5%AD_Boys_Republic/Beautiful/" title="소년공화국 (Boys Republic) - Beautiful - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sagashite ta Beautiful <br>hibi no naka ni afure te <br>itsu demo I'll be with you <br>mirai e to tsuzuku <br>michi o arui te ki ta kedo <br>bokura wa mada <br>nani ka o sagashimotome <br>kitto sore wa mo <br>te ni ire teru kamo shire nai <br>yume ya kibo to chigau keredo <br>kotae dake ga subete ja naku te <br>tanoshimu koto ga ima o <br>kaeru kara shinji te susumo u <br>Get your style We go <br>sagashite ta Beautiful <br>hibi no naka ni afure te <br>bokura o ima mo tsuyoku mamoru kara <br>machigau koto mo aru sa <br>kokai shi nai yo ni <br>nan do demo iu yo <br>bokura wa ashita o iki te ku <br>tomawari no kazu <br>omoide ga aru <br>muda nante nai taisetsu na <br>Cry &amp; Smile <br>so donnani michi ga kurai yoru demo <br>Where is beautiful <br>you know <br>Life is beautiful <br>we go <br>kimi o terashitsuzukeru yo <br>So We'll be stars <br>tsurai toki koso warao u Yeah <br>me ippai ni doko made mo <br>bokura ni shika miserare nai <br>sono saki e iko u <br>Get your style We go <br>sagashite ta Beautiful <br>hibi no naka ni afure te <br>bokura o ima mo tsuyoku mamoru kara <br>machigau koto mo aru sa <br>kokai shi nai yo ni <br>nan do demo iu yo <br>bokura wa ashita o iki te ku <br>nagashi ta namida no kazu wa <br>kesshite uragira nai <br>kotae o michibiku kibo ni naru <br>yukkuri de ii yo <br>doko ni mo ika nai kara <br>itsu demo I'll be with you <br>sagashite ta Beautiful <br>hibi no naka ni afure te <br>bokura o ima mo tsuyoku mamoru kara <br>machigau koto mo aru sa <br>kokai shi nai yo ni <br>nan do demo iu yo <br>bokura wa ashita o iki te ku <br>]]></content><category term="소년공화국 (Boys Republic)" label="소년공화국 (Boys Republic)"/><category term="Beautiful" label="Beautiful"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소년공화국_Boys_Republic/流れる星に花束を___Nagareru_Hoshini_Hanatabao_흐르는_별에_꽃다발을/</id><title>소년공화국 (Boys Republic) - 流れる星に花束を / Nagareru Hoshini Hanatabao (흐르는 별에 꽃다발을) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:15:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:15:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84%EA%B3%B5%ED%99%94%EA%B5%AD_Boys_Republic/%E6%B5%81%E3%82%8C%E3%82%8B%E6%98%9F%E3%81%AB%E8%8A%B1%E6%9D%9F%E3%82%92___Nagareru_Hoshini_Hanatabao_%ED%9D%90%EB%A5%B4%EB%8A%94_%EB%B3%84%EC%97%90_%EA%BD%83%EB%8B%A4%EB%B0%9C%EC%9D%84/" title="소년공화국 (Boys Republic) - 流れる星に花束を / Nagareru Hoshini Hanatabao (흐르는 별에 꽃다발을) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Moshimo anata no nani ka o hitotsu <br>wakeaeru to shi tara <br>boku wa itami o erabu daro u <br>kakaesugiteru nimotsu o boku ni <br>azuke te kure ta nara <br>kitto kokoro goto karuku naru kara <br>sekai ga anata o kizutsukeru <br>yoru mo aru <br>soredemo mae o mui te iru anata ni <br>boku ga dekiru koto sono kotae <br>wa tada hitotsu <br>anata o omou koto tada sore <br>shika deki nai kedo <br>nagareru hoshi ni kasaneru omoi <br>anata no sono negai ga kanai <br>masu yo ni <br>anata no yume wa <br>anata dake no mono <br>tatoe toku hanare te mo itsumo <br>gawa ni iru <br>boku no omoi wa ima koko ni oi <br>te oko u <br>hanataba totomoni <br>dare ka no koe ni fui ni <br>kizutsuki kanashiku natta toki <br>boku ga tonari de sasae te <br>ageru kara <br>sekai ga bokura o hikihanasu <br>yoru mo aru <br>miage ta sora ga ni nin o <br>tsunage te <br>ashibaya ni mata anata no <br>moto e mukau <br>yatto kizui ta kono omoi ga <br>honmono da kara <br>tatoeba ai mo sono yasashi sa mo <br>amarini utsukushiku te me ni wa <br>mie nai <br>anata ga boku ni oshie te kure ta <br>aisuru koto no imi mo <br>itami mo subete <br>sonna anata no koto <br>mamorinuku koto o <br>ima koko de chikao u <br>moshimo anata no <br>namida ame no yo ni <br>hakanaku hike te mo <br>nan do mo tsutsumikomi <br>kokoro aru sonna basho <br>atatameru dakara <br>moichido waratte iyo u <br>furidashi ta ame yagate nakiyami <br>tsukiakari ga terashidasu bokura <br>ni nin o <br>doko made mo arui te iko u <br>nagareru hoshi ni kasaneru omoi <br>anata no sono negai ga kanai <br>masu yo ni <br>anata no yume wa <br>anata dake no mono <br>tatoe toku hanare te mo itsumo <br>gawa ni iru <br>boku no omoi wa ima koko ni oi <br>te oko u <br>tsubomi datta bokura mo itsuka <br>konna kaze ni kirei ni sake ru <br>koto o <br>wasure nai de hoshii kara <br>hanataba totomoni <br>]]></content><category term="소년공화국 (Boys Republic)" label="소년공화국 (Boys Republic)"/><category term="流れる星に花束を / Nagareru Hoshini Hanatabao (흐르는 별에 꽃다발을)" label="流れる星に花束を / Nagareru Hoshini Hanatabao (흐르는 별에 꽃다발을)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/boku_no_lyric_no_bouyomi/SKYs_the_limit/</id><title>boku no lyric no bouyomi - SKY`s the limit - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:15:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:15:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/boku_no_lyric_no_bouyomi/SKYs_the_limit/" title="boku no lyric no bouyomi - SKY`s the limit - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sunrise 히카리츠츠마레테 <br>Being alive, being vivid <br>It'll be better for your life <br>츠요쿠우츠쿠시쿠와타시가카가야쿠 <br>We are beautiful <br>시아와세나히비 <br>에가키다시타미라이토 <br>하나야카사가츠츠미코무 <br>하나타바가마우마치노나카 <br>도노잇슌모와타시와와타시 <br>타다 summer color 미니마톳테 <br>아리노마마데마타와랏타 <br>코노마마노와타시다케 <br>아이오 아이오 아사노카게니카쿠레 <br>Party time 마다네오와라나이 <br>에가오미치테 <br>코레와킷토모우운메이 <br>Sunrise 히카리츠츠마레테 <br>Being alive, being vivid <br>It'll be better for your life <br>츠요쿠우츠쿠시쿠와타시가카가야쿠 <br>We are beautiful <br>카제가후이테 <br>히라히라토마우카미가 <br>유메노나카쟈나이 <br>카왓테쿠히비가 <br>히카리가사시테아타타카쿠호호에무요 <br>다레노메모 <br>키니세즈니 <br>아루키다스 <br>We are beautiful <br>"시아와세소우"오오이카케루지분오 <br>하나야카다난테오모에나쿠테 <br>하나타바가마우마치노나카 <br>코노잇슌노와타시가스베테 <br>사카사나마마이키오시테 <br>아다바나사카스 <br>카레나이나 <br>카멘고시노세카이다케 <br>아이오 아이오 <br>쿄코우노마마데오도루 <br>혼토와난테이미나이요 <br>타이요우아비테 i gotta post my picture <br>타노시코토밧카리노 <br>진세이난카쟈나이케도 <br>쟈아세메테이마다케 <br>아얏테유메미세테 <br>키세츠하즈레노유키게시키 <br>이치방키레이나키미데와랏테 <br>Sunrise 히카리츠츠마레테 <br>Being alive, being vivid <br>It'll be better for your life <br>츠요쿠우츠쿠시쿠와타시가카가야쿠 <br>We are beautiful <br>코와레소우나 <br>우타카타오아츠메타라 <br>유메노나카타케데 <br>코왓테쿠히비가 <br>히카리가사시테아타타카쿠호호에무요 <br>카자라나이모노와나이아루키다스 <br>We are beautiful]]></content><category term="boku no lyric no bouyomi" label="boku no lyric no bouyomi"/><category term="SKY`s the limit" label="SKY`s the limit"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/どうぶつビスケッツ/ようこそジャパリパ-クへ___Youkoso_Jyapariparkhe_애니메이션_케모노프렌즈_오프닝_테마/</id><title>どうぶつビスケッツ - ようこそジャパリパ-クへ / Youkoso Jyapariparkhe (애니메이션 `케모노프렌즈` 오프닝 테마) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:15:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:15:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%E3%81%A9%E3%81%86%E3%81%B6%E3%81%A4%E3%83%93%E3%82%B9%E3%82%B1%E3%83%83%E3%83%84/%E3%82%88%E3%81%86%E3%81%93%E3%81%9D%E3%82%B8%E3%83%A3%E3%83%91%E3%83%AA%E3%83%91-%E3%82%AF%E3%81%B8___Youkoso_Jyapariparkhe_%EC%95%A0%EB%8B%88%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4%EC%85%98_%EC%BC%80%EB%AA%A8%EB%85%B8%ED%94%84%EB%A0%8C%EC%A6%88_%EC%98%A4%ED%94%84%EB%8B%9D_%ED%85%8C%EB%A7%88/" title="どうぶつビスケッツ - ようこそジャパリパ-クへ / Youkoso Jyapariparkhe (애니메이션 `케모노프렌즈` 오프닝 테마) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[웰컴투 요-코소 자파리파크! <br>쿄오모 돗탄밧탄 오오사와기 <br>우-! 가오-! <br>다카라카니 와라이와라에바 후레은즈 (후레은즈) <br>게응카시떼 슷쨔까멧쨔까 시떼모 나카요시 (후후후) <br>케모노와 이떼모 노케모노와 이나이 <br>혼또노 아이와 고꼬니 아루 <br>호라 키미모 테오 쓰나이데 다이보오켄 <br>(완 츠 스리) <br>웰컴투 요-코소 자파리파크! <br>쿄오모 돗탄밧탄 오오사와기 <br>스가타 카타치모 쥬닌 토이로 다까라 히까레아우노 <br>유우구레 소라니 유비오 솟또 까사네따라 <br>하지메마시떼 (하지메마시떼) <br>키미오 못또 시리따이나 <br>우-! 가오-! <br>후리무케바 아찌라코찌라데 토라부루 (에?) (토라부루) <br>나은떼콧따 덴덴바라바라 친뿐칸뿐 마토만나이 (우우) <br>케모노데스모노 오오메니미떼떼네 <br>민나 지유우니 이키떼이루 <br>소오 키미모 카자라나쿠떼 다이죠부 <br>(하이 도오조) <br>나이스 츠 미츠 유 자파리파크! <br>쿄오까라와 도오조 요로시쿠네 <br>이쯔모 이쯔데모 야사시이 에가오 키미오 마앗떼이따노 <br>히라카레따 게에또 유메오 잇빠이 카타앗따라 <br>도꼬마데데모 (도꼬마데데모) <br>쓰즈이떼쿠 그레이트 쟈니 <br>(고꼬와 자파리파크! 와따시와 사바루캿또노 사바루다요!) <br>(하이요 간밧떼이키마스요) <br>(요시! 아라이상니 오마카세나노다!) <br>(민나 이쿠와요!) <br>(못또 오야메자사나이또) <br>(잇쇼켄메이 간바리마스!) <br>(록꾸니 이쿠세!) <br>(모, 모오 혼방데스까?) <br>오 히가시에 호에로 니시에 호에로 <br>세카이츄우니 히비케 사파리메로디 <br>(웰컴투 요오코소 자파리파크!) <br>웰컴투 요오코소 자파리파크! <br>쿄오모 돗딴밧딴 오오사와기 <br>스가타 카타치모 쥬닌 토이로 다까라 히까레아우노 <br>유우구레 소라니 유비오 솟또 까사네따라 <br>하지메마시떼 (하지메마시떼) <br>키미오 못또 시리따이나 <br>우-! 가오-! <br>라라라라 라라라라 <br>오 웰컴투 더 자파리파크! (자파리파크) <br>라라라라 (라라라라) 라라라라라라 <br>아츠마레 토모다치 (하이하이) <br>라라라라 (라라라라) 라라라라 (라라라라) <br>오 웰컴투 더 자파리파크! (자파리파크) <br>라라라라 (라라라라) 라라라라라라 <br>스테키나 타비다치 <br>요오코소 자파리파크!]]></content><category term="どうぶつビスケッツ" label="どうぶつビスケッツ"/><category term="ようこそジャパリパ-クへ / Youkoso Jyapariparkhe (애니메이션 `케모노프렌즈` 오프닝 테마)" label="ようこそジャパリパ-クへ / Youkoso Jyapariparkhe (애니메이션 `케모노프렌즈` 오프닝 테마)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/She-Devils/The_World_Laughs/</id><title>She-Devils - The World Laughs - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:16:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:16:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/She-Devils/The_World_Laughs/" title="She-Devils - The World Laughs - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want to go inside of you <br>And control the way you move <br>I want to go inside of you <br>And control the ways you go <br><br>Inject you with stranger things <br>Together now we can go <br>Together now we can go <br><br>When I hear you sad <br>I want to hold your hand <br>And pull you closer <br>But you won't go <br><br>I want you to know <br>You're one with it <br>I want you to know <br>You're one with it]]></content><category term="She-Devils" label="She-Devils"/><category term="The World Laughs" label="The World Laughs"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이소연/이_길_끝에서/</id><title>이소연 - 이 길 끝에서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:16:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:16:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B8%B8_%EB%81%9D%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C/" title="이소연 - 이 길 끝에서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바쁜 하룰 보내도 여전히 <br>흔적 없는 내 발자국 <br>애써 날 다독 이지만 <br>또 다시 제자리 걸음뿐 <br>바쁜 하룰 보내도 여전히 <br>보이지 않는 내 모습 <br>애써 날 위로 하지만 <br>또 다시 제자리 걸음뿐 <br>혼자 서 있는 외롭고 쓸쓸한 길 <br>주저 앉아 버린다 해도 <br>혼자 서 있는 이 길 끝에서 <br>웃고 있는 널 만나러 간다 <br>혼자 서 있는 외롭고 쓸쓸한 길 <br>주저 앉아 버린다 해도 <br>혼자 서 있는 이 길 끝에서 <br>웃고 있는 널 만나러 간다 <br>주저 앉아 버린다 해도 <br>혼자 서 있는 이 길 끝에서 <br>웃고 있는 널 만나러 간다 <br>]]></content><category term="이소연" label="이소연"/><category term="이 길 끝에서" label="이 길 끝에서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비아이지_BIG/낯설어_Inst/</id><title>비아이지 (B.I.G) - 낯설어 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:19:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:19:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80_BIG/%EB%82%AF%EC%84%A4%EC%96%B4_Inst/" title="비아이지 (B.I.G) - 낯설어 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1 2 3 let's go 후 baby 후 <br>Tell me I'm going crazy <br>Tell me what you want <br>너 왜 그래 무슨 일이야 <br>오늘따라 니 얼굴이 어두워 보여 <br>고민이 있다면 내게 말해봐 <br>누구에게도 말하지 않을게 <br>마치 날카로운 날이 선 것처럼 <br>내 맘을 모두 베어버릴 것처럼 girl <br>정말 아무 일도 없는데 <br>왜 그러냐고 내게 짜증내는 girl <br>왠지 낯설어 널 마주하고 있으면 <br>아무 말 없이 멍 때리는 <br>너를 볼 때면 <br>조금 더 깊게 빠르게 <br>네게 다가갈 수 있게 <br>아무리 노력해도 <br>넌 피곤해보여 <br>내겐 하나뿐인 나만의 my girl <br>대체 왜 그런지 말해 oh my girl <br>아무리 달래보고 웃고 <br>풀어줘도 내가 안 보이는지 <br>니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>점점 니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>이런 내 맘이 녹슬어 <br>자꾸만 삐그덕 삐그덕 거려 <br>니가 니가 <br>니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>점점 니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>어색한 니가 난 싫어 <br>자꾸만 삐그덕 삐그덕 거려 <br>니가 니가 니가 낯설어 <br>요즘 넌 사랑한단 말도 안 해 <br>나 이런 거지같은 <br>광대노릇 그만 할래 <br>자꾸 넌 꿍해 왜 그래 <br>불만 있으면 말해 <br>이러다가 내가 미쳐 죽기를 바래 <br>마치 처음 마주한 사람처럼 <br>원래 몰랐던 그런 사이처럼 girl <br>너는 도대체 왜 나를 만나고 있냐고 <br>너 땜에 I‘m gonna crazy <br>뭣 때문에 말을 안해 지금 장난해 <br>안 그래도 이 더운 날에 <br>자꾸 열 받게 <br>너 때문에 뱅뱅 미치겠어 lady <br>아무 말이라도 내게 해줘 baby <br>내겐 하나뿐인 나만의 my girl <br>대체 왜 그런지 말해 oh my girl <br>아무리 달래보고 웃고 <br>풀어줘도 내가 안 보이는지 <br>니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>점점 니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>이런 내 맘이 녹슬어 <br>자꾸만 삐그덕 삐그덕 거려 <br>니가 니가 <br>니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>점점 니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>어색한 니가 난 싫어 <br>자꾸만 삐그덕 삐그덕 거려 <br>니가 니가 니가 낯설어 <br>따뜻하기만 했던 넌 어디로 갔는지 <br>나밖에 몰랐는데 <br>뭣 때문에 니가 변했는지 <br>baby tell me why <br>내게 말을 해줘 내가 잘못 했어 <br>baby tell me why <br>내겐 너 하나가 전분데 <br>니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>점점 니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>이런 내 맘이 녹슬어 <br>자꾸만 삐그덕 삐그덕 거려 <br>니가 니가 <br>니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>점점 니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>어색한 니가 난 싫어 <br>자꾸만 삐그덕 삐그덕 거려 <br>니가 니가 니가 낯설어 <br>]]></content><category term="비아이지 (B.I.G)" label="비아이지 (B.I.G)"/><category term="낯설어 (Inst.)" label="낯설어 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비아이지_BIG/HELLO_HELLO_Inst/</id><title>비아이지 (B.I.G) - HELLO HELLO (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:19:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:19:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80_BIG/HELLO_HELLO_Inst/" title="비아이지 (B.I.G) - HELLO HELLO (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ay B.I.G in the house babe <br>I got your back big brother <br>bring it <br>Hey baby 잠깐만 You stop <br>don’t close to me 너는 뭐가 <br>그리 급해 <br>왜 자꾸 다가와 You stop <br>talk to me 네 맘 들킨 걸 <br>baby you’re mine <br>너의 은밀해진 눈빛이 <br>날 또 홀리니 <br>나의 감각이 눈을 떠 <br>완벽해져 버린 분위기 <br>You’re the only one 날 유혹해 <br>Your eyes 위험할 것만 같아 <br>Dangerous Dangerous <br>dangerous inside <br>Gotta get your love <br>오 I’ll make it over tonight <br>다쳐도 I'm okay <br>오 붉게 물든 너와 나 <br>가시 돋친 너의 red lips red lips <br>왜 그리 달콤한데 <br>말 좀 해봐 <br>Hello Hello Hello Hello <br>woo Girl so dangerous <br>It’s alright <br>우리뿐이야 더 다가와 <br>오 향기에 취해가는 기분 <br>that’s so good <br>so look around 네 주변 둘러봐 <br>나 같은 남자가 어딨나 <br>I'm a sniper <br>날 봤담 늦었다는 거 <br>네가 원하는 거 어디 가는 거 <br>뭐 다 말하지 않아도 알아 <br>can't stop it <br>이미 내 맘은 love you <br>중독이 된 것만 같아 기분은 <br>oh yeah oh yeah <br>나쁜 여잔 걸 알면서 <br>go ahead go ahead <br>사랑이란 포이즌에 빠져버린 boy <br>I don't care give me kiss <br>Gotta get your love <br>오 I’ll make it over tonight <br>다쳐도 I'm okay <br>오 붉게 물든 너와 나 <br>가시 돋친 너의 red lips red lips <br>왜 그리 달콤한데 <br>말 좀 해봐 <br>Hello Hello Hello Hello <br>woo Girl so dangerous <br>I think you was a bad girl <br>Please don't beat <br>around the bush girl <br>Girl I wanna see your colors <br>It's not a true colors <br>설명은 필요 없어 맘이 보인 걸 <br>완벽할 필요 없어 <br>you’re so beautiful <br>뭔가에 홀린 것 같아 <br>이미 늦은 것 같아 <br>널 놓을 수가 없어 <br>Gotta get your love <br>오 I’ll make it over tonight <br>이제야 알겠어 <br>오 누가 꺾인 꽃인지 <br>바라봐줘 나의 마지막 <br>꽃잎이 떨어지는 그 순간을 <br>다 끝났어 over over over over <br>woo over over over <br>Gotta get your love <br>오 I’ll make it over tonight <br>다쳐도 I'm okay <br>오 붉게 물든 너와 나 가시 <br>돋친 너의 red lips red lips <br>왜 그리 달콤한데 <br>말 좀 해봐 <br>Hello Hello Hello Hello woo <br>Girl so dangerous <br>]]></content><category term="비아이지 (B.I.G)" label="비아이지 (B.I.G)"/><category term="HELLO HELLO (Inst.)" label="HELLO HELLO (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/벤지_비아이지/듀엣/</id><title>벤지 (비아이지) - 듀엣 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:19:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:19:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B2%A4%EC%A7%80_%EB%B9%84%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80/%EB%93%80%EC%97%A3/" title="벤지 (비아이지) - 듀엣 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yes Let's Make It Last <br>This Song Is About U Yeah <br>시작해 Come On <br>이 노랜 너를 위한 Love Song <br>다른 건 아무 의미 없어 <br>하늘이 주신 You're My Diamond <br>소중해 We Gotta Go <br>연애 참 달콤해 사랑은 상큼해 <br>첨 봤을 때부터 어머나 <br>푹 빠져버린 My Baby <br>아끼지 않을래 사랑해 사랑해 <br>흔하지만 참 따뜻한 말 널 사랑해 <br>횡단보도 사이 <br>너와 나 두 손 흔들면서 마주 봐 <br>영화 속 한 장면처럼 <br>수줍게 너의 이름 크게 불러 볼까 <br>니가 없는 하루 <br>너무 길어 길어 길어 <br>생각조차 하기 싫 싫 싫어 <br>머릿속이 아득해져 와 Yeah <br>이 순간이 영원하길 빌어 빌어 <br>이 노랜 너를 위한 Love Song <br>너 아닌 다른 건 아무 의미 없어 <br>하늘이 주신 You're My Diamond <br>소중해 We Gotta Go <br>연애 참 달콤해 사랑은 상큼해 <br>첨 봤을 때부터 어머나 <br>푹 빠져버린 My Baby <br>아끼지 않을래 사랑해 사랑해 <br>흔하지만 참 따뜻한 말 널 사랑해 <br>환상의 듀엣 듀엣 듀엣 <br>듀엣 듀엣 듀엣 <br>Let's Do It Do It Do It <br>Do It Do It Do It <br>환상의 듀엣 듀엣 듀엣 <br>듀엣 듀엣 듀엣 <br>Let's Do It Do It Do It <br>Do It Do It Do It <br>애기 같은 얼굴 So Cute <br>반면에 몸매가 So Good <br>완벽이란 단어 존재 하는 이유 <br>굳이 말하자면 당연히 For U <br>사랑이란 건 당기면 <br>민다고 하지만 난 안 밀어 <br>천사를 밀었다간 <br>분명 하늘이 노해 <br>천벌을 내릴 거야 나에게 <br>이 노랜 너를 위한 Love Song <br>너 아닌 다른 건 아무 의미 없어 <br>하늘이 주신 You're My Diamond <br>소중해 We Gotta Go <br>단 둘이 손잡고 걸으며 <br>너와 눈을 마주쳐 <br>가장 밝은 얼굴로 Uh <br>활짝 웃어 주면 <br>이게 행복이지 뭐 별거 있겠어 <br>Just You &amp; Me You &amp; Me Uh Uh <br>You &amp; Me You &amp; Me Uh Uh <br>You &amp; Me 너와 나 언제나 <br>이렇게 함께 변함없이 <br>연애 참 달콤해 사랑은 상큼해 <br>첨 봤을 때부터 어머나 <br>푹 빠져버린 My Baby <br>아끼지 않을래 사랑해 사랑해 <br>흔하지만 참 따뜻한 말 널 사랑해 <br>환상의 듀엣 듀엣 듀엣 <br>듀엣 듀엣 듀엣 <br>Let's Do It Do It Do It <br>Do It Do It Do It <br>환상의 듀엣 듀엣 듀엣 <br>듀엣 듀엣 듀엣 <br>Let's Do It Do It Do It <br>Baby One More Time <br>아끼지 않을래 사랑해 사랑해 <br>흔하지만 참 따뜻한 말 널 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="벤지 (비아이지)" label="벤지 (비아이지)"/><category term="듀엣" label="듀엣"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비아이지_BIG/123/</id><title>비아이지 (B.I.G) - 1.2.3 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:19:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:19:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80_BIG/123/" title="비아이지 (B.I.G) - 1.2.3 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know it’s time Feel the vibe <br>널 처음 본 순간 <br>꼭 잡힐 듯 달아날 듯 난 점점 미쳐가 <br>손에 닿을 것 같아 니가 보일 것 같아 <br>시간이 멈춘다면 <br>너 없는 1분1초가 꿈처럼 허전해 <br>멍하니 있기엔 이 순간이 허무해 <br>완벽한 계획아래 <br>Can’t stop me Ain’t nobody <br>나에게 끌려온다 <br>깊게 베인 짙은 향기 <br>날 자극해 날 자극해 <br>선명해진 니 목소리 <br>날 부르네 날 부르네 <br>1 2 3 I know you can feel it <br>지금 느낌대로 <br>Come with me <br>난 상관없어 맘이 시킨 대로 <br>Closer now closer now <br>널 거부하긴 이미 늦었어 <br>1 2 3 너에게 간다 점점 느껴진다 <br>Don't with me <br>뛰는 심장이 터질 것만 같다 <br>Closer now Closer now Closer now <br>Baby I'm here <br>멀리서 헤매진 말아줘 <br>오늘밤이 지나면 더는 볼 수 없어 <br>So baby I'm ready to get you <br>열두 시가 되기 전까지 <br>네 마음을 나에게 보여줘 <br>I will change your mind <br>1 2 3 I know you can feel it <br>지금 느낌대로 <br>Come with me <br>난 상관없어 맘이 시킨 대로 <br>Closer now closer now <br>널 거부하긴 이미 늦었어 <br>1 2 3 너에게 간다 점점 느껴진다 <br>Don't with me <br>뛰는 심장이 터질 것만 같다 <br>Closer now Closer now Closer now <br>paradise 새까만 마음을 <br>하얗게 불 태워 <br>burn better wild <br>너의 아름다움은 잠든 날 깨워 girl <br>알 수 없는 끌림에 여기까지 왔어 <br>너도 내가 끌리듯이 그래 <br>너의 모든 게 눈 부셔 <br>시간은 열두 실 가리키려고 하지만 <br>어두울수록 밝은 별은 더 빛나는 듯이 <br>1 2 3 I know you can feel it <br>지금 느낌대로 <br>Come with me <br>난 상관없어 맘이 시킨 대로 <br>Closer now closer now <br>널 거부하긴 이미 늦었어 <br>1 2 3 너에게 간다 <br>Don't with me <br>뛰는 심장이 <br>Closer now Closer now Closer now <br>]]></content><category term="비아이지 (B.I.G)" label="비아이지 (B.I.G)"/><category term="1.2.3" label="1.2.3"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비아이지_BIG/낯설어/</id><title>비아이지 (B.I.G) - 낯설어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:19:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:19:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80_BIG/%EB%82%AF%EC%84%A4%EC%96%B4/" title="비아이지 (B.I.G) - 낯설어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1 2 3 let's go 후 baby 후 <br>Tell me I'm going crazy <br>Tell me what you want <br>너 왜 그래 무슨 일이야 <br>오늘따라 니 얼굴이 어두워 보여 <br>고민이 있다면 내게 말해봐 <br>누구에게도 말하지 않을게 <br>마치 날카로운 날이 선 것처럼 <br>내 맘을 모두 베어버릴 것처럼 girl <br>정말 아무 일도 없는데 <br>왜 그러냐고 내게 짜증내는 girl <br>왠지 낯설어 널 마주하고 있으면 <br>아무 말 없이 멍 때리는 <br>너를 볼 때면 <br>조금 더 깊게 빠르게 <br>네게 다가갈 수 있게 <br>아무리 노력해도 <br>넌 피곤해보여 <br>내겐 하나뿐인 나만의 my girl <br>대체 왜 그런지 말해 oh my girl <br>아무리 달래보고 웃고 <br>풀어줘도 내가 안 보이는지 <br>니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>점점 니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>이런 내 맘이 녹슬어 <br>자꾸만 삐그덕 삐그덕 거려 <br>니가 니가 <br>니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>점점 니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>어색한 니가 난 싫어 <br>자꾸만 삐그덕 삐그덕 거려 <br>니가 니가 니가 낯설어 <br>요즘 넌 사랑한단 말도 안 해 <br>나 이런 거지같은 <br>광대노릇 그만 할래 <br>자꾸 넌 꿍해 왜 그래 <br>불만 있으면 말해 <br>이러다가 내가 미쳐 죽기를 바래 <br>마치 처음 마주한 사람처럼 <br>원래 몰랐던 그런 사이처럼 girl <br>너는 도대체 왜 나를 만나고 있냐고 <br>너 땜에 I‘m gonna crazy <br>뭣 때문에 말을 안해 지금 장난해 <br>안 그래도 이 더운 날에 <br>자꾸 열 받게 <br>너 때문에 뱅뱅 미치겠어 lady <br>아무 말이라도 내게 해줘 baby <br>내겐 하나뿐인 나만의 my girl <br>대체 왜 그런지 말해 oh my girl <br>아무리 달래보고 웃고 <br>풀어줘도 내가 안 보이는지 <br>니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>점점 니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>이런 내 맘이 녹슬어 <br>자꾸만 삐그덕 삐그덕 거려 <br>니가 니가 <br>니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>점점 니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>어색한 니가 난 싫어 <br>자꾸만 삐그덕 삐그덕 거려 <br>니가 니가 니가 낯설어 <br>따뜻하기만 했던 넌 어디로 갔는지 <br>나밖에 몰랐는데 <br>뭣 때문에 니가 변했는지 <br>baby tell me why <br>내게 말을 해줘 내가 잘못 했어 <br>baby tell me why <br>내겐 너 하나가 전분데 <br>니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>점점 니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>이런 내 맘이 녹슬어 <br>자꾸만 삐그덕 삐그덕 거려 <br>니가 니가 <br>니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>점점 니가 낯설어 낯설어 <br>어색한 니가 난 싫어 <br>자꾸만 삐그덕 삐그덕 거려 <br>니가 니가 니가 낯설어 <br>]]></content><category term="비아이지 (B.I.G)" label="비아이지 (B.I.G)"/><category term="낯설어" label="낯설어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비아이지_BIG/HELLO_HELLO/</id><title>비아이지 (B.I.G) - HELLO HELLO - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:19:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:19:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80_BIG/HELLO_HELLO/" title="비아이지 (B.I.G) - HELLO HELLO - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ay B.I.G in the house babe <br>I got your back big brother <br>bring it <br>Hey baby 잠깐만 You stop <br>don’t close to me 너는 뭐가 <br>그리 급해 <br>왜 자꾸 다가와 You stop <br>talk to me 네 맘 들킨 걸 <br>baby you’re mine <br>너의 은밀해진 눈빛이 <br>날 또 홀리니 <br>나의 감각이 눈을 떠 <br>완벽해져 버린 분위기 <br>You’re the only one 날 유혹해 <br>Your eyes 위험할 것만 같아 <br>Dangerous Dangerous <br>dangerous inside <br>Gotta get your love <br>오 I’ll make it over tonight <br>다쳐도 I'm okay <br>오 붉게 물든 너와 나 <br>가시 돋친 너의 red lips red lips <br>왜 그리 달콤한데 <br>말 좀 해봐 <br>Hello Hello Hello Hello <br>woo Girl so dangerous <br>It’s alright <br>우리뿐이야 더 다가와 <br>오 향기에 취해가는 기분 <br>that’s so good <br>so look around 네 주변 둘러봐 <br>나 같은 남자가 어딨나 <br>I'm a sniper <br>날 봤담 늦었다는 거 <br>네가 원하는 거 어디 가는 거 <br>뭐 다 말하지 않아도 알아 <br>can't stop it <br>이미 내 맘은 love you <br>중독이 된 것만 같아 기분은 <br>oh yeah oh yeah <br>나쁜 여잔 걸 알면서 <br>go ahead go ahead <br>사랑이란 포이즌에 빠져버린 boy <br>I don't care give me kiss <br>Gotta get your love <br>오 I’ll make it over tonight <br>다쳐도 I'm okay <br>오 붉게 물든 너와 나 <br>가시 돋친 너의 red lips red lips <br>왜 그리 달콤한데 <br>말 좀 해봐 <br>Hello Hello Hello Hello <br>woo Girl so dangerous <br>I think you was a bad girl <br>Please don't beat <br>around the bush girl <br>Girl I wanna see your colors <br>It's not a true colors <br>설명은 필요 없어 맘이 보인 걸 <br>완벽할 필요 없어 <br>you’re so beautiful <br>뭔가에 홀린 것 같아 <br>이미 늦은 것 같아 <br>널 놓을 수가 없어 <br>Gotta get your love <br>오 I’ll make it over tonight <br>이제야 알겠어 <br>오 누가 꺾인 꽃인지 <br>바라봐줘 나의 마지막 <br>꽃잎이 떨어지는 그 순간을 <br>다 끝났어 over over over over <br>woo over over over <br>Gotta get your love <br>오 I’ll make it over tonight <br>다쳐도 I'm okay <br>오 붉게 물든 너와 나 가시 <br>돋친 너의 red lips red lips <br>왜 그리 달콤한데 <br>말 좀 해봐 <br>Hello Hello Hello Hello woo <br>Girl so dangerous <br>]]></content><category term="비아이지 (B.I.G)" label="비아이지 (B.I.G)"/><category term="HELLO HELLO" label="HELLO HELLO"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Axwell/More_Than_You_Know/</id><title>Axwell - More Than You Know - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:21:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:21:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Axwell/More_Than_You_Know/" title="Axwell - More Than You Know - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Chorus] <br>I just need to get it off my chest <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>You should know that baby you're the best <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>Yeah, more than you know <br><br>[Verse 1] <br>I saw it coming, from miles away <br>I better speak up if I got something to say <br>'Cause it ain't over, until she sings <br>You had your reasons, you had a few <br>But you knew that I would go anywhere for you <br>'Cause it ain't over, until she sings <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I just need to get it off my chest <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>You should know that baby you're the best <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>Yeah, more than you know <br><br>[Post-Chorus] <br>I just... <br>I just... <br><br><br>[Verse 2] <br>Your good intentions are sweet and pure <br>But they can never tame a fire like yours <br>No it ain't over, until she sings <br>Right where you wanted, down on my knees <br>You got me begging, pretty baby set me free <br>'Cause it ain't over, until she sings <br><br>[Pre-Chorus] <br>Come a little closer, let me taste your smile <br>Until the morning lights <br>Ain't no going back the way you look tonight <br>I see it in your eyes <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I just need to get it off my chest <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>You should know that baby you're the best <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>Yeah, more than you know <br><br>Yeah, more than you know <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>Yeah, more than you know <br><br>[Post-Chorus] <br>I just... <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I just need to get it off my chest <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>You should know that baby you're the best <br>Yeah, more than you know <br>Yeah, more than you know]]></content><category term="Axwell" label="Axwell"/><category term="More Than You Know" label="More Than You Know"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phoenix/Ti_Amo/</id><title>Phoenix - Ti Amo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:27:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:27:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phoenix/Ti_Amo/" title="Phoenix - Ti Amo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let me tell you what it is <br>Do you mind if I do <br>I know I can be honest with you <br>'Cause I don't like it as it is <br><br>I don't like it as it is <br>A disaster scenario <br>So don't look at what you did <br>This melted Gelato <br><br>Love you Ti amo Je t'aime Te quiero <br>It's not love but wait <br><br>I'll be standing by the jukebox <br>Champagne or Prosecco <br>I was playing classics by the Buzzcocks <br>Battiato and Lucio <br><br>Love you Ti amo Je t'aime Te quiero <br>Open up your legs <br><br>Don't tell me, don't tell me no <br>Don't tell me, don't tell me no no <br>Don't tell me, don't tell me no <br>I'll say Ti amo till we get along <br>Don't tell me, don't tell me no <br>Don't tell me, don't tell me no no <br>Don't tell me, don't tell me no <br>I'll say Ti amo till we get along <br><br>You don't mind it as it is <br>Bonanza, che bello <br>Well I'll show you how to win <br>My festival di Sanremo <br><br>Love you Ti amo Je t'aime Te quiero <br>It's not over yet <br><br>Now I'm looking like the bad cop <br>Sunbathing in Rio <br>Switching unsophisticated soft rock <br>To Beethoven's Concerto <br><br>Love you Ti amo Je t'aime Te quiero <br>Open up your legs <br><br>Don't tell me, don't tell me no <br>Don't tell me, don't tell me no no <br>Don't tell me, don't tell me no <br>I'll say Ti amo till we get along <br>Don't tell me, don't tell me no <br>Don't tell me, don't tell me no no <br>Don't tell me, don't tell me no <br>I'll say Ti amo till we get along <br><br>ca y est c'est fini <br>Je veux croire que le meilleur est a venir <br>Je sais que le pire l'est aussi <br>Alors laisse moi compter les moutons <br>Chanter nos chansons, rever a l'unisson]]></content><category term="Phoenix" label="Phoenix"/><category term="Ti Amo" label="Ti Amo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Palace/Break_The_Silence_Acoustic/</id><title>Palace - Break The Silence (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:27:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:27:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Palace/Break_The_Silence_Acoustic/" title="Palace - Break The Silence (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want to see in your soul <br>I want to tame this animal <br>Give me shame, you show me lies <br>I want to change my alibis <br><br>Cheated, always loved you <br>Broken hearts who rumble <br>Feasted on foundations <br>Bathed in blood of angels <br>Found you out, your weakness <br>Drowned you out, I'm sleepless <br>Leave my mind, your feeding <br>On my heart <br><br>So break the silence <br>Just give me a reason <br>We have creedons <br>Now we are poisoned <br><br>So break the silence <br>Just give me a reason <br>We have creedons <br>Now we are poisoned <br><br>I want to feel how it's true <br>These chemicals in me and you <br>I want to fight with desire <br>I want to burn in your fire <br><br>Cheated, always loved you <br>Broken hearts who rumble <br>Feasted on foundations <br>Bathed in blood <br><br>So break the silence <br>Just give me a reason <br>We have creedons <br>Now we are poisoned <br><br>So break the silence <br>Just give me a reason <br>We have creedons <br>Now we are poisoned]]></content><category term="Palace" label="Palace"/><category term="Break The Silence (Acoustic)" label="Break The Silence (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Why_Dont_You_Do_Right/</id><title>Shirley Horn - Why Don`t You Do Right - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:27:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:27:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Why_Dont_You_Do_Right/" title="Shirley Horn - Why Don`t You Do Right - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You had plenty money back in 42 <br>You've let other women make a fool of you <br>Why don't you do right <br>Like some other men do <br>Get out of here and get me some money too <br>You're sitting 'round wondering what it's all about <br>If you ain't got no money gonna put you out <br>Why don't you do right <br>Like some other men do <br>Get out of here and get me some money too <br>If you had prepared many years ago <br>You wouldn't be wandering on from door to door <br>Why don't you do right <br>Like some other men do <br>Get out of here and get me some money too <br>If you had prepared many years ago <br>You wouldn't be wandering on from door to door <br>Why don't you do right <br>Like some other men do <br>Get out of here and get me some money too <br>Get out of here and get me some money too <br>Get me some money too, get me some money too <br>Get me some money, get me some money, get me some money too]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="Why Don`t You Do Right" label="Why Don`t You Do Right"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/The_Very_Thought_Of_You/</id><title>Shirley Horn - The Very Thought Of You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:27:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:27:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/The_Very_Thought_Of_You/" title="Shirley Horn - The Very Thought Of You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The very thought of you and I forget to do <br>The little ordinary things everyone ought to do <br>I'm living in a kind of daydream <br>I'm happy as a queen <br>And foolish though it may seem <br>To me it's everything <br>The mere idea of you the longing here for you <br>You'll never know how slow the moments go <br>till I'm near to you <br>I see your face in every flower <br>Your eyes in stars above <br>It's just the thought of you <br>The very thought of you my love <br>I see your face in every flower <br>Your eyes in stars above <br>It's just the thought of you <br>The very thought of you my love]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="The Very Thought Of You" label="The Very Thought Of You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/My_Heart_Stood_Still/</id><title>Shirley Horn - My Heart Stood Still - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:27:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:27:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/My_Heart_Stood_Still/" title="Shirley Horn - My Heart Stood Still - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I took one look at you <br>That's all I meant to do <br>And then my heart stood still <br><br>My feet could step and walk <br>My lips could move and talk <br>And yet my heart stood still <br><br>Though not a single word was spoken <br>I could tell you knew <br>That unfelt clasp of hands <br>Told me so well you knew <br>I never lived at all <br>Until the thrill of that moment <br>When my heart stood still <br><br>I took one look at you <br>That's all I meant to do <br>And then my heart stopped right there <br><br>My feet could step and walk <br>My lips could move and talk <br>And yet my heart stood still <br><br>Though not a single word was spoken <br>I could tell you knew <br>That unfelt claps of hands <br>Told me so well you knew <br>I never lived at all <br>Until the thrill of that moment <br>When my heart stood still]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="My Heart Stood Still" label="My Heart Stood Still"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/The_Rules_Of_The_Road/</id><title>Shirley Horn - The Rules Of The Road - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:28:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:28:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/The_Rules_Of_The_Road/" title="Shirley Horn - The Rules Of The Road - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So these are the ropes <br>The tricks of the trade <br>The rules of the road <br>You're one of the dopes <br>For whom they were made <br>The rules of the road <br><br>You follow that kiss <br>And recklessly miss <br>A bend of the road <br>Then suddenly this <br>The end of the road <br><br>So love is a hoax <br>A glittering string <br>Of little white lies <br>But these are the jokes <br>And what if they bring <br>The tears to your eyes <br><br>Well love often shows a funny return <br>The brighter it glows <br>The longer you burn <br>And Lord only knows <br>Love has little concern <br>For the fools of the road <br><br>That's how it goes <br>You live and you learn <br>The rules of the road <br><br>Well love often shows a funny return <br>The brighter it glows <br>The longer you burn <br>And Lord only knows <br>Love has little concern <br>For the fools of the road <br><br>That's how it goes <br>You live and you learn <br>The rules of the road <br>The rules of the road]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="The Rules Of The Road" label="The Rules Of The Road"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/I_Got_Lost_In_His_Arms/</id><title>Shirley Horn - I Got Lost In His Arms - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:28:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:28:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/I_Got_Lost_In_His_Arms/" title="Shirley Horn - I Got Lost In His Arms - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I got lost in his arms <br>and i had to stay <br>it was dark in his arms and i lost my way <br><br>from the dark came a voice and it seemed to say <br>there you go, there you go <br>how i felt when i fell, i just can recall <br>but his arms held me fast and it broke the fall <br>and i sad to my heart as it foolishly came jumping all <br>around <br>i got lost, and look what i found <br>how i felt when i fell i just cant recall <br>but his arms held me fast and it broke the fall <br>and i sad to my heart as it foolishly kept jumping all <br>around <br>i got lost, but look what i found]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="I Got Lost In His Arms" label="I Got Lost In His Arms"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Solitary_Moon/</id><title>Shirley Horn - Solitary Moon - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:28:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:28:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Solitary_Moon/" title="Shirley Horn - Solitary Moon - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When the night is wrapped around us <br>And the dawn might come too soon <br>When the only light that's found us <br>Is the solitary moon <br>When the songbird in a willow sings a soft and soulful tune <br>Once again you share my pillow <br>Making love to me tenderly here <br>As we share the silent moon <br>As it slowly sails above us in its solitary flight <br>Seems the moon must surely love us <br>As it bathes us in its flight <br>Say that we can spent the day through a sunlit afternoon <br>Let your kisses say you stay here <br>And make love to me tenderly here <br>As we share the silent moon <br><br>Say that we can spent the day through a sunlit afternoon <br>Let your kisses say you stay here <br>And make love to me tenderly here <br>As we share the silent moon <br>The Solitary Moon <br>No Ordinary Moon <br>The Solitary Moon]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="Solitary Moon" label="Solitary Moon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/The_Best_Is_Yet_To_Come/</id><title>Shirley Horn - The Best Is Yet To Come - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:28:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:28:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/The_Best_Is_Yet_To_Come/" title="Shirley Horn - The Best Is Yet To Come - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Out of the tree of life I just picked me a plum <br>You came along and everything starting to hum <br>Still it's a real good bet the best is yet to come <br><br>The best is yet to come, and babe won't it be fine <br>You think you've seen the sun but you ain't seen it shine <br><br>Wait till the warm up's underway <br>Wait till our lips have met <br>Wait till you see that sunshine day, ain't nothing like it yet <br><br>The best is yet to come, and babe won't it be fine <br>The best is yet to come, come the day your mine <br>Come the day your mine <br><br>I'm gonna teach you to fly, we've only tasted the wine <br>We're gonna drink that cup dry <br>Wait till your charms are ripe for these arms to surround <br><br>You think you've flown before but you ain't left the ground <br>Wait till you're locked in my embrace, wait till I draw you near <br>Wait till you've seen that sunshine place, ain't nothing like it here <br><br>The best is yet to come, and babe won't it be fine <br>The best is yet to come, come the day you're mine <br>Come the day you're mine, come the day you're mine <br>The best is yet to come, and babe won't it be fine]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="The Best Is Yet To Come" label="The Best Is Yet To Come"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Youre_My_Thrill/</id><title>Shirley Horn - You`re My Thrill - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:28:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:28:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Youre_My_Thrill/" title="Shirley Horn - You`re My Thrill - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been 'neath the moon before <br>Held by the charms of other arms <br>I heard love's old tune before <br>And it used to bore me 'till you stood before me <br><br>You're my thrill <br>You do something to me <br>You send chills right through me <br>When I look at you 'cause you're my thrill <br>You're my thrill <br><br>How my pulse increases <br>I just go to pieces <br>When I look at you 'cause you're my thrill <br>Hm <br>Nothing seems to matter <br>Hm <br>Here's my heart on a silver platter <br>Where's my will <br>Why this strange desire <br>That keeps mounting higher <br>When I look at you I cant keep still <br>You're my thrill <br>Thrill]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="You`re My Thrill" label="You`re My Thrill"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/Himlen_ar_oskyldigt_bla/</id><title>Ted Gardestad - Himlen ar oskyldigt bla - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:32:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:32:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/Himlen_ar_oskyldigt_bla/" title="Ted Gardestad - Himlen ar oskyldigt bla - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Himlen ar oskyldigt bla <br>som ogon nar barnen ar sma <br>Att regndroppar faller som tararna gor <br>rar inte stjarnorna for <br>alskling jag vet hur det kanns <br>nar broar till tryggheten branns <br>Fast tiden har jagat oss in i en vra <br>ar himlen sa oskyldigt bla <br><br>Nar vi vaxte upp, lekte livet <br>vi var evighetens hopp <br>Det var helt sjalvklart att var <br>framtid skulle bli <br>oforbrukat fri <br><br>Somrar svepte fram <br>jorden varmde vara fotter dar vi sprang <br>Ragen gungade, och graset vaxte gront <br>Hela livet var sa skont <br><br>Himlen ar oskyldigt bla <br>som ogon nar barnen ar sma <br>Att regndroppar faller som tararna gor <br>det rar inte stjarnorna for <br>alskling, jag vet hur det kanns <br>nar broar till tryggheten branns <br>Fast tiden har jagat oss in i en vra <br>ar himlen sa oskyldigt bla <br><br>Frusna pa en strand <br>Flog vi med drakar medans <br>tiden flot iland <br>Vi var barn som ingen ondska kunde na <br>himlen var sa bla <br><br>Nu tar molnen mark <br>Jag var forblindad av att solen sken sa stark <br>Men mina ogon kommer alltid le mot dig <br>Kan det begaras mer av mig <br><br>Himlen ar oskyldigt bla <br>djupaste hav likasa <br>Att regndroppar faller som tararna gor <br>det rar inte stjarnorna for <br>alskling, jag vet hur det kanns <br>nar broar till tryggheten branns <br>Fast tiden har jagat, oss in i en vra <br>ar himlen sa oskyldigt bla]]></content><category term="Ted Gardestad" label="Ted Gardestad"/><category term="Himlen ar oskyldigt bla" label="Himlen ar oskyldigt bla"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/For_karlekens_skull/</id><title>Ted Gardestad - For karlekens skull - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:32:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:32:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/For_karlekens_skull/" title="Ted Gardestad - For karlekens skull - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Utanfor fonstret slar varen ut <br>Marken blir gron igen <br>Allt som var dott, vacks till liv <br>det kan ocksa vi <br>Mm <br>Sa lange vi andas <br>Ute till havs styr en fiskebat <br>Langs en fri horisont <br>Den gungar sa tryggt in mot hamn <br>som jag i din famn <br>Mm <br>Sa lange vi alskar <br><br>Det ar for oss solen gar opp <br>Lyser som guld, for karlekens skull <br>Solen gar upp, sa oskuldsfull <br>Lyser pa oss for karlekens skull <br><br>Hogt pa ett berg star en katedral <br>och pekar upp mot skyn <br>Men det ar for himlen i dig <br>och jorden i mig <br>Mm <br>Vi alskar varandra <br><br>Det ar for oss solen gar opp <br>Lyser som guld, for karlekens skull <br>Solen gar upp, sa oskuldsfull <br>Lyser pa oss for karlekens skull <br><br>Mmmm <br><br>Lyser som guld, for karlekens skull <br>Lyser pa oss, for karlekens skull]]></content><category term="Ted Gardestad" label="Ted Gardestad"/><category term="For karlekens skull" label="For karlekens skull"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/Oh_vilken_harlig_da/</id><title>Ted Gardestad - Oh, vilken harlig da` - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:32:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:32:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/Oh_vilken_harlig_da/" title="Ted Gardestad - Oh, vilken harlig da` - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[steg upp pa morgonen <br>innan din dag var riktigt vaken <br>woowow vilken harlig dag <br><br>smog mig pa kna till sjon <br>for att fa se dig bada naken <br>woowow vilken harlig dag <br><br>lalalalalalala <br>lalalalalalala <br>lalalalalalala <br><br>ah sag du mig <br>sag du vem det var <br><br>jag hade satt mig ner <br>nar du tog av dig dina klader <br>woowow vilken harlig dag <br><br>fick syn pa svalorna <br>dom kunde lova vackert vader <br>woowow vilken harlig dag <br><br>lalalalalalalala <br>lalalalalalalala <br>lalalalalalalala <br><br>ah sag du mig <br>sag du att det var jag <br><br>du lag pa rygg <br>o sog ut saften fran ett stra <br>och du hade ingen annan <br>an dig sjalv att tanka pa <br>men trodde du <br><br>att du var ensam i det bla <br>trots att bakom jag sag pa <br>jag vet att jag blev smatt generad <br>mmmm <br>men jag tror aven att <br>aven du var intresserad <br><br>sag du mig <br>sag du att det var jag <br><br>lalalalalalalalala <br>lalalalalalalalala <br>lalalalalalalalala <br><br>ah sag du mig <br>sag du att det var jag <br><br>jag tror du horde mig <br>nar du forsvann <br>inunder kjolen <br><br>woowow vilken harlig dag <br><br>sa jag fick fly ivag <br>och jag sprang naken <br>bort mot solen <br>woowow vilken harlig dag <br><br>lalalala lalalalalala x6]]></content><category term="Ted Gardestad" label="Ted Gardestad"/><category term="Oh, vilken harlig da`" label="Oh, vilken harlig da`"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/Antligen_pa_vag/</id><title>Ted Gardestad - Antligen pa vag - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:32:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:32:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/Antligen_pa_vag/" title="Ted Gardestad - Antligen pa vag - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[antligen pa vag <br>Jag forlanger mina steg <br>Luften smakar som en jordgubbspaj <br>En solig dag i maj <br><br>Traden star i blom <br>Marken tacks av jungfrudom <br>Och nu hanger det pa varje kvist <br>En solskensoptimist <br><br>Fran norr till soder Torn <br>Till jordens alla horn <br>Sa leder vagen hem till dig <br>Framfor mina ogon oppnar sig <br>En solig vag till dig <br><br>antligen pa vag <br>Langtan bor i mina steg <br>Jag har lamnat allt som tynger mig <br>Pa vagen hem till dig <br><br>Fran vast till osterlen <br>Pa ang och mo och sten <br>Sa slingrar sig en vag till dig <br><br>antligen pa vag <br><br>Jag forlanger min steg <br>Framfor mina ogon oppnar sig <br>En solig vag till dig]]></content><category term="Ted Gardestad" label="Ted Gardestad"/><category term="Antligen pa vag" label="Antligen pa vag"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/I_den_stora_sorgens_famn/</id><title>Ted Gardestad - I den stora sorgens famn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/I_den_stora_sorgens_famn/" title="Ted Gardestad - I den stora sorgens famn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I den stora sorgens famn <br>finns sma ogonblick av skratt <br>sa som stjarnor tittar fram <br>ut ur evighetens natt <br>och i solens forsta stralar <br>flyger svalorna mot skyn <br>for att binda skora tradar <br>tvinna tradar <br>till en tross <br>mellan oss <br>sa vi nar varandra <br><br>i den harda tidens brus <br>finns de skrik som ingen hor <br>allt forsvinner i ett sus <br>som nar vinden sakta dor <br>alla tararna har torkat <br>till kristaller pa min kind <br>jag har ropat allt jag orkat <br>allt jag orkat efter dig <br>hor du mig <br>kan vi na varandra <br><br>i den langa vinterns spar <br>trampas frusna blommor ner <br>och dar ensamheten gar <br>biter kylan alltid mer <br>anda har jag aldrig tvekat <br>mellan morker eller ljus <br>for nar manens skara bleknat <br>har allt pekat at ditt hall <br>och fran mitt hall <br>kan vi na varandra <br><br>i den stora sorgens famn]]></content><category term="Ted Gardestad" label="Ted Gardestad"/><category term="I den stora sorgens famn" label="I den stora sorgens famn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/Come_Give_Me_Love/</id><title>Ted Gardestad - Come Give Me Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/Come_Give_Me_Love/" title="Ted Gardestad - Come Give Me Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jag vet en van som bor i huset intill <br>Och hon har lovat mej allt va jag vill <br>mmmhm jag vet en van, som ar lika blaogd som jag <br>vi borde fa det bra <br><br>nar mina fingrar inte kanner mer <br>nar mina ogon inte langre ser <br>nar livet vander <br>ska jag annu be come give me love, come give me love <br><br>kom ge mej varlden <br>kom ge mej fred <br>kom sank ditt huvud <br>och lagg dej ner <br>kom ge mej kroppen <br>kom ge mej allt som du har <br>och jag ska stanna kvar <br><br>jag vet ett rum langt in dit vi brukar ga <br>om vi ska gomma oss, bara vi tva <br>mmmhm, jag vet en van, som ar lika morkradd som jag <br>vi gjorde slut idag <br><br>nar mina oron inte langre hor <br>nar bladen faller och en stjarna dor <br>nar livet vander <br>ska jag annu be come give me love, come give me love <br><br>kom ge mej solen <br>kom ge mej hav <br>kom ge mej jorden <br>vi lever av <br>kom ge mej kroppen <br>kom ge mej allt som du har <br>och jag ska stanna kvar <br>mmm <br><br>kom ge mej sommar <br>kom ge mej liv <br>kom ge mej karlek och livs motiv <br>kom ge mej kroppen <br>kom ge mej allt som du har <br>och jag ska stanna kvar <br>mmm <br><br>kom ge mej sanning <br>kom ge mej tid <br>kom ge mej kunskap <br>kom ge mej frid <br>kom ge mej doften <br>kom ge mej allt som du har <br>och jag ska stanna kvar <br>mmm <br><br>kom ge mej varlden <br>kom ge mej fred <br>kom sank ditt huvud <br>och lagg dej ner <br>kom ge mej kroppen <br>kom ge mej allt som du har <br>och jag ska stanna kvar i bakgrund samtidigt som man sjunger nedanstaende fyra rader <br><br>nar mina oron inte langre hor <br>nar bladen faller och en stjarna dor <br>nar livet vander <br>ska jag annu be <br><br>kom ge mej varlden <br>kom ge mej fred <br>kom sank ditt huvud <br>och lagg dej ner <br>kom ge mej kroppen <br>kom ge mej allt som du har <br>och jag ska stanna kvar]]></content><category term="Ted Gardestad" label="Ted Gardestad"/><category term="Come Give Me Love" label="Come Give Me Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/Ett_stilla_regn/</id><title>Ted Gardestad - Ett stilla regn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/Ett_stilla_regn/" title="Ted Gardestad - Ett stilla regn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ett stilla regn, fyller sparen efter mina steg <br>ett stilla regn, moter marken pa min vandringsvag <br>Ett stilla regn <br><br>det faller parlor fran himmlen och jag kan kanna, dom smyckar mitt har <br>Jag blundar lange och tanker a det blir skont, snart kommer en var <br><br>Ett stilla regn, svalkar luften som jag andas in <br>Ett stilla regn, varje vattenpuss ar din och min <br>Ett stilla regn <br><br>Det rinner silver fran taken och jag kan se, hur det blanker mot mig <br>Det brister sakta i molnen och det blir sol, den lyser pa dig <br><br>Ett stilla regn, samlas till en spegel i min hand <br>Ett stilla regn, skoljer snackorna vid havets strand <br><br>Ett stilla regn]]></content><category term="Ted Gardestad" label="Ted Gardestad"/><category term="Ett stilla regn" label="Ett stilla regn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/Sol_vind_och_vatten/</id><title>Ted Gardestad - Sol, vind och vatten - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/Sol_vind_och_vatten/" title="Ted Gardestad - Sol, vind och vatten - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[annu spelar syrsor <br>till vindarnas sus <br>annu rullar kulorna <br>pa skolgardens grus <br>Och an stralar solen <br>pa brunbranda ben <br>annu ruvar faglarna <br>fast timmen ar sen <br><br>Det finns tid till forsoning <br>innan dagen ar forbi <br>For jag tror, jag tror pa friheten <br>jag lever i <br>Och ar det inte verklighet <br>sa drommer jag <br><br>Sol, vind och vatten ar <br>det basta som jag vet <br>men det ar pa dig jag <br>tanker i hemlighet <br>Sol, vind och vatten <br>hoga berg och djupa hav <br>Det, ar mina drommar vavda av <br><br>Jag vill veta vagen <br>till herdarnas hus <br>Jag behover att omges <br>av en ledstjarnas ljus <br>Det skymmer vid sion <br>och natten blir sval <br>Men an doftar blommorna <br>i skuggornas dal <br><br>Det finns tid till forsoning <br>innan natten slagit ut <br>For jag tror, jag tror att livet <br>far ett lyckligt slut <br>Och ar det inte verklighet <br>sa drommer jag <br><br>Sol, vind och vatten ar <br>det basta som jag vet <br>men det ar pa dig jag <br>tanker i hemlighet <br>Sol, vind och vatten <br>hoga berg och djupa hav <br>Det ar mina drommar vavda av <br><br>Sol, vind och vatten <br>hoga berg och djupa hav <br>Det ar mina drommar vavda av <br>Mm, Ja, det ar mina drommar vavda av]]></content><category term="Ted Gardestad" label="Ted Gardestad"/><category term="Sol, vind och vatten" label="Sol, vind och vatten"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/Universum/</id><title>Ted Gardestad - Universum - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ted_Gardestad/Universum/" title="Ted Gardestad - Universum - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Universum <br>finns det plats for mig <br>oppnar du din sjal <br>Sa varm, sa kall <br>Sa stark, sa klen <br>Hur ska var varld se ut <br>Tusen ar fran nu <br><br>Kan vi leva da <br>Kan vi alska da <br>tror du <br><br>Om det fanns en tidsmaksin <br>dar tid gick ut och in <br>kunde jag folja varldens gang <br>fran tid till tid <br>Kunde se hur livet ar <br>nar vara barn tar vid <br><br>Universum <br>Vantar du pa mig <br>Finner jag din sjal <br>Sa smal, sa bred <br>Sa rund, sa lang <br>hur ska var varld se ut <br>Tusen ar fran nu <br><br>Kan vi sjunga da <br>Kan vi skratta da <br>Tror du <br><br>Universums framtidsvy <br>ger bara huvudbry <br>men inatt ska jag somna in <br>och sova lugnt <br>men nar morgondagen gryr <br>blir da mitt huvud tungt]]></content><category term="Ted Gardestad" label="Ted Gardestad"/><category term="Universum" label="Universum"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Pedaco_De_Mim/</id><title>Simone - Pedaco De Mim - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Pedaco_De_Mim/" title="Simone - Pedaco De Mim - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, pedaco de mim <br>Oh, metade afastada de mim <br>Leva o teu olhar <br>Que a saudade e o pior tormento <br>e pior do que o esquecimento <br>e pior do que se entrevar <br><br>Oh, pedaco de mim <br>Oh, metade exilada de mim <br>Leva os teus sinais <br>Que a saudade doi como um barco <br>Que aos poucos descreve um arco <br>E evita atracar no cais <br><br>Oh, pedaco de mim <br>Oh, metade arrancada de mim <br>Leva o vulto teu <br>Que a saudade e o reves de um parto <br>A saudade e arrumar o quarto <br>Do filho que ja morreu <br><br>Oh, pedaco de mim <br>Oh, metade amputada de mim <br>Leva o que ha de ti <br>Que a saudade doi latejada <br>e assim como uma fisgada <br>No membro que ja perdi <br><br>Oh, pedaco de mim <br>Oh, metade adorada de mim <br>Lava os olhos meus <br>Que a saudade e o pior castigo <br>E eu nao quero levar comigo <br>A mortalha do amor, adeus]]></content><category term="Simone" label="Simone"/><category term="Pedaco De Mim" label="Pedaco De Mim"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Itamarandiba/</id><title>Simone - Itamarandiba - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Itamarandiba/" title="Simone - Itamarandiba - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No meio do meu caminho <br>Sempre havera uma pedra <br>Plantarei a minha casa <br>Numa cidade de pedra <br>Itamarandiba, pedra comida <br>Pedra miuda rolando sem vida <br>Como e miuda e quase sem brilho <br>A vida do povo que mora no vale <br>No caminho dessa cidade <br>Passaras por Turmalina <br>Sonharas com Pedra Azul <br>Viveras em Diamantina <br>No caminho dessa cidade <br>As mulheres sao morenas <br>Os homens serao felizes <br>Como se fossem meninos]]></content><category term="Simone" label="Simone"/><category term="Itamarandiba" label="Itamarandiba"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/To_Voltando/</id><title>Simone - To Voltando - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/To_Voltando/" title="Simone - To Voltando - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pode ir armando o coreto <br>E preparando aquele feijao preto <br>Eu to voltando <br>Poe meia duzia de Brahma pra gelar <br>Muda a roupa de cama <br>Eu to voltando <br><br>Leva o chinelo pra sala de jantar <br>Que e la mesmo que a mala eu vou largar <br>Quero te abracar, pode se perfumar <br>Porque eu to voltando <br><br>Da uma geral, faz um bom defumador <br>Enche a casa de flor <br>Que eu to voltando <br>Pega uma praia, aproveita, ta calor <br>Vai pegando uma cor <br>Que eu to voltando <br><br>Faz um cabelo bonito pra eu notar <br>Que eu so quero mesmo e despentear <br>Quero te agarrar <br>Pode se preparar porque eu to voltando <br>Poe pra tocar na vitrola aquele som <br>Estreia uma camisola <br>Eu to voltando <br><br>Da folga pra empregada <br>Manda a criancada pra casa da avo <br>Que eu to voltando <br>Diz que eu so volto amanha se alguem chamar <br>Telefone nao deixa nem tocar <br>Quero la, la, la, ia, porque eu to voltando]]></content><category term="Simone" label="Simone"/><category term="To Voltando" label="To Voltando"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Saindo_De_Mim/</id><title>Simone - Saindo De Mim - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Saindo_De_Mim/" title="Simone - Saindo De Mim - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Voce foi saindo de mim <br>Com palavras tao leves <br>De uma forma tao branda <br>De quem partiu alegre <br><br>Voce foi saindo de mim <br>Com sorriso impune <br>Como se toda faca <br>Nao tivesse dois gumes <br><br>Voce foi saindo de mim <br>Devagar e pra sempre <br>De uma forma sincera <br>Definitivamente <br><br>Voce foi saindo de mim <br>Por todos os meus poros <br>E ainda esta saindo <br><br>Nas vezes em que choro <br>Nas vezes em que choro <br><br>Voce foi saindo de mim]]></content><category term="Simone" label="Simone"/><category term="Saindo De Mim" label="Saindo De Mim"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Vento_Nordeste/</id><title>Simone - Vento Nordeste - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Vento_Nordeste/" title="Simone - Vento Nordeste - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Criancas nos claros da tarde <br>Cachorros na boca da noite <br>Os galos nos dentes do dia <br>Cada desejo e um acoite <br><br>Eu nunca volto nem vou, apenas sou <br>Eu nunca volto nem vou, apenas sou <br><br>Aberta aquela janela <br>Este peito estrangulado <br>O que nao digo me queima <br>Nao satisfaz o falado <br><br>Nao te odeio nem te amo, apenas chamo <br>Nao te odeio nem te amo, apenas chamo <br><br>Viaja o vento nordeste <br>Cavalo do meu segredo <br>Se estas comigo distraio <br>Se vais, eu morro de medo <br><br>Eu nao me lembro nem esqueco, adormeco <br>Eu nao me lembro nem esqueco, adormeco]]></content><category term="Simone" label="Simone"/><category term="Vento Nordeste" label="Vento Nordeste"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Outra_Vez/</id><title>Simone - Outra Vez - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Outra_Vez/" title="Simone - Outra Vez - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Voce foi o maior dos meus casos <br>De todos os abracos o que eu nunca esqueci <br>Voce foi dos amores que eu tive <br>O mais complicado e o mais simples pra mim <br>Voce foi o melhor dos meus erros <br>A mais estranha historia que alguem ja escreveu <br>E e por essas e outras que a minha saudade <br>Faz lembrar de tudo outra vez <br>Voce foi a mentira sincera <br>Brincadeira mais seria que me aconteceu <br>Voce foi o caso mais antigo <br>O amor mais amigo que me apareceu <br>Das lembrancas que eu trago na vida <br>Voce e a saudade que eu gosto de ter <br>So assim sinto voce bem perto de mim outra vez <br>Esqueci de tentar te esquecer <br>Resolvi te querer por querer <br>Decidi te lembrar quantas vezes eu tenha vontade <br>Sem nada perder <br>Voce foi toda a felicidade <br>Voce foi a maldade que so me fez bem <br>Voce foi o melhor dos meus planos <br>E o pior dos enganos que eu pude fazer <br>Das lembrancas que eu trago na vida <br>Voce e a saudade que eu gosto de ter <br>So assim sinto voce bem perto de mim outra vez]]></content><category term="Simone" label="Simone"/><category term="Outra Vez" label="Outra Vez"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Cordilheira/</id><title>Simone - Cordilheira - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Cordilheira/" title="Simone - Cordilheira - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Eu quero ter a sensacao das cordilheiras <br>Desabando sobre as flores inocentes e rasteiras <br>Eu quero ver a procissao dos suicidas <br>Caminhando para a morte pelo bem de nossas vidas <br><br>Eu quero crer na solucao dos evangelhos <br>Obrigando os nossos mocos ao poder dos nossos velhos <br>Eu quero ler o coracao dos comandantes <br>Condenando os seus soldados pela orgia dos farsantes <br><br>Eu quero apenas ser cruel naturalmente <br>E descobrir onde o mal nasce e destruir sua semente <br>Eu quero apenas ser cruel naturalmente <br>E descobrir onde o mal nasce e destruir sua semente <br><br>Eu quero ter a sensacao das cordilheiras <br>Desabando sobre as flores inocentes e rasteiras <br>Eu quero ser da legiao dos grandes mitos <br>Transformando a juventude num exercito de aflitos <br><br>Eu quero ver a ascensao de Iscariotes <br>E no sabado um Jesus crucificado em cada poste <br>Eu quero ler na sagracao dos estandartes <br>Uma frase escrita a fogo pelo punho de deus Marte <br><br>Desabando sobre as flores <br>Caminhando para a morte <br>Obrigando os nossos mocos <br>Condenando os seus soldados <br>Transformando a juventude <br>Um Jesus crucificado <br>Eu quero ter a sensacao das cordilheiras]]></content><category term="Simone" label="Simone"/><category term="Cordilheira" label="Cordilheira"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Condenados/</id><title>Simone - Condenados - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Condenados/" title="Simone - Condenados - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ah, meu amor, estamos condenados <br>Nos ja podemos dizer que somos um <br>Nos somos um <br>E nessa fase do amor em que se e um <br>e que perdemos a metade cada um <br><br>Ah, meu amor, estamos mais safados <br>Hoje tiramos mais proveito do prazer <br>E somos um <br>Quando dormimos juntos, sonhos separados <br>Que nos nao vamos confessar de modo algum <br><br>Ah, meu amor, ah, meu amor <br>Quantas pequenas traicoes <br>Pobres mentiras diplomaticas <br>De puras intencoes, estamos condenados <br><br>Ah, meu amor, de discretos pecados <br>Formamos esse ser tao uno divisivel <br>Parece incrivel <br>Que nos tentemos que ele dure eternamente <br>Nessas metades incompletas, mas decentes <br><br>Ah, meu amor, estamos mais safados <br>Hoje tiramos mais proveito do prazer <br>E somos um <br>Quando dormimos juntos, sonhos separados <br>Que nos nao vamos confessar de modo algum <br><br>Ah, meu amor, ah, meu amor, ah, meu amor]]></content><category term="Simone" label="Simone"/><category term="Condenados" label="Condenados"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Povo_Da_Raca_Brasil/</id><title>Simone - Povo Da Raca Brasil - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Povo_Da_Raca_Brasil/" title="Simone - Povo Da Raca Brasil - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Poe a mao na agua, poe a mao no fogo <br>Poe a mao na brasa do meu coracao <br>Poe a mao na magoa, poe a mao no povo <br>Poe a mao na massa pra fazer o pao <br><br>Ponha fe na vida, ponha o pe na terra <br>Fale com quem fala o mesmo que voce <br>Sonhe com quem sonha o mesmo que voce <br>Viva com o povo da raca Brasil <br><br>Poe a mao na agua, poe a mao no fogo <br>Poe a mao na brasa do meu coracao <br>Poe a mao na magoa, poe a mao no povo <br>Poe a mao na massa pra fazer o pao <br><br>Venha para a rua ver o movimento <br>De Joao, Maria, Tereza e Jose <br>Gente que nasceu, amou, sofreu aqui <br>Todo dia carregando a mesma cruz <br><br>Poe a mao na agua, poe a mao no fogo <br>Poe a mao na brasa do meu coracao <br>Poe a mao na magoa, poe a mao no povo <br>Poe a mao na massa pra fazer o pao <br><br>Mate a minha sede, mate a minha fome <br>Faca do meu corpo o seu corpo irmao <br>Com um no bem dado como um cipo <br>Que ninguem consegue nunca desatar <br><br>Poe a mao na agua, poe a mao no fogo <br>Poe a mao na brasa do meu coracao <br>Poe a mao na magoa, poe a mao no povo <br>Poe a mao na massa pra fazer o pao <br><br>Sonhe com um sonho que ninguem sonhara <br>Sonhe com um povo gemeo siames <br>Que nenhuma forca pode separar <br>Que nasceu unido e unido vai viver <br><br>Poe a mao na agua, poe a mao no fogo <br>Poe a mao na brasa do meu coracao <br>Poe a mao na magoa, poe a mao no povo <br>Poe a mao na massa pra fazer o pao]]></content><category term="Simone" label="Simone"/><category term="Povo Da Raca Brasil" label="Povo Da Raca Brasil"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Sob_Medida/</id><title>Simone - Sob Medida - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Sob_Medida/" title="Simone - Sob Medida - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Se voce cre em Deus erga as maos para os ceus e agradeca <br>Quando me cobicou sem querer acertou na cabeca <br>Eu sou sua alma gemea <br>Sou sua femea, seu par, sua irma <br>Seu jeito, seu gesto <br>Sou perfeita porque igualzinha a voce <br>Eu nao presto, eu nao presto <br>Traicoeira e vulgar sou sem nome e sem lar sou aquela <br>Eu sou filha da rua, eu sou cria da sua costela <br>Sou bandida, sou solta na vida e sob medida <br>Pros carinhos seus <br>Meu amigo, se ajeite comigo e de gracas a Deus <br>Se voce cre em Deus encaminhe pros ceus uma prece <br>E agradeca ao Senhor, voce tem o amor que merece]]></content><category term="Simone" label="Simone"/><category term="Sob Medida" label="Sob Medida"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Comecar_De_Novo/</id><title>Simone - Comecar De Novo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simone/Comecar_De_Novo/" title="Simone - Comecar De Novo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Comecar de novo e contar comigo <br>Vai valer a pena ter amanhecido <br>Ter me rebelado, ter me debatido <br>Ter me machucado, ter sobrevivido <br>Ter virado a mesa, ter me conhecido <br>Ter virado o barco, ter me socorrido <br><br>Comecar de novo e contar comigo <br>Vai valer a pena ter amanhecido <br>Sem as tuas garras, sempre tao seguras <br>Sem o teu fantasma, sem tua moldura <br>Sem tuas escoras, sem o teu dominio <br>Sem tuas esporas, sem o teu fascinio <br><br>Comecar de novo e contar comigo <br>Vai valer a pena ter amanhecido <br>Sem as tuas garras, sempre tao seguras <br>Sem o teu fantasma, sem tua moldura <br>Sem tuas escoras, sem o teu dominio <br>Sem tuas esporas, sem o teu fascinio <br><br>Comecar de novo e contar comigo <br>Vai valer a pena ja ter te esquecido]]></content><category term="Simone" label="Simone"/><category term="Comecar De Novo" label="Comecar De Novo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Amazons/Black_Magic_Acoustic/</id><title>The Amazons - Black Magic (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:33:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:33:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Amazons/Black_Magic_Acoustic/" title="The Amazons - Black Magic (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tell me, baby <br>Do you still feel the way you did <br>'Cause I can't tell, baby <br>No, I can't tell what's in your head <br>But I don't know where to turn <br>But if you wanna' change your mind <br>I'll take you and we'll run <br><br>Black magic, come on <br>Just let me on now, I believe <br>Black magic, come on <br><br>You know it's crazy, baby <br>How I still see you in my sleep <br>And I can't shift the way you're always on my mind, mind <br>But I don't know where to turn <br>But if you wanna' change your mind <br>I'll take you and we'll run <br><br>Black magic, come on <br>Just let me on now I believe <br>Black magic, come on <br><br>Don't you let me at all <br>When I've given all I've got to give <br>Black magic, come on <br><br>Do you still feel the way you did <br>Do you still feel the way you did]]></content><category term="The Amazons" label="The Amazons"/><category term="Black Magic (Acoustic)" label="Black Magic (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ida_Jenshus/Someone_To_Love_Live/</id><title>Ida Jenshus - Someone To Love (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:34:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:34:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ida_Jenshus/Someone_To_Love_Live/" title="Ida Jenshus - Someone To Love (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not myself <br>When I'm alone <br>I'm just someone <br><br>I might have known <br>I've always kept <br>Someone close <br>That's when I feel <br>Like me the most <br><br>Driving home I thought of you and I felt cold <br>Will you still be there when I need someone to hold <br><br>Could you be there for me <br>Would you do that for me <br>Will you be that someone I can hold <br><br>You and I <br>Both need our space <br>Life is fast <br>And hard to pace <br>But when I start <br>To feel alone <br>Can't you meet <br>Me back at home <br>Back home <br><br>There's something in me that isn't right <br>Something's missing when you stay out of sight <br><br>Could you be there for me <br>Would you do that for me <br>Could you come somewhere that I belong <br>Would you go there with me <br>When the night surrounds me <br>Would you be that someone I can hold <br><br>In the dark <br>The empty bed <br>Feels like rocks <br>Under my head <br>I can't sleep <br>I'm too tired <br>My strength is gone <br>My nerves are wired <br><br>As I lay here the streets seem far too still <br>Can this emptiness be something you can fill <br><br>Could you be there for me <br>Would you do that for me <br>Could you come somewhere that I belong <br>Would you go there with me <br>When the night surrounds me <br>Will you be that someone I can hold]]></content><category term="Ida Jenshus" label="Ida Jenshus"/><category term="Someone To Love (Live)" label="Someone To Love (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marika_Hackman/Violet/</id><title>Marika Hackman - Violet - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:34:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:34:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marika_Hackman/Violet/" title="Marika Hackman - Violet - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Under violet skies, I watched you give into the wild <br>Some throbbing howl <br>Eat me alive <br>I love your mouth <br><br>I’d like to roll around your tongue <br>Caught like a bicycle spoke <br>You eat, I’ll grow and grow <br>Swelling up until you choke <br><br>With my violet eyes, I'll make you succumb to my mind <br>And through it all <br>I’ll keep you blind and close my mouth <br><br>I hold you here between my teeth <br>Slack like an elephant’s trunk <br>I’ll fight the urge to bite <br>Or I'll get sticky resin in my gums <br><br>I love your mouth <br>I love your mouth <br>I love your mouth <br>I love your mouth <br><br>Under violet skies, I watched you give into the wild <br>Some throbbing howl <br>Eat me alive <br>I love your mouth <br><br>With my violet eyes, I made you succumb to my mind <br>And through it all <br>I kept you blind <br>I love your mouth <br><br>I’d like to roll around your tongue <br>Caught like a bicycle spoke <br>You eat, I’ll grow and grow <br>Swelling up until you choke]]></content><category term="Marika Hackman" label="Marika Hackman"/><category term="Violet" label="Violet"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_E/모해_mohae_Inst/</id><title>San E - 모해 (mohae) (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:35:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:35:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_E/%EB%AA%A8%ED%95%B4_mohae_Inst/" title="San E - 모해 (mohae) (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모해 <br>카톡 한번 훑다가 보내 <br>이상한 뜻 아냐 마 오해 <br>별거 아냐 그냥 뭐 하며 사나 <br>급 생각나서 순수하게 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>커피 밥도 좋고 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>나야 술도 좋고 <br>요즘 뭐 해 바빠 문자 안부 인사차 <br>본지 꽤 된 듯 나 더 잘생겨졌다 <br>웃기지 ㅋㅋ 궁금하지도 않냐 <br>정 없다 넌 참 <br>난 좀 보고 싶던데 <br>근데 진짜 100퍼센트 뻥 안치고 딴 <br>뜻은 없어 이상하게 생각하지 마 <br>Yah you think I'm lying <br>진짜야 난 거짓말 티 나 <br>내 얼굴 봐봐 <br>아차차 우 못 보지 최근 사진 볼래 <br>솔직히 난 아까부터 네 프사 보네 <br>Huh 근데 이거 너야 <br>왜 이리 이뻐진 거야 <br>뭐 한 거야 웃는 이모티콘 하하 <br>모해 <br>카톡 한번 훑다가 보내 <br>이상한 뜻 아냐 마 오해 <br>별거 아냐 그냥 뭐 하며 사나 <br>급 생각나서 순수하게 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>커피 밥도 좋고 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>나야 술도 좋고 <br>근데 왜 아직까지 안 자는 거야 왜 <br>Oh 폰 만지다 보니 나도 그래 <br>사실 한잔했어 수지가 너로 보이네 <br>취한 듯 우 달빛이 널 부르래 <br>로맨틱하지 않니 엄마 왈 <br>근데 넌 왜 없니 <br>인정 어 인정 비커우즈 암 찌질해 <br>그러니 전화도 못 하고 <br>문자로 이렇게 취중진담 <br>김동률 아 뭐래 쓋 <br>넌 언제 편해 <br>나 혼자 얘기하니 <br>왜 계속 답이 없지 <br>아 엄마가 불러 갔니 <br>그건 이해 읽으면 말해 꼭 <br>뭐래 <br>카톡 한번 훑다가 보내 <br>이상한 뜻 아냐 마 오해 <br>별거 아냐 그냥 이상한 사람 <br>아 자꾸 연락 와 암튼 <br>모해 넌 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>커피 밥도 좋고 <br>모해 넌 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>나야 술도 좋고 <br>잠깐만 근데 이 사람 <br>이 사람 미쳤나 봐 어머머 <br>무섭게 왜 이래 기다려봐 wait <br>차단했어 암튼 너는 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>커피 밥도 좋고 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>나야 술도 좋고 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>다시 들어와 봤다 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>]]></content><category term="San E" label="San E"/><category term="모해 (mohae) (Inst.)" label="모해 (mohae) (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_E/모해_mohae_Feat_볼빨간사춘기/</id><title>San E - 모해 (mohae) (Feat. 볼빨간사춘기) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:35:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:35:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_E/%EB%AA%A8%ED%95%B4_mohae_Feat_%EB%B3%BC%EB%B9%A8%EA%B0%84%EC%82%AC%EC%B6%98%EA%B8%B0/" title="San E - 모해 (mohae) (Feat. 볼빨간사춘기) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모해 <br>카톡 한번 훑다가 보내 <br>이상한 뜻 아냐 마 오해 <br>별거 아냐 그냥 뭐 하며 사나 <br>급 생각나서 순수하게 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>커피 밥도 좋고 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>나야 술도 좋고 <br>요즘 뭐 해 바빠 문자 안부 인사차 <br>본지 꽤 된 듯 나 더 잘생겨졌다 <br>웃기지 ㅋㅋ 궁금하지도 않냐 <br>정 없다 넌 참 <br>난 좀 보고 싶던데 <br>근데 진짜 100퍼센트 뻥 안치고 딴 <br>뜻은 없어 이상하게 생각하지 마 <br>Yah you think I'm lying <br>진짜야 난 거짓말 티 나 <br>내 얼굴 봐봐 <br>아차차 우 못 보지 최근 사진 볼래 <br>솔직히 난 아까부터 네 프사 보네 <br>Huh 근데 이거 너야 <br>왜 이리 이뻐진 거야 <br>뭐 한 거야 웃는 이모티콘 하하 <br>모해 <br>카톡 한번 훑다가 보내 <br>이상한 뜻 아냐 마 오해 <br>별거 아냐 그냥 뭐 하며 사나 <br>급 생각나서 순수하게 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>커피 밥도 좋고 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>나야 술도 좋고 <br>근데 왜 아직까지 안 자는 거야 왜 <br>Oh 폰 만지다 보니 나도 그래 <br>사실 한잔했어 수지가 너로 보이네 <br>취한 듯 우 달빛이 널 부르래 <br>로맨틱하지 않니 엄마 왈 <br>근데 넌 왜 없니 <br>인정 어 인정 비커우즈 암 찌질해 <br>그러니 전화도 못 하고 <br>문자로 이렇게 취중진담 <br>김동률 아 뭐래 쓋 <br>넌 언제 편해 <br>나 혼자 얘기하니 <br>왜 계속 답이 없지 <br>아 엄마가 불러 갔니 <br>그건 이해 읽으면 말해 꼭 <br>뭐래 <br>카톡 한번 훑다가 보내 <br>이상한 뜻 아냐 마 오해 <br>별거 아냐 그냥 이상한 사람 <br>아 자꾸 연락 와 암튼 <br>모해 넌 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>커피 밥도 좋고 <br>모해 넌 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>나야 술도 좋고 <br>잠깐만 근데 이 사람 <br>이 사람 미쳤나 봐 어머머 <br>무섭게 왜 이래 기다려봐 wait <br>차단했어 암튼 너는 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>커피 밥도 좋고 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>나야 술도 좋고 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>다시 들어와 봤다 <br>모해 모해 모해 모해 모해 <br>]]></content><category term="San E" label="San E"/><category term="모해 (mohae) (Feat. 볼빨간사춘기)" label="모해 (mohae) (Feat. 볼빨간사춘기)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chantal_Acda/Fight_Back_Radio_Edit/</id><title>Chantal Acda - Fight Back (Radio Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:36:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:36:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chantal_Acda/Fight_Back_Radio_Edit/" title="Chantal Acda - Fight Back (Radio Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When it brightens the dark we al had <br>And stayed like that <br>Keep me walking and breathing instead <br>We are all like that <br>Hard to notice and good to forget <br>Stay here with us <br>A song kept in pieces <br>Story well kept <br>How we noticed better well I fought back <br>To belong somewhere hidden in books <br>We will loose track <br>Lost track <br>And I fought to find hidden places we might <br>Please don't loose a soul <br>To keep balanced and more <br>I don't see how this could be certain <br>Could be missed <br>We all sought this warmth <br>Water floating then died <br><br>They are hunting for lifes we regret <br>They are wrong there <br>Broken families and children in bed <br>They will hear them <br>Keep alike going as simple as that <br>We should fight back <br>We should fight back <br>And I fought to find hidden places we might <br>Please don't loose a soul <br>To keep balanced and more <br>I don't see how this could be certain <br>Could be missed <br>We all sought this warmth <br>Water floating then died <br><br>And I fought to find hidden places we might <br>Please don't loose a soul <br>To keep balanced and more <br>I don't see how this could be certain <br>Could be missed <br>We all sought this warmth <br>Water floating then died]]></content><category term="Chantal Acda" label="Chantal Acda"/><category term="Fight Back (Radio Edit)" label="Fight Back (Radio Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Love_For_Sale/</id><title>Shirley Horn - Love For Sale - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:36:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:36:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Love_For_Sale/" title="Shirley Horn - Love For Sale - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love for sale, appetizing, young love for sale <br>Love that's fresh and still unspoiled <br>Love that's only slightly soiled <br>Love for sale <br><br>Who will buy <br>Who would like to sample my supply <br>Who's prepared to pay the price <br>For a trip to paradise Love for sale <br><br>Let the poet's pipe of love in their childish way <br>I know every type of love better far than they <br>If you want the thrill of love I've been through the mill of love <br>Old love, new love, every love but true love <br><br>Love for sale, appetizing, young love for sale <br>If you want to buy my wares <br>Follow me and climb the stairs <br>'Cause I've got love, nothing but love <br>I've got love for sale]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="Love For Sale" label="Love For Sale"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Its_Love/</id><title>Shirley Horn - It`s Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:36:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:36:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Its_Love/" title="Shirley Horn - It`s Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've always been just a little bit involved <br>With this boy or that, and that was that <br>I thought that love was a game of kiss and run <br>He tipped his hat, and that was that, then bang <br>Out of the blue something happened, something new, you <br><br>It's love, it's love <br>Well, who would've thought it <br>If this is love then why have I fought it <br>What a way to feel, I could touch the sky <br>What a way to feel, I have found my guy <br><br>It's love at last, I've someone to cheer for <br>It's love at last, I've learnt what I'm here for <br>I've heard it said, you would know it when you see it <br>Well, I see it, I know it, it's love <br><br>It's love, it's love <br>Well, who would've thought it <br>If this is love then why have I fought it <br>What a way to feel, I could touch the sky <br>What a way to feel, I have found my guy <br><br>It's love at last, I've someone to cheer for <br>It's love at last, I've learnt what we're here for <br>I've heard it said, you would know it when you see it <br>Well, I see it, I know it, I feel it, it's love]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="It`s Love" label="It`s Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Do_It_Again/</id><title>Shirley Horn - Do It Again - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:36:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:36:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Do_It_Again/" title="Shirley Horn - Do It Again - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You really shouldn't have done it <br>You hadn't any right <br>I really shouldn't have let you <br>Kiss me <br>And although it was wrong <br>I never was strong <br>So as long as you've begun it <br>And you know you shouldn't have done it <br><br>Oh <br>Do it again <br>I may say no, no, no, no, no <br>But do it again <br>My lips just ache <br>To have you take the kiss <br>That's waiting for you <br>You know if you do <br>You won't regret it <br>Come and get it <br><br>Oh <br>No one is near <br>I may cry oh Oh oh oh oh <br>But no one can hear <br>Mamma may scold me <br>Coz' she told me <br>It was naughty but then <br><br>Please <br>Do it again <br>Yes do it again And again and again and again and again and again <br>Turn out the light <br>And hold me close <br>In your arms <br>All through the night <br>I know tomorrow morning <br>You will say <br>Goodbye and amen <br><br>But until then <br>Please do it again]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="Do It Again" label="Do It Again"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/The_Second_Time_Around/</id><title>Shirley Horn - The Second Time Around - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:36:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:36:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/The_Second_Time_Around/" title="Shirley Horn - The Second Time Around - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love is lovelier the second time around <br>Just as wonderful with both feet on the ground <br>It's that second time you hear your love song sung <br>Makes you think perhaps that love, like youth, is wasted on the young <br>Love's more comfortable the second time you fall <br>Like a friendly home the second time you call <br>Who can say what brought us to this miracle we've found <br>There are those who'll bet love comes but once, and yet <br>I'm oh, so glad we met the second time around <br>Who can say what brought us to this miracle we've found <br>There are those who'll bet love comes but once, and yet <br>I'm oh, so glad we met the second time around]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="The Second Time Around" label="The Second Time Around"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Only_The_Lonely/</id><title>Shirley Horn - Only The Lonely - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:36:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:36:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Only_The_Lonely/" title="Shirley Horn - Only The Lonely - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Each place I go, only the lonely go <br>Some little small cafe <br>The songs I know, only the lonely know <br>Each melody recalls a love that used to be <br><br>The dreams I dream, only the lonely dream <br>Of lips as warm as May <br>That hopeless scheme, only the lonely scheme <br>That soon somewhere you'll find the one that used to care <br><br>And you'll recall each fun time <br>Those picnics at the beach when love was new <br>It well could be the one time <br>A hopeless little dream like that comes true <br><br>If you find love, hang on to each caress <br>And never let love go <br>For when it's gone you'll know the loneliness <br>The heartbreak only the lonely know]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="Only The Lonely" label="Only The Lonely"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Ten_Cents_A_Dance/</id><title>Shirley Horn - Ten Cents A Dance - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:36:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:36:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Ten_Cents_A_Dance/" title="Shirley Horn - Ten Cents A Dance - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ten cents a dance, that's what they pay me <br>Gosh, how they weigh me down <br>Ten cents a dance, pansies and rough guys <br>Tough guys who tear my gown <br><br>Seven to midnight I hear drums <br>Loudly the saxophone blows <br>Trumpets are tearing my eardrums <br>Customers crush my toes <br><br>Sometimes I think I've found my hero <br>But it's a queer romance <br>All that you need is a ticket <br>Come on, big boy, ten cents a dance]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="Ten Cents A Dance" label="Ten Cents A Dance"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Theres_A_Boat_Thats_Leavin_Soon_For_New_York_From_Porgy_And_Bess/</id><title>Shirley Horn - There`s A Boat That`s Leavin` Soon For New York (From `Porgy And Bess`) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:37:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:37:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Theres_A_Boat_Thats_Leavin_Soon_For_New_York_From_Porgy_And_Bess/" title="Shirley Horn - There`s A Boat That`s Leavin` Soon For New York (From `Porgy And Bess`) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[That's the thing, ain' it An' membuh there's <br>Where that come from Listen There's a boat dat's <br>Leavin' soon for New York Come wid me, dat's where <br>We belong, sister <br><br>You an' me kin live dat high life in New York <br>Come wid me, dere you can't go wrong, sister <br>I'll buy you de swellest mansion <br>Up on upper Fi'th Avenue <br><br>An' through Harlem we'll go struttin' <br>We'll go astruttin' <br>An' dere'll be nuttin' <br>Too good for you <br><br>I'll dress you in silks and satins <br>In de latest Paris styles <br>And de blues you'll be forgettin' <br>You'll be forgettin' <br><br>There'll be no frettin' <br>Jes nothin' but smiles <br>Come along wid me, Hey dat's de place <br>Don't be a fool, come along, come along <br><br>There's a boat dat's leavin' soon for New York <br>Come wid me, dat's where we belong, sister <br>Dat's where we belong Come on, Bess <br><br>You low, crawlin' hound Get away from my door, I tells <br>You, leave it, you rattlesnake Dat's what you is <br>A rattlesnake]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="There`s A Boat That`s Leavin` Soon For New York (From `Porgy And Bess`)" label="There`s A Boat That`s Leavin` Soon For New York (From `Porgy And Bess`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/My_Future_Just_Passed_From_Safety_In_Numbers/</id><title>Shirley Horn - My Future Just Passed (From `Safety In Numbers`) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:37:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:37:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/My_Future_Just_Passed_From_Safety_In_Numbers/" title="Shirley Horn - My Future Just Passed (From `Safety In Numbers`) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There goes the boy I dreamed all through school about <br>There goes the boy I'll now be a fool about <br>Ring down the curtain, I'm certain at present <br>My future just passed <br><br>Don't even know if he has been spoken for <br>If he is tied, the ties must be broken, for <br>Life can't be that way,to wake me then break me <br>My future just passed <br><br>Stars in the blue, tho' you're at a distance <br>You can at least reassure me <br>Sometimes a girl encounters resistance <br>Help Me to win this boy <br><br>Here are my arms, may she find illusion there <br>Look in my heart, there is no confusion there <br>Now that I'm loving, I'm living at last <br>My future just passed]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="My Future Just Passed (From `Safety In Numbers`)" label="My Future Just Passed (From `Safety In Numbers`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Loads_Of_Love/</id><title>Shirley Horn - Loads Of Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:37:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:37:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shirley_Horn/Loads_Of_Love/" title="Shirley Horn - Loads Of Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I never have been handed much <br>I never have demanded much <br>I just want money, a nice position and loads of lovely love <br>I never have expected much <br>I never have rejected much <br>I want my dinner, some smart conversation and loads of lovely love <br><br>Some people go for quantity <br>Others go for quality <br><br>I've got the answer now it's not how much but how <br>I do not ask for bliss I guess it all boils down to this I guess <br>I just want money and then more money and loads of lovely love <br>I just want money, a nice position and loads of lovely love <br>I want my dinner, some smart conversation and loads of lovely love <br>I just want money and then more money and loads of lovely love <br><br>Some people go for quantity <br>Others go for quality <br><br>I've got the answer now it's not how much but how <br>I do not ask for bliss I guess it all boils down to this I guess <br>I just want money and then more money and loads of lovely love <br>Loads of lovely love <br>I want my dinner, some smart conversation, a nice position will do <br>But I want loads and loads and loads of lovely love]]></content><category term="Shirley Horn" label="Shirley Horn"/><category term="Loads Of Love" label="Loads Of Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Never_Ever_Land/</id><title>Trippie Redd - Never Ever Land - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:38:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:38:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Never_Ever_Land/" title="Trippie Redd - Never Ever Land - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Big 14 , know what the fuck goin' on <br>Ooooooohhhh, yeah <br>A love to you, you lil' lil' lil' bitch <br><br>Headed to the top, baby you and I <br>We in love baby, you and I <br>I think we gon' be okay, baby you and I <br>'Cause I don't give a fuck unless it's just you and I <br>We gone argue and break up, baby you and I <br>Then make up and make love, baby you and I <br>I'ma tell you how I feel when the time is right <br>Tell you how I feel when the time is right <br>Baby I love, you, ayy <br>Baby I love, you, ayy <br>You, you <br><br>shawty sippin' Rozay with me <br>Girl you got my love lil' baby, don't play with me <br>Say you mine's lil' baby, don't play with me <br>I play with he, so never run game on me <br>And you know I keep a motherfuckin' K on me <br>You talk down my lil' baby she gon' spray with me <br>Like A to Z, they love me 'cause my cadences <br>We gone make it to the top, baby wait and see, wait and see <br>Back on the scene with my baby <br>Countin' all this guap with my baby <br><br>Headed to the top, baby you and I <br>We in love baby, you and I <br>I think we gon' be okay, baby you and I <br>'Cause I don't give a fuck unless it's just you and I <br>We gone argue and break up, baby you and I <br>Then make up and make love, baby you and I <br>I'ma tell you how I feel when the time is right <br>Tell you how I feel when the time is right <br>And I love]]></content><category term="Trippie Redd" label="Trippie Redd"/><category term="Never Ever Land" label="Never Ever Land"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Can_You_Rap_Like_Me_/</id><title>Trippie Redd - Can You Rap Like Me? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:38:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:38:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Can_You_Rap_Like_Me_/" title="Trippie Redd - Can You Rap Like Me? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Remember, there's always tomorrow <br>P Soul on the track <br><br>Uh, ayy, uh, ayy, uh <br>Can you rap like me huh <br>Uh, ayy, uh, ayy, uh <br>I gotta get my fresh paper boy <br>Optimistic, inflicted the <br>My vision a place I visit while lifted <br>Moolah I get it get it, the life I live my decision <br>They told me to go and get it <br>I got it so now I'm living <br>Revolution of fury, the lean got my vision blurry <br>Ballin' like Stephen Curry <br>Gold fangs in my mouth so purty <br>Trippie bring demolition and I ain't talking no derbies <br>Absorb your flow like I'm Kirby <br>The lies you tell will not hurt me <br>Try to reach for the stars if people don't get too far <br>They want all of the money, all the expensive cars <br>It's few people that ever make it but yet I still gotta go hard <br>A lot of artists that make it are evil, hearts black as tar, yeah <br>Ok and this for every rapper that had a shot at sending me <br>Your efforts ain't getting you anywhere in this industry <br>Lyrically demonically dominate your flow, illest ly <br>My venomous rhymes wine and dine on you mentally <br>Motivate the motivations, said got too much chemistry <br>Fatality, like Liu Kang told me to finish him <br>Even a hawk couldn't take this much intensity <br>I'm the bullet in the barrel in the gun that shot Kennedy <br>Mind is racing 'bout hating, contemplation with Haitians <br>Jamaicans, sitting on five g pacing <br>Back and forth, waiting and dating <br>You get the picture, don't take this <br>Boy this life is real, you couldn't fake this <br>Throw it up, regurgitation <br>Can't shit on me, you constipated <br>Is you mad 'cause we do this on a daily basis <br>Yeah, or is you mad 'cause we made it <br>Every day faded, we out here paper chasing bitch, ahh <br>Ayy, ahh, ayy, ahh, ayy <br>Can you rap like me huh <br>Ayy, ahh, ayy, ahh, ayy, ahh <br>Can you rap like me]]></content><category term="Trippie Redd" label="Trippie Redd"/><category term="Can You Rap Like Me?" label="Can You Rap Like Me?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Limitless/</id><title>Trippie Redd - Limitless - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:38:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:38:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Limitless/" title="Trippie Redd - Limitless - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[14, 14, 14 baby <br>Woah, 14, 14, 14 baby <br>Huh <br><br>All my life I been limitless, nigga never had a limit, huh <br>Yeah, rollin' around in the Rari, you still in the Civic <br>Yeah, rollin' around in my city, I feel like I'm Diddy <br>Yeah, all these niggas they some suckers, I show 'em no pity <br>Young nigga gotta floss, hey <br>Dabbing on 'em with the sauce, huh <br>Feeling like a young boss, huh <br>Feeling like I'm Rick Ross, huh <br>Hundred dollars in the city man <br>All these fuck niggas man they hate it, huh <br>Now I made it out, when I come back better show appreciation <br><br>Appreciate my time difference <br>Appreciate my rhymes different <br>Appreciate my grind different <br>Appreciate that I did it <br>Appreciate that I did it, appreciate that I did it <br>Actavis with oil sippin', Actavis with oil sippin' yeah <br>This thirty got me limping, woah <br>Ball like Scottie Pippen, yeah <br>They hate me 'cause I'm different, woah yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Appreciate my time difference <br>Appreciate my rhymes different <br>Appreciate my grind different <br>Appreciate that I did it <br>Appreciate that I did it, appreciate that I did it <br>Actavis with oil sippin', Actavis with oil sippin' woah <br><br>All my life I been limitless, nigga never had a limit, huh <br>Yeah, rollin' around in the Rari, you still in the Civic <br>Yeah, rollin' around in my city, I feel like I'm Diddy <br>Yeah, all these niggas they some suckers, I show 'em no pity <br>Young nigga gotta floss, hey <br>Dabbing on 'em with the sauce, huh <br>Feeling like a young boss, huh <br>Feeling like I'm Rick Ross, huh <br>Hundred dollars in the city man <br>All these fuck niggas man they hate it, huh <br>Now I made it out, when I come back better show appreciation <br><br>I been trippin' all week off the narcotics <br>Takeoff on Pluto, got some hoes beside me <br>Sipping Hi Tech, moving like a zombie <br>That boy say he looking for me, come and find me <br>Pull up with trip and we tweaking <br>VVS's on me blinging <br>Smoking dope with the demons <br>Dress according to the seasons <br>Pop a perc, then I leave the surf <br>I ain't coming back <br>I'm making plays in the field like a running back <br>Louis V tennis shoes, I'm trapping on avenues <br>Alexander McQueen my protege <br>I'm sipping on lean out of lemonade <br>I pop me a xan then I levitate <br>You can't live how I live <br>'cause I wake up every day with pints in my fridge <br><br>All my life I been limitless, nigga never had a limit, huh <br>Yeah, rollin' around in the Rari, you still in the Civic <br>Yeah, rollin' around in my city, I feel like I'm Diddy <br>Yeah, all these niggas they some suckers, I show 'em no pity <br>Young nigga gotta floss, hey <br>Dabbing on 'em with the sauce, huh <br>Feeling like a young boss, huh <br>Feeling like I'm Rick Ross, huh <br>Hundred dollars in the city man <br>All these fuck niggas man they hate it, huh <br>Now I made it out, when I come back better show appreciation <br><br>All of my life I been limitless <br>My hoes different colors like MandMs <br>I been spending them Benjamins <br>I been spending them Benjamins <br>Some G Star and jeans, yeah <br>I feel no what is <br>I'm fucking on your lil bitch again <br>She sucking all on my dick again <br>Pull up to the club, these hoes like there he go <br>She so thick woah, I might just take this bitch home <br>Yeah, my Rafs fit like a moose <br>Her pussy so wet like some goop <br>Nigga want beef, I'm like who <br>Shoot at your ass like a hoop <br><br>All my life I been limitless, nigga never had a limit, huh <br>Yeah, rollin' around in the Rari, you still in the Civic <br>Yeah, rollin' around in my city, I feel like I'm Diddy <br>Yeah, all these niggas they some suckers, I show 'em no pity <br>Young nigga gotta floss, hey <br>Dabbing on 'em with the sauce, huh <br>Feeling like a young boss, huh <br>Feeling like I'm Rick Ross, huh <br>Hundred dollars in the city man <br>All these fuck niggas man they hate it, huh <br>Now I made it out, when I come back better show appreciation]]></content><category term="Trippie Redd" label="Trippie Redd"/><category term="Limitless" label="Limitless"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Stoves_On_14th_Feat_Black_Jezuss/</id><title>Trippie Redd - Stoves On 14th (Feat. Black Jezuss) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:38:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:38:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Stoves_On_14th_Feat_Black_Jezuss/" title="Trippie Redd - Stoves On 14th (Feat. Black Jezuss) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Drop my top down <br>I feel good <br>Drop my top down <br>In yo hood <br>Steady, spending <br>on them drugs <br>Made it out the trenches nigga <br>Made it out the mud woah <br><br>I hope these young niggas learn <br>I hope these stupid bitches learn <br>I hope these stupid bitches burn <br>Better thank god that they learn <br>Better pray to god that they learn <br>Cause in my hood they on bad terms <br>So imma make these niggas hurt wooaa <br>Thank god for the stove <br>Thank tom for a stove <br>Without edison I wouldn't be here <br>So I thank god for the stove <br>Gotta thank time for the stove <br>Gotta thank my mom for the stove <br>Gotta thank the block for the stove wooaa <br><br>Drop my top down <br>I feel good <br>Drop my top down <br>In yo hood <br>Steady, spending <br>on them drugs <br>Made it out the trenches nigga <br>Made it out the mud woah <br><br>Made it out the trenches <br>I made it out the hood <br>They want me back in the hood <br>So I can't lack in my hood <br>Cause niggas hating on me <br>They want me resting for good <br>So I told in my hood <br>To still make sure that I'm good <br>just like it's a chopper <br>I see it I like it yo bitch I might swap her <br>Lil trippie at glizzy's house so I might pop ya <br>They save me can't save till the get a doctor <br><br>Drop my top down <br>I feel good <br>Drop my top down <br>In yo hood <br>Steady, spending <br>on them drugs <br>Made it out the trenches nigga <br>Made it out the mud woahh <br><br>Drop my top down <br>I feel good <br>Drop my top down <br>In yo hood <br>Steady, spending <br>on them drugs <br>Made it out the trenches nigga <br>Made it out the mud woahh <br><br>Yeah Yeah, Yeah Yeah <br>Yeah Yeah, Yeah Yeah <br>Yeah Yeah, Yeah Yeah <br>Yeah Yeah, Yeah Yeah]]></content><category term="Trippie Redd" label="Trippie Redd"/><category term="Stoves On 14th (Feat. Black Jezuss)" label="Stoves On 14th (Feat. Black Jezuss)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/No_Smoke_No_Smoke_1400_BC___Sauce_Feat_Pachino/</id><title>Trippie Redd - No Smoke No Smoke 1400 B.C. / Sauce (Feat. Pachino) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:38:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:38:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/No_Smoke_No_Smoke_1400_BC___Sauce_Feat_Pachino/" title="Trippie Redd - No Smoke No Smoke 1400 B.C. / Sauce (Feat. Pachino) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All these shooters with me, yeah they on go, ayy <br><br>Swear they don't want smoke, no <br>Haters don't want smoke <br>No smoke, no smoke <br>They don't want no smoke <br><br>They don't want no smoke, on the block with my goons <br>I hit a nigga up, I don't like to pick and choose <br>I just fuck on every ho that come into my DMs <br>I be getting all this money, I don't spend it on BMs <br>I ain't got no baby but your bitch my lil baby <br>Dare a nigga play me, I'ma shoot him, is you crazy <br>Yeah I'm going brazy, off the codeine, bitch I'm brazy <br>Blowing all this dope, it got me motherfuckin' lazy <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah <br><br>Dripping in the sauce <br>It don't make sense, all this motherfuckin' sauce <br>It don't make sense, all this motherfuckin' sauce <br>It don't make sense, all this motherfuckin' sauce <br><br>It don't make sense, all this motherfuckin' sauce <br>Put water on the Rollie, and the wrist yeah that's DeVoss <br>I don't like your bitch 'cause she keep asking what it cost <br>You ain't a boss if you ain't never took a loss <br>Said he put it on the B's, yeah he put it on the B's <br>Even if he ain't crip, man I hope them niggas C <br>Man if she ain't topping then that bitch she gotta leave <br>I don't smoke no mids, man I only smoke OGs <br>Smoke gorilla, smoke gorilla, like a nigga in the jungle <br>Talking up under they lip, all them niggas do is mumble <br>Out to 10k last week, nigga that's just on a humble <br>And any time I speak I need a bundle when I come through <br><br>Dripping in the sauce <br>It don't make sense, all this motherfuckin' sauce <br>It don't make sense, all this motherfuckin' sauce <br>It don't make sense, all this motherfuckin' sauce]]></content><category term="Trippie Redd" label="Trippie Redd"/><category term="No Smoke No Smoke 1400 B.C. / Sauce (Feat. Pachino)" label="No Smoke No Smoke 1400 B.C. / Sauce (Feat. Pachino)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Poles_1469/</id><title>Trippie Redd - Poles 1469 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:38:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:38:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Poles_1469/" title="Trippie Redd - Poles 1469 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Aye, Big 14, bitch <br>Yuh, aye <br>Whoooa, saucy, yaaah <br>Huh, aye <br><br>1400, bitch, you know I tote a pole <br>With 6ix9ine, bitch, you know we tote them poles <br>Tote a pole, tote a pole, tote a pole <br>You talk down, we gon' let that shit go <br>Let it blow, let it blow, let it blow <br>Got the scope, got the scope, got the scope <br>223's and I put 'em to your nose <br>Let it go, bitch, we let that shit go <br><br>Yeah, and send shots off at your dome <br>Pussy boy, we'll pull up at your home <br>You're home alone, home alone, home alone <br>Hit your chromosome, bitch, chromosome, uh <br>Balling, White Iverson, ain't talking Post Malone <br>Haha, yeah, 14, yeah, 14, yeah, aye, uh <br>Tote a pole, tote a pole, tote a pole <br>Let it go, let it go, let it go <br><br>SCUUUMGAAANG <br>I'm toting big shit big shit <br>Get the wig split wig split <br>4 5, I call out the big bitch big stick <br>We don't miss shit miss shit <br>Get the rims hit limbs hit <br>Hollow tip, hit you with a cross hit <br>Big drum on the gun, that's a pump with a fat beam <br>Catch him in the bed while he sleep, that's a wet dream <br>That's a wet dream <br>This nigga tryna test me <br>Close range, hot shot, nigga, fuck with a vest, b <br>If a nigga try to test me, I off him <br>Put a hole in his head, he a dolphin you a dolphin <br>Pull up to the block, you don't want it <br>Pull up with the Glock, you won't want it <br>I leave a nigga flat, no warning <br>ScumGang, bitch, we on it, you dont want it <br><br>1400, bitch, you know I tote a pole <br>With 6ix9ine, bitch, you know we tote them poles <br>Tote a pole, tote a pole, tote a pole <br>You talk down, we gon' let that shit go <br>Let it blow, let it blow, let it blow <br>Got the scope, got the scope, got the scope <br>223's and I put 'em to your nose <br>Let it go, bitch, we let that shit go]]></content><category term="Trippie Redd" label="Trippie Redd"/><category term="Poles 1469" label="Poles 1469"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/It_Takes_Time/</id><title>Trippie Redd - It Takes Time - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:38:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:38:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/It_Takes_Time/" title="Trippie Redd - It Takes Time - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You know time is of the essence <br>Yeah I tried lil baby <br>Put your feelings to the side lil baby <br>You got too much pride lil baby <br>I ain't have time yesterday <br>But today I got time lil baby <br>'Cause you been up on my mind lil baby <br>I really think you mines lil baby <br>I hope you shine lil baby <br>But this shit takes time lil baby <br>This shit takes time lil baby, yeah <br><br>You know time is of the essence <br>Girl you gotta be patient, you gotta be patient <br>You know time is of the essence <br>Girl you gotta be patient, you gotta be patient <br>Time is of the essence, you know time is of the essence <br>Yeah you gotta be patient, time is of the essence <br>Girl you gotta be patient, you gotta be patient <br><br>Don't got time for a ho <br>I'm on the grind lil ho <br>Sippin' wine lil ho <br>Yeah I'm doing all these shows <br>Blowing dough with some hoes <br>Got some Act to pour, yeah murder what she wrote <br>And you know I took her soul <br>I always take her soul <br>Love scars woe <br>Baby love scars woe <br>Baby hurt to the bone, yeah hurt to the bone <br>I got your bitch hitting my phone <br>She want the dick on the low <br>Yeah I thought you should know <br>Said I thought you should know <br>Run my whole fucking hood like a pope <br>Yeah murder what she wrote <br>I said murder what she wrote <br>'Cause you know I took her soul <br>Yeah you know I took her soul <br>You know I took her soul <br>But I won't be hittin' phones <br><br>You know time is of the essence <br>Yeah I tried lil baby <br>Put your feelings to the side lil baby <br>You got too much pride lil baby <br>I ain't have time yesterday <br>But today I got time lil baby <br>'Cause you been up on my mind lil baby <br>I really think you mines lil baby <br>I hope you shine lil baby <br>But this shit takes time lil baby <br>This shit takes time lil baby, yeah <br><br>You know time is of the essence <br>Girl you gotta be patient, you gotta be patient <br>You know time is of the essence <br>Girl you gotta be patient, you gotta be patient <br>Time is of the essence, you know time is of the essence <br>Yeah you gotta be patient, time is of the essence <br>Girl you gotta be patient, you gotta be patient <br><br>Hundred bands on a coupe <br>Hundred bands on a coupe <br>And I just lost the roof <br>Play a bitch like a flute <br>Yeah you niggas hella poop <br>I'm sending shots at your crew <br>Nigga pow pow pow pow <br>Yeah shoot a bitch down <br>See me 'round, see me pow <br>And I'm shooting AKs <br>SK, RPK, HK <br>Young nigga I aim it at your face <br>To the moon, I'm in space <br>Yeah I just bought my mom a new Wraith <br>Thanking god for a brand new day <br>And I'm on the road, I'm just thinking 'bout your face <br>I'm just thinking 'bout your face <br>Thinking 'bout your face, I been thinking 'bout your face <br><br>You know time is of the essence <br>Yeah I tried lil baby <br>Put your feelings to the side lil baby <br>You got too much pride lil baby <br>I ain't have time yesterday <br>But today I got time lil baby <br>'Cause you been up on my mind lil baby <br>I really think you mines lil baby <br>I hope you shine lil baby <br>But this shit takes time lil baby <br>This shit takes time lil baby, yeah <br><br>You know time is of the essence <br>Girl you gotta be patient, you gotta be patient <br>You know time is of the essence <br>Girl you gotta be patient, you gotta be patient <br>Time is of the essence, you know time is of the essence <br>Yeah you gotta be patient, time is of the essence <br>Girl you gotta be patient, you gotta be patient <br><br>Hundred bands on a coupe <br>Hundred bands on a coupe <br>Hundred bands on a coupe <br>Hundred bands on a coupe]]></content><category term="Trippie Redd" label="Trippie Redd"/><category term="It Takes Time" label="It Takes Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Blade_Of_Woe_Feat_Famous_Dex/</id><title>Trippie Redd - Blade Of Woe (Feat. Famous Dex) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:39:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:39:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Blade_Of_Woe_Feat_Famous_Dex/" title="Trippie Redd - Blade Of Woe (Feat. Famous Dex) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ohhhhh woe huh <br>I'm saucing bitch, yeah ayye <br>Big 14 hoe <br>I thought you knew <br>I thought you knew <br>Hol' up <br><br>It's 'ight yeah, it's 'ight, it's 'ight, it's 'ight, yeah <br>It's 'ight, it's 'ight, it's 'ight, yeah <br>It's 'ight, it's 'ight, it's 'ight, yeah <br><br>Got a knife on my finger, I was stabbed in the back back <br>Stabbed in the back, I was stabbed in the back yeah <br>I'm up at the top, they tried to hold me in the back in the in the back <br>Hold in the back, They tried to hold me in the back <br>They tried to hold me in the back, homie don't get wacked <br>Hanging with them Bs, and you know we yellin' slatt <br>Few niggas talk down, don't want to know the aftermath <br>Keep my brothers 'round me and I keep me a strap <br>Yeah I keep me a MAC, pussy boy your getting tip <br>Dex hit my line and said lil' bro we gotta win we gotta win <br>Got me sitting in the back sipping on that jin <br>1400 gang till' die nigga represent, for the set I represent <br><br>Woah aye I gotta check on my right now <br>Right now Right now Right now Right now Yeah ayye <br><br>It's ight yeah, it's ight, it's ight, it's ight, yeah <br>It's ight, it's ight, it's ight, yeah <br>It's ight, it's ight, it's ight, yeah <br><br>I got my 30 on my waist I do <br>Run up on me I'ma spray I will <br>Tatts up on my face ah what <br>My lil brother beat the case <br>Smoking dopey to the face what <br>Take a knee and say my grace I did <br>My shooters,they don't play ah what <br>Call up Trippie, he don't play yeah ah Dexter <br><br>Woah They tried to stab me in the back <br>They can't keep me in the back <br>I'm signing, I'm signing baby wowwww <br><br>It's ight yeah, it's ight, it's ight, it's ight, yeah <br>It's ight, it's ight, it's ight, yeah <br>It's ight, it's ight, it's ight, yeah <br><br>Got a knife on my finger, I was stabbed in the back back <br>Stabbed in the back, I was stabbed in the back yeah <br>I'm up at the top, they tried to hold me in the back <br>Hold m in the back, tried to hold me in the back]]></content><category term="Trippie Redd" label="Trippie Redd"/><category term="Blade Of Woe (Feat. Famous Dex)" label="Blade Of Woe (Feat. Famous Dex)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jorge_Onate/Se_Te_Hizo_Tarde/</id><title>Jorge Onate - Se Te Hizo Tarde - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:39:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:39:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jorge_Onate/Se_Te_Hizo_Tarde/" title="Jorge Onate - Se Te Hizo Tarde - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pienso que se te hizo tarde <br>para decirme que me quieres <br>para decirme que hoy que amas <br><br>si ayer mataste un gran amor <br>o es que no recuerdas mi alma triste llorando <br>cuando me decias que me alejara <br>que lo que querias no era yo <br>cuantas veces yo esperaba y <br>no llegaba un te amo <br>cuantas veces yo quedaba <br>con las ganas de un beso <br>cuantas veces yo esperaba <br>que me dieras la mano <br>cuanto tiempo yo ocultaba <br>en soledad mi tormento <br><br>y eso no lo sabes tu <br>y eso tu no lo sabes <br>que mientras jugabas al amor, mi amor <br><br>yo me iba olvidando de ti <br><br>se te hizo, se te hizo tarde <br>pa valorar mis sentimientos <br>se te hizo, se te hizo tarde <br>para llevarte aqui dentro <br>y ahora que pena me da <br><br>resulta y pasa que ya no eres mi tormento <br>se te hizo, se te hizo tarde ya yo no te quiero <br><br>aveses suele no tenerte <br>pero no puedo ser el mismo <br>que se moria por tus besos <br>que te entregava el corazon <br>ya no pude seguir <br>como un tonto esperando <br>a que me quizieras, o me dejaras <br>con el alma llena de dolor <br>me canse de amarte tanto y que no hizieras lo mismo <br>me canse de ser aquel que se creia algo tuyo <br>me canse de no creer que mendigaba un cario <br>me aburri de ver que no era <br>casi nada en tu mundo <br>y ahora que vienes a mi <br><br>con tu arrepentimiento <br>quiero que tu sepas que esta ves mi amor <br>esta ves te toca sufrir <br><br>se te hizo, se te hizo tarde <br>pa valorar mis sentimientos <br><br>se te hizo, se te hizo tarde <br>para llevarte aqui dentro <br>y ahora que pena me da <br>resulta y pasa que ya no eres mi tormento <br><br>se te hizo, se te hizo tarde <br>pa valorar mis sentimientos <br>se te hizo, se te hizo tarde <br>ya yo no te quiero]]></content><category term="Jorge Onate" label="Jorge Onate"/><category term="Se Te Hizo Tarde" label="Se Te Hizo Tarde"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Deeply_Scared_Feat_unotheactivist/</id><title>Trippie Redd - Deeply Scared (Feat. unotheactivist) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:39:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:39:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Deeply_Scared_Feat_unotheactivist/" title="Trippie Redd - Deeply Scared (Feat. unotheactivist) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[On foe 'nem <br>Uno said on bro 'nem <br>Yeah <br>Love scars, love scars, love scars <br><br>You been scarred too deep, I can tell <br>I can tell, yeah I can tell <br>You been scarred too deep, I can tell <br>I can tell, yeah I can tell <br>You been scarred too deep, I can tell <br>I can tell, yeah I can tell <br>You been scarred too deep, I can tell <br>I can tell, yeah I can tell <br><br>all your love for nothing <br>Ride or die, and ride a wire for nothing <br>All year gone and on your own for stunting <br>Say you ain't been worried, bitch you fronting <br>I ain't worried 'bout you bitch, ayy <br>I ain't worried 'bout you bitch, oh <br>I ain't worried 'bout you bitch, ayy <br>I ain't worried 'bout you bitch, no <br><br>I don't get it <br>Said I'm right at home when I'm in it <br>It's been a minute <br>Said she home alone and gon' get it <br>Man I'm all alone on these missions <br>But you don't understand <br>Tryna get to these bands and I'm nothing like your mans <br>Baby girl there's a difference <br>I could probably change your whole life in one minute <br>If it feel right come hop in my Benz <br>Tell me if you love me, I don't do pretend friends <br>I did it before, I won't do it again <br>Tell me that she hate me, yeah yeah, I'm off a xan <br>Tell me that she want to try one, go Peter Pan <br>I'ma hop right out the car, all of the water, I think I need land, ooh <br>Fucked a lil thot, I'm star, I'm fuckin' a star, just send the ho plans <br>Know that you wanna go far, baby girl grab my hand <br>Told you from the start you can't ride without no bands <br>Listen me, you cannot bring no green racks or no xans <br>Christmas tree, light him up then wrap him in saran <br>Baby be with me, we can go feature these foreign lands <br>Believe in me <br>You always leaving me <br>Rolled up, Maserati doors up <br>Wrist froze up, all y'all bitches chose up <br><br>You been scarred too deep, I can tell <br>I can tell, yeah I can tell <br>You been scarred too deep, I can tell <br>I can tell, yeah I can tell <br>You been scarred too deep, I can tell <br>I can tell, yeah I can tell <br>You been scarred too deep, I can tell <br>I can tell, yeah I can tell <br><br>Baby what's the hold up <br>Baby what's the hold up <br>Baby what's the hold up <br>I tried to hold it down <br>I tried to hold it down yeah <br>Baby what's the hold up <br>Baby what's the hold up <br>I tried to hold it down <br>I tried to hold it down <br>Baby what's the hold up <br>I tried to hold it down]]></content><category term="Trippie Redd" label="Trippie Redd"/><category term="Deeply Scared (Feat. unotheactivist)" label="Deeply Scared (Feat. unotheactivist)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Romeo__Juliet/</id><title>Trippie Redd - Romeo &amp; Juliet - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:39:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:39:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Romeo__Juliet/" title="Trippie Redd - Romeo &amp; Juliet - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love Scars, skurt <br>You, you <br>A Love Letter To You <br><br>Baby, yo' love is my medicine <br>Baby yo' love is my medicine, when I'm up, bring me down <br>Yo' love is my medicine, lil' baby <br>Huh Yo' love is my medicine, when I'm up, bring me down <br>Ohhhhhhhh <br>Yoooooo loooovveeee, baby yoooooooo loooooovvvveee <br><br>Hey, yo' love, is so amazing <br>It's all i want, got a nigga faded <br>Shawty on fire, yeah she really blazin' <br>Flames Armageddon, yelling Jesus save me <br>I'ma take his soul, if she try to play me <br>'Cause that's all mine, that's my lil' baby <br>I'm in all white, like the fucking navy <br>Throwin' up the Roc', like a nigga Jay Z <br>Awwww, don't play me, nooooooo <br>Uh, no, don't play me, nooooo <br>Ay, no , don't play me, noooo <br>Yeah, don't play me, noooooooo <br>'Cause <br><br>Yo' love is my medicine <br>Ayy, yo' love is my medicine, when I'm up, bring me down <br>Yo' love is my medicine, lil' baby <br>Huh Yo' love is my medicine, when I'm up, bring me down <br>Baby your love is my medicine <br>Baby your love is my medicine, when I'm up, bring me down <br>Your love is my medicine lil baby <br>Your love is my medicine, when i'm up, bring me down <br>Ooooooh <br>Yoooooo loooovveeee, baby yoooooooo loooooovve <br><br>Your love is my medicine <br>Baby, your love is my medicine, when i'm up <br>Bring me down <br>Your love is my medicine, baby <br>Your love is my medicine, when im up, bring me down <br>Oooohhh <br>Your love <br>Baby your love]]></content><category term="Trippie Redd" label="Trippie Redd"/><category term="Romeo &amp; Juliet" label="Romeo &amp; Juliet"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Love_Scars_Pt_2___Rack_City_Feat_ANTIPoP__Chris_King/</id><title>Trippie Redd - Love Scars Pt. 2 / Rack City (Feat. ANTIPoP &amp; Chris King) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:39:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:39:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Love_Scars_Pt_2___Rack_City_Feat_ANTIPoP__Chris_King/" title="Trippie Redd - Love Scars Pt. 2 / Rack City (Feat. ANTIPoP &amp; Chris King) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ooh, aye <br>14, 14, 14, babe yeah <br><br>In rack city counting up a four <br>I was trapping, getting it by my 'lone <br>Rocket got them pints for the low <br>Chris got the rocket, he gon' blow <br>Murder what she wrote <br>We came through and took her soul <br>She want that dick then she get boned <br>Rack city blowing dope, bitch <br>She off the molly and the coke, bitch <br>You wan' touch then you get poked, bitch <br>Run my hood like the pope pope, bitch <br><br>They thought I was dead but I'm still alive <br>I just needed time to relax bitch <br>I just needed time, now I'm back bitch <br>The money coming faster than an evidence <br>Please play this at my funeral <br>If I die tomorrow tell my mama that I'm sorry for the life I chose <br>But this the life I chose <br><br>Mama I'm sorry <br>This is the life for me <br>Nobody loves me but me <br>Nobody loves me but me <br>I fucked my girl last week <br>Told her get on her knees <br>Then she sucked on my D <br>Then that bitch hit the streets, she ain't fuckin' with me <br><br>No more, no more, no more, no more <br>No more, no more, no more, no more <br><br>I see more tombstones than the undertaker <br>And if we fuck now we can't cuddle later <br>The chopper make roaches scatter, fuck a huddle breaker <br>This MAC, I aim it at your face, I cannot make up <br>Brrat, I got the pounds and that ain't from Jamaica <br>Smoke, this thing I'm shooting fuck up god's creation <br>Ah, you the best, who am I replacing <br>Woah, oh that's a vest well it's your mind I'm aimed at <br>Scars of love from warfare with automatics <br>Bullets burn like lava, chopper spitting volcanic <br>Codeine and percocets, spend a kidney and a liver <br>Stupid bitch fuck me over, I get it, I still miss her woah <br><br>In rack city counting up a four <br>I was trapping, getting it by my 'lone]]></content><category term="Trippie Redd" label="Trippie Redd"/><category term="Love Scars Pt. 2 / Rack City (Feat. ANTIPoP &amp; Chris King)" label="Love Scars Pt. 2 / Rack City (Feat. ANTIPoP &amp; Chris King)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Love_Scars/</id><title>Trippie Redd - Love Scars - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:39:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:39:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trippie_Redd/Love_Scars/" title="Trippie Redd - Love Scars - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Aye <br>Lil 14, yeah <br><br>You used to say you in love <br>I used to say that shit back <br>taking that shit from the heart <br>now look where the fuck where we at <br>Girl you got me, just going out bad <br>Love scars, you got me real sad <br>Lookin like you had a past <br>I just thought this shit was the last, oh <br><br>Shawty <br>I just want your love for a minute <br>I be captain baby <br>you can be lieutenant <br>swear I lose my mind everytime that I'm in it <br>you won't get a dime, naw naw neva <br><br>Spend it, spend it <br>I been here for a minute, minute <br>aye <br>playin games with me shawty <br>this is not no scrimmage, scrimmage <br>Swear that I did it, did it <br>I do it, I does it, I does it <br>Shoutout my buddy, my wodie <br>lil nigga, and shout out my bousins, woah <br>I swear I'm bloodied up b's <br>never throwing up, c's <br>these niggas is disgusting <br>something like a disease <br>your bitch pussy nasty as fuck <br>she got a lil bit of yeast <br>gettin all the money, count it up <br>count up all my green, woah <br>Girl you got me going out, bad <br>girl you got me real sad <br>devil in me make me mad <br><br>You used to say you in love, yeah <br>shawty you so fucked up <br>You used to say you in love <br>you got me so fucked up <br>shawty I dont need you anyway <br>I just sit back in my balenciaga's <br>I'm just sippin that lemonade <br>mixin it with hennessy <br>dominating any enemy]]></content><category term="Trippie Redd" label="Trippie Redd"/><category term="Love Scars" label="Love Scars"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silvia_Perez_Cruz/Corrandes_D´Exili/</id><title>Silvia Perez Cruz - Corrandes D´Exili - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:39:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:39:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silvia_Perez_Cruz/Corrandes_D%C2%B4Exili/" title="Silvia Perez Cruz - Corrandes D´Exili - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Una nit de lluna plena <br>tramuntarem la carena <br>lentament, sense dir res <br>Si la lluna feia el ple <br>tambe el feu la nostra pena <br><br>L'estimada m'acompanya <br>de pell bruna i aire greu <br>com una marededeu <br>que han trobat a la muntanya <br><br>Perque ens perdoni la guerra <br>que l'ensagna, que l'esguerra <br>abans de passar la ratlla <br>m'ajec i beso la terra <br>i l'acarono amb l'espatlla <br><br>A Catalunya deixi <br>el dia de ma partida <br>mitja vida com dormida <br>l'altra meitat vingue amb mi <br>per no deixar me sens vida <br><br>Avui en terres de Franca <br>i dema mes lluny potser <br>no em morire d'enyoranca <br>ans d'enyoranca viure <br><br>En ma terra del Valles <br>tres turons fan una serra <br>quatre pins un bosc espes <br>cinc quarteres massa terra <br>com el Valles no hi ha res <br><br>Que els pins cenyessin la cala <br>l' ermita dalt d' un pujol <br>i a la plana un tenderol <br>que batega com onades <br><br>I una recanca infinita <br>i una esperanca desfeta <br>I una patria tan petita <br>Que l' ensomio completa]]></content><category term="Silvia Perez Cruz" label="Silvia Perez Cruz"/><category term="Corrandes D´Exili" label="Corrandes D´Exili"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silvia_Perez_Cruz/Nao_Sei/</id><title>Silvia Perez Cruz - Nao Sei - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:39:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:39:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silvia_Perez_Cruz/Nao_Sei/" title="Silvia Perez Cruz - Nao Sei - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fecho os olhos pra lembrar me de voce <br>com as maos agarro o violao <br>tenho medo de esquecer de voce <br>meu pai <br><br>voaria pra chegar ate o ceu <br>passear contigo e conversar <br>abracada eternamente <br>abracados <br><br>nao sei, nao sei, nao sei <br>eu juro que nao sei <br>quero aprender <br>o que eu tenho que fazer <br>pra conseguir te de nascer <br><br>eu sei, eu sei, ja sei <br>a saudade o que e <br>um coracao todo feito de papel <br><br>voce esta perto <br>voce esta longe <br><br>passa o dia, passa a noite <br>passa o trem <br>uma primavera, uma vida inteira passa <br>tanto tempo pra chorar por voce <br>demais <br><br>obrigada, as viagens sonhadas <br>de cantar contigo e perceber <br>o que e que passa, mais ou menos <br>na tua cabeca <br><br>nao sei, nao sei, nao sei <br>eu juro que nao sei <br>quero aprender <br>o que eu tenho que fazer <br>pra conseguir te de nascer <br><br>eu sei, eu sei, ja sei <br>a saudade o que e <br>um coracao todo feito de papel <br><br>voce esta perto <br>voce esta longe]]></content><category term="Silvia Perez Cruz" label="Silvia Perez Cruz"/><category term="Nao Sei" label="Nao Sei"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silvia_Perez_Cruz/Gallo_Rojo_Gallo_Negro/</id><title>Silvia Perez Cruz - Gallo Rojo, Gallo Negro - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:39:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:39:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silvia_Perez_Cruz/Gallo_Rojo_Gallo_Negro/" title="Silvia Perez Cruz - Gallo Rojo, Gallo Negro - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cuando canta el gallo negro <br>Es que ya se acaba el dia <br>Si cantara el gallo rojo <br><br>Otro gallo cantaria <br><br>Ay si es que yo miento <br>Qu'el cantar que yo canto <br>Lo borre el viento <br>Ay que desencanto <br>Si me borrara el viento <br>Lo que yo canto <br><br>Se encontraron en la arena <br>Los dos gallos frente a frente <br>El gallo negro era grande <br>Pero el rojo era valiente <br><br>Se miraron cara a cara <br>Y ataco el negro primero <br>El gallo rojo es valiente <br>Pero el negro es traicionero <br><br>Gallo negro, gallo negro <br>Gallo negro, te lo advierto <br>No se rinde un gallo rojo <br>Mas que cuando esta ya muerto]]></content><category term="Silvia Perez Cruz" label="Silvia Perez Cruz"/><category term="Gallo Rojo, Gallo Negro" label="Gallo Rojo, Gallo Negro"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silvia_Perez_Cruz/Ai_Ai_Ai/</id><title>Silvia Perez Cruz - Ai, Ai, Ai - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:39:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:39:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silvia_Perez_Cruz/Ai_Ai_Ai/" title="Silvia Perez Cruz - Ai, Ai, Ai - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Happy, happy <br>ai, ai, ai <br>And make me happy <br>nice, cute and funny <br>Ai, ai, ai <br><br>And let me fly <br>it's not time to cry <br>Ai, ai, ai <br><br>And leave my room <br>my shirts, my spoon <br>my door, my walls <br>my mom, my dolls <br>and leave my bed <br>my bear, my bread <br>I'll jump to the sun <br>and you will not catch me <br><br>I'll wear a cape <br>ride a horse to escape <br>Ai, ai, ai <br>With a secret map <br>for mom and dad]]></content><category term="Silvia Perez Cruz" label="Silvia Perez Cruz"/><category term="Ai, Ai, Ai" label="Ai, Ai, Ai"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silvia_Perez_Cruz/Tonada_De_Luna_Llena/</id><title>Silvia Perez Cruz - Tonada De Luna Llena - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:40:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:40:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Silvia_Perez_Cruz/Tonada_De_Luna_Llena/" title="Silvia Perez Cruz - Tonada De Luna Llena - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yo vide una garza mora <br>Dandole combate a un rio <br>Asi es como se enamora <br><br>Tu corazon con el mio <br>Yo vide una garza mora <br>Dandole combate a un rio <br>Asi es como se enamora <br>Asi es como se enamora <br>Tu corazon con el mio <br>Tu corazon con el mio <br>Luna luna luna llena <br>Menguante <br>Luna luna luna llena <br>Menguante <br><br>Anda muchacho a la casa <br>Y me traes la carabina jiooo <br>Pa mata este gavilan <br>Que no me deja gallina <br><br>La luna me esta mirando <br>Yo no se lo que me ve <br>Yo tengo la ropa limpia <br>Ayer tarde la lave <br><br>Luna luna luna llena <br>Menguante]]></content><category term="Silvia Perez Cruz" label="Silvia Perez Cruz"/><category term="Tonada De Luna Llena" label="Tonada De Luna Llena"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Negrita/Lasciami_Dormire_Remastered_2017/</id><title>Negrita - Lasciami Dormire (Remastered 2017) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:40:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:40:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Negrita/Lasciami_Dormire_Remastered_2017/" title="Negrita - Lasciami Dormire (Remastered 2017) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[C'e una ragazza che gioca col mio baricentro <br>lei mi accompagna nei posti che non vedrei mai <br>se lei non c'e la tristezza mi avvolge di un velo <br>e se non c'e io capisco dipendo da lei <br>Lasciami dormire ancora <br>lasciami sognare ancora <br><br>C'e una sostanza che offende la voglia di vita <br>e lascio che lei mi prenda, mi porti con se <br>che senza ali ne gambe, io poi mi stanco <br>e visto dal pavimento il mondo non e piu lui <br><br>Lasciami dormire ancora <br>lasciami sognare ancora <br>lasciami soffrire ancora <br>che non so dire se sto male <br><br>C'e una voce che affonda fra i miei pensieri <br>ed e qua dentro che danza e non smette mai <br>e adesso ho un'ala spezzata, scivolo giu <br>il mio telefono e sveglio ma non suona piu <br><br>Lasciami dormire ancora <br>lasciami sognare ancora <br>lasciami soffrire ancora <br>che non so dire se sto male <br>lasciami sognare ancora <br>Lasciami dormire ancora <br>Lasciami dormire ancora <br>Lasciami dormire ancora]]></content><category term="Negrita" label="Negrita"/><category term="Lasciami Dormire (Remastered 2017)" label="Lasciami Dormire (Remastered 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Negrita/A_Modo_Mio_Remastered_2017/</id><title>Negrita - A Modo Mio (Remastered 2017) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:40:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:40:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Negrita/A_Modo_Mio_Remastered_2017/" title="Negrita - A Modo Mio (Remastered 2017) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Prende bene stare fuori oggi che e primavera <br>Prende bene andare in giro con il sole che saluta la sera <br>Oggi che e primavera <br>E ho buttato via i pensieri via la noia e il magone <br>Li ho buttati tutti quanti stamani tutti dentro a un bidone <br>E fuoco col kerosene <br>E a modo mio, a modo mio sono <br>Contento un poco anch'io <br>E a modo mio, a modo mio sono <br>Contento un giorno anch'io <br>E a modo mio, ringrazio Dio oggi <br>La storia la faccio io, a modo mio <br><br>E' che oggi sono in forma oggi e un giorno speciale <br>Di quei giorni che non vengono spesso come le eclissi di sole <br>Che le puoi quasi contare <br>E le bambine, le bambine oggi sono gentili <br>Le bambine oggi fanno un sorriso ai fischi dei militari <br>Oggi e un giorno alla pari <br><br>E a modo mio, a modo mio sono <br>Contento un poco anch'io <br>E a modo mio, a modo mio sono <br>Contento un giorno anch'io <br>E a modo mio, ringrazio Dio oggi <br>La storia la faccio io, a modo mio]]></content><category term="Negrita" label="Negrita"/><category term="A Modo Mio (Remastered 2017)" label="A Modo Mio (Remastered 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Negrita/Era_Magico_Remastered_2017/</id><title>Negrita - Era Magico (Remastered 2017) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T17:40:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T17:40:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Negrita/Era_Magico_Remastered_2017/" title="Negrita - Era Magico (Remastered 2017) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Io non ricordo piu cosa mi feri qualche tempo fa <br>Io ero Robin Hood piccolo cosi e non piangevo mai <br>Ed era magico magico magico <br>Era magico magico magico <br><br>Io non ricordo piu cosa mi feri qualche tempo fa <br>Volts, schegge d'energia da una radio che somigliava a noi <br><br>Ed era magico magico magico <br>Era magico magico magico <br><br>Ed era magico magico magico <br>Ma ora vomito vomito vomito <br><br>Io non ricordo piu cosa mi feri qualche tempo fa <br>Io non odiavo io m'innamoravo io e non tradivo mai <br><br>Ed era magico magico magico <br>Ma ora vomito vomito vomito]]></content><category term="Negrita" label="Negrita"/><category term="Era Magico (Remastered 2017)" label="Era Magico (Remastered 2017)"/></entry></feed>