<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:51:21+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤오/서점/</id><title>윤오 - 서점 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:03:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:03:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%98%A4/%EC%84%9C%EC%A0%90/" title="윤오 - 서점 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[화려한 글자들 사이로 <br>반짝이던 너의 눈빛 <br>그곳에서 너는 <br>아름다운 책이였네 <br>꺼내 보려 했지만 <br>너무 높은 곳에 있어 <br>꺼내 볼 수 없었던 나의 <br>아름다운 작은 책 <br>몇년이 지나 <br>다시 그곳을 찾아갔지 <br>날 둘러 싼 공기는 <br>그대로 였지만 <br>바라볼 곳이 없어 <br>그대로 나와 버렸네 <br>내가 찾던 책이 없어져서 <br>지금도 나는 <br>다시 이곳을 찾아와 <br>아름다운 책을 찾네 <br>잃어버린 너를 꿈꾸네 <br>아름다운 나의 작은 책 <br>지금도 나는 <br>다시 이곳을 찾아와 <br>아름다운 책을 찾네 <br>잃어버린 너를 꿈꾸네 <br>아름다운 나의 작은 책 <br>찾고싶은 나의 책 <br>]]></content><category term="윤오" label="윤오"/><category term="서점" label="서점"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤오/안경이_부서지던_날/</id><title>윤오 - 안경이 부서지던 날 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:03:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:03:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%98%A4/%EC%95%88%EA%B2%BD%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B6%80%EC%84%9C%EC%A7%80%EB%8D%98_%EB%82%A0/" title="윤오 - 안경이 부서지던 날 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 안경이 부서지고 나서야 <br>나는 당신을 제대로 볼 수 있었어요 <br>당신의 처음과 나의 끝이 <br>이렇게 만났다 해도 <br>오해하지 말아줘요 <br>내가 그댈 쉽게 보지 않았음을 <br>이제 그댈 어떻게 봐야 할지 <br>많은 걱정이 앞선다는 걸 <br>안경 속의 나의 착각이 <br>남김없이 모두 다 부서졌죠 <br>그날밤 내가 보았던 것이 <br>그대가 숨겨놓은 눈동자였길 <br>내 안경이 부서지고 나서야 <br>나는 당신을 제대로 볼 수 있었어요 <br>이제 그댈 어떻게 봐야 할지 <br>많은 걱정이 앞선다는 걸 <br>많은 걱정이 앞선다는 걸 <br>]]></content><category term="윤오" label="윤오"/><category term="안경이 부서지던 날" label="안경이 부서지던 날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤오/여름_감기/</id><title>윤오 - 여름, 감기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:03:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:03:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%98%A4/%EC%97%AC%EB%A6%84_%EA%B0%90%EA%B8%B0/" title="윤오 - 여름, 감기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[해마다 여름에 <br>찾아오는 감기는 <br>뜬금없이 나에게 나타나 <br>날 괴롭히네 <br>이 더운 날에 <br>콜록이던 내 모습이 <br>한없이 초라해지네 <br>지금 이대로 <br>이 무더운 여름이 가면 <br>그때는 잊을 수 있을까 <br>이 상태로 원래 네가 있던 <br>겨울이 오면 <br>그땐 편안해 질까 <br>날씨는 더워도 <br>내 마음의 날씨는 <br>꽃샘추위 같은 <br>바람만이 불고 있네 <br>심한 일교차에 <br>아파오는 내 마음이 <br>너무나 혼란스럽네 <br>지금 이대로 <br>이 무더운 여름이 가면 <br>그때는 잊을 수 있을까 <br>이 상태로 원래 네가 있던 <br>겨울이 오면 <br>그땐 편안해 질까 <br>너를 언젠간 알고 나서 부턴 <br>작은 바람에도 난 흔들리네 <br>지금 이대로 <br>이 무더운 여름이 가면 <br>그때는 잊을 수 있을까 <br>이 상태로 원래 네가 있던 <br>겨울이 오면 <br>그땐 편안해질까 <br>지금 이대로 <br>이 무더운 여름이 가면 <br>그때는 잊을 수 있을까 <br>이 상태로 원래 네가 있던 <br>겨울이 오면 <br>그땐 편안해질까 <br>]]></content><category term="윤오" label="윤오"/><category term="여름, 감기" label="여름, 감기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤오/우주여행/</id><title>윤오 - 우주여행 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:04:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:04:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%98%A4/%EC%9A%B0%EC%A3%BC%EC%97%AC%ED%96%89/" title="윤오 - 우주여행 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리는 우주 안에 있죠 <br>붉은색 조명 하나만이 <br>우리 둘을 비추고 있어요 <br>하지만 보이지가 않죠 <br>우린 점점 취해가요 <br>정해둔 목적지도 없이 <br>그러다 빛을 보았어요 <br>날 어쩔 수 없게 만들었죠 <br>많은 별들을 지나서 <br>결국 여기까지 오게 됐어요 <br>영원하기를 바래요 <br>이곳에서 당신과 함께라면 <br>우리는 시간 밖에 있죠 <br>세상은 모두 정지한 채 <br>우리 둘만 움직이고 있어요 <br>아무도 이 사실은 몰라요 <br>많은 별들을 지나서 <br>결국 여기까지 오게 됐어요 <br>영원하기를 바래요 <br>이곳에서 당신과 함께라면 <br>캄캄한 밤하늘에 <br>길을 잃고 힘들게 헤맬 때도 <br>서로의 눈빛이 <br>별빛이 돼 주길 바래요 <br>어떤 어둠이 밀려와도 <br>처음 만났던 곳에 서 있을게요 <br>영원하기를 바래요 <br>우리만의 아름다운 모습들로 <br>우리만의 아름다운 모습들로 <br>]]></content><category term="윤오" label="윤오"/><category term="우주여행" label="우주여행"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤오/봄/</id><title>윤오 - 봄 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:04:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:04:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%98%A4/%EB%B4%84/" title="윤오 - 봄 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꽃은 피기만 하는 건 아닐 텐데 <br>지는 꽃들도 무수히 많을 테지만 <br>사람들은 왜 봄의 그런 꽃은 <br>하나도 기억하려고 하지 않을까 <br>피었다 바로 지는 꽃도 있고 <br>만개하여 지는 꽃도 있어 <br>남의 손에 지는 꽃도 있고 <br>피지도 못한 채 지는 꽃도 있어 <br>가슴 아파하지마 <br>봄이라고 모두 다 <br>시작만을 알리는 건 아니니까 <br>가슴 아파하지마 <br>이건 네 잘못이 아니잖아 <br>왜 네가 사과를 해야 하는 거니 <br>날씨는 점점 따뜻해져만 가고 <br>우리의 마음은 <br>점점 추워지기만 해 <br>사람들은 화사한 벚꽃만 <br>보고 싶어했지 <br>지는 벚꽃을 <br>위로해주는 이 없었네 <br>피었다 바로 지는 꽃도 있고 <br>만개하여 지는 꽃도 있어 <br>남의 손에 지는 꽃도 있고 <br>피지도 못한 채 지는 꽃도 있어 <br>가슴 아파하지마 <br>봄이라고 모두 다 <br>시작만을 알리는 건 아니니까 <br>가슴 아파하지마 <br>이건 네 잘못이 아니잖아 <br>왜 네가 사과를 해야 하는 거니 <br>넌 잘못한 게 하나도 없어 <br>가슴 아파하지마 <br>봄이라고 모두 다 <br>시작만을 알리는 건 아니니까 <br>사는 건 원래 그런 거니까 <br>가슴 아파하지마 <br>이건 네 잘못이 아니잖아 <br>왜 네가 사과를 해야 하는 거니 <br>넌 잘못한 게 하나도 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="윤오" label="윤오"/><category term="봄" label="봄"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시아/Bye_Bye/</id><title>시아 - Bye Bye - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:04:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:04:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EC%95%84/Bye_Bye/" title="시아 - Bye Bye - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이젠 안녕해야 돼 <br>너의 사랑 지쳤어 <br>나를 구속하려는 너 <br>나는 이제는 못 참아 <br>사랑이란건 다른거야 <br>집착하는게 아닌거야 <br>서로 아끼며 배려하는 <br>그런게 사랑이야 <br>이젠 안녕 안녕 잘가요 <br>우리 사랑은 여기까지 <br>그동안 즐거웠어 <br>힘들기만 하진 않았어 <br>안녕 안녕 잘가요 <br>너의 행복을 빌어줄게 <br>너도 나를 놓아줘 <br>나를 웃으면서 보내줘 <br>이젠 안녕해야 돼 <br>우리 사랑 끝이야 <br>남은 미련 절대 없어 <br>내 마음은 널 떠났어 <br>울며 잡아도 소용없어 <br>찌질한 모습 보이지마 <br>쿨하게 이별하는거야 <br>마음을 비우면 돼 <br>이젠 안녕 안녕 잘가요 <br>우리 사랑은 여기까지 <br>그동안 즐거웠어 <br>힘들기만 하진 않았어 <br>안녕 안녕 잘가요 <br>너의 행복을 빌어줄게 <br>너도 나를 놓아줘 <br>나를 웃으면서 보내줘 <br>이젠 안녕 안녕 잘가요 <br>우리 사랑은 여기까지 <br>그동안 즐거웠어 <br>힘들기만 하진 않았어 <br>안녕 안녕 잘가요 <br>너의 행복을 빌어줄게 <br>너도 나를 놓아줘 <br>나를 웃으면서 보내줘 <br>]]></content><category term="시아" label="시아"/><category term="Bye Bye" label="Bye Bye"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Monsters_Dive/Shade_Feat_appear/</id><title>Monsters_Dive - Shade (Feat. appear) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:04:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:04:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Monsters_Dive/Shade_Feat_appear/" title="Monsters_Dive - Shade (Feat. appear) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What can I do? What should I do? <br>I can’t see anything <br>Something pulls me under <br>Falling into the darkest depth! <br>Please save me, Please help me! <br>Please! Please! Please runaway from here! <br><br>Don’t stop! I’ll never escape! I can’t breathe anymore! <br>What can I do? What should I do? <br>I can’t see anything <br><br>*Take my hand, Take my hand Bring me into the light! <br>(Spread the wings for freedom! Fly to the last escape!) <br>Take my hand, Take my hand Take me into the tunnel! <br>(Runaway From here!) <br><br>How long has time passed by? How many days have past me? <br>Purple rain is falling down from the window outside <br>I hear you singing the hymns. Arrogant angel’s broken wings <br>Black feather is floating, dancing on the floor with me! <br><br>Ashes to ashes, Dust to dust <br><br>Don’t stop! I’ll never escape! I can’t breathe anymore! <br>What can I do? What should I do? <br>I can’t see anything <br><br>*Take my hand, Take my hand Bring me into the light! <br>(Spread the wings for freedom! Fly to the last escape!) <br>Take my hand, Take my hand Take me into the tunnel! <br>(Runaway From here!)]]></content><category term="Monsters Dive" label="Monsters Dive"/><category term="Shade (Feat. appear)" label="Shade (Feat. appear)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이태강/별_하나에/</id><title>이태강 - 별 하나에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:05:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:05:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%83%9C%EA%B0%95/%EB%B3%84_%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EC%97%90/" title="이태강 - 별 하나에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[별 하나에 추억과 <br>별 하나에 사랑과 <br>별 하나에 쓸쓸함과 <br>별 하나에 동경과 <br>별 하나에 시와 <br>별 하나에 어머니 어머니 <br>]]></content><category term="이태강" label="이태강"/><category term="별 하나에" label="별 하나에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lanesoul/어디에_있니_Feat_SoulT/</id><title>Lanesoul - 어디에 있니 (Feat. Soul.T) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:05:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:05:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lanesoul/%EC%96%B4%EB%94%94%EC%97%90_%EC%9E%88%EB%8B%88_Feat_SoulT/" title="Lanesoul - 어디에 있니 (Feat. Soul.T) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아침에 눈을 뜨니 <br>밤새 공부하고 <br>쌓인 피로감이 <br>또 다시 나를 반기지 <br>내 오른손에 <br>살며시 쥐어진 휴대폰 <br>의 시계엔 지금이 일곱 시 반이지 <br>졸린 눈을 한 채로 <br>수업을 들으러 가는 <br>내 모습엔 20대의 현실이 <br>투영 돼있어 <br>새내기 때 막연히 <br>좋아 보였는데 <br>이제 보니 한숨 쉬던 <br>형들의 입장을 알겠어 <br>그들과 딱히 다른 모습으로 <br>살고 싶었던 건 <br>아니지만 날 이끌던 <br>열정을 쫓아 <br>하고 싶은 것만 하며 살았어 <br>남들은 취업 준비할 때 <br>나만 혼자 삐딱선 <br>부모님은 이런 나를 <br>걱정해 현재의 <br>만족만을 위해 살기엔 <br>남은 시간이 없대 <br>나도 잘 알지 못하는 <br>내 미래에 대한 관심 <br>그런 것 다 접고 <br>음악을 하는 게 마냥 좋았지 <br>철없는 내 모습조차 품어준 한동 <br>어릴 때 꿈을 지켜준 추억의 장소 <br>그래 이곳은 하나도 변한 게 없어 <br>변했다면 또 조급해진 <br>내 모습이겠지 뭐 <br>어디에 있니 넌 어디에 있니 <br>꿈이 많던 그 시절의 <br>내 모습은 대체 어딨지 <br>현실에 부딪치며 나는 조금씩 <br>어둠에 잠식되어 <br>점차 빛을 거두지 <br>어디에 있니 넌 어디에 있니 <br>꿈이 많던 그 시절의 <br>내 모습은 대체 어딨지 <br>나를 괴롭힌 현실에 작아진 <br>내게 저 달빛은 <br>이제 너무나도 차갑지 <br>많은 걸 바란 것은 아니지 난 <br>이 길에 발을 디딘 것으로 <br>감사하기만 <br>할 뿐야 그분이 예비하신 땅 <br>가나안의 주의 자손처럼 <br>겸손하게 길을 걷는다 <br>세상의 모든 게 <br>내가 바래왔던 대로 <br>전부 이뤄졌음 해서 <br>잠들기 전에 두 손 모아 <br>기도를 올리지 매번 <br>밤하늘의 달을 보며 <br>홀로 주문을 외곤 했어 <br>내가 행복하기 위해 <br>이기적일 수 밖에 <br>없는 게 삶이기에 <br>난 가면을 쓴 채로 살아야만 해 <br>내 감정을 숨기는 게 당연하대 <br>이상과 현실의 괴리는 나에겐 <br>밤새 날 잠 못 들게 하는 nightmare <br>정말 난 좋은 것만 보고 싶었네 <br>내 사람한테 상처주기 싫었네 <br>이 길에 깊숙이 패인 <br>자유에 대한 대가로 <br>내가 떠맡은 책임 <br>그 무게를 견디는 것이 <br>내가 할 일 <br>난 안될 거란 무력감이 <br>날 외롭게 하지 <br>저 밤하늘이 내게 너무 차가워도 <br>너마저 내 곁을 떠나진 말아줘 <br>저 밤하늘이 내게 너무 차가워도 <br>절대 포기하지 말아줘 <br>어디에 있니 넌 어디에 있니 <br>꿈이 많던 그 시절의 <br>내 모습은 대체 어딨지 <br>현실에 부딪치며 나는 조금씩 <br>어둠에 잠식되어 <br>점차 빛을 거두지 <br>어디에 있니 넌 어디에 있니 <br>꿈이 많던 그 시절의 <br>내 모습은 대체 어딨지 <br>나를 괴롭힌 현실에 작아진 <br>내게 저 달빛은 <br>이제 너무나도 차갑지 <br>넌 어디에 있니 <br>지금 보이지 않아도 <br>It’s alright you'll be alright <br>I know it's time to shine <br>어디에 있니 넌 어디에 있니 <br>꿈이 많던 그 시절의 <br>내 모습은 대체 어딨지 <br>현실에 부딪치며 나는 조금씩 <br>어둠에 잠식되어 <br>점차 빛을 거두지 <br>어디에 있니 넌 어디에 있니 <br>꿈이 많던 그 시절의 <br>내 모습은 대체 어딨지 <br>나를 괴롭힌 현실에 작아진 <br>내게 저 달빛은 <br>이제 너무나도 차갑지 <br>넌 어디에 있니 <br>지금 보이지 않아도 <br>It’s alright you'll be alright <br>I know it's time to shine <br>]]></content><category term="Lanesoul" label="Lanesoul"/><category term="어디에 있니 (Feat. Soul.T)" label="어디에 있니 (Feat. Soul.T)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아린_A_LIN/After_TIME/</id><title>아린_A_LIN - After TIME - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:05:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:05:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EB%A6%B0_A_LIN/After_TIME/" title="아린_A_LIN - After TIME - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[20 내 나름 힘든 시간이 지나고 <br>17 또 다시 1 처음부터라도 <br>before time is 21 <br>잡혀있지 않다면 <br>after time 꼭 나의 시간 eh <br>to anyone 2 1 <br>기횐 올 거니까 <br>seveenteen 1 2 <br>기횔 잡으니깐 <br>지금부턴 내 그림을 그려 <br>drawing paper <br>내 그림을 보여줘 <br>play the audio listen <br>항상 숨기만 했던 <br>질것만 같다던 주변인's <br>내가 등을 져 <br>난 after time 만을 기다려 <br>난 더 큰 그림을 그려 <br>all focuses on me <br>after time <br>time and now <br>after time <br>time and now <br>언제나 난 그 시간 후에 <br>그 시간 후엔 누구보다 앞에 <br>after time <br>time and now <br>after time <br>time and now <br>언제나 난 그 시간 후에 <br>그 시간 후엔 누구보다 앞에 <br>시간은 계속 흘러 <br>뒤는 보지 않고 <br>조여와 나사 <br>내 머릿속 안까지 <br>no woo woo wah <br>조인 마음 그보다 크게 <br>난 꿈을 잡아 <br>after time time and now <br>to anyone 2 1 <br>아무도 없으니까 <br>seventeen 1 2 <br>아무도 못 따라와 <br>지금부터 내 그림을 그려 <br>drawing paper <br>내 그림을 보여줘 <br>play the audio only <br>항상 숨기만 했던 <br>질것만 같다던 주변인's <br>내가 등을 져 <br>난 기다리지 않고 <br>난 바빠서 <br>난 더 큰 그림을 그려 <br>all foucses on me <br>after time <br>time and now <br>after time <br>time and now <br>언제나 난 그 시간 후에 <br>그 시간 후엔 누구보다 앞에 <br>after time <br>time and now <br>after time <br>time and now <br>언제나 난 그 시간 후에 <br>그 시간 후엔 누구보다 앞에 <br>]]></content><category term="아린 (A:LIN)" label="아린 (A:LIN)"/><category term="After TIME" label="After TIME"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kana_Bathe_카나베잇/RideAway/</id><title>Kana_Bathe_카나베잇 - RideAway - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:06:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:06:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kana_Bathe_%EC%B9%B4%EB%82%98%EB%B2%A0%EC%9E%87/RideAway/" title="Kana_Bathe_카나베잇 - RideAway - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Can you take me a ride <br>이 자리를 벗어나서 <br>아까부터 느껴졌어 <br>Sip it slow down <br>How about behave a wild <br>Yea 저 멀리 <br>짧게 지나치는 이 거리의 빛은 <br>These make me numb numb numb <br>Cuz I left here none none none <br>You know the party's done done <br>It's over 거의 잠들어있는 날 깨워줘 <br>막혀있지 지금 시간의 traffic <br>돌아서 가 저 코너 <br>잘 짜여진 샛길 <br>도피해 옆 좌석에서 <br>네 집으로 간 다음 <br>달릴 거야 like these wheels <br>벗어나서 out of streets <br>넌 내게 여러가지의 얼굴을 <br>가지고 있다고 했어 <br>알아챘지 <br>how dare you tag my color <br>내 표정이 바뀔 때마다 <br>원래 꾸며진 게 <br>보기 좋으니까 모든 건 <br>어쩌면 우리 모두 <br>바라고 있는 건지도 몰라 <br>Further away from the real <br>Take me away away <br>노란 줄을 타고 <br>Where Tarxan's live <br>yea I'm the Jane <br>안전한 곳으로 고속으로 <br>We 'bout to ride <br>We 'bout to ride to your bed <br>These make me numb numb numb <br>Cuz I left here none none none <br>You know the party's done done <br>It's over 거의 잠들어있는 날 깨워줘 <br>Take me to your bed <br>Take me to your bed <br>Take me to your bed <br>Take me to your bed <br>난 불투명해 <br>붉은 조명 널 흐려지게 해 <br>Should've get your mind <br>넌 불분명해 <br>굳이 검열할 필요 없지 난 <br>Need no identifying <br>You got the money <br>꺼내 보여 넌 <br>But I don't need that <br>I don't mean that <br>단지 하나 난 필요해 <br>너의 젖어가는 ice sweat <br>사이다 컵 목을 적셔 <br>우린 빠져 나와 <br>Driving like we're Bonnie&amp;Clyde <br>만약 여기 나 혼자 계속 남았다면 <br>다음 밤은 없었겠지 <br>gun high speed <br>거리에서 떨어져 우린 shut down <br>의심은 끊이지 않지 virtual war <br>내 머릿속을 헤집어놓지 <br>넌 이해할 필요 없으니까 <br>벗어나줘 멀리 <br>Ride away <br>108 gas-oil <br>달려 저 다리를 넘어서 드라이브 <br>도로 위 heavy bass <br>808 run no break <br>잠깐의 신호에도 숨이 차 <br>Run away to your whoo <br>맡겨둘게 긴장을 풀래 til dawn <br>Private zone 네 구역 안에서 <br>편히 숨 쉬게 해 줘 <br>These make me numb numb numb <br>Cuz I left here none none none <br>You know the party's done done done <br>Stay until the dawn dawn dawn <br>You're prescription <br>]]></content><category term="Kana Bathe (카나베잇)" label="Kana Bathe (카나베잇)"/><category term="RideAway" label="RideAway"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cruen/Look_So_Good_Feat_Chaplynn/</id><title>Cruen - Look So Good (Feat. Chaplynn) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:06:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:06:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cruen/Look_So_Good_Feat_Chaplynn/" title="Cruen - Look So Good (Feat. Chaplynn) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Three two one go <br>Dance with me tonight <br>Dance with me all night <br>Dance with me tonight <br>Dance with me all night <br>Dance with me tonight <br>Dance with me all night <br>Dance with me tonight <br>Dance with me all night <br>I want you babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>I need you babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>I want you babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>I need you babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>I want you babe <br>Look so good <br>I need you babe <br>Look so good <br>I want you babe <br>Look so good <br>I need you babe <br>Look so good <br>Yeah you look so good <br>just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>Yeah you look so good <br>just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>Yeah you yeah just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>Yeah you yeah just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>Yeah you look so good <br>just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>Yeah you look so good <br>just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>Yeah you yeah just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>Yeah you yeah just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>Three two one go <br>I want you babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>I need you babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>I want you babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>I need you babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>I want you babe <br>Look so good <br>I need you babe <br>Look so good <br>I want you babe <br>Look so good <br>I need you babe <br>Look so good <br>Hey you make me feel so good <br>I do wanna <br>Hey you make me feel so good <br>I do wanna <br>Hey you hey I do <br>Hey you hey I do <br>Hey you make me feel so good <br>I do wanna <br>Na na na na <br>Hey you make me feel so good <br>I do wanna <br>Na na na na <br>Hey you hey I do <br>Na na na na <br>Hey you hey I do <br>Na na na na <br>Hey you <br>Hey you <br>Hey you <br>Hey you <br>Hey you <br>Hey you <br>Hey you Hey you <br>Hey you Hey you <br>Hey <br>Yeah you look so good <br>my my my babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>my my my babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>my my my babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>my my my babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>Yeah you look so good <br>just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>Yeah you yeah just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>Yeah you yeah just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>Yeah you look so good <br>just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>Yeah you look so good <br>just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>Yeah you yeah just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>Yeah you yeah just come with me <br>Na na na na <br>I want you babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>I need you babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>I want you babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>I need you babe <br>Yeah you look so good <br>I want you babe <br>Look so good <br>I need you babe <br>Look so good <br>I want you babe <br>Look so good <br>I need you babe <br>Look so good <br>Dance with me tonight <br>Dance with me all night <br>Dance with me tonight <br>Dance with me all night <br>Dance with me tonight <br>Dance with me all night <br>Dance with me tonight <br>Dance with me all night <br>]]></content><category term="Cruen" label="Cruen"/><category term="Look So Good (Feat. Chaplynn)" label="Look So Good (Feat. Chaplynn)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Esbell_에즈벨/Everlasting_I_Love_You_Feat_이자현/</id><title>Esbell_에즈벨 - Everlasting I Love You (Feat. 이자현) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:06:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:06:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Esbell_%EC%97%90%EC%A6%88%EB%B2%A8/Everlasting_I_Love_You_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%EC%9E%90%ED%98%84/" title="Esbell_에즈벨 - Everlasting I Love You (Feat. 이자현) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그저 바라만 봐도 내 입가에 <br>수줍은 미소를 선물해주는 사람 <br>그저 내 손만 잡아도 내 맘에 <br>따뜻한 평안을 전해주는 사람 <br>언제나 난 니 편이 되어줄게 <br>잡은 너의 두 손 놓지 않을게 <br>지금처럼 든든한 너만의 하늘이 되어 <br>아낄게 저 빛보다 <br>소중한 널 내게 보내준 <br>사람들에게 감사하며 <br>지킬게 너만은 내 품에서 <br>이젠 말할게 너에게 <br>Everlasting I Love you <br>그저 바라만 봐도 내 입가에 <br>수줍은 미소를 선물해주는 사람 <br>그저 내 손만 잡아도 내 맘에 <br>따뜻한 평안을 전해주는 사람 <br>언제나 난 니 편이 되어줄게 <br>잡은 너의 두 손 놓지 않을게 <br>지금처럼 든든한 너만의 하늘이 되어 <br>아낄게 저 빛보다 <br>소중한 널 내게 보내준 <br>사람들에게 감사하며 <br>지킬게 너만은 내 품에서 <br>이젠 말할게 너에게 <br>Everlasting Everlasting I Love you <br>아낄게 저 빛보다 <br>소중한 널 내게 보내준 <br>사람들에게 감사하며 <br>지킬게 너만은 내 품에서 <br>이젠 말할게 <br>I wanna your love 너에게 <br>Everlasting I Love you <br>]]></content><category term="Esbell (에즈벨)" label="Esbell (에즈벨)"/><category term="Everlasting I Love You (Feat. 이자현)" label="Everlasting I Love You (Feat. 이자현)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Esbell_에즈벨/5월의_크리스마스_Christmas_of_May_Feat_이정욱_이자현/</id><title>Esbell_에즈벨 - 5월의 크리스마스 (Christmas of May) (Feat. 이정욱, 이자현) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:06:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:06:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Esbell_%EC%97%90%EC%A6%88%EB%B2%A8/5%EC%9B%94%EC%9D%98_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%A4%EB%A7%88%EC%8A%A4_Christmas_of_May_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%EC%A0%95%EC%9A%B1_%EC%9D%B4%EC%9E%90%ED%98%84/" title="Esbell_에즈벨 - 5월의 크리스마스 (Christmas of May) (Feat. 이정욱, 이자현) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 이제야 왔나요 그대 <br>나를 모두 가질 한사람 <br>왜 이제야 알았죠 우린 <br>이미 서로의 전부란걸 <br>힘겨워 무너질 때도 <br>그대라면 함께라면 <br>난 웃을 수 있죠 <br>마주한 우리 더는 두렵지 않아 <br>지금 내 곁에선 그대의 고운 <br>두 손 놓지 않을게 <br>내 숨이 다하도록 <br>It's true Your're the first <br>and lasting on my mind <br>each and everyday <br>어두운 지난 상처도 <br>그대라면 함께라면 <br>난 견딜 수 있죠 <br>마주한 우리 더는 두렵지 않아 <br>지금 내 곁에선 그대의 고운 <br>두 손 놓지 않을게 <br>내 숨이 다하도록 <br>이젠 영원토록 그대 곁에서 <br>함께하기를 <br>내 숨이 다하도록 <br>It's true Your're the first time <br>그대 곁에서 그대 곁에서 <br>It's just like heaven <br>This is Christmas of my life <br>]]></content><category term="Esbell (에즈벨)" label="Esbell (에즈벨)"/><category term="5월의 크리스마스 (Christmas of May) (Feat. 이정욱, 이자현)" label="5월의 크리스마스 (Christmas of May) (Feat. 이정욱, 이자현)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Esbell_에즈벨/Sweet_So_Sweet_Feat_이자현/</id><title>Esbell_에즈벨 - Sweet So Sweet (Feat. 이자현) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:06:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:06:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Esbell_%EC%97%90%EC%A6%88%EB%B2%A8/Sweet_So_Sweet_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%EC%9E%90%ED%98%84/" title="Esbell_에즈벨 - Sweet So Sweet (Feat. 이자현) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[두근대는 가슴 설레는 발걸음 <br>두 손을 꼭 잡고 함께 걸어가 <br>나를 봐 내 눈에 가득한 널 <br>누구보다 멋져보여 <br>세상 가장 큰 선물은 너야 <br>다가와 내 볼에 입 맞추고 <br>살며시 기대 안겨 <br>서로의 사랑을 확인하지 <br>이제야 꿈꿔왔던 내 사랑이 시작됐어 <br>행복해 너만 보면 자꾸 웃음이나 <br>함께 있지 않아도 난 너를 느끼지 <br>니 향기 니 얼굴 너의 모든걸 <br>말해봐 니 맘도 나와 같은지 <br>매일 설레여 꿈꾸는지 <br>마법처럼 온 세상이 너야 <br>다가와 내 입에 입 맞추고 <br>부드러운 목소리로 한번 더 <br>니 맘을 고백해줘 <br>이제야 꿈꿔왔던 내 사랑이 시작됐어 <br>행복해 너만 보면 자꾸 웃음이나 <br>나 이대로 니 품에 안겨 잠들면 <br>말없이 내 머릴 감싸 안으면 <br>그 어떤 행복도 지금 <br>내 맘과 바꿀 순 없어 <br>이제야 꿈꿔왔던 내 사랑이 시작됐어 <br>행복해 행복해 너만 보면 <br>자꾸 웃음이 나 <br>]]></content><category term="Esbell (에즈벨)" label="Esbell (에즈벨)"/><category term="Sweet So Sweet (Feat. 이자현)" label="Sweet So Sweet (Feat. 이자현)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ian_Bledsoe/3312/</id><title>Ian_Bledsoe - 3312 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:07:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:07:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ian_Bledsoe/3312/" title="Ian_Bledsoe - 3312 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't like complicated <br>대충 주차했더니 두줄이 된 <br>기름 한방울 없는 예술가 예술가 <br>괜찮다고 말하지 않을꺼야 <br>계속 차에 치이는 정신력 정신력 <br>혼자 있는 공간 혼자 있는 시간 <br>뇌 속으로 잠수 해저 깊숙한 곳 <br>에서 날 짓눌러 해저 해저 해저 <br>가득찬 음식물 봉투 에이 <br>요리만 즐거울 뿐 에 에이 <br>라잌 제임스 하든 에 에이 <br>내가 뭘 하든 에 에이 <br>상관 하지 않았으면 하는 <br>시선들을 피해 <br>목에 동메달 몇갤 걸고 <br>결승점 없는 마라톤 뛰어 <br>언젠간 나도 대려 가겠지 <br>왜 가끔 그럴때 있어 <br>다들 가장 소중한것도 무의미 할 때 <br>뭘 의미할까 바다같은 인생 <br>잔잔할꺼면 풀장에서나 놀아 <br>애드먼즈 행성에 들릴꺼여 <br>내 옆구리에 서핑보드 보여 <br>산 같은 파도도 내 엔진엔 손 못대 <br>또 새로운 자리를 찾아 야지 왜 <br>이정도면 괜찮잖아 왜 <br>NO NO NO 안주 없이 한잔해야지 <br>맨정신으론 무서워 <br>어설퍼 보이는 생각 <br>해피피트 마냥 감시당해 <br>날 위해서라는데 <br>I Don't give a fuck <br>내가 죽은 것 <br>처럼 꾸밀꺼야 폴 <br>엑스벤 처럼 기횔봐 <br>아직은 뭐 나쁘지 않아 <br>조만간 흥행과 <br>깊이 둘다 취할꺼야 <br>라잌 라잌 부산행 <br>야간열차를 탄것 같군 <br>라잌 라잌 라잌 성공을 <br>뜸 들이는 장인의 뇌구조 <br>라잌 라잌 라잌 미로같아 <br>얼핏보면 꽉막힌 것 같아 <br>]]></content><category term="Ian Bledsoe" label="Ian Bledsoe"/><category term="3312" label="3312"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ian_Bledsoe/8701/</id><title>Ian_Bledsoe - 8701 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:07:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:07:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ian_Bledsoe/8701/" title="Ian_Bledsoe - 8701 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언젠가는 너 없이 살아야 된데 너를 <br>다시 용서할 수 있다면 <br>그게 좋을 텐데 <br>그럴 수가 없어 <br>흑백 동내에 비처럼 내리는 벌건줄 <br>가난이 죄라면 나도 전과자라서 <br>그들과 한 이불을 덮고 잠을 청해 <br>잠깐 나갈때도 좌물쇠를 채우고 <br>열쇠를 삼키듯 고요속에 침넘김 <br>한 여름밤 에어컨 없는 찝찝함 <br>창문을 잠궈놓지 내 현급이 위태로워 <br>한집 걸러 한집을 털어버리는데 뭐 <br>이젠 Beretta를 <br>내 심볼 위에 두고 싶어 <br>철창은 사람같아서 믿을 수 없어 <br>사람 죽는게 한순간이라는걸 믿어 <br>그 믿음이 날 몇번이고 살려내고 <br>어제는 폭팔음에 잠이 달아나 <br>무장하고 나가면 미란다 법칙이 들려 <br>돈에 쫒겨 막다른 골목을 배회할때 <br>나도 알아 그 골목의 끝은 낭떠러지 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>마른걸레 짜내듯 내리는 빗물 <br>숨 못쉬는 현실 <br>마치 Pippen의 defense <br>주황불을 보면 더 쎄게 밟아 <br>자신감이 하늘을 찌르는 친구들 <br>부족한건 물과 소금 필요한건 담배 <br>선을 넘은 안심과 자극들에 취해 <br>내 옆집은 법무부 새벽에는 고요해 <br>그 사이로 관통하는 수많은 택시 <br>한번쯤은 상상하는 쇠고랑 찬 내모습 <br>그게 현실이 되면 인생을 되돌아봐 <br>벌건줄을 얻고 세상을 배웠다면 <br>무지함의 징그러움 찡그리는 미간 <br>다 알꺼야 이 세상에서 <br>그게 어떤 의미인지 <br>철창을 사이에 둔 부모와 아들 <br>찾고 있어 어디로든 이어지지 <br>않는 완벽한 탈옥을 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>어딜 가 쉿 <br>벌건 울음소리 상투적인 대화들 <br>우주에서 떠내려오듯 작은 돚단배 <br>위에 남겨져 운명을 믿지는 않는데 <br>가끔 만나는 친구같이 어색해 <br>늙고 있어 시간을 <br>소비하는 Hilton처럼 <br>증오와 분노 알약에 넣고 물과 삼켜 <br>이 동내를 탈출할 수 있는 내 믿음 <br>숫자를 매주 marking해 <br>오직 그것뿐 <br>언젠가는 너 없이 살아야 된데 너를 <br>다시 용서할 수 있다면 <br>그게 좋을 텐데 <br>그럴 수가 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="Ian Bledsoe" label="Ian Bledsoe"/><category term="8701" label="8701"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/말라/LIKE_ME_Feat_COCO/</id><title>말라 - LIKE ME (Feat. COCO) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:07:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:07:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%90%EB%9D%BC/LIKE_ME_Feat_COCO/" title="말라 - LIKE ME (Feat. COCO) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무도 못해 내 <br>스타일은 모두의 롤 모델 돼 <br>wassup kid <br>i know u wanna be me <br>asian hit man kill bill <br>놀지 원 없이 <br>강남에서부터 신사 <br>이태원 까지 <br>내 outfit justin b <br>같이 over fit erthing <br>내 스타일 베끼기엔 조금 무겁지 <br>ur crew losers 전부 <br>네 어머니 보다 랩못하는건 연구 <br>안 한 니들탓 digging <br>해봐라 youtube <br>가서 내 이름 치고 싹다 베껴 우태운 <br>뽑아야지 new benz <br>whre is atm i need some cash <br>south cream 과 pop the champagne <br>오늘만 사는 새끼들 뒤지고 난 내일 <br>위해 자 네 여자 위에서 <br>나 every night <br>in the car i did it mofucker <br>열이 나 <br>겁이 나 넌 네 여친이 떠나갈까봐 <br>to me asian sultan in da house <br>제대로 소문나 아잇 <br>like me like me just do it like me <br>나이키 같이 아냐 <br>malla 같이 like me <br>like me like me just do it like me <br>south k 같이 하던지 <br>아니면 like me <br>like me like me just do it like me <br>나이키 같이 아냐 <br>malla 같이 like me <br>like me like me just do it like me <br>south k 같이 하던지 <br>아니면 like me <br>자 들어간다 <br>아가들아 랩은 이렇게 하는 거란다 <br>형 알아 근데 나도 형처럼 멋있게 <br>랩 하고 싶은데 어려워 <br>그래 물론 그게 쉽진 않지 <br>나같은 사기캐릭은 반칙 <br>이거든 밑거름이 탄탄하지 않은 이 <br>어쩔수 있나 허풍 가득한 거품뿐 <br>가끔씩 랩에 싫증이 나면 <br>형들한테 call 해 <br>같이 놀러 갈래 홍대나 건대 <br>이태원에 우리가 뜨면 <br>여자들은 되지 걸레 <br>너의 총각딱지를 떼주마 <br>클럽에서 인기남이 되구파 <br>대구빡 굴려봤자니께 <br>내 춤을 따라해 그럼 백프로야 <br>like me like me just do it like me <br>나이키 같이 아냐 <br>malla 같이 like me <br>like me like me just do it like me <br>south k 같이 하던지 <br>아니면 like me <br>like me like me just do it like me <br>나이키 같이 아냐 <br>malla 같이 like me <br>like me like me just do it like me <br>south k 같이 하던지 <br>아니면 like me <br>like me like me just do it like me <br>나이키 같이 아냐 <br>malla 같이 like me <br>like me like me just do it like me <br>south k 같이 하던지 <br>아니면 like me <br>]]></content><category term="말라" label="말라"/><category term="LIKE ME (Feat. COCO)" label="LIKE ME (Feat. COCO)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조정훈/와서_먹고_마시라/</id><title>조정훈 - 와서 먹고 마시라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:07:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:07:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%A0%95%ED%9B%88/%EC%99%80%EC%84%9C_%EB%A8%B9%EA%B3%A0_%EB%A7%88%EC%8B%9C%EB%9D%BC/" title="조정훈 - 와서 먹고 마시라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[목마른 자들아 나아오라 <br>돈 없는 자들도 나아오라 <br>주께서 값없이 내어 주리니 <br>와서 먹고 마시라 <br>목마른 자들아 나아오라 <br>돈 없는 자들도 나아오라 <br>주께서 값없이 내어 주리니 <br>와서 먹고 마시라 <br>만날 만할 때에 주를 찾으라 <br>가까이 계실 때 주를 부르라 <br>악한 자 불의한 자는 <br>그 길과 생각 버리고 <br>돌아오라 용서하시리 <br>목마른 자들아 나아오라 <br>돈 없는 자들도 나아오라 <br>주께서 값없이 내어 주리니 <br>와서 먹고 마시라 <br>목마른 자들아 나아오라 <br>돈 없는 자들도 나아오라 <br>주께서 값없이 내어 주리니 <br>와서 먹고 마시라 <br>나의 생각은 너희와 다르며 <br>나의 길은 너의 길과 다르니 <br>긍휼을 베푸시는 우리 주님께 <br>돌아오라 용서하시리 <br>목마른 자들아 나아오라 <br>돈 없는 자들도 나아오라 <br>주께서 값없이 내어 주리니 <br>와서 먹고 마시라 <br>목마른 자들아 나아오라 <br>돈 없는 자들도 나아오라 <br>주께서 값없이 내어 주리니 <br>와서 먹고 마시라 <br>목마른 자들아 나아오라 <br>주께서 값없이 내어 주리니 <br>목마른 자들아 나아오라 <br>주께서 값없이 내어 주리니 <br>와서 먹고 마시라 <br>와서 먹고 마시라 <br>와서 먹고 마시라 <br>와서 먹고 마시라 <br>]]></content><category term="조정훈" label="조정훈"/><category term="와서 먹고 마시라" label="와서 먹고 마시라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Juel/REALLY_WANNA_KNOW_Prod_by_Juel/</id><title>Juel - REALLY WANNA KNOW (Prod. by Juel) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:07:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:07:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Juel/REALLY_WANNA_KNOW_Prod_by_Juel/" title="Juel - REALLY WANNA KNOW (Prod. by Juel) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wanna know I wanna know <br>I wanna know ya ya baby <br>I wanna know I wanna know <br>I wanna know I wanna know <br>ya ya yeah ya ya yeah yeah <br>Let's talk about it girl <br>I Just really wanna know <br>everyday money on ma mind <br>eyday money on ma mind <br>I Can do it baby all night <br>I Can do it baby all night <br>You know what I'm <br>talkin bout baby know <br>All for money and you <br>Skrt <br>I wanna know I wanna know <br>I wanna know ya ya <br>I wanna know I wanna know <br>I wanna know ya ya <br>I wanna know I wanna know <br>I wanna know <br>ya ya yeah ya ya yeah <br>you got something I want you <br>I got deferent life style I'll show you <br>I know what you do baby I know <br>eveyday I getting fukin dollers <br>she just know who's fukin baller Drrrrr <br>나도 알아 뭘 원하고 너의 성격 <br>넌 갖고싶은건 다 사야돼 <br>니 몸매에 그 tattoo <br>미치게하는건 Sexy한 말투 <br>and attitude <br>내가 돈을 벌고있는 이유 <br>I wanna know bout u <br>돈을 쓰고 싶게 만들어 만들어 <br>어디든 데리고 갈께 <br>그전엔 널 데리러갈께 <br>they know I got something <br>모두가 널 매일 부러워하게 <br>Just turn up for me <br>Just turn up for me <br>they said she is look like an art <br>she just wanna love me <br>내 손가락 Medusa <br>두개가 널 보고 웃지 <br>이젠 열손가락부터 허리 <br>목까지 난 Medusa를 입지 <br>you killing'em <br>진짜는 진짜가 알아본단말 <br>Hiphop은 my life style <br>내 신발만 보잖아 <br>I wanna know ya <br>Let's talk about it girl <br>I Just really wanna know <br>everyday money on ma mind <br>eyday money on ma mind <br>I Can do it baby all night <br>I Can do it baby all night <br>You know what I'm <br>talkin bout baby know <br>All for money and you <br>Skrt <br>I wanna know I wanna know <br>I wanna know ya ya <br>I wanna know I wanna know <br>I wanna know ya ya <br>I wanna know I wanna know <br>I wanna know <br>ya ya yeah ya ya yeah <br>you gotta know it <br>you gotta know it <br>알지 I don't need a fukin <br>other bitchs <br>Tell me What u want baby <br>What u like baby <br>누가 뭐래도 <br>you kiling'em baby <br>매일 매일 매일 <br>we gon' party like ma birthday <br>널 위해 일해 <br>I do the work you know <br>monday to sunday <br>내 동네로 데려갈께 <br>니가 있기엔 여긴 너무 작네 <br>원하는건 내겐 뭐든 말해 <br>내가 있으니 없지 니 Nightmare <br>내가 Hiphop이면 너는 Medusa <br>나말고 안돼 <br>I'm cool But You are not <br>I'm gonna get this money <br>you want too <br>곧 돈을 흩뿌릴께 <br>we gon’ perfect Tonight <br>I Tonight I Tonight <br>I'm stil on it baby <br>I'm so fly I'm so fly I'm so fly <br>she's so professional <br>so sometimes sensual <br>I I mean baby you're my world <br>you know <br>I know you got something too <br>Imma spend ma money on you <br>내가 돈을 벌고있는 이유 <br>하늘 높이 나는 기분 <br>you ain't even single <br>But fly on ma bed like an egle yeah <br>말해줘 시간이 없잖아 <br>drrrra I just wanna know ya <br>Let's talk about it girl <br>I Just really wanna know <br>everyday money on ma mind <br>eyday money on ma mind <br>I Can do it baby all night <br>I Can do it baby all night <br>You know what I'm <br>talkin bout baby know <br>All for money and you <br>Skrt <br>I wanna know I wanna know <br>I wanna know ya ya <br>I wanna know I wanna know <br>I wanna know ya ya <br>I wanna know I wanna know <br>I wanna know <br>ya ya yeah ya ya yeah <br>Skrt <br>I wanna know I wanna know <br>I wanna know ya ya <br>I wanna know I wanna know <br>I wanna know ya ya <br>I wanna know I wanna know <br>I wanna know <br>ya ya yeah baby yeah <br>]]></content><category term="Juel" label="Juel"/><category term="REALLY WANNA KNOW (Prod. by Juel)" label="REALLY WANNA KNOW (Prod. by Juel)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Owell_Mood_오웰_무드/990/</id><title>Owell_Mood_오웰_무드 - 990 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:11:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:11:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Owell_Mood_%EC%98%A4%EC%9B%B0_%EB%AC%B4%EB%93%9C/990/" title="Owell_Mood_오웰_무드 - 990 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Need more fee vert <br>In the starry night be lay back <br>No more covert <br>Stay overnight be perfect <br>Girl I know where you at <br>The 990 bus's stoppin woo <br>아직까진 가지마 <br>아직 하지 않은 말까지 <br>하기까지가 babe woo <br>꺼내기가 너무 어려워 <br>재촉하는 bus schedule이 서러워 <br>날 원래 기다리지만 <br>너 하나만큼은 나 기다리고 싶어 <br>Babe 딱 5분이면 돼 이젠 <br>Christine ma princess <br>Don't pushin me in excess <br>Bad girl <br>Don't you stayin all night <br>Baby stay around me <br>and say my name <br>Leave steps <br>in the city all night <br>Baby come in around me <br>and hold my hand <br>No no drink <br>to make glasses dry yeah <br>No no drink <br>to make glasses dry yeah <br>지금 11시 40분 이게 마지막 <br>버스란 걸 너보다 더 잘 알아 <br>많은 걸 바라지는 않아 괜찮아 <br>그냥 떨고 있는 두 손을 잡아줘 <br>Babe 기억해 지금 내 말 <br>괜히 많은 생각하지마 <br>Draw an anology <br>to you from Rodin <br>It takes too long <br>I can't take 2 hares <br>No no drink <br>to make glasses dry yeah <br>No no drink <br>to make glasses dry yeah <br>Need more fee vert <br>In the starry night be lay back <br>No more covert <br>Stay overnight be perfect <br>Bad girl <br>Don't you stayin all night <br>Baby stay around me <br>and say my name <br>Leave steps <br>in the city all night <br>Baby come in around me <br>and hold my hand <br>No no drink <br>to make glasses dry yeah <br>No no drink <br>to make glasses dry yeah <br>]]></content><category term="Owell Mood (오웰 무드)" label="Owell Mood (오웰 무드)"/><category term="990" label="990"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Owell_Mood_오웰_무드/알겠어_I_Guess_So/</id><title>Owell_Mood_오웰_무드 - 알겠어 (I Guess So) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:11:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:11:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Owell_Mood_%EC%98%A4%EC%9B%B0_%EB%AC%B4%EB%93%9C/%EC%95%8C%EA%B2%A0%EC%96%B4_I_Guess_So/" title="Owell_Mood_오웰_무드 - 알겠어 (I Guess So) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그냥 아무 일도 없었다고 <br>심심해서 잠깐 그냥 나왔다고 <br>I just do no nose <br>in to your privacy <br>I just do no nose <br>in to your fantasy <br>baby take your phone <br>ringin’ all night long <br>baby 어서 말해 지금 집이라고 <br>투덜대지마 나는 다 알아 <br>남들은 몰라도 나는 다 알아 <br>내가 널 생각하는 마음과는 <br>다른 것 같아 날 생각하는 마음 <br>니가 아니라고 하는 그 차이가 <br>우릴 멀어지게 해 밖에 나가 <br>술을 마시건 I don’t care about it <br>클럽을 가던 I don’t care about it <br>절대 나만한 남자는 <br>나밖에 없다고 <br>큰소리 치던 너는 어디에 babe <br>알겠어 그만해 이제 <br>알겠어 니 맘 이제 <br>알겠어 그냥 꺼져줄게 babe <br>꺼져줄게 babe <br>꺼져줄게 babe <br>꺼져줄게 babe <br>꺼져줄게 babe <br>꺼져줄게 babe <br>그냥 아무 일도 없었다고 <br>심심해서 잠깐 그냥 나왔다고 <br>I just do no nose <br>in to your privacy <br>I just do no nose <br>in to your fantasy <br>baby take your phone <br>ringin’ all night long <br>baby 어서 말해 지금 집이라고 <br>투덜대지마 나는 다 알아 <br>남들은 몰라도 나는 다 알아 <br>투덜대지마 나는 다 알아 <br>남들은 몰라도 나는 다 알아 <br>보고 싶다고 말을 못했어 <br>하기가 싫었어 <br>자존심 상했어 <br>예전과 다르다고 생각했어 <br>하지만 같았어 <br>여전히 좋은 <br>니 목소리가 들릴 때면 <br>난 항상 웃음이 나왔고 <br>난 그거면 만족해 <br>내 폰은 니가 없으면 <br>쓸모 없는 시계가 돼 <br>알겠어 그만해 이제 <br>알겠어 니 맘 이제 <br>알겠어 그냥 꺼져줄게 babe <br>알겠어 그만해 이제 <br>알겠어 니 맘 이제 <br>알겠어 그냥 꺼져줄게 babe <br>꺼져줄게 babe <br>꺼져줄게 babe <br>꺼져줄게 babe <br>]]></content><category term="Owell Mood (오웰 무드)" label="Owell Mood (오웰 무드)"/><category term="알겠어 (I Guess So)" label="알겠어 (I Guess So)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Elijah_N/Missing_Whats_You/</id><title>Elijah_N - Missing What`s You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:13:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:13:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Elijah_N/Missing_Whats_You/" title="Elijah_N - Missing What`s You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm getting chills When they tell me you are not yourself <br>I'm trying to move But it's hard I'm out of breath <br>oho ooh <br><br><br>Nothing belongs to you and I <br>all the picture of you cut like a knife <br>Whatever they call us <br>Whatever they'll do <br>They're running in circles, Circle of fools <br>Whatever we will risk and nothing to prove <br>But in the dark, it's starting to <br>Whatever they call us <br>Whatever they'll do <br>We're running together I'll be here for you <br>Whatever we will miss We'll find something new <br>But in the dark, I'm starting to <br>Missing what's you <br>I see your face your mouth looks like mine <br>Pretend to be <br>Surrounded by ghosts in white <br>And ahaooo <br>Nothing belongs to you and I <br>Oooh all the picture of you cut like a knife <br>Whatever they call us <br>Whatever they'll do <br>They're running in circles <br>Circle of fools <br>Whatever we will risk and nothing to prove <br>But in the dark, it's starting to <br>Whatever they call us <br>Whatever they'll do <br>Were running together I'll be here for you <br>Whatever we will miss <br>We will find something new <br>But in the dark, I'm starting to <br>Missing whats you <br>Missing whats you]]></content><category term="Elijah N" label="Elijah N"/><category term="Missing What`s You" label="Missing What`s You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mondays/Be_With_You/</id><title>Mondays - Be With You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:13:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:13:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mondays/Be_With_You/" title="Mondays - Be With You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You gotta listen up, listen up <br>There's not a thing that I can’t get from you <br>Boy I don’t need that much need that much <br>How can I tell you what I wanna do? <br><br>I never needed you to give me things <br>I never needed gifts or diamond rings <br>All I ever need I, need I <br>All I ever need is here with you <br><br>Baby there's a this place were we can go <br>Where it's always shining like the snow <br>Listen to your heart beat don’t you know <br>That I just wanna be with you? <br>Baby there's a place were we can go <br>Where it's always shining like the snow <br>Listen to your heart beat don’t you know <br>That I just wanna be with you? <br><br>Oh, oh <br><br>Oh, I can’t get enough, get enough <br>Don’t ever let me be away from you <br>I’m gonna hold you tight, hold you tight <br>Cuz your the only thing I can’t lose <br><br>I never needed you to give me things <br>I never needed gifts or diamond rings <br>All I ever need I, need I <br>All I ever need is here with you <br><br>Baby there's a place were we can go <br>Where it's always shining like the snow <br>Listen to your heart beat don’t you know <br>That I just wanna be with you? <br>Baby there's a place were we can go <br>Where it's always shining like the snow <br>Listen to your heart beat don’t you know <br>That I just wanna be with you? <br><br>You can’t buy your way into my heart <br>But you don’t see that I just want you <br>You get me things <br>But I don’t care <br><br>Baby there's a place were we can go <br>Where it's always shining like the snow <br>Listen to your heart beat don’t you know <br>That I just wanna be with you? <br>Baby there's a place were we can go <br>Where it's always shining like the snow <br>Listen to your heart beat don’t you know <br>That I just wanna be with you?]]></content><category term="Mondays" label="Mondays"/><category term="Be With You" label="Be With You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jennifer_Morrison/A_Happy_Beginning/</id><title>Jennifer_Morrison - A Happy Beginning - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:13:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:13:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jennifer_Morrison/A_Happy_Beginning/" title="Jennifer_Morrison - A Happy Beginning - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tomorrow is uncertain <br>who knows what it will bring <br>But one thing is for sure, love <br>with you I have everything <br>And happily ever after <br>is the way these stories go <br>Used to think that's what I wanted <br>but now I finally know <br>There's no storm we can't out run <br>We will always find the sun <br>Leave the past and all it's scars <br>A Happy beginning now is ours <br>We can celebrate together <br>a longtime wish come true <br>What makes it even better <br>today your story starts anew <br>But villains casting curses <br>we can overcome them all <br>If we all stand strong together <br>There's no way we can fall <br>There's no storm we can't out run <br>we will always find the sun <br>Leave the past and all its scars <br>a happy beginning now is ours <br>There's no place we can decide <br>take my hand and join the fight, past the powers <br>we'll find the stars <br>A happy beginning now is ours <br>Nah Nah Nah Nah Nah <br>There's no storm we can't out run <br>we will always find the sun <br>Leave the past and all its scars <br>A happy beginning now is ours <br>There's no place we can decide <br>take my hand and join the fight, past the powers <br>we'll find the stars <br>A happy beginning now is ours <br>A happy beginning now is ours]]></content><category term="Jennifer Morrison" label="Jennifer Morrison"/><category term="A Happy Beginning" label="A Happy Beginning"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jennifer_Morrison/Emmas_Theme/</id><title>Jennifer_Morrison - Emma`s Theme - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:13:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:13:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jennifer_Morrison/Emmas_Theme/" title="Jennifer_Morrison - Emma`s Theme - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Once I lived in darkness, out there on my own <br>Lived to brave the world alone <br>Everything seemed hopeless No chance to break free <br><br>Couldn't hear the song inside of me <br>Once upon a time a song inspired them ？？ be brave <br>They gave me up because my fate was as the one who'd save <br>The world from your dark magic and the wicked things you do <br>They placed a song inside my heart more powerful than you <br>All the years of running ？？ no not anymore <br>I know what I'm living for <br>I'm no longer searching <br>Turns out all along, the answer was inside me ？？ with a song]]></content><category term="Jennifer Morrison" label="Jennifer Morrison"/><category term="Emma`s Theme" label="Emma`s Theme"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ginnifer_Goodwin/Charmings_Vs_Evil_Queen/</id><title>Ginnifer_Goodwin - Charmings Vs. Evil Queen - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:13:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:13:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ginnifer_Goodwin/Charmings_Vs_Evil_Queen/" title="Ginnifer_Goodwin - Charmings Vs. Evil Queen - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a powerful magic when two hearts are one <br>A powerful magic rise the sun <br>Goodness will triumph <br><br>And evils undone <br>When you dare to heed loves call <br>Cause love is the most powerful magic of all <br><br>Down with love, down with hope <br>Don't need blind faith to cope <br>Or inspiring songs in my heart <br>Got the magic I need <br>For my darkest of deeds <br>Love at times can entrance <br>But love doesn't stand a chance <br>No, no <br>Love doesn't stand a chance <br><br>There's a powerful magic <br>When two voices soar <br>I'm ever more hopeful for what lies in store <br><br>Once I loved and once I learned <br>Love is weakness <br>Love will leave you burned <br><br>Nothing will stop us, no not anymore <br>With our daughter's fate at stake <br>Happy ending you will see <br>But happy ending will end with me <br>Seems we find a big chance <br>Love doesn't stand a chance <br>Now let our song show the powerful magic <br>We can make <br>Got you where I want you now <br>Your speel as soon be broken <br>Let us see how strong you are <br>When everything is spoken]]></content><category term="Ginnifer Goodwin" label="Ginnifer Goodwin"/><category term="Charmings Vs. Evil Queen" label="Charmings Vs. Evil Queen"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rebecca_Mader/Wicked_Always_Wins/</id><title>Rebecca_Mader - Wicked Always Wins - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:13:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:13:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rebecca_Mader/Wicked_Always_Wins/" title="Rebecca_Mader - Wicked Always Wins - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Finally the moment I was hoping would come <br>The moment he would realize he chose the wrong one <br>There isn't any curse I could cast to match this feeling <br>The pain I knew when Rumple turned his back on my heart at last will be Regina's when her life falls apart <br>Suddenly the future's looking more appealing <br>Once I was filled with rage <br>Now I enjoy the ride <br>It's so electrifying <br>Watching all her dreams denied <br>Oh I will fly into tomorrow <br>my sister full of sorrow finally paying for her sins <br>I'll smile all the while she is crying <br>Inside she's slowly dying <br>Wicked always wins <br>Oh evil may be powerful <br>But wicked always wins <br>If mum could see me now she would ache with regret <br>Cause she'd witness all the glory wickedness gets <br>She went and made Regina queen and my blood boil <br>But that's all history <br>Time they all understood what they call green with envy I just call looking good <br>Oh I will fly into tomorrow <br>My sister full of sorrow finally paying for her sins <br>The strife her life was so enchanted she took it all for granted <br>Now she'll dream what could've been <br>Oh evil may be powerful <br>But wicked always <br>I'll give her a magic gift to bring the Charmings down <br>When Regina stands victorious I'll swoop right into town <br>When he learns the spells was mine <br>Oh Rumple he will see he should've chosen me <br>So I will fly into tomorrow <br>Delighting in her sorrow as a better day begins <br>This time nobody's gonna stop me <br>No evil's gonna taunt me <br>Oh wicked always wins <br>Her happy ending will be mine <br>Cause wicked always wins]]></content><category term="Rebecca Mader" label="Rebecca Mader"/><category term="Wicked Always Wins" label="Wicked Always Wins"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Colin_ODonoghue/Revenge_Is_Gonna_Be_Mine/</id><title>Colin_ODonoghue - Revenge Is Gonna Be Mine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:13:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:13:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Colin_ODonoghue/Revenge_Is_Gonna_Be_Mine/" title="Colin_ODonoghue - Revenge Is Gonna Be Mine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My dear Prince and Princess <br>Your offer is meaningless <br>Don't give a damn ‘bout your rank <br><br>The gold in your sack, well it isn't worth jack… <br>I should make you fools go walk the plank <br>Your riches would fill other pirates with glee <br>But none of those pirates are me They're not he <br>Singin' yo ho keep your jewels divine <br>Yo ho ？？ and your manners refined <br>Cuz even more precious than rum in a stein is <br>Revenge, revenge, revenge, and it's gonna be mine <br>Revenge, revenge, revenge…is gonna be mine <br><br>I've savaged and pillaged and pilfered each village <br>My conquest I'm justly proud of He's proud of… <br>Each time that I plunder, I leave to an asunder <br>A pirate's life is one to love One to love <br>And yet my heart's hardened as hard as a rock ？？ <br>Won't rest ‘til I skin me a croc Gonna skin me a croc <br>Singin yo ho You can beg me, bring wine <br>But yo ho ？？ you'll be wasting your time <br>That croc in my hand ？？ wanna tear out his spine <br>Revenge, revenge, revenge…is gonna be mine <br>Revenge, revenge, revenge…is gonna be mine <br>Once I sailed toward a horizon where I might find happiness waiting <br>Until that croc destroyed my life and filled me with hate unabaiting <br>Some say ‘Let it go' but I say ‘HELL NO' <br>I'm finally on the right path <br>Soon the dark one will feel he will feel <br>The fire of this pirate's wrath <br>Singing yo ho, I'll slaughter this swine <br>Yo ho, must be fate's design <br>At last our tales will again intertwine <br>Revenge, revenge, revenge is gonna be mine <br>Oh, it's gonna be <br>Oh, it's gonna be <br>Oh, it's gonna be mine <br>Oh, it's gonna be <br>Oh, it's gonna be <br>Oh, it's gonna be mine]]></content><category term="Colin O`Donoghue" label="Colin O`Donoghue"/><category term="Revenge Is Gonna Be Mine" label="Revenge Is Gonna Be Mine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lana_Parrilla/Love_Doesnt_Stand_A_Chance/</id><title>Lana_Parrilla - Love Doesn`t Stand A Chance - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:13:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:13:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lana_Parrilla/Love_Doesnt_Stand_A_Chance/" title="Lana_Parrilla - Love Doesn`t Stand A Chance - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So, the Charmings think their love is <br>Strong enough to defeat me <br>Well, there's one thing they don't know <br><br>Mirror mirror, could not be clearer <br>and love is a waste of time <br>I'm here to tell you with love's magic spell <br>you cannot match the power of mine <br><br>Once I loved and once I learned <br>Love is weakness <br>Love will leave you burned <br><br>Down with love, down with hope <br>Don't need blind faith to cope <br>Or inspiring songs in my heart <br>Got the magic I need <br>For my darkest of deeds <br>Love at times can entrance <br>but love doesn't stand a chance <br>Love doesn't stand a chance <br><br>Mirror mirror, the times draws nearer <br>For me to enact my curse <br>Those happy feelings <br>That send them reeling <br>Will soon become the reverse <br><br>Down with love, down with hope <br>Don't need blind faith to cope <br>Or inspiring songs in my heart <br>Got the magic I need <br>For my darkest of deeds <br>Love at times can entrance <br>but love doesn't stand a chance <br>Love doesn't stand a chance <br><br>Stole my shot at one true love <br>That's what she did to me <br>Now that little bitch will wish <br>She never ever knew me <br><br>Down with love, down with dreams <br>Down with goodness schemes <br>'Gonna rip the song right from their hearts <br>Got the magic I need <br>For my darkest of deeds <br>Watch my curse kill romance <br>So love doesn't stand a chance <br>No, no, no <br>Love doesn't stand a chance]]></content><category term="Lana Parrilla" label="Lana Parrilla"/><category term="Love Doesn`t Stand A Chance" label="Love Doesn`t Stand A Chance"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ginnifer_Goodwin/Powerful_Magic/</id><title>Ginnifer_Goodwin - Powerful Magic - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:14:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:14:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ginnifer_Goodwin/Powerful_Magic/" title="Ginnifer_Goodwin - Powerful Magic - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Good morning, friend <br>Oh, my dear, something's wrong <br>Cause all my words are coming out in song <br><br>A rhythm stirs, deep within my soul <br>I'm saying things in ways I can't control <br><br>Ah, what's going on <br>Someone cast a spell or curse <br>Cause what I say is coming out in verse <br>My voice just soars, had no idea it could <br>Now I'm singing out, and my do I sound <br>Good <br><br>What could be the reason <br><br>I think, I know my Love <br>It's all because the wish I made <br>Upon the star above <br>With music in our hearts <br>We'll defeat the Evil Queen <br><br>How <br>Cause love expressed through song <br>is a weapon like the Queen has never seen <br><br>There's a powerful magic <br>When two are hearts are one <br>A powerful magic, bright as the sun <br><br>Goodness will triumph <br>And evils undone <br>When you dare to heed loves call <br><br>Cause love is the most powerful magic of all <br>There's a powerful magic <br>When two voices soar <br><br>I'm ever more hopeful for what lies in store <br><br>Nothing will stop us, no not anymore <br>Watch the wish you made come true <br><br>That is the love and its powerful magic can do <br>Feel the song inside our hearts <br>That is where the magic starts <br><br>Oh it grows with every note <br>Soaring sweetly from my throat <br>Every line ends with a rhyme <br><br>Don't know how but its sublime <br>With a melody so strong <br>How can we go wrong <br>Because powerful magic <br>we now have the means <br>Cause love can defeat powers, curses or beans <br>And the unhappy ending let that be the Queen's <br>With our daughter's fate at stake <br>Seems we found a lucky break <br>Now let our song show the powerful magic <br>We can make]]></content><category term="Ginnifer Goodwin" label="Ginnifer Goodwin"/><category term="Powerful Magic" label="Powerful Magic"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Noah_Bartfield/Let_It_Be_Love/</id><title>Noah_Bartfield - Let It Be Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:16:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:16:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Noah_Bartfield/Let_It_Be_Love/" title="Noah_Bartfield - Let It Be Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday you asked me, “Is it worth it?” <br>I told you it was, I told you it was <br>You thought that I would leave you any moment <br>I told you, “That’s not what love does, That’s not what love does” <br>You’ve gotta let it rise, let it fall <br>Let it grow on it’s own for a while <br>Let it do what it please, let it rest when it needs <br>Let it be love, Let it be love, Let it be, love <br>You thought that i would pass by like the others <br>You were wrong, You were wrong <br>I know that you've been hurt bad and I’m sorry <br>But that’s not what love does, that’s not what love does <br>If you let it rise, let it fall <br>Let it grow on it’s own for a while <br>Let it do what it please, let it rest when it needs <br>Let it be love, Let it be love, Let it be, love <br>I know it’s hard <br>To let your guard down <br>But trust me <br>Let it rise, let it fall <br>Let it grow on it’s own for a while <br>Let it do what it please, let it rest when it needs <br>Let it be love, Let it be love, Let it be, love <br>Let it be love, Let it be love, Let it be, love <br>Let it be love, Let it be love, Let it be, love]]></content><category term="Noah Bartfield" label="Noah Bartfield"/><category term="Let It Be Love" label="Let It Be Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/뮤폴로지/홀로그램/</id><title>뮤폴로지 - 홀로그램 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:17:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:17:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AE%A4%ED%8F%B4%EB%A1%9C%EC%A7%80/%ED%99%80%EB%A1%9C%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%A8/" title="뮤폴로지 - 홀로그램 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[카푸치노 자욱에 <br>홀린 듯 뻗은 팔이 <br>홀로그램처럼 <br>흐릿흐릿 해 <br>해맑은 미소에 <br>떨림을 다잡아도 <br>내 맘 어쩔 수가 없네요 <br>그댄 너무 예쁘네요 <br>우 바람이 불어와요 <br>내 바람이 될까요 <br>나는 그냥 지나요 <br>귓가에 속삭이며 <br>바이아 바이아 바이아 바 오 에 오 <br>홀로그램 카푸치노 <br>부드러운 그대 <br>예쁜 입술 어쩔 수가 없네요 <br>우 바람이 불어와요 <br>내 바람이 될까요 <br>또 나는 그냥 지나요 <br>귓가에 속삭이며 <br>바이아 바이아 바이아 바 오 <br>바이아 바이아 바이아 바 오 에 오 <br>]]></content><category term="뮤폴로지" label="뮤폴로지"/><category term="홀로그램" label="홀로그램"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/보이스_메모리/부는_날_Feat_해리안/</id><title>보이스_메모리 - 부는 날 (Feat. 해리안) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:17:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:17:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4_%EB%A9%94%EB%AA%A8%EB%A6%AC/%EB%B6%80%EB%8A%94_%EB%82%A0_Feat_%ED%95%B4%EB%A6%AC%EC%95%88/" title="보이스_메모리 - 부는 날 (Feat. 해리안) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람이 부는 날 <br>그대가 떠난 날 <br>스쳐간 바람이 <br>모질게 널 데려가는데 <br>찬 바람이 불어와 <br>내 마음이 아려와 <br>그녀를 데려오라고 <br>바람에게 속삭여 봐도 <br>하염없이 걷고 있다 <br>너와 이별한 그 날에 <br>천천히 걸으려 했는데 <br>바람이 자꾸만 자꾸만 밀어서 <br>좋은 사람 만나라고 <br>마음에도 없었던 아픈 말을 하고 <br>날 떠나지 말라고 말하고 싶은데 <br>불어오는 바람이 말문을 막아서 <br>바람이 부는 날 <br>그대가 떠난 날 <br>스쳐간 바람이 <br>모질게 널 데려가는데 <br>찬 바람이 불어와 <br>내 마음이 아려와 <br>그녀를 데려오라고 <br>바람에게 속삭여 봐도 <br>찬 바람만 불어와 <br>바람은 멎었고 잔잔한 날인데 <br>이미 저 멀리 날아가 버린 너 <br>바람아 듣고 있다면 <br>다시 내 곁으로 불어와줘 <br>내 사랑 <br>바람이 부는 날 <br>내가 그댈 찾는 날 <br>스쳐간 바람이 <br>모질게 널 데려간대도 <br>바람이 불어와 <br>내 마음도 불어와 <br>널 찾아올 거야 <br>바람이 되어서라도 <br>바람이 부는 날 <br>]]></content><category term="보이스 메모리" label="보이스 메모리"/><category term="부는 날 (Feat. 해리안)" label="부는 날 (Feat. 해리안)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/보이스_메모리/부는_날_Ballad_Ver_Feat_새벽_Midnight/</id><title>보이스_메모리 - 부는 날 (Ballad Ver.) (Feat. 새벽 `Midnight`) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:17:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:17:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4_%EB%A9%94%EB%AA%A8%EB%A6%AC/%EB%B6%80%EB%8A%94_%EB%82%A0_Ballad_Ver_Feat_%EC%83%88%EB%B2%BD_Midnight/" title="보이스_메모리 - 부는 날 (Ballad Ver.) (Feat. 새벽 `Midnight`) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람이 부는 날 <br>그대가 날 떠난 날 <br>날 스쳐간 바람이 <br>모질게 널 데려가는데 <br>찬 바람이 불어와 <br>내 마음이 아려와 <br>그댈 데려오라고 <br>바람에게 속삭여 봐도 <br>하염없이 걷고 있다 <br>너와 이별한 그 날에 <br>천천히 걸으려 했는데 <br>바람이 자꾸만 자꾸만 밀어서 <br>좋은 사람 만나라고 <br>마음에도 없었던 아픈 말을 하고 <br>날 떠나지 말라고 말하고 싶은데 <br>불어오는 바람이 말문을 막아서 <br>바람이 부는 날 <br>그대가 날 떠난 날 <br>날 스쳐간 바람이 <br>모질게 널 데려가는데 <br>찬 바람이 불어와 <br>내 마음이 아려와 <br>그댈 데려오라고 <br>바람에게 속삭여 봐도 <br>찬 바람만 불어와 <br>바람은 멎었고 잔잔한 날인데 <br>이미 저 멀리 날아가 버린 너 <br>바람아 듣고 있다면 <br>다시 내 곁으로 불어와줘 <br>내 사랑 <br>바람이 부는 날 <br>내가 널 찾는 날 <br>날 스쳐간 바람이 <br>모질게 널 데려간대도 <br>바람이 불어와 <br>내 마음도 불어와 <br>널 찾아올 거야 <br>바람이 되어서라도 <br>바람이 부는 날 <br>]]></content><category term="보이스 메모리" label="보이스 메모리"/><category term="부는 날 (Ballad Ver.) (Feat. 새벽 `Midnight`)" label="부는 날 (Ballad Ver.) (Feat. 새벽 `Midnight`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_Jeronimo/Cabo_San_Juan/</id><title>San_Jeronimo - Cabo San Juan - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:21:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:21:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_Jeronimo/Cabo_San_Juan/" title="San_Jeronimo - Cabo San Juan - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cambiaremos de estacion <br>Como cambias de cancion <br>Cuando aun quieres bailar <br>pero se ha hecho tarde ya <br><br>Y en el kilometro diez <br>no vere los nidos que <br>tantas tardes dibuje <br>con tu cabeza en mis pies <br><br>No suena, el miedo <br>Es ciego y sincero <br>Te enviare una postal <br>cuando cruce San Juan]]></content><category term="San Jeronimo" label="San Jeronimo"/><category term="Cabo San Juan" label="Cabo San Juan"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_Jeronimo/Matadero/</id><title>San_Jeronimo - Matadero - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:21:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:21:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_Jeronimo/Matadero/" title="San_Jeronimo - Matadero - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Veintitres de abril, moja el roco <br>En el matadero de mi primo <br>Las cabezas ruedan al vaco <br>Masacre metal de doble filo <br><br>Piden tiempo <br>Mas]]></content><category term="San Jeronimo" label="San Jeronimo"/><category term="Matadero" label="Matadero"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_Jeronimo/Fue_Ayer/</id><title>San_Jeronimo - Fue Ayer - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:21:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:21:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_Jeronimo/Fue_Ayer/" title="San_Jeronimo - Fue Ayer - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hace sol en el pueblo de ayer <br>Res tu y ro yo sin querer <br>Era gris, aquel suelo era gris <br>Y pise tu vestido al salir <br><br>Sopla enero <br>¿volveras el proximo sabado <br>Hoy no hay sueo y la orquesta muere al amanecer]]></content><category term="San Jeronimo" label="San Jeronimo"/><category term="Fue Ayer" label="Fue Ayer"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_Jeronimo/Plaza_Pomposa/</id><title>San_Jeronimo - Plaza Pomposa - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:21:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:21:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_Jeronimo/Plaza_Pomposa/" title="San_Jeronimo - Plaza Pomposa - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A las tres, siesta en el mantel <br>Vuelvo a ver las horas caer <br><br>Y en tu mar, huele a piel <br>Helados en noviembre <br>Las piedras gritan que pronto va a acabar <br>Y el cielo grita quedate un da mas]]></content><category term="San Jeronimo" label="San Jeronimo"/><category term="Plaza Pomposa" label="Plaza Pomposa"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_Jeronimo/Piscinas/</id><title>San_Jeronimo - Piscinas - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:21:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:21:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_Jeronimo/Piscinas/" title="San_Jeronimo - Piscinas - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hay dudas en mi plato en noches de verano <br>Al lado de <br>Piscinas, vacas, sin vida <br><br>Es Castilla la que me ve crecer <br>Marcas en la pared <br>Suspira, vaca, sin vida]]></content><category term="San Jeronimo" label="San Jeronimo"/><category term="Piscinas" label="Piscinas"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_Jeronimo/Linea_Dos/</id><title>San_Jeronimo - Linea Dos - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:21:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:21:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_Jeronimo/Linea_Dos/" title="San_Jeronimo - Linea Dos - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Suda el reloj en el salon <br>Enredo all mis domingos <br><br>La lnea dos termina aqu <br>Es la hora de <br><br>Enredo all tardes sin ti]]></content><category term="San Jeronimo" label="San Jeronimo"/><category term="Linea Dos" label="Linea Dos"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_Jeronimo/Capitanes_Intrepidos/</id><title>San_Jeronimo - Capitanes Intrepidos - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:21:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:21:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/San_Jeronimo/Capitanes_Intrepidos/" title="San_Jeronimo - Capitanes Intrepidos - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sietante <br>Dime que no duele recorrer las calles otra vez <br>Descorcha el vino y ven]]></content><category term="San Jeronimo" label="San Jeronimo"/><category term="Capitanes Intrepidos" label="Capitanes Intrepidos"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Elephante/Troubled_Feat_Debs_Daughter/</id><title>Elephante - Troubled (Feat. Deb`s Daughter) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:21:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:21:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Elephante/Troubled_Feat_Debs_Daughter/" title="Elephante - Troubled (Feat. Deb`s Daughter) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I cross my heart 'cause it keeps me safe <br>It's to many sinners and not enough saints <br>And where I'm from people don't wear capes <br>No superhero's gonna save the day <br><br>And if these tears should fall and break some ground <br>May the sun come up and drag it out <br>'Cause the world's in need of love right now <br>It don't feel too sane, day by day <br><br>My heart is troubled troubled, troubled, troubled, troubled <br>My heart is troubled troubled, troubled, troubled, troubled <br>My heart is troubled troubled, troubled, troubled, troubled <br>My heart is troubled troubled, troubled, troubled <br><br>Day by day, my heart is <br>My heart is troubled troubled <br>My heart is <br>My heart is troubled <br><br>Love my town and I love my city <br>Am I a big cliche with a <br>If we wanna see change we gotta change our plans <br>Stop sittin' around and wasting time <br><br>And if these tears should fall and break some ground <br>May the sun come up and drag it out <br>'Cause the world's in need of love right now <br>It don't feel too sane, day by day <br><br>My heart is troubled troubled, troubled, troubled, troubled <br>My heart is troubled troubled, troubled, troubled, troubled <br>My heart is troubled troubled, troubled, troubled, troubled <br>My heart is troubled troubled, troubled, troubled <br><br>Day by day, my heart is <br>My heart is troubled troubled <br>My heart is <br>My heart is troubled <br><br>And if these tears should fall and break some ground <br>May the sun come up and drag it out <br>'Cause the world's in need of love right now <br>It don't feel too sane, day by day <br><br>My heart is troubled <br>Troubled <br>My heart is troubled <br>Troubled <br>My heart is troubled <br>Troubled <br>Troubled <br><br>Day by day, my heart is <br>Troubled, troubled, troubled, troubled <br>Troubled, troubled, troubled, troubled <br>My heart is troubled, troubled, troubled, troubled <br>Troubled, troubled, troubled <br><br>My heart is troubled]]></content><category term="Elephante" label="Elephante"/><category term="Troubled (Feat. Deb`s Daughter)" label="Troubled (Feat. Deb`s Daughter)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한기란/밤_Inst/</id><title>한기란 - 밤 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:22:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:22:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EA%B8%B0%EB%9E%80/%EB%B0%A4_Inst/" title="한기란 - 밤 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 밤도 잠 못 이루고 <br>애꿎은 시간만 보내다 <br>아침이 밝아 올 때까지 <br>너를 떠올리고 있다 <br>너는 나의 맘의 방 속에 <br>지치지도 않고선 매일 <br>아침이 밝아 올 때까지 <br>문을 두드리고 있다 <br>넌 이런 나를 알긴 하는지 <br>나만 혼자 이러고 있는 건지 <br>억울해서 밤에 잠도 안 오는 건지 <br>왜 나만 이렇게 속이 새까맣게 타 <br>들어 갈 때까지 <br>애태우고 있어야 하는지 몰라 <br>I can't get you out of my mind <br>I don't know am i out of my mind <br>Oh God <br>What did you do to me <br>너 내게 무슨 짓을 한 거야 <br>아무리 밀어내려 해도 <br>계속 그대로잖아 <br>이대로 계속 이러면 <br>오늘 밤도 잠은 못 잘 거야 <br>왜 나만 이렇게 속이 새까맣게 타 <br>들어 갈 때까지 <br>애태우고 있어야 하는지 몰라 <br>I can't get you out of my mind <br>I don't know am i out of my mind <br>Oh God <br>What did you do to me <br>오늘 밤도 잠 못 이루고 <br>애꿎은 시간만 보내다 <br>아침이 밝아 올 때까지 <br>너를 떠올리고 <br>]]></content><category term="한기란" label="한기란"/><category term="밤 (Inst.)" label="밤 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한기란/밤/</id><title>한기란 - 밤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:22:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:22:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EA%B8%B0%EB%9E%80/%EB%B0%A4/" title="한기란 - 밤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 밤도 잠 못 이루고 <br>애꿎은 시간만 보내다 <br>아침이 밝아 올 때까지 <br>너를 떠올리고 있다 <br>너는 나의 맘의 방 속에 <br>지치지도 않고선 매일 <br>아침이 밝아 올 때까지 <br>문을 두드리고 있다 <br>넌 이런 나를 알긴 하는지 <br>나만 혼자 이러고 있는 건지 <br>억울해서 밤에 잠도 안 오는 건지 <br>왜 나만 이렇게 속이 새까맣게 타 <br>들어 갈 때까지 <br>애태우고 있어야 하는지 몰라 <br>I can't get you out of my mind <br>I don't know am i out of my mind <br>Oh God <br>What did you do to me <br>너 내게 무슨 짓을 한 거야 <br>아무리 밀어내려 해도 <br>계속 그대로잖아 <br>이대로 계속 이러면 <br>오늘 밤도 잠은 못 잘 거야 <br>왜 나만 이렇게 속이 새까맣게 타 <br>들어 갈 때까지 <br>애태우고 있어야 하는지 몰라 <br>I can't get you out of my mind <br>I don't know am i out of my mind <br>Oh God <br>What did you do to me <br>오늘 밤도 잠 못 이루고 <br>애꿎은 시간만 보내다 <br>아침이 밝아 올 때까지 <br>너를 떠올리고 <br>]]></content><category term="한기란" label="한기란"/><category term="밤" label="밤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/열방에_외치세_Live_With_Grace_Hill_Worship/</id><title>김성배 - 열방에 외치세 Live (With Grace Hill Worship) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EC%97%B4%EB%B0%A9%EC%97%90_%EC%99%B8%EC%B9%98%EC%84%B8_Live_With_Grace_Hill_Worship/" title="김성배 - 열방에 외치세 Live (With Grace Hill Worship) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오직 성령이 임하면 <br>너희가 권능을 받고 <br>유대와 사마리아 땅 끝까지 <br>나의 증인 되리라 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>오직 성령이 임하면 <br>너희가 권능을 받고 <br>유대와 사마리아 땅 끝까지 <br>나의 증인 되리라 <br>내 주께 받은 사명 열방에 나아가 <br>예수 십자가 사랑을 전하리 <br>내 주께 받은 은혜 세상에 외치리 <br>예수 십자가 승리 선포하리 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="열방에 외치세 Live (With Grace Hill Worship)" label="열방에 외치세 Live (With Grace Hill Worship)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/지금은_엘리야_때처럼_Live_With_Grace_Hill_Worship/</id><title>김성배 - 지금은 엘리야 때처럼 Live (With Grace Hill Worship) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EC%A7%80%EA%B8%88%EC%9D%80_%EC%97%98%EB%A6%AC%EC%95%BC_%EB%95%8C%EC%B2%98%EB%9F%BC_Live_With_Grace_Hill_Worship/" title="김성배 - 지금은 엘리야 때처럼 Live (With Grace Hill Worship) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지금은 엘리야 때처럼 <br>주 말씀이 선포되고 <br>또 주의 종 모세의 때와 같이 <br>언약이 성취되네 <br>비록 전쟁과 기근과 핍박 <br>환난 날이 다가와도 <br>우리는 광야의 외치는 소리 <br>주의 길을 예비하라 <br>보라 주님 구름 타시고 <br>나팔 불 때에 다시 오시리 <br>모두 외치세 이는 은혜의 해니 <br>시온에서 구원이 임하네 <br>보라 주님 구름 타시고 <br>나팔 불 때에 다시 오시리 <br>모두 외치세 이는 은혜의 해니 <br>시온에서 구원이 임하네 <br>임하네 <br>에스겔의 환상처럼 <br>마른 뼈가 살아나며 <br>또 주의 종 다윗의 때와 같이 <br>예배가 회복되네 <br>추수할 때가 이르러 <br>들판은 희어졌네 <br>우리는 추수할 일꾼 되어 <br>주 말씀을 선포하리 <br>보라 주님 구름 타시고 <br>나팔 불 때에 다시 오시리 <br>모두 외치세 이는 은혜의 해니 <br>시온에서 구원이 임하네 <br>보라 주님 구름 타시고 <br>나팔 불 때에 다시 오시리 <br>모두 외치세 이는 은혜의 해니 <br>시온에서 구원이 임하네 <br>보라 주님 구름 타시고 <br>나팔 불 때에 다시 오시리 <br>모두 외치세 이는 은혜의 해니 <br>시온에서 구원이 임하네 <br>보라 주님 구름 타시고 <br>나팔 불 때에 다시 오시리 <br>모두 외치세 이는 은혜의 해니 <br>시온에서 구원이 임하네 <br>보라 주님 구름 타시고 <br>나팔 불 때에 다시 오시리 <br>모두 외치세 이는 은혜의 해니 <br>시온에서 구원이 임하네 <br>보라 주님 구름 타시고 <br>나팔 불 때에 다시 오시리 <br>모두 외치세 이는 은혜의 해니 <br>시온에서 구원이 임하네 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="지금은 엘리야 때처럼 Live (With Grace Hill Worship)" label="지금은 엘리야 때처럼 Live (With Grace Hill Worship)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/하나님의_나팔소리_Live_With_Grace_Hill_Worship/</id><title>김성배 - 하나님의 나팔소리 Live (With Grace Hill Worship) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%98_%EB%82%98%ED%8C%94%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC_Live_With_Grace_Hill_Worship/" title="김성배 - 하나님의 나팔소리 Live (With Grace Hill Worship) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나님의 나팔 소리 <br>천지 진동할 때에 <br>예수 영광 중에 구름 타시고 <br>천사들을 세계 만국 <br>모든 곳에 보내어 <br>구원받은 성도들을 모으리 <br>하나님의 나팔 소리 <br>천지 진동할 때에 <br>예수 영광 중에 구름 타시고 <br>천사들을 세계 만국 <br>모든 곳에 보내어 <br>구원받은 성도들을 모으리 <br>나팔 불 때 나의 이름 <br>나팔 불 때 나의 이름 <br>나팔 불 때 나의 이름 <br>부를 때에 잔치 참여 하겠네 <br>무덤 속에 잠자는 자 <br>그때 다시 일어나 <br>영화로운 부활 승리 얻으리 <br>주가 택한 모든 성도 <br>구름 타고 올라가 <br>공중에서 주의 얼굴 뵈오리 <br>나팔 불 때 나의 이름 <br>나팔 불 때 나의 이름 <br>나팔 불 때 나의 이름 <br>부를 때에 잔치 참여 하겠네 <br>나팔 불 때 나의 이름 <br>나팔 불 때 나의 이름 <br>나팔 불 때 나의 이름 <br>부를 때에 잔치 참여 하겠네 <br>다시 오실 날 알 수 없으니 <br>항상 기도하고 깨어 있어서 <br>주의 얼굴 마주하기까지 <br>우리 기다리겠네 <br>나팔 불 때 너의 이름 <br>나팔 불 때 너의 이름 <br>나팔 불 때 너의 이름 <br>부를 때에 잔치 참여 하겠네 <br>나팔 불 때 너의 이름 <br>나팔 불 때 너의 이름 <br>나팔 불 때 너의 이름 <br>부를 때에 잔치 참여 하겠네 <br>나팔 불 때 우리 이름 <br>나팔 불 때 우리 이름 <br>나팔 불 때 우리 이름 <br>부를 때에 잔치 참여 하겠네 <br>나팔 불 때 우리 이름 <br>나팔 불 때 우리 이름 <br>나팔 불 때 우리 이름 <br>그 때까지 우리 기다리겠네 <br>그 때까지 우리 기다리겠네 <br>그 때까지 우리 기다리겠네 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="하나님의 나팔소리 Live (With Grace Hill Worship)" label="하나님의 나팔소리 Live (With Grace Hill Worship)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/주_예수의_이름_높이세_Live_With_Grace_Hill_Worship/</id><title>김성배 - 주 예수의 이름 높이세 Live (With Grace Hill Worship) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EC%A3%BC_%EC%98%88%EC%88%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%9D%B4%EB%A6%84_%EB%86%92%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B8_Live_With_Grace_Hill_Worship/" title="김성배 - 주 예수의 이름 높이세 Live (With Grace Hill Worship) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수의 이름 높이세 <br>온 땅을 덮는 깃발처럼 <br>모든 사람 진리를 보며 <br>길 되신 주를 알리 <br>주 예수의 이름 높이세 <br>온 땅을 덮는 깃발처럼 <br>모든 사람 진리를 보며 <br>길 되신 주를 알리 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수의 이름 높이세 <br>온 땅을 덮는 깃발처럼 <br>모든 사람 진리를 보며 <br>길 되신 주를 알리 <br>주 예수의 이름 높이세 <br>온 땅을 덮는 깃발처럼 <br>모든 사람 진리를 보며 <br>길 되신 주를 알리 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>한 걸음씩 전진하며 <br>이 땅을 정복해가네 <br>기도로 무기 삼으면 <br>원수는 무너지리 <br>주 예수의 이름 높이세 <br>온 땅을 덮는 깃발처럼 <br>모든 사람 진리를 보며 <br>길 되신 주를 알리 <br>주 예수의 이름 높이세 <br>온 땅을 덮는 깃발처럼 <br>모든 사람 진리를 보며 <br>길 되신 주를 알리 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>한 걸음씩 전진하며 <br>이 땅을 정복해가네 <br>기도로 무기 삼으면 <br>원수는 무너지리 <br>원수는 무너지리 <br>원수는 무너지리 <br>원수는 무너지리 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>주 예수여 주 예수여 <br>높임을 받으시옵소서 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="주 예수의 이름 높이세 Live (With Grace Hill Worship)" label="주 예수의 이름 높이세 Live (With Grace Hill Worship)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/놀라운_이름_예수_Live_With_Grace_Hill_Worship/</id><title>김성배 - 놀라운 이름 예수 Live (With Grace Hill Worship) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EB%86%80%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4_%EC%9D%B4%EB%A6%84_%EC%98%88%EC%88%98_Live_With_Grace_Hill_Worship/" title="김성배 - 놀라운 이름 예수 Live (With Grace Hill Worship) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[예수 놀라운 생명의 이름 <br>예수 죽음을 이기신 이름 <br>예수 놀라운 생명의 이름 <br>예수 죽음을 이기신 이름 <br>예수 안에 권세 <br>모두 선포해 <br>예수 안에 승리 <br>모두 선포해 <br>온 민족과 열방 가운데 <br>그의 이름 높이 들리 <br>모두 나와 함께 경배하세 <br>그 이름 예수 <br>온 민족과 열방 가운데 <br>그의 이름 높이 들리 <br>모두 나와 함께 경배하세 <br>그 이름 예수 <br>예수 놀라운 생명의 이름 <br>예수 죽음을 이기신 이름 <br>예수 놀라운 생명의 이름 <br>예수 죽음을 이기신 이름 <br>예수 안에 권세 <br>모두 선포해 <br>예수 안에 승리 <br>모두 선포해 <br>온 민족과 열방 가운데 <br>그의 이름 높이 들리 <br>모두 나와 함께 경배하세 <br>그 이름 예수 <br>온 민족과 열방 가운데 <br>그의 이름 높이 들리 <br>모두 나와 함께 경배하세 <br>그 이름 예수 <br>예수 예수 예수 예수 <br>예수 예수 예수 예수 <br>예수 생명의 이름 <br>예수 놀라운 이름 <br>예수 죽음을 이기신 이름 <br>예수 생명의 이름 <br>예수 놀라운 이름 <br>예수 죽음을 이기신 이름 <br>예수 생명의 이름 <br>예수 놀라운 이름 <br>예수 죽음을 이기신 이름 <br>예수 생명의 이름 <br>예수 놀라운 이름 <br>예수 죽음을 이기신 이름 <br>예수 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="놀라운 이름 예수 Live (With Grace Hill Worship)" label="놀라운 이름 예수 Live (With Grace Hill Worship)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/우리_기쁨으로_Live_With_Grace_Hill_Worship/</id><title>김성배 - 우리 기쁨으로 Live (With Grace Hill Worship) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EA%B8%B0%EC%81%A8%EC%9C%BC%EB%A1%9C_Live_With_Grace_Hill_Worship/" title="김성배 - 우리 기쁨으로 Live (With Grace Hill Worship) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 기쁨으로 주 앞에 나아가 <br>주를 찬양 예배하네 <br>우리 기쁨으로 주 얼굴 구하며 <br>주의 영광 바라보네 <br>우리 기쁨으로 주 앞에 나아가 <br>주를 찬양 예배하네 <br>우리 기쁨으로 주 얼굴 구하며 <br>주의 영광 바라보네 <br>찬양의 제사 드리며 <br>감사의 제사 드리며 <br>기쁨의 찬양 향기 되어 주 앞에 <br>영원한 제사 드리네 <br>우리 기쁨으로 주 앞에 나아가 <br>주를 찬양 예배하네 <br>우리 기쁨으로 주 얼굴 구하며 <br>주의 영광 바라보네 <br>찬양의 제사 드리며 <br>감사의 제사 드리며 <br>기쁨의 찬양 향기 되어 주 앞에 <br>영원한 제사 드리네 <br>우리 기쁨으로 주 앞에 나아가 <br>주를 찬양 예배하네 <br>우리 기쁨으로 주 얼굴 구하며 <br>주의 영광 바라보네 <br>기뻐하라 찬양하라 <br>모두 소리 높여 <br>기뻐하라 찬양하라 <br>모두 소리 높여 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 <br>할렐루야 찬양 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 <br>할렐루야 찬양 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="우리 기쁨으로 Live (With Grace Hill Worship)" label="우리 기쁨으로 Live (With Grace Hill Worship)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/시편_5편_Feat_장지혜/</id><title>김성배 - 시편 5편 (Feat. 장지혜) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EC%8B%9C%ED%8E%B8_5%ED%8E%B8_Feat_%EC%9E%A5%EC%A7%80%ED%98%9C/" title="김성배 - 시편 5편 (Feat. 장지혜) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나의 왕 나의 하나님이여 <br>나의 부르짖음 응답하소서 <br>내가 주께 기도합니다 <br>나는 오직 주의 <br>풍성한 사랑을 인하여 <br>나는 오직 주의 <br>풍성한 사랑을 힘입어 <br>주의 집에 들어가 <br>주를 경외함으로 나아갑니다 <br>나의 왕 나의 하나님이여 <br>나의 부르짖음 응답하소서 <br>내가 주께 기도합니다 <br>나는 오직 주의 <br>풍성한 사랑을 인하여 <br>나는 오직 주의 <br>풍성한 사랑을 힘입어 <br>주의 집에 들어가 <br>주를 경외함으로 나아갑니다 <br>나는 오직 주의 <br>풍성한 사랑을 인하여 <br>나는 오직 주의 <br>풍성한 사랑을 힘입어 <br>주의 집에 들어가 <br>주를 경외함으로 나아갑니다 <br>주께 나아갑니다 <br>주께 나아갑니다 <br>주께 나아갑니다 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="시편 5편 (Feat. 장지혜)" label="시편 5편 (Feat. 장지혜)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/말씀에_붙잡혀/</id><title>김성배 - 말씀에 붙잡혀 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EB%A7%90%EC%94%80%EC%97%90_%EB%B6%99%EC%9E%A1%ED%98%80/" title="김성배 - 말씀에 붙잡혀 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[황무지에 홀로 피고 지는 <br>들꽃 같아도 <br>내가 너와 항상 함께 있으리니 <br>말씀에 붙잡혀 말씀에 붙잡혀 <br>말씀에 붙잡혀 새 힘을 받아 <br>다시 일어서라 <br>사막에 모래 같은 <br>대적들이 너를 둘러싸도 <br>아무도 너를 해치 못하리니 <br>말씀에 붙잡혀 말씀에 붙잡혀 <br>말씀에 붙잡혀 지혜를 얻어 <br>밝히 증언하라 <br>눈에 보이는 건 <br>저 무심한 철새뿐이어도 <br>너를 돕는 나의 백성 많으리니 <br>말씀에 붙잡혀 말씀에 붙잡혀 <br>말씀에 붙잡혀 환상을 보고 <br>말씀에 붙잡혀 말씀에 붙잡혀 <br>말씀에 붙잡혀 새 힘을 받아 <br>다시 일어서라 주와 동행하라 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="말씀에 붙잡혀" label="말씀에 붙잡혀"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/묵은_땅을_갈고/</id><title>김성배 - 묵은 땅을 갈고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EB%AC%B5%EC%9D%80_%EB%95%85%EC%9D%84_%EA%B0%88%EA%B3%A0/" title="김성배 - 묵은 땅을 갈고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그동안 나를 보호해주던 <br>껍질을 깨고 다시 날으려 하네 <br>지금껏 나를 지탱해주던 <br>기둥을 찍고 다시 세우려 하네 <br>더 온전하고 아름다운 <br>삶과 세상을 <br>열어주시는 그분만 따름이니 <br>새로 사는 길이 험하고 고달파도 <br>숨겨진 은총 꽃비처럼 내리고 <br>기쁨과 평강 숨결처럼 다가와 <br>주님 계시는 곳에 나 있기 원하네 <br>언제나 내가 기대어 살던 <br>언덕을 헐고 다시 일어서려네 <br>나의 묵은 땅 갈아엎고 <br>언제나 주께 속하기 원해 <br>더 온전하고 아름다운 <br>삶과 세상을 <br>열어주시는 그분만 따름이니 <br>새로 사는 길이 험하고 고달파도 <br>숨겨진 은총 꽃비처럼 내리고 <br>기쁨과 평강 숨결처럼 다가와 <br>주님 계시는 곳에 나 있기 원하네 <br>새로 사는 길이 험하고 고달파도 <br>숨겨진 은총 꽃비처럼 내리고 <br>기쁨과 평강 숨결처럼 다가와 <br>주님 계시는 곳에 나 있기 원하네 <br>원하네 원하네 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="묵은 땅을 갈고" label="묵은 땅을 갈고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/우리의_노래_Feat_안혜정_Branch_Band/</id><title>김성배 - 우리의 노래 (Feat. 안혜정, Branch Band) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EC%9D%98_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98_Feat_%EC%95%88%ED%98%9C%EC%A0%95_Branch_Band/" title="김성배 - 우리의 노래 (Feat. 안혜정, Branch Band) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나님 우리들 <br>하나되게 부르셨네 <br>우리 모습 서로 달라도 <br>함께 찬양하리 <br>하나님 우리들 <br>하나되게 부르셨네 <br>우리 모습 서로 달라도 <br>함께 찬양하리 <br>한 마음으로 주 이름 높일 때 <br>한 아버지 안에 하나 될 때에 <br>아름다운 화음 되어 울리리 <br>천사들도 놀라워 <br>함께 노래 부르게 되리 <br>이 기쁨의 노래는 주님이 주신 것 <br>이 믿음의 노래는 주님이 주신 것 <br>하나님 우리들 <br>하나되게 부르셨네 <br>우리 모습 서로 달라도 <br>함께 찬양하리 <br>한 마음으로 주 이름 높일 때 <br>한 아버지 안에 하나 될 때에 <br>아름다운 화음 되어 울리리 <br>천사들도 놀라워 <br>함께 노래 부르게 되리 <br>이 기쁨의 노래는 주님이 주신 것 <br>이 믿음의 노래는 주님이 주신 것 <br>이 소망의 노래는 주님이 주신 것 <br>이 사랑의 노래는 주님이 주신 것 <br>이 기쁨의 노래는 주님이 주신 것 <br>이 믿음의 노래는 주님이 주신 것 <br>이 소망의 노래는 주님이 주신 것 <br>이 사랑의 노래는 주님이 주신 것 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="우리의 노래 (Feat. 안혜정, Branch Band)" label="우리의 노래 (Feat. 안혜정, Branch Band)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/사랑은_Feat_이동희_이시온/</id><title>김성배 - 사랑은 (Feat. 이동희, 이시온) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%80_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%ED%9D%AC_%EC%9D%B4%EC%8B%9C%EC%98%A8/" title="김성배 - 사랑은 (Feat. 이동희, 이시온) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑은 언제나 오래참고 <br>사랑은 언제나 온유하며 <br>사랑은 시기하지 않으며 <br>자랑도 교만도 아니하네 <br>이것이 우리 주님 약속하신 <br>온전한 사랑이라 <br>사랑은 모든 것을 감싸주며 <br>바라고 믿고 참아내며 <br>사랑은 영원토록 변함없네 <br>믿음과 소망과 사랑 중에 <br>믿음과 소망과 사랑 중에 <br>그중에 제일은 사랑이라 <br>사랑은 무례히 행치 않고 <br>자기의 유익을 구하지 않고 <br>사랑은 성내지 아니하며 <br>진리와 함께 기뻐하네 <br>이것이 우리 주님 약속하신 <br>온전한 사랑이라 <br>사랑은 모든 것을 감싸주고 <br>바라고 믿고 참아내며 <br>사랑은 영원토록 변함없네 <br>믿음과 소망과 사랑 중에 <br>믿음과 소망과 사랑 중에 <br>그중에 제일은 사랑이라 <br>주님 우리에게 주신 모든 능력 <br>오직 주의 사랑가운데 행할 때 <br>완전케 되리 <br>사랑은 모든 것을 감싸주고 <br>바라고 믿고 참아내며 <br>사랑은 영원토록 변함없네 <br>믿음과 소망과 사랑 중에 <br>믿음과 소망과 사랑 중에 <br>그중에 제일은 사랑이라 <br>그중에 제일은 사랑이라 <br>그중에 제일은 사랑이라 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="사랑은 (Feat. 이동희, 이시온)" label="사랑은 (Feat. 이동희, 이시온)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/성령이_계시네_Feat_김성환/</id><title>김성배 - 성령이 계시네 (Feat. 김성환) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B3%84%EC%8B%9C%EB%84%A4_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%ED%99%98/" title="김성배 - 성령이 계시네 (Feat. 김성환) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 매일 기쁘게 <br>순례의 길 행함은 <br>주의 팔이 나를 안보함이요 <br>내가 주의 큰 복을 <br>받는 참된 비결은 <br>주의 영이 함께 함이라 <br>성령이 계시네 <br>할렐루야 함께 하시네 <br>성령이 계시네 <br>할렐루야 함께 하시네 <br>전에 죄에 빠져서 <br>평안함이 없을 때 <br>예수 십자가의 공로 힘입어 <br>그 발 아래 엎드려 <br>참된 평화 얻음은 <br>주의 영이 함께 함이라 <br>성령이 계시네 <br>할렐루야 함께 하시네 <br>성령이 계시네 <br>할렐루야 함께 하시네 <br>성령이 계시네 <br>할렐루야 함께 하시네 <br>성령이 계시네 <br>할렐루야 함께 하시네 <br>성령이 계시네 <br>성령안에서 노래하며 춤을춰 <br>성령이 계시네 <br>할렐루야 함께 하시네 <br>성령이 계시네 <br>할렐루야 함께 하시네 <br>성령의 강물 흘러 넘치네 <br>우리의 마음에 <br>우리의 영혼에 우리의 모든 삶에 <br>성령이 계시네 <br>할렐루야 함께 하시네 <br>성령이 계시네 <br>할렐루야 함께 하시네 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="성령이 계시네 (Feat. 김성환)" label="성령이 계시네 (Feat. 김성환)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/열방에_외치세_Feat_강찬/</id><title>김성배 - 열방에 외치세 (Feat. 강찬) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EC%97%B4%EB%B0%A9%EC%97%90_%EC%99%B8%EC%B9%98%EC%84%B8_Feat_%EA%B0%95%EC%B0%AC/" title="김성배 - 열방에 외치세 (Feat. 강찬) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오직 성령이 임하면 <br>너희가 권능을 받고 <br>유대와 사마리아 땅 끝까지 <br>나의 증인 되리라 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>오직 성령이 임하면 <br>너희가 권능을 받고 <br>유대와 사마리아 땅 끝까지 <br>나의 증인 되리라 <br>내 주께 받은 사명 열방에 나아가 <br>예수 십자가 사랑을 전하리 <br>내 주께 받은 은혜 세상에 외치리 <br>예수 십자가 승리 선포하리 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>열방에 외치세 열방에 외치세 <br>나와 내 교회는 외치리 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="열방에 외치세 (Feat. 강찬)" label="열방에 외치세 (Feat. 강찬)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/성령의_바람_불어와_Feat_정승복/</id><title>김성배 - 성령의 바람 불어와 (Feat. 정승복) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9%EC%9D%98_%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C_%EB%B6%88%EC%96%B4%EC%99%80_Feat_%EC%A0%95%EC%8A%B9%EB%B3%B5/" title="김성배 - 성령의 바람 불어와 (Feat. 정승복) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[성령의 바람 불어와 <br>죽었던 영혼 살리네 <br>생명의 근원 여호와 <br>죽었던 무덤 열리네 <br>마른뼈들 향해 대언하라 <br>생기야 사방에서 불어라 <br>마른뼈들 향해 대언하라 <br>생기야 사방에서 불어라 <br>오 하나님 온땅으로 <br>여호와 하나님 알게하소서 <br>오 하나님 온땅으로 <br>여호와 하나님 보게하소서 <br>성령의 바람 불어와 <br>죽었던 영혼 살리네 <br>생명의 근원 여호와 <br>죽었던 무덤 열리네 <br>마른뼈들 향해 대언하라 <br>생기야 사방에서 불어라 <br>마른뼈들 향해 대언하라 <br>생기야 사방에서 불어라 <br>오 하나님 온땅으로 <br>여호와 하나님 알게하소서 <br>오 하나님 온땅으로 <br>여호와 하나님 보게하소서 <br>마른뼈들 향해 대언하라 <br>생기야 사방에서 불어라 <br>마른뼈들 향해 대언하라 <br>생기야 사방에서 불어라 <br>오 하나님 온땅으로 <br>여호와 하나님 알게하소서 <br>오 하나님 온땅으로 <br>여호와 하나님 보게하소서 <br>오 하나님 열방으로 <br>여호와 하나님 예배케하소서 <br>오 하나님 열방으로 <br>여호와 하나님 선포케하소서 <br>오 하나님 온땅으로 <br>여호와 하나님 알게하소서 <br>오 하나님 온땅으로 <br>여호와 하나님 보게하소서 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="성령의 바람 불어와 (Feat. 정승복)" label="성령의 바람 불어와 (Feat. 정승복)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/오순절_그날_이르러_Feat_곽병훈/</id><title>김성배 - 오순절 그날 이르러 (Feat. 곽병훈) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EC%98%A4%EC%88%9C%EC%A0%88_%EA%B7%B8%EB%82%A0_%EC%9D%B4%EB%A5%B4%EB%9F%AC_Feat_%EA%B3%BD%EB%B3%91%ED%9B%88/" title="김성배 - 오순절 그날 이르러 (Feat. 곽병훈) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오순절 그날 이르러 <br>기다리니 기다리니 <br>약속하신 성령 오셨네 <br>새 언약 새 날 새 이스라엘 <br>시작됐네 시작됐네 <br>그 하신 약속 이루셨네 <br>하나님의 나라 하나님의 뜻 <br>이뤄지리 이뤄지리 <br>이 땅 위에 이뤄지리 <br>하나님의 나라 하나님의 뜻 <br>이뤄지리 이뤄지리 <br>이 땅 위에 이뤄지리라 <br>정결한 신부 주의 교회 <br>기다릴 때 기다릴 때 <br>약속하신 주님 오시리 <br>새 하늘 새 땅 새 예루살렘 <br>시작되리 시작되리 <br>그 하신 약속 이루시리 <br>하나님의 나라 하나님의 뜻 <br>이뤄지리 이뤄지리 <br>이 땅 위에 이뤄지리 <br>하나님의 나라 하나님의 뜻 <br>이뤄지리 이뤄지리 <br>이 땅 위에 이뤄지리라 <br>새 하늘 새 땅 <br>새 예루살렘 시작되리 <br>새 하늘 새 땅 <br>새 예루살렘 시작되리 <br>새 하늘 새 땅 <br>새 예루살렘 시작되리 <br>새 하늘 새 땅 <br>새 예루살렘 시작되리 <br>새 하늘 새 땅 <br>새 예루살렘 시작되리 <br>새 하늘 새 땅 <br>새 예루살렘 시작되리 <br>새 하늘 새 땅 <br>새 예루살렘 시작되리 <br>새 하늘 새 땅 <br>새 예루살렘 시작되리 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="오순절 그날 이르러 (Feat. 곽병훈)" label="오순절 그날 이르러 (Feat. 곽병훈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/약속하신_성령_Feat_진보라/</id><title>김성배 - 약속하신 성령 (Feat. 진보라) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EC%95%BD%EC%86%8D%ED%95%98%EC%8B%A0_%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9_Feat_%EC%A7%84%EB%B3%B4%EB%9D%BC/" title="김성배 - 약속하신 성령 (Feat. 진보라) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[약속하신 성령 하늘에서 임하여 <br>권능의 옷 입히시네 <br>약속하신 말씀 내 안에 이루어져 <br>생수의 강 넘쳐나네 <br>내 안과 밖 가득 채우소서 <br>내 안과 밖 가득 채우소서 <br>주의 권능 안에 살도록 <br>날 이끄소서 <br>오 주님 날 충만하게 하소서 <br>약속하신 성령 하늘에서 임하여 <br>권능의 옷 입히시네 <br>약속하신 말씀 내 안에 이루어져 <br>생수의 강 넘쳐나네 <br>내 안과 밖 가득 채우소서 <br>내 안과 밖 가득 채우소서 <br>주의 권능 안에 살도록 <br>날 이끄소서 <br>오 주님 날 충만하게 하소서 <br>내 안과 밖 가득 채우소서 <br>내 안과 밖 가득 채우소서 <br>주의 권능 안에 살도록 <br>날 이끄소서 <br>오 주님 날 충만하게 <br>내 안과 밖 가득 채우소서 <br>내 안과 밖 가득 채우소서 <br>내 안과 밖 가득 채우소서 <br>내 안과 밖 가득 채우소서 <br>주의 권능 안에 살도록 <br>날 이끄소서 <br>오 주님 날 충만하게 하소서 <br>내 안과 밖 가득 채우소서 <br>내 안과 밖 가득 채우소서 <br>주의 권능 안에 살도록 <br>날 이끄소서 <br>오 주님 날 충만하게 하소서 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="약속하신 성령 (Feat. 진보라)" label="약속하신 성령 (Feat. 진보라)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/흐르는_내_눈물_Feat_양아인/</id><title>김성배 - 흐르는 내 눈물 (Feat. 양아인) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%ED%9D%90%EB%A5%B4%EB%8A%94_%EB%82%B4_%EB%88%88%EB%AC%BC_Feat_%EC%96%91%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B8/" title="김성배 - 흐르는 내 눈물 (Feat. 양아인) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 모든 것 다 아시는 <br>좋으신 아바 아버지 <br>그 품 안에 내 모든 연약함 <br>다 품어주시네 날 안아주시네 <br>흐르는 내 눈물 닦아주시며 <br>참 좋은 친구라 말씀하시네 <br>답답한 내 마음 주께 나눌 때 <br>조용히 다가와 위로하시네 <br>깨어지고 상한 마음 <br>주님께 모두 드릴 때 <br>그의 사랑 내 안에 채우사 <br>다함 없는 은혜 내게 채우시네 <br>흐르는 내 눈물 닦아주시며 <br>참 좋은 친구라 말씀하시네 <br>답답한 내 마음 주께 나눌 때 <br>조용히 다가와 위로하시네 <br>흐르는 내 눈물 닦아주시며 <br>참 좋은 친구라 말씀하시네 <br>답답한 내 마음 주께 나눌 때 <br>조용히 다가와 위로하시네 <br>흐르는 내 눈물 닦아주시며 <br>참 좋은 친구라 말씀하시네 <br>답답한 내 마음 주께 나눌 때 <br>조용히 다가와 위로하시네 <br>조용히 다가와 위로하시네 <br>조용히 다가와 위로하시네 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="흐르는 내 눈물 (Feat. 양아인)" label="흐르는 내 눈물 (Feat. 양아인)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/열방의_아버지_Feat_정승복/</id><title>김성배 - 열방의 아버지 (Feat. 정승복) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EC%97%B4%EB%B0%A9%EC%9D%98_%EC%95%84%EB%B2%84%EC%A7%80_Feat_%EC%A0%95%EC%8A%B9%EB%B3%B5/" title="김성배 - 열방의 아버지 (Feat. 정승복) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[열방의 아버지 우리를 부르셨네 <br>하늘의 노래를 우리에게 주셨네 <br>온 땅이 주님 앞에 돌아오며 <br>주께서 행하신 일 찬양하네 <br>하나님 독생자 만유의 구세주 <br>주 보혈이 완전한 사랑 이루셨네 <br>하늘의 천사도 온 땅의 백성도 <br>그 크신 구원 소리 높여 찬양하라 <br>열방의 아버지 우리를 부르셨네 <br>하늘의 노래를 우리에게 주셨네 <br>온 땅이 주님 앞에 돌아오며 <br>주께서 행하신 일 찬양하네 <br>하나님 독생자 만유의 구세주 <br>주 보혈이 완전한 사랑 이루셨네 <br>하늘의 천사도 온 땅의 백성도 <br>그 크신 구원 소리 높여 찬양하라 <br>하나님 독생자 만유의 구세주 <br>주 보혈이 완전한 사랑 이루셨네 <br>하늘의 천사도 온 땅의 백성도 <br>그 크신 구원 소리 높여 찬양하라 <br>하나님 독생자 만유의 구세주 <br>주 보혈이 완전한 사랑 이루셨네 <br>하늘의 천사도 온 땅의 백성도 <br>그 크신 구원 소리 높여 찬양하라 <br>하나님 독생자 만유의 구세주 <br>주 보혈이 완전한 사랑 이루셨네 <br>하늘의 천사도 온 땅의 백성도 <br>그 크신 구원 소리 높여 찬양하라 <br>하나님 독생자 만유의 구세주 <br>주 보혈이 완전한 사랑 이루셨네 <br>하늘의 천사도 온 땅의 백성도 <br>그 크신 구원 소리 높여 찬양하라 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="열방의 아버지 (Feat. 정승복)" label="열방의 아버지 (Feat. 정승복)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/왕의_문_열렸으니_Feat_김성수/</id><title>김성배 - 왕의 문 열렸으니 (Feat. 김성수) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EC%99%95%EC%9D%98_%EB%AC%B8_%EC%97%B4%EB%A0%B8%EC%9C%BC%EB%8B%88_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EC%88%98/" title="김성배 - 왕의 문 열렸으니 (Feat. 김성수) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왕의 문 열렸으니 <br>모두 함께 들어가 <br>왕의 문 열렸으니 <br>모두 함께 들어가 <br>이 곳에 하늘의 보좌 <br>이 곳에 하늘의 영광 <br>이 곳에 하늘의 노래로 가득하네 <br>왕의 문 열렸으니 <br>모두 함께 들어가 <br>왕의 문 열렸으니 <br>모두 함께 들어가 <br>이 곳에 하늘의 보좌 <br>이 곳에 하늘의 영광 <br>이 곳에 하늘의 노래로 가득하네 <br>이 곳에 하늘의 보좌 <br>이 곳에 하늘의 영광 <br>이 곳에 하늘의 노래로 가득하네 <br>이 곳에 하늘의 보좌 <br>이 곳에 하늘의 영광 <br>이 곳에 하늘의 노래로 가득하네 <br>이 곳에 하늘의 보좌 <br>이 곳에 하늘의 영광 <br>이 곳에 하늘의 노래로 가득하네 <br>왕의 문 열렸으니 <br>모두 함께 들어가 <br>거룩 거룩 하신 주 <br>영원 영원 하신 주 <br>전지 전능 하신 주 <br>높고 위대 하신 주 <br>왕의 문 열렸으니 <br>모두 함께 들어가 <br>거룩 거룩 하신 주 <br>영원 영원 하신 주 <br>전지 전능 하신 주 <br>높고 위대 하신 주 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="왕의 문 열렸으니 (Feat. 김성수)" label="왕의 문 열렸으니 (Feat. 김성수)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/놀라우신_주_Feat_강찬/</id><title>김성배 - 놀라우신 주 (Feat. 강찬) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:23:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:23:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EB%86%80%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B0%EC%8B%A0_%EC%A3%BC_Feat_%EA%B0%95%EC%B0%AC/" title="김성배 - 놀라우신 주 (Feat. 강찬) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바다에 가장 깊은 곳 <br>산 위에 가장 높은 곳도 <br>하늘 위 저 우주도 <br>땅 위에 작은 티끌들도 <br>하나님 모두 만드셨네 <br>하나님 모두 지으셨네 <br>하나님 모두 다스리네 <br>가장 높으신 가장 위대하신 <br>모두 알 수 없고 모두 셀 수 없네 <br>오 놀라우신 주 <br>은혜 깊으신 측량할 수 없네 <br>모두 소리 높여 모두 찬양하세 <br>오 놀라우신 주 놀라우신 주 <br>바다에 가장 깊은 곳 <br>산 위에 가장 높은 곳도 <br>하나님 모두 만드셨네 <br>하나님 모두 지으셨네 <br>하나님 모두 다스리네 <br>가장 높으신 가장 위대하신 <br>모두 알 수 없고 모두 셀 수 없네 <br>오 놀라우신 주 <br>은혜 깊으신 측량할 수 없네 <br>모두 소리 높여 모두 찬양하세 <br>오 놀라우신 주 <br>가장 높으신 가장 위대하신 <br>모두 알 수 없고 모두 셀 수 없네 <br>오 놀라우신 주 <br>은혜 깊으신 측량할 수 없네 <br>모두 소리 높여 모두 찬양하세 <br>오 놀라우신 주 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="놀라우신 주 (Feat. 강찬)" label="놀라우신 주 (Feat. 강찬)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성배/내려놓음_Feat_진보라/</id><title>김성배 - 내려놓음 (Feat. 진보라) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:24:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:24:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%B0%B0/%EB%82%B4%EB%A0%A4%EB%86%93%EC%9D%8C_Feat_%EC%A7%84%EB%B3%B4%EB%9D%BC/" title="김성배 - 내려놓음 (Feat. 진보라) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 사랑했던 그 모든 것 <br>내가 붙잡고 있던 모든 것 <br>내가 포기할 수 없던 모든 것들을 <br>주님께 내려놓습니다 <br>끝없이 보이지 않는 소망과 <br>끝없는 의심과 두려움 <br>내 속에 깨어지기 쉬운 <br>연약함들을 <br>주님께 내어드립니다 <br>나를 먹이시고 나를 입히시니 <br>내겐 아무 걱정 없네 <br>나를 지으시고 내 이름 아시니 <br>내겐 두려움 전혀 없네 <br>내가 사랑했던 그 모든 것 <br>내가 붙잡고 있던 모든 것 <br>내가 포기할 수 없던 모든 것들을 <br>주님께 내려놓습니다 <br>나를 먹이시고 나를 입히시니 <br>내겐 아무 걱정 없네 <br>나를 지으시고 내 이름 아시니 <br>내겐 두려움 전혀 없네 <br>나를 먹이시고 나를 입히시니 <br>내겐 아무 걱정 없네 <br>나를 지으시고 내 이름 아시니 <br>내겐 두려움 전혀 없네 <br>내겐 두려움 전혀 없네 <br>내겐 두려움 전혀 없네 <br>]]></content><category term="김성배" label="김성배"/><category term="내려놓음 (Feat. 진보라)" label="내려놓음 (Feat. 진보라)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이진욱/잊고싶어요/</id><title>이진욱 - 잊고싶어요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:24:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:24:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%84%EC%9A%B1/%EC%9E%8A%EA%B3%A0%EC%8B%B6%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="이진욱 - 잊고싶어요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[님 없는 이 시간은 싫어요 <br>어떤 일 해도 우울해 <br>당신을 품에 안던 그 생각만 <br>머리에 박혀있어요 <br>당신을 만나던 그 시간은 <br>내 인생 전부였어요 <br>바람이 불어오던 추운 날도 <br>우린 늘 함께였는데 <br>그때를 생각하진 않겠지만 <br>날 사랑한 적 있잖아요 <br>나 지금 지난 날을 잊고 싶어요 <br>꺼져달란 말을 해줘요 <br>날 떠난 당신 잊고 살래요 <br>당신 생각 잊고 싶어요 <br>한번만이라도 다시 날 찾아와서 <br>꺼져달란 말 해줘요 <br>당신을 만나던 그 시간은 <br>내 인생 전부였어요 <br>바람이 불어오던 추운 날도 <br>우린 늘 함께였는데 <br>그때를 생각하진 않겠지만 <br>날 사랑한 적 있잖아요 <br>나 지금 지난 날을 잊고 싶어요 <br>꺼져달란 말을 해줘요 <br>날 떠난 당신 잊고 살래요 <br>당신 생각 잊고 싶어요 <br>한번만이라도 다시 날 찾아와서 <br>꺼져달란 말 해줘요 <br>한번만이라도 다시 날 찾아와서 <br>꺼져달란 말 해줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="이진욱" label="이진욱"/><category term="잊고싶어요" label="잊고싶어요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/넌_내게_반했어/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 넌 내게 반했어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EB%84%8C_%EB%82%B4%EA%B2%8C_%EB%B0%98%ED%96%88%EC%96%B4/" title="발라드_공장 - 넌 내게 반했어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One two One two three yeah <br>워우 워우 워 워 워어어 <br><br>(넌 내게 반했어)화려한 조명속에 빛나고 있는 <br>(넌 내게 반했어)웃지 말고 대답해봐 <br>(넌 내게 반했어)뜨거운 토요일밤의 열기속에 <br>(넌 내게 반했어)솔직하게 말을 해봐 <br><br>도도한 눈빛으로 제압하려 해도 <br>난 그런 속임수에 속지 않어 예예 <br>워우 워우 워 워 워어어 <br><br>(넌 내게 반했어)애매한 그눈빛은 뭘 말하는거니 <br>(넌 내게 반했어)춤을 춰줘 come on come on <br>(넌 내게 반했어)내눈과 너의 눈이마주쳤던 순간 <br>(넌 내게 반했어)튀었던 정열의 불꽃들 <br><br>oh stand by me stand by me stand by me <br>원한다면 밤하늘의 별도 따줄텐데 <br>oh stand by me stand by me stand by me <br>내 볼에다 입맞춰줘 오우예 <br><br>oh stand by me stand by me stand by me <br>원한다면 밤하늘의 별도 따줄텐데 <br>oh stand by me stand by me stand by me <br>내 볼에다 입맞춰줘 오우예 <br><br>워우 워우 워 워 워어어 <br><br>(넌 내게 반했어 넌 내게 반했어 넌 내게 반했어 <br>넌 내게 반했어 넌 내게 반했어 넌 내게 반했어 <br>넌 내게 반했어 넌 내게 반했어 넌 내게 반했어 <br>넌 내게 반했어 넌 내게 반했어 넌 내게 반했어 <br>넌 내게 반했어 넌 내게 반했어 넌 내게 반했어 넌 내게) <br>반했어~]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="넌 내게 반했어" label="넌 내게 반했어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/너를_보내고/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 너를 보내고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC_%EB%B3%B4%EB%82%B4%EA%B3%A0/" title="발라드_공장 - 너를 보내고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[구름낀 하늘은 왠지 니가 살고 있는 나라일 것 같아서 <br>창문들 마저도 닫지 못하고 하루종일 서성이며 있었지 <br>삶의 작은 문턱 조차 쉽사리 넘지 못했던 너에게 나는 <br>무슨 말이 하고 파서 였을까 <br><br>먼산 언저리마다 너를 남기고 돌아서는 <br>내게 시간은 그만 놓아주라는데 <br>난 왜 너 닮은 목소리마저 <br>가슴에 품고도 같이 가자 하지 못했나 <br><br>길 잃은 작은 새 한마리가 하늘 향해 그리움 외칠 때 <br>같이 놀던 어린 나무 한 그루 혼자 남게 되는게 싫었지 <br>해 저가는 넓은 들판 위에서 차가운 바람불어도 <br>들려오던 노래 내 곁에 없었지 <br><br>먼산 언저리마다 너를 남기고 돌아서는 <br>내게 시간은 그만 놓아주라는데 <br>난 왜 너 닮은 목소리마저 <br>가슴에 품고도 같이가자 하지 못했나 아 <br><br>먼산 언저리마다 너를 남기고 돌아서는 <br>내게 시간은 그만 놓아주라는데 <br>난 왜 너 닮은 목소리마저 <br>가슴에 품고도 같이가자 하지 못했나]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="너를 보내고" label="너를 보내고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/사고쳤어요/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 사고쳤어요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%82%AC%EA%B3%A0%EC%B3%A4%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="발라드_공장 - 사고쳤어요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[말해버렸어 사랑한단말 그만 고백해버렸어 <br>너의 뒤에서 사랑한단말 그만 입밖에 내버렸어 <br><br>영원히 내마음 숨기려고 했는데 <br>나홀로 사랑은 너무아파 <br>혼자서 꿈꾸고 바라고 바라보고 <br>그건 너무 힘든데 <br><br>어쩌지 내 가슴이 이렇게 결국 사고를 치나봐 <br>사랑은 안돼 난 안돼 아무리 막아서 봐도 <br>아플 줄 알면서도 또 대책없이 사고를 치나봐 <br>어느새 널 향해 내 가슴이 사랑을 저질러 버렸나봐 <br><br>다시는 사랑은 안하려고 했는데 <br>뒤에 올 상처가 너무아파 <br>누군갈 원하고 그리고 기다리고 <br>그건 너무 힘든데 <br><br>어쩌지 내가슴이 이렇게 결국 사고를 치나봐 <br>사랑은 안돼 난 안돼 아무리 막아서 봐도 <br>아플 줄 알면서도 또 대책 없이 사고를 치나봐 <br>어느새 널 향해 내 가슴이 사랑을 저질러 버렸나봐 <br><br>자꾸만 겁이나 너무 아파 질까봐 <br>이젠 다시 쓸 수도 없게 <br>가슴이 깨어지고 부서질까봐 <br><br>어쩌지 내눈물이 또 눈치없이 말썽을 피나봐 <br>울기는 싫어 다 싫어 아무리 참아 내봐도 <br>널 데려 와 달라고 보고싶다고 말썽을 피나봐 <br>내게는 단한번 눈길조차 안주는 너인줄도 모르고]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="사고쳤어요" label="사고쳤어요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/사랑해도_될까요/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 사랑해도 될까요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4%EB%8F%84_%EB%90%A0%EA%B9%8C%EC%9A%94/" title="발라드_공장 - 사랑해도 될까요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[문이 열리네요 그대가 들어오죠 <br>첫 눈에 난 내 사람인걸 알았죠 <br>내 앞에 다가와 고갤 숙이며 비친 얼굴 <br>정말 눈이 부시게 아름답죠 <br><br>웬일인지 낯설지가 않아요 <br>설레고 있죠 내 맘을 모두 가져간 그대 <br><br>조심스럽게 얘기할래요 용기내 볼래요 <br>나 오늘부터 그대를 사랑해도 될까요 <br><br>처음인걸요 분명한 느낌 놓치고 싶지 않죠 <br>사랑이 오려나봐요 그대에겐 늘 좋은것만 줄께요 <br><br>웬일인지 낯설지가 않아요 <br>설레고 있죠 내 맘을 모두 가져간 그대 <br><br>참 많은 이별 참 많은 눈물 잘 견뎌냈기에 <br>좀 늦었지만 그대를 만나게 됐나봐요 <br><br>지금 내 앞에 앉은 사람을 사랑해도 될까요 <br>두근거리는 맘으로 그대에게 고백할께요 <br><br>조심스럽게 얘기할래요 용기 내볼래요 <br>나 오늘부터 그대를 사랑해도 될까요 <br><br>처음인걸요 이 느낌 놓치고 싶지 않죠 <br>사랑이 오려나봐요 그대에겐 늘 좋은것만 줄께요 <br><br>내가 그대를 사랑해도 될까요]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="사랑해도 될까요" label="사랑해도 될까요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/Please/</id><title>발라드_공장 - Please - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/Please/" title="발라드_공장 - Please - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[제발 나를 보아요 <br>고개 들어 웃음을 보여요 그대여 <br>슬픔을 보이면 보낼 수 없잖아 <br>웃으며 나를 떠나가줘요 <br><br>왜 이제야 떠나는 거냐고 <br>원망하며 붙잡지 않을게 그대여 <br>날 잊어버리고 행복할 수 있게 <br>나 먼저 그대를 돌아설게 <br><br>잊지 못할 것 같아 <br>하지만 그대 지워야만 해 이젠 <br>그대를 위한 선택이야 <br>정말 사랑했다면 <br>나보다 좋은 사람 만나기를 바래 <br>못다한 사랑을 위해 <br><br>미안하다 말하지 말아요 <br>함께 했던 수많은 추억도 버리고 <br>우연히 만나도 모르는 것처럼 <br>나 먼저 그대를 외면할게 <br><br>잊지 못할 것 같아 <br>하지만 그대 지워야만 해 이젠 <br>그대를 위한 선택이야 <br>정말 사랑했다면 <br>나보다 좋은 사람 만나기를 바래 <br>못다한 사랑을 위해 <br>내 마지막 바램이야]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="Please" label="Please"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/마리아/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 마리아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EB%A7%88%EB%A6%AC%EC%95%84/" title="발라드_공장 - 마리아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자 지금 시작해 조금씩 뜨겁게 <br>우~ 두려워하지마 <br>펼쳐진 눈앞에 저 태양이 길을 비춰 <br>우~절대 멈추지마 <br><br>마리아 아베마리아 <br>저 흰구름 끝까지 날아 <br>마리아 아베마리아 <br>거친파도따윈 상관없이 <br><br>기적은 이렇게 눈앞에 니 앞에 펼쳐잇어 <br>우~절대멈추지마 <br><br>마리아 아베마리아 <br>저 흰구름 끝까지 날아 <br>마리아 아베마리아 <br>거친 파도 따윈 상관없이 <br><br>마리아 <br><br>멈춰버린 심장전체가 <br>겉잡을 수 없이 뛰어와 <br><br>마리아 아베마리아 <br>저 흰구름 끝까지 날아 <br>마리아 아베마리아 <br>거친 파도 따윈 상관없이 <br><br>마리아 아베마이라 <br>저 흰구름 끝까지 날아 <br>마리아 아베마리아 <br>거친 파도 따윈 상관없이]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="마리아" label="마리아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/My_Love/</id><title>발라드_공장 - My Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/My_Love/" title="발라드_공장 - My Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ <br>사랑해 그 말은 무엇보다 아픈 말 <br>숨죽여서 하는 말 이젠 하기 힘든 말 <br>Oh 햇살이 밝은 아침보다 밤의 달빛이 어울려요 <br>이별의 그 입맞춤 잠시 접어둔채 이대로 이렇게 <br><br>힘껏 안아줄게 널 그리고 말할게 <br>나 이렇게 너를 외치면서 My Love <br>넌 보지 못할 내 마지막 눈물 <br><br>힘껏 안아줄게 널 그리고 보낼게 <br>나 또 한번 너를 외치면서 My Love <br>넌 듣지 못할 사랑한단 내 말 <br><br>괜찮아 그 말은 안쓰러운 거짓말 <br>애쓰면서 웃어도 우린 그저 눈물만 <br><br>Oh 햇살이 밝은 아침보다 밤의 달빛이 어울려요 <br>이별의 그 입맞춤 잠시 접어둔채 이대로 이렇게 <br><br>힘껏 안아줄게 널 그리고 말할게 <br>나 이렇게 너를 외치면서 My Love <br>넌 보지 못할 내 마지막 눈물 <br><br>힘껏 안아줄게 널 그리고 보낼게 <br>나 또 한번 너를 외치면서 My Love <br>넌 듣지 못할 사랑한단 내 말 <br><br>(나 이렇게 너를 외치)면서 My Love <br>넌 보지 못할 내 마지막 눈물 <br>(나 이렇게 너를 외치)면서 My Love <br>넌 듣지 못할 사랑한단 내 말 My Love]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="My Love" label="My Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/화장을_고치고/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 화장을 고치고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%ED%99%94%EC%9E%A5%EC%9D%84_%EA%B3%A0%EC%B9%98%EA%B3%A0/" title="발라드_공장 - 화장을 고치고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우연히 날 찾아와 사랑만 남기고 간 너 <br>하루가 지나 몇해가 흘러도 아무 소식도 없는데 <br>세월에 변해버린 날 보며 실망할까봐 <br>오늘도 나는 설레이는 맘으로 화장을 다시 고치곤해 <br><br>아무것도 난 해준게 없어 <br>받기만 했을뿐 그래서 미안해 <br>나같은 여자를 왜 사랑했는지 <br>왜 떠나야 했는지 <br>어떻게든 우리 다시 사랑해야해 <br><br>살다가 널 만나면 모질게 따지고 싶어 <br>힘든 세상에 나홀로 남겨두고 왜 연락한번 없었느냐고 <br><br>아무것도 난 해준게 없어 <br>받기만 했을뿐 그래서 미안해 <br>나같은 여자를 왜 사랑했는지 <br>왜 떠나야 했는지 <br>어떻게든 우리 다시 사랑해야해 <br><br>그땐 너무 어려서 몰랐던 사랑을 <br>이제야 알겠어 보잘 것 없지만 <br>널위해 남겨둔 내 사랑을 받아줘 <br>어떻게든 우린 다시 사랑해야해]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="화장을 고치고" label="화장을 고치고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/정신이_나갔었나봐/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 정신이 나갔었나봐 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%A0%95%EC%8B%A0%EC%9D%B4_%EB%82%98%EA%B0%94%EC%97%88%EB%82%98%EB%B4%90/" title="발라드_공장 - 정신이 나갔었나봐 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[정신이 나갔었나봐 그땐 내가 어떻게 너를 떠나가 <br>너만을 사랑해 정말 미안해 눈물만 흘러내려 <br>정신이 나갔었나봐 그땐 내가 어떻게 너를 떠나가 <br>너무나 보고파 네가 보고파 제발 날 용서해줘 <br>정신이 나갔었나봐 <br><br>후회해도 이미 늦었다는걸 알아 슬퍼해도 이젠 모두 소용없단 걸 <br>바람이 불어오고 내 맘이 시려 와도 널 다시는 볼 수 없니 <br>baby 나를 떠나가지마 oh baby 나는 너 하나뿐야 <br>그대여 돌아와 날 꽉 안아줘 너 없인 견딜 수 없어 <br><br>정신이 나갔었나봐 그땐 내가 어떻게 너를 떠나가 <br>너만을 사랑해 정말 미안해 눈물만 흘러내려 <br>정신이 나갔었나봐 그땐 내가 어떻게 너를 떠나가 <br>너무나 보고파 네가 보고파 제발 날 용서해줘 <br>정신이 나갔었나봐 <br><br>사랑한단 말을 못했어 미안해서 고맙다는 말도 못했어 떠날까봐 <br>come back to me my girl my girl 오늘밤 너 땜에 잠 못 이루고 <br>baby 나를 떠나가지마 oh baby 나는 너 하나뿐야 <br>그대여 돌아와 날 꽉 안아줘 너 없인 견딜 수 없어 <br><br>정신이 나갔었나봐 그땐 내가 어떻게 너를 떠나가 <br>너만을 사랑해 정말 미안해 눈물만 흘러내려 <br>정신이 나갔었나봐 그땐 내가 어떻게 너를 떠나가 <br>너무나 보고파 니가 보고파 제발 날 용서해줘 <br>정신이 나갔었나봐 <br><br>살며시 안아주고 싶어 살며시 입 맞추고 싶어 <br>그대의 품에서 나 잠들고 싶어 Yeah yeah yeah <br>스뚭뚭뚭따다 <br>스뚭뚭뚭따다 <br><br>그땐 정말로 정신이 나갔었나봐]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="정신이 나갔었나봐" label="정신이 나갔었나봐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/아름다운_구속/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 아름다운 구속 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%95%84%EB%A6%84%EB%8B%A4%EC%9A%B4_%EA%B5%AC%EC%86%8D/" title="발라드_공장 - 아름다운 구속 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 하루 행복하길 <br>언제나 아침에 눈 뜨면 기도를 하게 돼 <br>달아날까 두려운 행복 앞에 <br><br>널 만난건 행운이야 <br>휴일에 해야 할 일들이 내게도 생겼어 <br>약속하고 만나고 헤어지고 <br><br>조금씩 집 앞에서 널 들여 보내기가 힘겨워지는 나를 어떡해 <br>처음이야 내가 드디어 내가 사랑에 난 빠져 버렸어 <br>혼자인게 좋아 나를 사랑했던 나에게 또다른 내가 온 거야 <br><br>아름다운 구속인걸 <br>사랑은 얼마나 사람을 변하게 하는지 <br>살아있는 오늘이 아름다워 <br><br>조금씩 집 앞에서 널 들여 보내기가 힘겨워지는 나를 어떡해 <br>처음이야 내가 드디어 내가 사랑에 난 빠져 버렸어 <br>혼자인게 좋아 나를 사랑했던 나에게 또다른 내가 또다른 내가 된거야 <br><br>처음이야 내가 드디어 내가 사랑에 난 빠져버렸어 <br>혼자인게 좋아 나를 사랑했던 나에게 또다른 내가 온거야 <br><br>내앞에 니가 온거야]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="아름다운 구속" label="아름다운 구속"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/눈물잔/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 눈물잔 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EB%88%88%EB%AC%BC%EC%9E%94/" title="발라드_공장 - 눈물잔 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나처럼 말하고 나처럼 웃네요 <br>그댄 나를 너무 많이 닮았죠 <br>말하지 않아도 마음을 읽네요 <br>그런 그댈 이제 내가 떠나죠 <br><br>내가 그대에게 미안할까봐 <br>가는 이유조차 묻질 않네요 <br>내가 사랑한 사람 <br>나보다 더 나를 잘 알죠 <br><br>그대 없으면 나는 무너지겠지만 <br>너무 보고 싶겠지만 슬프지 않아요 <br>힘들 때마다 눈물로 잔을 채울때마다 <br>얼마만큼 사랑했는지 기억할테니까 <br><br>나처럼 가깝고 나처럼 편해서 <br>가끔씩은 그댈 잊고 살아도 <br>밤이면 길어진 내 그림자처럼 <br>변함없이 나의 뒤에 있었죠 <br><br>아무것도 잘해 준 것 없는데 <br>결국 눈물밖에 준 것 없는데 <br>내가 사랑한 사람 <br>바보처럼 날 따라왔죠 <br><br>그대 없으면 나는 무너지겠지만 <br>너무 보고 싶겠지만 슬프지 않아요 <br>힘들때마다 눈물로 잔을 채울때마다 <br>얼마만큼 사랑했는지 기억할테니까 <br><br>마지막으로 부탁 하나만 해도 될까요 <br>다른 사람 만나게 되면 천천히 닮아요]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="눈물잔" label="눈물잔"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/이별이_오지_못하게/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 이별이 오지 못하게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84%EC%9D%B4_%EC%98%A4%EC%A7%80_%EB%AA%BB%ED%95%98%EA%B2%8C/" title="발라드_공장 - 이별이 오지 못하게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[정말날 사랑하나요 그래요 그거면 되요 <br>너무 많은걸 바래서 마음이 아프나 봐요 <br>슬픔이 우릴찾아도 나를떠나면 안돼요 <br>이미 시작된사랑을 어떻게 보내야 하는지 <br>나는 잘 모르니까요 <br><br>이별이 오지 못하게 하늘에 기도 할까요 <br>서로만 사랑하도록 이대로만 <br>어디든 가지 못하게 깊숙히 숨겨둘까요 <br>우리사랑 이대로만 <br><br><br>그대를 만나기전에 난 어디에 있었는지 <br>그대 만났던 그날 난 다시 태어났던거죠 <br>그대밖에 난 몰라요 오~~~우~~~ <br><br>이별이 오지 못하게 하늘에 기도할까요 <br>서로만 사랑하도록 이대로만 <br>어디든 가지 못하게 깊숙히 숨겨둘까요 <br>우리사랑 아~ <br><br>우~~~아~~~~~ 눈가려도 보이니까 그대만 보면되니까 <br>두 눈을 감고 살까요 그럴까~요 <br>그댄 잊으면 안돼요 <br>그대만 있으면 되요 <br>그러면 난 행복해요]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="이별이 오지 못하게" label="이별이 오지 못하게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/걸음이_느린_아이/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 걸음이 느린 아이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EA%B1%B8%EC%9D%8C%EC%9D%B4_%EB%8A%90%EB%A6%B0_%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4/" title="발라드_공장 - 걸음이 느린 아이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[함께 걸으면 손닿지 못할만큼 한참을 뒤에 오던 그녀였죠 <br>빨리 오라며 그녀를 다그치고 답답한 마음에 난 앞서서 걸었는데 <br><br>천천히 걸을걸 그랬죠 먼저간 날 잃었었는지 <br>그녀가 오질 않네요 <br><br>하루를 헤매다 돌아온 그녀는 <br>어제보다 많이 다른 모습이죠 <br>날 보며 웃는 미소도 <br>그 향기도 모두 예전과 같은데 <br>낯설은 그대 모습 <br><br>사소한 일로 많이 다툰 날이었죠 평소완 다른 그녀 모습보고 <br>먼저 다가가 그녈 달래봤지만 내말도 들으려 않은채 울고있죠 <br><br>사랑하는 사람있다고 허락해 줄수만 있다면 <br>그 사랑 안고 싶다고 <br><br>고개를 저으면 그저 난 저으면 <br>예전처럼 다시 만날수 있나요 <br>조금 더 함께 하고파 <br>그렇게도 천천히 걷던 그녀를 <br>알지못한 내 죄로 보내야 하나요 <br><br>그대 혼자서 나를 남겨둔채 가는건 <br>여린 그대가 참 힘든일이라 <br>나 그대 따라서 이별이란 <br>슬픈 세상에 나도 함께 갈께요 <br><br>고개를 저으면 그저 난 저으면 <br>예전처럼 다시 만날 수 있나요 <br>조금 더 함께 하고파 <br>그렇게도 천천히 걷던 그녀를 <br>난 보내야만 하죠]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="걸음이 느린 아이" label="걸음이 느린 아이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/울컥/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 울컥 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%9A%B8%EC%BB%A5/" title="발라드_공장 - 울컥 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈물이 눈물이 차올라서 떠나간 니가 또 미워져서 <br>우는데 오늘도 니가 미워 우는데 <br>삼켜도 삼켜도 주르르륵 화장은 눈물로 번져가고 <br>어떡하란말야 끝난거잖아 <br><br>조금 더 울다가 지쳐서 잠들면 잊을까 <br>니 기억 모두 지워본다 지워본다 <br>넌 그대로잖아 한걸음 떼기가 힘들어 <br>내사랑 이별에 무너져 두팔로 막아서지만 <br>오 어떻게 너를 데리고 가면 이제 난 어떡해 <br><br>아파도 아파도 괜찮다고 이별이 뭐 그리 대수냐고 <br>웃는데 사랑이 지겨워서 웃는데 <br>모른체 모른체 살다가도 취한밤 니가 또 생각나고 <br>이제 너의 품에 쉴 수 없는데 <br><br>조금 더 울다가 지쳐서 잠들면 잊을까 <br>니 기억 모두 지워본다 지워본다 <br>넌 그대로 잖아 한걸음 떼기가 힘들어 <br>내사랑 이별에 무너져 두팔로 막아서지만 <br>오 어떻게 너를 데리고 가면 이제 난 어떡해 <br><br>내게로 돌아와 날 안아 준다면 한번만 <br>주문을 걸어 돌아온다 돌아온다 <br>넌 멀리 있잖아 쓰러져 가는 날 지켜줘 <br>죽도록 그리워 바람아 내 사랑 데려다 줄래 <br>오 한번만 정말 못잊을 사람 내게로 돌아와]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="울컥" label="울컥"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/나는_나비/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 나는 나비 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84/" title="발라드_공장 - 나는 나비 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 모습이 보이지 않아 앞길도 보이지 않아 <br>나는 아주 작은 애벌레 <br>살이 터져 허물 벗어 한 번 두 번 다시 <br>나는 상처 많은 번데기 <br><br>추운 겨울이 다가와 힘겨울지도 몰라 <br>봄바람이 불어오면 이제 나의 꿈을 찾아 날아 <br><br>날개를 활짝 펴고 세상을 자유롭게 날거야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 나는 아름다운 나비 <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 세상을 자유롭게 날거야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 나는 아름다운 나비 <br>워우워 우~ 워우워 우~ <br><br>거미줄을 피해 날아 꽃을 찾아 날아 <br>사마귀를 피해 날아 꽃을 찾아 날아 <br>꽃들의 사랑을 전하는 나비 <br><br>날개를 활짝 펴고 세상을 자유롭게 날거야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 나는 아름다운 나비 <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 세상을 자유롭게 날거야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 나는 아름다운 나비 <br><br>날개를 활짝 펴고 세상을 자유롭게 날거야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 나는 아름다운 나비 <br>워우워 우~ 워우워 우~ <br>워우워 우~ 워우워 우~]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="나는 나비" label="나는 나비"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/총맞은것처럼/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 총맞은것처럼 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%B4%9D%EB%A7%9E%EC%9D%80%EA%B2%83%EC%B2%98%EB%9F%BC/" title="발라드_공장 - 총맞은것처럼 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[총맞은것처럼 정신이 너무 없어 <br><br>웃음만 나와서 그냥 웃었어 그냥 웃었어 그냥 <br><br>허탈하게 웃으며 하나만 묻자 했어 <br><br>우리 왜헤어져 어떻게 헤어져 어떻게 헤어져 어떻게 <br><br>구멍난 가슴에 우리 추억이 흘러 넘쳐 <br>잡아보려해도 가슴을 막아도 손가락 사이로 빠져나가 <br><br>심장이 멈춰도 이렇게 아플거 같진 않아 <br>어떻게 좀 해줘 날 좀 치료해줘 <br>이러다 내 가슴 다 망가져 구멍난 가슴이 <br><br>어느새 눈물이 나도 모르게 흘러 <br>이러기 싫은데 정말 싫은데 정말 싫은데 정말 <br><br>일어서는 널 따라 무작정 쫓아갔어 <br>도망치듯 걷는 너의 뒤에서 너의 뒤에서 소리쳤어 <br><br>구멍난 가슴에 우리 추억이 흘러 넘쳐 <br>잡아보려해도 가슴을 막아도 손가락 사이로 빠져나가 <br><br>심장이 멈춰도 이렇게 아플거 같진 않아 <br>어떻게 좀 해줘 날 좀 치료해줘 이러다 내 가슴 다 망가져 <br><br>총맞은 것처럼 정말 가슴이 너무 아파 <br><br>이렇게 아픈데 이렇게 아픈데 살 수가 있다는 게 이상해 <br><br>어떻게 너를 잊어 내가 그런거 나는 몰라 몰라 <br>가슴이 뻥 뚫려 채울 수 없어서 죽을만큼 아프기만 해 <br><br>총맞은것처럼]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="총맞은것처럼" label="총맞은것처럼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/One_Love/</id><title>발라드_공장 - One Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/One_Love/" title="발라드_공장 - One Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이젠 내가 돌아서려 해 <br>다신 그 사람과 니 앞에서 보이지 않게 <br>이젠 너에겐 어떤 바램도 <br>작은 기대조차 할 수 없는 나잖아 <br><br>하지만 시간이 많이 지난 후에도 <br>나의 숨결 나의 향기 네게 묻어있다면 <br>언제나 힘들던 이룰 수 없던 사랑 <br>너에게도 너무 큰 아픔이었다면 <br><br>다시 내게 돌아와 너를 떠나보내고 <br>후회하고 있는 내게 함께 할 수 없음이 <br>나에겐 너무도 커다란 아픔인걸 아니 <br><br>언제나 힘들던 이룰 수 없던 사랑 <br>너에게도 너무 큰 아픔이었다면 돌아와줘 <br><br>후회 없는 사랑하기 위해 <br>내가 택한 사람은 너뿐야 <br>언젠간 내게 돌아와 줄 너잖아 <br><br>힘든 시간 다 지나고 오랜 간절함에 되찾은 <br>내 마지막 사랑인걸 <br><br>다시 내게 돌아와 너를 떠나보내고 <br><br>후회하고 있는 내게 함께 할 수 없음이 <br>나에겐 너무도 커다란 <br>아픔인걸 아니]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="One Love" label="One Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/원하고_원망하죠/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 원하고 원망하죠 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%9B%90%ED%95%98%EA%B3%A0_%EC%9B%90%EB%A7%9D%ED%95%98%EC%A3%A0/" title="발라드_공장 - 원하고 원망하죠 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아직 누굴 사랑할 수 없는.. <br>그대 지친 가슴을 난 너무나 잘 알죠.. <br><br>변함없이 그대 곁을 지켜왔지만.. <br>그댄 지나버린 사랑 그 안에만 사는 걸.. <br><br>원하고 원망하죠..그대만을.. <br>내게 다가온 시간을 힘겹게 만드는 사람.. <br>지난 날들을..그대의 아픈 얘기를 모르고 싶은걸.. <br><br>소리내어 환히 웃을 때도.. <br>그대 가슴은 울고 있는 걸 느끼죠.. <br><br>그런 그댈 끌어안아 주고 싶지만.. <br>이런 내 맘 들키지 않기로 한걸요.. <br><br>원하고 원망하죠..그대만을.. <br>내게 다가올 시간을 힘겹게 만드는 사람.. <br><br>그대 지난 날들을..그대의 아픈 얘기를 모르고 싶은걸.. <br><br>지금 그대는 빈 자릴 채워줄 누구라도 필요한거겠죠.. <br>잠시 그대 쉴 곳이 되어주기엔.. <br>나는 너무나 욕심이 많은걸.. <br><br>원하고 원망하죠..그대만을.. <br>내게 다가올 내일을 후회로 만드는 사람.. <br><br>이런 내 맘을 혼자서 얘기할께요.. <br>그댈 너무 사랑해요..]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="원하고 원망하죠" label="원하고 원망하죠"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/눈물아_안녕/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 눈물아 안녕 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EB%88%88%EB%AC%BC%EC%95%84_%EC%95%88%EB%85%95/" title="발라드_공장 - 눈물아 안녕 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[참 힘겨웠었어 늘 울기만 했어 <br>모두가 나를 떠나가던 날 <br>심장을 베는 그 차가운 말들 <br>너마저도 없었다면 어땠을지 <br>나 울지 않아 다시는 못난 바보처럼 <br>아파했던 만큼 한 뼘 더 자란 가슴이니까 <br>힘들지만 내 맘이 기댈 수 있게 곁에 있어 주겠니 <br>나의 어제 나의 상처 나의 눈물 이젠 안녕 <br><br>다 지나갈꺼야 또 시간이 가면 <br>가슴 속 새 살 돋아날꺼야 oh <br>사랑에 데인 그 흉터까지도 <br>사랑으로 덮어주던 너로 인해 <br>나 울지 않아 다시는 못난 바보처럼 <br>아파했던 만큼 한 뼘 더 자란 가슴이니까 <br>힘들지만 내 맘이 기댈 수 있게 곁에 있어 주겠니 <br>나의 어제 나의 상처 나의 눈물 이젠 안녕 <br><br>이제는 처음 태어난 것처럼 <br>낯선 첫 걸음 내딛어 보려해 <br>위태롭지만 나를 지켜봐줄래 <br>나 한 걸음 더 햇빛 속으로 나설꺼야 <br>지난 시간들은 내일을 위한 디딤돌인걸 <br>다시 한번 너에게 갈 수 있도록 손을 잡아 주겠니 <br>아픈 기억 아픈 상처 아픈 눈물아 안녕]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="눈물아 안녕" label="눈물아 안녕"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/남자를_몰라/</id><title>발라드_공장 - 남자를 몰라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:35:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:35:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EB%82%A8%EC%9E%90%EB%A5%BC_%EB%AA%B0%EB%9D%BC/" title="발라드_공장 - 남자를 몰라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[매 번 늦어도 이해할게 누굴 만났니 먼저 묻지 않을게 <br>고집스런 내 사랑 너의 말은 변명이라도 믿고 싶을테니 <br><br>눈 비비는척 눈물 닦아내고 다음 약속도 잡을 이유 만들지 <br>니 맘보다 한숨과 친해져도 널 보기 위해 난 사니까 <br><br>수없이 어긋난데도 기다릴게 <br>아무리 가슴 아파도 웃어볼게 <br>떠나선 안돼 서둘러 져버리진 마 <br>날 밀어내도 깊어지는 이 사랑을 봐 <br>내입을 막아도 세상이 다 아는데 <br>왜 너만 몰라 왜 널 지킬 남자를 몰라 <br><br>잊어보려고 해도 소용없어 하루도 못가 너만 또 찾는 나인걸 <br>혼자가 더 좋다는 슬픈 니 말 눈물이 자꾸 지워버려 <br><br>수없이 어긋난대도 기다릴게 <br>아무리 가슴 아파도 웃어볼게 <br>떠나선 안돼 서둘러 져버리진 마 <br>날 밀어내도 깊어지는 이 사랑을 봐 <br>내 입을 막아도 세상이 다 아는데 <br>왜 너만 몰라 왜 널 지킬 남자를 몰라 <br><br>니 맘에 누가 있든 괜찮아 한 번쯤 못이긴 척 돌아봐 <br>보여줄게 더 많아 쉽게 보낼 수 없어 가지마 Yeah~ <br><br>Uh Yeah~ 널 원해야만 견뎌내는 내 가슴이야 <br>날마다 울어도 볼 때마다 행복해 <br>왜 너만 몰라 왜 강한 내 사랑을 몰라]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="남자를 몰라" label="남자를 몰라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Moon_Bounce/Lungs_Feat_Ehiorobo/</id><title>Moon_Bounce - Lungs (Feat. Ehiorobo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:36:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:36:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Moon_Bounce/Lungs_Feat_Ehiorobo/" title="Moon_Bounce - Lungs (Feat. Ehiorobo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby <br>This is the most I've ever <br>Held my tongue befo <br>The most I've ever held my <br>Baby the most I've ever held my lungs <br>These emotions have a shelf life <br>Lock off those <br>You could tie me <br>You could tie me up <br>Tie me down <br>I won't interrupt <br>Or make a sound <br>Lock off those <br>You could tie me <br>You could tie me up <br>Tie me down <br>Anything just don't scream at me <br>alright Damn <br>Perhaps I wanna be afraid of <br>what you might do <br>Next to me <br>Reality begins to fray <br>Surrender to the fantasy <br>Perhaps I wanna be afraid of <br>what you might do <br>Next to me <br>Reality begins to fray <br>Surrender to the fantasy <br>You can tie me you can tie <br>tie me to the <br>tie me to the <br>With my tongue tied <br>My hands locked <br>I'll listen for the pistols cock <br>It's hard to punish daddy <br>when he's beggin' to get <br>Sock and bopped <br>So cold I can feel you in my lungs <br>my emotions tell you <br>You can tie me up <br>So cold I can feel you in my lungs <br>my emotions tell you <br>You can tie me up <br>So cold <br>I can feel you <br>Feel you <br>You <br>You <br>So cold I can <br>Feel you in my lungs <br>]]></content><category term="Moon Bounce" label="Moon Bounce"/><category term="Lungs (Feat. Ehiorobo)" label="Lungs (Feat. Ehiorobo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hooul/It_Was_Beautiful/</id><title>Hooul - It Was Beautiful - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:38:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:38:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hooul/It_Was_Beautiful/" title="Hooul - It Was Beautiful - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니 말들이 맴맴 돌아 <br>하루 종일 제자리에 있는듯해 <br>뒤로 가고 싶어도 가지 못해 <br>더는 앞으로는 안 가고픈 난데 <br>지금 이순간이 꿈이 아니라 <br>너무 헷갈리는 reality <br>차라리 이 말 한마디만 <br>해줄 수 있겠니 <br>This time is dream <br>시간은 자꾸만 흘러가 <br>어찌 흘러갈까 <br>Oh 로라 같은 우리 <br>그리고 무표정한 my lady <br>사랑이 식는다는 게 <br>네 눈으로 보인단 게 힘이 들어 <br>드라마 주인공이 돼버린 듯 <br>길모퉁이에 가만히 기대 서있어 <br>When is your mind and <br>will come back <br>with that look to see me <br>하루 빨리 좋았던 때로 <br>그때 맘 편히 good night과 함께 잠들던 <br>그때의 그때 그 밤처럼 That day <br>Um <br>Yeah e yeah <br>Uh uh baby <br>언젠가 올 줄 안 시간이지만 <br>난 아직인데 <br>give me the the time <br>별처럼 수놓았던 널 어찌 보낼까 <br>이 자리서 널 위해 기도할게 baby <br>When is your mind and <br>will come back <br>with that look to see me <br>하루 빨리 좋았던 때로 oh oh ooh <br>그때 맘 편히 good night과 함께 잠들던 <br>그때의 그때 그 밤처럼 <br>When is your mind and <br>will come back <br>with that look to see me <br>하루 빨리 좋았던 때로 oh oh ooh <br>mind you can't show <br>with that look of the first time <br>그때 그 밤 그때 그 밤처럼 <br>]]></content><category term="Hooul" label="Hooul"/><category term="It Was Beautiful" label="It Was Beautiful"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hong_E/하늘_다녀오겠습니다/</id><title>Hong_E - 하늘 다녀오겠습니다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:40:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:40:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hong_E/%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98_%EB%8B%A4%EB%85%80%EC%98%A4%EA%B2%A0%EC%8A%B5%EB%8B%88%EB%8B%A4/" title="Hong_E - 하늘 다녀오겠습니다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니가 그렇게 좋아하던 하늘이 <br>언젠가부터 난 자꾸 미워져 <br>오늘도 너를 보내주지않는 하늘이 <br>언젠가부터 난 정말 싫어져 <br>니가 오던날 달려가 널 안아주던 <br>나의 미소는 <br>이제는 널 안을수 없어 <br>너의 이름만 슬픈 노래만 불러 <br>내가 울잖아 이 바보야 <br>혹시 한번쯤은 너도 <br>내가 보고싶지 않니 <br>너도 나처럼 울고 있다면 <br>내가 갈께 너의 곁에 사랑해 <br>정말 널 사랑해 <br>니가 그렇게 좋아하던 하늘이 <br>언젠가부터 난 자꾸 미워져 <br>오늘도 너를 보내주지않는 하늘이 <br>언젠가부터 난 정말 싫어져 <br>니가 가던 날 달려와 날 안아주던 <br>너의 입술도 <br>이제는 나의 것이 아냐 <br>보고싶다고 너의 이름만 불러 <br>내가 울잖아 이 바보야 <br>또 이렇게 울고있는 <br>내가 가엽지도 않니 <br>너도 나처럼 울고 있다면 <br>내가 갈께 너의 곁에 사랑해 정말 널 <br>내가 흘려온 눈물만큼 <br>하늘에선 비가 내려 <br>기다리지 말라는듯 <br>이 비가 니가 우는거라면 <br>내가 갈께 너의 곁에 <br>사랑해 정말 널 사랑해 <br>오늘도 너를 보내주지 않는 하늘이 <br>언젠가부터 난 정말 싫어져 <br>]]></content><category term="Hong E" label="Hong E"/><category term="하늘 다녀오겠습니다" label="하늘 다녀오겠습니다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Faas/Why_Bother/</id><title>Luke_Faas - Why Bother - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:41:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:41:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Faas/Why_Bother/" title="Luke_Faas - Why Bother - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1] <br>Why bother? <br>Why bother stretch my hand <br>Why bother? <br>Why bother? <br>You for your demand <br>My brother <br><br>[Pre-Chrous] <br>Your reputations sticks to you as glue <br>You had a none trust <br>Not only a few <br>Now your returning <br>Could this be my clue? <br>Do I go away and never bother <br>Why bother? <br><br>[Chrous] <br>I won't waste the gravel energy on you <br>Why would I bother? <br>Why bother? <br>I won't spread the rest with sympathy <br>Why would I bother? <br>Why bother? <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>Why bother? <br>Why would I even care? <br>Why bother? <br>Why bother? <br>The anything but fail <br>Why bother? <br><br><br>[Pre-Chrous] <br>Your reputations sticks to you as glue <br>You had a none trust <br>Not only a few <br>Now your returning <br>Could this be my clue? <br>Do I go away and never bother <br>Why bother? <br><br>[Chrous] <br>I won't waste the gravel energy on you <br>Why would I bother? <br>Why bother? <br>I won't spread the rest with sympathy <br>Why would I bother? <br>Why bother? <br><br>[Bridge] <br>I won't waste the gravel energy on you <br>Why would I bother? <br>Why bother? <br>I won't spread the rest with sympathy <br>Why would I bother? <br>Why bother?]]></content><category term="Luke Faas" label="Luke Faas"/><category term="Why Bother" label="Why Bother"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Snoop_Dogg/420_Blaze_Up_Feat_Devin_The_Dude_Wiz_Khalifa__DJ_Battlecat/</id><title>Snoop_Dogg - 420 (Blaze Up) (Feat. Devin The Dude, Wiz Khalifa &amp; DJ Battlecat) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:45:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:45:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Snoop_Dogg/420_Blaze_Up_Feat_Devin_The_Dude_Wiz_Khalifa__DJ_Battlecat/" title="Snoop_Dogg - 420 (Blaze Up) (Feat. Devin The Dude, Wiz Khalifa &amp; DJ Battlecat) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1: Snoop Dogg] <br>Whenever I'm down and out I get back to myself <br>I roll a motherfucking fat bat to myself <br>Leave it to beaver, America gon' legalize but I ain't believe her <br>Til she finally did it <br>Overworked but I'm still committed <br>All things under the letter G, Snoop Dogg done did it <br>Gracefully gazing unto the sky <br>A lot of people smoke just to get by <br>But I see things much differently <br>Medically, physically, mentally, theoretically <br>Put it in a letter so you let it be <br>One day we'll all agree and have peace up under a big chronic tree <br>If I had my way at 4:20 every day you could blaze a J <br>And not have to answer to nobody <br>I live my life like it's a party <br>So let's go cuz <br><br>[Hook] <br>So go ahead and blaze up <br>Today's the day to blaze up (Yeah, yeah ooh) <br>So go ahead and put your J's up (And smoke) <br>Na-na-na-na-na-nanana (Get high) <br>Na-na-na-na-na-nananana <br><br>[Verse 2: Devin The Dude] <br>I blaze up soon as I raise up from out of my sleep <br>I got me a sweet <br>I hope they legalize it here, I'm tired of police <br>You think you could smoke like me &amp; Snoop, don't try to compete <br>I'll still blaze with ya, fire that ho up <br>If smoking weed is going down, then I'ma show up <br>Weed is where I'm needed, it's a necessity <br>If I ain't got it, little shit get the best of me <br>I even put it in my food, I got a brownie recipe <br>You eat one piece man your ass'll be fucked up for six or seven hours or so <br>You don't like edibles? Then I got plenty of flowers to blow <br>Smoke it in the paper, cigar, a bong <br>Don't worry about the haters, just vibe to the song <br>And do it however you please, you please <br>Today's the day to smoke weed <br><br><br>[Hook] <br>So go ahead and blaze up <br>Today's the day to blaze up (Yeah, yeah ooh) <br>So go ahead and put your J's up (And smoke) <br>Na-na-na-na-na-nanana (Get high) <br>Na-na-na-na-na-nanana <br><br>[Verse 3: Wiz Khalifa] <br>Damn, a pound ain't really nothing now <br>Remember smoking with my cousin <br>Now we all Raw cone stuffing <br>Enough to wake neighbors up <br>KK my favorite flavor <br>And you ain't gotta ask cause we major <br>I smoke like them old players <br>Only put it in the paper <br>I just started recently letting niggas smoke blunts around me <br>Known to keep the room cloudy <br>Get a bad bitch, sit her down, let her smoke, now she open <br>The best trees I be smoking <br>Smell it through the bag so it's potent <br>Even get it on the plane, TSA don't even notice <br>Ran in the burner, he done taught a young nigga how to grow it <br>A pothead but I be focused <br>And it ain't in my session if it's bullshit <br>Only the best what you dealing with <br>It's legal now, everybody's doing this <br><br><br>[Hook] <br>So go ahead and blaze up <br>Today's the day to blaze up (Yeah, yeah ooh) <br>So go ahead and put your J's up (And smoke) <br>Na-na-na-na-na-nanana (Get high) <br>Na-na-na-na-na-nanana <br>Go ahead and blaze up <br>Today's the day to blaze up <br>So go ahead and put your J's up <br>Na-na-na-na-na-nanana <br>Na-na-na-na-na-nanana na <br><br>[Outro] <br>Come and smoke with me tonight, tonight]]></content><category term="Snoop Dogg" label="Snoop Dogg"/><category term="420 (Blaze Up) (Feat. Devin The Dude, Wiz Khalifa &amp; DJ Battlecat)" label="420 (Blaze Up) (Feat. Devin The Dude, Wiz Khalifa &amp; DJ Battlecat)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Snoop_Dogg/Swivel_Feat_Stress/</id><title>Snoop_Dogg - Swivel (Feat. Stress) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:46:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:46:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Snoop_Dogg/Swivel_Feat_Stress/" title="Snoop_Dogg - Swivel (Feat. Stress) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Hook: Stresmatic &amp; Snoop Dogg] <br>I can send a missile <br>I got my head on a swivel, swivel <br>I got my head on a swivel <br>Eyes peeled when I wiggle <br>I got my head on a swivel, swivel <br>I got my head on a swivel <br>This is not a starter pistol (No, no) <br>I got my head on a swivel, swivel (Yeah) <br>I got my head on a swivel <br>If you need me just whistle <br>I got my head on a swivel, swivel <br>I got my head on a swivel <br><br>[Verse 1: Snoop Dogg] <br>From the depths of the sea <br>Blowing trees in the big leagues <br>I got a plan, I'm going ham on all you DBs <br>You better double me up, safety cover me up <br>Single coverage won't work boy, I'll burn him up <br>Give me the damn ball, move the chains at the same time <br>Dressed to impress when it's game time, flame mine <br>I'm wide open, hoping, scoping out the scene <br>Catch a quick screen, cake walk on your whole team <br>Will he beam, will he run, will he walk, talk, or will he lean <br>I need riders and goons when I build a team <br>I get it cracking with the snap of the wrist <br>It's nothing less than a championship, now peep this <br><br>[Pre-Hook: Snoop Dogg] <br>Call a few plays then break the huddle <br>Check that D, they in the zone no rebuttal <br>I can throw a strike down the pipe about 80 <br>Hand full of rings, I'm shady like Brady <br><br>[Hook: Stressmatic &amp; Snoop Dogg] <br>I can send a missile <br>I got my head on a swivel, swivel <br>I got my head on a swivel <br>Eyes peeled when I wiggle <br>I got my head on a swivel, swivel <br>I got my head on a swivel <br>This is not a starter pistol (No, no) <br>I got my head on a swivel, swivel (Yeah) <br>I got my head on a swivel <br>If you need me just whistle <br>I got my head on a swivel, swivel <br>I got my head on a swivel <br><br>[Verse 2: Snoop Dogg] <br>I'm in full beast mode, too cold to be cut down <br>Lifting weights, staying in shape, won't be shut down <br>Antonio Brown or Julio Jones <br>One on each side, now who do you zone <br>They on me like a bloodhound cause I won't go down <br>It's like a merry-go-round the way I'm bending my routes <br>I'm so sick with this, they can't stick me <br>Stick to to this <br>Sports Illustrated, get a flick of this <br>Lost him, cross him, quarterback toss <br>Highest point homie had the Randy Moss him <br>One hand as I shook him off me <br>Some OBJ with a dab of that DJ coffin, get off me]]></content><category term="Snoop Dogg" label="Snoop Dogg"/><category term="Swivel (Feat. Stress)" label="Swivel (Feat. Stress)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/J-scot_제이스캇/EDEN_Feat_일리/</id><title>J-scot_제이스캇 - EDEN (Feat. 일리) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:50:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:50:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/J-scot_%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4%EC%BA%87/EDEN_Feat_%EC%9D%BC%EB%A6%AC/" title="J-scot_제이스캇 - EDEN (Feat. 일리) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Errday Errnight Always <br>All the time's a wave <br>sta tarara rata <br>Errday Errnight Always <br>Errtime All the time <br>'s a wave <br>Errday Errnight Always <br>Errtime and Now <br>Um <br>Errday Errnight Always <br>Errtime and Now <br>susturu tutu <br>안녕 내 목소리 기억나니 <br>넌 내가 랩하는 걸 좋아했었는데 <br>가을남자는 들어봤니 <br>군대서 쓰고 너에게 <br>첨으로 들려줬었는데 <br>이제는 어디에나 올라와 있지 <br>너가 듣고싶을 때 언제든지 <br>그냥 들으면 돼 <br>나는 너의 목소리를 <br>들을 수가 없지만 <br>너는 아무때나 그냥 찾아 들으면 돼 <br>아직도 내 발걸음은 꿈을 쫒아 다녀 <br>넌 하고 싶은 일을 하는 <br>날 부러워했잖아 <br>그런 널 보면 난 감사함을 느꼈지 <br>너의 꿈 너의 몫까지 <br>내가 다 이룰테니 <br>부디 나를 잊지 않길 <br>물론 좋아하는 마음은 이제 없지만 <br>좋은 추억으로 남길 <br>아픈 기억은 다 사라지고 <br>좋은 추억만이 남길 <br>Errday and Errnight <br>Always and Errtime <br>Errday and Errnight <br>Errday and Errnight <br>Always and Errtime <br>Errday and Errnight <br>Always and Errtime and Now <br>Errday Errnight Always <br>Errtime and Now <br>sta taradara rata <br>Errday Errnight Always <br>Errtime and Now <br>susturu tutu <br>카톡 프로필 사진 없어지고 <br>페이스북 연애중 없어지고 <br>어디서 뭘 하며 살아가는지도 <br>이제는 알 수 없지만 <br>웃을 때 높아지는 목소리 톤도 <br>오른쪽 손바닥에 있는 작은 점도 <br>네가 샤워할 때 맞추는 <br>물의 온도까지도 <br>너무나 선명하게 남아있는데 <br>Errday Errnight Always <br>All the time's a wave <br>]]></content><category term="J-scot (제이스캇)" label="J-scot (제이스캇)"/><category term="EDEN (Feat. 일리)" label="EDEN (Feat. 일리)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전혜인/봄_라일락/</id><title>전혜인 - 봄, 라일락 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:50:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:50:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%ED%98%9C%EC%9D%B8/%EB%B4%84_%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%BC%EB%9D%BD/" title="전혜인 - 봄, 라일락 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[슬그머니 또 다시 봄이 찾아와 <br>봄은 연인들과 벚꽃을 달고 오지 <br>사랑하는 사람과 <br>눈 맞추며 손 잡고 벚꽃을 찾아 <br>모두가 하나 같이 벚꽃을 찾아 <br>근데 있잖아 라일락도 있잖아 <br>라일락 향기 나와 함께 <br>맡아보지 않겠니 <br>왜 사람들은 벚꽃만 찾는 걸까 <br>너는 왜 벚꽃만 보는 걸까 <br>라일락도 있는데 <br>여기 나도 있는데 <br>누군가는 나를 찾기도 하지 <br>누군가는 나를 예쁘다고 하지만 <br>벚꽃뿐인 너에게 난 그저 <br>시들어버린 라일락일 뿐이지 <br>그렇지 않니 <br>근데 있잖아 라일락도 있잖아 <br>라일락 향기 나와 함께 <br>맡아보지 않겠니 <br>왜 사람들은 벚꽃만 찾는 걸까 <br>너는 왜 벚꽃만 보는 걸까 <br>라일락도 있는데 <br>시들 시들 시들 시들 <br>시들 시들 라일락 <br>시들 시들 시들 시들 <br>시들 시들 라일락 <br>근데 있잖아 라일락도 있잖아 <br>라일락 향기 나와 함께 <br>맡아보지 않겠니 <br>왜 사람들은 벚꽃만 찾는 걸까 <br>너는 왜 벚꽃만 보는 걸까 <br>라일락도 있는데 <br>여기 나도 있는데 <br>]]></content><category term="전혜인" label="전혜인"/><category term="봄, 라일락" label="봄, 라일락"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeri_Southern/Scarlet_Ribbons_For_Her_Hair/</id><title>Jeri_Southern - Scarlet Ribbons (For Her Hair) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:50:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:50:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeri_Southern/Scarlet_Ribbons_For_Her_Hair/" title="Jeri_Southern - Scarlet Ribbons (For Her Hair) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You know I peeked in to say goodnight <br>When I heard my child in prayer <br>She said, And for me some scarlet ribbons <br>Scarlet ribbons for my hair <br><br>All the stores were closed and shuttered <br>And all the streets were dark and bare <br>In our town, no scarlet ribbons <br>Not one ribbon for her hair <br><br>Through the night my heart was aching <br>And just before the dawn was breaking <br>I peeked in and on her bed <br>In gay profusion lying there <br>Lovely ribbons, scarlet ribbons <br>Scarlet ribbons for her hair <br><br>If I live to be a hundred <br>I will never, never know from where <br>Came those lovely scarlet ribbons <br>Scarlet Ribbons for her hair <br><br>Scarlet ribbons, there's magic in the air <br>Scarlet, scarlet ribbons for her hair]]></content><category term="Jeri Southern" label="Jeri Southern"/><category term="Scarlet Ribbons (For Her Hair)" label="Scarlet Ribbons (For Her Hair)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeri_Southern/I_Hadnt_Anyone_Till_You/</id><title>Jeri_Southern - I Hadn`t Anyone Till You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:50:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:50:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeri_Southern/I_Hadnt_Anyone_Till_You/" title="Jeri_Southern - I Hadn`t Anyone Till You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I hadn't anyone till you <br>I was a lonely one 'til you <br>I used to lie awake and wonder if there could be <br>A someone in the wide world just made for me <br>Now I see <br><br>I had to save my love for you, I saved my love for you <br>I never gave my love 'til you, I saved it all for you <br>And through my lonely heart demanding it <br>Cupid took a hand in it <br>I hadn't anyone till you <br><br>I kept my love in secrecy <br>I put it under lock and key <br>I had to save my love for you <br>I never gave my love away <br>I waited for that lucky day <br>When I could give it to you <br><br>And through my lonely heart demanding it <br>Cupid took a hand in it <br>I hadn't anyone till you]]></content><category term="Jeri Southern" label="Jeri Southern"/><category term="I Hadn`t Anyone Till You" label="I Hadn`t Anyone Till You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeri_Southern/Too_Marvelous_For_Words/</id><title>Jeri_Southern - Too Marvelous For Words - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:51:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:51:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeri_Southern/Too_Marvelous_For_Words/" title="Jeri_Southern - Too Marvelous For Words - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're just too marvelous, too marvelous for words <br>Like glorious, glamorous and that old standby amorous <br>It's all too wonderful, I'll never find the words <br>That say enough, tell enough, I mean they just aren't swell enough <br><br>You're much too much and just too very, very <br>To ever be in Webster's Dictionary <br>And so I'm borrowing a love song from the birds <br>To tell you that you're marvelous, too marvelous for words <br><br>You're much, you're too much and just too very, very <br>To ever be, to ever be in Webster's Dictionary <br>And so I'm borrowing a love song from the birds <br>To tell you that you're marvelous, tell you that you're marvelous <br>Tell you that you're marvelous, too marvelous for words]]></content><category term="Jeri Southern" label="Jeri Southern"/><category term="Too Marvelous For Words" label="Too Marvelous For Words"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeri_Southern/Its_De-Lovely/</id><title>Jeri_Southern - It`s De-Lovely - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:51:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:51:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeri_Southern/Its_De-Lovely/" title="Jeri_Southern - It`s De-Lovely - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The night is young, the skies are clear <br>So if you want to go walking, dear <br>It's delightful, it's delicious, it's de lovely <br>I understand the reason why <br>You're sentimental, 'cause so am I <br>It's delightful, it's delicious, it's de lovely <br>You can tell at a glance <br>What a swell night this is for romance <br>You can hear dear Mother Nature <br>Murmuring low <br>Let yourself go <br><br>So please be sweet, my chickadee <br>And when I kiss you, just say to me <br>It's delightful, it's delicious <br>It's delectable, it's delirious <br>It's dilemma, it's delimit, it's deluxe <br>It's de lovely <br><br>I feel a sudden urge to sing <br>The kind of ditty that invokes the spring <br><br>I'll control my desire to curse <br>While you crucify the verse <br><br>This verse I started seems to me <br>The Tin Pantithesis of a melody <br><br>So spare us all the pain <br>Just skip the darn thing and sing the refrain <br><br>Mi, mi, mi, mi <br>Re, re, re, re <br>Do, sol, mi, do, la, si <br><br>The night is young, the skies are clear <br>So if you want to go walking, dear <br>It's delightful, it's delicious, it's de lovely <br>I understand the reason why <br>You're sentimental, 'cause so am I <br>It's delightful, it's delicious, it's de lovely <br>You can tell at a glance <br>What a swell night this is for romance <br>You can hear dear Mother Nature <br>Murmuring low <br>Let yourself go <br><br>So please be sweet, my chickadee <br>And when I kiss you, just say to me <br>It's delightful, it's delicious <br>It's, it's de lovely]]></content><category term="Jeri Southern" label="Jeri Southern"/><category term="It`s De-Lovely" label="It`s De-Lovely"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeri_Southern/Let_Me_Love_You/</id><title>Jeri_Southern - Let Me Love You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-07T20:51:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-07T20:51:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeri_Southern/Let_Me_Love_You/" title="Jeri_Southern - Let Me Love You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If someone makes you cry and you're feeling blue <br>Let me love you <br>You can always count on me <br>I'll be there, wait and see <br>To love you <br><br>Let me love you <br>Let me kiss you <br>Let me show you whadda I can do <br>For someone like you <br><br>If someone breaks your heart and it starts to fall apart <br>Let me love you <br>You can always come to me to soothe your misery <br>And to love you <br><br>Let me love you <br>Let me kiss you <br>Let me show you whadda I can do <br>For someone like you <br><br>If someone leaves you at the door, teardrops on the floor <br>Let me love you <br>You can always call on me <br>I'll be there willingly <br>To love you <br><br>Let me love you <br>Let me kiss you <br>Let me show you whadda I can do <br>For someone like you]]></content><category term="Jeri Southern" label="Jeri Southern"/><category term="Let Me Love You" label="Let Me Love You"/></entry></feed>