<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:20:12+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/진짜일_리_없어/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 진짜일 리 없어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:35:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:35:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%A7%84%EC%A7%9C%EC%9D%BC_%EB%A6%AC_%EC%97%86%EC%96%B4/" title="발라드 공장 - 진짜일 리 없어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이게 진짜일 리 없어 <br><br>주변을 지나던 사람들 하나 둘씩 느려지고 <br>주위의 모든 게 갑자기 들리지가 않아 <br>세상은 갑자기 멈춰진 흑백사진 같은데 <br>니 목소리만 메아리처럼 헤어지자 <br><br>이게 진짜일 리 없어 니가 날 떠나는 게 <br>꿈속인 게 틀림 없어 눈물도 나지 않는 게 <br>누가 나 좀 꼬집어 줬으면 해 꿈이라면 나를 깨워줬음 해 <br>아님 내가 살 수 없어 <br>이게 진짜일 리 없어 그건 안돼 <br><br>조금씩 주변의 사람들 움직이기 시작했고 <br>니가 일어서는 모습이 영화처럼 보여 음... <br>떠나는 널 잡아보려고 손을 내밀려 해도 <br>온몸이 돌처럼 다 굳어버린 것 같아 <br><br>이게 진짜일 리 없어 니가 날 떠나는 게 <br>꿈속인 게 틀림 없어 눈물도 나지 않는 게 <br>누가 나 좀 꼬집어 줬으면 해 꿈이라면 나를 깨워줬음 해 <br>아님 내가 살 수 없어 이게 진짜일 리 없어 <br><br>오~~~니가 떠나고 나서야 머리가 움직이나 봐 <br>그대 뒤를 쫓아 거리를 헤매어 뛰지만 <br><br>이게 진짜일 리 없어 니가 날 떠나는 게 <br>꿈속인 게 틀림 없어 눈물도 나지 않는 게 <br>누가 나 좀 꼬집어 줬으면 해 꿈이라면 나를 깨워줬음 해 <br>아님 내가 살 수 없어 <br>이게 진짜일 리 없어 이게 진짜일 리 없어 <br><br>정말 니가 떠났나 봐]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="진짜일 리 없어" label="진짜일 리 없어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/하루/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 하루 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:35:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:35:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%ED%95%98%EB%A3%A8/" title="발라드 공장 - 하루 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우~~~ 아~~~ <br><br>사랑이 날 또 아프게 해요 <br>사랑이 날 또 울게 하네요 <br>그렇게 사랑했던 추억마저 잊어달라며 <br>사랑은 잔인하게 떠나가네요 <br><br>정말 내가 괜찮을까요 그대가 한 그 인사처럼 <br>그래 그댄 눈 가린 채 모르는 척 떠나는 게 차라리 편할 테죠 <br>변할 수도 있는 거겠죠 저 바람도 매일이 다른데 <br>그래도 이 세상에 살고 싶단 행복을 준 건 너무나도 고마웠어요 <br><br>사랑이 날 또 아프게 해요 <br>사랑이 날 또 울게 하네요 <br>그렇게 사랑했던 추억마저 잊어달라며 <br>사랑은 잔인하게 떠나가네요 <br><br>잊을 수도 있을 거예요 그대처럼 나도 변하겠죠 <br>하지만 그 날까지 내가 어찌 살아낼까요 벌써 그댈 보고 싶어요 <br><br>사랑이 날 또 아프게 해요 <br>사랑이 날 또 울게 하네요 <br>그렇게 사랑했던 추억마저 잊어달라며 <br>사랑은 잔인하게 떠나가네요 <br>이렇게 또 하루가 지나 가네요 <br><br>아~~~~~~~~~아~~~~ <br><br>(사랑이 날 또 아프게 해요) 아프게하네요 <br>(사랑이 날 또 울게 하네요) 떠나네요 <br>다시는 못쓰게 된 내 가슴은 이렇게 아픈데 <br>사랑은 꿈을 깨듯 허무하네요 <br>이렇게 또 하루가 지나 가네요]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="하루" label="하루"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/헤어지는_중입니다/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 헤어지는 중입니다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:35:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:35:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%ED%97%A4%EC%96%B4%EC%A7%80%EB%8A%94_%EC%A4%91%EC%9E%85%EB%8B%88%EB%8B%A4/" title="발라드 공장 - 헤어지는 중입니다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[햇살이 눈부셔 눈을 감고 말았죠 <br>흐르던 눈물이 멈추질 않네요 <br>가까스로 일어나도 다시 휘청거려요 <br>이제는 정말 끝인가요 <br><br>보란듯이 살거야 나약해지면 안돼 <br>그 사람보다 더 행복해져야 돼 <br>절대 뒤돌아 보지마 이런 못난 가슴아 <br>왜 혼자서 난 멈출줄 모르니 <br><br>사랑해서 후회없다던 사랑해서 보내준다던 <br>잔인한 거짓말 어떻게 그럴수 있어 <br>사랑한다면 왜 이렇게 힘들게 하는지 <br><br>이별했죠 이별한거 맞죠 <br>심장이 미쳐서 아직도 착각하고 있나봐요 <br>미련한 내가 나조차 너무 싫은데 <br>서러움에 내 맘이 무너져요 <br>정말 지운건 아닌지 덜컥 겁이 나 울죠 <br>당신 없는 나 이렇게 살아요 <br><br>사랑해서 후회없다던 사랑해서 보내준다던 <br>잔인한 거짓말 어떻게 그럴 수 있어 <br>사랑한다면 왜 이렇게 힘들게 하는지 <br><br>이별했죠 이별한거 맞죠 <br>심장이 미쳐서 아직도 착각하고 있나봐요 <br>미련한 내가 나조차 너무 싫은데 <br>서러움에 내 맘이 무너져요 <br>정말 지운건 아닌지 덜컥 겁이 나 울죠 <br>당신 없는 나 어떻게 살아요]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="헤어지는 중입니다" label="헤어지는 중입니다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/이별이_다_그렇죠/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 이별이 다 그렇죠 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:35:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:35:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84%EC%9D%B4_%EB%8B%A4_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A0%87%EC%A3%A0/" title="발라드 공장 - 이별이 다 그렇죠 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[숙인 고갤 들어요 어떤 얘기도 들어 줄수 있어요 아무말 않고서 <br>다시는 볼 수 없다는 못된 그 말을 쉽게 할 순 없어도 해야만 하니까 <br><br>그 오랜 시간을 나의 행복만 바랬죠 <br>부족한 모자란 내 모습마저 지운 채 <br><br>알아요 그대가 이별을 말해도 <br>나를 사랑한 가슴이 그댈 붙잡고 놓지 않는 걸 알죠 <br>그래요 나를 버려도 괜찮아요 <br>걱정만하던 그대 미래는 <br>나를 저 멀리 보내야 행복한걸 아니까 <br><br>그대의 넓은 어깨에 너무나 오래 나만 기대 있었죠 미련한 욕심에 <br>더 원할 수가 없어요 그대 내 눈에 너무 지쳐 보여서 나도 잘 알아서 <br><br>놓아요 놓아요 그대 모르게 놓친듯 <br>잊어요 잊어요 참 미안하단 그마음 <br><br>알아요 차갑게 내 등 떠밀어도 <br>그대 얼굴을 흐르는 많은 눈물은 나를 속일 수 없죠 <br>그래요 정말 나를 잘 보냈어요 <br>언제나 내게 짖던 미소가 <br>작은 약속도 하나 남지 않은걸 아니까 <br><br>나는 가줄 수 있어요 아주 조그만 추억이면 <br>나를 살게 할 수 있어요 언제라도 감사하면서 <br>알아요 내가 버려진걸 알아도 숨이 자꾸 날 막아도 <br>손가락 하나 잡아낼 수 없는 걸 <br>사랑도 변할 수 있는걸 모르고 너무 늦게 알아버려서 슬퍼 못해요 <br>모두 내 탓 이란 걸 아니까]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="이별이 다 그렇죠" label="이별이 다 그렇죠"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/돌멩이/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 돌멩이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:35:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:35:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EB%8F%8C%EB%A9%A9%EC%9D%B4/" title="발라드 공장 - 돌멩이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흙먼지가 날리고 비바람이 불어와 뼈속까지 아픈데 난 이를 악문다 <br>아둥바둥 거리는 나의삶을 위해서 내 맘둘곳 찾아서 난 길을 떠난다 <br>나는 돌멩이 이리치이고 저리치여도 굴러가다 보면 좋은날 오겠지 <br>내 꿈을 찾아서 내사랑 찾아서 나는 자유로운 새처럼 맘껏 하늘을 날고싶어 <br><br>굴러 난 굴러간다 내 몸이 부서져 한줌의 흙이 되도 <br>굴러 난 굴러간다 내 사랑 찾아서 내 꿈을 찾아서 <br><br>머뭇거릴 새 없이 모두 지나버렸어 시간이라는 놈은 피도 눈물도 없어 <br>구르고 또 굴러서 멍투성이가 되도 세상 끝에 홀로 서 당당히 선다 <br>나는 돌멩이 이리치이고 저리치여도 굴러가다 보면 좋은날 오겠지 <br>내 꿈을 찾아서 내사랑 찾아서 나는 자유로운 새처럼 맘껏 하늘을 날고싶어 <br><br>굴러 난 굴러간다 내 몸이 부서져 한줌의 흙이 되도 <br>굴러 난 굴러간다 내 사랑 찾아서 내 꿈을 찾아서 <br><br>움추렸던 가슴을 활짝 펴 이젠 나의길을 가는거야 <br>멈추지마 멈추지마 멈추지마 꿈꾸는 돌멩이 <br>달려라 돌멩이 날아라 돌멩이 <br><br>굴러 난 굴러간다 내 몸이 부서져 한줌의 흙이되도 <br>굴러 난 굴러간다 내 사랑 찾아서 내 꿈을 찾아서 어어어 <br><br>랄라랄라랄라 <br>랄라랄라랄라라 <br>랄라랄라랄라 <br>힘내라 돌멩이]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="돌멩이" label="돌멩이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/사랑해요/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 사랑해요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:35:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:35:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="발라드 공장 - 사랑해요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[스쳐가나요 우리의 사랑은 가슴 아픈 추억인가요 <br>돌아서네요 그대의 마음은 눈물로도 잡을순 없나요 <br><br>My love 사랑해요 사랑해요 그대 듣고 있나요 <br>My love 잊지 말아요 지우지 말아요 우리의 사랑을 <br><br>나의 눈물이 그대 보이나요 하루하루 그리워합니다 <br>가슴 떨리던 그대 입맞춤도 이제는 추억이 됐나봐요 <br><br>My love 사랑해요 사랑해요 그대 듣고 있나요 <br>My love 잊지 말아요 지우지 말아요 우리의 사랑을 <br><br>매일 난 그리움속에 하루를 버티는데 그댄 어딨나요 <br><br>내가 미안해요 미안해요 그댈 잊지 못해서 <br>My love 돌아와줘요 떠나지 말아요 내 곁에서 <br><br>제발]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="사랑해요" label="사랑해요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/물고기자리/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 물고기자리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:36:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:36:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EB%AC%BC%EA%B3%A0%EA%B8%B0%EC%9E%90%EB%A6%AC/" title="발라드 공장 - 물고기자리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[혹시 그대가 어쩌다가 사랑에 지쳐 어쩌다가 <br>어느 이름모를 낯선 곳에 날 혼자두진 않겠죠 <br>비에 젖어도 꽃은 피고 구름가려도 별은 뜨니 <br>그대에게 애써 묻지않아도 그게 사랑인걸 믿죠 <br><br>저기 하늘끝에 떠 있는 별처럼 <br>해뜨면 사라지는 그런 나 되기 싫어요 <br><br>사랑한다면 저 별처럼 항상 거기서 빛을 줘요 <br>그대 눈부신 사랑에 두눈 멀어도 돼 <br>하늘에 박힌 저 별처럼 당신의 아픔으로 묶여 <br>움직일 수가 없지만 난 변하지 않을테니 <br><br>작은 꽃잎위에 맺힌 이슬처럼 <br>해뜨면 사라지는 그런 나 되기 싫어요 <br><br>사랑한다면 저 별처럼 항상 거기서 빛을 줘요 <br>그대 눈부신 사랑에 두눈 멀어도 돼 <br>하늘에 박힌 저 별처럼 당신의 아픔으로 묶여 <br>움직일 수가 없지만 난 변하지 않을테니 <br><br>비에 젖어도 꽃은 피고 구름가려도 별은 뜨니 <br>묻지 않아도 난 알아요 그대 내 사랑인 걸 <br>작은 꽃잎에 이슬처럼 저기 하늘끝 저 별처럼 <br>다시 해뜨면 사라지는 내가 되긴 싫어요 <br>변하지 않을테니]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="물고기자리" label="물고기자리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/꿈에/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 꿈에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:36:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:36:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EA%BF%88%EC%97%90/" title="발라드 공장 - 꿈에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어떤 말을 해야하는지 난 너무 가슴이 떨려서 <br>우리 옛날 그대로의 모습으로 만나고 있네요 <br><br>이건 꿈인 걸 알지만 지금 이대로 깨지 않고서 영원히 잠 잘 수 있다면 <br>날 안아주네요 예전 모습처럼 그동안 힘들었지 나를 보며 위로하네요 <br>내 손을 잡네요 지친 맘 쉬라며 지금도 그대 손은 그때처럼 따뜻하네요 <br><br>혹시 이게 꿈이란 걸 그대가 알게 하진 않을거야 <br>내가 정말 잘할거야, 그대 다른 생각 못하도록 <br>그대 이젠 가지마요, 그냥 여기서 나와 있어줘요 <br>나도 깨지 않을게요, 이젠 보내지 않을거예요 <br><br>계속 나를 안아주세요 예전 모습처럼 그동안 힘들었지 나를 보며 위로하네요 <br>내 손을 잡네요 지친 맘 이젠 쉬라며 지금도 그대 손은 그때처럼 따뜻하네요 <br>대답해줘요 그대도 나를 나만큼 그리워했다고 <br><br>아 예~~~~~~~~~~오~~~~ <br><br>바보같이 즐거워만 하는 날 보며 (날 보며) 안스런 미소로 (슬픈 미소로) <br>이제 나 먼저갈게 미안한 듯 얘길하네요. <br>나처럼 그대도(그대도) 알고 있었군요(꿈이라는 걸) <br>그래도 고마워요, 이렇게라도 만나줘서. <br><br>날 안아주네요 작별인사라며 나 웃어줄게요 이렇게 보내긴 싫은데 <br>뒤돌아 서네요 다시 그때처럼 나 잠 깨고 나면 또 다시 혼자 있겠네요 <br>저 멀리 가네요 이젠 익숙하죠 나 이제 울게요 또 다시 보내기 싫은데 <br><br>보이지 않아요. 오~~예~~~ <br><br>이제 다시 눈을 떴는데 가슴이 많이 시리네요. <br>고마워요. 사랑해요. <br>나 괜찮아요. 다신 오지 말아요.]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="꿈에" label="꿈에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/거친_인생/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 거친 인생 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:36:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:36:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EA%B1%B0%EC%B9%9C_%EC%9D%B8%EC%83%9D/" title="발라드 공장 - 거친 인생 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이젠 비웃지마라 가진게 없다지만 <br>마음은 세상 가장 따뜻한 남자야 <br>욕하지마라 이런 날 탓하지마라 <br>오직 단 하나뿐인 순정이 있으니 <br><br>이 삶을 선택한건 내가 아니야 <br>첨부터 정해져있던 거친 내 인생 <br>하지만 후회는 없이 살았지 <br>어떤 남자보다도 뜨거운 가슴안고 <br><br>그러던 나에게 너무 순수한 너를 준거야 <br>한번도 몰랐던 가슴 뛰는 사랑을 <br><br>비웃지마라 가진게 없다지만 <br>마음은 세상 가장 따뜻한 남자야 <br>욕하지마라 이런 날 탓하지마라 <br>오직 단 하나뿐인 순정이 있으니 <br><br>너아닌 누구도 나를 웃게한 사람 없잖아 <br>낯설은 행복을 내게 줘서 고맙다 <br><br>상처 가득한 인생에 나 울지만 <br>아무도 나를 쓰러트릴순 없잖아 <br>다시 일어나 세상과 맞서볼테다 <br>다시 소리쳐 본다 <br><br>비웃지마라 가진게 없다지만 <br>마음은 세상 가장 따뜻한 남자야 <br>욕하지마라 이런 날 탓하지마라 <br>오직 단 하나뿐인 순정이 있으니]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="거친 인생" label="거친 인생"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/안녕이라고_말하지마/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 안녕이라고 말하지마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:36:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:36:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%95%88%EB%85%95%EC%9D%B4%EB%9D%BC%EA%B3%A0_%EB%A7%90%ED%95%98%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88/" title="발라드 공장 - 안녕이라고 말하지마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[떨리는 너의 입술을 난 난 처음 보았지 <br>무슨 말 하려고 말 하려고 오 뜸만 들이는지 <br>슬픈 예감은 다 맞는단 노래 가사처럼 <br>설마 아니겠지 아닐꺼야 오 아니어야만 돼 <br><br>벌써 넌 나를 떠나 니 마음마저 떠나 또 몸마저도 떠나는데 <br>난 몰라 널 잡을 방법을 좀 누가 내게 말해줘요 <br><br>오늘밤 그 말만은 말아요 왜 날 버리고 갔나요 <br>나 마음이 아파 가슴이 아파 눈물 차올라요 <br>아직은 안녕 우린 안돼요 넌 그 입을 더 열지마 <br>안녕이라고 내게 말하지마 <br><br>차가운 너의 한마디가 날 주저앉혔지 <br>세상 무너질 듯 무너진 듯 오 눈물만 눈물만 <br><br>지금 순간이 가면 이 순간이 지나면 영영 우린 이별인데 <br>사랑해 죽도록 사랑한 날 날 버리지 말아줘요 <br><br>오늘밤 그 말만은 말아요 왜 날 버리고 갔나요 <br>나 마음이 아파 가슴이 아파 눈물 차올라요 <br>아직은 안녕 우린 안돼요 넌 그 입을 더 열지마 <br>안녕이라고 내게 말하지마 <br><br>이별이 뭔지 나는 몰라요 그냥 서럽고 서러워 <br>나 사연이 많아 추억이 많아 가슴 찢어져요 <br><br>아직은 안녕 우린 안돼요 넌 그 입을 더 열지마 <br>안녕이라고 내게 말하지마 안녕이라고 내게 말하지마]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="안녕이라고 말하지마" label="안녕이라고 말하지마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/비와_당신/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 비와 당신 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:36:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:36:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EB%B9%84%EC%99%80_%EB%8B%B9%EC%8B%A0/" title="발라드 공장 - 비와 당신 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이젠 당신이 그립지 않죠 <br>보고 싶은 마음도 없죠 <br>사랑한 것도 잊혀 가네요 조용하게 <br>알 수 없는 건 그런 내 맘이 <br>비가 오면 눈물이 나요 <br>아주 오래 전 당신 떠나던 그날처럼 <br><br>이젠 괜찮은데 사랑 따윈 저버렸는데 <br>바보 같은 난 눈물이 날까 <br><br>아련해지는 빛 바랜 추억 <br>그 얼마나 사무친 건지 <br>미운 당신을 아직도 나는 그리워하네 <br><br>이젠 괜찮은데 사랑 따윈 저버렸는데 <br>바보 같은난 눈물이 날까 <br><br>다신 안 올 텐데 잊지 못한 내가 싫은데 <br>언제까지 내 맘은 아플까 <br><br>이젠 괜찮은데 사랑 따윈 저버렸는데 <br>바보 같은 난 눈물이 날까]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="비와 당신" label="비와 당신"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/여수_밤바다/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 여수 밤바다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:36:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:36:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EC%97%AC%EC%88%98_%EB%B0%A4%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%A4/" title="발라드 공장 - 여수 밤바다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여수 밤바다 이 조명에 담긴 <br>아름다운 얘기가 있어 <br>네게 들려주고파 전활 걸어 <br>뭐하고 있냐고 <br>나는 지금 여수 밤바다 여수 밤바다 <br><br>아 아 아 아 아 아 아 <br>너와 함께 걷고 싶다 <br>이 바다를 너와 함께 걷고 싶어 <br>이 거리를 너와 함께 걷고 싶다 <br>이 바다를 너와 함께 걷고 싶어 <br>여수 밤바다 <br><br>여수 밤바다 이 바람에 걸린 <br>알 수 없는 향기가 있어 <br>네게 전해주고파 전활 걸어 <br>뭐하고 있냐고 <br>나는 지금 여수 밤바다 여수 밤바다 <br><br>아 아 아 아 아 아 아 <br>너와 함께 걷고 싶다 <br>이 바다를 너와 함께 걷고 싶어 <br>이 거리를 너와 함께 걷고 싶다 <br>이 바다를 너와 함께 너와 함께 오 <br><br>바다 이 조명에 담긴 아름다운 얘기가 있어 <br>네게 들려주고파 전활 걸어 뭐하고 있냐고 <br>나는 지금 여수 밤바다 여수 밤바다 <br><br>아 바다 아아아 하아아아 <br>하아오오 하 아아아 허오 아아아아 <br><br>뭐하고 있냐고 나는 지금 여수 밤바다]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="여수 밤바다" label="여수 밤바다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/기억상실/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 기억상실 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:36:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:36:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EA%B8%B0%EC%96%B5%EC%83%81%EC%8B%A4/" title="발라드 공장 - 기억상실 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[떠난다고 그래서 떠나라고 말했어 <br>사랑하다 한번쯤 하는 말이라서 <br>올 거라고 다 안다고 거울에 비친 나를 달래고 <br>벌써 손가락 열개를 다 접고 애써 하루를 또 세어도 <br><br>보이지 않아 아직도 내 사랑 하나 못찾고 <br>더듬거리는 손으로 네 사진을 찾다가 <br>자꾸 멀어버리는 내 눈은 한참 눈물 쏟아내고 <br>내 맘은 지독한 멍이 생기고 <br><br>잊으라고 그래서 안된다고 말했어 <br>살아가다 한번쯤 만날 것 같아서 <br>나 운다고 아프다고 어느새 지친 소릴 내보고 <br>(네가 걸어오던 길에서) 멈춰서 <br>(안아주던 곳에서) 난 눈물을 닦아봐도 <br><br>보이지 않아 아직도 내 사랑 하나 못찾고 <br>더듬거리는 손으로 네 사진을 찾다가 (그 사진을 보다가) <br>자꾸 멀어버리는 내 눈은 한참 눈물 쏟아내고 <br>내 맘은 지독한 멍이 생기고 <br><br>사랑에 부딪혀 (부딪혀) <br>네가 깊게 새긴 네가 소리없이 남긴 (네가 소리없이 남긴) <br>너란 상처들로 덮힌 나를 불쌍하다고 느낀다면 (불쌍하다고) <br>미안하다 느끼면 (느낀다면) 다시 날 사랑할까 <br><br>화장을 하고 지우고 옷을 꺼내고 입어도 <br>아무리 해도 하나도 기억할 수 없나봐 (너를 기억할수 없나봐) <br>사랑한다는 말도 들었던 웃는 내 모습을 찾고 (내 모습을 찾고) <br>돌아올 널 위해 내가 같아야만 하는데 <br>조금도 (조금도) 기억이 (기억이) 나지를 않아]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="기억상실" label="기억상실"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/발라드_공장/나를_외치다/</id><title>발라드 공장 - 나를 외치다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:36:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:36:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%93%9C_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EC%99%B8%EC%B9%98%EB%8B%A4/" title="발라드 공장 - 나를 외치다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새벽이 오는 소리 눈을 비비고 일어나 <br>곁에 잠든 너의 얼굴 보면서 <br>힘을 내야지 절대 쓰러질 순 없어 <br>그런 마음으로 하루를 시작하는데 <br>꿈도 꾸었었지 뜨거웠던 가슴으로 <br>하지만 시간이 나를 버린 걸까 <br>두근거리는 나의 심장은 아직도 이렇게 뛰는데 <br><br>절대로 약해지면 안된다는 말 대신 <br>뒤쳐지면 안된다는 말 대신 <br>오~지금 이순간 끝이 아니라 <br>나의 길을 가고 있다고 외치면 되 <br><br>지쳐버린 어깨 거울 속에 비친 내가 <br>어쩌면 이렇게 초라해 보일까 <br>똑같은 시간 똑같은 공간에 <br>왜이렇게 변해 버린걸까 <br><br>끝이 있는 걸까 시작뿐인 내인생에 <br>걱정이 앞서는 건 또 왜일까 <br>강해지자고 뒤돌아보지 말자고 <br>앞만 보고 달려 가자고 <br><br>절대로 약해지면 안된다는 말 대신 <br>뒤쳐지면 안된다는 말 대신 <br>오~지금 이순간 끝이 아니라 <br>나의 길을 가고 있다고 외치면 되 <br><br>오~ 지금 이 순간 끝이 아니라 <br>나의 길을 가고 있다고 외치면 되 <br><br>약해지면 안된다는 말 대신 <br>뒤쳐지면 안된다는 말 대신 <br>약해지면 안된다는 말 대신 <br>뒤쳐지면 안된다는 말 대신 <br>나의 길을 간다고]]></content><category term="발라드 공장" label="발라드 공장"/><category term="나를 외치다" label="나를 외치다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/All_Around_The_World_67_Ver_Feat_Desiigner__67/</id><title>Mura Masa - All Around The World (67 Ver.) (Feat. Desiigner &amp; 67) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:36:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:36:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/All_Around_The_World_67_Ver_Feat_Desiigner__67/" title="Mura Masa - All Around The World (67 Ver.) (Feat. Desiigner &amp; 67) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This goes for all around the world <br>To the world is gone <br>This go all around the world <br>So we carry on <br>This goes for all around the world <br>To the world is gone <br>This go all around the world <br>So we carry on, git, git <br>Thank God I got it <br>Thank God, yeah, nigga, I got it <br>Thank God, cut the trills, they watchin' <br>Thank God I be gettin', can't stop it <br>Thank God I got it <br>Thank God I be countin' this money <br>Thank God, thinkin', livin', they funny <br>Livin' close, yeah and countin' these hundreds, oh shit <br>I be livin' life on the ball shit <br>I'ma cop me a wheel and I ghost it <br>Black and white, it's the panda, the ghost is <br>Give a toast to the Grammy's, I go shit <br>All night with the bag <br>All night with the swag <br>All night with the bag <br>All <br><br>This goes for all around the world <br>To the world is gone <br>This go all around the world <br>So we carry on <br>This goes for all around the world <br>To the world is gone <br>This go all around the world <br>So we carry on, git, git <br>They say I go, got it, I go, get <br>I'm on top of the world on my ball shit <br>In the party, get it started, get retarded <br>Baby what's your favorite car, the Aston Martin <br>Gotta hit on the gas just to get it started <br>Gotta kick on the gas just to get it started <br>Hear the 'Rari, hear it mumble, hear it roar <br>Say that she hate monsters <br>Engine started, she hate monsters <br>Engine farted, she hate monsters <br>Get retarded, I've been chillin' <br>I drink out and go to Beamers <br>Lord I need it, Lord I need it, Lord I need it <br>Got them mad 'cause I drill and they all defeated <br>I be ridin', keep sayin', Lord, 'cause I need it <br>Lord I need it, Lord I need it, Lord I need it <br>'Cause he help me come back from all my demons <br><br>This goes for all around the world <br>To the world is gone <br>This go all around the world <br>So we carry on <br>This goes for all around the world <br>To the world is gone <br>This go all around the world <br>So we carry on]]></content><category term="Mura Masa" label="Mura Masa"/><category term="All Around The World (67 Ver.) (Feat. Desiigner &amp; 67)" label="All Around The World (67 Ver.) (Feat. Desiigner &amp; 67)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JDale/Living_in_my_world/</id><title>J.Dale - Living in my world - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:37:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:37:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JDale/Living_in_my_world/" title="J.Dale - Living in my world - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[시간이 쉴새 없이 흘러가 <br>계절은 바뀌어가고 <br>여전히 난 변한 것 하나 없지만 <br>흐르는 대로 그저 흘러가 <br>내 본능적인 욕망이 <br>내 삶을 가득 채울 때 <br>그 삶의 끝엔 후회이지만 <br>사랑이 가득한 인생의 끝에는 <br>좋은 추억과 따뜻함이 남지 <br>현실과 동떨어진 꿈인 걸 알아 <br>모두가 외면할거라는 것도 알아 <br>세상을 모른다 그 누가 뭐래도 <br>I’m I’m living in my world <br>I’m living in my world oh oh <br>I’m living in my world oh oh <br>I’m living in my world oh oh <br>I’m living in my world oh oh <br>I’m living in my world oh <br>ohohohoh <br>I’m living in my world oh <br>ohohohoh <br>I’m living in my world oh <br>ohohohoh <br>I’m living in my world oh <br>ohohohoh <br>I’m living in my world <br>숨겨왔던 모든 꿈을 세상에 외칠 때 <br>사람들이 모두 외면해도 But <br>Your dream is a prize for living <br>in this world <br>Then don’t look back anymore <br>현실과 동떨어진 꿈인 걸 알아 <br>모두가 외면할거라는 것도 알아 <br>세상을 모른다 그 누가 뭐래도 <br>I’m I’m living in my world <br>I’m living in my world oh oh <br>I’m living in my world oh oh <br>I’m living in my world oh oh <br>I’m living in my world oh oh <br>I’m living in my world oh <br>ohohohoh <br>I’m living in my world oh <br>ohohohoh <br>I’m living in my world oh <br>ohohohoh <br>I’m living in my world oh <br>ohohohoh <br>Yeah living in my world <br>I’m living in my world oh oh <br>I’m living in my world oh oh <br>I’m living in my world <br>]]></content><category term="J.Dale" label="J.Dale"/><category term="Living in my world" label="Living in my world"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김덕팔/안아줘/</id><title>김덕팔 - 안아줘 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:37:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:37:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%8D%95%ED%8C%94/%EC%95%88%EC%95%84%EC%A4%98/" title="김덕팔 - 안아줘 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 잘 모르겠어 네가 있을 땐 <br>아무렇지 않은 척 하고 있을 땐 <br>네가 옆에 있을 때도 <br>너의 곁에 있고 싶게 만들어 널 <br>안아주고 싶어 널 보고 있을 땐 <br>널 보고 있으면 널 안고 싶은 걸 bae <br>Yes alright you so shine <br>네가 앞에 있으니까 <br>네게 닿고 싶으니까 <br>너를 안고 싶으니까 <br>안아줘 더 안아줘 날 <br>지금 네가 느낀 감정은 어때 <br>안아줘 더 안아줘 날 <br>지금 내게 말해 <br>right now right now <br>안아줘 더 안아줘 날 <br>나와 같다면 나와 같다면 <br>안아줘 더 안아줘 날 <br>그렇다면 내게 말해줘 <br>나 왜이래 왜 이러는지 <br>나조차도 모르겠어 <br>난 궁금해 넌 어때 어때 어때 어때 <br>널 바라만 보고 있어 <br>전혀 티 내지도 못해 <br>이렇게 널 안아만 <br>주고 싶은 나인데 <br>널 보고 있으면 널 안고 싶은 걸 bae <br>Yes alright you so shine <br>네가 앞에 있으니까 <br>네게 닿고 싶으니까 <br>너를 안고 싶으니까 <br>안아줘 더 안아줘 날 <br>지금 니가 느낀 감정은 어때 <br>안아줘 더 안아줘 날 <br>지금 내게 말해 <br>right now right now <br>안아줘 더 안아줘 날 <br>나와 같다면 나와 같다면 <br>안아줘 더 안아줘 날 <br>그렇다면 내게 말해줘 <br>Bae yea 이 감정이 <br>bae yea 이 떨림이 yea <br>지금 우리 이 느낌이 똑같다면 <br>나와 같다면 주저 하지 않아도 돼 <br>너를 안을 수 있게 다가와줘 내게 <br>널 보고 있으면 널 안고 싶은 걸 bae <br>Yes alright you so shine <br>네가 앞에 있으니까 <br>네게 닿고 싶으니까 <br>너를 안고 싶으니까 <br>안아줘 더 안아줘 날 <br>지금 니가 느낀 감정은 어때 <br>안아줘 더 안아줘 날 <br>지금 내게 말해 <br>right now right now <br>안아줘 더 안아줘 날 <br>나와 같다면 나와 같다면 <br>안아줘 더 안아줘 날 <br>그렇다면 내게 말해줘 <br>]]></content><category term="김덕팔" label="김덕팔"/><category term="안아줘" label="안아줘"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송유경/핑계대지마/</id><title>송유경 - 핑계대지마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:37:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:37:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EC%9C%A0%EA%B2%BD/%ED%95%91%EA%B3%84%EB%8C%80%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88/" title="송유경 - 핑계대지마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이런 저런 핑계대지마 <br>그런 저런 핑계대지마 <br>속 시원히 말을 해봐요 <br>왜 나를 피하는지 <br>이별이 두렵나요 두려운가요 <br>아픔이 싫어선가요 <br>자꾸만 피한다고 <br>될일은 아니지요 <br>그래도 얘긴해야죠 <br>싫으면 싫다고 해요 <br>가슴은 아플지라도 <br>끝낼건 끝내야겠죠 <br>눈물을 흘릴지라도 <br>핑계만 대지말아요 <br>사랑 사랑 사랑 사랑 사랑이 <br>이별 이별 이별 이별이 되도 <br>이렇게 지내는 건 싫어요 <br>핑계만 대지말아요 <br>이런 저런 핑계대지마 <br>그런 저런 핑계대지마 <br>속 시원히 말을 해봐요 <br>왜 나를 피하는지 <br>이런 저런 핑계대지마 <br>그런 저런 핑계대지마 <br>속 시원히 말을 해봐요 <br>왜 나를 피하는지 <br>이별이 두렵나요 두려운가요 <br>아픔이 싫어선가요 <br>자꾸만 피한다고 <br>될일은 아니지요 <br>그래도 얘긴해야죠 <br>싫으면 싫다고 해요 <br>가슴은 아플지라도 <br>끝낼건 끝내야겠죠 <br>눈물을 흘릴지라도 <br>핑계만 대지말아요 <br>사랑 사랑 사랑 사랑 사랑이 <br>이별 이별 이별 이별이 되도 <br>이렇게 지내는 건 싫어요 <br>핑계만 대지말아요 <br>이런 저런 핑계대지마 <br>그런 저런 핑계대지마 <br>속 시원히 말을 해봐요 <br>왜 나를 피하는지 <br>왜 나를 피하는지 <br>]]></content><category term="송유경" label="송유경"/><category term="핑계대지마" label="핑계대지마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송유경/사랑의_부산항_추억의_요코하마항/</id><title>송유경 - 사랑의 부산항 추억의 요코하마항 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:37:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:37:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EC%9C%A0%EA%B2%BD/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%98_%EB%B6%80%EC%82%B0%ED%95%AD_%EC%B6%94%EC%96%B5%EC%9D%98_%EC%9A%94%EC%BD%94%ED%95%98%EB%A7%88%ED%95%AD/" title="송유경 - 사랑의 부산항 추억의 요코하마항 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꽃피는 봄이 오면 <br>내발길은 나도 몰래 부산항으로 <br>그리운 당신이 나를 기다리던 <br>부둣가로 걸어 갑니다 <br>둘이서 커피향에 함께 취하던 <br>그 찻집 그 자리에 <br>그리운 당신이 내게 미소 짓던 곳 <br>나 혼자 앉아 봅니다 <br>팔짱을 정답게 끼고 <br>둘이서 늘 같이 걷던 추억의 바닷가 <br>나 홀로 거닐면서 당신 그려 봅니다 <br>돌아와요 부산항에 <br>노랠 불러주던 내 사랑 <br>못잊어 못잊어서 <br>내 발길은 부산항으로 <br>눈부신 봄이 오면 <br>내발길은 나도 몰래 요코하마로 <br>보고픈 당신이 나를 기다리던 <br>바닷가로 걸어 갑니다 <br>둘이서 술향기에 함께 취하던 <br>그 술집 그 자리에 <br>그리운 당신이 나를 웃게 했던 곳 <br>나혼자 앉아 봅니다 <br>화려한 네온사인 아래 <br>둘이서 늘 같이 걷던 낭만의 밤거리 <br>나 홀로 거닐면서 당신 그려 봅니다 <br>블루 라이트 요코하마 <br>노랠 불러주던 내 사랑 <br>보고파 보고파서 <br>내 발길은 요코 하마로 <br>못잊어 못잊어서 <br>내 발길은 부산항으로 <br>]]></content><category term="송유경" label="송유경"/><category term="사랑의 부산항 추억의 요코하마항" label="사랑의 부산항 추억의 요코하마항"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송유경/봄꽃향연/</id><title>송유경 - 봄꽃향연 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:37:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:37:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EC%9C%A0%EA%B2%BD/%EB%B4%84%EA%BD%83%ED%96%A5%EC%97%B0/" title="송유경 - 봄꽃향연 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[화사한 봄 꽃들이 눈부신 하늘 아래 <br>오색 빛 꽃잎 되어 바람에 휘날리네 <br>달콤한 꽃 향기는 허공에 가득하고 <br>우리들 사랑은 새롭게 태어나네 <br>아 <br>꽃 비가 쏟아지는 공원의 오솔길을 <br>노래를 부르면서 랄랄랄라 걸어가네 <br>꽃 향기에 취해버린 우리 사랑 <br>꽃 구름 되어버린 우리 사랑 <br>아 아 아 아 아 <br>오늘은 봄 꽃 향연 <br>연초록 꽃잎들이 신나게 춤을 추는 <br>강변 길 언덕에는 꽃 보라 휘날리네 <br>두 손을 마주잡고 즐겁게 거니는데 <br>꽃 바람 불어와서 꽃 나비 되었네요 <br>아 <br>꽃 비가 쏟아지는 공원의 오솔길을 <br>노래를 부르면서 랄랄랄라 걸어가네 <br>꽃 향기에 취해버린 우리 사랑 <br>꽃 구름 되어버린 우리 사랑 <br>아 아 아 아 아 <br>오늘은 봄 꽃 향연 <br>]]></content><category term="송유경" label="송유경"/><category term="봄꽃향연" label="봄꽃향연"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송유경/나만의_사랑/</id><title>송유경 - 나만의 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:37:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:37:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EC%9C%A0%EA%B2%BD/%EB%82%98%EB%A7%8C%EC%9D%98_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="송유경 - 나만의 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어쩌다가 이렇게 만나 <br>정이 들 줄 알았다면 <br>차라리 말을 해볼걸 <br>그대가 나를 속태운다고 <br>말이나 해볼 걸 한마디 못하고 <br>가슴만 태우네요 <br>아아아 이 가슴 어떡하나요 <br>나만의 사랑 그대여 <br>어쩌다가 이렇게 만나 <br>애가 탈줄 알았다면 <br>차라리 말을 해볼걸 <br>그대가 나를 속태운다고 <br>말이나 해볼 걸 한마디 못하고 <br>가슴만 태우네요 <br>아아아 이 가슴 어떡하나요 <br>나만의 사랑 그대여 <br>말이나 해볼 걸 한마디 못하고 <br>가슴만 태우네요 <br>아아아 이 가슴 어떡하나요 <br>나만의 사랑 그대여 <br>나만의 사랑 그대여 <br>]]></content><category term="송유경" label="송유경"/><category term="나만의 사랑" label="나만의 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송유경/당신의_사랑/</id><title>송유경 - 당신의 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:37:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:37:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EC%9C%A0%EA%B2%BD/%EB%8B%B9%EC%8B%A0%EC%9D%98_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="송유경 - 당신의 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그땐 몰랐죠 당신의 사랑 <br>그렇게 큰 줄 몰랐죠 <br>세월 지나 알게 되었죠 <br>나만을 사랑해준 걸 <br>이제는 알아요 당신의 사랑 <br>참 많이 고생했어요 <br>눈빛 그 속엔 진실한 사랑 <br>가득이 찬 걸 알아요 <br>사랑해요 사랑합니다 <br>당신 하나만을 사랑합니다 <br>알아요 알아요 당신의 사랑 <br>당신의 그 사랑 <br>그땐 몰랐죠 당신의 사랑 <br>그렇게 힘이 들 줄은 <br>세월 지나 알게 되었죠 <br>나만을 위해서란 걸 <br>이제는 알아요 당신의 사랑 <br>참 많이 고생했어요 <br>눈빛 그 속엔 진실한 사랑 <br>가득이 찬 걸 알아요 <br>사랑해요 사랑합니다 <br>당신 하나만을 사랑합니다 <br>알아요 알아요 당신의 사랑 <br>당신의 그 사랑 <br>이제는 알아요 당신의 사랑 <br>참 많이 고생했어요 <br>눈빛 그 속엔 진실한 사랑 <br>가득이 찬 걸 알아요 <br>사랑해요 사랑합니다 <br>당신 하나만을 사랑합니다 <br>알아요 알아요 당신의 사랑 <br>당신의 그 사랑 <br>당신의 그 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="송유경" label="송유경"/><category term="당신의 사랑" label="당신의 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송유경/그래_그래요/</id><title>송유경 - 그래 그래요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:37:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:37:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EC%9C%A0%EA%B2%BD/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%98_%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%98%EC%9A%94/" title="송유경 - 그래 그래요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이렇게도 사랑이 <br>나를 울려 울려요 <br>너무나 가슴 아파요 <br>이런 게 사랑이면 <br>그런 게 사랑이면 <br>시작은 하지 말 걸 그랬죠 <br>그래요 그래요 보내 드리죠 <br>그래요 그래요 떠나 가세요 <br>뒤돌아 보지 말고 떠나요 <br>아무런 말 말아요 <br>그래 그래요 그래 그래요 <br>아무 말도 하지 말고 떠나요 <br>눈물은 흘리지 않게 <br>이렇게도 사랑이 <br>나를 울려 울려요 <br>너무나 가슴 아파요 <br>이런 게 사랑이면 <br>그런 게 사랑이면 <br>시작은 하지 말 걸 그랬죠 <br>그래요 그래요 보내 드리죠 <br>그래요 그래요 떠나 가세요 <br>뒤돌아 보지 말고 떠나요 <br>아무런 말 말아요 <br>그래 그래요 그래 그래요 <br>아무 말도 하지 말고 떠나요 <br>눈물은 흘리지 않게 <br>그래 그래요 그래 그래요 <br>아무 말도 하지 말고 떠나요 <br>눈물은 흘리지 않게 <br>]]></content><category term="송유경" label="송유경"/><category term="그래 그래요" label="그래 그래요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/키스엔_KissN/내게말해_Love_like_i_do_Feat_하이솔/</id><title>키스엔 (KissN) - 내게말해 (Love like i do) (Feat. 하이솔) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:39:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:39:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%82%A4%EC%8A%A4%EC%97%94_KissN/%EB%82%B4%EA%B2%8C%EB%A7%90%ED%95%B4_Love_like_i_do_Feat_%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%EC%86%94/" title="키스엔 (KissN) - 내게말해 (Love like i do) (Feat. 하이솔) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[hey you <br>난 새로운걸 찾고 있어 <br>그게 바로 너 인거 같애 <br>hey you 이 stage <br>이 노래가 끝나면 <br>no no no no <br>믿기지 않겠지만 oh <br>난 니 앞으로 걸어가 <br>사랑을 말해 I do <br>I know there somebody <br>now love like I do <br>i like this <br>리듬에 맡겨줘요 <br>give it up give it up <br>I know there somebody <br>now love like I do <br>넌 내게 말해 넌 내게만 해 <br>love me love me love me <br>now love like I do <br>내게만 속삭여줄래요 <br>넌 내게 말해 넌 내게만 해 <br>love me love me <br>love me now love like I do <br>날 놓치지 않았으면 해 <br>love like I do <br>oh 나의 star 한번도 없었어 <br>just loser 내게 니가 없다면 <br>oh need somebody love you <br>wannabe somebody love you baby <br>내게만 내게만 넌 내게 빠져버렸어 <br>내게 지금 당장 떠나자면 <br>나는 바로 갈래 바라보는 내내 <br>get hooked on yrah yeah <br>꿀 떨어지니까 널 사랑하니까 <br>너와 나 함께라면 <br>어디든 작품이 될 테니까 <br>baby you baby you baby you baby <br>hurry up hurry up hurry up baby <br>매일 아침 네 옆자리에 <br>날 보고 싶다면 지금 내게 말해 <br>love I do <br>사랑을 말해 I do <br>I know there somebody <br>now love like I do <br>i like this <br>리듬에 맡겨줘요 <br>give it up give it up <br>I know there somebody <br>now love like I do <br>넌 내게 말해 넌 내게만 해 <br>love me love me love me <br>now love like I do <br>내게만 속삭여줄래요 <br>넌 내게 말해 넌 내게만 해 <br>love me love me <br>love me now love like I do <br>날 놓치지 않았으면 해 <br>love like I do <br>]]></content><category term="키스엔 (KissN)" label="키스엔 (KissN)"/><category term="내게말해 (Love like i do) (Feat. 하이솔)" label="내게말해 (Love like i do) (Feat. 하이솔)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박동훈/환절기/</id><title>박동훈 - 환절기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:39:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:39:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EB%8F%99%ED%9B%88/%ED%99%98%EC%A0%88%EA%B8%B0/" title="박동훈 - 환절기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[손쓸 틈 없이 <br>가늘어져 버린 시간 <br>이전의 너는 <br>늘 그렇듯 사라져 가고 <br>흐르는 순간에 <br>가만히 선을 맞출 때 <br>어느덧 짙어져 오는 <br>새로운 너와 함께 <br>그래야겠지 <br>늘 변함없이 새로운 <br>그 모습으로 <br>날 찾아오는 너에게 <br>내 맘이 물들어 <br>더욱더 영글어가는 <br>나를 보여주고픈 <br>맘을 가져야겠지 <br>코끝에 닿는 <br>익숙한 간지러움에 <br>창문을 열어 <br>다가올 너를 맞이해 <br>이제는 하루가 <br>다시 달라질 것 같은 <br>작은 기대감 속에 <br>바뀐 이 계절 속에 <br>]]></content><category term="박동훈" label="박동훈"/><category term="환절기" label="환절기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박동훈/그녀는_아름다워/</id><title>박동훈 - 그녀는 아름다워 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:39:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:39:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EB%8F%99%ED%9B%88/%EA%B7%B8%EB%85%80%EB%8A%94_%EC%95%84%EB%A6%84%EB%8B%A4%EC%9B%8C/" title="박동훈 - 그녀는 아름다워 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기다릴게 <br>참 아름다운 말이야 <br>찾아오는 거야 <br>누구도 없이 <br>음악을 멈추려 했지만 <br>그러지 못했고 <br>손가락은 자연스레 <br>머리를 훑었어 <br>그 이후는 잘 모르겠어 <br>그녀는 아름다워 <br>그렇지 않아 <br>그녀는 아름다워 <br>낡은 바구니를 들어 <br>가진 모든 것을 엮었어 <br>이렇게도 <br>그녀는 아름다워 <br>구름이 수만 번을 지났어 <br>나는 변하지 않았었네 <br>낡은 집으로 돌아가며 <br>그녀는 아름다워 <br>낡은 바구니를 들어 <br>가진 모든 것을 엮었어 <br>이렇게도 <br>그녀는 아름다워 <br>구름이 수만 번을 지났어 <br>나는 변하지 않았었네 <br>낡은 집으로 돌아가며 <br>그녀는 아름다워 <br>그렇지 않아 <br>그녀는 아름다워 <br>]]></content><category term="박동훈" label="박동훈"/><category term="그녀는 아름다워" label="그녀는 아름다워"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Godley__Creme/Punchbag/</id><title>Godley &amp; Creme - Punchbag - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:47:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:47:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Godley__Creme/Punchbag/" title="Godley &amp; Creme - Punchbag - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If I brought a note to school <br>That said my days were numbered <br>They'd leave me <br>Numb and bleeding <br>Or strangle me with jump-leads <br>Momma, momma, momma <br>In my world <br>The birds don't sing <br>The bells don't ring <br>The bicycle bells, the bicycle bells <br>Momma, momma, momma, Help me <br>I wish I could blend <br>Into the background <br>I've no excuses for my lack of guts <br>Lack of guts <br>What is it about me <br>That draws attention <br>Fourth form atrocities <br>Punchbag <br>Come and get it Socrates <br>Got to hit back <br>Get down on your knees <br>Ready for the polythene bag <br>I've never been a natural <br>At physical things <br>I've never been good at cross-country running <br>Since the first football hit me in the ear <br>Like a frozen cannonball <br>And the knees buckled <br>And stayed bent <br>And the laughs came <br>And the nerve went <br>And "Dirty Jew" <br>Was written on the blackboard <br>Fourth form atrocities <br>Punchbag <br>Come and get it Socrates <br>Got to hit back <br>Get down on your knees <br>Ready for the polythene <br>Ready for the polythene <br>Ready for the polythene <br>Bag treatment <br>Running through the corridors <br>Far too many obstacles <br>Bursting, bursting <br>Bursting for the crap I know <br>They'll never let me have <br>Fourth form punchbag <br>Oh God I wish that I was <br>Thicker than I am <br>And thinner than I am <br>Oh God I wish that I had <br>Normal ears <br>And clearer skin <br>I'm praying for the day <br>When handsome's out <br>And ugly's in <br>Fourth form punchbag <br>Fourth form punchbag <br>To Jesus I pray <br>For strength to survive <br>Your Christian soldiers <br>Smell blood <br>I torture myself in private <br>To prepare me for the pain <br>I talk to myself in public <br>On the buses and the train <br>My father just ignores it <br>'Cause it goes against the grain <br>Momma, momma, momma, Help me <br>Fourth form punchbag <br>Fourth form punchbag <br>Booming round the corridors <br>Like guadiamus igitur <br>Fourth form punchbag <br>Fourth form punchbag <br>Can <br>I <br>Please <br>Get <br>Up <br>Now <br>No <br>When]]></content><category term="Godley &amp; Creme" label="Godley &amp; Creme"/><category term="Punchbag" label="Punchbag"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Godley__Creme/Group_Life/</id><title>Godley &amp; Creme - Group Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:47:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:47:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Godley__Creme/Group_Life/" title="Godley &amp; Creme - Group Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't have no penpal to write to <br>Don't have no Pentel to write with <br>Don't have no pencil to bite through <br>GROUP LIFE <br>Recording - Mono - 4 Track - 8 Track - 16 - 24 <br>Tours - Clubs - Vans - Crew - Rig - Heap Big Productions <br>Holidays - Blackpool - Antigua - Villas - Weekend - When <br>GONE <br>Oh were we using <br>Or were we used <br>'Cos on a good night <br>When the juices flowed <br>We cruised <br>But on a bad night... <br>Oh Donna, You make me break up <br>You make me break down <br>Am I crazy, Am I mad <br>GROUP LIFE <br>Recording - Grundig - Revox - Teac - Dolby - Helios <br>Press - Shock - Horror - Probe - Split - Yes <br>Hologram - Interesting - Possibilities - Gizmo - Film - Dome <br>Ampex Now <br>Am I crazy <br>Am I mad <br>We are <br>Group life, still life <br>Group life, still life <br>Group life, still life <br>Group life still]]></content><category term="Godley &amp; Creme" label="Godley &amp; Creme"/><category term="Group Life" label="Group Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Godley__Creme/Art_School_Canteen/</id><title>Godley &amp; Creme - Art School Canteen - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:47:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:47:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Godley__Creme/Art_School_Canteen/" title="Godley &amp; Creme - Art School Canteen - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let me tell you what it's all about <br>Walking round with your talent hanging out <br>I'm feeling ragged as a scrubber's tights <br>Must have had too much to paint <br>Last night's routine <br>Art school canteen <br>Art school canteen <br>Art school canteen <br>Come in late and go home earlier <br>One day a week or maybe less <br>So I lied about the funeral <br>I was really playing chess <br>But I was seen <br>By the coffee machine <br>Art school canteen <br>I'd cut my ear off to spite my face <br>But it's been done <br>No, maybe that's too weird <br>I'd better sketch it out on Kodatrace <br>And redesign my beard <br>Does getting into Zappa <br>Mean getting out of Zen <br>Sex has reared its ugly head at last <br>But it didn't look ugly then <br>Begin the Beguine <br>Art school canteen <br>Art school canteen]]></content><category term="Godley &amp; Creme" label="Godley &amp; Creme"/><category term="Art School Canteen" label="Art School Canteen"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Godley__Creme/Sandwiches_Of_You/</id><title>Godley &amp; Creme - Sandwiches Of You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:47:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:47:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Godley__Creme/Sandwiches_Of_You/" title="Godley &amp; Creme - Sandwiches Of You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'd like to know you better <br>And maybe take you home <br>I'd like to meet your father <br>But really not tonight <br>We'll be stopping off at Dayvilles <br>For pistachio and beer <br>It's the flavour of the month but <br>You're my flavour of the year <br><br>I could eat <br>Sandwiches of you <br>You could eat <br>Sandwiches of me <br><br>Oh my papa <br>He will not approve <br>He won't like your car <br>Or the way that you conduct yourself <br>In public <br>Your move <br><br>Shame, shame on you <br>I want to keep this friendship platonic <br>I respect the fact that you're waiting <br>For Mister Right <br>Am I wrong <br>Let's pull over <br>Please let's pull over <br>And discuss the ramifications <br>Of a lasting and complex relationship <br>Like mature and responsible people do <br>Am I getting through <br><br>I could eat <br>Sandwiches of you <br>You could eat <br>Sandwiches of me <br>I could eat <br>Sandwiches of you <br>You could eat <br>Sandwiches of me]]></content><category term="Godley &amp; Creme" label="Godley &amp; Creme"/><category term="Sandwiches Of You" label="Sandwiches Of You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Godley__Creme/This_Sporting_Life/</id><title>Godley &amp; Creme - This Sporting Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:47:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:47:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Godley__Creme/This_Sporting_Life/" title="Godley &amp; Creme - This Sporting Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Are you bored <br>Are you jaded <br>Has all the enthusiasm faded <br>Are you one of those people <br>Like glazed fruit <br>Who sit there in shell-shock <br>Till the dot on your screen disappears <br>Are you one of those people <br>Or are you just afraid <br>Are you one who craves excitement <br>Were you tailor made <br>For this sporting life <br>Living on a knife edge <br>This sporting life's forever changing <br>Are you one of these people <br>The keys please quick <br>Every second counts <br>I've signed the book <br>Gimme the keys <br>The elevator opens its mouth <br>Like Jonah and the whale <br>The elevator spits me out <br>Into a freak show <br>It's a freak show <br>And into a swarm of flies <br>Do.....do not disturb <br>Do.....do not disturb <br>The sign on the door read: <br>Do not disturb <br>Strange looks from the bellman <br>As he takes me down the hallway <br>Through a firedoor to a stairwell <br>Skidding, skidding, skidding, skidding <br>Out of control, out of control <br>Do.....do not disturb <br>Do.....do not disturb <br>The sign on the door read <br>The sign on the door said <br>The sign on the door read <br>Do not disturb <br>This is the Bad Samaritans <br>Hello loved one <br>Sorry there was nobody here <br>To take your call personally <br>However, we understand <br>What you're going through <br>How you've travelled life's highway <br>With your smile on upside-down <br>And now you think you've found <br>The ultimate answer to all your problems <br>Don't be hasty <br>Why waste a life <br>Wait until there's a crowd down below <br>Give a little when you go <br>Are you one of these people <br>Jump jump jump jump jump...... <br>There's a fruitcake in the window <br>Someone fetch the cops <br>For God's sake get a camera <br>Before the bastard drops <br>A little to the left <br>A little to the right <br>A little to the left <br>Maybe tonight's the night <br>Why are we waiting <br>We're waiting <br>A little to the left <br>Right down the middle <br>A little to the right <br>X marks the spot <br>You ain't gonna be <br>On This is Your Life's tonight <br>This sporting life <br>Needs organising <br>We'd gladly lose the cup <br>If we could stick the knife in <br>This sporting life <br>This sporting life <br>This sporting life's forever changing <br>Are you bored <br>Are you jaded <br>Has all enthusiasm faded <br>Are you one of those people]]></content><category term="Godley &amp; Creme" label="Godley &amp; Creme"/><category term="This Sporting Life" label="This Sporting Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Stay_With_Me/</id><title>Sweet - Stay With Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:48:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:48:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Stay_With_Me/" title="Sweet - Stay With Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Why don't you stay with me <br>Come on and play with me <br>You know I'm out of my tree <br><br>Honey, why did you walk away <br>When you knew I had something to say <br>Sittin' here drinking alone <br>Left wondering why you ain't gonna phone <br><br>But I know, baby <br>That you were just sent for me <br>You're driving me crazy <br>I'm begging right down on my knees <br><br>Why don't you stay with me <br>(Yeah) <br>Come on and play with me <br>(Yeah) <br>You know I'm out of my tree <br>Lay down your love <br><br>I ain't satisfied 'cause you never tried <br>When making love was a matter of pride <br>I heard it from friends just the other day <br>That you're coming back, maybe this time you'll stay <br><br>Whenever you're near me <br>I see the truth in your lies <br>Please open your heart to me <br>I'm begging you down on my knees <br><br>Why don't you stay with me <br>(Yeah, yeah) <br>Come on and play with me <br>(Yeah) <br>You know I'm out of my tree <br>(Baby, baby, baby, it's alright) <br>Lay down your love <br>(Alright) <br><br>Falling in love wasn't easy <br>But people need love to survive <br>If I knew then, all the things I know now <br>There'd be more then enough to go 'round <br><br>Why don't you stay with me <br>(Yeah) <br>Come on and play with me <br>(Yeah) <br>You know I'm out of my tree <br>(Baby, baby, baby, it's alright) <br>Lay down your love <br><br>Why don't you stay with me <br>(Yeah) <br>Come on and play with me <br>(Yeah) <br>You know I'm out of my tree <br>(Baby, baby, babe, it's alright) <br>Lay down your love <br><br>Why don't you stay with me <br>(Come on stay with me, baby) <br>Come on and play with me <br>(No, no) <br>You know I'm out of my tree <br>(Oh, come on baby, you know it's alright) <br>Lay down your love <br>(Yeah, whoppie)]]></content><category term="Sweet" label="Sweet"/><category term="Stay With Me" label="Stay With Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Hold_Me/</id><title>Sweet - Hold Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:48:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:48:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Hold_Me/" title="Sweet - Hold Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I packed the bag <br>Said I'm leaving here <br>As I moved on <br>Turning, no waving hands <br>I should have known better <br>Than to believe that she really cared <br>But though I know better <br>When somebody leaves you <br>It isn't the end of the world <br><br>I drew down the blind <br>Tried to get me some sleep <br>Oh, I felt my eyes close <br>And the hurt went away <br>I woke up next morning <br>And a new day was already dawning <br>You're my reason for living <br>You came into my life and you kissed <br>All my heartaches away <br><br>Hold me, hold me <br>So that I can love again <br>Hold me, hold me <br>So that I can love again <br><br>Hold me, hold me <br>So that I can love again <br>Hold me, hold me <br>So that I can love again <br><br>You gave me a new start <br>So I gave you my heart <br>I'll lay down my soul for you <br>I'll weave it to gold for you <br>Don't let me chase rainbows <br>'Cause if you ever leave me <br>It will be the end of the world <br><br>Hold me, hold me <br>So that I can love again <br>Hold me, hold me <br>So that I can love again <br><br>Your love has set me free <br>You make me laugh all day <br>Your love is all I need <br>No way, well I've found mine <br><br>Hold me, hold me <br>So that I can love again <br>Hold me, hold me <br>So that I can love again]]></content><category term="Sweet" label="Sweet"/><category term="Hold Me" label="Hold Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Mother_Earth/</id><title>Sweet - Mother Earth - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:48:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:48:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Mother_Earth/" title="Sweet - Mother Earth - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Smiling eyes in a sea of faces <br>Stealing time for secret places <br>Making love in the afternoon <br><br>This is the third stone from the sun <br>He made it for everyone <br>This is the third stone from the sun <br>He made it for everyone <br><br>Mother Earth is calling you <br>Mother Earth is calling you <br>Mother Earth is calling you <br>Today <br><br>Rolling Stones should rock together <br>Like the storm cloud crystal weather <br>Silver sun when the day is done <br><br>This is the third stone from the sun <br>He made it for everyone <br>This is the third stone from the sun <br>He made it for everyone <br><br>Mother Earth is calling you <br>Mother Earth is calling you <br>Mother Earth is calling you <br>Today <br><br>This is the next stone from the sun <br>He made it for everyone <br><br>Mother Earth is calling you <br>Mother Earth is calling you <br>Mother Earth is calling you <br>Today]]></content><category term="Sweet" label="Sweet"/><category term="Mother Earth" label="Mother Earth"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Eye_Games/</id><title>Sweet - Eye Games - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:48:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:48:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Eye_Games/" title="Sweet - Eye Games - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In the discos and the bars <br>They're playing eye games <br>Venus is watching Mars <br>They're playing come and try games <br>They're playing eye games <br><br>Electric attraction in the night air <br>Eyes meet and break away <br>You can't show who you care <br>It's one of love's puzzles <br>Dark secrets in her eyes <br>Does it mean I'm on the right track <br>Is there a chance for romance <br><br>In the discos and the bars <br>They're playing eye games <br>Venus is watching Mars <br>They're playing come and try games <br>They're playing eye games <br><br>All round the city <br>They're stealing glances <br>She looks so pretty <br>I'll have to take my chances <br>The music's getting louder <br>You try to talk to her <br>You find it hard to concentrate <br>Wandering eyes must watch and wait <br><br>In the discos and the bars <br>They're playing eye games <br>Venus is watching Mars <br>They're playing come and try games <br>They're playing eye games <br>They're playing eye games <br>They're playing eye games]]></content><category term="Sweet" label="Sweet"/><category term="Eye Games" label="Eye Games"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Discophony_Dis-Kof-O-Ne/</id><title>Sweet - Discophony (Dis-Kof-O-Ne) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:48:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:48:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Discophony_Dis-Kof-O-Ne/" title="Sweet - Discophony (Dis-Kof-O-Ne) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I met a girl who likes to dance <br>But there's only one way to get inside her pants <br>That's if I dance <br>Baby, there's no chance <br><br>Zombies brainwashed by the rhythm <br>Trapped inside their own escapism <br>In prison, I don't wanna be there <br>No, I don't wanna be there <br><br>Can't stand that disco music pain in my head <br>Can't stand that disco music pain in my head <br>Everyone said disco is dead <br>With it's boom, boom, boom, boom, ahh <br><br>Give me a drink while you're rollerskating <br>I'll be here if you're waiting to be fed in your bed <br>I ain't gonna dance <br>Disco ain't worth your masturbating <br>Rock and roll will still keep accelerating <br>I'll always be there, yeah, I'll always be there <br><br>Can't stand that disco music pain in my head <br>Can't stand that disco music pain in my head <br>Everyone said disco is dead <br>With it's boom, boom, boom, boom, ahh <br><br>Can't stand that disco music pain in my head <br>Can't stand that disco music pain in my head <br>Everyone said disco is dead <br>With it's boom, boom, boom, boom, ahh]]></content><category term="Sweet" label="Sweet"/><category term="Discophony (Dis-Kof-O-Ne)" label="Discophony (Dis-Kof-O-Ne)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Dorian_Gray/</id><title>Sweet - Dorian Gray - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:48:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:48:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Dorian_Gray/" title="Sweet - Dorian Gray - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Why all those younger guys <br>Falling for you in burlesque disguise <br>Making you feel like you're thirty <br>Just being dirty, you think I care <br><br>Who was that millionaire <br>Showing you his piles of golden hair <br>He was so rich but uneasy <br>Trying to tease me but I don't care <br><br>Painting your face <br>Hiding the pace of life <br>Beautiful past under the mask <br>You wear <br><br>You're a movie star who's caught in a dream <br>The silver screen, you know what I mean <br>You're a movie star who's caught in a dream <br>The silver screen, you know what I mean <br><br>How can you sleep at night <br>Knowing the secrets, secrets, secrets <br>Secrets you lock up tight <br>Taking ya chip off ya shoulder <br>It's good being older without a care <br><br>Painting your face <br>Hiding the pace of life <br>Beautiful past under the mask <br>That you wear, yeah <br><br>You're a movie star who's caught in a dream <br>The silver screen, you know what I mean <br>You're a movie star who's caught in a dream <br>The silver screen, you know what I mean <br><br>You're a movie star who's caught in a dream <br>The silver screen, you know what I mean <br>You're a movie star who's caught in a dream <br>The silver screen, you know what I mean]]></content><category term="Sweet" label="Sweet"/><category term="Dorian Gray" label="Dorian Gray"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Big_Apple_Waltz/</id><title>Sweet - Big Apple Waltz - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:48:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:48:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Big_Apple_Waltz/" title="Sweet - Big Apple Waltz - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Manhattan Skyline, surround me <br>Just like a lady, you're still holding <br>Your light burning for me to see <br>'Cause I'd do most anything <br>For all those nights that you bring to me <br><br>All of your love <br>I've been so long in the city <br>The city has been so long inside of me <br>Been so long, it's a pity, I'm so far away <br>But I still do The Big Apple Waltz <br><br>I'd buy an empire in any state <br>Building the future around you <br>'Cause where love grows, it's never too late <br>We'll paint a heart on the wall <br>For the whole of the world to see <br><br>All of my love <br>I've been so long in the city <br>The city has been so long inside of me <br>Been so long, it's a pity, I'm so far away <br>But I still do The Big Apple Waltz <br><br>Loving you, is my feeling of dej?-vu <br>Loving you, I know it's true, oh yeah <br><br>We'll paint a heart on the wall <br>For the whole of the world to see <br><br>All of our love <br>I've been so long in the city <br>The city has been so long inside of me <br>Been so long, it's a pity, I'm so far away <br>But I still do The Big Apple Waltz <br><br>I've been so long in the city <br>The city has been so long inside of me]]></content><category term="Sweet" label="Sweet"/><category term="Big Apple Waltz" label="Big Apple Waltz"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Play_All_Night/</id><title>Sweet - Play All Night - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:48:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:48:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Play_All_Night/" title="Sweet - Play All Night - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All I wanna do is play all night for you <br>If the system blows the fuse <br>It ain't gonna make the national news <br><br>All I wanna do is play all night for you <br>If the system blows the fuse <br>It ain't gonna make the national news <br><br>Your old man sees where you gonna go 'cause you can't go far <br>Said I'm going downtown to see some rock and roll in my boyfriend's car <br>I listen to the radio hot cuts from the show <br>One night in town I wanna be around to hear the band say <br><br>All I wanna do is rock and roll with you <br>If the system blows the fuse <br>It ain't gonna make the national news <br><br>All I wanna do is rock and roll with you <br>If the system blows the fuse <br>It ain't gonna make the national news <br><br>Then she took off her shirt and she threw it to the stars said it gotta be the grass <br>Some young thing with a fake ID and a backstage pass <br>There's nothing she won't do <br>To have her way with you <br>It's gotta be tonight 'cause tomorrow I'm gone <br>So you hear what I say <br><br>All I wanna do is play all night for you <br>If the system blows the fuse <br>It ain't gonna make the national news <br><br>All I wanna do is play all night for you <br>If the system blows the fuse <br>It ain't gonna make the national news <br><br>All I wanna do is play all night for you <br>All I wanna do is play all night for you <br><br>All I wanna do is play all night for you <br>If the system blows the fuse <br>It ain't gonna make the national news]]></content><category term="Sweet" label="Sweet"/><category term="Play All Night" label="Play All Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Call_Me/</id><title>Sweet - Call Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:48:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:48:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Call_Me/" title="Sweet - Call Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hilton hotel, the room was small <br>Square box, two beds and four walls <br>I need a girl who is kind <br>Relief of my mind and body <br>I remembered the magazine add <br>Pretty girls who will visit your pad <br>A knock at my door <br>Don't know what's in store for me <br><br>She said <br>Call me, call anytime (Call me) <br>Call me, when you wanna unwind (Call me) <br>Call me, daytime or night (Call me) <br>Call me and I'll turn on your light <br>Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh <br>Call me freephone <br><br>She walked in I had to be strong <br>I felt she had always belonged <br>Ooh, I must keep calm <br>The sweat in my palm won't go away <br>She said: "Now please relax my friend <br>I'll stay here 'till the very end" <br>She took off her shoes <br>Don't know what to do <br>Then I heard her say <br><br>Call me, call anytime (Call me) <br>Call me, when you want to unwind (Call me) <br>Call me, daytime or night (Call me) <br>Call me and I'll turn on your light <br>Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh <br><br>I lay on my belly she rubbed in petrolium jelly <br>Her hand felt so good <br>Lie on my back, nearly blowing my stack oh, I wish she would <br>Surrender the sweets <br>What she does with her feet <br>She satisfies and her pocket don't lie <br>Then she waved her goodbye <br><br>Call me, call anytime (Call me) <br>Call me, when you want to unwind (Call me) <br>Call me, daytime or night (Call me) <br>Call me and I'll turn on your light]]></content><category term="Sweet" label="Sweet"/><category term="Call Me" label="Call Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Tomorrow/</id><title>Needles - Tomorrow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:48:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:48:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Tomorrow/" title="Needles - Tomorrow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Like some long lost loser I still got my ruts <br>I want to cross these mountains but I got no guts <br>The winter is back all cold and rain <br>Hitting hard hard against sycophants and window panes saying…Everything’s not fine <br>When every word hangs dead on the line <br>Everything’s not good <br>When you’re left alone with a curse of a life you could…Goddamnit I get it <br>Goddamnit I know <br>It’s hard to get somewhere with nowhere to go <br>Just sleep.]]></content><category term="Needles" label="Needles"/><category term="Tomorrow" label="Tomorrow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Something_New/</id><title>Needles - Something New - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:48:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:48:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Something_New/" title="Needles - Something New - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So long to simple days <br>Caught between catastrophe and hope <br>Lay low and pause to pray <br>For all the rain to wash to away the things that help us cope <br>There’s shaking to be done <br>Cower till the courtesy of night <br>Set in with sinking sun <br>Another course of counting all the second till the light <br>While you’re sleeping I’m making myself into something new <br>To stop from keeping you awake <br>It’s all I ever do <br>Just stop this now.]]></content><category term="Needles" label="Needles"/><category term="Something New" label="Something New"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Untitled_Youre_Fine/</id><title>Needles - Untitled (You`re Fine) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:48:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:48:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Untitled_Youre_Fine/" title="Needles - Untitled (You`re Fine) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It don’t tale a lion to be better than me <br>There’s not much to watch on a broken TV <br>The phone won’t stop wringing for the hundred thousandth time and everyone keeps telling me you’re fine <br>There’s not much left <br>Just nothing and smoke <br>Crash the morning like the world’s oldest joke <br>The rain won’t stop pouring in that corner of my mind where everyone keeps telling me you’re fine <br>Maybe now you get why I hate going home <br>All empty space and that same fucking phone.]]></content><category term="Needles" label="Needles"/><category term="Untitled (You`re Fine)" label="Untitled (You`re Fine)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Pressure_Points/</id><title>Needles - Pressure Points - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:49:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:49:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Pressure_Points/" title="Needles - Pressure Points - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Those great escapes that we’ve tried to make have seemed to come between us now <br>Northern states might have come too late but we’ll just work this out somehow <br>Those eyes are the best that I’ve known <br>These lines are the farthest I go <br>When twists of fate never seem to take I end up feeling boring so <br>A three hour wait is a real heartbreak but I’ll call you in the morning though <br>I’ll try I just hate being home <br>It’s fine I’m just not good on my own <br>I’m pretty much the same <br>All pressure points and pain <br>Like everyone.]]></content><category term="Needles" label="Needles"/><category term="Pressure Points" label="Pressure Points"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/All_The_Same/</id><title>Needles - All The Same - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:49:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:49:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/All_The_Same/" title="Needles - All The Same - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Woke up on the wrong side it’s all the same <br>Hide hard from the daylight it’s all the same <br>Everyone has bad nights it’s all the same <br>But at least we’re doing alright it’s all the same <br>You were sitting in the back <br>Making plans for later and flirting heart attack <br>You were counting hours alone <br>A mix of bad behaviour and a two time broken home <br>Nothing makes you sick like lying in bed and waiting for life to quit <br>Nothing makes you go like lying awake in a house that’s not a home.]]></content><category term="Needles" label="Needles"/><category term="All The Same" label="All The Same"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Boil/</id><title>Needles - Boil - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:49:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:49:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Boil/" title="Needles - Boil - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe and boil <br>Seethe and soil <br>Breathe and boil <br>Curse and toil <br>I guess I’ll say goodnight before the carbon takes the light <br>And your breath takes the room and the silence kills me <br>With red eyes seeking warm cast across a place less torn <br>Let’s make this short and sweet.]]></content><category term="Needles" label="Needles"/><category term="Boil" label="Boil"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Miracle/</id><title>Needles - Miracle - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:49:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:49:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Miracle/" title="Needles - Miracle - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Try to fix up <br>Try to do right <br>Drink a bad night away with your ghost <br>It’s a mix up but a good fight <br>For a dull life that crawls to the coast <br>And all the friends you’ve made cut a clear path to your grave <br>It’s a miracle <br>Try fix fix it <br>With a dull knife <br>For a short life that bleeds out too long <br>Try to hide out <br>Try and find out <br>Try to scrape up and get home to you <br>And all the words you spoke were emotionally broke <br>It’s just capital <br>Lie awake too long to a minor song.]]></content><category term="Needles" label="Needles"/><category term="Miracle" label="Miracle"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Sleep/</id><title>Needles - Sleep - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:49:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:49:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Sleep/" title="Needles - Sleep - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Good enough is the hardest position but at least I got it made <br>It’s rough it’s the hardest position but at least I’m getting laid <br>That’s a lie I just keep all the neighbours awake on a Friday night <br>I don’t care because all I need is this porch and these broken stairs <br>When you’re stuck with all of these heroes that never gave a fuck <br>It’s fine because all of the greatest idols degrade in time <br>Like awake <br>Remember the best times you were the only fake <br>Pay no mind to all of the forgotten friends you’ve left behind <br>And just sleep <br>It’s all alright just get back tonight.]]></content><category term="Needles" label="Needles"/><category term="Sleep" label="Sleep"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Time_And_Tide/</id><title>Needles - Time And Tide - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:49:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:49:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Time_And_Tide/" title="Needles - Time And Tide - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[From grieve to groan <br>Crafting chemtrails across fairweather homes <br>From leaf to loam <br>There is something about being your own <br>The places where you loom have all but lost their bloom and dragged and dried <br>Carve a light <br>Through the pitches of October night <br>Wrong a right <br>Before the bastards make mercy their might <br>The places where you go <br>Are further than you know <br>And hard to hide <br>There’s nothing here but fun <br>For saints and never runs <br>With time and tide.]]></content><category term="Needles" label="Needles"/><category term="Time And Tide" label="Time And Tide"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Back_To_The_Bright/</id><title>Needles - Back To The Bright - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:49:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:49:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Back_To_The_Bright/" title="Needles - Back To The Bright - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Still talking circles at 3am <br>Still not convinced of the shape we’re in <br>Start stop the bleeding in the morning light <br>Keep fighting the feeling until it’s gone <br>You said this nothing is all we got <br>I closed my eyes and tried to keep them shut <br>We’ll grace tomorrow but we’ll chase tonight <br>We’ll break ourselves up in the the places we’re stuck <br>And drag ourselves back to the bright <br>I’m all for heartbreak <br>I’m all for pain <br>I’m all bad nights and really good fights <br>I’m all for forgetting your name.]]></content><category term="Needles" label="Needles"/><category term="Back To The Bright" label="Back To The Bright"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Violet/</id><title>Needles - Violet - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:49:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:49:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Violet/" title="Needles - Violet - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The palest eyes shit through boredom <br>OK one more drink and we’re out of here <br>Sleep a little longer but just keep waking up the same <br>Another head, another bed, another heart, and another year <br>Just waiting for the winter <br>Just waiting for September to fall and take us all down with it <br>The safest lies make the morning <br>A little guilt and a little fear <br>Bad dreams we’ll remember <br>The slowest silent sigh that carried you far away <br>Do you still sing the same songs every day Do you still feel violet in the winter]]></content><category term="Needles" label="Needles"/><category term="Violet" label="Violet"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Good_Night/</id><title>Needles - Good Night - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:49:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:49:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Needles/Good_Night/" title="Needles - Good Night - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Good night Allison it’s been so long <br>Tried to send a letter got the address wrong <br>Stars explode over Southwood Plantation Road <br>while the rain falls heavy on my coast <br>Good night Allison I gotta say <br>My worst intentions get the best of me <br>May you run and roam <br>Never missing home or the one that I know you hate the most <br>Good night Allison it’s time to go <br>But there’s just one thing that I hope you know <br>You’ll rise and fall with the best of them all <br>and I’ll still fall asleep in all my clothes.]]></content><category term="Needles" label="Needles"/><category term="Good Night" label="Good Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/Dead_End_Poem/</id><title>Octavia Sperati - Dead End Poem - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:54:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:54:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/Dead_End_Poem/" title="Octavia Sperati - Dead End Poem - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I close my eyes <br>As fire swept clean the earth <br>Nothing left to strangle <br>As the cords were torn from our hearts <br><br>As we emerged <br>From darker dungeons <br>Splendor of yellow hells <br>Expanded swollen eyes <br><br>No words were said <br>As fire swept clean the earth <br>Would the mothers be crying <br>If they saw the torches in their hands <br><br>A kiss was placed upon my cheek <br>And all colors came back <br>Melting in solid blue hues]]></content><category term="Octavia Sperati" label="Octavia Sperati"/><category term="Dead End Poem" label="Dead End Poem"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/Provenance_Of_Hate/</id><title>Octavia Sperati - Provenance Of Hate - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:54:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:54:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/Provenance_Of_Hate/" title="Octavia Sperati - Provenance Of Hate - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[To spectate your inferiority <br>What use are you to me <br><br>And your presence is passing me by <br>All the time <br><br>It's infesting me and I eliminate it <br>By offering to the wind <br><br>Unsuccessful in your attempt <br>To outshine my brilliant superiority <br>And I will paint your shadow red all over <br><br>With my spirit I enter you <br>What use are you to me <br>It's infesting me and I eliminate it all the time]]></content><category term="Octavia Sperati" label="Octavia Sperati"/><category term="Provenance Of Hate" label="Provenance Of Hate"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/Deprivation/</id><title>Octavia Sperati - Deprivation - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:54:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:54:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/Deprivation/" title="Octavia Sperati - Deprivation - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Strange faces <br>In a night time <br>Weird places <br>Desperately looking for an exit <br><br>Stripped naked <br>For a lifetime <br>Try to break it <br>Every night has its dawn <br><br>Bad vibrations <br>For the right time <br>Prevent destructions <br>Don't you regret your ever closed eyes <br><br>You run in slow motion <br>Escape from its presence and strain <br>To be approaching to you <br>Closer and closer <br>Suddenly quite awake and soaking wet <br>In the dark you can see their eyes everywhere <br><br>Try to wake up <br>During night time <br>Impenetrable <br>Through the dark time <br>In need of sleeping <br>Deprived of your deep sleep <br><br>You run in slow motion <br>Escape from its presence and strain <br>To be approaching to you <br>Closer and closer <br>Suddenly quite awake and soaking wet <br>In the dark you can see their eyes everywhere]]></content><category term="Octavia Sperati" label="Octavia Sperati"/><category term="Deprivation" label="Deprivation"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/The_Final_Rest/</id><title>Octavia Sperati - The Final Rest - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:55:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:55:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/The_Final_Rest/" title="Octavia Sperati - The Final Rest - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I am waiting, waiting for the words to come <br>Silence is taking, taking up the space that... <br>Naked skin wrapped in showers of silver... <br>Sun's out defrosting years of clogged up strain <br><br>Two tied up souls inhaling <br>Searching for their own lived lives <br>Longing to flush upon its shore to come to final rest <br>Venomous clouds throw the sun into a shade <br>The drunken earth begs for her as the sky is missing its moon <br><br>My world is shaking, breaking up the solid ground <br>Slowly I'm waking, waking up to see through years of pain <br>Drunken soul sinking, drowning in its misery <br>Clear eyes are watching, staring at the vast sun <br><br>Slow rivers of golden memories <br>Shivering down their broken spine <br>Longing to flush upon its shore to come to final rest <br>Venomous clouds throw the sun into a shade <br>The drunken earth begs for her as the sky is missing its moon]]></content><category term="Octavia Sperati" label="Octavia Sperati"/><category term="The Final Rest" label="The Final Rest"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/And_Then_The_World_Froze/</id><title>Octavia Sperati - ...And Then The World Froze - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:55:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:55:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/And_Then_The_World_Froze/" title="Octavia Sperati - ...And Then The World Froze - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe I was wrong <br>Maybe I just imagined all these things <br>Do you want to be here- with me <br>Are you sorry you came <br>All those times on the street <br>Why didn't you talk to me <br><br>Don't be afraid- I had to escape <br>It was burning me up inside <br><br>Sun seems pale <br>The world froze <br>To echoes of strife <br><br>Storms embrace us <br>Walls are moaning <br>Let us avoid the edges of broken glass <br><br>Time standing still <br>The world froze <br>My story wrapped in cold cold rain drops collapsing on your soul <br>I'm freezing <br>Where is the love <br><br>Do you see these floods- in my eyes <br>Would you stand me up <br>If I needed your strength <br>Would your force reach me <br><br>Don't get me wrong- I had to be strong <br><br>Sun seems pale <br>The world froze <br>To echoes of strife <br><br>Words are soaring <br>Thoughts are drifting <br>Let us avoid the edges of broken hearts <br><br>Blood running strong <br>To echoes of strife <br>The sun seems pale and lost in its cosmic chaos <br>Am freezing <br>Where is the love <br><br>Maybe I was wrong <br>Maybe I just imagined all these things <br>Did you want to be here- with me <br>Are you sorry you came <br>All those times on the street <br>Why didn't you walk with me <br><br>Don't be afraid- I had to escape]]></content><category term="Octavia Sperati" label="Octavia Sperati"/><category term="...And Then The World Froze" label="...And Then The World Froze"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/Dont_Believe_A_Word/</id><title>Octavia Sperati - Don`t Believe A Word - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:55:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:55:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/Dont_Believe_A_Word/" title="Octavia Sperati - Don`t Believe A Word - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't believe me if I tell you <br>Not a word of this is true <br>Don't believe me if I tell you <br>Especially if I tell you I'm in love with you <br><br>Don't believe me if I tell you <br>That I wrote this song for you <br>There just might be some other silly, pretty boy I'm singing to <br><br>Don't believe a word <br>Words are so easily spoken <br>And your heart is just like a promise, made to be broken <br><br>Don't believe a word <br>'Cause words can tell lies <br>And lies are no comfort <br>When there're tears in your eyes <br><br>Don't believe me if I tell you <br>Not a word of this is true <br>Don't believe me if I tell you <br>Especially if I tell you I'm in love with you <br>Don't believe a word <br><br>I don't believe a word <br>Don't believe it, don't believe it <br>Not a single word]]></content><category term="Octavia Sperati" label="Octavia Sperati"/><category term="Don`t Believe A Word" label="Don`t Believe A Word"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/Going_North/</id><title>Octavia Sperati - Going North - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:55:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:55:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/Going_North/" title="Octavia Sperati - Going North - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[He's heading north <br>With silent shout <br>And quiet reverence <br>The wish to be granted <br><br>He's come to catch <br>His midnight sun <br>A star to wish upon <br>Bleached in northern lights <br><br>It's cold, he's told it's beauty was irresistible <br>He's brave; he's safe in this land of his dreams <br>The moon will rise to see him off <br><br>One day there will be time to put his mind to rest <br>He will find his cave <br>A shelter to keep them out <br>It's dark, the mark appears in the distance of his tired eyes <br>The golden light hits his unconscious mind <br>It proves the goal is here for him <br><br>He has come too close <br>The end so fair and sparkling <br>Wind will blow his mind back to where it belongs <br><br>Time will change; and time will broaden his mind <br>Monuments of ancient beliefs are written in stone <br>Not fading to keep the word of faith]]></content><category term="Octavia Sperati" label="Octavia Sperati"/><category term="Going North" label="Going North"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/Moonlit/</id><title>Octavia Sperati - Moonlit - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:55:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:55:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/Moonlit/" title="Octavia Sperati - Moonlit - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There she is, looking down at me <br>Down at us, gazing with a sigh <br>Bright as always, clouds give way <br>Tonight so sharp, so clear and solid <br>Knows all her missions, never ever failed <br>The roar will rise to kill in the name... <br><br>How can they "forget" and never regret <br>Not taking their chances and heal <br>It's awful and true, this manic award <br>Blowing their souls to pieces for him <br><br>You're going down and that is the end <br>No heroes left but fallen men <br>She catches it all so gently with a shine <br>They're on their thrones, looking down at us <br>With hate and loss the aim remains <br>So unfairly in their misery <br><br>How can they go on and never look back <br>When will they accept and give in <br>All over the fear comes closer to us <br>The stars will shine beyond the end]]></content><category term="Octavia Sperati" label="Octavia Sperati"/><category term="Moonlit" label="Moonlit"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/Guilty_Am_I/</id><title>Octavia Sperati - Guilty Am I - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T07:55:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T07:55:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Octavia_Sperati/Guilty_Am_I/" title="Octavia Sperati - Guilty Am I - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Death in front of my feet <br>The path I no longer see <br>The interference of yours to my so wanted solitude <br><br>The stars rise from utter darkness <br>And leads me <br>It is the only course open to me <br>You shadow is stuck with the enemy <br>With nowhere to go <br>Nowhere to hide <br>Sleepless dreaming of no agony <br><br>Unimpeachable appear you now too close to me <br>And nowhere to run to <br>No one to blame <br>I hope this hunting will come to an end <br><br>Blood is all over moats <br>Of my deep sunken memory <br>The shattered soul of mine <br>Will it ever be healed again <br><br>This maze of endless fear from unknown emptiness <br>It leads me <br>Crossing the ominous signs opened to me <br><br>Your shadow is stuck with the enemy <br>With no face to seek <br>No words to tell <br>Sleepless dreaming of no agony <br><br>Unimpeachable appear you now to close to me <br>With no one to turn to <br>And no trail of home <br>I hope this haunting will come to an end]]></content><category term="Octavia Sperati" label="Octavia Sperati"/><category term="Guilty Am I" label="Guilty Am I"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/76호/신세계/</id><title>76호 - 신세계 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:03:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:03:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/76%ED%98%B8/%EC%8B%A0%EC%84%B8%EA%B3%84/" title="76호 - 신세계 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[New world 이건 흩어진 이미지 <br>New world 마치 그려놓은 듯이 <br>New world 여긴 생각할게 없지 <br>New world New world <br>Everything's gonna be OK <br>She gotta be loved today <br>Everything's gonna be OK <br>He gotta be loved today <br>Every gonna be Oh Oh Oh <br>We gonna be Oh Oh Oh <br>Every gonna be Every gonna be <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>New world 우린 꿈속에 있겠지 <br>New world 모두 던져버린 듯이 <br>New world 여긴 생각할게 없지 <br>New world New world <br>Everything's gonna be OK <br>She gotta be loved today <br>Everything's gonna be OK <br>He gotta be loved today <br>Every gonna be Oh Oh Oh <br>We gonna be Oh Oh Oh <br>Every gonna be Every gonna be <br>Every gonna be Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>]]></content><category term="76호" label="76호"/><category term="신세계" label="신세계"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/일렉펀트/이끼/</id><title>일렉펀트 - 이끼 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:03:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:03:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%BC%EB%A0%89%ED%8E%80%ED%8A%B8/%EC%9D%B4%EB%81%BC/" title="일렉펀트 - 이끼 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[침대 위에 뿌리내린 이끼인 듯 <br>그저 천장만 바라보고 있지 <br>울렁이는 창문은 어지럽고 <br>납덩이 같은 담요는 날 짓누르지 <br>해야 할 것들을 찾아보지만 <br>내 나침반은 돌아만 가고 <br>노력조차 버거워져 다시 누워 <br>그렇게 천장만 바라보고 있지 <br>의지는 이미 다른 곳으로 <br>위안 마저 버린 나태함 <br>휴지처럼 굴러다니는 <br>정신은 계속 나약해져만 가네 <br>화면 속 자신과 사랑하며 <br>알 수 없는 너의 지저귐을 흘리며 <br>무서운 이야기만 넘치는 세상 <br>담을 둘러 뿌리내려 퍼져만 가네 <br>의지는 이미 다른 곳으로 <br>위안 마저 버린 나태함 <br>휴지처럼 굴러다니는 <br>정신은 계속 나약해져만 가네 <br>침대 위에 뿌리내린 이끼인 듯 <br>침대 위에 뿌리내린 이끼인 듯 <br>침대 위에 뿌리내린 이끼인 듯 <br>침대 위에 뿌리내린 이끼인 듯 <br>]]></content><category term="일렉펀트" label="일렉펀트"/><category term="이끼" label="이끼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신다정/할_수만_있다면/</id><title>신다정 - 할 수만 있다면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:03:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:03:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EB%8B%A4%EC%A0%95/%ED%95%A0_%EC%88%98%EB%A7%8C_%EC%9E%88%EB%8B%A4%EB%A9%B4/" title="신다정 - 할 수만 있다면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[늦은 새벽 저절로 떠지는 눈 <br>꿈속에서도 날 괴롭히는 너 <br>선명한 너의 모습에 <br>난 다시 잠들지 못해 <br>난 아직도 멈춰진 시간 속에 <br>너를 그리며 깨어나지 못해 <br>선명한 너의 모습에 <br>오늘도 잠들지 못해 <br>나를 바라보며 <br>사랑한다 속삭이던 그대는 <br>이젠 더 이상 없다는 걸 잘 알면서도 <br>할 수만 있다면 <br>널 알기 전으로 돌아가고 싶어 <br>처음부터 없었던 일처럼 <br>우리가 사랑한 <br>수많은 추억이 이젠 날 괴롭혀 <br>다시 돌아갈 수 없단 걸 알면서도 <br>난 아직도 멈춰진 시간 속에 <br>너를 그리며 깨어나지 못해 <br>선명한 너의 모습에 <br>오늘도 잠들지 못해 <br>아무 말도 없이 <br>그저 나를 안아주던 그대는 <br>이젠 더 이상 없다는 걸 잘 알면서도 <br>할 수만 있다면 <br>널 알기 전으로 돌아가고 싶어 <br>처음부터 없었던 일처럼 <br>우리가 사랑한 <br>수많은 추억이 이젠 날 괴롭혀 <br>다시 돌아갈 수 없단 걸 <br>할 수만 있다면 <br>널 알기 전으로 돌아가고 싶어 <br>모든 추억들이 사라져도 <br>우리가 사랑한 <br>수많은 추억이 이젠 날 괴롭혀 <br>다시 돌아갈 수 없단 걸 알면서도 <br>]]></content><category term="신다정" label="신다정"/><category term="할 수만 있다면" label="할 수만 있다면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/청춘낭만사_Green_Spring_Romance/기다림의_바다/</id><title>청춘낭만사 (Green Spring Romance) - 기다림의 바다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:06:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:06:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%AD%EC%B6%98%EB%82%AD%EB%A7%8C%EC%82%AC_Green_Spring_Romance/%EA%B8%B0%EB%8B%A4%EB%A6%BC%EC%9D%98_%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%A4/" title="청춘낭만사 (Green Spring Romance) - 기다림의 바다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기다림에 단 한번도 지쳤던 적 없어 <br>파도소리가 너의 목소린 것 같아서 <br>그리움에 아픔에 유통기한은 없어 <br>너 없는 세상 난 숨 쉴 수가 없어 <br>꿈 속에 너는 그대론데 <br>혹시 변한 내 모습 못 알아볼까봐 <br>오늘도 노을이 내린 바다 <br>또 하루가 끝나고 <br>너 없는 내일이 오겠지 <br>너를 부르고 불러봐도 <br>내 작은 목소린 늘 그렇듯 <br>파도에 부서지고 <br>눈물이 내려앉은 바다에 <br>비가 오나 눈이 오나 늘 언제나 <br>너를 기다리면 네가 오나 <br>무섭게 바다는 고요하네 <br>네가 떠난 세상도 아무 일 없는 듯 <br>내게는 슬픔에 물든 바다 <br>또 하루가 끝나도 <br>너 없는 내일이 오듯이 <br>너를 부르고 불러봐도 <br>내 작은 목소린 늘 그렇듯 <br>파도에 부서지고 <br>눈물이 내려앉은 바다에 <br>비가 오나 눈이 오나 늘 언제나 <br>너를 기다리면 네가 오나 <br>너를 부르고 불러봐도 <br>내 작은 목소린 늘 그렇듯 <br>파도에 부서지고 <br>눈물이 내려앉은 바다에 <br>비가 오나 눈이 오나 늘 언제나 <br>너를 기다리면 <br>]]></content><category term="청춘낭만사 (Green Spring Romance)" label="청춘낭만사 (Green Spring Romance)"/><category term="기다림의 바다" label="기다림의 바다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/느루_Neuru/산책/</id><title>느루 (Neuru) - 산책 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:10:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:10:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8A%90%EB%A3%A8_Neuru/%EC%82%B0%EC%B1%85/" title="느루 (Neuru) - 산책 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어느샌가 내 맘속에 핀 꽃 향기가 <br>간지럽게 내 맘속에 부는 바람이 <br>창문을 두드리며 <br>내게 손짓하고 우우우 <br>이끌리듯 나온 거리 <br>따스한 햇살아래 눈 감아 <br>야이야 <br>콧노래가 나와 <br>야이야 <br>콧노래가 나와 <br>]]></content><category term="느루 (Neuru)" label="느루 (Neuru)"/><category term="산책" label="산책"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카_폴리_OST/헬리의_생일_English_Ver/</id><title>로보카 폴리 OST - 헬리의 생일 (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:10:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:10:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4_%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_OST/%ED%97%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%9D%98_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC_English_Ver/" title="로보카 폴리 OST - 헬리의 생일 (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Happy birthday to you <br>Happy birthday to you <br>Happy birthday Dear Helly <br>Happy birthday to you <br>Happy birthday to you <br>Happy birthday to you <br>Happy birthday Dear Helly <br>Happy birthday to you <br>Happy birthday to you <br>Happy birthday to you <br>Happy birthday Dear Helly <br>Happy birthday to you <br>Happy birthday <br>Happy birthday <br>Happy birthday <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="헬리의 생일 (English Ver.)" label="헬리의 생일 (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카_폴리_OST/헬리의_생일/</id><title>로보카 폴리 OST - 헬리의 생일 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:10:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:10:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4_%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_OST/%ED%97%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%9D%98_%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%BC/" title="로보카 폴리 OST - 헬리의 생일 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생일 축하합니다 <br>생일 축하합니다 <br>사랑하는 헬리의 <br>생일 축하합니다 <br>생일 축하합니다 <br>생일 축하합니다 <br>사랑하는 헬리의 <br>생일 축하합니다 <br>생일 축하합니다 <br>생일 축하합니다 <br>사랑하는 헬리의 <br>생일 축하합니다 <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="헬리의 생일" label="헬리의 생일"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카_폴리_OST/항구의_크레인_세쌍둥이_English_Ver/</id><title>로보카 폴리 OST - 항구의 크레인 세쌍둥이 (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:10:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:10:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4_%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_OST/%ED%95%AD%EA%B5%AC%EC%9D%98_%ED%81%AC%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8_%EC%84%B8%EC%8C%8D%EB%91%A5%EC%9D%B4_English_Ver/" title="로보카 폴리 OST - 항구의 크레인 세쌍둥이 (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The Brothers are crane triplets <br>who live down at the port <br>You may think that they're <br>similar but take another look <br>Orange Lefy's the strong one <br>his muscles are of steel <br>Blue Lety's quite intelligent <br>he learned so much at school <br>And that leaves yellow Leky <br>who listens to his heart <br>Yes they're three different people <br>who'll never be apart <br>The Brothers are crane triplets <br>who live down at the port <br>You may think that they're <br>similar but take another look <br>Orange Lefy's the strong one <br>his muscles are of steel <br>Blue Lety's quite intelligent <br>he learned so much at school <br>And that leaves yellow Leky <br>who listens to his heart <br>Yes they're three different people <br>who'll never be apart <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="항구의 크레인 세쌍둥이 (English Ver.)" label="항구의 크레인 세쌍둥이 (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카_폴리_OST/항구의_크레인_세쌍둥이/</id><title>로보카 폴리 OST - 항구의 크레인 세쌍둥이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:10:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:10:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4_%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_OST/%ED%95%AD%EA%B5%AC%EC%9D%98_%ED%81%AC%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8_%EC%84%B8%EC%8C%8D%EB%91%A5%EC%9D%B4/" title="로보카 폴리 OST - 항구의 크레인 세쌍둥이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[항구에 살고 있는 크레인 세쌍둥이 <br>언제나 함께 있어 행복하지요 <br>주황색 레피는 아주 힘이 쎄요 <br>파란색 레티는 아주 똑똑해요 <br>노란색 레키는 책임감이 강해요 <br>언제나 함께 있어 행복하지요 <br>항구에 살고 있는 크레인 세쌍둥이 <br>언제나 함께 있어 행복하지요 <br>주황색 레피는 아주 힘이 쎄요 <br>파란색 레티는 아주 똑똑해요 <br>노란색 레키는 책임감이 강해요 <br>언제나 함께 있어 행복하지요 <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="항구의 크레인 세쌍둥이" label="항구의 크레인 세쌍둥이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카_폴리_OST/브룸스타운으로_오세요_English_Ver/</id><title>로보카 폴리 OST - 브룸스타운으로 오세요 (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:10:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:10:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4_%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_OST/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A3%B8%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80%EC%9A%B4%EC%9C%BC%EB%A1%9C_%EC%98%A4%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94_English_Ver/" title="로보카 폴리 OST - 브룸스타운으로 오세요 (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come on over to Brooms Town <br>Everybody gather 'round <br>Sit around together <br>everybody sing along <br>Chugga choo choo <br>The train's excited too <br>And singing along with you <br>La la la la la <br>La la la la la <br>C'mon let's all walk together <br>and follow the Brooms Town train <br>Now if you're having fun <br>too come and dance all around <br>Chugga choo choo <br>The train is having fun too <br>And singing along with you <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="브룸스타운으로 오세요 (English Ver.)" label="브룸스타운으로 오세요 (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카_폴리_OST/브룸스타운으로_오세요/</id><title>로보카 폴리 OST - 브룸스타운으로 오세요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:10:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:10:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4_%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_OST/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A3%B8%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80%EC%9A%B4%EC%9C%BC%EB%A1%9C_%EC%98%A4%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94/" title="로보카 폴리 OST - 브룸스타운으로 오세요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[브룸스타운으로 오세요 <br>모두 모두 모이세요 <br>옹기종기 모여 앉아 노래 불러요 <br>칙칙폭폭 기차도 신이 나서 <br>노래를 하네요 <br>랄라 랄라라 랄라 랄라라 <br>브룸스타운 기찻길을 따라 <br>모두 함께 걸어가요 <br>신이 나면 마음대로 춤도 추세요 <br>칙칙폭폭 기차도 신이 나서 <br>춤을 추네요 <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="브룸스타운으로 오세요" label="브룸스타운으로 오세요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/채희/사무치는_그리움/</id><title>채희 - 사무치는 그리움 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:13:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:13:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B1%84%ED%9D%AC/%EC%82%AC%EB%AC%B4%EC%B9%98%EB%8A%94_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9B%80/" title="채희 - 사무치는 그리움 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1.세월이 흘러가듯 가슴속에 그리움 <br>얼마나 세월이 가야 이내 맘을 그댄 알까요 <br><br>얼마나 애를 태워야 운명처럼 다가 설까요 <br>행여나 스치는 바람 내 마음 전해 주려나 <br><br>그리움만큼 나를 울리고 추억속에 <br>울고 웃던 생각이 나네 <br><br>사랑보다 더 아픈게 그리움이라 햇던가 <br>그동안 흘러간 시간을 모아 널 다시 만들고 싶어 <br><br>2.그리움만큼 나를 울리고 추억속에 <br>웃고 울던 생각이 나네 <br><br>사랑보다 더 아픈 게 그리움이라 햇던가 <br>그동안 흘러간 시간을 모아 널 다시 만들고 싶어 <br><br>사랑보다 더 아픈 게 그리움이라 햇던가 <br>그동안 흘러간 시간을 모아 널 다시 만들고 싶어 <br><br>널 다시 만들고 싶어]]></content><category term="채희" label="채희"/><category term="사무치는 그리움" label="사무치는 그리움"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/채희/사랑인_것을/</id><title>채희 - 사랑인 것을 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:13:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:13:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B1%84%ED%9D%AC/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B8_%EA%B2%83%EC%9D%84/" title="채희 - 사랑인 것을 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[행여나 날 찾아 돌아올것만 같아 <br>등불을 밝혀 둡니다 <br>혹시 길이 엇갈려 나를 못보더라도 <br>흔적 하나 남겨 주세요 <br>유난히도 밝은 달빛을 등지고 <br>당신을 보내던 그날 <br>눈물이 마르도록 후회하고 또 해도 <br>그것이 사랑인 것을 <br><br>행여나 날 찾아 돌아올것만 같아 <br>등불을 밝혀 둡니다 <br>혹시 길이 엇갈려 나를 못보더라도 <br>흔적 하나 남겨 주세요 <br>백년이 흐르고 천년이 흘러도 <br>당신만 사랑합니다 <br>슬픔만일 지라도 아픔만일 지라도 <br>그것이 사랑인 것을 <br>그것이 사랑인 것을]]></content><category term="채희" label="채희"/><category term="사랑인 것을" label="사랑인 것을"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안지은/너와_나_둘/</id><title>안지은 - 너와 나, 둘 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:16:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:16:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%A7%80%EC%9D%80/%EB%84%88%EC%99%80_%EB%82%98_%EB%91%98/" title="안지은 - 너와 나, 둘 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[조심스레 내 손을 잡고 <br>생긋 웃어 보이던 네 모습 <br>머릿속에 문득 떠올라 <br>한결 같이 자상한 네 미소가 <br>재미없던 하루하루도 <br>너와 함께 한다면 새로워 <br>자주 걷던 골목골목도 <br>네 손 잡고 간다면 난 좋아 <br>너와 나 둘만의 시간 속에 <br>언제나 따스한 네 품 안에 <br>안겨서 노래 부를래 <br>평생을 네 곁에 <br>함께 할 수 있다는 생각에 <br>설레어와 <br>너의 옆에 두 눈을 감고 <br>기대 나도 모르게 잠이 들면 <br>그 어떤 곳보다 아늑해 <br>마치 나를 감싸 안는 요람 같아 <br>재미없던 하루하루도 <br>너와 함께 한다면 새로워 <br>자주 걷던 골목골목도 <br>네 손 잡고 간다면 난 좋아 <br>너와 나 둘만의 시간 속에 <br>언제나 따스한 네 품 안에 <br>안겨서 노래 부를래 <br>평생을 네 곁에 <br>함께 할 수 있다는 생각에 <br>설레어와 <br>누군가 상처 줄 때 <br>언제든 I will be your side <br>쉴 곳이 필요할 땐 <br>내 품에 널 안아 줄게 <br>너와 나 둘만의 시간 속에 <br>언제나 따스한 네 품 안에 <br>안겨서 노래 부를래 <br>평생을 네 곁에 <br>함께 할 수 있다는 생각에 <br>설레어와 <br>너와 나 둘만의 시간 속에 <br>언제나 따스한 네 품 안에 <br>안겨서 노래 부를래 <br>평생을 네 곁에 <br>함께 할 수 있다는 생각에 <br>설레어와 <br>]]></content><category term="안지은" label="안지은"/><category term="너와 나, 둘" label="너와 나, 둘"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김시형/치유_With_김동현/</id><title>김시형 - 치유 (With 김동현) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:16:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:16:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%8B%9C%ED%98%95/%EC%B9%98%EC%9C%A0_With_%EA%B9%80%EB%8F%99%ED%98%84/" title="김시형 - 치유 (With 김동현) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마음속에 깊이 새겨 있는 <br>그 순간 아팠던 시간을 기억해 <br>아무것도 할 수가 없는 시간들을 <br>그저 흘려 보내야 했던 <br>어둠에서 나올 수 없었던 <br>빛을 찾아 헤메였던 순간들 <br>얼마나 두려움에 떨고 있었을까 <br>그 모습 생각할 때 <br>꿈을 꿔도 그 자리에 <br>너의 모습 떠올라 잊지 못하고 <br>한번이라도 한번만이라도 <br>너의 곁으로 갈 수 있게 되면 <br>후회하지 않도록 너를 <br>따뜻하게 안아주고 싶고 <br>너를 둘러 싼 모든 아픔을 <br>씻어 버릴 수 있게 <br>흘러가는 세월 속에 기대보네 <br>놓쳐버린 많은 시간들을 <br>이제라도 돌려 볼 수 있다면 <br>조그만 상처라도 어루만진 후에 <br>이제는 헤어지네 <br>꿈을 꿔도 그 자리에 <br>너의 모습 떠올라 잊지 못하고 <br>한번이라도 한번만이라도 <br>너의 곁으로 갈 수 있게 되면 <br>후회하지 않도록 너를 <br>따뜻하게 안아주고 싶고 <br>너를 둘러 싼 모든 아픔을 <br>씻어 버릴 수 있게 <br>흘러가는 기억의 세월에 기대보네 <br>]]></content><category term="김시형" label="김시형"/><category term="치유 (With 김동현)" label="치유 (With 김동현)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강성균/더_가까이/</id><title>강성균 - 더 가까이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:17:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:17:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%84%B1%EA%B7%A0/%EB%8D%94_%EA%B0%80%EA%B9%8C%EC%9D%B4/" title="강성균 - 더 가까이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나의 영혼이 주님께 피하오니 <br>나를 주의 품에 안아 주시고 <br>나의 평생에 주님만 따르오니 <br>주를 더욱 의지합니다 <br>더 가까이 더 가까이 <br>주님 계신 곳에 나 거하며 <br>더 가까이 더 가까이 <br>주님 계신 곳에 나 나아가리 <br>나의 영혼이 주님께 피하오니 <br>나를 주의 품에 안아 주시고 <br>나의 평생에 주님만 따르오니 <br>주를 더욱 의지합니다 <br>더 가까이 더 가까이 <br>주님 계신 곳에 나 거하며 <br>더 가까이 더 가까이 <br>주님 계신 곳에 나 나아가리 <br>더 가까이 더 가까이 <br>주님 계신 곳에 나 거하며 <br>더 가까이 더 가까이 <br>주님 계신 곳에 나 나아가리 <br>주님께 더 주님께 더욱 가까이 <br>주님께 더 주님께 더욱 가까이 <br>주님께 더 주님께 더욱 가까이 <br>주님께 더 주님께 더욱 가까이 <br>더 가까이 더 가까이 <br>주님 계신 곳에 나 거하며 <br>더 가까이 더 가까이 <br>주님 계신 곳에 나 나아가리 <br>더 가까이 더 가까이 <br>주님 계신 곳에 나 거하며 <br>더 가까이 더 가까이 <br>주님 계신 곳에 나 나아가리 <br>]]></content><category term="강성균" label="강성균"/><category term="더 가까이" label="더 가까이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강성균/내_신을_벗고_Feat_한나영/</id><title>강성균 - 내 신을 벗고 (Feat. 한나영) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:17:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:17:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%84%B1%EA%B7%A0/%EB%82%B4_%EC%8B%A0%EC%9D%84_%EB%B2%97%EA%B3%A0_Feat_%ED%95%9C%EB%82%98%EC%98%81/" title="강성균 - 내 신을 벗고 (Feat. 한나영) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주 없이 살 수 없는 <br>나의 삶을 주께 고백하네 <br>주 없이 갈 수 없는 <br>나의 길을 보내 <br>내 신을 벗고 믿음의 눈을 들어 <br>주만 바라보리 <br>나의 왕 나의 주 <br>내 평생 주만 예배하리 <br>내 신을 벗고 믿음의 눈을 들어 <br>주만 따라가리 <br>내 소망 내 생명 <br>나의 유일한 사랑 주 밖에 없네 <br>주 없이 살 수 없는 <br>나의 삶을 주께 고백하네 <br>주 없이 갈 수 없는 <br>나의 길을 보내 <br>내 신을 벗고 믿음의 눈을 들어 <br>주만 바라보리 <br>나의 왕 나의 주 <br>내 평생 주만 예배하리 <br>내 신을 벗고 믿음의 눈을 들어 <br>주만 따라가리 <br>내 소망 내 생명 <br>나의 유일한 사랑 주 밖에 없네 <br>내 신을 벗고 믿음의 눈을 들어 <br>주만 바라보리 <br>나의 왕 나의 주 <br>내 평생 주만 예배하리 <br>내 신을 벗고 믿음의 눈을 들어 <br>주만 따라가리 <br>내 소망 내 생명 <br>나의 유일한 사랑 <br>나의 유일한 사랑 <br>나의 유일한 사랑 주 밖에 없네 <br>주 밖에 없네 <br>주 밖에 없네 <br>]]></content><category term="강성균" label="강성균"/><category term="내 신을 벗고 (Feat. 한나영)" label="내 신을 벗고 (Feat. 한나영)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강성균/그러나_하나님_Feat_마커스_이동희/</id><title>강성균 - 그러나 하나님 (Feat. 마커스 이동희) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:17:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:17:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%84%B1%EA%B7%A0/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%AC%EB%82%98_%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EB%8B%98_Feat_%EB%A7%88%EC%BB%A4%EC%8A%A4_%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%ED%9D%AC/" title="강성균 - 그러나 하나님 (Feat. 마커스 이동희) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈물을 흘려도 소리를 질러도 <br>다 표현 못 할 탄식이 있네 <br>절망의 수렁과 고통의 바다에서 <br>다 이해 못 할 탄식이 있네 <br>그러나 우리 주 하나님 <br>신실하심 나는 믿네 <br>주의 계획으로 인도하시며 <br>나를 영광으로 영접하실 <br>탄식에서 찬양으로 <br>나의 노래 바꾸신 이 오직 주님 <br>눈물을 흘려도 소리를 질러도 <br>다 표현 못 할 탄식이 있네 <br>절망의 수렁과 고통의 바다에서 <br>다 이해 못 할 탄식이 있네 <br>그러나 우리 주 하나님 <br>신실하심 나는 믿네 <br>주의 계획으로 인도하시며 <br>나를 영광으로 영접하실 <br>탄식에서 찬양으로 <br>나의 노래 바꾸신 이 오직 주님 <br>오직 주님 <br>그러나 우리 주 하나님 <br>신실하심 나는 믿네 <br>주의 계획으로 인도하시며 <br>나를 영광으로 영접하실 <br>탄식에서 찬양으로 <br>나의 노래 바꾸신 이 오직 주님 <br>오직 주님 <br>오직 주님 <br>오직 주님 <br>오직 주님 <br>오직 주님 <br>]]></content><category term="강성균" label="강성균"/><category term="그러나 하나님 (Feat. 마커스 이동희)" label="그러나 하나님 (Feat. 마커스 이동희)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강성균/나의_영혼에/</id><title>강성균 - 나의 영혼에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:17:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:17:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%84%B1%EA%B7%A0/%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%98%81%ED%98%BC%EC%97%90/" title="강성균 - 나의 영혼에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나의 영혼에 유일한 만족 되시는 <br>사랑스런 주님 음성 듣길 원하네 <br>세상 헛된 바람들로 지쳐버린 <br>나의 영혼 주님의 옷자락 만집니다 <br>주님은 나의 사랑 <br>주님은 나의 노래 <br>주님은 나의 모든 것 <br>아시는 아바 아버지 <br>주님은 나의 사랑 <br>주님은 나의 노래 <br>주님은 나의 앉고 <br>일어섬을 아시네 <br>나의 영혼에 유일한 만족 되시는 <br>사랑스런 주님 음성 듣길 원하네 <br>세상 헛된 바람들로 지쳐버린 <br>나의 영혼 주님의 옷자락 만집니다 <br>주님은 나의 사랑 <br>주님은 나의 노래 <br>주님은 나의 모든 것 <br>아시는 아바 아버지 <br>주님은 나의 사랑 <br>주님은 나의 노래 <br>주님은 나의 앉고 <br>일어섬을 아시네 <br>주님은 나의 사랑 <br>주님은 나의 노래 <br>주님은 나의 모든 것 <br>아시는 아바 아버지 <br>주님은 나의 사랑 <br>주님은 나의 노래 <br>주님은 나의 앉고 <br>일어섬을 <br>나의 앉고 일어섬을 <br>나의 앉고 일어섬을 아시네 <br>]]></content><category term="강성균" label="강성균"/><category term="나의 영혼에" label="나의 영혼에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강성균/신실하신_주사랑/</id><title>강성균 - 신실하신 주사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:17:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:17:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%84%B1%EA%B7%A0/%EC%8B%A0%EC%8B%A4%ED%95%98%EC%8B%A0_%EC%A3%BC%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="강성균 - 신실하신 주사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주의 인자하심이 <br>생명보다 나으므로 <br>나의 입술이 <br>주를 찬양합니다 <br>주의 신실하심이 <br>먼저 나를 사랑하시며 <br>한없는 은혜로 <br>자녀 삼으신 나의 주 <br>신실하신 주사랑 <br>신실하신 기다리심을 <br>변함없는 그 자리에서 <br>나를 인도하심을 <br>신실하신 주사랑 <br>신실하신 기다리심을 <br>나의 주께 고백하는 말 <br>주는 선하십니다 <br>주의 인자하심이 <br>생명보다 나으므로 <br>나의 입술이 <br>주를 찬양합니다 <br>주의 신실하심이 <br>먼저 나를 사랑하시며 <br>한없는 은혜로 <br>자녀 삼으신 나의 주 <br>신실하신 주사랑 <br>신실하신 기다리심을 <br>변함없는 그 자리에서 <br>나를 인도하심을 <br>신실하신 주사랑 <br>신실하신 기다리심을 <br>나의 주께 고백하는 말 <br>주는 선하십니다 <br>신실하신 주사랑 <br>신실하신 기다리심을 <br>변함없는 그 자리에서 <br>나를 인도하심을 <br>신실하신 주사랑 <br>신실하신 기다리심을 <br>나의 주께 고백하는 말 <br>주는 선하십니다 <br>신실하신 나의 주님 <br>변함없는 그 자리에서 <br>나를 인도하심을 <br>신실하신 주사랑 <br>신실하신 기다리심을 <br>나의 주께 고백하는 말 <br>주는 선하십니다 <br>]]></content><category term="강성균" label="강성균"/><category term="신실하신 주사랑" label="신실하신 주사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시나브로_XINABRO/뇌전수리검_Raiden_Shuriken_Feat_Prod_Barchee/</id><title>시나브로 (XINABRO) - 뇌전수리검 (Raiden Shuriken) (Feat, Prod. Barchee) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:17:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:17:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EB%82%98%EB%B8%8C%EB%A1%9C_XINABRO/%EB%87%8C%EC%A0%84%EC%88%98%EB%A6%AC%EA%B2%80_Raiden_Shuriken_Feat_Prod_Barchee/" title="시나브로 (XINABRO) - 뇌전수리검 (Raiden Shuriken) (Feat, Prod. Barchee) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오스 <br>와타시 타치노 슈리켄와 <br>제타이 하즈레나이 <br>와타시와 테키노 <br>신조오 네라으 카이시 <br>나의 모든 기를 <br>수리검의 끝에 모아 일격으로 <br>적을 실수없이 단 한번에 처리 <br>나의 모든 기를 <br>수리검의 끝에 모아 일격으로 <br>적을 실수없이 단 한번에 처리 <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>나의 모든 기를 <br>수리검의 끝에 모아 일격으로 <br>적을 실수없이 단 한번에 처리 <br>나의 모든 기를 <br>수리검의 끝에 모아 일격으로 <br>적을 실수없이 단 한번에 처리 <br>시간이 더 빨리와서 빨리가야지 <br>할일 아직 많이 있잖아 코를 반이나 <br>먹은 소릴 들었다면 알겠지만 <br>콧물 조차 녹음하는데는 개의치 않아 <br>확실해 내 목소리가 가는 곳 <br>목적이 다다를때까진 <br>머리 위의 물음표 <br>What the 정신병 <br>머리 아플 것은 이젠 없다고 <br>해내는 일만 남어 볼 건 <br>미래와의 박수 <br>합작이 되어가는중 <br>본전은 안 치니까 불려가는 중이지 <br>돈다발 뿌리는 나를 봐 <br>아침에 머리에다 품은 짓이 <br>변화를 주니 So <br>가만 가만 있을 수는 없잖어 <br>난 그냥 멋져 단순하게 살래 <br>몰라 뭐가 진리인지도 필요하지 않지 <br>Rhyme도 안 맞추는 이 4마디를 보면 <br>넌 뭐라 생각할지 난 그게 궁금하지 <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>나의 모든 기를 <br>수리검의 끝에 모아 일격으로 <br>적을 실수없이 단 한번에 처리 <br>나의 모든 기를 <br>수리검의 끝에 모아 일격으로 <br>적을 실수없이 단 한번에 처리 <br>세간의 화두를 찜할래 <br>내 간이 부었는지는 <br>너가 확인해 조만간에 <br>그래 야 내 어깨에는 <br>추가 좀 많아 휴가는 No 꿈이야 <br>안 구르면 가라앉는 걸 <br>어째 수영같은거야 <br>하나를 원해 저 많은 것 중에서도 <br>이름을 놓을 날 한국힙합의 서두에 <br>계획 앞에 행동이 늘 서야 돼 선두에 <br>그래야 온대요 날 태울 <br>성공의 선장님이 <br>Bling Bling <br>도금이 된 황금배를 타래 <br>그 담에 다이아 닻 내려 <br>신대륙에 착지해 <br>성 안엔 나의 형제와 <br>식구만을 초대한 뒤에 <br>Let's Party PaParty <br>가만두지말어 팔다리 yeahy <br>누가 누가 나보다 심장이 두껍냐 <br>가벼운 내 피부 잘 날아다니지 <br>Fly Fly Over the moon Over the moon <br>실력없는 뜬구름 재껴 <br>뚫어가서 달에 박어 지문 <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>나의 모든 기를 <br>수리검의 끝에 모아 일격으로 <br>적을 실수없이 단 한번에 처리 <br>나의 모든 기를 <br>수리검의 끝에 모아 일격으로 <br>적을 실수없이 단 한번에 처리 <br>다음 세기 다음 세기 <br>아니 다음 다음 세기 <br>새끼의 새끼의 <br>다음 세기의 다음 다음 새끼 <br>그 다다다다 다음 새끼 다음 다음 다음 <br>다다다다다다다다 다음 새끼들까지 <br>내 목소리 들리게 집어던져대 내 <br>모가진 돌부처의 어깨 날아가지 높게 <br>잘해 평소에 <br>레버리대서사시의 시작을 <br>알리는 총성이 울려퍼져 <br>도시란 계곡에 물흐르듯이 <br>몰려오던 시꺼먼 차들이 길을 터 <br>모세가 실존했을 수도 <br>있구나 싶은 맘이 들어 <br>태생이 꼴리는대로 살어 <br>살얼음 위라도 거침 없이 걷지 <br>커진 균열 사이 <br>흩날리는 눈같은 먼질 먹지 <br>벗지 마스크 내성이 생긴 호흡기 <br>수리검 수리검 우린 뇌전수리검 <br>퓩퓩퓩A <br>수리검 수리검 우린 뇌전수리검 <br>퓩퓩퓩A <br>수리검 수리검 우린 뇌전수리검 <br>퓩퓩퓩A <br>수리검 수리검 우린 뇌전수리검 <br>MotherFxxker <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>정확하게 타겟에게 맞게 돼 <br>내 뇌전수리검 뇌전수리검 <br>]]></content><category term="시나브로 (XINABRO)" label="시나브로 (XINABRO)"/><category term="뇌전수리검 (Raiden Shuriken) (Feat, Prod. Barchee)" label="뇌전수리검 (Raiden Shuriken) (Feat, Prod. Barchee)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/수란_SURAN/수란_水蘭/</id><title>수란 (SURAN) - 수란 (水蘭) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:17:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:17:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%88%98%EB%9E%80_SURAN/%EC%88%98%EB%9E%80_%E6%B0%B4%E8%98%AD/" title="수란 (SURAN) - 수란 (水蘭) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[라이라이야 라이라이야 <br>라이라이야 아아아 <br>손 내밀면 닿을 것 같아 <br>부푼 가슴 어떡할까 <br>나의 마음을 구름에 실어본다 <br>missing you missing you <br>그리움은 눈물이 되어 <br>그대의 가슴을 적셔주길 <br>아프지 않나요 저만 이런가요 <br>매일 그리워하다 울죠 <br>사랑이 원래 이렇게 아픈가요 <br>말해줘요 <br>눈물이라도 닿을 까봐서 운다 <br>라이라이야 라이라이야 <br>라이라이야 아아아 <br>missing you missing you <br>그리움은 빗물이 되어 <br>아픈 내 가슴을 적셔주길 <br>아프지 않나요 저만 이런가요 <br>매일 그리워하다 울죠 <br>사랑이 원래 이렇게 아픈가요 <br>말해줘요 <br>눈물이 될까요 빗물이 될까요 <br>그대의 가슴에 닿을까요 <br>사랑이 원래 이렇게 아픈가요 <br>말해줘요 <br>눈물이라도 닿을 까봐서 운다 <br>눈물이라도 닿을 까봐서 운다 <br>]]></content><category term="수란 (SURAN)" label="수란 (SURAN)"/><category term="수란 (水蘭)" label="수란 (水蘭)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Getter/Something_Good/</id><title>Getter - Something Good - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:17:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:17:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Getter/Something_Good/" title="Getter - Something Good - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Heart beats fast <br>Colours and promises <br>How to be brave <br>How can I love when I'm afraid to fall <br>But watching you stand alone <br>All of my doubt suddenly goes away somehow <br><br>One step closer <br><br>I have died every day waiting for you <br>Darling, don't be afraid <br>I have loved you for a thousand years <br>I'll love you for a thousand more <br><br>Time stands still <br>Beauty in all she is <br>I will be brave <br>I will not let anything take away <br>What's standing in front of me <br>Every breath <br>Every hour has come to this <br><br>One step closer <br><br>I have died every day waiting for you <br>Darling, don't be afraid <br>I have loved you for a thousand years <br>I'll love you for a thousand more <br><br>And all along I believed I would find you <br>Time has brought your heart to me <br>I have loved you for a thousand years <br>I'll love you for a thousand more <br><br>One step closer <br>One step closer <br><br>I have died every day waiting for you <br>Darling, don't be afraid <br>I have loved you for a thousand years <br>I'll love you for a thousand more <br><br>And all along I believed I would find you <br>Time has brought your heart to me <br>I have loved you for a thousand years <br>I'll love you for a thousand more]]></content><category term="Getter" label="Getter"/><category term="Something Good" label="Something Good"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비더제이_BtheJ/제기차기/</id><title>비더제이 (BtheJ) - 제기차기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:17:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:17:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%EB%8D%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4_BtheJ/%EC%A0%9C%EA%B8%B0%EC%B0%A8%EA%B8%B0/" title="비더제이 (BtheJ) - 제기차기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이런 제길 차자 이런 제길 차자 <br>이런 제길 차자 이런 제길 차자 <br>이런 제 길 찾아 이런 제 길 찾아 <br>이런 제 길 찾아 이젠 네 길 찾아 <br>이런 제길 차자 아무 생각 없이 <br>이런 제길 차자 아무 생각 없이 <br>이런 제 길 제 길 허 <br>이런 제 길 찾아 아무 생각 없이 <br>이젠 네 길 찾아 아무 생각 없이 <br>이젠 네 길 찾아 아무 생각 없이 <br>이젠 네 길 네 길 허 <br>이젠 네 길 찾아 <br>힘들고 외롭고 괴로우니 제 길 찾아 <br>더럽고 서럽고 치사하니 <br>제 길 찾아 허 <br>세월도 떠나고 님도 떠나니 <br>제 길 찾아 <br>뻘짓 그만하고 이제 그만 <br>네 길 찾아 어허 <br>제길 차 제길 차 제길 차 제길 차 <br>제길 차 제길 제길 제길 차 제길 차 <br>제길 차 제길 차 제길 차 제길 차 <br>제길 차 제길 제길 제길 차 제길 차 <br>이런 제길 차자 이런 제길 차자 <br>이런 제길 차자 이런 제길 차자 <br>이런 제 길 찾아 이런 제 길 찾아 <br>이런 제 길 찾아 이젠 네 길 찾아 <br>인생은 빙글빙글 돌아가는 회전목마 <br>어디론가 가다가도 다시 돌아온다 <br>끊임없이 계속되는 제자리 걸음마 <br>똑같은 해가 뜨고 또 날이 저문다 <br>반복되는 Up &amp; Down 리듬 속에 <br>미련들은 다 쏙 뺀 다음 <br>어두운 밤 계속되는 Party <br>Gettin' Jiggy with it <br>Gettin' Jeggy with it <br>힘들고 외롭고 괴로우니 제 길 찾아 <br>더럽고 서럽고 치사하니 <br>제 길 찾아 허 <br>세월도 떠나고 님도 떠나니 <br>제 길 찾아 <br>뻘짓 그만하고 이제 그만 <br>네 길 찾아 어허 <br>제길 차 제길 차 제길 차 제길 차 <br>제길 차 제길 제길 제길 차 제길 차 <br>제길 차 제길 차 제길 차 제길 차 <br>제길 차 제길 제길 제길 차 제길 차 <br>제제제제기를 차 제제제제기를 랄라 <br>제제제기를 차 제제제제제기를 <br>제제제제기를 차 제제제제기를 랄라 <br>제제제기를 차 제제제제제기를 <br>]]></content><category term="비더제이 (BtheJ)" label="비더제이 (BtheJ)"/><category term="제기차기" label="제기차기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마블제이_MarvelJ/Jay_world/</id><title>마블제이 (Marvel.J) - Jay world - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:17:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:17:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%B8%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4_MarvelJ/Jay_world/" title="마블제이 (Marvel.J) - Jay world - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[uh 이건 JAY WORLD <br>내 앨범 이름은 GRADUATION <br>uh uh 난 준비 돼있어 <br>어떤 유혹을 해도 Yeah <br>Imma dream chaser <br>MOFUCKER 굳건한 태도 <br>나는 내 삶을 멋지게 사는 법을 알어 <br>big baller <br>나는 사소한 거 하나까지 <br>감사할 줄 알아 <br>넌 랩퍼를 자처하며 mc가 <br>뭔지 모르고 떠드는 애 <br>힙합 한다고 목소리 까뒤집고 <br>여기저기 또 떠벌리는 애 <br>그렇게 돈 벌고 싶냐 씨발놈아 <br>난 떳떳하게 나의 능력 팔어 <br>날 물로 봐도 어쩔 수 없어 <br>난 공익도 아냐 <br>내 학자금 대출 어느덧 천을 넘어 <br>BUT 난 머리부터 발끝까지 <br>전부 내 돈 <br>FUCK FUCK 어느 <br>녀석들은 엄마 돈으로 <br>등록금 내고 밥 먹어 먹어 <br>UH UH 돈 벌러 왔어 듣고 와라 <br>난 씨잼처럼 밥을 나가서 사먹어 <br>BUT 난 내가 번 내 돈으로 <br>설령 그게 몇 천원 컵라면이어도 <br>난 모자라서 늘 네 머리 위에 있지 <br>이미 벼랑 끝이라서 잃을 게 없지 <br>넌 네 자식부터 손주까지 <br>꿈도 못 꿀 간지 <br>but 난 5년째 루키 난 <br>그 사실이 fuck that shit <br>많은 랩퍼들은 내 <br>무명에 의문을 품겠지 <br>지금도 솔직히 믹싱비 없어서 죽겠지 <br>but 난 곧 베이식 형이 말했듯 <br>한국 힙합 씬 미랠 이끌겠지 <br>올려놔라 당장 나의 기대치 <br>Just do ma thang <br>딱 내가 하는 만큼 받고 싶어 <br>나의 크루 안에 <br>갇혀 아이언 형과 아이들로 <br>전락할 생각 없네 <br>니가 뭘 알아 나에 대해 대체 <br>내 신념 절대 굽지 않네 <br>나는 태도가 분명해 내 모든 <br>삶 안에 것들의 감사 할 줄 아네 <br>그게 내 최고의 힘이네 <br>내 빽은 주님이네 두려울 게 없어 <br>내 자존감은 하늘을 찌르고 <br>있지 니키 미나즈 <br>같은 년 엉덩이 두 짝을 <br>후려칠 때까지 멈추지 않지 <br>내 GRADUATION <br>아직 말하지 난 절대 <br>실수 반복치 않아 <br>이제 술 취하면 입 다물지 아마 <br>힙합이라고 하고픈 말 다 뱉지 않아 <br>그게 내 성공의 걸림돌이 <br>될 걸 알아서 <br>하지만 내 음악 내 트랙 <br>위에선 그딴 일 없지 <br>겸손은 하나 내 인생에 도움 안 될 <br>인간들 존중 안 해 빨 일 없지 <br>난 항상 최고를 상상해 애미야 시로 <br>내 랩은 상당해 매번 다 죽여서 <br>명절에 사촌들 Forgive me <br>Forgive me 내가 좀 잘났어 <br>신께서 제일 공들인 놈 하나 <br>뽑으라면 그게 바로 나일 걸 <br>신경 안 써 회사나 Lable <br>이젠 시급 벌어 만든 내 앨범이 <br>자랑스러운 내 swag이고 <br>이걸 누가 부정하겠어 <br>그걸로 만져야지 versace sace <br>Gucci Louis 또는 죽이는 집 <br>내가 하고픈 일 음악하고 벌지 <br>내 첫 번째 꿈이자 최종 목표지 <br>그 다음 목푠 태권도 Chillin' <br>with my Kyunghee bro <br>지도자 피가 흘러 싸울아비의 정신도 <br>싸움 나면 난 바로 <br>사과하지 죄송합니다 <br>농담 반 진담 반 joke 그 녀석 <br>쓰러진 시첸 <br>치우기 귀찮으니까 <br>프리스타일하던 형들이 <br>부러워 난 여기까지 <br>왔지 아직 멀었지만 이젠 그 <br>형들에게 나는 인정을 받기 시작했지 <br>와라 많이 나의 돈 나의 명예 <br>그것들은 내 인생을 폼 나게 해 <br>내가 내가 되어가는 것 날 담금질 해 <br>Welcome to my graduation <br>]]></content><category term="마블제이 (Marvel.J)" label="마블제이 (Marvel.J)"/><category term="Jay world" label="Jay world"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카폴리_자동차_동요/붕붕붕_스쿨버스_안전송_English_Ver/</id><title>로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 붕붕붕 스쿨버스 안전송 (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:18:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:18:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9E%90%EB%8F%99%EC%B0%A8_%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/%EB%B6%95%EB%B6%95%EB%B6%95_%EC%8A%A4%EC%BF%A8%EB%B2%84%EC%8A%A4_%EC%95%88%EC%A0%84%EC%86%A1_English_Ver/" title="로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 붕붕붕 스쿨버스 안전송 (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[He, he. Drive safe! Let’s roll! <br><br>Make way for school B. Vroom vroom vroom, vroom vroom vroom. <br>Make way for school B. Vroom vroom. Vroom vroom. <br>321! Oh~ <br><br>Get on the bus! Now, you stop! Look right left! Look right left! <br>Get on the bus! Now you stop! Look right and left! <br>321! Oh~ <br><br>Take a ride! Now, you stop! Buckle on! Buckle on! <br>Take a ride! Now you stop! Everybody! <br>"Buckle on!" <br>321! Oh~ <br><br>Don’t move around, stay in your seat, in your seat! <br>Don’t move around, stay in your seat, in your seat! <br>321! Oh~ <br><br>Here we go with School B. La la la. La la la. <br>Here we go with School B. La la la la. <br><br>321! Ha Ha Ha~]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="붕붕붕 스쿨버스 안전송 (English Ver.)" label="붕붕붕 스쿨버스 안전송 (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카폴리_자동차_동요/쓱싹쓱싹_클리니_청소송_English_Ver/</id><title>로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 쓱싹쓱싹 클리니 청소송 (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:18:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:18:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9E%90%EB%8F%99%EC%B0%A8_%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/%EC%93%B1%EC%8B%B9%EC%93%B1%EC%8B%B9_%ED%81%B4%EB%A6%AC%EB%8B%88_%EC%B2%AD%EC%86%8C%EC%86%A1_English_Ver/" title="로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 쓱싹쓱싹 클리니 청소송 (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s go! <br>Okay! Cleany ok! Okay! Cleany ok! <br><br>Hey, good morning everyone. Here Cleany come. Vroom vroom. <br>It’s time to clean everything. It makes me feel so good. <br>The garbage in the garbage can. <br>The things are in places. <br>It’s cleaning time. Fun! Cleany time! All together! “Let’s clean!” <br><br>Okay? Okay! <br><br>Pick it, pick it! Pick it up! <br>Clean it, clean it! Clean it up! <br><br>Pick it up! Clean it up! <br>It makes me feel so good! <br><br>Okay! Cleany, okay! <br>Okay? Okay!]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="쓱싹쓱싹 클리니 청소송 (English Ver.)" label="쓱싹쓱싹 클리니 청소송 (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카폴리_자동차_동요/영차차_브룸스타운의_항구팀_English_Ver/</id><title>로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 영차차 브룸스타운의 항구팀 (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:18:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:18:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9E%90%EB%8F%99%EC%B0%A8_%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/%EC%98%81%EC%B0%A8%EC%B0%A8_%EB%B8%8C%EB%A3%B8%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80%EC%9A%B4%EC%9D%98_%ED%95%AD%EA%B5%AC%ED%8C%80_English_Ver/" title="로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 영차차 브룸스타운의 항구팀 (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yo-ho! Yo-ho-ho! Yo-heave-ho! Harbour! <br>Yo-ho! Yo-ho-ho! Yo-heave-ho! Harbour! <br><br>We are harbour three cranes. <br>Leky! Lety! Lefy! <br>Super harbour three cranes. <br>Leky! Lety! Lefy! <br><br>Lift up, up, up! <br>Lift down, down, down! <br><br>Containers! <br>Heavy things! <br>Move, move, move, done! <br><br>We are harbour three cranes. <br>Leky! Lety! Lefy! <br><br>Harbour! <br>Harbour! <br><br>We are harbour vehicles. <br>Terry! Cici! Lifty! <br>Super harbour vehicles. <br>Terry! Cici! Lifty! <br><br>On the sea, sea, sea. <br>On a road, road, road. <br><br>Containers! <br>Heavy things! <br>Move, move, move, done! <br><br>We are harbour vehicles. <br>Terry! Cici! Lifty!]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="영차차 브룸스타운의 항구팀 (English Ver.)" label="영차차 브룸스타운의 항구팀 (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카폴리_자동차_동요/으라차차_공사장_친구들_English_Ver/</id><title>로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 으라차차 공사장 친구들 (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:18:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:18:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9E%90%EB%8F%99%EC%B0%A8_%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/%EC%9C%BC%EB%9D%BC%EC%B0%A8%EC%B0%A8_%EA%B3%B5%EC%82%AC%EC%9E%A5_%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC%EB%93%A4_English_Ver/" title="로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 으라차차 공사장 친구들 (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One, two, three, four! One, two, three, four! <br><br>Go! Go! Excavator! <br>Go! Go! Go! Bulldozer! <br><br>Dig it up! Lift it up! Excavator, Poke! <br>Vroom-pa-vroom-pa-vroom-pa-boom! <br><br>Push, push the dirt away. Bulldozer, Bruner! <br>Vroom-pa-vroom-pa-vroom-pa-boom! <br><br>Go! Go! Dump Truck! <br>Go! Go! Go! Steamroller! <br><br>Carry and dump the dirt. Dump truck, Dumpoo! <br>Vroom-pa-vroom-pa-vroom-pa-boom! <br><br>Roll and roll. Press! Press! Steamroller, Max! <br>Vroom-pa-vroom-pa-vroom-pa-boom! <br><br>One, two, three, four! One, two, three, four! <br>We are the world best construction team. <br>The greatest friendship! Supreme teamwork. <br>We are the world best construction team. <br>The greatest friendship! Supreme teamwork. <br><br>Go! Go! Excavator! <br>Go! Go! Go! Bulldozer! <br>Go! Go! Dump Truck! <br>Go! Go! Go! Steamroller! <br><br>Go! Go! Construction team!]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="으라차차 공사장 친구들 (English Ver.)" label="으라차차 공사장 친구들 (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카폴리_자동차_동요/삐뽀삐뽀_용감한_구조대_English_Ver/</id><title>로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 삐뽀삐뽀 용감한 구조대 (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:18:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:18:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9E%90%EB%8F%99%EC%B0%A8_%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/%EC%82%90%EB%BD%80%EC%82%90%EB%BD%80_%EC%9A%A9%EA%B0%90%ED%95%9C_%EA%B5%AC%EC%A1%B0%EB%8C%80_English_Ver/" title="로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 삐뽀삐뽀 용감한 구조대 (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Emergency! Emergency! All unit ready to move out! <br>To the rescue! <br><br>I’m Poli. Police car, Poli. I patrol day and night. <br>I’m Roy. Fire truck, Roy. I go to put out a fire. <br>I’m Amber. Ambulance, Amber. I help emergency patients. <br>I’m Helly. Helicopter, Helly. I fly whenever you need help. <br>Good job, guys! <br><br>Ling-a-ling-ding-dong! Nee-naw, nee-naw! <br>Ling-a-ling-ding-dong! Nee-naw, nee-naw! <br>Ling-a-ling-ding-dong! Nee-naw, nee-naw! <br>Ling-a-ling-ding-dong! Nee-naw, nee-naw! <br><br>Super Duper Brave Rescue Team. <br>Poli! Roy! Amber! Helly! <br>Super Duper Brave Rescue Team. <br>Poli! Roy! Amber! Helly! <br><br>Ling-a-ling-ding-dong! Nee-naw, nee-naw! <br>Ling-a-ling-ding-dong! Nee-naw, nee-naw! <br>Ling-a-ling-ding-dong! Nee-naw, nee-naw! <br>Ling-a-ling-ding-dong! Nee-naw, nee-naw!]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="삐뽀삐뽀 용감한 구조대 (English Ver.)" label="삐뽀삐뽀 용감한 구조대 (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카폴리_자동차_동요/붕붕붕_스쿨버스_안전송/</id><title>로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 붕붕붕 스쿨버스 안전송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:18:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:18:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9E%90%EB%8F%99%EC%B0%A8_%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/%EB%B6%95%EB%B6%95%EB%B6%95_%EC%8A%A4%EC%BF%A8%EB%B2%84%EC%8A%A4_%EC%95%88%EC%A0%84%EC%86%A1/" title="로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 붕붕붕 스쿨버스 안전송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[헤헷! 오늘도 안전하게! 출발! <br><br>스쿨비가 달려요.붕붕붕붕붕붕! <br>스쿨비가 달려요. 붕붕 붕붕! <br><br>321! 오~ <br><br>조심조심 살펴요. 오른쪽왼쪽! <br>조심조심 살펴요. 오른쪽 왼쪽! <br><br>321! 오~ <br><br>안전벨트 매야죠.착착착착착착! <br>안전벨트 매야죠. 착착착착! <br><br>321! 오~ <br><br>버스에선 얌전히 제자리제자리. <br>버스에선 얌전히 자리 제자리. <br><br>321! 오~ <br><br>스쿨비와 달려요.랄랄라랄랄라~ <br>스쿨비와 달려요.랄랄랄라! <br><br>321!와~~ 하하하하하!]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="붕붕붕 스쿨버스 안전송" label="붕붕붕 스쿨버스 안전송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카폴리_자동차_동요/쓱싹쓱싹_클리니_청소송/</id><title>로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 쓱싹쓱싹 클리니 청소송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:18:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:18:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9E%90%EB%8F%99%EC%B0%A8_%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/%EC%93%B1%EC%8B%B9%EC%93%B1%EC%8B%B9_%ED%81%B4%EB%A6%AC%EB%8B%88_%EC%B2%AD%EC%86%8C%EC%86%A1/" title="로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 쓱싹쓱싹 클리니 청소송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[클리니 출동! <br><br>오케이! 준비, 오케이! 오케이! 준비, 오케이! <br><br>아침 일찍 클리니가 달려가요.부릉 붕붕! <br>청소는 정말 즐거워. 기분이 좋아~ <br>휴지는 휴지통에, 물건은 제자리에 <br>우리 모두 모여 다함께 청소해요. <br><br>오케이? 오케이! <br><br>쓱싹쓱싹 깨끗이! <br>쓱싹쓱싹 청소해! <br>쓱쓱쓱!싹싹싹! <br>기분이 좋아. <br><br>오케이! 청소, 오케이! <br>오케이? 오케이!]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="쓱싹쓱싹 클리니 청소송" label="쓱싹쓱싹 클리니 청소송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카폴리_자동차_동요/영차차_브룸스타운의_항구팀/</id><title>로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 영차차 브룸스타운의 항구팀 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:18:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:18:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9E%90%EB%8F%99%EC%B0%A8_%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/%EC%98%81%EC%B0%A8%EC%B0%A8_%EB%B8%8C%EB%A3%B8%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80%EC%9A%B4%EC%9D%98_%ED%95%AD%EA%B5%AC%ED%8C%80/" title="로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 영차차 브룸스타운의 항구팀 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리는 영차차브룸스 항구팀.오예! <br>우리는 영차차브룸스 항구팀.오예! <br><br>크레인 삼형제! <br>레키! 레티! 레피! <br>즐겁게 일해요. <br>레키! 레티! 레피! <br>올려요, 위로 위로! <br>내려요, 아래 아래로! <br><br>무거운 짐 <br>모두 <br>우리에게 맡겨요! 예! <br>크레인 삼형제! <br>레키! 레티! 레피! <br><br>브룸스! <br>브룸스! <br><br>항구 짐을 나르는 <br>테리! 씨씨! 리프티! <br>즐겁게 일해요. <br>테리! 씨씨! 리프티! <br>바다 위에서 <br>땅 위에서 <br><br>무거운 짐 <br>모두 <br>우리에게 맡겨요. 예! <br>항구 짐을 나르는 <br>테리! 씨씨! 리프티!]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="영차차 브룸스타운의 항구팀" label="영차차 브룸스타운의 항구팀"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카폴리_자동차_동요/으라차차_공사장_친구들/</id><title>로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 으라차차 공사장 친구들 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:18:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:18:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9E%90%EB%8F%99%EC%B0%A8_%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/%EC%9C%BC%EB%9D%BC%EC%B0%A8%EC%B0%A8_%EA%B3%B5%EC%82%AC%EC%9E%A5_%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC%EB%93%A4/" title="로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 으라차차 공사장 친구들 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나, 둘, 셋, 넷! 하나, 둘, 셋, 넷! <br><br>Go! Go!포클레인! <br>Go! Go! Go! 불도저! <br><br>쿵! 쿵! 땅 파는 나는 포클레인! <br>쿵-따-쿵-따-쿵-따-쿵! <br><br>쭉! 쭉! 흙 밀어내는 나는 불도저! <br>쭈욱-쭉-쭈욱-쭉-쭈욱-쭉-쭉! <br><br>Go! Go! 덤프트럭! <br>Go! Go! Go! 스팀롤러! <br><br>부릉! 부릉! 흙 나르는 나는 덤프트럭! <br>부릉-파-부릉-파-부릉-파-부릉! <br><br>꾹! 꾹! 땅 누르는 나는 스팀롤러! <br>꾸욱-꾹-꾸욱-꾹-꾸욱-꾹-꾹! <br><br>하나, 둘, 셋, 넷! 하나, 둘, 셋, 넷! <br>으라차차 공사장 친구들. <br>세계 최고 팀워크, 우리가 간다! <br>으라차차 공사장 친구들. <br>다 함께 힘을 모아~ 얍! <br><br>Go! Go! 포클레인! <br>Go! Go! Go! 불도저! <br>Go! Go! 덤프트럭! <br>Go! Go! Go! 스팀롤러! <br><br>공사장친구들!]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="으라차차 공사장 친구들" label="으라차차 공사장 친구들"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로보카폴리_자동차_동요/삐뽀삐뽀_용감한_구조대/</id><title>로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 삐뽀삐뽀 용감한 구조대 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:18:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:18:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%B3%B4%EC%B9%B4%ED%8F%B4%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9E%90%EB%8F%99%EC%B0%A8_%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/%EC%82%90%EB%BD%80%EC%82%90%EB%BD%80_%EC%9A%A9%EA%B0%90%ED%95%9C_%EA%B5%AC%EC%A1%B0%EB%8C%80/" title="로보카폴리 자동차 동요 - 삐뽀삐뽀 용감한 구조대 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사고 발생! 사고 발생! <br>모든 대원들은 지금 당장 출동해줘! <br>출동! <br><br>나는 폴리. 경찰차 폴리. <br>씽씽씽 마을 지켜요. <br>나는 로이. 소방차 로이. <br>용감하게 불을 끄죠. <br>난 엠버. 구급차 엠버. <br>응급 환자 싣고 병원 가요. <br>나는 헬리. 헬리콥터 헬리. <br>도움 필요한 곳 어디든 날아가죠. <br>모두들 수고했어! <br><br>링어링딩동! 삐뽀삐뽀! <br>링어링딩동! 삐뽀삐뽀! <br>링어링딩동! 삐뽀삐뽀! <br>링어링딩동! 삐뽀삐뽀! <br><br>슈퍼 두퍼 용감한 구조대 <br>폴리! 로이! 엠버! 헬리! <br>슈퍼 두퍼 용감한 구조대. <br>폴리! 로이! 엠버! 헬리! <br>슈퍼 두퍼 구조대! <br><br>링어링딩동! 삐뽀삐뽀! <br>링어링딩동! 삐뽀삐뽀! <br>링어링딩동! 삐뽀삐뽀! <br>링어링딩동! 삐뽀삐뽀!]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="삐뽀삐뽀 용감한 구조대" label="삐뽀삐뽀 용감한 구조대"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/준코코_Juncoco/POOL_PARTY/</id><title>준코코 (Juncoco) - POOL PARTY - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:19:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:19:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A4%80%EC%BD%94%EC%BD%94_Juncoco/POOL_PARTY/" title="준코코 (Juncoco) - POOL PARTY - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Everybody put your hands up <br>가슴이 타오를 pool party <br>Be brave <br>Everybody 같이 Jumping <br>Jumping <br>믿지 못할 지금 이순간 <br>feel so good <br>마치 우주 속 미지의 세계로 <br>나를 초대한 것 같아 <br>look at you you <br>look at me yeah <br>믿지 못할 이순간 yeah <br>Everybody put your hands up <br>가슴이 타오를 pool party <br>Be brave <br>Everybody 같이 Jumping <br>Jumping <br>믿지 못할 지금 이순간 <br>feel so good <br>]]></content><category term="준코코 (Juncoco)" label="준코코 (Juncoco)"/><category term="POOL PARTY" label="POOL PARTY"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유승우/오빠_PROD_Brother_Su/</id><title>유승우 - 오빠 (PROD. Brother Su) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:20:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:20:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EC%8A%B9%EC%9A%B0/%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%A0_PROD_Brother_Su/" title="유승우 - 오빠 (PROD. Brother Su) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 오빠란 말이 그렇게 <br>듣기 좋은 말인지 몰랐네 <br>그냥 부르는 것뿐인데 <br>자꾸 기분이 좋아지는 게 <br>난 오빠란 말에 그렇게 <br>환장하는 형들 이해 못했는데 <br>입 모양부터 소리까지 <br>어떻게 이런 말이 있나 싶네 <br>살면서 정말 <br>수천 수백 번도 넘게 <br>지겹도록 들었는데 <br>니가 그러니까 <br>왠지 멋진 남자라도 <br>된 것 같은데 <br>괜히 모른 척 하고 싶어 <br>한 번 더 니가 날 불러주게 <br>웃음 나는 걸 참고 있어 <br>그 말이 뭐라고 이렇게 좋은데 <br>그저 그런 하루였었는데 <br>전부 피곤해 미치겠었는데 <br>커피도 자양강장제 비타민도 <br>안 받는 그런 날이었는데 <br>근데 웃겨 나 진짜 이상해 <br>니가 웃으며 날 부르던 그 순간에 <br>막 힘이 나 웃음이 나고 <br>주책없이 기분을 감출 수가 없는데 <br>살면서 정말 <br>수천 수백 번도 넘게 <br>지겹도록 들었는데 <br>니가 그러니까 <br>왠지 뭐든지 다 할 수 <br>있을 것 같애 <br>괜히 모른 척 하고 싶어 <br>한 번 더 니가 날 불러주게 <br>웃음 나는 걸 참고 있어 <br>그 말이 뭐라고 이렇게 좋은데 <br>모든 게 특별해 <br>전부 다 변했어 <br>니가 날 불러준 그 때부터 <br>너라서 특별해 <br>평생 듣고 싶어 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 지금처럼 my baby <br>괜히 모른 척 하고 싶어 <br>한 번 더 니가 날 불러주게 <br>웃음 나는 걸 참고 있어 <br>그 말이 뭐라고 이렇게 좋은데 <br>괜히 모른 척 하고 싶어 <br>웃음 나는 걸 참고 있어 <br>그 말이 뭐라고 이렇게 좋은데 <br>]]></content><category term="유승우" label="유승우"/><category term="오빠 (PROD. Brother Su)" label="오빠 (PROD. Brother Su)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VAV/ABC_Middle_of_the_Night_Inst/</id><title>VAV - ABC (Middle of the Night) (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:20:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:20:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VAV/ABC_Middle_of_the_Night_Inst/" title="VAV - ABC (Middle of the Night) (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Til’ the middle of the night <br>Uh Come on <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>oh oh oh oh oh <br>Til’ the middle of the night <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>oh oh oh oh oh <br>Listen <br>오늘따라 왜 이리 예쁘게 웃는 건데 <br>네게만 약한 내 심장 <br>감당 할 수가 없게 <br>달콤한 눈빛이 동그란 두 볼이 <br>나에게 속삭여 Yeah <br>너도 내 맘과 같단 말 Uh <br>하늘엔 달 널 비춘 별 네 옆엔 나 <br>뗄 수 없는 한 쌍 같아 Ah baby Yeah <br>함께한 시간만큼 <br>커져버린 욕심에 Yeah <br>붙잡아 두고 싶은 맘 Uh <br>나 빼고 뭐든 No So dangerous <br>Got it all <br>속으로 앓고 있어 I’m jealous <br>Way to go <br>이런 말 못해 겉으론 멋있게 <br>Ready 1 2 3 4 5 <br>Til’ the middle of the night <br>너와 나 <br>꽉 잡은 두 손 모아 Baby <br>별빛 따라 Fly 날아가 <br>함께 보낸 시간들 만큼 <br>차곡차곡 A B C Hey One <br>Two Three Hey 차오르는 달 <br>Til’ the middle of the night <br>오늘 밤 <br>꼭 거짓말처럼 거짓말처럼 <br>Oh 꿈만 같은 밤 <br>Ayno <br>발그래진 두 볼이 말해 내가 좋다고 <br>속내를 가릴 그녀는 마치 <br>마릴린 먼로 whahh <br>여자의 존심은 hill 보다 <br>더 높다며 I know I know I know <br>Hey bartender come here <br>and give me a drink <br>해뜨긴 멀었는데 <br>벌써 내 동공은 풀림 babe <br>For fun tonight for your delight <br>Tonight I’m yours <br>지금부터 해 뜰 때까지 <br>until the dawn <br>함께 하고 싶은 열 가지 <br>내 옆에서 지켜봐 하나씩 보여줄게 <br>넌 까딱까딱 확신을 줘 확신을 줘 <br>나도 모르게 반응하네 <br>입술을 쪽 chu <br>자 이대로 이 밤을 밝혀줘 <br>1 2 3 here we go <br>Til’ the middle of the night <br>너와 나 <br>꽉 잡은 두 손 모아 Baby <br>별빛 따라 Fly 날아가 <br>함께 보낸 시간들 만큼 <br>차곡차곡 A B C Hey One <br>Two Three Hey 차오르는 달 <br>Til’ the middle of the night <br>오늘 밤 <br>꼭 거짓말처럼 거짓말처럼 <br>Oh 꿈만 같은 밤 <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh 꿈만 같은 밤 <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh 꿈만 같은 밤 <br>Ooh girl 딴 생각은 마 <br>내 곁에 머물러 항상 웃음만 줄게 <br>I got a crush on you <br>I hope my dreams come true <br>you’re my lady <br>너에게 one step two step 다가갈게 <br>자 이대로 손 놓지 말아줘 <br>Til’ the middle of the <br>Til’ the middle of the night <br>점점 더 <br>깊숙이 빠져들어 네게 <br>쏟아지는 Light 너처럼 <br>차갑게 다 식은 내 마음도 <br>하나둘씩 A B C Hey One <br>Two Three Hey 녹여주는 너 <br>Til’ the middle of the night <br>오늘 밤 <br>내 곁에 머물러 내게 머물러 <br>Oh 기적 같은 밤 <br>]]></content><category term="VAV" label="VAV"/><category term="ABC (Middle of the Night) (Inst.)" label="ABC (Middle of the Night) (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리디아_Lydia/우리_사랑했다면_Inst/</id><title>리디아 (Lydia) - 우리 사랑했다면 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T08:20:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T08:20:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%94%94%EC%95%84_Lydia/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%96%88%EB%8B%A4%EB%A9%B4_Inst/" title="리디아 (Lydia) - 우리 사랑했다면 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑이 시작되던 <br>잠 못 이루던 그날 그때로 <br>우리 다시 돌아갈 순 없을까 <br>모든 것이 궁금하고 <br>어떤 피곤함도 모르는 <br>마치 영원할 것만 같던 <br>사랑의 순간도 희미해져 가 <br>우리 사랑했다면 됐어 <br>모두 진심이라면 <br>그 아름다웠던 <br>사랑을 담아두려 해 <br>우리 사랑했기에 <br>좋았었던 기억만 <br>간직한 채 나 돌아서려 해 <br>심하게 다퉜던 날 <br>밤새 울다 지쳐 돌아선 그때 <br>그날로 다시 돌아갈 순 없을까 <br>전과 널 비교하고 <br>결국 변한 건 나였어 <br>너에게 어떤 아픔 <br>자라나고 있는지 알지 못했어 <br>우리 사랑했다면 됐어 <br>모두 진심이라면 <br>그 아름다웠던 <br>사랑을 담아두려 해 <br>우리 사랑했기에 <br>좋았었던 기억만 <br>간직한 채 나 돌아서려 해 <br>모두 남김없이 <br>후회 없이 사랑했다면 <br>우리 이제 더 이상 <br>돌아보지 말자 <br>우리 사랑했다면 됐어 <br>모두 진심이라면 <br>그 아름다웠던 <br>사랑을 담아두려 해 <br>우리 사랑했기에 <br>좋았었던 기억만 <br>간직한 채 나 돌아서려 해 <br>]]></content><category term="리디아 (Lydia)" label="리디아 (Lydia)"/><category term="우리 사랑했다면 (Inst.)" label="우리 사랑했다면 (Inst.)"/></entry></feed>