<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:11:39+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/떠나가지마_Remix_Feat_더블캐슬/</id><title>헤이노 - 떠나가지마 (Remix) (Feat. 더블캐슬) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:11:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:11:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EB%96%A0%EB%82%98%EA%B0%80%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88_Remix_Feat_%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/" title="헤이노 - 떠나가지마 (Remix) (Feat. 더블캐슬) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[병에든 건 술 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병이든 건 나아아아 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병이든 건 나아아아 <br>병에 든 거 같이 답답해 <br>너무 아파아아 <br>얼마 전까지는 살갗게 <br>대하 넌 너가아아 <br>사랑은 원래 변하나 봐 아아 <br>너만은 그러지 않기르으을 <br>바랬는데 떠나나 봐아아 <br>결국 나를 떠나나 봐아아 <br>bye bye 잘 가 잊지 않을게 <br>담배를 펴서 폐가 아파 <br>너와의 사랑이 깊었나 봐 <br>떠나가지마 떠나가지마 <br>bye bye 잘 가 잊지 않을게 <br>담배를 펴서 폐가 아파 <br>너와의 사랑이 깊었나 봐 <br>떠나가지마 떠나가지마 <br>난 담배를 많이 피는 흡연자 <br>난 바람을 많이 피는 방랑자 <br>내가 너무 나빠 그만 만나자 <br>해놓고 지금 후회 하고 있다 <br>있다 있다 만나고 싶다 <br>너를 너무 보고 싶다 <br>너를 너무 너무 사랑했던 나 <br>너를 너무 너무 아프게 했던 나 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병이든 건 나아아아 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병이든 건 나아아아 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병이든 건 나아아아 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병이든 건 나아아아 <br>우리 사랑 이제 여기까진 가봐 <br>내 사랑이 너무 많이 부족했어 <br>너무 예쁜 너는 행복하길 바래 <br>나의 하나뿐인 사랑 떠나가네 <br>병에 든 거 같이 답답해 <br>너무 아파아아아 <br>얼마 전까지는 살갗게 <br>대하던 너가아아아 <br>사랑은 원래 변하나 봐 아아 <br>너만은 그러지 않기르으을 <br>바랬는데 떠나나 봐아아 <br>결국 나를 떠나나 봐아아 <br>bye bye 잘 가 잊지 않을게 <br>담배를 펴서 폐가 아파 <br>너와의 사랑이 깊었나 봐 <br>떠나가지마 떠나가지마 <br>bye bye 잘 가 잊지 않을게 <br>담배를 펴서 폐가 아파 <br>너와의 사랑이 깊었나 봐 <br>떠나가지마 떠나가지마 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병이든 건 나아아아 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병이든 건 나아아아 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병이든 건 나아아아 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병이든 건 나아아아 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병이든 건 나아아아 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병이든 건 나아아아 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병이든 건 나아아아 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병에든 건 술 <br>병이든 건 나아아아 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="떠나가지마 (Remix) (Feat. 더블캐슬)" label="떠나가지마 (Remix) (Feat. 더블캐슬)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/모두가_잠든_밤에_Feat_Tase/</id><title>헤이노 - 모두가 잠든 밤에 (Feat. Tase) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:11:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:11:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EB%AA%A8%EB%91%90%EA%B0%80_%EC%9E%A0%EB%93%A0_%EB%B0%A4%EC%97%90_Feat_Tase/" title="헤이노 - 모두가 잠든 밤에 (Feat. Tase) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모두가 잠든 밤에 <br>난 계속 음악해에에 <br>너가 한숨 자면 <br>노래가 한곡 완성되에에 <br>이게 동화라면 <br>그건 늙지않는 피터패엔 <br>시간이 계속 가도 <br>나의 열정은 영원해에 <br>안녕 긴 훅을 지나 왔구나 <br>그럼 랩을 들려줘야 되겠지 <br>난 사실 아무생각 없기 땜에 <br>걍 막 말해서라도 가살 떼우네 <br>뭘 기대 한건데 넌 나한테 <br>돈도 안주면서 왜 그래 나한테 <br>욕 좀 하지 말어 난 맘이 나약해 <br>너무 아프잖아 안돼 빨리 나야돼 <br>타이스 한테 말해 너가 자고 일어나면 <br>내가 멋진 곡을 만들어 피처링을 줄게 <br>배리본즈처럼 난 예고 했지만 <br>이렇게 될거란걸 사실 예감 했지만 <br>아 어렵다 <br>음악이란 정말 끝이 없는 것만 같다 <br>모두가 잠든 밤에 <br>난 계속 음악해에에 <br>너가 한숨 자면 <br>노래가 한곡 완성되에에 <br>이게 동화라면 <br>그건 늙지않는 피터패엔 <br>시간이 계속 가도 <br>나의 열정은 영원해에 <br>눈떠 보니 헤이노 비트가 나와있네요 <br>기분 좋다 컴퓨터 켜 첫 가사는 A yo <br>야 저기 피드백봐 <br>별로 보이고 싶어하는 인공위성들 <br>밤 하늘 반짝 거린 모습 <br>많이 별로 우린 곧 저기 별로 <br>가려면 밤이 와야 먼저 <br>밤이 될때는 흉물도 알아볼수 없어 <br>내가 철 들었기 때문에 에펠탑 <br>계속 봐 날 계속봐 마이크 쥔 모습 <br>계속봐 만들게 효과 불러봐 오빠 <br>내가 나이 좀많아 의식의 흐름과 <br>fresh해 불러봐 혹은 물어봐 <br>물불 안가리니까 <br>날 꽉 잡고 있던 이성 옆에 잠든 밤 <br>모두가 잠든 밤에 <br>난 계속 음악해에에 <br>너가 한숨 자면 <br>노래가 한곡 완성되에에 <br>이게 동화라면 <br>그건 늙지않는 피터패엔 <br>시간이 계속 가도 <br>나의 열정은 영원해에 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="모두가 잠든 밤에 (Feat. Tase)" label="모두가 잠든 밤에 (Feat. Tase)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/Say_Feat_Tase/</id><title>헤이노 - Say (Feat. Tase) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:11:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:11:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/Say_Feat_Tase/" title="헤이노 - Say (Feat. Tase) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[say my name say my name <br>say my name <br>새까만 밤을 지나 너의 눈 앞에 <br>say my name say my name <br>say my name say my name <br>이제 불러줄때야 <br>yes say my name <br>say my name say my name <br>say my name <br>새까만 밤을 지나 너의 눈 앞에 <br>say my name say my name <br>say my name say my name <br>이제 불러줄때야 <br>yes say my name <br>yes say my name 드뎌 몇일만에 <br>다시 곡을 써 왠지 내가 별로란 생각에 <br>못했던 삶을 되찿네 a <br>이러곤 나는 못살어 a <br>나를 뒤따르는 부담감은 항상 <br>그럴때의 내 모습은 앙상 <br>뭐가 맞는 지는 나도 모르지이 <br>그저 느껴보는거지 나의 feel <br>내 팬은 늘어가도 나는 못 느껴 <br>내 랩은 무언가를 그려 오늘더 <br>바쁜 나날 그 공기들 타고 날아가 <br>시간은 빨러 난 노려 딱 하나만 <br>누군 말해 랩은 그냥 멋지기만 하면되 <br>누군가를 걱정말래 나는 이미 잘한대 <br>그래 알어 알지만 더 원해 난 <br>최고가 되기전엔 난 <br>아니 어쩌면 평생을 난 <br>이런 부담감에 매일 휩 싸여 <br>지쳐 싸워 가며 살아가야겠지 <br>그것도 괜찮아보이긴해 <br>난 무대 위 혹은 이렇게 <br>곡을 만들때가 제일 행복해 <br>내가 누군진 알거 없지만 <br>네게 하고픈 말이 하나 있어 <br>say my name say my name <br>say my name <br>새까만 밤을 지나 너의 눈 앞에 <br>say my name say my name <br>say my name say my name <br>이제 불러줄때야 <br>yes say my name <br>say my name say my name <br>say my name <br>새까만 밤을 지나 너의 눈 앞에 <br>say my name say my name <br>say my name say my name <br>이제 불러줄때야 <br>yes say my name <br>say my name say my name <br>say my name <br>네 입이 열릴때 이름 나오길 바래 <br>여길 대뇌인 다음에 넌 내 모습 닮네 <br>어쩜 비교 이상의 것 개체가 같네 <br>알게 된 것같아 이 곳에서 살아남는 법 <br>누군가에겐 랩은 그저 자랑하는 것 <br>너는 알아 이 곳을 사랑하는 법 <br>가사와 표현은 너를 따라가는 곡 <br>생김새가 다르듯 <br>각자 원하는건 다르지 <br>뜻 따르지만서도 <br>항상 바르지 못한 태도 <br>모든 것을 감수해도 원하는 것을 <br>얻는다 해도 지킬 수 있어 <br>고민 쌓인듯한 행동 <br>매일 매일 매일 채워지는 공책 속에 <br>pain and gain 쥘수 있을까 손에 <br>작년에 포기한 것이 <br>너무 커서 힘들어도 <br>모든것을 바칠 수 있어 <br>기도 간절히 원해 <br>내 자신을 벌해 눈 풀려 <br>나태 자신은 신발끈 풀려 <br>작은 방해 요소 때문에 <br>모든 것이 멈춰 <br>합리화 하는 모습 이해 못해 굼뜬 몸 <br>퉁퉁 부은 눈 밤마다 젖은 배게 <br>나를 불러줘 여까지 들리게 내게 <br>시간은 배가 되고 있어 노력의 정도 <br>멀리 돌아가진 않아 <br>지키는 태도 길은 正道 <br>정말 들리는가 내가 하고싶은 말들 <br>실어증을 깨는 순간들 질러줄게 악을 <br>많은 나를 집중하는 하늘 높은 bable <br>모든것의 근간은 내 신념으로부터 <br>i my me mine 단어 대표하는 대상 <br>암막이와도 확실 여기 빛이 된다 <br>지금 굽힌 무릎이 꿇음이 아닌 <br>더 높은 곳에 도달 위한 <br>추진 얻기 위한 자세다 <br>say my name say my name <br>say my name <br>새까만 밤을 지나 너의 눈 앞에 <br>say my name say my name <br>say my name say my name <br>이제 불러줄때야 <br>yes say my name <br>say my name say my name <br>say my name <br>새까만 밤을 지나 너의 눈 앞에 <br>say my name say my name <br>say my name say my name <br>이제 불러줄때야 <br>yes say my name <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="Say (Feat. Tase)" label="Say (Feat. Tase)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/미안/</id><title>헤이노 - 미안 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:11:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:11:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%88/" title="헤이노 - 미안 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 기분이 어떤지는 나 말고 <br>절대로 몰라 <br>그래 어떻게 알 수 있겠어 <br>내 발음이 어쩌네 <br>내 가사가 어쩌네 <br>떠들어만 대던 애 <br>들은 고맙지만 안 변해 <br>내가 벌써 엄청나게 <br>오랜 시간을 하다 보니까 <br>이미 굳어 버린 확고한 나의 스타일 <br>걍 내 맘대로 나를 믿고 가야지 <br>어느덧 너무 특별해진 라이밍 <br>빌어먹을 세상에 완벽한 건 없으니까 <br>그냥 계속 밀어 붙어 나의 길 <br>나를 믿는 일이 쉽지 않어 어쩔 땐 <br>별 볼 일 없어 보이거든 내가 여태 <br>해온 모든 것이 부질 없이 느껴지고 <br>전부 끝나버릴 것만 같은 <br>기분까지 들어 <br>그 누구도 내가 뭐가 해낼 거란 기댄 <br>하지 않어 <br>아직 나는 힘이 남아도는 대도 <br>잠시 멈춰서면 <br>다신 갈 수 없을 것만 같아 <br>내가 나를 믿어야지 <br>아님 누가 나를 믿겠어 <br>더 가보려 해 <br>조금 비틀 댈지도 몰라도 <br>뭘 두려워해 <br>더는 잃을 것도 없잖아 넌 <br>그저 가보려 해 <br>이 끝에 뭐가 있는지는 몰라도 <br>뭘 두려워해 <br>어차피 이대로는 만족 못하잖어 <br>무수히 많은 발전과 실패를 계속 <br>겪어왔고 이젠 곡을 망쳐도 돼 <br>전 부 다 내가 하기 때문에 <br>혹시 내 여정을 보고 있는 가요 <br>1집부터 8집까지 1년반이 됐어 <br>가끔 절더라도 다시 돌아갈 순 없어 <br>그래도 안 멈춰 난 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="미안" label="미안"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/백조의호수/</id><title>헤이노 - 백조의호수 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:11:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:11:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EB%B0%B1%EC%A1%B0%EC%9D%98%ED%98%B8%EC%88%98/" title="헤이노 - 백조의호수 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 노랜 마치 <br>백조의 호수 같지이 예 <br>외로움이 담긴 노랠 부르지이 예 <br>느낀다면 같이 <br>따라 불러야지이이 예 <br>그래 이건 마치 <br>백조의 호수 같지이 예 <br>난 원래가 좀 이상한 놈 <br>이런 노래들이 내 안에 들어있어 <br>그래서인가 아무도 안 듣겠지 <br>50대가 돼도 노랠 만들겠지 <br>어쩔 수 없나봐 <br>내가 이런걸 뭘 어쩔까요 <br>난 비극 속 짐승과 같아 <br>제발 저리가요 <br>세상에 동화는 없지 <br>나 같은 놈은 결국 <br>외롭게 살다가 <br>외롭게 사라지는 거군 <br>거부할 수가 없어 내 안에 느낌 <br>사람들은 이런 날 보고 비웃지 <br>어쩌겠어 내가 이런 남자인걸 <br>이해해줘 나 좀 다 장난인걸 <br>모든 걸 털어내고 있어 <br>예술가 같이 <br>솔직하게 나를 드러내는 거지 <br>이런 내가 거지 같은 거지 <br>그치만 거짓보다는 나은 거지 <br>모든 걸 털어내고 있어 <br>예술가 같이 <br>솔직하게 나를 드러내는 거지 <br>이런 내가 거지 같은 거지 <br>그치만 거짓보다는 나은 거지 <br>이 노랜 마치 <br>백조의 호수 같지이 예 <br>외로움이 담긴 노랠 부르지이 예 <br>느낀다면 같이 <br>따라 불러야지이이 예 <br>그래 이건 마치 <br>백조의 호수 같지이 예 <br>친구들은 떠났고 <br>나 혼자 꿈을 못 놔 <br>미운 오리 새낀 <br>결국 미운 오리 새끼지 <br>아 그래 바로 이게 인생이지 <br>참 더럽게도 안 풀려 미친 <br>내가 이런 노랠 하고 <br>있는 꼴을 보면 <br>이럴라고 계속 했니 <br>하고 슬프겠지 <br>슬퍼하지마 난 행복하니까 <br>아는 체 하지마 좀 창피하니까 <br>너희들은 잘 살고 있는지는 <br>사실 궁금하지 않아 <br>나 말고는 안 궁금해 <br>그치만 너흰 나를 <br>궁금해 했으면 해 <br>왜냠 난 <br>관심 먹고 사는 예술가니까 <br>모든 걸 털어내고 있어 <br>예술가 같이 <br>솔직하게 나를 드러내는 거지 <br>이런 내가 거지 같은 거지 <br>그치만 거짓보다는 나은 거지 <br>모든 걸 털어내고 있어 <br>예술가 같이 <br>솔직하게 나를 드러내는 거지 <br>이런 내가 거지 같은 거지 <br>그치만 거짓보다는 나은 거지 <br>이 노랜 마치 <br>백조의 호수 같지이 예 <br>외로움이 담긴 노랠 부르지이 예 <br>느낀다면 같이 <br>따라 불러야지이이 예 <br>그래 이건 마치 <br>백조의 호수 같지이 예 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="백조의호수" label="백조의호수"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/bitchs_hate_me_Feat_더블캐슬/</id><title>헤이노 - bitchs hate me (Feat. 더블캐슬) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:11:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:11:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/bitchs_hate_me_Feat_%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/" title="헤이노 - bitchs hate me (Feat. 더블캐슬) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[얼마를 마셔도 undrunkin' <br>심장이 멎어도 heart break <br>그딴 건 나한텐 늘상 있는 일 <br>너만 보면 죽을 것 같은 일상이 <br>죽을 것 같은 일상이 <br>얼마를 마셔도 undrunkin' <br>심장이 멎어도 heart break <br>그딴 건 나한텐 늘상 있는 일 <br>너만 보면 죽을 것 같은 일상이 <br>죽을 것 같은 일상이 <br>너의 다리만 봐도 <br>난 구속 당하고 <br>너의 가슴을 봐도 <br>난 구속 당하고 <br>너의 얼굴을 쳐다만 봐도 <br>구속 당하고 <br>난 내가 차라리 <br>장님이었으면 좋겠고 <br>이걸 다른 여자가 들으면 <br>날 싫어할 것 같고 <br>이걸 내 요즘 썸녀가 들으면 <br>기겁할 것 같고 <br>그래도 괜찮아 들어도 괜찮아 <br>넌 bad bitch가 아니니까 <br>나한테 빠져도 괜찮아 <br>니 얼굴에 난 트러블 <br>내가 care 해줄게 about me <br>내 어깨 내 귓볼 내 콧잔등 <br>너와 함께 해 without me <br>제발 날 버리지마 <br>넌 kindness 착한 거 다 알어 <br>내 카톡 읽어주길 <br>내 전화 받아주길 <br>bitchs hate me <br>넌 아니란 걸 알어 <br>bitchs hate me <br>넌 아니란 걸 알어 <br>bitchs hate me <br>넌 아니란 걸 알어 <br>bitchs hate me <br>넌 아니란 걸 알어 <br>얼마를 마셔도 undrunkin' <br>심장이 멎어도 heart break <br>그딴 건 나한텐 늘상 있는 일 <br>너만 보면 죽을 것 같은 일상이 <br>죽을 것 같은 일상이 <br>얼마를 마셔도 undrunkin' <br>심장이 멎어도 heart break <br>그딴 건 나한텐 늘상 있는 일 <br>너만 보면 죽을 것 같은 일상이 <br>죽을 것 같은 일상이 <br>bitchs hate me <br>bitchs hate me <br>bitchs hate me <br>bitchs hate me <br>bitchs hate me <br>bitchs hate me <br>bitchs hate me <br>bitchs hate me <br>다 날 싫어해 <br>내가 뭘 잘못했길래 <br>어 그니까 싫다는 거 아냐 <br>나도 싫어 <br>다 싫어 다 싫어 나도 <br>다 싫어 <br>대체 다들 왜 나를 싫어해 <br>니가 뭔데 이런 내 <br>맘을 갖고 놀아 왜 <br>나도 싫어 이젠 <br>그래 많이 울렸지 나는 억눌렸지 <br>사람들은 나랑 달러 <br>나도 그걸 알어 <br>나는 혼자인 게 맞어 <br>아우 외로웠던 봐암 <br>나도 적응 했어 <br>이젠 전부 저리가으 <br>여자들이 많아도 <br>나랑은 상관 없어 <br>앞으로 내 여자친구는 <br>항상 없어 워우 <br>얼마를 마셔도 undrunkin' <br>심장이 멎어도 heart break <br>그딴 건 나한텐 늘상 있는 일 <br>너만 보면 죽을 것 같은 일상이 <br>죽을 것 같은 일상이 <br>얼마를 마셔도 undrunkin' <br>심장이 멎어도 heart break <br>그딴 건 나한텐 늘상 있는 일 <br>너만 보면 죽을 것 같은 일상이 <br>죽을 것 같은 일상이 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="bitchs hate me (Feat. 더블캐슬)" label="bitchs hate me (Feat. 더블캐슬)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/심심풀이_Feat_Tase_더블캐슬/</id><title>헤이노 - 심심풀이 (Feat. Tase, 더블캐슬) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:11:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:11:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EC%8B%AC%EC%8B%AC%ED%92%80%EC%9D%B4_Feat_Tase_%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/" title="헤이노 - 심심풀이 (Feat. Tase, 더블캐슬) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 눈 뜨는 순간부터 <br>잠들 때까지 <br>머리 속엔 랩과 음악 생각뿐 <br>퇴근 하고 나면 <br>곡 만들다 보면 <br>출근 시간되어 <br>있는 일이 허다하군 <br>내 랩 스킬 <br>넌 벌써 파악하기 전에 바꿔 <br>문장이 좀 달라도 <br>말이 통한다는 거죠 <br>더 공부해 너 한국어 영어 <br>한마디도 안 쓰고도 <br>너보다 더 힙합 같은 걸 난 해내 <br>이젠 배어버린 <br>내 예술가의 냄새 <br>네모들은 구린 랩 <br>한번만 좀 들어달라고 생떼 <br>아주 고생해 부족함을 몰라요 <br>오 이걸 듣건 말건 내게 이건 그냥 <br>심심풀이 랩이야 <br>난 이젠 담배 피러 갈 테야 <br>오 오 오 <br>마이크 이어 받았지 헤이노에게 <br>딱히 할 말 없으니 <br>둘러볼게 주변을 <br>부르는 이슈 분노에 부르르 <br>bitch 많이 쓰는 욕 <br>변호하고 싶진 않지만 <br>몸 팔아먹는 swag 하면서 <br>피드백은 싫대 <br>ay 오늘의 인기 검색어 <br>7년 전 누구처럼 <br>이슈몰이로 뜬 새끼랑 <br>다를 것 없는 이곳 씬에 <br>beast 야생에 <br>니가 살기 위한 지침서 <br>be east 동쪽에서 힙합 <br>그럼 먹어 감자를 <br>남자를 여자를 <br>그런 벽 쌓으면서 랩하네 <br>그러면서 판단은 <br>장르의 벽을 제 발로 깨달래 <br>어쩌면 대단해 표현의 자유 <br>그 줏대의 기준에 <br>창과 방패가 될 수 있어 <br>니 면상만 두껍다면 <br>여전해 요절해 <br>노력의 끝은 당해 <br>여론에 한방에 <br>원래 정치판에서는 <br>뭣도 안 돼도 너무 당당해 <br>엊그제 술 어제도 술 오늘도 술 <br>이러다 위장이 뚫려 <br>술이 줄줄줄줄줄줄줄 <br>술만 늘어 술병만 들면 <br>귀를 갱 귀를 갱 <br>귀를 갱 귀를 갱 갱 갱스터 <br>랩만 안 늘어 <br>맨날 랩만 해도 <br>햄스터 휠 햄스터 휠 햄스터 휠 <br>twenty five twenty seven <br>제자리걸음만 2년째 <br>이제 난 앨범이 다섯 개 <br>그래 앨범이 무려 다섯 개 <br>내 인생 왜이래 <br>어쩌다 빚더미 천만 원 <br>난 갚을 수 있지 <br>그런데 갚지를 않지 <br>키움 증권 키워줘 빚더미 <br>천만 원 굴리지 <br>내년엔 억을 굴리지 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="심심풀이 (Feat. Tase, 더블캐슬)" label="심심풀이 (Feat. Tase, 더블캐슬)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/너와_나/</id><title>헤이노 - 너와 나 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:11:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:11:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EB%84%88%EC%99%80_%EB%82%98/" title="헤이노 - 너와 나 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리가 벌써 헤어진 지 <br>몇 달이 지났어 <br>여전히 가끔 생각하곤 하지 <br>그 날 밤을 <br>서로에 대한 미칠 듯한 <br>집착과 기대 <br>둘은 오직 서로 의지한 채로 기대 <br>이 세상을 등 돌리고 <br>싶던 거야 아마도 <br>다른 건 필요 없었다고 <br>너의 품이 작아도 <br>거기 안겨 있을 땐 <br>깊은 사랑을 느껴 <br>쓸데없는 생각들을 잊은 채 <br>그래 그땐 음악마저도 <br>널 대신 할 수 없을 것만 같았어 <br>절대 넌 날 떠나가지 <br>않을 것만 같았어 <br>내 요구들은 <br>너를 구속하고 말았었지 <br>그래 그땐 오직 너뿐 <br>난 너만 알았었지 <br>무척이나 힘들었을 거야 알아 <br>우리 이걸 실패라고 <br>생각하지 말자 <br>다만 우린 서로 너무 소중했을 뿐 <br>이 사랑이 생각보다 <br>약하다는 것을 몰랐을 뿐 <br>너와 난 <br>결국 알 수 없게 됐어 이젠 <br>이게 마지막이라면 <br>좀 더 아팠음 해 <br>특별 할 것 같던 <br>우리 역시 멀어져 가 <br>사랑이란 생각보다 약한가 봐 <br>너와 난 <br>결국 알 수 없게 됐어 이젠 <br>이게 마지막이라면 <br>좀 더 아팠음 해 <br>특별 할 것 같던 <br>우리 역시 멀어져 가 <br>사랑이란 생각보다 약한가 봐 <br>원했던 만큼 애절 했어 <br>많은 감정들을 매일 네게 전했어 <br>겨울이란 계절에서 <br>봄이 왔지만 그때가 더 따듯했어 <br>어쩌다가 너와 내가 이렇게 <br>멀어져 버린 건지 이제 의미 없게 <br>살아가는 듯한 <br>공허함에 눈 떠 매일 <br>내가 뭘 하던 추억들을 추적해 <br>자꾸 떠오르는 너의 모습에 <br>내가 혼자라는 것을 실감해 <br>사실 맘이 복잡해 널 생각하면 <br>여러 감정들이 나를 잠식해 <br>어쩌면 이 모든 게 끝나 너와 내가 <br>더는 특별하지 않을 때가 오겠지 <br>너무 슬퍼하지마 너와 난 <br>그래도 우린 평생 <br>잊지 못할 만큼 사랑했잖아 <br>너와 난 <br>결국 알 수 없게 됐어 이젠 <br>이게 마지막이라면 <br>좀 더 아팠음 해 <br>특별 할 것 같던 <br>우리 역시 멀어져 가 <br>사랑이란 생각보다 약한가 봐 <br>너와 난 <br>결국 알 수 없게 됐어 이젠 <br>이게 마지막이라면 <br>좀 더 아팠음 해 <br>특별 할 것 같던 <br>우리 역시 멀어져 가 <br>사랑이란 생각보다 약한가 봐 <br>결국에는 사랑이 <br>이긴다고 하던 너의 말 <br>나를 향해 짓던 너의 예쁜 미소가 <br>함께 보낸 시간들이 줬던 행복과 <br>너와 함께 했던 모든 게 다 떠올라 <br>언제라도 우린 절대 <br>잊지 못하겠지 <br>너무 강렬했던 <br>첫사랑을 남긴 채로 <br>나의 20대는 너로 시작해서 <br>너로 인해 끝이나 소중했던 기억 <br>후회 따윈 없어 <br>이 모든 게 나와 함께 살아가겠지 <br>나는 이야기를 계속 이어가겠지 <br>너무 오랜 기다림과 짧았던 만남 <br>서로 볼 수 없던 그 미칠듯한 밤들 <br>우리 이야기를 담아 만든 가사들 <br>오직 둘만 있는 듯한 험한 세상에 <br>이젠 홀로 남아 살아가겠지 <br>이 모든걸 품은 채로 <br>너와 난 <br>결국 알 수 없게 됐어 이젠 <br>이게 마지막이라면 <br>좀 더 아팠음 해 <br>특별 할 것 같던 <br>우리 역시 멀어져 가 <br>사랑이란 생각보다 약한가 봐 <br>너와 난 <br>결국 알 수 없게 됐어 이젠 <br>이게 마지막이라면 <br>좀 더 아팠음 해 <br>특별 할 것 같던 <br>우리 역시 멀어져 가 <br>사랑이란 생각보다 약한가 봐 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="너와 나" label="너와 나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/메에에/</id><title>헤이노 - 메에에 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:11:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:11:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EB%A9%94%EC%97%90%EC%97%90/" title="헤이노 - 메에에 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[고갤 도리 도리 Baby <br>나를 거부하는 제스쳐 <br>내 취향은 너무 독특해 <br>아무도 이해 하지 못하는 래퍼 <br>하지만 공연장에 지배자야 난 <br>한국 힙합의 미래라고 난 <br>볼륨을 가득 담은 목소리에 <br>겁이 없지 완전 벌꿀 오소리네 <br>그저께 부터 매일 <br>하루 한곡씩을 만들어 <br>끝이 없는 아이디어 <br>니들 내 말 잘들어 <br>난 너희 위에 군림해 <br>다들 나를 받들어 <br>내가 뜨면 너흰 기횐 없어 <br>그냥 잠들어 <br>왜 이렇게 요즘 이게 <br>재밌는지 모르겠어 <br>이러다가 진짜 정상까지 오르겠어 <br>밥 먹고 일갔다가 오면 녹음만해 <br>믿어봐 진짜 너희 위에 오를 만해 <br>그냥 일어나면 녹음해 <br>사실 잠도 안자 계속 녹음해 <br>난 1년 내내 곡을 내 <br>다른 래퍼들은 맨날 골골대 <br>그냥 일어나면 녹음해 <br>사실 잠도 안자 계속 녹음해 <br>난 1년 내내 곡을 내 <br>다른 래퍼들은 맨날 골골대 <br>이거 이곡에는 뭐 큰 의미는 없어 <br>그냥 뭔가 가볍게 한번 <br>곡을 만들어 보고 싶었어 <br>그래도 이거 너무 <br>대충한거 같긴 한대 <br>알게 뭐야 <br>내 앨범이야 맘대로 할거야 <br>그러면 이제 벌스 2도 한번 해봐야지 <br>어젠 인터뷰를 내 팬과 함께 <br>나의 4집 cd에다가 싸인했네 <br>취향과는 별개로 내 실력은 <br>인정 받어 흥분말고 침착하게 해야쥐 <br>랩은 내 인생에 큰 축복이야 <br>점점 변해가는 삶 안믿기지 <br>이건 나를 위한 트랙 <br>그러니 전부 내 맘대로해 <br>랩이 나를 갖고 아니 내가 랩을 갖고 <br>살아가는 삶은 점점 뚜렷하게 보이네 <br>앞날이 꼬인 애 이젠 아니네 <br>꿈에다가 골인해 아 오직 내 <br>꿈만 믿어 왔어 재능 없던 내가 <br>하루 두세시간 자며 이제야 <br>빛을 발해 미친 말해 꿈이라니 <br>이젠 이게 바로 나의 현실이야 <br>그냥 일어나면 녹음해 <br>사실 잠도 안자 계속 녹음해 <br>난 1년 내내 곡을 내 <br>다른 래퍼들은 맨날 골골대 <br>그냥 일어나면 녹음해 <br>사실 잠도 안자 계속 녹음해 <br>난 1년 내내 곡을 내 <br>다른 래퍼들은 맨날 골골대 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="메에에" label="메에에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/거짓말해줘/</id><title>헤이노 - 거짓말해줘 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:11:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:11:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EA%B1%B0%EC%A7%93%EB%A7%90%ED%95%B4%EC%A4%98/" title="헤이노 - 거짓말해줘 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[딱 하루만 난 너를 원해 <br>어차피 나도 돌아가야해 <br>다 거짓말해줘 <br>그냥 거짓말해줘 <br>거짓말 해줘 <br>그냥 거짓말 해줘 <br>다 미친 건데 기대 하지마 <br>그냥 오늘 밤만 이렇게 <br>널 안고 싶어 모르는 채로만 <br>다 믿고 싶어 딱 오늘만 <br>솔직히 말해 다 알게 뭔데 <br>그냥 오늘 밤만 이렇게 <br>널 안고 싶어 모르는 채로만 <br>다 믿고 싶어 딱 오늘만 <br>이제 나도 믿지 않을거야 <br>그아무도 없지 믿을수가 <br>헤어지고 또 다시 만나도 <br>아무리 배워도 실패뿐 <br>지쳤어 나도 이젠 못하겠어 <br>그놈에 사랑 따위 더는 못하겠어 <br>뭐가 잘못인지 궁금하지 않아 <br>하기 싫어졌어 누굴 바보로 아나 <br>내가 이런 노랠 왜 하는 건지 <br>맨날 피곤해 너도 헤어지던지 <br>먹구름은 결국엔 게어지겠지 <br>대체 여태 왜 얽메여지냈지 <br>내 말 듣긴 해 너는 전혀 모르지 <br>우린 자꾸 왜 서로 미워하는지 <br>그럴 거면 왜 대체 함께 하는지 <br>걍 헤어져 난 떠날거야 멀리 <br>사랑은 결국엔 <br>나를 배신하고 말지이 <br>그러면 나에겐 <br>상처들만 가득 남지 <br>지독한 외롬에 <br>덩그러니 혼자 남지 <br>이제는 그만할래 <br>처음 부터 혼자인게 훨씬 낫지 <br>다 미친 건데 기대 하지마 <br>그냥 오늘 밤만 이렇게 <br>널 안고 싶어 모르는 채로만 <br>다 믿고 싶어 딱 오늘만 <br>솔직히 말해 다 알게 뭔데 <br>그냥 오늘 밤만 이렇게 <br>널 안고 싶어 모르는 채로만 <br>다 믿고 싶어 딱 오늘만 <br>거짓말 해줘 그냥 거짓말 해줘 <br>거짓말 해줘 그냥 거짓말 해줘 <br>사랑 같은건 난 믿고 싶지 않아 <br>거짓말 해줘 그냥 거짓말 해줘 <br>거짓말 해줘 그냥 거짓말 해줘 <br>거짓말 해줘 그냥 거짓말 해줘 <br>사랑 같은건 난 믿고 싶지 않아 <br>거짓말 해줘 그냥 거짓말 해줘 <br>매일 그냥 거짓말해 거짓말이 <br>거짓말이 아닐때까지 <br>계속 거짓말해줘 <br>매일 그냥 거짓말해 거짓말이 <br>거짓말이 아닐때까지 <br>계속 거짓말해줘 <br>매일 그냥 거짓말해 거짓말이 <br>거짓말이 아닐때까지 <br>계속 거짓말해줘 <br>매일 그냥 거짓말해 거짓말이 <br>거짓말이 아닐때까지 <br>계속 거짓말해줘 <br>다 미친 건데 기대 하지마 <br>그냥 오늘 밤만 이렇게 <br>널 안고 싶어 모르는 채로만 <br>다 믿고 싶어 딱 오늘만 <br>솔직히 말해 다 알게 뭔데 <br>그냥 오늘 밤만 이렇게 <br>널 안고 싶어 모르는 채로만 <br>다 믿고 싶어 딱 오늘만 <br>사랑은 결국엔 <br>나를 배신하고 말지이 <br>그러면 나에겐 <br>상처들만 가득 남지 <br>지독한 외롬에 <br>덩그러니 혼자 남지 <br>이제는 그만할래 <br>처음부터 혼자인게 훨씬 낫지 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="거짓말해줘" label="거짓말해줘"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/rap_star/</id><title>헤이노 - rap star - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:12:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:12:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/rap_star/" title="헤이노 - rap star - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[스웩 우린 넘어 가고 있네 <br>겁도 없이 메이저의 문을 두들겨 <br>Ghost type 노멀한 걸론 날 못 때려 <br>난 팀의 아인슈타인 거만한 천재형 <br>그랬어 나는 하날 봐도 열을 배워 <br>지치지를 않어 더운 여름에도 <br>일 끝나면 녹음 <br>일 끝나면 비트메이킹 <br>나 덕분에 우린 팀은 <br>찍어 높은 레이팅 <br>더 브레킹 볼 내 변화구 <br>분위기는 나로 인해서 뜨겁게 변하고 <br>작업중엔 안받아 여자친구 전화도 <br>이건 당연한거 우릴 본 받아둬 <br>헤이노쉽은 바다로 <br>내 머리는 파마로 <br>베베 꼬여 내가 있는 곳은 딴 나라로 <br>변한 듯해 아무도 없는 <br>분위기를 풍겨 <br>이건 랩에 미친 어느 노력파의 품격 <br>우리 역시 마찬가지 꿈 꿔 랩 스타 <br>니가 만들어줘 나를 A 랩 스타 <br>A 랩 스타 A 랩 스타 <br>say 랩 스타 say 랩 스타 <br>우리 역시 마찬가지 꿈 꿔 랩 스타 <br>니가 만들어줘 나를 A 랩 스타 <br>A 랩 스타 A 랩 스타 <br>say 랩 스타 say 랩 스타 <br>어제 쓰다만 가살 다시 적어 <br>이걸 통해서 내 세상 문을 열어 <br>잠이 덜 깨서 아직 손이 떨려 <br>부담과 걱정이 또 내게 덤벼 <br>음악을 만드는건 결국 자신과의 싸움 <br>난 지고 싶지 않어 항상 마지막 <br>기회라고 생각하고 모든걸 내쳐놓고 <br>몰입 올인해 그니까 보니 <br>내 삶은 텅볐어 <br>오직 하나 내가 고집 부릴 꿈인데 <br>댓가가 좀 크지 이게 나의 전부지 <br>다 버렸어 랩 말곤 다 놔버렸어 <br>가버렸어 너 마저 날 떠나버렸어 <br>이젠 뒤가 없어 나는 원해 랩 스탈 <br>내 심장을 뛰게 하는 단어 랩 스타 <br>내가 되야할건 정해졌어 랩 스타 <br>나의 매순간을 바쳐 <br>되고 말어 랩 스타 <br>우리 역시 마찬가지 꿈 꿔 랩 스타 <br>니가 만들어줘 나를 A 랩 스타 <br>A 랩 스타 A 랩 스타 <br>say 랩 스타 say 랩 스타 <br>우리 역시 마찬가지 꿈 꿔 랩 스타 <br>니가 만들어줘 나를 A 랩 스타 <br>A 랩 스타 A 랩 스타 <br>say 랩 스타 say 랩 스타 <br>나도 한번쯤은 되고 싶어 <br>많은 관객들 <br>을 보고 싶어 가보고싶어 <br>다른 래퍼들과 <br>작업 해보고 싶어 나도 <br>돈 걱정 없이 경쟁 해보고 싶어 <br>내 실력을 알고 싶어 나도 <br>동경 하지 저 큰 무대 위에 래퍼들 <br>돈 자랑하는 더 큐 같은 그런 래퍼들 <br>예쁜 여자들을 독식하는 래퍼들 <br>미치도록 멋진 꿈을 이룬 래퍼들 <br>내 주변 래퍼들은 위기감이 없어 <br>재미 없어 더 큰 물로 <br>가보고 싶어 나도 <br>여긴 꿈이 없어 다들 지겨워졌어 <br>낮은 수준 땜에 <br>관객들이 없어 하나도 <br>이제 내가 향할 곳은 확실해 졌어 <br>내 모든걸 걸어볼 때가 됐어 나도 <br>랩 말고는 다 필요 없어 <br>반드시 하고 말아 되는거야 나도 <br>랩 스타 <br>우리 역시 마찬가지 꿈 꿔 랩 스타 <br>니가 만들어줘 나를 A 랩 스타 <br>A 랩 스타 A 랩 스타 <br>say 랩 스타 say 랩 스타 <br>우리 역시 마찬가지 꿈 꿔 랩 스타 <br>니가 만들어줘 나를 A 랩 스타 <br>A 랩 스타 A 랩 스타 <br>say 랩 스타 say 랩 스타 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="rap star" label="rap star"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/i_can_2015/</id><title>헤이노 - i can (2015) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:12:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:12:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/i_can_2015/" title="헤이노 - i can (2015) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 눈을 감은 채로 말해 i can <br>잘 알거든 현실속의 난 약해 <br>슈퍼스타 참 웃기는 나의 꿈 <br>다시 물어봐 정말 할수있냐고 <br>그럴땐 주변 모든걸 잊어버려 <br>어려운 현재 내 모습은 <br>다 거짓말이야 <br>내가 원한건 없어 다 강제야 <br>이 모습은 세상에 대한 방패야 <br>처음 열정이란 이름의 꿈은 <br>이젠 사치 <br>다들 말해 포기하고 다른길을 찿길 <br>내가 왜 못할거라고만 생각해 <br>나를 비웃는 사람들이 전부 깨닫게 <br>정말 누구보다 잘 하고 싶었어 <br>그렇게 11년이 지나 난 스물다섯 <br>이젠 내 자신이 의심스럽기도해 <br>그래서 난 눈을 감은 채로 말해 <br>i can <br>눈을 감은 채로 말해 i can <br>거짓말이라도 좋아 my dream <br>꿈속에선 이미 터트린 Champagne <br>한번만 내 이름을 불러줘 <br>Jack Heino <br>눈을 감은 채로 말해 i can <br>거짓말이라도 좋아 my dream <br>꿈속에선 이미 터트린 Champagne <br>한번만 내 이름을 불러줘 <br>Jack Heino <br>내가 처음 원했던 걸 아직 까지도 <br>간직하고 있어 이런 나의 방식도 <br>한 두명 씩 응원하는 사람들이 생겨 <br>음악은 내가 찿아 낸 삶의 해법 <br>내가 믿는 것은 내가 들인 노력이고 <br>실패한다고해도 놓지 않아 이걸 <br>14년이 지난 아직 까지 나는 믿어 <br>오늘도 가사들로 나의 성을 지어 <br>어쩌면 구질구질하게 보일지도 <br>언젠가 내 앞에도 벽이 놓일지도 <br>모르지만 계속 오르지 난 오로지 난 <br>이걸 위해 삶을 살아가는 중이야 <br>늦었다고 다들 안된다고 말해도 <br>i can 변할 일은 없을 것 같네 <br>기나긴 자신과의 싸움 <br>그래서 난 눈을 감은 채로 말해 <br>i can <br>눈을 감은 채로 말해 i can <br>거짓말이라도 좋아 my dream <br>꿈속에선 이미 터트린 Champagne <br>한번만 내 이름을 불러줘 <br>Jack Heino <br>눈을 감은 채로 말해 i can <br>거짓말이라도 좋아 my dream <br>꿈속에선 이미 터트린 Champagne <br>한번만 내 이름을 불러줘 <br>Jack Heino <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="i can (2015)" label="i can (2015)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김일리/Good_Thing/</id><title>김일리 - Good Thing - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:13:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:13:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9D%BC%EB%A6%AC/Good_Thing/" title="김일리 - Good Thing - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[걱정마 <br>everythings will be okay <br>근데 아직 난 기억해 <br>나 그만 악몽에 빠져 <br>gloomy all day 보냈지 <br>자그마치 육개월이 넘게 <br>하지만 필요했어 <br>이겨내기 위한 동기부여를 해서 <br>넘어진 나를 또 일으켜 <br>줄 무언가는 어디있나 <br>한때는 기를 써 <br>믿을 수 없는 시간 속에서 <br>일어났지 이렇게 <br>내가 좋아하는 것 <br>내 기분을 더 더 좋게 하는 것 <br>뭐가 있을까 <br>찾으려 고민하면서 발견한 건 <br>내가 날 좋아하는 법 <br>멋있는 옷과 단정한 머리 <br>좋은 음악 가사가 주는 <br>생각할 거리 <br>그것들을 정리하며 <br>주욱 걷는 거지 <br>덕분에 걸음 걸어 <br>전보다도 더 멋지게 <br>Let's do it <br>Good Thing Good Thing <br>내가 사랑하는 것들은 <br>나를 사로잡아서 <br>나로 살아가고 싶게 만들어 <br>그래 그런 것들 <br>lalala <br>Good Thing Good Thing <br>내가 사랑하는 것들은 <br>나를 사로잡아서 <br>나로 살아가고 싶게 만들어 <br>그래 그런 것들 <br>lalala <br>당당히 걸음 걸어가다가도 <br>가끔 길가의 자갈돌 <br>걸려 넘어지기도 해 <br>어쨌든 우리는 <br>넘어지는 걸 막을 순 없겠지 <br>툭툭 털고 일어나기로 해 <br>but 난 아직 미로 헤매이지 <br>이 길 어디에 답 있는지 몰라 <br>짱나고 좀 지치기도 해 <br>그럴 땐 딱 눈 감고서 쉬기로 해 <br>잃어버린 하룬 좀 아쉽기도 해 <br>허나 난 아직 남아있는 게 많지 <br>좋은 음악 하고픈 맘이 많지 <br>만땅 땅 하니까 적어 내려가 <br>결국엔 내 영감이 된 잃었던 하루가 <br>내게로 돌아온 듯 한 <br>느낌 느껴 두 배로 nice <br>예전엔 전혀 생각치 못했던 <br>사고방식이야 <br>엄청 새로워 <br>조금의 텀 하나로 바뀌는 flow 같아 <br>신선하고 좋은 vibe <br>yeah i gotcha <br>and i'm feel it <br>Good Thing Good Thing <br>내가 사랑하는 것들은 <br>나를 사로잡아서 <br>나로 살아가고 싶게 만들어 <br>그래 그런 것들 <br>lalala <br>Good Thing Good Thing <br>내가 사랑하는 것들은 <br>나를 사로잡아서 <br>나로 살아가고 싶게 만들어 <br>그래 그런 것들 <br>lalala <br>그래 그런 것들 <br>물 흐르듯 들은 것들처럼 <br>아니 더 멋지게 만들어 <br>나를 울리고 웃기도 했던 <br>기억들을 <br>다시 떠올리고 적은 후 <br>부른 것을 <br>누군가의 귀에 댈 수 있기를 <br>또 그게 나의 기회 될 수 있기를 <br>바라는 맘과 같은 무게의 믿음 <br>그 믿음이 늘 나를 이끌었지 늘 <br>Good Thing Good Thing <br>내가 사랑하는 것들은 <br>나를 사로잡아서 <br>나로 살아가고 싶게 만들어 <br>그래 그런 것들 <br>lalala <br>Good Thing Good Thing <br>내가 사랑하는 것들은 <br>나를 사로잡아서 <br>나로 살아가고 싶게 만들어 <br>그래 그런 것들 <br>lalala <br>]]></content><category term="김일리" label="김일리"/><category term="Good Thing" label="Good Thing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GeeCee_지씨/YEYE/</id><title>GeeCee (지씨) - YEYE - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:15:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:15:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GeeCee_%EC%A7%80%EC%94%A8/YEYE/" title="GeeCee (지씨) - YEYE - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[일단 시작부터 제일 큰 그림 <br>그려 see further <br>이렇게 상상만 하다가는 <br>머리 다 빠져 <br>버려 아니 보여 줄래 <br>나의 Class is loyal <br>부릉부릉 시동으로 <br>느껴지는 예열 <br>씩씩하게 한땐 내가 <br>낸데 자신감이 <br>시시하면 이건 운동으로 안돼 <br>축축 처진 어깨 칙칙해진 <br>분위기에 네가 있어 <br>다시 힘이 나는 나네 fly high <br>진정해 나의 마음아 <br>긴장감이 필요할 때엔 <br>오랜만에 느껴보는 이런 떨림 <br>할까 말까 고민이면 <br>몰라 몰라 그냥 해 <br>DAYDAY 지금이 맘 편할 때 <br>지금이 내일 보다 더 젊을 때네 <br>YE YE Do it again &amp; again <br>MAYDAY 언젠가 힘이 들 때 <br>언제나 곁에 있어 힘이 돼줄게 <br>YE YE Do it &amp; Get it Get it <br>라운지 같은 Vibe의 남양주 <br>파란 하늘 파라다이스 <br>남몰래 떠나기를 <br>좋아해 나 원래 <br>변덕이 죽 끓기도 <br>하지 뭐 막 이래 <br>모든 일이 지치고 쉽게 질리고 <br>내 잔고 지긋지긋해도 <br>이건 real 실화고 <br>딱 잘라 말해 모든 음악이 <br>갑자기 듣기 싫어질 때 <br>뭔가를 바로 하기 yes <br>진정해 나의 마음아 <br>긴장감이 필요할 때엔 <br>오랜만에 느껴보는 이런 떨림 <br>할까 말까 고민이면 <br>몰라 몰라 그냥 해 <br>DAYDAY 지금이 맘 편할 때 <br>지금이 내일 보다 더 젊을 때네 <br>YE YE Do it again &amp; again <br>MAYDAY 언젠가 힘이 들 때 <br>언제나 곁에 있어 힘이 돼줄게 <br>YE YE Do it &amp; Get it Get it <br>달콤했던 Dreams It's my creams <br>빨주노초파남보 내 멋대로 그림 <br>It has never been my object to <br>record my my dreams <br>Why stop dreaming <br>when you wake up <br>YE YE 물들어와 배 띄워라 <br>YE YE 바람 불어 연 날려라 <br>Goodday Mate <br>그 담날 걱정 따윈 하지 마 <br>넌 그냥 아름다워 <br>DAYDAY 지금이 맘 편할 때 <br>지금이 내일 보다 더 젊을 때네 <br>YE YE Do it again &amp; again <br>MAYDAY 언젠가 힘이 들 때 <br>언제나 곁에 있어 힘이 돼줄게 <br>YE YE Do it &amp; Get it Get it <br>]]></content><category term="GeeCee (지씨)" label="GeeCee (지씨)"/><category term="YEYE" label="YEYE"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luveda/Lost_Feat_Moody_G/</id><title>Luveda - Lost (Feat. Moody G) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:20:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:20:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luveda/Lost_Feat_Moody_G/" title="Luveda - Lost (Feat. Moody G) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lost in the crowded train station <br>watching the giant screen of words <br>No fine lips and tongue <br>telling me where to go <br>unless got asked it <br>Lost in the empty space station <br>Not even got interested in <br>Searching the manual <br>everyone reads but I can't <br>'cause so drowsed with it <br>Lost in the middle of way back home <br>walking the streets until darkness <br>No fine ladies and gentlemen <br>who let me <br>back on my way easily <br>It's phenomenal <br>Phenomenal <br>Phenomenal <br>Lost in the crowded train station <br>watching the giant screen of words <br>No fine lips and tongue <br>telling me where to go <br>unless got asked it <br>Lost in the empty space station <br>Not even got interested in <br>Searching the manual <br>everyone reads but I can't <br>'cause so drowsed with it <br>A lot of <br>lots of things I don't even care <br>I don't even care <br>I don't even care <br>I don't even care <br>I don't even care <br>It's phenomenal <br>I don't even care <br>Phenomenal <br>It's phenomenal <br>I don't even care <br>I don't even care <br>Phenomenal <br>I don't even care <br>It's phenomenal <br>]]></content><category term="Luveda" label="Luveda"/><category term="Lost (Feat. Moody G)" label="Lost (Feat. Moody G)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Night_So_Long/</id><title>HAIM - Night So Long - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Night_So_Long/" title="HAIM - Night So Long - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I say goodbye to love again <br>In loneliness my only friend <br>In loneliness my only fear <br>The night's here <br>And I say goodbye to love once more <br>No shadow darkening my door <br>Until your memory is gone <br>The night so long <br>Then I say goodbye to love again <br>In loneliness my only friend <br>In loneliness my only fear <br>The night's here <br>And I say goodbye to love once more <br>No shadow darkening my door <br>Until your memory is gone <br>The night so long <br>I say goodbye to love again <br>so long <br>I say goodbye to love again <br>so long <br>I say goodbye to love again <br>so long <br>I say goodbye to love again <br>so long <br>]]></content><category term="HAIM" label="HAIM"/><category term="Night So Long" label="Night So Long"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Right_Now/</id><title>HAIM - Right Now - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Right_Now/" title="HAIM - Right Now - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Gave you my love, you gave me nothing <br>Said what I gave wasn't enough <br>You had me feeling I was foolish <br>Forever thinking this could be the one <br><br>I wasn't even in the running <br>Already had your mind made up <br>You left me searching for a reason <br>Why'd you leave, left me in the dust <br><br>And now you're saying that you need me babe <br>Right now, right now <br>And now you're saying that you need me babe <br>Right now, right now <br>And now you're saying that you love me, love me babe <br>Right now, right now <br>And now you're saying that you need <br>Saying that you need <br>Saying that you need me <br>Right now <br><br>Gave you my love, thought I could trust you <br>You let me down at every turn <br>You had me hanging on a dream you never believed <br>You gave me your word <br><br>Finally on the other side now <br>And I could see for miles <br>And I've forgotten every line <br><br>And now you're saying that you need me babe <br>Right now, right now <br>And now you're saying that you need me babe <br>Right now, right now <br>And now you're saying that you love me, love me babe <br>Right now, right now <br>And now you're saying that you need <br>Saying that you need <br>Saying that you need me <br>Right now <br><br>Did you think this would be easy <br>Thought this would be easy <br>Not now, not now <br>I know you heard me through an open window <br>Whispers carried to your ear <br>Whispers sounded so clear <br><br>Somehow it's so clear now <br>Somehow it's so clear now <br>What's that sound <br>That's your fading away <br><br>And now you're saying that you need me babe <br>Right now, right now <br>And now you're saying that you need me babe <br>Right now, right now <br>And now you're saying that you love me, love me babe <br>Right now, right now <br>And now you're saying that you need <br>Saying that you need <br>Saying that you need me <br>Right now <br><br>And now you're saying that you need me babe <br>Right now, right now <br>And now you're saying that you need me babe <br>Right now, right now <br>And now you're saying that you love me, love me babe <br>Right now, right now <br>And now you're saying that you need <br>Saying that you need <br>Saying that you need me <br>Right now <br>Right now, right now]]></content><category term="HAIM" label="HAIM"/><category term="Right Now" label="Right Now"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Walking_Away/</id><title>HAIM - Walking Away - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Walking_Away/" title="HAIM - Walking Away - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You don't wanna talk, don't wanna work it out <br>If you were gonna face it, you would've by now <br>When were you around, when were you a <br>I waited hours and hours, hearing loud sirens <br>Suffered through lies differently <br>You see, now I'm not coming around <br>Coming around, coming around <br><br>I'm walking away, walking away, walking away <br>Walking away, walking away <br>Walking away, walking away, walking away <br>Walking away, walking away <br><br>You don't wanna give and you don't wanna know how <br>If you were gonna change things, you wouldn't been there <br>What were you around, when were you are <br>Trying not think about it, baby <br>Running up and down the stairs <br>'Til there's nothing left between us but what we won't say <br><br>Walking away, walking away, walking away <br>Walking away, walking away <br>Walking away, walking away, walking away <br>Walking away, walking away <br><br>I don't know what's said so many times before <br>But now it's keeping me away <br>I know you did it so many times before <br>But I never thought I'd be the one you betrayed <br>Away, I'm not gonna wait <br>Nothing you could say that'll make me rethink <br>Every chance that we had and messed up <br>All the times it got away from us <br>Away, I'm not gonna wait <br>Nothing you could say that'll make me rethink <br>Every chance that we had and messed up <br>All the times it got away from us <br><br>Say something, say something, say something <br>While I can still heal, while I can still heal <br>Say something, say something, say something <br>While I can still heal, while I can still heal <br>Say something, say something, say something <br>While I can still heal, while I can still heal <br><br>Away, I'm not gonna wait <br>Nothing you could say that'll make me rethink <br>Every chance that we had and messed up <br>All the times it got away from us <br>x6]]></content><category term="HAIM" label="HAIM"/><category term="Walking Away" label="Walking Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Found_It_In_Silence/</id><title>HAIM - Found It In Silence - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Found_It_In_Silence/" title="HAIM - Found It In Silence - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wanted an honest man <br>I thought I found one of them <br>Stood by him every time I was scared <br>I was blind, wasn't I <br>Thought he was an honest man <br>Who could put me back together again <br>Tried so hard to read his mind, through his eyes <br>I was scared, I was blind <br><br>But I found it in silence, I finally see <br>There's no turning back, I know what's good for me <br>I found it in silence, I finally see <br>There's no turning back, I know what's good for me <br><br>Three fingers on the edge <br>You always talk me down in the end <br>Made me think you were right, all this time <br>Not this time, not this time <br>Both of us, holding back <br>But you were the most guilty of that <br>Someone else on your mouth, all this time <br>I was right, wasn't I <br><br>You told me, don't walk away <br>You told me not to walk away <br>You told me not to walk, walk, walk <br><br>But I found it in silence, I finally see I finally see <br>There's no turning back, I know what's good for me <br>I found it in silence, I finally see I finally see <br>There's no turning back, I know what's good for me <br>Found it in silence found it in silence, finally see finally see <br>There's no turning back, I know what's good for me <br>Found it in silence found it in silence, finally see finally see <br>There's no turning back, I know what's good for me <br><br>It was always for the better <br>And I guess I should have known <br>The truth is, it's your issue, I know I need to let it go <br>And though I have found happiness, in my life that's truly mine <br>You'd think I could just laugh it off, but it gets me every time <br><br>But I found it in silence <br>Found it in, found it in silence <br>Found it in, found it in silence <br>Found it in, found it in silence <br>Found it in, found it in silence <br>Finally see <br>Found it in silence, finally <br>Found it in silence, finally see <br>Found it in silence, finally <br><br>I found it in silence, I finally see <br>There's no turning back, I know what's good for me <br>]]></content><category term="HAIM" label="HAIM"/><category term="Found It In Silence" label="Found It In Silence"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Kept_Me_Crying/</id><title>HAIM - Kept Me Crying - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Kept_Me_Crying/" title="HAIM - Kept Me Crying - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you sleep, are you dreaming of me <br>Hurts to say, but I'm always awake <br><br>If you want me, I'm waiting for you <br>If you call me, I'll pick up <br>No, I shouldn't, but I can't give up of you <br><br>Kept me crying for so long, my tears have dried <br>When I hear your voice, those tears they come back to mind <br>So don't call me just to tell me <br>You don't love me anymore <br>Still it wrecks me 'cause <br><br>I was your lover <br>I was your friend <br>Now I'm only just someone you call <br>When it's late enough to forget <br>I was your lover <br>I was your friend <br>Now I'm only just someone you call <br>When it's late enough to forget <br><br>When you leave, I can't stop my heart hurting <br>Hurts to say I keep thinking you're stay <br><br>If you want me, I'll be waiting for you <br>If you call me, I'll pick up <br>No, I shouldn't, but I can't give up of you <br><br>Kept me crying for so long, my tears have dried <br>When I hear your voice, those tears they come back to mind <br>So don't call me up just to tell me <br>You don't love me anymore <br>Still it wrecks me 'cause <br><br>I was your lover <br>I was your friend <br>Now I'm only just someone you call <br>When it's late enough to forget <br>I was your lover <br>I was your friend <br>Now I'm only just someone you call <br>When it's late enough to forget <br>I've got the cover, I can't pretend <br>That I'm anything more to you now <br>Someone just hard to forget <br>And after all these tears <br>After all my years of trying <br>I don't wanna hear <br>That nothing meant anything <br><br>I was your lover <br>I was your friend <br>]]></content><category term="HAIM" label="HAIM"/><category term="Kept Me Crying" label="Kept Me Crying"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/You_Never_Knew/</id><title>HAIM - You Never Knew - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/You_Never_Knew/" title="HAIM - You Never Knew - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It was a weight on my shoulders <br>A strain on my back <br>But I loved to have you <br>right there by my side <br>You couldn't take it <br>You couldn't take it <br>It used to be <br>when we were alone <br>We shared such beautiful moments <br>But lately it's been such a mess <br>You couldn't take it <br>You couldn't take it <br>Go on and say it <br>Was my love too much <br>for you to take <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>Don't keep me waiting <br>Say the words that you're too <br>scared to say <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>I need to hear you say it <br>Was my love too much <br>for you to take <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>Don't keep me waiting <br>Say the words that you're too <br>scared to say <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>I came home to see you <br>you weren't around <br>Excuses were one <br>right after the other <br>You couldn't take it <br>You couldn't take it <br>You woke up from another dream <br>another fight you didn't mean <br>Still time after time <br>I came running to get you <br>You couldn't take it <br>You couldn't take it <br>Go on and say it <br>Was my love too much <br>for you to take <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>Don't keep me waiting <br>Say the words that you're too <br>scared to say <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>I need to hear you say it <br>Was my love too much <br>for you to take <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>Don't keep me waiting <br>Say the words that you're too <br>scared to say <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>You couldn't take it <br>Another heart another day <br>So much time just thrown away <br>You couldn't take it <br>You know I love to be in love <br>You couldn't take it <br>So tired of trying to show you <br>I worked so hard <br>Go on and say it <br>Was my love too much <br>for you to take <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>Oh don't keep me waiting <br>Say the words that you're too <br>scared to say <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>I need to hear you say it <br>Was my love too much <br>for you to take <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>Don't keep me waiting <br>Say the words that you're too <br>scared to say <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>I guess you never knew <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>I guess you never knew <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>I guess you never knew <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>I guess you never knew <br>I guess you never knew <br>what was good for you <br>]]></content><category term="HAIM" label="HAIM"/><category term="You Never Knew" label="You Never Knew"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Something_To_Tell_You/</id><title>HAIM - Something To Tell You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Something_To_Tell_You/" title="HAIM - Something To Tell You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[On the way down, a fall from grace <br>I was in for a heavy one when I could feel you pull away <br>On the way down, it almost was too much to take <br>Even though I tried, it was never enough for running in the same damn place <br><br>But I never stopped or gave up <br>I couldn't ever let you go <br>'Cause in the end, I was innocent, I was innocent <br>I let you know that it's no good <br>But you could never say it first <br>I know you're hurt <br>Tell me how you feel, tell me how you feel <br><br>'Cause I got something to tell you, but I don't know why <br>It's so hard to let you know that we're not seeing eye to eye <br>Because I know if I tell you that everything's alright <br>Oh, we could stay in this moment, I'd never say goodbye <br>Oh, I'll never say goodbye <br><br>Heavy was the sound I could not lift <br>I could run for a million miles and never get away from it <br>But knowing that now, I couldn't be content <br>Even when it was looking up for us, it was difficult to pretend <br><br>But I never stopped or gave up <br>I couldn't ever let you go <br>'Cause in the end, I was innocent, I was innocent <br>I let you know that it's no good <br>But you could never say it first <br>I know you're hurt <br>Tell me how you feel, tell me how you feel <br><br>'Cause I got something to tell you, but I don't know why <br>It's so hard to let you know that we're not seeing eye to eye <br>Because I know if I tell you that everything's alright <br>Oh, we could stay in this moment, I'd never say goodbye <br>Oh, I'll never say goodbye <br><br>I never stopped or gave up <br>I couldn't ever let you go <br>'Cause in the end, I was innocent <br>I never stopped or gave up <br>I couldn't ever let you go <br>'Cause in the end, baby, I was innocent <br>I never stopped or gave up <br>I couldn't ever let you go <br>'Cause in the end, I was innocent, I was innocent <br>I let you know that it's no good <br>But you could never say it first <br>I know you're hurt <br>Tell me how you feel, tell me how you feel <br><br>'Cause I got something to tell you, but I don't know why <br>It's so hard to let you know that we're not seeing eye to eye <br>Because I know if I tell you that everything's alright <br>Oh, we could stay in this moment, I'd never say goodbye <br>Oh, I'll never say goodbye <br>But I don't know why <br>It's so hard to let you know that we're not seeing eye to eye <br>Because I know if I tell you that everything's alright <br>Oh, we could stay in this moment, I'd never say goodbye <br>Oh, I'll never say goodbye <br><br>Never say goodbye <br>Oh, I'll never say goodbye <br>Never say goodbye <br>Oh, I'll never say goodbye <br>Never say goodbye, never say goodbye <br>Never say goodbye <br>Oh, I'll never say goodbye <br>Never say goodbye]]></content><category term="HAIM" label="HAIM"/><category term="Something To Tell You" label="Something To Tell You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Ready_For_You/</id><title>HAIM - Ready For You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Ready_For_You/" title="HAIM - Ready For You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe I was trying to forget <br>All my crazy reactions over my ex <br>Maybe you played way too hard to get <br>So I kept it moving to another one night stand <br><br>I promise I will treat you right, treat you right, babe <br>'Cause that's all I wanna do, oh <br>I promise I will treat you right, treat you right, babe <br>So that's what I'm gonna do <br><br>I promise I'll treat you right <br>Been waiting my whole damn life <br>Baby, it's about time <br>I wasn't ready for you <br>Funny how this whole game played <br>Three years since I learned your name <br>The wrong time, the wrong place <br>I wasn't ready for you <br><br>Maybe I couldn't tell you why <br>I didn't hide the first night I met you <br>We were locking eyes <br>They said you'd be like all the other guys <br>Two faced, but too numb to know it <br>Telling your pretty lies <br><br>But I promise I will treat you right, treat you right, babe <br>'Cause that's all I wanna do, oh <br>I promise I will treat you right, treat you right, babe <br>So that's what I'm gonna do <br><br>I promise I'll treat you right <br>Been waiting my whole damn life <br>Baby, it's about time <br>I wasn't ready for you <br>Funny how this whole game played <br>Three years since I learned your name <br>The wrong time, the wrong place <br>I wasn't ready for you <br><br>Keep thinking about you <br>Thinking you almost slipped through <br>There won't be another day I let you get away <br>I keep calling 'til your guard comes down <br>'Cause I wanna keep you around <br>'Cause we started something good <br>But just know that before you <br>I wasn't ready for you <br>I wasn't ready for you <br>When you first met me for you <br>That's what I'm gonna do <br>I wasn't ready, I wasn't ready for you, baby <br>I wasn't ready for you, baby <br>For you, baby, for you, baby <br>I wasn't ready for you <br><br>I promise I'll treat you right <br>Been waiting my whole damn life waiting my whole damn life <br>Baby, it's about time <br>I wasn't ready for you I wasn't ready for you <br>Funny how this whole game played <br>Three years since I learned your name <br>The wrong time, the wrong place <br>I wasn't ready for you <br><br>I wasn't ready, baby <br>I wasn't ready for you <br>I wasn't ready <br>I wasn't ready for you <br>I wasn't ready, baby <br>I wasn't ready for you, babe <br>I wasn't ready <br>I wasn't ready for you <br>I wasn't ready, I wasn't ready, no <br>I wasn't ready <br>I wasn't ready for you <br>I wasn't ready]]></content><category term="HAIM" label="HAIM"/><category term="Ready For You" label="Ready For You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Little_Of_Your_Love/</id><title>HAIM - Little Of Your Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Little_Of_Your_Love/" title="HAIM - Little Of Your Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Give me just a little of your love <br><br>You're just another recovering heart <br>I wasn't even gonna try <br>You wouldn't even give up time <br>Could be so easy, you make it hard <br>Don't think about love too much <br>My love is gonna be enough <br><br>You're so close now <br>And I know now <br><br>You gotta give me just a little of your love, baby <br>And I'll try <br>You gotta give me just a little of your love, baby <br>And I'll try <br>You gotta give me just a little of your love, baby <br>And I'll try <br>You gotta give me just a little of you love, give me just a little of your love <br><br>Don't it feel like that night was from a dream <br>Ooh, ooh, ooh <br>I've never felt nothing like that <br>Looking at you, looking right back <br>You say nothing is ever as good as it seems <br>Ooh, ooh, ooh <br>Stop running your mouth like that <br>'Cause you know I'm gonna give it right back <br><br>You're so close now <br>Don't let me down Don't let me down <br>So don't let me down <br><br>You gotta give me just a little of your love, baby <br>And I'll try <br>You gotta give me just a little of your love, baby <br>And I'll try <br>You gotta give me just a little of your love, baby <br>And I'll try <br>You gotta give me just a little of you love, give me just a little of your love <br><br>Oh with a little strength baby <br>Oh, I'll never let you down <br>With a little love, a little love, a little love, a little love <br>Give me just a little of your love, baby <br>You gotta give me just a little of your love, baby <br>You gotta give me just a little of your love, baby <br>You gotta give me just a little of your love, give me just a little of your love <br><br>Give me just a little of your love ha <br>Give me just a little of your love come on <br>Give me just a little of your love baby <br>Give me just a little of your love <br>Give me just a little of your love <br>You gotta give me just a little of your love, baby <br>Give me just a little of your love just a little of your love <br>You gotta give me just a little of your love, baby <br>Give me just a little of your love just a little of your love <br><br>Give me just a little of your love ha, ha <br>Give me just a little of your love ha, come on <br>Give me just a little of your love <br>Give me just a little of your love, give me just a little of your love <br>Give me just a little of your love <br>Give me just a little of your love <br>Give me just a little of your love <br>Give me just a little of your love, just a little of your love <br>Give me just a little of your love <br>Give me just a little of your love <br>Give me just a little of your love]]></content><category term="HAIM" label="HAIM"/><category term="Little Of Your Love" label="Little Of Your Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Nothings_Wrong/</id><title>HAIM - Nothing`s Wrong - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Nothings_Wrong/" title="HAIM - Nothing`s Wrong - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Counting the hours <br>With nothing to say <br>Going though the motions <br>It's slipping away <br>We were so gallant <br>So unafraid <br>Sleeping back to back <br>You're turning away <br><br>How could you tell me nothing's wrong T tell me <br>Tell me, tell me nothing's wrong T tell me <br>It was good, but now it's gone T tell me <br>Tell me, tell me nothing's wrong T tell me <br>How could you tell me nothing's wrong T tell me <br>Go on, tell me what you want T tell me <br>Boy, you're telling me all along T tell me <br>Just tell me nothing's wrong <br><br>Sound of the times <br>Sound of your crimes <br>Thinking about the other night <br>Was it all in my mind <br>I was so foolish, I was so blind <br>Why do we do this to each other, baby <br>Heartbreak by design <br><br>How could you tell me nothing's wrong <br>Just tell me baby <br>Tell me, tell me nothing's wrong <br>Could you tell me nothing's wrong <br>It was good, but now it's gone <br>Tell me, tell me nothing's wrong <br>T tell me nothing's wrong <br>How could you tell me nothing's wrong <br>Just tell me baby <br>Go on, tell me what you want T tell me <br>Boy, you're telling me all along T tell me <br>Just tell me nothing's wrong T tell me <br><br>It's obvious <br>Be honest <br>It's obvious Could you tell me nothing's wrong <br>Be honest <br>It's obvious <br>Be honest <br>It's obvious Just tell me baby <br>Be honest <br>It's obvious <br>Be honest <br>Be honest, be honest <br><br>Tell me nothing's wrong <br>T tell me nothing's wrong <br>T tell me nothing's wrong <br>Yeah, yeah <br><br>How could you tell me nothing's wrong T tell me <br>Go on, tell me what you want T tell me <br>Boy, you're telling me all along T tell me <br>Just tell me nothing's wrong <br>Just tell me baby <br>How could you tell me nothing's wrong T tell me <br>Tell me, tell me nothing's wrong T tell me <br>How could you tell me nothing's wrong T tell me <br>Tell me, tell me nothing's wrong T tell me <br>How could you tell me nothing's wrong T tell me <br>Go on, tell me what you want T tell me <br>Boy, you're telling me all along]]></content><category term="HAIM" label="HAIM"/><category term="Nothing`s Wrong" label="Nothing`s Wrong"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Want_You_Back/</id><title>HAIM - Want You Back - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAIM/Want_You_Back/" title="HAIM - Want You Back - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Some things are long forgotten <br>Some things were never said <br>We were on one endless road <br>But I had a wandering heart <br>I said we were opposite lovers <br>Said it from the beginning <br>You kept trying to prove me wrong <br>Said you'd always see it through <br>And I know that I ran you down <br>So you ran away with your heart <br>But just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you <br>I'll take the fall and the fault in us <br>I'll give you all the love <br>I never gave before I left you <br>Just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you <br>I'll take the fall and the fault in us <br>I'll give you all the love <br>I never gave before I left you <br>I know it's hard to hear it <br>And it may never be enough <br>But don't take it out on me now <br>'Cause I blame it all on myself <br>And I had a fear of forgiveness <br>Said it from the beginning <br>I was too proud to say I was wrong <br>Said you'd always see me through <br>All that time is gone <br>no more fearing control <br>I'm ready for the both of us now <br>But just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you <br>I'll take the fall and the fault in us <br>I'll give you all the love <br>I never gave before I left you <br>Just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you <br>Just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you <br>Just know that I want you <br>I'll take the fall and the fault in us <br>I'll give you all the love <br>I never gave before I left you <br>Just know that I want you back baby <br>Just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you <br>I'll take the fall and the fault in us <br>I'll give you all the love <br>I never gave before I left you <br>Just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you <br>I'll take the fall and the fault in us <br>I'll give you all the love <br>I never gave before I left you <br>Just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you <br>I'll take the fall and the fault in us <br>I'll give you all the love <br>I never gave before I left you <br>Just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you <br>Just know that I want you back <br>Just know that I want you <br>Just know that I want you <br>I'll take the fall and the fault in us <br>I'll give you all the love <br>I never gave before I left you <br>Just know that I want you back baby <br>Just know that I want you <br>Just know that I want you back baby <br>I'll take the fall and the fault in us <br>I'll give you all the love <br>I never gave before I left you <br>]]></content><category term="HAIM" label="HAIM"/><category term="Want You Back" label="Want You Back"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Capital_Cities/Swimming_Pool_Summer_THCSRS_Remix/</id><title>Capital Cities - Swimming Pool Summer (THCSRS Remix) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Capital_Cities/Swimming_Pool_Summer_THCSRS_Remix/" title="Capital Cities - Swimming Pool Summer (THCSRS Remix) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I break a sweat at the ch?teau <br>A party crowd that I don't know <br>La dolce vita head to toe <br>I kiss a cheek to say hello <br>She takes a sip of champagne <br>It's elegant, but not vain <br>She calls attention to her vein <br>And then she dives into my brain <br><br>Swimming pool summer <br>Gimme your number <br>Under your cover <br>I wanna take the heat <br><br>She comes up for a breath <br>Fuck the rest, she's the best <br>Her eyes are laser beaming me <br>Suspending all reality <br>And just as soon as she smiles <br>She puts her sunglasses on <br>I haven't felt this in a while <br>She breaks me down in style <br><br>Swimming pool summer <br>Gimme your number <br>Under your cover <br>I wanna take the heat <br><br>Physical wonder <br>A sensual hunter <br>Under your cover <br>I can't escape the heat <br>I can't escape the heat <br>I can't escape the heat <br><br>Swimming pool summer <br>Gimme your number <br>Under your cover <br>I wanna take the heat <br><br>Physical wonder <br>A sensual hunter <br>Under your cover <br>I can't escape the heat <br>I can't escape the heat <br>I can't escape the heat <br>I can't escape the heat <br>I can't escape the heat]]></content><category term="Capital Cities" label="Capital Cities"/><category term="Swimming Pool Summer (THCSRS Remix)" label="Swimming Pool Summer (THCSRS Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Capital_Cities/Girl_Friday_Feat_Rick_Ross/</id><title>Capital Cities - Girl Friday (Feat. Rick Ross) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Capital_Cities/Girl_Friday_Feat_Rick_Ross/" title="Capital Cities - Girl Friday (Feat. Rick Ross) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She's a ohh <br>She's a yeah <br>She's a hah <br>She's a woo <br>She's a aha <br>She's a hoh <br>Boss <br><br>She's my Girl Friday <br>She's my Girl Friday <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday <br>She's my Girl Friday <br>She's my Girl Friday <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday <br><br>Hello <br>You are the one I wanna take out on the weekend <br>Oh, hi <br>Do not pretend you wanna end what we got going <br>Okay <br>How about a movie <br>Baby, tell me that you're free then <br>I'm sorry But I think I got Tuesday and Wednesday open <br><br>She's got things to do everyday of the week <br>While I'm just playing hide and desperately seek <br>I wait around the clock, but her calendar is blocked <br>I'm a hard place <br>And she's a rock, she's a rock <br><br>She's my Girl Friday <br>She's my Girl Friday <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday <br>She's my Girl Friday <br>She's my Girl Friday It's the biggest boss <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday Yeah, I love this <br><br>I think we fell in love outside a Wingstop <br>Put the joint out when I hopped right out the t top <br>You're looking like something I could deal with <br>Get between your thighs, maybe have that happy meal with <br>Either way I got to put you on the calendar <br>Take you on a tour so someone call my manager <br>Biggest boss got my shirt off, off at Coachella <br>Biggest blunts, everybody got their own fetish <br>So we at the concert at the frat house <br>Drink with live music 'til we passed out <br>Everybody rocking with the big boss <br>Let's roll another joint soon as class out <br>Said this year we wanna do it bigger <br>So you came and got the right <br>On stage and I'm looking for the best kitties <br>Put your middle finger up for Capital Cities <br><br>She's my Girl Friday <br>She's my Girl Friday It's the biggest event of the year <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday It's the biggest boss <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday Capital Cities <br>She's my Girl Friday Put your fingers in the air <br>She's my Girl Friday <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday Hold 'em up <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday Woooooooo <br>She's my Girl Friday <br>She's my Girl Friday <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday <br>She's my Girl Friday <br>She's my Girl Friday Boss <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday <br>I'm her Boy Wednesday Woo, woo <br>Okay <br>She's a <br>She's a <br>Oh, hi <br>She's a <br>She's a <br>Oh, hi <br>She's a Boss]]></content><category term="Capital Cities" label="Capital Cities"/><category term="Girl Friday (Feat. Rick Ross)" label="Girl Friday (Feat. Rick Ross)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Capital_Cities/Swimming_Pool_Summer/</id><title>Capital Cities - Swimming Pool Summer - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Capital_Cities/Swimming_Pool_Summer/" title="Capital Cities - Swimming Pool Summer - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I break a sweat at the ch?teau <br>A party crowd that I don't know <br>La dolce vita head to toe <br>I kiss a cheek to say hello <br>She takes a sip of champagne <br>It's elegant, but not vain <br>She calls attention to her vein <br>And then she dives into my brain <br><br>Swimming pool summer <br>Gimme your number <br>Under your cover <br>I wanna take the heat <br><br>She comes up for a breath <br>Fuck the rest, she's the best <br>Her eyes are laser beaming me <br>Suspending all reality <br>And just as soon as she smiles <br>She puts her sunglasses on <br>I haven't felt this in a while <br>She breaks me down in style <br><br>Swimming pool summer <br>Gimme your number <br>Under your cover <br>I wanna take the heat <br><br>Physical wonder <br>A sensual hunter <br>Under your cover <br>I can't escape the heat <br>I can't escape the heat <br>I can't escape the heat <br><br>Swimming pool summer <br>Gimme your number <br>Under your cover <br>I wanna take the heat <br><br>Physical wonder <br>A sensual hunter <br>Under your cover <br>I can't escape the heat <br>I can't escape the heat <br>I can't escape the heat <br>I can't escape the heat <br>I can't escape the heat]]></content><category term="Capital Cities" label="Capital Cities"/><category term="Swimming Pool Summer" label="Swimming Pool Summer"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DZ/Grind_사랑과_평화/</id><title>DZ - Grind (사랑과 평화) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DZ/Grind_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EA%B3%BC_%ED%8F%89%ED%99%94/" title="DZ - Grind (사랑과 평화) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>gotta rap grab tht cash <br>fuck peace love yeah mobbing <br>send tht cash grab tht shit <br>우주위지 mothufucka <br>gotta rap grab tht cash <br>fuck peace love yeah mobbing <br>send tht cash grab tht shit <br>우주위지 mothufucka <br>yo 소매를 걷어 비젼을 맺어 <br>불씨는 꺼져 평화는 뻗어 <br>puff it and pass off <br>불어도 매번 잡히는 애들 <br>don't giv a fcuk abt hey ninja 의 <br>숨결은 높아 하 높아 난 보이지 노파 <br>각막을 각색 우주선 폭파 <br>난 차원을 통과 야 사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>i told u i dont fuck wit no bottom <br>높은데 있어도 ain't no problem <br>기분은 언제나 up up and away <br>yeah bitch we puff puff anyways <br>got cash and mula we gonn pay <br>언제나 사랑과 평화 없이는 <br>안 놀아 절대로 we don play <br>사람과 편한 관계는 변하구 <br>뜨거운 여자 머리 위에 화산 분출 <br>감옥에서 구출 <br>부재중 전화 문제는 잠수부 <br>그들은 내 위에서 잠을 자 쿨 쿨 <br>내가 가진 자질 자질 <br>아무도 못 막아 아무도 못 막아 <br>아무도 못 막을 꺼야 <br>난 그냥 우주선을 타고 <br>올라가곤 했어 친구들과 <br>우리는 주차장에서 주구장창 <br>시간을 보내 음악 <br>내가 가장 좋아하는 총은 <br>은총 장전해 은총알 <br>가득 채우고 태우고 방심하다 <br>맞을 수 있어 <br>비 오듯 흐르는 땀 넌 인형처럼 <br>뽑힐 수 있어 <br>그러면 그녀를 어떻게 불러 <br>call taxi I missed fuck u bus <br>난 그냥 약을 터트려 모험 <br>작은 나 방에 날 계집 <br>나는 다시 돌아와 춘향 <br>이몽룡 정신이 몽롱 <br>gotta rap grab tht cash <br>fuck peace love yeah mobbing <br>send tht cash grab tht shit <br>우주위지 mothufucka <br>gotta rap grab tht cash <br>fuck peace love yeah mobbing <br>send tht cash grab tht shit <br>우주위지 mothufucka <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>모르다면 말을 말어 <br>난 구름 위 두둥실 위 <br>fpl shit 원을 돌려 <br>난 쓸 줄도 알고 버는 법도 <br>알아 병신 같은 fuck boys <br>fuck yall eat dat 중지 <br>motherfucker uh <br>위로만 올라가서 난 직진 <br>fuck peace and love <br>우린 올라가지 너 네는 또 내려가지 <br>yeah we bakin and cookin shit up <br>모조리 쓸어 담어 빛만 늘지 넌 <br>i got dat mofuckin shit <br>매일 우주로 출석 <br>gotta stack and make more money <br>버는 대로 난 keep deposit <br>못 볼 것도 이미 봤지 <br>그래도 돌리고 돌려 위로만 가겠지 <br>넌 편안히 잠이나 들어 <br>난 오늘도 축배를 들어 <br>내 맘대로 그리는 지도 <br>또 세우지 또 다른 기록 <br>gotta rap grab tht cash <br>fuck peace love yeah mobbing <br>send tht cash grab tht shit <br>우주위지 mothufucka <br>gotta rap grab tht cash <br>fuck peace love yeah mobbing <br>send tht cash grab tht shit <br>우주위지 mothufucka <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>사랑과 평화를 갈어 <br>]]></content><category term="DZ" label="DZ"/><category term="Grind (사랑과 평화)" label="Grind (사랑과 평화)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DZ/Stone_Cold_Feat_Kigga_Dbo/</id><title>DZ - Stone Cold (Feat. Kigga, Dbo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DZ/Stone_Cold_Feat_Kigga_Dbo/" title="DZ - Stone Cold (Feat. Kigga, Dbo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>stun stun stun <br>stoner life we chillin <br>무거운 공기 압박감에 <br>숨을 못셔 기침 <br>무중력상태 도피 난 텔레파시 <br>dolphin <br>같은 것을 원해 heavy stoner <br>난 더 깊이 들이 마셔 <br>fuck it 쭉 빵 빵하게 더 부어봐 <br>내 손에는 부부젤라와 포도 쥬스 <br>this dat fuckin' good <br>kush let me finesse <br>ninja on the mission <br>가져와바 swisha <br>나는 계속해서 rollin' tht <br>pass it to me purple swagg <br>날아가는 로켓 펀치라인 불이 붙었네 <br>뒤통수 잡고 stun 기절상태 별 <br>보일 때 you'll kno it bitch <br>welcome to ma zone <br>i got 맥주 2캔 pop this shit <br>2 shot gunz and a whippin' cream <br>탱크처럼 들이 박어 <br>till i pass out 난 쓰러짐 <br>다시 일어나서 victory <br>난 반복해 이 짓거리 <br>손가락 3개 들어 fuck peace <br>and love yeah 세레모니 <br>I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>삐가리 돌 때까지 <br>I keep smokin that good shit <br>올라가서 찍어 정점 <br>FPL shit 말 안 해도 알지 <br>불타는 토요일엔 <br>주차장에서 we chillin <br>nobody can judge me <br>변함없이 난 계속 불지 <br>yeah cuz dz dbo got ma back <br>우린 올라가 우주위로 <br>keep rollin up and make it circle <br>끊임없이 큰 원을 그려 <br>독불장군 stunner daily <br>fuckin bread in ma pocket <br>순차적으로 끝내 길을 비켜 <br>u pussy ass motherfucker <br>좇같은 현실들 좇까 난 날 믿기에 <br>if u don fuck with me then <br>알아서들 잘 피해 <br>from the north to the south man <br>구름 위에서 우린 비행 <br>시작은 길바닥 주차장이 무대야 <br>일단 들이 박고 봐 bitch <br>fpl we so fuckin elevated <br>결과가 중요해 과정이라는 도마 위에 <br>yeah bitch I been hustlin <br>한 폭의 그림 나는 물감이 될께 <br>chop chop 때려 네 면상에다가 <br>I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>요즘 난 영혼을 소홀히 <br>다뤘어 바닥을 보니 <br>최고가 되고 싶은 놈이 <br>골이 빠개져 동이 터 <br>옹기종기 모여 <br>배신하지 않아 노력 <br>나는 사진을 오려 <br>내가 그녀를 보면 <br>그녀는 고양이처럼 요염 <br>대부분 배속 멈추지 않아 애송이 <br>나는 내 꺼를 니 앞에다가 두고 와 <br>부셔진 변화 고개 숙인 벼와 <br>불이 붙은 전화 안전핀 뽑힌 소화기 <br>물끄럼 불꺼 부끄러 <br>누가 날 태웠 마실 것에다 약을 타 <br>나는 가로 새로워 이제 약 올라 <br>코알라처럼 자 <br>그리고 꿈꾸는 듯이 여자 <br>Im so cool Im so cold <br>I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>I'm a stone cold steve austin <br>heavy stunna heavy stoner <br>]]></content><category term="DZ" label="DZ"/><category term="Stone Cold (Feat. Kigga, Dbo)" label="Stone Cold (Feat. Kigga, Dbo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DZ/Twenty_4_Seven/</id><title>DZ - Twenty 4 Seven - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DZ/Twenty_4_Seven/" title="DZ - Twenty 4 Seven - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[24/7 up in heavn <br>I'm chilling on this cloud everyday <br>맛이 간 표정은 헤벌레 <br>내일은 맑은 하늘 깨끗해 <br>다시 더럽히고 더럽혀진 내 두 손 <br>watch me motherfucker <br>다시 나는 날을 죽여 또 나는 날 죽여 <br>watch me motherfucker <br>I'm 24/7 up in heavn <br>bitch I'm 24/7 up in heavn <br>I'm 24/7 up in heavn <br>bitch I'm 24/7 up in heavn <br>yo it ain't shit so I vape <br>this and vape tht <br>딴 랩퍼들을 rape hey 조심해 <br>ninjaz comin for ya <br>랩퍼들의 title <br>난 필요 없지 survival <br>난 랩퍼들의 bible <br>pray for wat u need <br>oh lord 병신들을 죽여 주소서 <br>니가 주인공이라면은 소설 <br>난 잘하지 못해 가끔 조절 <br>선배님들의 랩 fuckin 고전 <br>문학 fuck tht shit <br>난 boombox 에서 시작 <br>난 t-dot 에서 진짜를 배웠지 <br>초록색 물감 <br>내 보라색 도화지 피부색 흑화 <br>내 정신병 훅 가 한번에 <br>빨고 또 뱉어 단번에 <br>후회하지 말고 딴걸 해 <br>자신 없으면 그냥 자결해 <br>bitch 자 살해 살살해 <br>24/7 up in heavn <br>I'm chilling on this cloud everyday <br>맛이 간 표정은 헤벌레 <br>내일은 맑은 하늘 깨끗해 <br>다시 더럽히고 더럽혀진 내 두 손 <br>watch me motherfucker <br>다시 나는 날을 죽여 또 나는 날 죽여 <br>watch me motherfucker <br>I'm 24/7 up in heavn <br>bitch I'm 24/7 up in heavn <br>I'm 24/7 up in heavn <br>bitch I'm 24/7 up in heavn <br>everyday 24 뒤집어도 420 <br>내 기념일 기념해 fuck the cops <br>im on ma way <br>연기를 뿌려 니 눈앞에 <br>but 쇠고랑은 안 찰래 <br>검은 축복 늘 감사해 <br>꼬리가 길어도 감출래 i kno <br>신이시여 나를 지켜 주소서 <br>난 천국의 문을 감히 열고서 <br>들어가지 I'm in ma zone <br>limbo 상태 한심한 놈 <br>간지러워 난 지겨워 이놈들 위에 <br>난 피카소 어지러워 <br>yeah dizzy life <br>난 입가셔 <br>I'm doing this forever and ever <br>thug life forever or never <br>살던가 아님 죽던가 <br>나랑 붙던가 날 불던가 <br>let's fuck up some commas <br>yeah t-dot의 방식 <br>난 죽여놔 뭐든 비트위에 <br>lucifer yeah <br>가끔은 겁이나 <br>내 형제나 적이 날 감당 못할 까봐 <br>너무 커가는 내 자신이 겁이나 oh <br>가짜는 저리가 느껴지는 거리감 <br>함부로 떨어 지지 못해 멀미 나는 <br>나의 높이 가 ho <br>24/7 up in heavn <br>I'm chilling on this cloud everyday <br>맛이 간 표정은 헤벌레 <br>내일은 맑은 하늘 깨끗해 <br>다시 더럽히고 더럽혀진 내 두 손 <br>watch me motherfucker <br>다시 나는 날을 죽여 또 나는 날 죽여 <br>watch me motherfucker <br>]]></content><category term="DZ" label="DZ"/><category term="Twenty 4 Seven" label="Twenty 4 Seven"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dbo_디보/그치/</id><title>Dbo (디보) - 그치 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dbo_%EB%94%94%EB%B3%B4/%EA%B7%B8%EC%B9%98/" title="Dbo (디보) - 그치 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 고장 나서 박스 나르고 <br>산타 할아버지 봤어 나는 못 <br>망치지마 청정구역 어 <br>그래 설움이 북 쳐 신문고 어 <br>그래 서른이 넘어 식물원 <br>너를 만나기 전 머릴 자르고 <br>흥 가벼운 발자국 지금도 <br>해가 질 때 강물이 그렁그렁 <br>지하철을 타 우린 닌자 거북이 <br>다들 알아 나는 돌연변이 <br>철새처럼 따뜻한 주전자 부리 <br>암컷용이 내게 말해 아 뜨거 수증기 <br>영웅이 필요해 내 표정 태권 브이 <br>숫자를 셀께 칠팔구십 어 금니 <br>난 돈 벌고 때려 때찌 엉덩이 <br>정글에서 쫓겨난 모글리 <br>같이 타잔 말도 못했어 어 그치 <br>I like gimchi I eat chickin <br>Im talking 바껴 얼굴이 <br>그때는 떠났고 기억은 내 금고 <br>적을 겨눈 총구 내 뒤를 찌르고 <br>있어 그러니까 영혼을 구조 <br>고마워요 조상님들 피 유전 <br>실망하지마 사랑을 줬어 그치 <br>가슴 깊은 곳 사랑이 업 uh 그치 <br>진짜 진짜 진짜로 살고 싶어 그치 <br>그리고 나는 배고픈 거 싫어 그치 <br>어 그치 어 그치 어 그치 그치 그치 <br>실망하지마 사랑을 줬어 그치 <br>가슴 깊은 곳 사랑이 업 uh 그치 <br>진짜 진짜 진짜로 살고 싶어 그치 <br>그리고 나는 배고픈 거 싫어 그치 <br>어 그치 어 그치 어 그치 그치 그치 <br>부셔버려 내가 실험 <br>이게 나 나 훨씬 <br>더 나 나는 역시 <br>머리를 써 열심히 박치기 <br>아니 난 별미로 열쇠 <br>크림을 내 혀로 녹여 <br>날 얼린 넌 여기 <br>나는 노리고 노려 <br>정상을 향해 노력 <br>닿을 수 없어도 뭐 <br>나는 하늘이 보여 <br>새 하얀 구름 모형 같이 순한 양 <br>매 날 때릴 꺼야 <br>petting her knee caps <br>Im homie ya know me <br>oh 희미한 노을 이미 한 몸 <br>어련하실까 좌표 살아 일해 문양 <br>우 외로운 늑대 아우 <br>내게 틀린걸 주지마 비리 비리 <br>이십 대가 됐어 <br>주차장에 가서 불을 붙여 <br>FPL crew 2012년도에 <br>계속했어 여전해 그건 안 변해 <br>게임을 못해 난 깨있을 때 해 <br>불씨 ok 함께 있을 때 chill <br>전혀 상관없어 어 손들고 벌써 <br>실망하지마 사랑을 줬어 그치 <br>가슴 깊은 곳 사랑이 업 uh 그치 <br>진짜 진짜 진짜로 살고 싶어 그치 <br>그리고 나는 배고픈 거 싫어 그치 <br>어 그치 어 그치 어 그치 그치 그치 <br>실망하지마 사랑을 줬어 그치 <br>가슴 깊은 곳 사랑이 업 uh 그치 <br>진짜 진짜 진짜로 살고 싶어 그치 <br>그리고 나는 배고픈 거 싫어 그치 <br>어 그치 어 그치 어 그치 <br>어 그치 그치 <br>]]></content><category term="Dbo (디보)" label="Dbo (디보)"/><category term="그치" label="그치"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/브리엘/Flight/</id><title>브리엘 - Flight - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%98/Flight/" title="브리엘 - Flight - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[도망치다보니 시속 700키로에 <br>창문 밖엔 구름들이 아래지 <br>무게 달다보니 감정들이 <br>시소위에 놀아 <br>묻지 말았으면해 <br>Circle round like we the gang so <br>spit much like let our soul go <br>freestyler freestyler <br>spit what you want won't <br>mind the skill son <br>그렇게 뱉어 펜은 버려 <br>볼륨은 최고치에 주차장에서 <br>한명 두명으로 즐겨 <br>느껴 왠지 이건 나의 운명 <br>숨셔 근데 요즘에 난 <br>좌회전 우회전 <br>비현실 꿈에서 <br>대충 만족하고 피했어 <br>모든것들을 빼고나니 난 시체 위 <br>다시 눈을 떠 <br>갓난애기 <br>paranoia paranoia <br>please don't kill me <br>want the world to be right there <br>up down 아래위 <br>감정들이 파도 칠 때 <br>빨리 상처들이 아무기를 바래 바늘질 <br>know you ain't rocky but if <br>you're sure <br>너의 실패를 삼켜 부딛혀 <br>다시 숨을 셔 숨을 셔 스물번 <br>숨을 것도 없어 다시 보게 되는 순서 <br>Circle round like we the gang so <br>spit much like let our soul go <br>freestyler freestyler freestyler <br>freestyler <br>앞뒤를 전혀 보지 않고 달렸어 <br>나의 종이 비행기 접어 날렸어 <br>날렵한줄 알아 낙엽들이 돼 <br>막연하게 달려 미로속에 길을 잃을 <br>때 <br>that panic thrust <br>that penny for your thoughts <br>paint it raw <br>pin it <br>flip it <br>got another penny for your <br>thoughts <br>spit it raw <br>back to the <br>Circle round like we the gang so <br>spit much like let our soul go <br>freestyler freestyler <br>spit what you want won't <br>mind the skill son <br>그렇게 뱉어 <br>그렇다면 지구는 제자리에 <br>아직 어려 우리는 <br>같은 우리 안에 우리야 <br>우리가 만난 거는 정말 운이야 <br>잊지않았으면해 타령한다면 <br>또 술이야 <br>앞을 보고 봐 <br>펀치라인들은 성지순례 <br>가린 눈을 뜨고 다시 꿈을 분해해 <br>t dot to our homes <br>gotta burn slow <br>show show gotta show like <br>low life low key <br>올라 저위 <br>멀리 멀리 <br>갈려면 벌어 벌어 <br>just a few puffs <br>take me heal me <br>from the rough like <br>Circle round like we the gang so <br>spit much like let our soul go <br>freestyler freestyler <br>spit what you want won't <br>mind the skill son <br>Circle round like we the gang so <br>spit much like let our soul go <br>freestyler freestyler <br>freestyler freestyler <br>도망치다보니 시속 700 키로에 <br>묻지 말았으면해 <br>flowing on and oh no <br>slow it gotta grow more <br>]]></content><category term="브리엘" label="브리엘"/><category term="Flight" label="Flight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DZ/검은_축복/</id><title>DZ - 검은 축복 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DZ/%EA%B2%80%EC%9D%80_%EC%B6%95%EB%B3%B5/" title="DZ - 검은 축복 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like I'm so blessed <br>since mamas womb <br>bitch let me levitate <br>참어 나의 숨 <br>I feel like I'm so blessed <br>since mamas womb <br>bitch let me levitate <br>참어 나의 숨 <br>Hey 남들과 달라서 <br>처음부터 갈길이 달랐어 <br>난 걸어가 wit ma fellaz <br>thug life 난 그냥 살았어 <br>사막안에 오아시스 <br>fuck all ma enemies <br>검은손이 나의 머리위 <br>I'm in a whole <br>another league bitch <br>yeah I’m alone <br>in this world <br>wit ma fuck peace and love <br>hey 내게 줘 내게 줘 <br>검은 축복 wait <br>legalize legalize <br>I don't need ur third eye <br>계속 외쳐 <br>I’m so high 합법적인 전파 <br>계속 떠들어봤자 <br>위험한 복은 내 손에 머물겠지 <br>신이 주신 한계 피고 나서 갈게 <br>피곤 하면 <br>잠시 날개를 높게 기지개 기지개 <br>날기 위한 도약 <br>내 피가 나의 독약 <br>curse me yeah I never love u <br>이게 병이라면 걸어 <br>나는 몽유 uh 눈을 감어 <br>눈을 감어 눈을 가려 <br>볼수 없는 사고 계산 착오 <br>whoa 타고난 바보 <br>난 타고 남은 것을 <br>갈고 닦어 uh <br>yeah I’m alone in this world <br>wit ma fuck peace and love <br>hey 내게 줘 내게 줘 <br>검은 축복 wait <br>I feel like I'm so blessed <br>since mamas womb <br>bitch let me levitate <br>참어 나의 숨 <br>I feel like I'm so blessed <br>since mamas womb <br>bitch let me levitate <br>참어 나의 숨 <br>난 피 고인 밉보인 <br>미운 오리새키 <br>but I keep goin <br>떠 다녀 검은 물이 깊이 고인 <br>썩은 바다에서 벗어나 <br>빛 보인 곳이 home sweet home <br>but I'm gettin low <br>여자들의 아랫도리와 시선 <br>올라갔다 내려와 나는 시소 <br>탄 기분알지 도시는 무질서 <br>what the fuck is goin on <br>나는 Iimbo 상태 마냥 그냥 <br>조용히 기도 이 검은 축복이 <br>나를 위로 올려 놓을때 <br>넌 찾아와 빈소 나는 빈손으로 <br>받어 평화와 사랑 <br>내가 죽고나서도 다시 또 살어 <br>받은 것이 많아서 감사해 <br>mama and dada 날 봐바 <br>이젠 I feel like don dada hey <br>I dont giv a fuck what ur sayin <br>and fuck all ur fame no wait <br>돈과 명예 내 앞에서 모든 것이 변해 <br>나는 정해진 길로 걸어가지 운명 <br>어쩌면 어머니의 자궁으로부터 <br>내가 태어나 나이 먹어서 운명 <br>할때까지 또 다시 불을 붙여 okayyy <br>I feel like I'm so blessed <br>since mamas womb <br>bitch let me levitate <br>참어 나의 숨 <br>I feel like I'm so blessed <br>since mamas womb <br>bitch let me levitate <br>참어 나의 숨 <br>I feel like I'm so blessed <br>since mamas womb <br>bitch let me levitate <br>참어 나의 숨 <br>]]></content><category term="DZ" label="DZ"/><category term="검은 축복" label="검은 축복"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dbo_디보/Mad_At_Me_Feat_DZ/</id><title>Dbo (디보) - Mad At Me (Feat. DZ) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dbo_%EB%94%94%EB%B3%B4/Mad_At_Me_Feat_DZ/" title="Dbo (디보) - Mad At Me (Feat. DZ) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어떻게 넌 아니 <br>내가 항상 원하던 것들이 <br>너무 많아 가져가기 힘들다는 걸 <br>이걸 들어 니가 내게 화났을 때 <br>니가 내게 화났을 때 <br>니가 내게 화났을 때 <br>니가 내게 화났을 때 <br>내 모든 실험이 내 거름이 되길 <br>내가 법 정했을 때 죄책감에 bill <br>세번째 갈메기 꽉 잡은 두 손 <br>앞에는 절벽 내게 힘을 주소서 <br>우주 소녀 <br>난 노력해 누가 <br>우리를 닥치라고 할까 <br>우리 그만하자 움직이지 않는 조각상 <br>그년 아무것도 그녀는 <br>아무것도 탓하지 않아 <br>우리들은 곧 도착하지 아마 <br>난 빌지않아 부탁하니까 야 <br>떨어져 봐 벌벌 떨어 멀어져 가 <br>풀어줘 날 벌어 돈 벌어 여경찰 <br>도망치다 연애질 넌 한번도 못했니 <br>붉은 상처 겪해진 그녀와 내 손에 쥔 <br>두 여자 걸어다녀 알아 <br>말하곤 해 환상 나는 화가 화가 화가 <br>어떻게 넌 아니 <br>내가 항상 원하던 것들이 <br>너무 많아 가져가기 힘들다는 걸 <br>이걸 들어 니가 내게 화났을 때 <br>니가 내게 화났을 때 <br>니가 내게 화났을 때 <br>니가 내게 화났을 때 <br>hey 내게 화났을 땐 말을 해줘 babe <br>같은 실수 다시 반복 wait <br>난 하난 알고 둘은 몰라 <br>세계는 곧 fuck peace love <br>내 말이 안통한다면 난 우주위로 <br>hey 넌 가만있어 ba-by <br>내가 다시 돌아오는 날이 pay day <br>gettin' money gettin' trees <br>뿌린대로 걷어 seeds <br>fast lane fast life <br>난 지금은 바빠 <br>내 음악 내 식구 내가족과 친구 <br>내 형제는 필요해 면죄와 믿음 <br>견제와 질투는 항상 내 옆에 <br>난 변태 중 ego 내성격은 뻔해 <br>불 보듯 뻔한건 초록색 연기 uh <br>yeahh bitch I'm trippin' <br>너무 높아서 난 구름위야 <br>why u mad at me hoe <br>]]></content><category term="Dbo (디보)" label="Dbo (디보)"/><category term="Mad At Me (Feat. DZ)" label="Mad At Me (Feat. DZ)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/브리엘/갈_생각_있어_Feat_Dbo/</id><title>브리엘 - 갈 생각 있어 (Feat. Dbo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%98/%EA%B0%88_%EC%83%9D%EA%B0%81_%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4_Feat_Dbo/" title="브리엘 - 갈 생각 있어 (Feat. Dbo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[같이 갈 생각 있어 <br>같이 갈 생각 있어 <br>도망치는거야 멀리 <br>but girl i need your trust like <br>smoke loud we bonnie clyde <br>ill kids we on our ride <br>우리꺼만 챙기면 돼 <br>finessin all them stacks now <br>fuck you anywhere don't care <br>pull out then we be <br>on our roll now <br>말어말어말어말어 <br>fuck the world 운명 우리가 만들어 <br>들었다놨다 다시 돌려놔 <br>zed is dead baby <br>yeah we be riding <br>on this chopper now <br>to the tropics right <br>누워서 chill <br>모래사장이 너무 하얘 <br>여기에 있다는거에 감사해 <br>god bless <br>아멘 아멘 <br>살아남아서 쟝고라해 pew pew <br>총알이 떨어져도 총이 하나 더 있어 <br>다 태워 태워 <br>get me sky high shit <br>뭘 입어도 넌 너무 야해 <br>like tell me <br>oh boy you the coolest <br>fool the world yeah <br>know the truth is a bit cruel <br>웃어 넘겨 we could play it too <br>단 둘이면 돼 <br>훌쩍 떠나고선 과거들은 <br>재미난 모험들이 돼 <br>champagne pop then we be <br>on to the next <br>표지판 옆에 나 <br>너 할꺼니 말꺼니 <br>말을 건내 어쩔껀데 <br>너 나랑 <br>같이 갈 생각 있어 <br>같이 갈 생각 있어 <br>도망치는거야 멀리 <br>but girl i need your trust like <br>smoke loud we bonnie clyde <br>ill kids we on our ride <br>우리꺼만 챙기면 돼 <br>finessin all them stacks now <br>I might be a liltle bit insane <br>you might never understand <br>I make that sand castle <br>but thunderstorm <br>Im not looking for love love <br>벚꽃이 떨어지고 파란 잎 <br>아무도 모르게 사라진 <br>우리의 사진 <br>걱정마 난 거기에서 나왔을 뿐이야 <br>거리에서 손을 잡고 도망가 어디야 <br>표지판 옆에 나 <br>너 할꺼니 말꺼니 <br>말을 건내 어쩔껀데 <br>너 나랑 <br>같이 갈 생각 있어 <br>같이 갈 생각 있어 <br>도망치는거야 멀리 <br>but girl i need your trust like <br>smoke loud we bonnie clyde <br>ill kids we on our ride <br>우리꺼만 챙기면 돼 <br>finessin all them stacks now <br>같이 갈 생각 있어 <br>같이 갈 생각 있어 <br>도망치는거야 멀리 <br>but girl i need your trust like <br>smoke loud we bonnie clyde <br>ill kids we on our ride <br>우리꺼만 챙기면 돼 <br>finessin all them stacks now <br>같이 갈 생각 있어 <br>갈 생각 있어 <br>갈 생각 있어 <br>but girl i need your trust like <br>]]></content><category term="브리엘" label="브리엘"/><category term="갈 생각 있어 (Feat. Dbo)" label="갈 생각 있어 (Feat. Dbo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dbo_디보/She_Kno_Tht/</id><title>Dbo (디보) - She Kno Tht - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dbo_%EB%94%94%EB%B3%B4/She_Kno_Tht/" title="Dbo (디보) - She Kno Tht - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[hey she kno tht <br>hey she kno tht <br>hey she kno tht <br>hey she kno tht <br>I'm so stoned bitch <br>she kno tht <br>get tht money doller bill won <br>she kno tht <br>young ninjaz on the grind man <br>she kno tht <br>fuck peace and love <br>she kno tht <br>get tht dollar dollar bill yo bitch <br>paper rollin pop tht pill uh bitch <br>she kno tht <br>I'm on some shit uh <br>기침 콜록 콜록 <br>빛이 펄럭 펄럭 uh <br>날아다녀 연처럼 high as fuck <br>바보처럼 턱 다물지 못해 cock <br>suckers lick ma fuckin balls <br>yeah i got balls <br>대놓고 나는 puff puff puff <br>like a boss <br>깡패와 양아치 <br>구별이 안돼 앞뒤 <br>쓰레기를 낚시 <br>있을게 다 있어 <br>겨냥하고 발사 깡통 <br>여전히 그들은 바쁜 <br>가보지 물건을 납품 <br>조그만한 텃밭을 가꿔 더워 <br>나는 돌렸어 우린 원을 그려 <br>원래부터 그런 녀석 <br>난 엮어 널 이것 저것 다 <br>이건 연어 비린내가 <br>얠 빌려 갈게 <br>hey she kno tht <br>hey she kno tht <br>hey she kno tht <br>hey she kno tht <br>I'm so stoned bitch <br>she kno tht <br>get tht money doller bill won <br>she kno tht <br>young ninjaz on the grind man <br>she kno tht <br>fuck peace and love <br>she kno tht <br>she kno tht i'm crazy <br>fuck peace love we crazy <br>가짜들은 lazy she kno tht so ugly <br>그녀는 알어 i don't fuck wit lame <br>come on babe <br>imma pop pop pop <br>tht pussy looks so damn <br>she kno i got tht bling <br>got tht lean got tht piff <br>what so real u kno me <br>결혼하자 i got ring <br>빙글 빙글 도는 세상 <br>그녀와 나는 춤을 <br>어울리는 노래야 <br>그녀는 따라부름 <br>춤 춤 춤 그년 어쩔 줄 몰라 <br>걱정을 말아 야 <br>누가 어쩌구 저쩌구 <br>피 적어줄게 적혈구 <br>야 난 풀어 문제를 모두 <br>그리고 사적이야 난 말해 <br>찾아와 오늘밤 그녀와 비행기 안 <br>난 너를 밖으로 데려가 <br>그리고 노을을 봐 난 자 난 자 <br>]]></content><category term="Dbo (디보)" label="Dbo (디보)"/><category term="She Kno Tht" label="She Kno Tht"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DZ/Ninja_Blade_Feat_Kigga/</id><title>DZ - Ninja Blade (Feat. Kigga) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DZ/Ninja_Blade_Feat_Kigga/" title="DZ - Ninja Blade (Feat. Kigga) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[chop chop chop <br>chop it like ninja blade <br>chop chop chop <br>chop it like ninja blade <br>chop chop chop <br>chop it like ninja blade <br>chop chop chop <br>chop it like ninja blade <br>다 썰어 버려 mo fucker <br>다 짤라 짤라 짤라 짤라 wait <br>다 썰어 버려 mo fucker <br>다 짤라 짤라 짤라 wait <br>hey i grind for ma g <br>till i get 21 now <br>i'm 24 bitch hustle like a pigeon <br>welcome to ma green zone <br>난 천연기념물 <br>여긴 청정지역 <br>난 천국으로 <br>고개 까딱 까딱 까딱 whoa <br>시간은 째깍 째깍 <br>쟤 봐라 넌 1 what <br>진짜는 내 손 안에서 <br>소용돌이 야 <br>mofucker 엪피엘 <br>we goin world wide <br>내 언어를 넘어 <br>날 알아볼 놈들 <br>죄다 돈을 가져와 <br>내가 뱉는 건 개소리 <br>내 사고 뺑소니 부딪히고 <br>bounce like a ninja <br>난 잡아 이놈들 사랑의 회초리 <br>대나무 숲을 베 모조리 <br>계산은 계산기라 배웠지 <br>내 평화의 눈초리 재수없지 <br>mofucker 난 외쳐 괴물의 꾀꼬리 <br>chop chop chop <br>chop it like ninja blade <br>chop chop chop <br>chop it like ninja blade <br>chop chop chop <br>chop it like ninja blade <br>chop chop chop <br>chop it like ninja blade <br>다 썰어 버려 mo fucker <br>다 짤라 짤라 짤라 짤라 wait <br>다 썰어 버려 mo fucker hey <br>다 짤라 짤라 짤라 wait <br>닥치는 대로 썰어 <br>mofucker 내 칼은 잘 썰려 <br>난 벽을 두 번 넘어 <br>기분은 최고조지 <br>맘대로 날아 mofucker <br>눈에 뵈는 게 없이 <br>우린 주차장 우주 위 <br>굳이 말하자면 shit <br>we the shit FPL <br>we the shit 몇 번씩 지껄였지 <br>freestylin on this street 너넨 꿈꿔 <br>I hustle for the mula <br>또는 돈은 가슴 안에 내 <br>그게 나의 미션 수행하지 <br>칼을 갈어 <br>벽을 넘어 올라가 <br>fuck peace and love on the misson <br>말만 많고 눈치 보는 <br>pussy ass mofucker <br>keep talkin bullshit <br>진짜들만 살아남아 호구들아 <br>난 원래 걱정이 없지 <br>생각 없이 행동해 병신아 <br>불 꺼진 방안엔 연기가 <br>흔적 없이 사라져 <br>연기만 높이 올라가 연기나 <br>I spit fuckin fire <br>쉬지 않고 계속 불어 <br>우린 더 매섭게 투척 <br>숨죽여 행동하지 <br>알아채도 <br>이미 늦어 썩은 랩퍼들 <br>싹을 잘라버리고 <br>다시 숨어 <br>그냥 해 ain't shit <br>what u got mofucker <br>FPL we keep it goin up and <br>i'm just <br>chop chop chop <br>chop it like ninja blade <br>chop chop chop <br>chop it like ninja blade <br>chop chop chop <br>chop it like ninja blade <br>chop chop chop <br>chop it like ninja blade <br>다 썰어 버려 mo fucker <br>다 짤라 짤라 짤라 짤라 wait <br>다 썰어 버려 mo fucker <br>다 짤라 짤라 짤라 wait <br>]]></content><category term="DZ" label="DZ"/><category term="Ninja Blade (Feat. Kigga)" label="Ninja Blade (Feat. Kigga)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dbo_디보/Battery_Feat_Kigga_DZ/</id><title>Dbo (디보) - Battery (Feat. Kigga, DZ) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:21:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:21:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dbo_%EB%94%94%EB%B3%B4/Battery_Feat_Kigga_DZ/" title="Dbo (디보) - Battery (Feat. Kigga, DZ) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I need a battery <br>I need a battery <br>I need a battery <br>bitch come bettle me <br>better better better me <br>better better better me <br>better better better me <br>pedal to the metal what's the matter <br>better better better me <br>better better better me <br>better better better me <br>pedal to the metal what's the matter <br>young Dbo Dregon Ball balling <br>용용 죽겠 검은 봉지 <br>나 범죄심리학 학교 <br>풀어 버려 참을성 달력에 <br>적어놔 그날까진 <br>안 나가 안 나가 안나 일기 <br>I did it whatever 말해도 <br>계속 말해 보라고 기말고사 <br>man I got it 우 아이 <br>man 아싸리 야이 <br>내가 악당이라니 <br>놈들을 유인 <br>풍선 불고 펑 무선 연결 구름 <br>풀어지는 주름 내가 계속 할 줄은 <br>몰랐어 심부름 전해줘 날 부를 <br>꺼야 누구는 주륵 주륵 쭉 울음 <br>우리는 유리들 깨질 수 있어요 <br>조심하슈 금이가유 <br>매일 한숨 흙 한줌 <br>남들과 섞일 수가 없다고 <br>중요해 둘 다 기름과 물 <br>I need a battery <br>I need a battery <br>I need a battery <br>bitch come bettle me <br>better better better me <br>better better better me <br>better better better me <br>pedal to the metal what's the matter <br>better better better me <br>better better better me <br>better better better me <br>pedal to the metal what's the matter <br>우린 움직여 두 배로 <br>이젠 시간이 아까워 <br>즐길 수 있으니 살어 <br>불 붙여 메마른 장작 <br>다 태우고 높이 올라 <br>우린 연기로 예술을 승화 <br>fuck peace and love <br>we been killin all nite <br>시작은 yonge and finch <br>주차장에서 봐 <br>쉬지 않고 달려도 <br>결관 보이지가 않아 <br>I need dat shit <br>움직이게 하는 건 바로 너야 <br>shout out to all of ma <br>homies and bitches <br>돌아보지 않고 난 직진 <br>숨돌릴 시간에 <br>한 줄 더 쓰고 나와 <br>나갈 때야 충전해 배터리 <br>정글 같은 이 도시 생각을 해 <br>계속 지켜나가는 초심 <br>fpl shit <br>필요 없어 가짜 친구 <br>형제들과 올라가 더 <br>맑은 공기 호흡해 <br>우주 안에서 우린 수영 <br>I need a battery <br>I need a battery <br>I need a battery <br>bitch come bettle me <br>better better better me <br>better better better me <br>better better better me <br>pedal to the metal what's the matter <br>better better better me <br>better better better me <br>better better better me <br>pedal to the metal what's the matter <br>hey charge ma phone <br>날이 밝어 <br>날씨는 맑어 두 다리 갖고 <br>난 다시 달려 <br>charge me charge me <br>다시 작업 내 방은 <br>차가워 마치 창고 <br>쌓이고 쌓여가 <br>작곡한 곡들 밤이 바껴 <br>시간이 아까워 멈추지 못해 <br>난 나를 단련 <br>내 엄마와 아빠가 나를 아꼈듯이 <br>창작한 세계는 내가 가꿔 <br>난 꽃에 물 줘 곧 시들어도 <br>다시 펴 다시 펴 사랑을 줘 <br>cuz I'm bout to fuck it <br>and puff it and munch mmmeow <br>초록색 muffin을 먹지 <br>솟아나 호랑이 힘이 <br>콘푸러스트는 내게 미미 <br>난 밥 대신 빵 먹어 <br>밥 대신 빵 대신 빵 대식가 <br>난 나쁜 놈 아냐 <br>넌 빵 대신 가 나의 형제들 <br>절대로 배신 안 함 <br>난 pop pop pop like this <br>and bang bang bang like this <br>넌 떨어질 수 있어 조심해 <br>해가 뜰 때면 난 욕심 내 <br>I need a battery <br>u got that amazing power <br>i need ur energy <br>충전해줘 green power <br>여자들은 먼저 샤워 <br>땀 흘리고 마셔 <br>난 gatorade 또 아침이 밝어 <br>]]></content><category term="Dbo (디보)" label="Dbo (디보)"/><category term="Battery (Feat. Kigga, DZ)" label="Battery (Feat. Kigga, DZ)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kigga/Elevated_Feat_Dbo/</id><title>Kigga - Elevated (Feat. Dbo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:22:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:22:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kigga/Elevated_Feat_Dbo/" title="Kigga - Elevated (Feat. Dbo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[from the bottom to the top <br>yeah we elevated <br>chillin with them OGs <br>가짠 can't relate <br>fuck dat 빽차 <br>yeah we still thuggin <br>fuck peace <br>and love we fuckin elevated <br>우린 위로 위로 더 높이 위로 <br>keep it canada finch 때부터 <br>keep hustle <br>실력 없이 나대는 놈들 <br>머리엔 비석 <br>still representin T dot city <br>motherfucker <br>been hustlin and grindin <br>시작은 주차장 길바닥 <br>3년이 지났어도 꾸준히 <br>내 형제들과 난 올라가 <br>항상 많은걸 원하기 때문에 <br>쉬지 못하지 <br>all I gotta do is <br>keep doin ma shit <br>큰불을 지피지 나지막이 <br>hustle for ma block <br>yeah we been killin all nite <br>불을 지피지 mofucker <br>we been killin all nite <br>그냥 하고 나서 <br>딴청 피우면 돼 한대나 <br>높은 곳이야 <br>신호 잘 잡히지 안테나 <br>시작부터 길바닥은 <br>FPL 우리 무대지 <br>다 들어와 책임 안 져 <br>뺑소니 대신 싸대기 <br>savage mode mofucker <br>말한대로 이뤄져 <br>그것을 믿고 따러 <br>fuck boys 허리 굽혀 한잔 따러 <br>from the bottom to the top <br>yeah we elevated <br>chillin with them OGs <br>가짠 can't relate <br>fuck dat 빽차 <br>yeah we still thuggin <br>fuck peace <br>and love we fuckin elevated <br>from the bottom to the top <br>yeah we elevated <br>chillin with them OGs <br>가짠 can't relate <br>fuck dat 빽차 <br>yeah we still thuggin <br>fuck peace <br>and love we fuckin elevated <br>아가 젖 더 먹고 와 <br>반가워 내 고추야 <br>만약 니가 왕자지 <br>엄마야 나는 공주야 <br>박지성처럼 주장 <br>봤지 반복되는 일상 <br>다 그렇게 돈 벌 때 <br>난 좆돼 안 그래 <br>나는 계산기 두드려 <br>죽은 친구들 묵념 <br>너도 봤어 잠깐 유명 <br>해졌다가 다시 유료 <br>겸손해서 미안 <br>보지에서 헤엄쳐 <br>헤어나올 수 없어 <br>나는 그 안에서 익사해 <br>영원해 영광의 흉터 풀어야 한 썰 <br>그녀는 옷 벗어 다 나와 함께 춤춰 <br>난 계속 밝혀 출처 <br>그들을 존중했어 <br>그리고 이게 지구본 <br>내가 손에서 돌려 <br>you know we're crazy <br>no feature 전 용기 <br>까먹지 아버지 나머지는 나머지 <br>now you know that I ain’t shit yet <br>사랑해 애기 <br>나 시간을 다 죽여 <br>너 어디서 왔어 우린 <br>from the bottom to the top <br>yeah we elevated <br>chillin with them OGs <br>가짠 can't relate <br>fuck dat 빽차 <br>yeah we still thuggin <br>fuck peace <br>and love we fuckin elevated <br>from the bottom to the top <br>yeah we elevated <br>chillin with them OGs <br>가짠 can't relate <br>fuck dat 빽차 <br>yeah we still thuggin <br>fuck peace <br>and love we fuckin elevated <br>]]></content><category term="Kigga" label="Kigga"/><category term="Elevated (Feat. Dbo)" label="Elevated (Feat. Dbo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승호/이미_지나가버린/</id><title>강승호 - 이미 지나가버린 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:22:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:22:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%ED%98%B8/%EC%9D%B4%EB%AF%B8_%EC%A7%80%EB%82%98%EA%B0%80%EB%B2%84%EB%A6%B0/" title="강승호 - 이미 지나가버린 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너무나 빨리 찾아온 날들 <br>하지만 아직 준비가 안된 나는 <br>기다려 주지 않던 날들 <br>귀담아 듣지 않던 나는 <br>이미 지나가버린 날에 <br>나 홀로 남아 <br>주워 담지 못하는 날을 바라봐 <br>이미 후회가 되어버린 나의 말들 <br>이젠 함께 하자는 말도 난 못해 <br>너무나 작게 들려온 말들 <br>하지만 아직 준비가 안된 나는 <br>기다려 주지 않던 날들 <br>귀담아 듣지 않던 나는 <br>이미 지나가버린 날에 <br>나 홀로 남아 <br>주워 담지 못하는 날을 바라봐 <br>이미 후회가 되어버린 나의 말들 <br>이젠 함께 하자는 말도 난 못해 <br>이미 지나가버린 날에 <br>나 홀로 남아 <br>주워 담지 못하는 날을 바라봐 <br>이미 후회가 되어버린 나의 말들 <br>이젠 함께 하자는 말도 난 못해 <br>]]></content><category term="강승호" label="강승호"/><category term="이미 지나가버린" label="이미 지나가버린"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승호/바다_Vocal_문형태/</id><title>강승호 - 바다 (Vocal. 문형태) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:22:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:22:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%ED%98%B8/%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%A4_Vocal_%EB%AC%B8%ED%98%95%ED%83%9C/" title="강승호 - 바다 (Vocal. 문형태) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넓고 넓은 바다 바라보면서 <br>모래사장 위에 앉아있었지 <br>높고 높은 구름 바라보면서 <br>모래사장 위에 앉아있었지 <br>바람을 타고 나는 <br>갈매기들아 <br>저기 저 바다 넘어 <br>뭐가 보이니 <br>넓고 넓은 바다 바라보면서 <br>모래사장 위에 앉아있었지 <br>높고 높은 구름 바라보면서 <br>모래사장 위에 앉아있었지 <br>바람을 타고 가는 <br>돛단배들아 <br>저기 저 바다 넘어 <br>너는 가봤니 <br>바람을 타고 나는 <br>갈매기들아 <br>저기 저 바다 넘어 <br>뭐가 보이니 <br>알려줘 알려줘 <br>알려줘 알려줘 <br>알려줘 <br>]]></content><category term="강승호" label="강승호"/><category term="바다 (Vocal. 문형태)" label="바다 (Vocal. 문형태)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Coco/omsl/</id><title>Coco - omsl - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:24:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:24:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Coco/omsl/" title="Coco - omsl - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[oh body very nice hot 해 <br>뒷목 to 엉덩이 i like that <br>white skin i said god damn <br>let’s Champagne and pop that <br>너 밖에 안보여 이 공간 <br>추월하자 우리 시공간 <br>내 팔베게 하고 좀 쉬고가 <br>그냥 가지말고 담배라도 피고가 <br>oh shit 역시는 역시 <br>골반은 수입산 <br>쟤들은 다 ugly fuck <br>의문의 1패를 남겨주고서 <br>은근슬쩍 팔을 감아 <br>니 허리를 건드리면 <br>뺨싸대기 혹은 잘되기 <br>너의 방뎅이 찰싹 때려주면 <br>울림이 like 카네기 홀 <br>너랑 늘어지고 퍼지고 싶어 <br>oh baby give me some <br>honey your waist of wave <br>난 그 위에 surfing <br>and let’s get down oh shit <br>그 아래선 twerk dance <br>every day every day <br>honey your waist of wave <br>난 그 위에 surfing <br>and let’s get down oh shit <br>그 아래선 fuck that <br>every day every day <br>ok 널 이대로 보내버리면 <br>후회할것 같어 <br>일단 번호 불러 줘봐 <br>보내게 카톡 <br>아 참 모를수도 있을테니 <br>WhatsApp 으로도 보낼께 <br>너는 외국인 cause that <br>서투른 한국말에 <br>어눌한 말투 sexy plus 귀염 <br>그게 중요한건 아니구 <br>일단 둘이 밖에 나가서 <br>얘기 plus beer <br>한잔해 둘이 밤세게 <br>빡세게 놀았나 그러다 자겠네 <br>자 내게 기대 괜찮네 bae <br>나쁜애는 아냐 우린 그냥 다 큰애 <br>난 그냥 단순하고 화끈해 <br>말이 안 통하면 어때 <br>너와 내가 필요한건 그저 <br>body language <br>이 뒤에 story 는 너의 선택 <br>go girl go play <br>we just gon be that way <br>go girl go straight <br>we just gon be that way <br>go girl no way <br>we just gon be that way <br>go girl go get it <br>we just gon be that way <br>honey your waist of wave <br>난 그 위에 surfing <br>and let’s get down oh shit <br>그 아래선 twerk dance <br>every day every day <br>honey your waist of wave <br>난 그 위에 surfing <br>and let’s get down oh shit <br>그 아래선 fuck that <br>every day every day <br>]]></content><category term="Coco" label="Coco"/><category term="omsl" label="omsl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Bus_Song/</id><title>The Kooks - Bus Song - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:24:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:24:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Bus_Song/" title="The Kooks - Bus Song - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do do do <br><br>You know today I stayed on the bus <br>Oh yeah I waited and waited until I was at your stop <br>The driver said to me just don't make a fuss <br>And I said in the end you've taken all my money, my friend <br><br>But ow ow, yes you love it as I take you on when you down <br>And ow ow, something happened and now I can't sing along <br>And ow ow, yes you hate it as I try to get under your skin <br>And ow ow, something happened and now you can't sing along <br><br>Do do do <br><br>But you know today I stayed on the train <br>Oh yes I waited and waited until I could not refrain <br>The driver said to me just don't make a fuss like you did on the bus <br>In the end you've taken all my money, you're not my friend <br><br>But ow ow, yes you love it as you take me on when I'm down <br>And ow ow, something happened and now I can't sing along <br>And ow ow, yes you love it as you try to get under my skin <br>And ow ow]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Bus Song" label="Bus Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Be_Mine_Demo/</id><title>The Kooks - Be Mine (Demo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:24:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:24:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Be_Mine_Demo/" title="The Kooks - Be Mine (Demo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I never thought we'd come this far <br>But then how we come that far <br>And I won't let them in <br>Cause she's my lover and not my friend <br><br>I'm so scared to lose you now <br>So easy to lose you now <br>Because there calling at my door <br>So I'm locking up my door <br><br>Now my thoughts are very dark <br>And my dreams are always dark <br>Don't let them take me away <br>Cause I want me to stay <br><br>But be mine, oh <br>Won't you be mine, oh <br>Be mine, oh oh <br><br>Take it all outside <br>Cause you don't need it <br>Don't need to cry, oh no <br>Take it all outside <br>Cause you don't need me <br>Don't need to cry <br><br>I never thought we'd come this far <br>But then how we come that far <br>And I won't let them in <br>Cause she's my lover and not my friend <br><br>I'm so scared to lose it now <br>Oh it's so easy to lose it now <br>Because they're calling at my door <br>So I'm locking up my door <br><br>Oh be mine, oh <br>Won't you be mine, oh <br>Be mine <br>Be mine <br><br>Take it all outside <br>Cause you don't need it <br>Don't need to cry, oh no <br>Take it all outside <br>Cause you don't need me <br>Don't need to cry, yeah <br><br>So be mine, oh oh <br>Be mine, oh <br>Be mine]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Be Mine (Demo)" label="Be Mine (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/If_Only_Demo/</id><title>The Kooks - If Only (Demo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:24:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:24:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/If_Only_Demo/" title="The Kooks - If Only (Demo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So hold your head and hold your tongue <br>But only say what you have to <br>And as a child, yes, I dreamed <br>Of holding her in the silver screen <br>She loved her man but loved him twice <br>I wish I'd been that passenger <br>Having fun, fly my kite <br>The devil inside won't control my life <br>And too much love, so little hate <br>The devil inside won't control my fate <br><br>Oh, if only, if only <br>Oh, he wasn't so lonely <br>He'd have someone to play with <br>Instead of bombing our neighbours, yeah, yeah <br><br>So here I go to see the world <br>With my eyes and with my soul <br>And too much love, so little hate <br>The devil inside won't control my fate <br><br>Oh, if only, if only <br>Oh, he wasn't so lonely <br>He'd have someone to play with <br>Instead of bombing our neighbours, yeah, yeah, yeah <br><br>So hold your head and run my time <br>The what of life no man can rhyme <br>So here we are and here we bleed <br>To be a victim, there's no need <br>Having fun, I never fight <br>The devil inside controls my life <br>Too much love so little hate <br>The devil inside will control my fate <br><br>Oh, if only, if only <br>Oh, he wasn't so lonely <br>He'd have someone to play with <br>Instead of bombing our neighbours <br>Oh, if only, if only <br>Oh, he wasn't so lonely <br>He'd have someone to play with <br>Instead of bombing our neighbours]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="If Only (Demo)" label="If Only (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Always_Where_I_Need_To_Be_Demo/</id><title>The Kooks - Always Where I Need To Be (Demo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:24:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:24:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Always_Where_I_Need_To_Be_Demo/" title="The Kooks - Always Where I Need To Be (Demo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She don't know who she is <br>I can take her anywhere <br>Do whatever comes naturally to you <br>You know she just don't care <br>You know she just don't care <br><br>'Cause I'm always where I need to be <br>Yeah, and I always thought I would end up <br>With you, eventually <br>Do dodo do do do do <br>Do dodo do do do do <br>Do dodo do do <br><br>Now I see her again <br>I ask to be her hummingbird <br>Whisper words in her ear <br>Oh now you know I just don't care <br><br>'Cause I'm always where I <br>Where I need to be <br>And I always thought <br>I would end up with you eventually <br>Do dodo do do do do <br>Do dodo do do do do <br>Do dodo do do <br><br>I'm a man, I'm a man I'm a man on the scene <br>I'm a man, and I can be so obscene <br>Because I always think that I know how to be <br>But I always thought that I would end up with you, eventually <br>Do dodo do do do do <br>Do dodo do do do do <br>Do dodo do do <br>I'm a man, I'm a man I'm a man on the scene <br>I'm a man, and I can be so obscene]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Always Where I Need To Be (Demo)" label="Always Where I Need To Be (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Gap_Demo/</id><title>The Kooks - Gap (Demo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:24:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:24:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Gap_Demo/" title="The Kooks - Gap (Demo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So put a spanner in the works <br>Of your mind <br>It's easier to work <br>But I don't mind <br>You're bitter in defeat so <br>Just don't try <br>To take away all the things <br>I'll do in my life <br><br>I have to break down all <br>the corners of the world <br>Don't heap this praise on me <br>I know I don't deserve it <br>But what's all this I see <br>Yeah you're leaving right beside me <br>And I miss you, and I need you <br>I do <br><br>But don't go, take my love <br>I won't let you, I'm saying please don't go <br>Don't go, take my love <br>I won't let you, I'm saying please don't go <br><br>Well leave your lover now <br>it's your turn <br>And see your mother now <br>I hope she's okay <br>You're bitter in defeat so <br>let's not try <br>To take away all the things we'll do in our lives <br><br>I have to break down all the corners of the world <br>Don't heap this praise on me <br>I know I don't deserve it <br>But what's all this I see <br>Yeah you're leaving right beside me <br>And I miss you, and I need you <br>I do <br><br>But don't go, take my love <br>I won't let you, I'm saying please don't go <br>Don't go, take my love <br>I won't let you, I'm saying please don't go <br><br>All of my life <br>trying to understand <br>All of my life <br>trying to hold a hand <br><br>I have to break down all <br>the corners of this world <br>Don't heap this praise on me <br>I know I don't deserve it <br>But what's all this I see <br>Yeah you're leaving right beside me <br>And I miss you, and I love you <br>That's true]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Gap (Demo)" label="Gap (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Lonely_Cat_Demo/</id><title>The Kooks - Lonely Cat (Demo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:24:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:24:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Lonely_Cat_Demo/" title="The Kooks - Lonely Cat (Demo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Life is simple if you've got faith, oh yeah <br>You don't have to choose <br>But I don't got none today <br>Life was easy yester year oh yeah <br>I didn't have to move <br>But I never even got to know you <br>So baby carry on in charge <br>Because I'm a full grown lonely cat <br>In the world <br>Without you beating by my side <br><br>Out of the dark get your uncorrupted air <br>And into the light you you need not prepare <br>Because I know you'll keep on travelling <br>Till you make your way back home <br>I'll try to take care of your home <br><br>Patch my life up with cellotape <br>It doesn't feel so safe <br>But all the same I don't have to choose <br>How sad baby is that <br>Yeah I'm a full grown lonely cat <br>In the world <br>Without you beating by my side <br><br>And out of the dark get you uncorrupted air <br>And into the light you, you need not prepare <br>Because I know you'll keep on travelling <br>Till you find your way back home <br>I'll try to take care of your home]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Lonely Cat (Demo)" label="Lonely Cat (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Creatures_Of_Habit/</id><title>The Kooks - Creatures Of Habit - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Creatures_Of_Habit/" title="The Kooks - Creatures Of Habit - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well I've been up all night I'm feelin' lonely <br>Twistin' the truth to be honest <br>I'm playing games with you <br>You made it easy when you gave me anything without a question <br>Woa oh <br>And I'm a creature of habit <br><br>So please don't stop the wheels <br>Shit is gettin' real <br>Real, baby <br><br>Every time I try to tell you <br>You turn the whole thing brown <br>And every time I try to tell you <br>You turn the whole thing brown <br><br>So don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it down <br>But don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it down <br>So don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it down <br><br>Get all the lights on top at such a petty celebration <br>Woa oh <br>We're all creatures of habit <br>And as the train crashes in the East and West celebrates peace <br>Woa oh <br>We call station to station <br><br>So please don't stop the wheels <br>This shit is gettin' real <br>Real, baby <br><br>Every time I try to tell you <br>You turn the whole thing brown <br>And every time I try to tell you <br>You turn the whole thing brown <br><br>So don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it down <br>Don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it down <br><br>Please, please don't let me down <br>Please, please just don't let me down <br>'Cause I'm a creature <br>don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it down <br>And I've been lonely, lonely, lonely low <br>Just a creature <br>don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it down <br>And I've been lonely, lonely, lonely low <br>don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it down <br>Lonely, lonely, lonely low <br><br>don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it, don't let it down <br>And every time I try to tell you <br>You turn the whole thing brown <br>And every time I try to tell you <br>You turn the whole thing brown <br>Every time I try to tell you <br>You turn the whole thing brown <br>And every time I try to tell you <br>You say, you say]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Creatures Of Habit" label="Creatures Of Habit"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Shine_On_Demo/</id><title>The Kooks - Shine On (Demo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Shine_On_Demo/" title="The Kooks - Shine On (Demo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Safety pins holding up the things <br>That make you mine <br>About your hair, you needn't care <br>You look beautiful all the time <br><br>Shine, shine, shine on <br>Yes, won't you shine, shine on <br><br>Your magazines rip people at the seams <br>But you still read <br>I must admit, I don't believe in it <br>But I see how you get sucked in <br><br>Shine, shine, shine on <br>Yes, won't you shine, shine on Sha la la la <br>Shine, shine, shine on <br>Yes, won't you shine, shine on <br><br>Because you're not done <br>Why do you bite the hand that feeds you <br>Why do you <br>Why do you bite the hand that feeds Yeah <br><br>Shine, shine, shine on <br>Yes, won't you shine, shine on Sha la la la <br>Shine, shine, shine on <br>Yes, won't you shine, shine on <br><br>Safety pins holding up the things <br>That make you mine <br>About your hair, you needn't care <br>You look beautiful all the time]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Shine On (Demo)" label="Shine On (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/The_Saboteur_Demo/</id><title>The Kooks - The Saboteur (Demo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/The_Saboteur_Demo/" title="The Kooks - The Saboteur (Demo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I am the saboteur and I'll let you into my world <br>Sometimes it's hard to live and sometimes it's hard to love you <br>I keep pushing you away, doing things so you won't stay with me <br>Wouldn't it be cool, if I could let it go <br>All of the things that I never seem to control <br>I am the saboteur and I'm fighting inside my mind <br>The harder I ignore is the more it crashes down <br>I see you by, you push me babe, see if I fade away in time <br>Wouldn't it be cool, if I could let it go <br>All of the things that I never seem to control <br>I am the saboteur and I'll let you into my world <br>I'm love in here but I'll let you know <br>Well I'm the big means anymore, anymore as I stand tall <br>Wouldn't it be cool, if i could let it go <br>Wouldn't it be cool, if i could let it all go <br>Wouldn't it be cool, if i could let it go <br>Wouldn't it be cool, if i could just let it all go]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="The Saboteur (Demo)" label="The Saboteur (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Suburbs_Demo/</id><title>The Kooks - Suburbs (Demo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Suburbs_Demo/" title="The Kooks - Suburbs (Demo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can only write what, comes into my head <br>So many things to think of, I'll think of you instead <br>So bring those blocks down my, lover to be <br>Don't be yourself tonight, just, be with me <br><br>You're a celebrated person, yeah I know <br>Doesn't mean you always have to, bring a show <br>So take those rocks off our, Majesty <br>You're no different to us, just, where you'll be <br><br>Yes I wish that we never made it, through all the summers <br>We kept them up instead of kicking us back <br>Down to the suburbs <br>Yes I wish that we never made it, through all the summers <br>We kept them up instead of kicking us back <br>Down, to the suburbs <br><br>It's not so easy as that, but you don't see <br>Like it's also hard on the other side, where I've been <br>Big houses and all of your cash, it don't make me happy <br>I've got my problems too, yeah just like you <br><br>Yes I wish that we never made it, through all the summers <br>We kept them up instead of kicking us back <br>Down to the suburbs <br>Yes I wish that we never made it, through all the summers <br>We kept them up instead of kicking us back <br>Down, to the suburbs <br>To the suburbs to the suburbs]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Suburbs (Demo)" label="Suburbs (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Naive_Alternate_Ver/</id><title>The Kooks - Naive (Alternate Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Naive_Alternate_Ver/" title="The Kooks - Naive (Alternate Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not saying it was your fault <br>Although you could have done more <br>Oh you're so naive yet so <br>How could this been done <br>By such a smiling sweetheart <br>Oh, and your sweet and pretty face <br>In such an ugly world <br>For something so beautiful <br>Oh, that every time I look inside <br><br>I know, she knows that I'm not fond of asking <br>True or false, it may be Well, she's still out to get me <br>And I know, she knows that I'm not fond of asking <br>True or false, it may be She's still out to get me <br><br>I may say it was your fault <br>Because I know you could have done more <br>Oh, you're so naive yet so <br>How could this be done <br>By such a smiling sweetheart <br>Oh, and your sweet and pretty face <br>In such an ugly word <br>For something so beautiful <br>That every time I look inside <br><br>I know, she knows that I'm not fond of asking <br>True or false, it may be Well, she's still out to get me <br>And I know, she knows that I'm not fond of asking <br>True or false, it may be She's still out to get me <br><br>So how could this be done <br>By such a smiling sweetheart <br>You're so naive yet so <br>You're such an ugly thing <br>For someone so beautiful <br>That every time you're on his side <br><br>I know, she knows that I'm not fond of asking <br>True or false, it may be Well, she's still out to get me <br>And I know, she knows that I'm not fond of asking <br>True or false, it may be She's still out to get me <br><br>Just don't let me down <br>Just don't let me down <br>Hold on to your kite <br>Just don't let me down <br>Just don't let me down <br>Hold on to your kite <br>Just don't let me down <br>Just don't let me down <br>Hold on to this kite <br>Just don't let me down]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Naive (Alternate Ver.)" label="Naive (Alternate Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Slave_To_The_Game/</id><title>The Kooks - Slave To The Game - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Slave_To_The_Game/" title="The Kooks - Slave To The Game - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Slave to the game of insecurity <br>I'm the first one to go his way <br>So she as her <br>From me because she's my honey bee <br>And know one knows I've been here before <br>In this room, the very same dance floor <br>Oh I've walked this floor <br><br>And it gets so hard for me to change you <br>Yeah it gets so hard if I change all those things that I do <br><br>Same as before <br>Different now it's a chore <br>Don't play a game you'll see that <br>You'll leave me wanting more oh oh oh <br>Same as before <br>Different now it's a chore <br>Well play a game you'll see <br>You'll leave me wanting more oh oh oh <br><br>Slave to the game of this insecurity <br>A game that's always out to get me <br>So be here when I get home <br>Oh to me it's always been the same <br>You've been a naughty girl going out again <br>Oh in the dark again <br><br>But it gets so hard for me to change you <br>Yeah it gets so hard if I change all those things that I do <br><br>Same as before <br>Different now it's a chore <br>Don't play a game you'll see <br>You'll leave me wanting more oh oh oh <br>Same as before <br>Different now it's a chore <br>Play a game you'll see that]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Slave To The Game" label="Slave To The Game"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/California/</id><title>The Kooks - California - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/California/" title="The Kooks - California - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't you know baby I'm a leading man <br>I dig down deep when I say I love you <br>Well I can hold my own with the best of them <br>I guarantee you, you never seen nothin' <br>Nothin' like this again <br><br>California say that you love me <br>From all the darkness I couldn't break through <br>Now, I miss the oceans when I go to sleep <br>Oh man, it's gonna break your heart <br><br>Don't you know that I'll do the things I could <br>I rubbed your back when you were sleeping <br>But all along baby it was understood <br>That you were leaving, absolutely <br>The very first day we met <br><br>California say that you love me <br>From all the darkness I couldn't break through <br>I'm gonna miss you <br>I'm gonna miss you <br>I'm gonna miss you <br><br>I'm gonna miss ya <br>I'm gonna miss you <br>I'm gonna miss ya <br>I'm gonna miss you]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="California" label="California"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Pull_Me_In/</id><title>The Kooks - Pull Me In - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Pull_Me_In/" title="The Kooks - Pull Me In - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I get this feeling sometimes <br>Like there's nothing in the world that isn't mine <br>And I could have it all <br>Maybe I should have it all <br><br>I'll take you out of your life <br>Just the one sweet night <br>And you could take it all <br>Oh maybe I could rip it off <br><br>It's easy to pick and choose <br>With you and me we can only lose <br>Just don't fight me off <br>And I won't write you off <br><br>Take me in and then you push me out <br>Fall all over yourself tonight <br>And just don't let it go, without a fight <br>Take me in and then you push me out <br>Fall all over yourself tonight <br>And just don't let it go, let it go <br><br>So here I am again <br>Singing songs about the summer <br>Cause that's when you and me <br>When we came to be <br><br>I brought you home to my guitar <br>And told you how sweet you really are <br>Cause you know what's on my mind <br>Is you getting all this time <br><br>It's easy to pick and choose <br>With you and me we can only lose <br>Just don't find me out <br>And I won't fight you off <br><br>Take me in and then you push me out <br>Fall all over yourself tonight <br>And just don't let it go, let it go <br><br>Oh no no, another girl, no no <br>Don't fight me off little girl]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Pull Me In" label="Pull Me In"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Sofa_Song_Demo/</id><title>The Kooks - Sofa Song (Demo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Sofa_Song_Demo/" title="The Kooks - Sofa Song (Demo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The city freeze before <br>I just realised I don't like you <br>Me and my girl <br>Are going out for some air <br>And I will do my best <br>Just to get under her dress <br>And catch you out if I can <br>On the other side of my sofa <br><br>Won't you come on over <br>At the side of my sofa <br>Oh won't you come on over <br><br>The city heated it up <br>It got blurry cause I'd had enough <br>And he tried to take your soul <br>But didn't realise you keep it in a different hole <br><br>Won't you come on over <br>At the side of my sofa <br>Oh won't you come on over <br><br>So here he comes, a man with <br>A loaded gun, I don't know if he <br>Wants my soul or my <br>Cash flow, I s'pose I don't know <br><br>So here he comes, a man with a <br>A loaded gun I don't know if he <br>Wants my girl's heart or her pearls <br>I s'pose I don't know <br>I s'pose I don't know <br>I s'pose I don't know <br>I s'pose I don't know <br>I s'pose I don't know]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Sofa Song (Demo)" label="Sofa Song (Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Eddies_Gun_2005_Ver/</id><title>The Kooks - Eddie`s Gun (2005 Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Eddies_Gun_2005_Ver/" title="The Kooks - Eddie`s Gun (2005 Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Did you see the way she looks at me <br>A honeybee got two lives and she's got me <br><br>I tried to love her back <br>And then I shrunk back into my wrap <br>And in the barrel of my gun <br>I hope I'm not the only one <br><br>Did you see the way she looks at me <br>She's got an eye for an awkward guy like me <br><br>I tried to love her back she's just a girl <br>And then I shrunk back into my wrap she's just a girl <br>And in the barrel of my gun <br>I hope I'm not the only one <br>And in the barrel of my gun <br>I hope I'm not the only one <br><br>Do do, do do do <br><br>I tried to love her back she's just a girl <br>And then I shrunk back into my wrap she's just a girl <br>And in the barrel of my gun <br>I hope I'm not the only one <br>And in the barrel of my gun <br>I hope I'm not the only one]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Eddie`s Gun (2005 Ver.)" label="Eddie`s Gun (2005 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Broken_Vow/</id><title>The Kooks - Broken Vow - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Broken_Vow/" title="The Kooks - Broken Vow - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I saw you in church on Sunday <br>I was walking by on my way to Monday <br>Cracked lips and a sad vogue <br>Something tune life that you just can't hear <br><br>Dry fuel but it hurts too much <br>Do you like it, when life gets rough <br>You always washing your hands in myth <br>Don't you know you can't get clean <br><br>I didn't know, didn't know <br>What I was running to <br>Didn't know, didn't know <br>What I was running to <br>I didn't know, didn't know <br>What I was running to <br>Didn't know, didn't know <br>What I was running to <br>Didn't know what I was running to <br><br>Oh girl don't stop now <br>Walking through the city like a holy cow <br>Oh girl don't stop now <br>Only way to heaven is a broken vow <br><br>Are you speaking in tongues <br>Yeah, I'll take sin <br>Your abstinence <br>Is such a loaded gun <br>Your stained glass and a holy ghost <br>I shall not take what I want the most <br><br>I didn't know, didn't know <br>What I was running to <br>Didn't know, didn't know <br>What I was running to <br>I didn't know, didn't know <br>What I was running to <br>Didn't know, didn't know <br>What I was running to <br>Didn't know what I was running to <br><br>Oh girl don't stop now <br>Walking through the city like a holy cow <br>Oh girl don't stop now <br>Only way to heaven is a broken vow <br><br>Oh girl don't stop now <br>Walking through the city like a holy cow <br>Oh girl don't stop now <br>Only way to heaven is a broken vow <br>Only way to heaven is a broken vow <br><br>Hide me in mirrors <br>I'm happy when all I have to do is just pretend <br>Then I'm feeling like time moves slow <br>And I lay and lift the fruit hang low <br>Low, low, low, let the fruit hang low <br><br>Oh girl don't stop now <br>Walking through the city like a holy cow <br>Oh girl don't stop now <br>The only way to heaven is a broken vow <br>Oh girl don't stop now <br>Walking through the city like a holy cow <br>Oh girl don't stop now <br>The only way to heaven is a broken vow <br>The only way to heaven is a broken vow <br>Oh girl don't stop now <br>Walking through the city like a holy cow <br>Oh girl don't stop now <br>The only way to heaven is a broken vow <br>Oh girl don't stop now <br>Walking through the city like a holy cow <br>Oh girl don't stop now <br>The only way to heaven is a broken vow <br>The only way to heaven is a broken vow]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Broken Vow" label="Broken Vow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Be_Who_You_Are/</id><title>The Kooks - Be Who You Are - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Be_Who_You_Are/" title="The Kooks - Be Who You Are - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[But you don't know who you are <br>The road's gonna take and make you walk too far <br>You are a liar, you are a thief, you are a star <br>But you don't know who you are <br><br>You are just a kid with a sentimental heart <br>Afraid of what would've happened before you were the star <br>And you don't need the baggage, and you don't need the stuff <br>And you don't need nobody to fill your empty cup <br><br>Ta ta, ta ta, ta ra ra ra <br>Ta ta, ta ra ra ra <br>Be who you are <br>Ta ta, ta ta, ta ra ra ra <br>Baby you're a star <br>Ta ta, ta ra ra ra <br><br>Never give up, caught a train <br>Never be a slave to your own name <br>You are a poet, you are a fake, you are a star <br>But you don't know who you are <br><br>We could shine a light, here inside the dark <br>And get a little closer to <br>And there's nothing left to win, and you can only lose <br>What's keeping you from doing what you always wanna do <br><br>Ta ta, ta ta, ta ra ra ra <br>Be who you are <br>Ta ta, ta ra ra ra <br>Be who you are <br>Ta ta, ta ta, ta ra ra ra <br>Baby you're a star <br>Ta ta, ta ra ra ra <br>Be who you are <br><br>Lately I've been feeling <br>Like the stars were rolling out for me <br>Stars were rolling out <br>Lately I've been feeling <br>But the stars were rolling out for me <br>Stars were rolling out <br>But maybe they're misleading <br>Is it just a light reflecting off the street <br><br>You are just a kid with a sentimental heart <br>And do it for yourself, and do it for the art <br>But you don't need the baggage, you don't need the stuff <br>You don't need nobody to fill your empty cup <br><br>Ta ta, ta ta, ta ra ra ra <br>Be who you are <br>Ta ta, ta ra ra ra <br>Be, be who you are <br>Ta ta, ta ta, ta ra ra ra <br>Be who you are <br>Ta ta, ta ra ra ra <br>Baby you're a star <br>Ta ta, ta ta, ta ra ra ra <br>Be who you are <br>Ta ta, ta ra ra ra <br>Be who you are <br>Ta ta, ta ta, ta ra ra ra <br>Baby you're a star <br>Ta ta, ta ra ra ra]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Be Who You Are" label="Be Who You Are"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Matchbox/</id><title>The Kooks - Matchbox - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Matchbox/" title="The Kooks - Matchbox - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Graciously, she sleeps <br>Walks alone on a lonely beat <br>She trips, falls into it all <br>And I wish I bite my lip and call her away <br>From you my little one <br>You my little one <br><br>Don't come too close <br>You don't wanna see my ghost <br>Your turn but I'm betrayed <br>By you my sweetheart <br>Don't you think that you went too far <br>Do you want to see my heart bleed <br>For you, you and him <br>Him and you you know my heart bleeds <br><br>All of us <br>We're going out tonight <br>We're gonna walk all over your cars <br>The kooks are out <br>In the streets <br>Oh we're gonna steal steal your skies <br>All of us <br>We're going out tonight <br>We're gonna walk all over your cars <br>The kooks are out <br>In the streets <br>Oh we're gonna steal your <br><br>I'm sorry <br>That I let you go <br>I let you down, I let you down my dear <br><br>I always seem to play these games with you my dear <br>I always, I always <br><br>All of us <br>We're going out tonight <br>We're gonna walk all over your cars <br>The kooks are out <br>In the streets <br>Oh we're gonna steal steal your skies <br>All of us <br>We're going out tonight <br>We're gonna walk all over your cars <br>The kooks are out <br>In the streets <br>Oh we're gonna steal steal your skies <br>Oh my Juliet, I'll never betray you my love <br>Oh my Juliet, I'll never I'll never betray you <br><br>Woah woaaaaaooooooaoaooo <br>Woah woaaaaaooooooaoaooo <br>Woah woaaaaaooooooaoaooo <br>Woah woaaaaaooooooaoaooo <br><br>Don't come too close <br>You don't wanna see my ghost <br>Your turn but I'm betrayed <br>By you my sweetheart]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Matchbox" label="Matchbox"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Eddies_Gun/</id><title>The Kooks - Eddie`s Gun - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Eddies_Gun/" title="The Kooks - Eddie`s Gun - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Did you see the way she looks at me <br>A honeybee got two lives and she's got me <br><br>I tried to love her back <br>And then I shrunk back into my wrap <br>And in the barrel of my gun <br>I hope I'm not the only one <br><br>Did you see the way she looks at me <br>She's got an eye for an awkward guy like me <br><br>I tried to love her back she's just a girl <br>And then I shrunk back into my wrap she's just a girl <br>And in the barrel of my gun <br>I hope I'm not the only one <br>And in the barrel of my gun <br>I hope I'm not the only one <br><br>Do do, do do do <br><br>I tried to love her back she's just a girl <br>And then I shrunk back into my wrap she's just a girl <br>And in the barrel of my gun <br>I hope I'm not the only one <br>And in the barrel of my gun <br>I hope I'm not the only one]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Eddie`s Gun" label="Eddie`s Gun"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Sway/</id><title>The Kooks - Sway - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Sway/" title="The Kooks - Sway - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Say whatever you have to say, I'll stand by you <br>Do whatever you have to do, to get it out and not become a reaction memory <br>To hurt the ones you love you know you never meant to but you do <br>oh yeah you do <br><br>Be whoever you have to be, I won't judge you <br>Sing whatever you have to sing to get it out and not become a recluse about you, how to come out <br>I know you never meant to but you do <br>oh but you do <br><br>Still I need your sway, because you always pay for it <br>And I, and I need your soul because you're always soulful <br>And I and I need your heart, because you're always in the right places <br><br>And take whatever you have to take, you know I love you <br>come however you have to come, and get it out and get it out <br><br>Take it out on me, take it out on me <br>I'll give it you all, I give it you all,i give it <br>I give you all I give it you all, yes I will give it you all <br><br>Cause I need your sway, because you always pay for it <br>And I, and I need your soul because you're always soulful <br>And I and I need your heart, because you're always in the right places <br><br>Oh yes I will, I will give it you all <br><br>Cause I need your sway, because you always pay for it <br>And I, and I need your soul because you're always soulful <br>And I and I need that heart, because you're always in the right places]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Sway" label="Sway"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Ooh_La/</id><title>The Kooks - Ooh La - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Ooh_La/" title="The Kooks - Ooh La - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In their eyes is a place that you finally discovered <br>That you love it here, you've got to stay <br>On the bottom of the rock, an island <br>On which you find you love it when you twitch <br>You feel that itch in you pettycoat <br>Your pretty pretty pettycoat <br><br>Then you smiled, he got wild <br>You didn't understand that there's money to be made <br>Beauty is a card that must get played <br>By organisation <br><br>And ooh la, she was such a good girl to me <br>And ooh la, the world just chewed her up and spat her out <br>And ooh la, she was such a good girl to me <br>And ooh la, the world just chewed her up and spat her out <br><br>The world can be a very big place <br>So be yourself don't get out of place <br>Love your man and love him twice <br>Go to Hollywood and pay the price <br>Oh go to Hollywood <br><br>And don't be a star, it's such a drag <br>Take care of yourself, don't begin to lag <br>It's a hard life to live, so live it well <br>I'll be your friend and not in pretend <br>I know you girl <br>In all situations <br><br>And ooh la, she was such a good girl to me <br>And ooh la, the world just chewed her up and spat her out <br>And ooh la, she was such a good girl to me <br>And ooh la, the world just chewed her up and spat her out <br><br>Pretty pretty pretty pretty pretty pretty pretty pretty pretty <br>Pretty pretty pettycoat <br>Pretty pretty pretty pretty pretty pretty pretty pretty pretty <br>Pretty pretty pretty pretty pretty pretty pretty pettycoat <br>In all situations <br><br>And ooh la, she was such a good girl to me <br>And ooh la, the world just chewed her up and spat her out <br>And ooh la, she was such a good girl to me <br>And ooh la, the world just chewed her up and spat her out]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Ooh La" label="Ooh La"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Forgive__Forget/</id><title>The Kooks - Forgive &amp; Forget - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Forgive__Forget/" title="The Kooks - Forgive &amp; Forget - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't say that I never moved you <br>Just because I saw the light before you did <br>Yes, I know that I never showed you <br>All the rooms inside of my soul <br><br>Yeah Yeah <br>You say you need someone to love you <br>But it ain't me <br><br>Walking up and down the hall <br>Frankie and his third lover <br>Speaking all the words she wants to hear <br>But that don't mean forever <br><br>Yeah <br>You say you need someone to love you <br>But it ain't me <br><br>Yeah <br>You say you need someone to love you <br>But it ain't me <br><br>Sitting down by the fire <br>Frankie plays the guitar <br>People playing make believe <br>They say, can we get a little higher <br><br>You give it away <br>You give it away <br>You give it away <br>You give it away <br>So easy baby <br><br>But I can't stand <br>An hour break <br>Another day <br>So let me make it easy babe <br><br>And it goes on and on <br><br>Packing her bags <br>She found somewhere to stay <br>And in the car to the station <br>You know the world looks a little brighter <br>And then there's no need for conversations <br>Tell me why <br><br>You give it away <br>You give it away <br>You give it away <br>You give it away <br>So easy baby <br><br>But I can't stand <br>An hour break <br>Another day <br>So let me make it easy babe <br><br>And it goes on <br><br>You say you need someone to love you <br>You say you need someone to love you <br>But it ain't me <br><br>Yeah <br>So I forgive and forget you <br>You say you need someone to love you <br>But it ain't me <br>So I forgive and forget you <br>Yeah <br>So I forgive and forget you <br>You say you need someone to love you <br>But it ain't me <br>So I forgive and forget you <br>You say you need someone to love you <br>But it ain't me <br>Yeah <br>So I forgive and forget you <br>You say you need someone to love you <br>But it ain't me <br>So I forgive and forget you]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Forgive &amp; Forget" label="Forgive &amp; Forget"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/You_Dont_Love_Me/</id><title>The Kooks - You Don`t Love Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/You_Dont_Love_Me/" title="The Kooks - You Don`t Love Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[But you don't love me the way that, I love you <br>'cause if you did girl you would not, do those things you do <br>You killed my heart just to see if, I will rise <br>Above your anger and above your lies <br><br>And all I see of you, is when you're not so busy <br>Oh your not so busy <br><br>And you don't love me the way that, I love you <br>'cause if you did boy you would not, do the things you do <br>You turned my life around, before that I am glad <br>However much I love you this love is getting bad <br><br>And oh my darling look at you <br>The words that only you could use <br>But you no you'll always be my girl, girl <br>I'll take you out just for a bite <br>Show you all the city sites <br>But you know you'll always be my girl, girl <br><br>But you don't love me the way that, I love you <br>'cause if you did boy you would not, do those things you do <br>You killed my heart just to see if, I will rise <br>Above your anger and above your lies <br><br>And all I see of you, is when you're not so busy <br>Oh your not so busy <br><br>But you don't love me you don't care, woman <br>And you don't love me you don't care, woman <br>'Cause you don't love me you don't care, woman <br>if you don't love me you don't care, woman <br>Oh woman]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="You Don`t Love Me" label="You Don`t Love Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Is_It_Me/</id><title>The Kooks - Is It Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Is_It_Me/" title="The Kooks - Is It Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Is it me, is it you <br>Is it the times that we're living through <br>Was it hard when I had to leave <br>That day you seemed to change <br>We all need someone to guide us <br>Someone to introduce the show <br>I needed someone just like you <br>Someone to let me know <br>I could loose it all <br><br>Well I began to breakdown <br>Searching overtime <br>Bring me a pig's heart <br>And a glass of wine <br>There was nothing that you could've done <br>There was nothing that you should've said <br>We're both still chasing shadows in our heads <br>It was all too soon <br><br>But is it me, is it you <br>Is it the times that we're going through <br>Was it hard, did your heart breakdown <br>Is your mind still in control <br>There is a violence in love <br>Some things I'll never understand <br>So where the bullets missed you out <br>They hit me and I'm falling down again <br><br>Well I began to breakdown <br>Searching overtime <br>Bring me a pig's heart <br>And a glass of wine <br>There was nothing that you could've done <br>There was nothing that you should've said <br>I'm still chasing shadows in my head <br>It was all too soon <br><br>Was it me, was it you <br>Was it the times that we're living through <br>On my way to see you again <br>You were my only friend <br>I know you needed someone to guide you <br>And the world you should've owned <br>I needed someone to guide me <br>Someone to let me know <br>I could loose it all]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Is It Me" label="Is It Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Sofa_Song/</id><title>The Kooks - Sofa Song - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Sofa_Song/" title="The Kooks - Sofa Song - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The city freeze before <br>I just realised I don't like you <br>Me and my girl <br>Are going out for some air <br>And I will do my best <br>Just to get under her dress <br>And catch you out if I can <br>On the other side of my sofa <br><br>Won't you come on over <br>At the side of my sofa <br>Oh won't you come on over <br><br>The city heated it up <br>It got blurry cause I'd had enough <br>And he tried to take your soul <br>But didn't realise you keep it in a different hole <br><br>Won't you come on over <br>At the side of my sofa <br>Oh won't you come on over <br><br>So here he comes, a man with <br>A loaded gun, I don't know if he <br>Wants my soul or my <br>Cash flow, I s'pose I don't know <br><br>So here he comes, a man with a <br>A loaded gun I don't know if he <br>Wants my girl's heart or her pearls <br>I s'pose I don't know <br>I s'pose I don't know <br>I s'pose I don't know <br>I s'pose I don't know <br>I s'pose I don't know]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Sofa Song" label="Sofa Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Down/</id><title>The Kooks - Down - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Down/" title="The Kooks - Down - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Woah yeah <br>I've been round town <br>There's a rumour baby, you're planning to bring me <br><br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br><br>You're tryna set me up <br>Tell me how to be <br>Yeah, you're talking behind me <br>You're talking behind me <br>You're talking behind my back <br>You wanna watch me fall <br>Watch me fall <br>But I won't break <br>I won't break <br>I know you'd like to hit me <br>Kick me to the ground <br>You're tryna be me <br>You're tryna bring me <br><br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br><br>Watch me yeah <br>Doo doo doo doo doo <br><br>I'm so sexual, it's all about the thrill <br>If you wanna please me, pleasure me <br>Let me know what's next <br>I'm gonna hit you up <br>Hit you up <br>Then I'm gonna let you down <br>Let you down <br>Just to prove a point <br>That you can't break a man who's already <br><br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br><br>Watch me yeah <br>Doo doo doo doo doo <br><br>Let's get a little louder, louder <br>A little louder, louder <br>I say la <br>I say la <br>I say la la la la la la la <br>La la la la la la la <br><br>There's a rumour baby <br>You're tryna bring me <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br><br>You're gonna let her bring me down <br>No no, there's no way <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Down down diggy de down down diggy diggy <br>Watch me yeah <br>Doo doo doo doo doo]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Down" label="Down"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Seaside/</id><title>The Kooks - Seaside - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Seaside/" title="The Kooks - Seaside - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to go to the seaside <br>I'm not trying to say that everybody wants to go <br>I fell in love at the seaside <br>I handled my charm with time and slight of hand <br><br>Do you want to go to the seaside <br>I'm not trying to say that everybody wants to go <br>I fell in love at the seaside <br>She handled her charm with time and slight of hand, and oh <br><br>But I'm just trying to love you <br>In any kind of way <br>But I find it hard to love you girl <br>When you're far away <br>Away <br><br>Do you want to go to the seaside <br>I'm not trying to say that everybody wants to go <br>But I fell in love on the seaside <br>On the seaside <br>In the seaside]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Seaside" label="Seaside"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Shine_On/</id><title>The Kooks - Shine On - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:25:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:25:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Shine_On/" title="The Kooks - Shine On - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Safety pins holding up the things <br>That make you mine <br>About your hair, you needn't care <br>You look beautiful all the time <br><br>Shine, shine, shine on <br>Yes <br>Wont you shine, shine on <br><br>Your magazines, at people at the seams <br>But you still read <br>I must admit, I don't believe in it <br>But I see how you get sucked in <br><br>Shine, shine, shine on <br>Yes <br>Wont you shine, shine on <br>Sha la la la <br>Shine, shine, shine on <br>Yes <br>Wont you shine, shine on <br><br>Because your not done <br><br>Why do you bite the hand that feeds you <br>Why do you <br>Why do you bite the hand that feedsyou <br><br>Shine, shine, shine on <br>Yes <br>Wont you shine, shine on <br>Sha la la la <br>Shine, shine, shine on <br>Yes <br>Wont you shine, shine on <br><br>Safety pins holding up the things <br>That make you mine <br>About your hair, you needn't care <br>You look beautiful all the time]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Shine On" label="Shine On"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/She_Moves_In_Her_Own_Way/</id><title>The Kooks - She Moves In Her Own Way - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:26:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:26:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/She_Moves_In_Her_Own_Way/" title="The Kooks - She Moves In Her Own Way - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So at my show on Monday <br>I was hoping someday <br>You'd be on your way to better things <br>It's not about your make up <br>Or how you try to shape up <br>To these tiresome paper dreams <br>Paper dreams, honey <br><br>So now you pour your heart out <br>You're telling me you're far out <br>You're not about to lie down for your cause <br>But you don't pull my strings <br>'Cos I'm a better man <br>Moving on to better things <br><br>Well uh oh, oh I love her because she moves in her own way <br>Well uh oh, oh she came to my show just to hear about my day <br><br>And at the show on Tuesday <br>She was in her mindset <br>Tempered furs and spangled boots <br>Looks are deceiving <br>Make me believe it <br>And these tiresome paper dreams <br>Paper dreams, honey <br>Yeah <br><br>So wont you go far <br>Tell me you're a keeper <br>Not about to lie down for your cause <br>And you don't pull my strings <br>'Cos I'm a better man <br>Moving on to better things <br><br>Well oh oh, oh I love her because she moves in her own way <br>Well oh oh, oh she came to my show just to hear about my day <br><br>yes I wish that we never made it <br>Through all the summers <br>They're keeping us instead of <br>Kicking us back <br>Down through the suburbs <br>yes I wish that we never made it <br>Through all the summers <br>They're keeping us instead of <br>Kicking us back <br>Down through the suburbs <br><br>But uh oh, I love her because she moves in her own way <br>But uh oh, she came to my show just to hear about my day <br>But uh oh, oh I love her because she moves in her own way <br>But uh oh, oh she came to my show just to hear about my day]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="She Moves In Her Own Way" label="She Moves In Her Own Way"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Bad_Habit/</id><title>The Kooks - Bad Habit - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:26:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:26:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Bad_Habit/" title="The Kooks - Bad Habit - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby got our head down <br>Baby got our head down to the ground <br>Looking for a stranger <br>Looking for a stranger to love <br>You got to dot your I's and cross your t's <br>You gotta let go, come with me <br>Looking for a stranger <br>Looking for a stranger to love <br><br>You say you want it, but <br>You can't get it in <br>You got yourself a bad habit for it <br>Oh look at you, walking up and down a pole <br>A saying please save me <br>You say you want it, but <br>You can't get it in <br>You got yourself a bad habit for it <br>Oh look at you, walking up and down a pole <br>A saying please <br>Oh man, oh man, oh man <br>You know I wish I had it all <br><br>Baby got our head down <br>Baby trying to stand down in the crowd <br>Looking for a stranger <br>Looking for a stranger to love <br>You got to dot your I's and cross your t's <br>You gotta let go, come with me <br>Looking for a stranger <br>Looking for a stranger to love <br><br>You say you want it, but <br>You can't get it in <br>You got yourself a bad habit for it <br>Oh look at you, walking up and down a pole <br>A saying please save me <br>You say you want it, but <br>You can't get it in <br>You got yourself a bad habit for it <br>Oh look at you, walking up and down a pole <br>A saying please <br>Oh man, oh man, oh man <br>You know I wish I had it all <br><br>You know I wish I had it all <br><br>You say you want it, but <br>You can't get it in <br>You got yourself a bad habit for it <br>Oh look at you, walking up and down a pole <br>A saying please <br>Oh man, oh man, oh man <br><br>You can't get it, it's a <br>A bad habit, such a <br>A bad habit such a bad bad habit <br>It's a, a bad habit]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Bad Habit" label="Bad Habit"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Junk_Of_The_Heart_Happy/</id><title>The Kooks - Junk Of The Heart (Happy) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:26:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:26:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Junk_Of_The_Heart_Happy/" title="The Kooks - Junk Of The Heart (Happy) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Junk of the heart is junk in my mind <br>So hard to leave you all alone <br>We get so drunk that we can hardly see <br>What use is that to you or me baby <br>See I notice nothing makes you shatter, no, no <br>You're a lover of the wild and a joker of the heart <br>But are you mine <br><br>I wanna make you happy <br>I wanna make you feel alive <br>Let me make you happy <br>I wanna make you feel alive at night <br>I wanna make you happy <br>You and good girl tonight <br>Yeah <br><br>We sink to be sunk, life is no race <br>When I'm not happy I'm in disgrace <br>So I spend time with guessing on you oh <br>You're a lover of the wild and a joker of the heart <br>But are you mine <br><br>I wanna make you happy <br>I wanna make you feel alive <br>Let me make you happy <br>I wanna make you feel alive at night <br>I wanna make you happy <br>If you're a good girl tonight <br>Yeah <br><br>La la la lala <br><br>Still I notice nothing makes you shatter no, no <br>You're a lover of the wild and a joker of the heart <br>But are you mine <br><br>I wanna make you happy <br>I wanna make you feel alive <br>Let me make you happy <br>I wanna make you feel alive at night <br>I wanna make you happy <br>You and good girl tonight]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Junk Of The Heart (Happy)" label="Junk Of The Heart (Happy)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Always_Where_I_Need_To_Be/</id><title>The Kooks - Always Where I Need To Be - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:26:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:26:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Always_Where_I_Need_To_Be/" title="The Kooks - Always Where I Need To Be - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She don't know who she is <br>I can take her anywhere <br>Do whatever comes naturally to you <br>You know she just don't care <br><br>'cause I'm always where I need to be <br>Yeah, and I always thought I would end up <br>With you, eventually <br>Do dodo do do do do <br><br>Now I see her again <br>I ask to be her hummingbird <br>Whisper words in her ear <br>Oh now you know I just don't care <br><br>'cause I'm always where I <br>Where I need to be <br>I i i always, always thought <br>I would end up with you eventually <br><br>I'm a man, I'm a man on the scene <br>I'm a man, and I can be so obscene <br>Because I always think that I know how to be <br>But I always thought that I would end up with you, eventually <br>I'm a man, I'm a man on the scene <br>I'm a man, and I can be so obscene]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Always Where I Need To Be" label="Always Where I Need To Be"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Naive/</id><title>The Kooks - Naive - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:26:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:26:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Kooks/Naive/" title="The Kooks - Naive - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not saying it was your fault <br>Although you could have done more <br>Oh you're so naive yet so <br>How could this been done <br>By such a smiling sweetheart <br>Oh, and your sweet and pretty face <br>In such an ugly world <br>For something so beautiful <br>Oh, that every time I look inside <br><br>I know, she knows that I'm not fond of asking <br>True or false, it may be Well, she's still out to get me <br>And I know, she knows that I'm not fond of asking <br>True or false, it may be She's still out to get me <br><br>I may say it was your fault <br>Because I know you could have done more <br>Oh, you're so naive yet so <br>How could this be done <br>By such a smiling sweetheart <br>Oh, and your sweet and pretty face <br>In such an ugly word <br>For something so beautiful <br>That every time I look inside <br><br>I know, she knows that I'm not fond of asking <br>True or false, it may be Well, she's still out to get me <br>And I know, she knows that I'm not fond of asking <br>True or false, it may be She's still out to get me <br><br>So how could this be done <br>By such a smiling sweetheart <br>You're so naive yet so <br>You're such an ugly thing <br>For someone so beautiful <br>That every time you're on his side <br><br>I know, she knows that I'm not fond of asking <br>True or false, it may be Well, she's still out to get me <br>And I know, she knows that I'm not fond of asking <br>True or false, it may be She's still out to get me <br><br>Just don't let me down <br>Just don't let me down <br>Hold on to your kite <br>Just don't let me down <br>Just don't let me down <br>Hold on to your kite <br>Just don't let me down <br>Just don't let me down <br>Hold on to this kite <br>Just don't let me down]]></content><category term="The Kooks" label="The Kooks"/><category term="Naive" label="Naive"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HYPERGENERIC/183_Syndrome_Feat_윤솔/</id><title>HYPERGENERIC - 183 Syndrome (Feat. 윤솔) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:26:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:26:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HYPERGENERIC/183_Syndrome_Feat_%EC%9C%A4%EC%86%94/" title="HYPERGENERIC - 183 Syndrome (Feat. 윤솔) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[진정성이 결여된 <br>다른 세상 속 자신을 추앙하며 <br>손가락 끝 욕망으로 <br>추함을 덮는다 <br>관심이란 쾌락에 <br>중독되어 도릴 포기했던 그들 <br>진실 앞에 도피하는 <br>비겁한 도망자 <br>양심 없이 툭 뱉은 말 <br>즉 더 많은 관심을 <br>쫓아가는 관심병 <br>옳지 못해 <br>당신의 옳지 못한 행동은 <br>옳지 못한 것들과 <br>가히 결탁한 결과 <br>쌓인 악행의 사상누각 <br>무엇으로도 <br>되돌릴 수 없는 인과응보 <br>피치 못해 벗어나려 해도 <br>남은 것은 단죄의 시간을 <br>달게 가질 것 no way <br>숫자와 숫자로 이뤄진 <br>세상 안을 벗어난 그 순간 <br>현실에선 소외된 <br>초라한 존재들 <br>거짓으로 세상을 뒤집어 <br>자신의 욕심을 채우려 하지만 <br>결말은 언제나 텅 빈 공허뿐 <br>질서 없는 공간에 <br>숨어 뱉어놓은 더러운 오물들이 <br>선한 이를 해한 후에 <br>악한을 구한다 <br>첫째 <br>이 땅의 진정한 성군을 모함하고 <br>놀림거리로 만든 죄 <br>둘째 <br>자식 잃은 부모와 <br>목숨 잃은 자식들을 <br>조롱하고 멸시한 죄 <br>입에 담기조차 힘든 <br>당신의 더러운 방종을 <br>앙다문 죄 <br>인의로 주벌하니 <br>당신은 대죄할 것 <br>침묵을 유지한 채 <br>숫자와 숫자로 이뤄진 <br>세상 안을 벗어난 그 순간 <br>현실에선 소외된 <br>초라한 존재들 <br>거짓으로 세상을 뒤집어 <br>자신의 욕심을 채우려 하지만 <br>결말은 언제나 텅 빈 공허뿐 <br>]]></content><category term="HYPERGENERIC" label="HYPERGENERIC"/><category term="183 Syndrome (Feat. 윤솔)" label="183 Syndrome (Feat. 윤솔)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HYPERGENERIC/정효/</id><title>HYPERGENERIC - 정효 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:26:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:26:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HYPERGENERIC/%EC%A0%95%ED%9A%A8/" title="HYPERGENERIC - 정효 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[집으로 돌아가는 캄캄한 골목길 <br>어스름히 가로등만 깜빡거릴 때 <br>하늘을 보니 별 한점도 보이질 않고 <br>쳇바퀴 같은 하루가 너무나 지겨워 <br>내일도 똑같겠지 그렇겠지 <br>오늘의 즐거움 내일로 미루긴 싫은데 <br>삶이 뜻대로 안되는 게 참 피곤하겠지 <br>넌 그렇게 난 이렇게 모두가 <br>똑같이 살 필요는 없지 <br>괜찮아 너는 절대로 틀리지 않았으니 <br>괜찮아 괜찮아 괜찮아 <br>더는 너를 잃지 않게 <br>다른 삶을 살지 않게 <br>너의 기억 저편의 끝에 <br>숨겨둔 한 조각 꿈에 <br>잠시 기대봐도 돼 <br>누구나 한번 뿐이 살아보지 않은 인생 <br>어줍잖은 충고 따윈 귀뒤로 흘려보내 <br>실시간으로 상영되는 세상이란 영화 <br>하나라도 더 눈에 담게 좀 걷는 건 어때 <br>좀 더디면 어때 누구나 속도는 달라 <br>겨우 이 정도로 졌다는 생각은 <br>버리도록 해 <br>가끔은 너도 버럭해 참지만 말구 <br>매일 알잖아 막상 붙으면 <br>별 거 아니라구 man <br>누구도 널 판단할 수 없어 감히 아무도 <br>비록 오늘 비참하고 괜히 맘이 아파도 <br>일어나 넌 니가 갈 길 잘 가고 있어 <br>나도 널 믿는데 니가 널 왜 못믿어 <br>더는 너를 잃지 않게 <br>다른 삶을 살지 않게 <br>너의 기억 저편의 끝에 <br>숨겨둔 한 조각 꿈에 <br>잠시 기대봐도 돼 <br>더는 너를 잃지 않게 <br>다른 삶을 살지 않게 <br>너의 기억 저편의 끝에 <br>숨겨둔 한 조각 꿈에 <br>잠시 기대봐도 돼 <br>]]></content><category term="HYPERGENERIC" label="HYPERGENERIC"/><category term="정효" label="정효"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HYPERGENERIC/유년_UNION/</id><title>HYPERGENERIC - 유년 (UNION) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:26:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:26:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HYPERGENERIC/%EC%9C%A0%EB%85%84_UNION/" title="HYPERGENERIC - 유년 (UNION) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[골목길 먼지 쌓인 담벼락 타며 <br>모험을 떠나놀던 <br>철부진 거뭇한 수염 난 어른 되어 <br>모나미 꽁다리 몽당연필 쥐던 <br>고사리 같은 손 <br>이젠 소주잔을 대신 쥐고 있네 <br>세월이 가도 몸은 컸어도 <br>여전히 철은 없는 우리들 <br>함께 있을 땐 무엇도 두렵지 않아 <br>그 시절 순수했던 친구들과 <br>아무 걱정 없이 놀던 <br>아련한 내 어린 시절 <br>억만금을 줘도 살 수 없는 <br>공간 안에 쌓인 추억되어 <br>돌아갈 수 없는 <br>우리 유년시절 그리워 <br>어디갈까 따라와 뻔하잖아 <br>목적지는 곰달래길 <br>오락실 동전많아 <br>시간 가는 줄 몰라 <br>철권 하다 킹오파 딴 건 몰라도 <br>너한테 지면 난 너무 열이 받아 <br>누군 학원으로 뭔가를 배우러 <br>누군 책방 만화 빌리러 <br>나는 집에 갈래 <br>오늘 가요 톱10에 <br>에쵸티 드디어 컴백해 <br>영원할 것 같았던 <br>빨리 어른이 되고 싶었던 <br>그 어떤 것도 함께라서 <br>그냥 마냥 다 좋았던 그 시절 <br>그 시절 순수했던 친구들과 <br>아무 걱정 없이 놀던 <br>아련한 내 어린 시절 <br>억만금을 줘도 살 수 없는 <br>공간 안에 쌓인 추억되어 <br>돌아갈 수 없는 <br>우리 유년시절 그리워 <br>그 시절 순수했던 친구들과 <br>아무 걱정 없이 놀던 <br>아련한 내 어린 시절 <br>억만금을 줘도 살 수 없는 <br>공간 안에 쌓인 추억되어 <br>돌아갈 수 없는 <br>우리 유년시절 <br>그 시절 순수했던 친구들과 <br>아무 걱정 없이 놀던 <br>아련한 내 어린 시절 <br>억만금을 줘도 살 수 없는 <br>공간 안에 쌓인 추억되어 <br>돌아갈 수 없는 <br>우리 유년시절 그리워 <br>]]></content><category term="HYPERGENERIC" label="HYPERGENERIC"/><category term="유년 (UNION)" label="유년 (UNION)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HYPERGENERIC/내려놔/</id><title>HYPERGENERIC - 내려놔 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:26:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:26:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HYPERGENERIC/%EB%82%B4%EB%A0%A4%EB%86%94/" title="HYPERGENERIC - 내려놔 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[축 처진 니 어깨가 <br>왠지 슬퍼 보여 <br>네가 원하던 것이 모두 다 <br>뜻대로 안된거니 <br>한줌 꽉진 모래 그처럼 <br>거의 너의 손에 잡힌 <br>모든것 새나가는구나 <br>니 삶의 전부인듯 바라던 <br>모든것들 꿈꿔온 많은 일들 <br>이 세상이 끝난듯 <br>눈 앞이 캄캄해 <br>어떻게 살아야 할 지 <br>믿겨지지가 않아 <br>숨이 막히는구나 <br>밤잠도 못이룰만큼 <br>불안해 어느 순간 <br>무너질 것만 같아 <br>지켜온 모든것 <br>힘들게 쌓아놓은 <br>너만의 멋진 성이 <br>무너질까 불안하구나 <br>조금만 욕심을 비워봐 <br>보다 넓은 맘으로 <br>이 세상을 둘러봐 <br>한동안 잊고 산 모든것 <br>새로운 맘으로 바라봐 <br>너 조금만 내려놔 내려놔 <br>좋은 성적만 1등은 아냐 <br>승진이 네 인생의 전부는 아냐 <br>가득찬 통장 잔고가 <br>니 인생의 완성을 <br>말해주는 것은 절대로 아냐 <br>먼훗날 니가 눈감을 때 <br>하늘에 한뼘 더 가까워질 때 <br>널 위에 눈물 흘려줄 사람 <br>그들에게 남겨질 <br>니 삶에 대한 기억이 <br>어떤 모습일지 <br>삶의 향이 지금보다 <br>더 짙어질 때 비로소 <br>깨닫게 되는 건 <br>커다란 부와 명예는 <br>작은 일상에 비하면 <br>먼지보다 못한 것 <br>부질 없는 허영 허세 <br>모두 때가 되면 <br>빈손으로 떠나는 법 <br>영원한 존재는 없는 것 <br>가볍게 또 가볍게 <br>내려놔 더 내려놔 <br>부모의 얼굴조차도 모르는 <br>말보다 사는 법을 <br>먼저 배운 한 아이는 <br>꿈꾸는 기회조차 박탈 당해 <br>평범히 사는 것이 <br>가장 큰 소원이었었지 <br>아무리 부어도 <br>채워지지 않는 구멍난 <br>옹기 같은 니 마음은 <br>감사의 기쁨을 잊었지 <br>소소한 일상에 눈 돌려봐 <br>넌 충분히 행복해 <br>고층 아파트만 집은 아냐 <br>슈퍼카만 달릴 수 있는 건 아냐 <br>온몸에 걸친 명품들이 <br>니 진정한 가치를 <br>높여주는 것은 절대로 아냐 <br>이 세상 소풍 끝나는 날에 <br>짊어진 모든 것 내리는 날에 <br>니 마지막을 지켜줄 사람 <br>그들에게 추억될 <br>니 짧지 않던 인생이 <br>어떤 모습일지 <br>삶의 향이 지금보다 <br>더 짙어질 때 비로소 <br>깨닫게 되는 건 <br>커다란 부와 명예는 <br>작은 일상에 비하면 <br>먼지보다 못한 것 <br>부질 없는 허영 허세 <br>모두 때가 되면 <br>빈손으로 떠나는 법 <br>영원한 존재는 없는 것 <br>가볍게 또 가볍게 <br>내려놔 더 내려놔 <br>넌 오늘도 인스타그램을 <br>켜 좋아요 버튼 누르며 <br>니 인생이랑 막 비교 <br>비교 해가며 한숨을 <br>뱉어내고 고개를 숙여 <br>보여지는 건 단지 <br>부분일 뿐 잘 들여다보면 <br>걔도 무일푼 <br>연연 하지마 <br>boy you should be cool <br>진짜와 가짜 그걸 가려낼 수 있는 <br>눈이 필요해 니가 가진 것 <br>니가 할 수 있는 것 많잖아 <br>임마 남들한텐 없는 것 <br>그 누군가에겐 <br>니가 되고 싶은 인생 <br>감사히 살어 <br>man love your family <br>and yourself <br>삶의 향이 지금보다 <br>더 짙어질 때 비로소 <br>깨닫게 되는 건 <br>커다란 부와 명예는 <br>작은 일상에 비하면 <br>먼지보다 못한 것 <br>부질 없는 허영 허세 <br>모두 때가 되면 <br>빈손으로 떠나는 법 <br>영원한 존재는 없는 것 <br>가볍게 또 가볍게 <br>내려놔 더 내려놔 <br>]]></content><category term="HYPERGENERIC" label="HYPERGENERIC"/><category term="내려놔" label="내려놔"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HYPERGENERIC/나비효과_Feat_윤솔/</id><title>HYPERGENERIC - 나비효과 (Feat. 윤솔) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:26:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:26:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HYPERGENERIC/%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84%ED%9A%A8%EA%B3%BC_Feat_%EC%9C%A4%EC%86%94/" title="HYPERGENERIC - 나비효과 (Feat. 윤솔) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[황폐했던 심연의 결론 <br>광대한 고뇌 매몰된 기백 <br>시도조차 해낼 수 없는 <br>부정적 사고 미완의 귀결 <br>작은 나비의 날갯짓은 <br>사나운 폭풍 되어 <br>상념을 쓸어간다 <br>어느 순간 번뇌는 사라진다 <br>힘겹게 디딘 첫 발자욱 <br>황홀한 광채 되어 <br>암흑을 걷어간다 <br>시작하라 첫발을 저어마라 <br>결과와는 무방한 격정 <br>경계를 허무는 연약한 몸짓 <br>아무것도 하지 않는다면 <br>그 어떤 일도 생기지 않는 법 <br>Who I am <br>답 없는 밤에다 매일 질문 던져 <br>불안해 끝과 끝 그리고 그 끝 마지막 <br>순간에 공허만이 나를 차지할지 <br>신은 꼭 나를 무시하고 겁만 줄까 왜 <br>잡념은 걱정을 낳고 <br>그 걱정의 잡념은 걱정을 낳아 <br>욕심을 방패 삼고 <br>짓눌려 좀먹힌 나를 봐 <br>아무것도 시작하지 않으면 <br>아무것도 아니게 돼 <br>날개를 펼쳐야 해 <br>지금이 시발점을 찍을 때 <br>작은 나비의 날갯짓은 <br>사나운 폭풍 되어 <br>상념을 쓸어간다 <br>어느 순간 번뇌는 사라진다 <br>힘겹게 디딘 첫 발자욱 <br>황홀한 광채 되어 <br>암흑을 걷어간다 <br>시작하라 첫발을 저어마라 <br>작은 나비의 날갯짓은 <br>사나운 폭풍 되어 <br>상념을 쓸어간다 <br>어느 순간 번뇌는 사라진다 <br>힘겹게 디딘 첫 발자욱 <br>황홀한 광채 되어 <br>암흑을 걷어간다 <br>시작하라 첫발을 저어마라 <br>]]></content><category term="HYPERGENERIC" label="HYPERGENERIC"/><category term="나비효과 (Feat. 윤솔)" label="나비효과 (Feat. 윤솔)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/차세빈/YOLO/</id><title>차세빈 - YOLO - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:27:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:27:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B0%A8%EC%84%B8%EB%B9%88/YOLO/" title="차세빈 - YOLO - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지나버린 시간은 <br>두 번 다시 돌아오지 않아 <br>닫혀버린 마음은 <br>제일 먼저 후회로 다가와 <br>그러지 마요 <br>너는 아직 몰라 <br>넌 끝을 몰라 <br>가장 아름다운 네 모습 <br>후회로 가득한 널 만들지마 <br>한번뿐인 지금 Let's do it <br>하루도 하루도 하루도 <br>왜 너를 위해 살지 못하니 <br>오늘밤 오늘밤 오늘밤 <br>자 준비됐어 난 <br>I'm ready get set go <br>Let's dance 하고픈 대로 <br>Can u join me <br>YOLO YOLO YOLO <br>Let's Dance 원하는 대로 <br>Can u feel this air <br>YOLO YOLO YOLO <br>떠나가는 사랑은 <br>널 찾아오지 않아 <br>가만히 기다리는 <br>네게 기회 따위는 없어 <br>그러지 마요 <br>너는 아직 몰라 <br>넌 끝을 몰라 <br>지금 이 순간을 즐겨봐 <br>후회로 가득한 널 만들지마 <br>한번뿐인 지금 Let's get it <br>오늘도 오늘도 오늘도 <br>왜 너를 사랑하지 못하니 <br>오늘밤 오늘밤 오늘밤 <br>자 준비됐어 난 <br>I'm ready get set go <br>Let's dance 하고픈 대로 <br>Can u join me <br>YOLO YOLO YOLO <br>Let's Dance 원하는 대로 <br>Can u feel this air <br>YOLO YOLO YOLO <br>You only live once only once yeah <br>나중은 없어 딱 한번뿐야 <br>Let's dance 하고픈 대로 <br>Can u join me <br>YOLO YOLO YOLO <br>Let's Dance 원하는 대로 <br>Can u feel this air <br>YOLO YOLO YOLO <br>]]></content><category term="차세빈" label="차세빈"/><category term="YOLO" label="YOLO"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Feellow/월요병/</id><title>Feellow - 월요병 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:27:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:27:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Feellow/%EC%9B%94%EC%9A%94%EB%B3%91/" title="Feellow - 월요병 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[월화수목금퇼 이불 밖을 <br>나설 힘도 없네 없네 <br>뭘 하자는 건지 침대에만 <br>종일 있고 싶네 <br>벌써 머리가 아파져 <br>점점 시간이 가까워져 <br>이렇게 살다간 월요병 걸리겠어 <br>한때는 그토록 원했던 출근길인데 <br>저번 주와 다름없이 식사는 패스 <br>모두가 똑같은 표정의 <br>사람들 속에서 흘러가 <br>언제나 그랬듯 오늘도 <br>주말을 향해서 흘러가 <br>I hate monday <br>어느새 또 월요일 <br>그때마다 걸리는 월요병 <br>매일 출근하는 건데 <br>월요일만 나설 힘이 없네 없네 <br>우울하기만 하네 <br>벌써부터 주말을 계획해 <br>맨날 똑같은 일상에 <br>퇴근 후에는 텅 빈 방에 <br>가방 던져놓고 넉다운 잠들었어 <br>지옥철 타고서 또다시 퇴근길인데 <br>차창 속에 내 모습은 무기력해 <br>모두가 똑같은 표정의 <br>사람들 속에서 흘러가 <br>언제나 그랬듯 오늘도 <br>주말을 향해서 흘러가 <br>I hate monday <br>어느새 또 월요일 <br>그때마다 걸리는 월요병 <br>긴 하루가 지나고 <br>텅 빈 집만이 기다려 <br>친구들 연락해볼까 <br>누구라도 상관없어 오늘 밤 <br>어느새 또 월요일 <br>그때마다 걸리는 월요병 <br>]]></content><category term="Feellow" label="Feellow"/><category term="월요병" label="월요병"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강다솔/다솔이와_동물친구들/</id><title>강다솔 - 다솔이와 동물친구들 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:28:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:28:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EB%8B%A4%EC%86%94/%EB%8B%A4%EC%86%94%EC%9D%B4%EC%99%80_%EB%8F%99%EB%AC%BC%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC%EB%93%A4/" title="강다솔 - 다솔이와 동물친구들 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뮤직~ 큐 <br><br>(엄마) <br>나는 강아지 나는 강아지 <br>(다솔) <br>멍멍멍멍 나는 강아지 <br><br>(아빠) <br>나는 고양이 나는 고양이 <br>(다솔) <br>미야옹미야옹 나는 고양이 <br><br>(다함께) <br>랄랄라랄랄라 우리들은 동물친구들 <br>랄랄라랄랄라 모두 모여라 <br><br><br>(아빠) <br>나는 돼지 나는 돼지 <br>(다솔) <br>꿀꿀꿀꿀 나는 돼지 <br><br>(엄마) <br>나는 병아리 나는 병아리 <br>(다솔) <br>뺩뺩뺩뺩 나는 병아리 <br><br>(다함께) <br>재미있는 동물 친구들]]></content><category term="강다솔" label="강다솔"/><category term="다솔이와 동물친구들" label="다솔이와 동물친구들"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/REBELE/Trippin_Chillin_Sillim/</id><title>REBELE - Trippin Chillin Sillim - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:28:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:28:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/REBELE/Trippin_Chillin_Sillim/" title="REBELE - Trippin Chillin Sillim - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[정상에 내려보는 View <br>볼 옆으로 자연스레 스쳐가는 구름 <br>눈까지 바른 선크림 따가워도 <br>내 땀방울들이 기분좋게 웃어줘 <br>Trippin <br>땀으로 젖은 티 <br>벗어 던지고 바람을 느끼지 <br>볼 옆으로 지나가는 구름 잡아타고 <br>날아 <br>가까워진 해 더 태워 까맣게 <br>Chillin <br>B.I.G Mountain Yes Ma Team <br>높아 진심 <br>In Da Sillim <br>Main Hip-Hop Crew 집합체 <br>Vol.2 Rebel &amp; Aim 우릴 기억한다면 <br>Get Familiar 다시 와서 <br>Hands Up In D Air <br>Yeah Yeah 나를 잘 몰라도 돼 너가 <br>마음가는대로 놀자 <br>해가 떨어지는 밤엔 <br>Trippin Chillin Sillim <br>도림천에서 아사히 한캔 딸래 <br>Join us <br>다 뿌리쳐 널 조이던 것들 잊고 <br>잔 부딪혀 날씬 덥더라도 Whatever <br>우리 음악으로 시원히 씻겨줄게 <br>Shower <br>매일 치여 다닐 너의 상처 위 <br>안식이 될꺼야 빨리 열어줄래 귀 <br>여운이 남을꺼야 다 뭐하나 <br>빠짐없이 준비했으니까 Let's Ride <br>정상에 내려보는 View <br>볼 옆으로 자연스레 스쳐가는 구름 <br>눈까지 바른 선크림 따가워도 <br>내 땀방울들이 기분좋게 웃어줘 <br>Trippin <br>땀으로 젖은 티 <br>벗어 던지고 바람을 느끼지 <br>볼 옆으로 지나가는 구름 <br>잡아타고 날아 <br>가까워진 해 더 태워 까맣게 <br>Chillin <br>Call us Kodiak 더 커버린 덩칠봐 <br>암만 거슬러들 봤자 한입거리 연어 <br>쫙 기지개를 켜니 무너진 개미굴 <br>다시 겨울잠은 Nope 엿봐라 볼륨 투 <br>원 투 스텝 밟던 때가 엊그제 이젠 <br>구름타고 Fly Highfive 달토끼와 <br>산만한놈들 필요해진 비아그라 <br>철갑 두른 태도 Pine tree <br>길이 기억될 이름 반짝이는 코 <br>가진 빅마운틴 <br>그래 팀 다운 팀 Yes ma team <br>아닌척말아 말하잖아 니 젖은 티가 <br>눈칫밥 먹느라 무거워진 몸 <br>니 맘 알아 다 재껴 뒤집어놔 폰 <br>들어 손 풀어 몸 축여 목 <br>걸어둬 먼지에 뒹굴었던 옷 <br>Brun it up <br>정상에 내려보는 View <br>볼 옆으로 자연스레 스쳐가는 구름 <br>눈까지 바른 선크림 따가워도 <br>내 땀방울들이 기분좋게 웃어줘 <br>Trippin <br>땀으로 젖은 티 <br>벗어 던지고 바람을 느끼지 <br>볼 옆으로 지나가는 구름 <br>잡아타고 날아 <br>가까워진 해 더 태워 까맣게 <br>Chillin <br>정상에 내려보는 View <br>볼 옆으로 자연스레 스쳐가는 구름 <br>눈까지 바른 선크림 따가워도 <br>내 땀방울들이 기분좋게 웃어줘 <br>Trippin <br>땀으로 젖은 티 <br>벗어 던지고 바람을 느끼지 <br>볼 옆으로 지나가는 구름 <br>잡아타고 날아 <br>가까워진 해 더 태워 까맣게 <br>Chillin <br>정상에 내려보는 View <br>볼 옆으로 자연스레 스쳐가는 구름 <br>눈까지 바른 선크림 따가워도 <br>내 땀방울들이 기분좋게 웃어줘 <br>Trippin <br>땀으로 젖은 티 <br>벗어 던지고 바람을 느끼지 <br>볼 옆으로 지나가는 구름 <br>잡아타고 날아 <br>가까워진 해 더 태워 까맣게 <br>Chillin <br>]]></content><category term="REBELE" label="REBELE"/><category term="Trippin Chillin Sillim" label="Trippin Chillin Sillim"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Still_Thrives_This_Love_MTV_Unplugged/</id><title>K.d. lang - Still Thrives This Love (MTV Unplugged) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:28:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:28:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Still_Thrives_This_Love_MTV_Unplugged/" title="K.d. lang - Still Thrives This Love (MTV Unplugged) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I often wonder <br>Is it so <br>All I am holding <br>Wants let go <br>How could I manage <br>I don't know <br><br>I often question <br>Is it so <br>Life's contradictions <br>Tend to grow <br>Spawning the choices <br>And the woe <br><br>But, still somehow thrives this love <br>Which I pray I'm worthy of <br>Still somehow thrives this love <br><br>I often wonder <br>Is it so <br>The lessons of patience <br>Are learned slow <br>And earnings of labour <br>May never show <br><br>But, still somehow thrives this love <br>Which I pray I'm worthy of <br>Still somehow thrives this love]]></content><category term="K.d. lang" label="K.d. lang"/><category term="Still Thrives This Love (MTV Unplugged)" label="Still Thrives This Love (MTV Unplugged)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Constant_Craving_MTV_Unplugged/</id><title>K.d. lang - Constant Craving (MTV Unplugged) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:28:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:28:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Constant_Craving_MTV_Unplugged/" title="K.d. lang - Constant Craving (MTV Unplugged) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Even through the darkest phase <br>Be it thick or thin <br>Always someone marches brave <br>Here beneath my skin <br><br>And constant <br>Constant <br>Craving <br>Craving <br>Has always <br>Always <br>Been <br><br>Maybe a great magnet pulls <br>All souls to what's true <br>Or maybe it is life itself <br>That feeds wisdom to its youth <br><br>Constant <br>Constant <br>Craving <br>Craving <br>Has always <br>Always <br>Been <br><br>Craving <br>Ah, constant craving <br>Has always been <br>Has always been <br><br>Constant <br>Constant <br>Craving <br>Craving <br>Has always <br>Always <br>Been <br>Constant <br>Constant <br>Craving <br>Craving <br>Has always <br>Always <br>Been <br><br>Craving <br>Ah, constant craving <br>Has always been <br>Has always been <br>Has always been <br>Has always <br>Always been <br>Has always <br>Always been <br>Has always been <br>Has always been <br>Has always been]]></content><category term="K.d. lang" label="K.d. lang"/><category term="Constant Craving (MTV Unplugged)" label="Constant Craving (MTV Unplugged)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Wash_Me_Clean_MTV_Unplugged/</id><title>K.d. lang - Wash Me Clean (MTV Unplugged) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:28:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:28:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Wash_Me_Clean_MTV_Unplugged/" title="K.d. lang - Wash Me Clean (MTV Unplugged) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You swim <br>Swim through my veins <br>Drown me <br>In your reign <br><br>My desire <br>Carries no shame <br>My will <br>Will harbour no pain <br><br>Wash <br>Wash me clean <br>Mend my wounded seams <br>Cleanse my tarnished dreams <br><br>Drink <br>Drink from my spell <br>Quench <br>Love's drying well <br><br>Wash <br>Wash me clean <br>Mend my wounded seams <br>Cleanse my tarnished dreams]]></content><category term="K.d. lang" label="K.d. lang"/><category term="Wash Me Clean (MTV Unplugged)" label="Wash Me Clean (MTV Unplugged)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Season_of_Hollow_Soul_MTV_Unplugged/</id><title>K.d. lang - Season of Hollow Soul (MTV Unplugged) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:28:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:28:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Season_of_Hollow_Soul_MTV_Unplugged/" title="K.d. lang - Season of Hollow Soul (MTV Unplugged) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Keen to the shifting of wind <br>I bend to it blind <br>To rid these kisses of sin <br>That must stay behind <br><br>Sour the fruit of neglect <br>The core of my doubt <br>Deprived are my veins you infect <br>With or without <br><br>Fate must have a reason <br>Why else endure the season <br>Of hollow soul <br>The ground on which we leave on <br>How strangely fuels the season <br>Of hollow soul hollow soul <br><br>Seed of uprooted chance <br>are grains of goodbye <br>Waving boughs so slowly dance <br>Questioning why <br><br>Fate must have a reason <br>Why else endure the season <br>Of hollow soul <br>The ground on which we leave on <br>How strangely fuels the season <br>Of hollow soul <br>La la la la <br>Fate must have a reason <br>Why else endure the season <br>Of hollow soul hollow soul <br><br>Fate must have a reason <br>Why else endure the season <br>Of hollow soul <br>La la la la <br>Fate must have a reason <br>Why else endure the season <br>Of hollow soul <br>La la la la <br>Fate must have a reason <br>Why else endure the season <br>Of hollow soul hollow soul]]></content><category term="K.d. lang" label="K.d. lang"/><category term="Season of Hollow Soul (MTV Unplugged)" label="Season of Hollow Soul (MTV Unplugged)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Miss_Chatelaine_MTV_Unplugged/</id><title>K.d. lang - Miss Chatelaine (MTV Unplugged) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:28:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:28:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Miss_Chatelaine_MTV_Unplugged/" title="K.d. lang - Miss Chatelaine (MTV Unplugged) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Just a kiss just a kiss <br>I have lived just for this <br>I can't explain why I've become <br>Miss Chatelaine <br><br>Just a smile just a smile <br>Hold me captive just a while <br>I can't explain why I've become <br>Miss Chatelaine <br><br>Every time your eyes meet mine <br>Clouds of qualm <br>Burst into sunshine <br><br>Just a sigh just a sigh <br>Words my love just reply <br>I can't explain why I've become <br>Miss Chatelaine <br>Miss Chatelaine <br><br>Zing <br><br>Just a smile just a smile <br>Hold me captive just a while <br>I can't explain why I've become <br>Miss Chatelaine <br><br>Every time your eyes meet mine <br>Clouds of qualm <br>Burst into sunshine <br><br>Just a kiss just a kiss <br>I have lived just for this <br>I can't explain why I've become <br>Miss Chatelaine <br><br>Miss Chatelaine <br>Miss Chatelaine <br>Miss Chatelaine <br>Miss Chatelaine]]></content><category term="K.d. lang" label="K.d. lang"/><category term="Miss Chatelaine (MTV Unplugged)" label="Miss Chatelaine (MTV Unplugged)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/So_It_Shall_Be_MTV_Unplugged/</id><title>K.d. lang - So It Shall Be (MTV Unplugged) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:28:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:28:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/So_It_Shall_Be_MTV_Unplugged/" title="K.d. lang - So It Shall Be (MTV Unplugged) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Shadows <br>Now curtain the moon <br>But faith swears <br>It will shine again soon <br>Shine with love <br>You've been hiding from me <br><br>Your kiss <br>Has hindered the day <br>A longing <br>That won't go away <br>You just keep knocking <br>And waking my heart <br>Like daylight chasing the dark <br><br>I can exist being caught by your kiss <br>Willingly <br>Or grant you control <br>Of my body and soul <br>Ask it and so it shall be <br><br>Shadows <br>Now curtain the moon <br>Still faith swears <br>It will shine again soon <br>Shine with love <br>You've been hiding from me <br>With that love <br>You've been hiding from me <br><br>I can exist being caught by your kiss <br>Willingly <br>Or grant you control <br>Of my body and soul <br>Ask it and so it shall be <br>Ask it and so it shall be]]></content><category term="K.d. lang" label="K.d. lang"/><category term="So It Shall Be (MTV Unplugged)" label="So It Shall Be (MTV Unplugged)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/The_Mind_of_Love_MTV_Unplugged/</id><title>K.d. lang - The Mind of Love (MTV Unplugged) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:28:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:28:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/The_Mind_of_Love_MTV_Unplugged/" title="K.d. lang - The Mind of Love (MTV Unplugged) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Talking to myself <br>Causing great concern for my health <br>Where is your head Kathryn <br>Where is your head <br><br>I'm trying hard to escape <br>This constant pull towards ache <br>Why do you fight Kathryn <br>Why do you fight <br><br>Surely help will arrive soon <br>And cure these self induced wounds <br>Why hurt yourself Kathryn <br>Why hurt yourself <br>Why hurt yourself <br><br>Can your heart conceal <br>What the mind of love reveals <br><br>I'm taking to myself again <br>It's causing great concern for my health <br>Where is your head Kathryn <br>Where is your head <br>Where is your head Kathryn <br>Where is your head <br><br>Can your heart conceal <br>What the mind of love reveals <br>Can your heart conceal <br>What the mind of love reveals <br>Can your heart conceal <br>What the mind of love reveals]]></content><category term="K.d. lang" label="K.d. lang"/><category term="The Mind of Love (MTV Unplugged)" label="The Mind of Love (MTV Unplugged)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Save_Me_MTV_Unplugged/</id><title>K.d. lang - Save Me (MTV Unplugged) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:28:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:28:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Save_Me_MTV_Unplugged/" title="K.d. lang - Save Me (MTV Unplugged) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Save me <br>Save me from you <br>But pave me <br>The way to you <br>Lead me upon the captive free <br>Gracious and tame like love can be <br>Lead me upon <br><br>Spoil me <br>Spoil me with you <br>And sell me with the world of you <br>Watch over me with a mother's eyes <br>Judging my worth only to glorify <br>Watch over me <br><br>Save me save me <br>Save me save me <br>Carry <br>Carry me through <br>And bury all my doubts of you <br>Clothe my desire with spell or prayer <br>I'll shroud every sign of need I swear <br>Clothe my desire <br><br>Save me save me <br>Save me save me <br>Save me save me <br>Save me save me]]></content><category term="K.d. lang" label="K.d. lang"/><category term="Save Me (MTV Unplugged)" label="Save Me (MTV Unplugged)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Constant_Craving/</id><title>K.d. lang - Constant Craving - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:28:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:28:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Constant_Craving/" title="K.d. lang - Constant Craving - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Even through the darkest phase <br>Be it thick or thin <br>Always someone marches brave <br>Here beneath my skin <br><br>And constant <br>Constant <br>Craving <br>Craving <br>Has always <br>Always <br>Been <br><br>Maybe a great magnet pulls <br>All souls to what's true <br>Or maybe it is life itself <br>That feeds wisdom to its youth <br><br>Constant <br>Constant <br>Craving <br>Craving <br>Has always <br>Always <br>Been <br><br>Craving <br>Ah, constant craving <br>Has always been <br>Has always been <br><br>Constant <br>Constant <br>Craving <br>Craving <br>Has always <br>Always <br>Been <br>Constant <br>Constant <br>Craving <br>Craving <br>Has always <br>Always <br>Been <br><br>Craving <br>Ah, constant craving <br>Has always been <br>Has always been <br>Has always been <br>Has always <br>Always been <br>Has always <br>Always been <br>Has always been <br>Has always been <br>Has always been]]></content><category term="K.d. lang" label="K.d. lang"/><category term="Constant Craving" label="Constant Craving"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Tears_of_Loves_Recall/</id><title>K.d. lang - Tears of Love`s Recall - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:28:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:28:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Tears_of_Loves_Recall/" title="K.d. lang - Tears of Love`s Recall - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love <br>Thing of might and dread <br>Stays the savior and poison to all <br>Of heart and head <br><br>Love <br>Force of death and birth <br>Still lies naked when next to the truth <br>So spins the earth <br><br>The tears of love's recall <br>Like blood to chocolate fall <br>And love <br>The common salt of thirst <br>Runs like water and cuts through the lives <br>Of blessed and cursed <br><br>The tears of love's recall <br>Like blood to chocolate fall <br><br>The tears of love's recall <br>Like blood of chocolate fall]]></content><category term="K.d. lang" label="K.d. lang"/><category term="Tears of Love`s Recall" label="Tears of Love`s Recall"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Outside_Myself/</id><title>K.d. lang - Outside Myself - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:28:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:28:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Outside_Myself/" title="K.d. lang - Outside Myself - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A thin ice covers my soul <br>My body's frozen and my heart is cold <br>And still so much about me is raw <br>I search for a place to unthaw <br><br>Something in me broods love into fear <br>It veils my vision, leaves my thoughts unclear <br>And my eyes from blue turn to grey <br>Hoping to mask what they say <br><br>I've been outside myself for so long <br>Any feeling I had is close to gone <br>I've been outside myself for so long <br><br>I have been in a storm of the sun <br>Basking, senseless to what I've become <br>A fool to worship just light <br>When after all, it follows night <br><br>I've been outside myself for so long <br>Any feeling I had is close to gone <br>I've been outside myself for so long <br>So long <br><br>I've been outside myself for so long <br>Any feeling I had is close to gone <br>I've been outside myself for so long]]></content><category term="K.d. lang" label="K.d. lang"/><category term="Outside Myself" label="Outside Myself"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Season_of_Hollow_Soul/</id><title>K.d. lang - Season of Hollow Soul - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:28:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:28:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Season_of_Hollow_Soul/" title="K.d. lang - Season of Hollow Soul - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Keen to the shifting of wind <br>I bend to it blind <br>To rid these kisses of sin <br>That must stay behind <br><br>Sour the fruit of neglect <br>The core of my doubt <br>Deprived are my veins you infect <br>With or without <br><br>Fate must have a reason <br>Why else endure the season <br>Of hollow soul <br>The ground on which we leave on <br>How strangely fuels the season <br>Of hollow soul hollow soul <br><br>Seed of uprooted chance <br>are grains of goodbye <br>Waving boughs so slowly dance <br>Questioning why <br><br>Fate must have a reason <br>Why else endure the season <br>Of hollow soul <br>The ground on which we leave on <br>How strangely fuels the season <br>Of hollow soul <br>La la la la <br>Fate must have a reason <br>Why else endure the season <br>Of hollow soul hollow soul <br><br>Fate must have a reason <br>Why else endure the season <br>Of hollow soul <br>La la la la <br>Fate must have a reason <br>Why else endure the season <br>Of hollow soul <br>La la la la <br>Fate must have a reason <br>Why else endure the season <br>Of hollow soul hollow soul]]></content><category term="K.d. lang" label="K.d. lang"/><category term="Season of Hollow Soul" label="Season of Hollow Soul"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Still_Thrives_This_Love/</id><title>K.d. lang - Still Thrives This Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T23:28:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T23:28:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kd_lang/Still_Thrives_This_Love/" title="K.d. lang - Still Thrives This Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I often wonder <br>Is it so <br>All I am holding <br>Wants let go <br>How could I manage <br>I don't know <br><br>I often question <br>Is it so <br>Life's contradictions <br>Tend to grow <br>Spawning the choices <br>And the woe <br><br>But, still somehow thrives this love <br>Which I pray I'm worthy of <br>Still somehow thrives this love <br><br>I often wonder <br>Is it so <br>The lessons of patience <br>Are learned slow <br>And earnings of labour <br>May never show <br><br>But, still somehow thrives this love <br>Which I pray I'm worthy of <br>Still somehow thrives this love]]></content><category term="K.d. lang" label="K.d. lang"/><category term="Still Thrives This Love" label="Still Thrives This Love"/></entry></feed>