<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:10:21+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김제경/틀림없이/</id><title>김제경 - 틀림없이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:49:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:49:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A0%9C%EA%B2%BD/%ED%8B%80%EB%A6%BC%EC%97%86%EC%9D%B4/" title="김제경 - 틀림없이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무것도 할 수 없고 <br>보잘것없는 존재라 생각했어 <br>한치 앞조차 보이지 않고 <br>끝도 없는 쓸쓸한 그곳에서 <br>그 어둠 속에 어디에선가 <br>희미하게 들리는 목소리가 <br>틀림없이 걷다 보면 <br>언젠가는 빛을 볼 거라고 <br>틀림없이 오 틀림없이 <br>오 그대여 주저앉지 마라 <br>오 그대여 쓰러지지 말아 <br>혼자인 것 같아 <br>외롭고 힘들겠지만 <br>걱정하지마 곁에 있을게 <br>틀림없이 걷다 보면 <br>언젠가는 빛을 볼 거라고 <br>틀림없이 걷다 보면 <br>언젠가는 빛을 볼 거라고 <br>틀림없이 오 틀림없이 <br>오 그대여 주저앉지 마라 <br>오 그대여 쓰러지지 말아 <br>혼자인 것 같아 <br>외롭고 힘들겠지만 <br>걱정하지마 곁에 있을게 <br>쓰러지지 말아 <br>혼자인 것 같아 <br>외롭고 힘들겠지만 <br>걱정하지마 곁에 있을게 <br>]]></content><category term="김제경" label="김제경"/><category term="틀림없이" label="틀림없이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김제경/So_High/</id><title>김제경 - So High - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:49:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:49:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A0%9C%EA%B2%BD/So_High/" title="김제경 - So High - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[먹먹하게 모든 게 <br>멈춘 듯이 그렇게 <br>당연한 것처럼 <br>내 모든 것 가라앉힌 채로 <br>거짓으로 내 마음 <br>움켜쥐고 있지만 <br>흔들려져 버린 물결처럼 <br>부서져만 가네 <br>so high so high so high <br>so high so high so high <br>아무 일도 없을 거야 <br>먹먹하게 모든 게 <br>멈춘 듯이 그렇게 <br>당연한 것처럼 <br>내 모든 것 가라앉힌 채로 <br>so high so high so high <br>so high so high so high <br>so high so high so high <br>so high so high so high <br>아무리 원한다 해도 <br>아무리 잡으려 해도 <br>아무 일 없을 거라고 <br>아무리 원한다 해도 <br>아무리 잡으려 해도 <br>아무리 원한다 해도 <br>아무리 잡으려 해도 <br>아무 일 없을 거라고 <br>아무리 원한다 해도 <br>아무리 잡으려 해도 <br>아무 일도 없을 거야 <br>먹먹하게 모든 게 <br>멈춘 듯이 그렇게 <br>]]></content><category term="김제경" label="김제경"/><category term="So High" label="So High"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fareoh/Illegal_Feat_Katelyn_Tarver/</id><title>Fareoh - Illegal (Feat. Katelyn Tarver) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:49:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:49:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fareoh/Illegal_Feat_Katelyn_Tarver/" title="Fareoh - Illegal (Feat. Katelyn Tarver) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Crashing, taking me under <br>Can't help but wonder <br>Why I buy the lies you sell <br>Take me higher <br>Faster and louder <br>Losing all my power <br>I don't even know myself <br><br>The more I get, the more I want <br>The more I know, the more I don't <br>The night is young and love is blind <br>And I've already closed my eyes <br><br>I don't wanna need you <br>But here I am, right at your door <br>It feels so illegal <br>I wonder why my heart wants more <br>Of your loving, hey! <br><br>Madness, tell them I've gone wild <br>Know looking back now <br>Sold out, I don't care at all <br>It's the moonlight <br>Fast cars and dark nights <br>Got me feeling so right <br>So nice, we could have it all <br><br>The more I get, the more I want <br>The more I know, the more I don't <br>The night is young, and love is blind <br>And I've already closed my eyes <br><br>I don't wanna need you <br>But here I am, right at your door <br>It feels so illegal <br>I wonder why my heart wants more <br>Of your loving, hey! <br><br>So give me more <br>More of your love <br>Can't get enough <br>'Nough of your love <br>So give me more <br>More of your life <br>Can't get enough <br>'Nough of your love <br><br>It feels so illegal <br>Wonder why my heart wants more]]></content><category term="Fareoh" label="Fareoh"/><category term="Illegal (Feat. Katelyn Tarver)" label="Illegal (Feat. Katelyn Tarver)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정슬기/내게_다가와/</id><title>정슬기 - 내게 다가와 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:50:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:50:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%8A%AC%EA%B8%B0/%EB%82%B4%EA%B2%8C_%EB%8B%A4%EA%B0%80%EC%99%80/" title="정슬기 - 내게 다가와 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내게 다가와 속삭여요 <br>괜찮을거야 힘을 줘요 <br>혹시나 아파서 아파서 울면 <br>안아줄래요 사랑으로 <br>하지 못한 말이 하고 싶은 말이 <br>너무 많이 남아서 <br>속이 닳아서 쓰린 건가봐 <br>속삭이며 말한 사랑한단 말들이 <br>바람 따라 전해지기를 <br>그대도 나와 같은 거죠 <br>괜찮을거야 함께라면 <br>혹시나 아파서 아파서 울면 <br>안아줄게요 사랑으로 <br>하지 못한 말이 하고 싶은 말이 <br>너무 많이 남아서 <br>속이 닳아서 쓰린 건가봐 <br>속삭이며 말한 사랑한단 말들이 <br>바람 따라 전해지기를 <br>사랑은 다 그래 사랑이 다 그래 <br>하지 못한 말들이 <br>속에 남아서 쓰린 거니까 <br>큰소리로 말해 사랑한단 말들이 <br>바람 따라 전해지기를 <br>]]></content><category term="정슬기" label="정슬기"/><category term="내게 다가와" label="내게 다가와"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제이디/Feel_It_Feat_기린/</id><title>제이디 - Feel It (Feat. 기린) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:50:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:50:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%EB%94%94/Feel_It_Feat_%EA%B8%B0%EB%A6%B0/" title="제이디 - Feel It (Feat. 기린) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[don't worry <br>nobody <br>괜찮아 <br>더가까이 느껴봐 <br>stay back <br>stay back <br>더이상 <br>뒷걸음 치지마 <br>눈빛 <br>몸짓 <br>니발끝 부터 너를 안을게 <br>두려워 하지말고 <br>두눈을 질끈감고 <br>내 입술을 느껴봐 <br>다가와 점점 <br>oh body to body <br>이밤이 다가도록 나와 부딪쳐봐 <br>사랑에 빠져버린 오늘밤 우린 <br>oh my my <br>feel it <br>don't stop <br>이것봐 너도날 원하잖아 <br>살며시 내게 안겨 <br>허리를 더 감싸줄래 <br>오 오 워우워 <br>몇번 눈이 마주쳤던 <br>사소한 핑계로 인해서 <br>지금 우리처럼 <br>끌어안고 있기도해 <br>신보다 더 먼저 믿게 된 <br>천사의 존재 <br>오늘 꿈엔 같이 구름 위를 <br>걷기로해 <br>과거는 잊기로해 다 믿기로해 <br>so we now take it away <br>다가와 점점 <br>oh body to body <br>이밤이 다가도록 나와 부딪쳐봐 <br>사랑에 빠져버린 오늘밤 우린 <br>oh my my <br>이대로 점점 <br>oh body to body <br>조금 더 니품안에서 잠들고싶어 <br>사르르 하얀밤의 너와 단 둘이 <br>all night long <br>오늘밤 매일밤 <br>달이져도 나는 <br>너를 느끼고싶어 <br>더 가까이 조금 더 가까이 <br>이밤이 지나도 <br>넌 내곁에 머물러줘 <br>다가와 점점 <br>oh body to body <br>이밤이 다가도록 나와 부딪쳐봐 <br>사랑에 빠져버린 오늘밤 우린 <br>oh my my <br>이대로 점점 <br>oh body to body <br>조금 더 니품안에서 잠들고싶어 <br>사르르 하얀밤의 너와 단 둘이 <br>all night long <br>feel it <br>all night tonight babe <br>feel it <br>all night tonight bebe <br>feel it <br>all night tonight babe <br>feel it <br>all night tonight bebe <br>feel it <br>all night tonight babe <br>feel it <br>all night tonight bebe <br>feel it <br>all night tonight babe <br>feel it <br>all night tonight bebe <br>]]></content><category term="제이디" label="제이디"/><category term="Feel It (Feat. 기린)" label="Feel It (Feat. 기린)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더_이스트라이트_TheEastLight/나는_나/</id><title>더 이스트라이트 (TheEastLight.) - 나는 나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:50:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:50:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94_%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%ED%8A%B8_TheEastLight/%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%82%98/" title="더 이스트라이트 (TheEastLight.) - 나는 나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아직도 난 꿈을 꾸고 있지만 <br>아무도 들어주지 않아 <br>초라한 내 자신을 감추려고 <br>오늘도 허세를 부린다 <br>나의 불안한 미래가 <br>나의 숨통을 조여 <br>여기가 어딘지 난 몰라 <br>나를 조롱하듯 비웃는 <br>저 많은 사람들 <br>어떻게 감당을 할까 <br>다 부셔버리자 <br>다 부셔버려라 <br>내일의 두려움의 벽을 <br>더 소리지르자 <br>더 소리질러라 <br>내가 더 강해질때까지 <br>오늘도 난 큰소리를 치지만 <br>아무도 들어주지 않아 <br>관심없는 일들의 강요만이 <br>오늘도 내게 고함친다 <br>내가 가고싶은 길을 <br>따라 나는 갈거야 <br>아무도 나를 막지못해 <br>내가 가는길이 옳다고 <br>난 믿고있지만 <br>사실 난 정말 두려워 <br>다 부셔버리자 <br>다 부셔버려라 <br>내일의 두려움의 벽을 <br>더 소리지르자 <br>더 소리질러라 <br>내 삶의 주인공은 나야 <br>나는 달려 갈거야 <br>난 내뜻대로 갈거야 <br>난 나는 나야 나의 길을 가 <br>나는 찾아갈거야 <br>난 내맘대로 갈거야 <br>난 나는 나야 나의 길을 가 <br>다 부셔버리자 <br>다 부셔버려라 <br>내일의 두려움의 벽을 <br>더 소리지르자 <br>더 소리질러라 <br>내 삶의 주인공은 나야 <br>]]></content><category term="더 이스트라이트 (TheEastLight.)" label="더 이스트라이트 (TheEastLight.)"/><category term="나는 나" label="나는 나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더_이스트라이트_TheEastLight/holla_홀라/</id><title>더 이스트라이트 (TheEastLight.) - holla (홀라) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:50:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:50:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94_%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%ED%8A%B8_TheEastLight/holla_%ED%99%80%EB%9D%BC/" title="더 이스트라이트 (TheEastLight.) - holla (홀라) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘도 또 눈을 뜨면 엄만 말하지 <br>이거 해라 저거 해라 꽉 찬 스케줄 <br>아침부터 저녁까지 쳇바퀴 돌 듯 <br>왔다 갔다 오락가락 배워야 한데 <br>Everybody Say Yeah Yeah <br>Everybody Say Holla Holla <br>Everybody Say <br>뭐든 잘해야 해 <br>Everybody Say Yeah Yeah <br>Everybody Say Holla Holla <br>Everybody Say <br>나의 미랠 위해 <br>친구도 없고 시간도 없고 <br>썰렁한 놀이터 <br>가라 하면 가고 오라 하면 <br>오고 우리는 똑같아 <br>시키면 해라 시키면 하지 뭐 <br>어차피 친구도 없는 <br>외톨이들뿐 <br>Everybody Say Yeah Yeah <br>Everybody Say Holla Holla <br>Everybody Say <br>뭐든 잘해야 해 <br>Everybody Say Yeah Yeah <br>Everybody Say Holla Holla <br>Everybody Say <br>나의 미랠 위해 <br>하지만 난 이제 굴렐 벗어나 Go away <br>내가 잘하는 걸 할거야 Go away <br>모두 같은 곳을 향해가지만 <br>난 나의 꿈을 찾아서 떠나 Oh <br>나는 아직 어린데 <br>왜 어른들은 강요를 할까 <br>다 같은 꿈 다 같은 길로 <br>우릴 가라고 하지 <br>나는 아직 어려서 <br>난 내가 하고픈 걸 잘 몰라 <br>난 할거야 난 내가 <br>하고 싶은 일을 할 거야 <br>Everybody Say Yeah Yeah <br>Everybody Say Holla Holla <br>Everybody Say <br>뭐든 잘해야 해 <br>Everybody Say Yeah Yeah <br>Everybody Say Holla Holla <br>Everybody Say <br>나의 미랠 위해 <br>Oh 난 이제 간다 날 위해 간다 <br>날 찾으러 간다 Yeah <br>난 뛰어간다 난 날아간다 <br>나의 꿈으로 간다 Go Go <br>난 이제 간다 날 위해 간다 <br>날 찾으러 간다 Yeah <br>난 뛰어간다 난 날아간다 <br>나의 미래로 간다 Go Go <br>Everybody Say Yeah Yeah Yeah <br>Holla Holla Holla Holla <br>모두 외쳐라 다 나와 함께 <br>소리 높여 외쳐라 <br>Yeah Yeah Yeah <br>Holla Holla Holla Holla <br>모두 부르자 다 나와 함께 <br>이 노래를 부르자 <br>Yeah Yeah Yeah <br>Holla Holla Holla Holla <br>Yeah Yeah Yeah <br>Holla Holla Holla Holla <br>]]></content><category term="더 이스트라이트 (TheEastLight.)" label="더 이스트라이트 (TheEastLight.)"/><category term="holla (홀라)" label="holla (홀라)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/청아/두려움_반_설레임/</id><title>청아 - 두려움 반 설레임 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:51:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:51:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%AD%EC%95%84/%EB%91%90%EB%A0%A4%EC%9B%80_%EB%B0%98_%EC%84%A4%EB%A0%88%EC%9E%84/" title="청아 - 두려움 반 설레임 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 하늘 참 맑아 <br>겨울 지나 바로 여름이네 <br>시간 참 빨라 봄을 느끼기도 전에 <br>벌써 summer <br>때론 나에게만 안 좋은 일이 <br>생기는 것 같은 느낌을 <br>받을 때가 있어 <br>그럴 땐 무척 혼자인 것 같지만 <br>그래도 이젠 괜찮아 <br>솔직히 슬프고 힘들긴 해 <br>그치만 난 혼자가 아니니까 <br>괜찮아라고 말할래 <br>세상 속 수많은 일들 <br>때론 이해할 수가 없지 <br>매일매일이 두려움 반 설렘이야 <br>어머 벌써 반오십이네 <br>다들 어른이라고 말하네 나에게 <br>부담되긴 하지만 지금이 난 좋아 <br>누군가에게 기쁨이 <br>될 수 있다는 기대 속에 <br>난 괜찮아 이젠 괜찮아 <br>솔직히 슬프고 힘들긴 해 <br>그치만 난 혼자가 아니니까 <br>괜찮아라고 말할래 <br>I'm okay not okay <br>I'm okay not okay <br>I'm okay not okay <br>I'm okay not okay <br>괜찮아 괜찮아 내가 있어 <br>괜찮아 괜찮아 내가 있잖아 <br>더 이상 두려워하지마 <br>내가 항상 너와 함께 하니까 <br>걱정마 <br>난 괜찮아 <br>]]></content><category term="청아" label="청아"/><category term="두려움 반 설레임" label="두려움 반 설레임"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Orwells/They_Put_A_Body_In_The_Bayou/</id><title>The Orwells - They Put A Body In The Bayou - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Orwells/They_Put_A_Body_In_The_Bayou/" title="The Orwells - They Put A Body In The Bayou - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They never came to town <br>He really gets me down <br>Take off that plastic crown <br>Coke nose and a pretty sound <br><br>Alright make it quick <br>Good songs make you rich <br>That feelin' it'll pass <br>Good boys come in last <br>Bad girl by my side <br>Poppin' pills on the fly <br>Cold grave when I die <br><br>I came by to see you <br>I just had to know <br>Who put the body in the bayou <br>Who left the tracks on the road <br><br>Told me act your age <br>That's why she's underage <br>Said her papa hates the Federales and <br>When he drinks too much he smacks her face <br><br>Alright make it quick <br>Good songs make you rich <br>That feelin' it'll pass <br>Good boys come in last <br>Bad girl by my side <br>Poppin' pills on the fly <br>Cold grave when I die <br><br>I came by to see you <br>I just had to know <br>Who put the body in the bayou <br>Who left the tracks on the road <br><br>I came by to see you <br>I just had to know <br>Who put the body in the bayou <br>Who left the tracks on the road]]></content><category term="The Orwells" label="The Orwells"/><category term="They Put A Body In The Bayou" label="They Put A Body In The Bayou"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강타_KANGTA/뚜뚜루_Marry_You_Feat_영준_Of_Brown_Eyed_Soul/</id><title>강타 (KANGTA) - 뚜뚜루 (Marry You) (Feat. 영준 Of Brown Eyed Soul) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%ED%83%80_KANGTA/%EB%9A%9C%EB%9A%9C%EB%A3%A8_Marry_You_Feat_%EC%98%81%EC%A4%80_Of_Brown_Eyed_Soul/" title="강타 (KANGTA) - 뚜뚜루 (Marry You) (Feat. 영준 Of Brown Eyed Soul) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[저기 멀리 그대가 보여 <br>다가서는 걸음이 떨려 <br>가벼운 인사에 오늘따라 내 맘은 흔들 <br>어디 선지 자꾸 들려오는 조그만 <br>어린아이의 웃음소리에 <br>또 한번 맘이 흔들 이제 <br>늦은 밤 혼자서 집으로 돌아오는 길이 <br>자꾸만 싫어져 나도 변하는 걸까 <br>우리와 닮아서 사랑스런 아이와 <br>그대 손을 꼭 잡고서 걷고만 싶은 밤 <br>우리 애는 나를 쏙 닮았네 어쩌네 <br>친구 녀석의 긴긴 자랑에 <br>괜시리 맘이 쓸쓸 이제 <br>늦은 밤 혼자서 집으로 돌아오는 길이 <br>자꾸만 싫어져 나도 변하는 걸까 <br>우리와 닮아서 사랑스런 아이와 <br>그대 손을 꼭 잡고서 걷고만 싶은 밤 <br>휴일 아침 들려오는 재잘대는 소리는 <br>눈을 뜨기도 전에 <br>나의 입가에 미소를 짓게 해 <br>누군가 만나서 나보다 사랑하는 일이 <br>너무나 놀라워 나는 변했으니까 <br>그대를 닮아서 사랑스런 아이와 <br>그댈 품에 꼭 안고서 말하고 싶은 밤 <br>늦은 밤 혼자서 집으로 돌아오는 길이 <br>자꾸만 싫어져 나도 변하는 걸까 <br>우리와 닮아서 사랑스런 아이와 <br>그대 손을 꼭 잡고서 걷고만 싶은 밤 <br>입을 맞추고서 잠들고 싶은 밤 <br>이 밤 이 밤 <br>]]></content><category term="강타 (KANGTA)" label="강타 (KANGTA)"/><category term="뚜뚜루 (Marry You) (Feat. 영준 Of Brown Eyed Soul)" label="뚜뚜루 (Marry You) (Feat. 영준 Of Brown Eyed Soul)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강타_KANGTA/사랑이_오네요_Love_Is_Coming/</id><title>강타 (KANGTA) - 사랑이 오네요 (Love Is Coming) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%ED%83%80_KANGTA/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4_%EC%98%A4%EB%84%A4%EC%9A%94_Love_Is_Coming/" title="강타 (KANGTA) - 사랑이 오네요 (Love Is Coming) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이른 아침 햇살에 나 눈을 뜨면 <br>조금은 달라진 나를 발견하죠 <br>매일 입던 셔츠 빚지 않던 머리 <br>오늘은 어제와 다르죠 <br>할 일 없이 티비 보던 주말에도 <br>매일같이 따분했던 평일에도 <br>널 만날 생각에 거울 앞에 앉아 <br>멋쩍은 웃음만 짓는 나 <br>사랑이 오네요 사랑이 다가오네요 <br>다시는 오지 않을 것만 같던 내 마음에 <br>사랑이 오네요 설레임에 터질 것 같은 <br>나에게도 사랑이 오네요 <br>할일없이 바라보던 거리에도 <br>매일같이 걷곤 했던 공원에도 <br>널 만날 것 같아 걸음을 늦추며 <br>멋쩍은 웃음만 짓는 나 <br>사랑이 오네요 사랑이 다가오네요 <br>다시는 오지 않을 것만 같던 내 마음에 <br>사랑이 오네요 설레임에 터질 것 같은 <br>나에게도 사랑이 오네요 <br>그대 때문에 내가 이래 <br>알면 알수록 더욱더 좋아질 것 같은데 <br>조금씩 더 조금씩 나 <br>그대를 닮아가고 있는데 <br>내 곁에 그대를 <br>사랑이 오네요 사랑이 다가오네요 <br>다시는 오지 않을 것만 같던 내 마음에 <br>사랑이 오네요 설레임에 터질 것 같은 <br>나에게도 사랑이 오네요 <br>]]></content><category term="강타 (KANGTA)" label="강타 (KANGTA)"/><category term="사랑이 오네요 (Love Is Coming)" label="사랑이 오네요 (Love Is Coming)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강타_KANGTA/Calling_Out_For_You/</id><title>강타 (KANGTA) - Calling Out For You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%ED%83%80_KANGTA/Calling_Out_For_You/" title="강타 (KANGTA) - Calling Out For You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh yeah 걸음까지 <br>절대 서두르지 않아 넌 Oh <br>잠시 멈춰 <br>휘파람 같은 향기를 내쉬어 <br>비처럼 넌 내려와 <br>내 맘을 다 <br>빈틈 없이 넌 가득 적시니까 <br>널 위해서 <br>움직여 난 <br>힘들어도 I’ll Try Try Try Try <br>별빛 스며 든 스며 든 체온과 <br>달콤한 목소리가 <br>Keep me calling out for you <br>매일 너만을 너만을 향해서 <br>달리는 내 시계가 <br>Keep me calling out for you <br>어두워질수록 눈부셔 더 눈부셔 <br>허전했던 내 방을 밝힌 네 빛이 <br>온통 채워 낸 채워 낸 이 밤과 <br>너의 그 몸짓들 다 <br>Keep me calling out for you <br>깊이 고민 <br>해도 좋아 신중하게 더 <br>들이쉬어 <br>몸에 밴 습관 같은 내 여유 <br>치열한 저 문 밖과 <br>머릿속과 <br>오늘의 나를 있게 한 모든 것 <br>날아와 봐 <br>꼭 네게 난 <br>보여 줄게 my pride pride pride pride <br>별빛 스며 든 스며 든 체온과 <br>달콤한 목소리가 <br>Keep me calling out for you <br>매일 너만을 너만을 향해서 <br>달리는 내 시계가 <br>Keep me calling out for you <br>어두워질수록 눈부셔 더 눈부셔 <br>허전했던 내 방을 밝힌 네 빛이 <br>온통 채워 낸 채워 낸 이 밤과 <br>너의 그 몸짓들 다 <br>Keep me calling out for you <br>Keep me calling keep me calling for you <br>Keep me calling keep me calling for you <br>You out Keep me calling out for you <br>아침이 드리워 네 뺨을 어루만져 <br>또 새로운 날이 시작된 시간도 <br>내게 날아든 날아든 너를 난 <br>보낼 수 없으니까 <br>Keep me calling out for you <br>]]></content><category term="강타 (KANGTA)" label="강타 (KANGTA)"/><category term="Calling Out For You" label="Calling Out For You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강타_KANGTA/단골식당_Diner/</id><title>강타 (KANGTA) - 단골식당 (Diner) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%ED%83%80_KANGTA/%EB%8B%A8%EA%B3%A8%EC%8B%9D%EB%8B%B9_Diner/" title="강타 (KANGTA) - 단골식당 (Diner) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넥타이 풀고 퇴근하는 길 <br>무심코 들어선 익숙한 이 식당 <br>사람들과 주고받는 소주잔 속에 <br>하루의 고단함이 무뎌질 때쯤 <br>우연히 발견한 식당 벽면에 <br>오래전 우리가 적어놨던 낙서 <br>또박또박 적혀있는 오래된 날짜 <br>오그라드는 말들에 조용히 웃음 짓다가 <br>그때는 참 그랬었는데 <br>우리 추억 모두 두려워 <br>이곳은 올 수도 없었는데 <br>이젠 기억조차 희미해진 <br>빛바랜 낙설 보고야 니가 떠올라 <br>너의 기억 속에 그때의 나는 <br>어떤 모습으로 살고 있을까 <br>삶의 무게에 지친 <br>지금의 내 모습관 다르겠지 <br>취해가는 내 모습 위로 <br>그때 기억들이 자꾸 살아나 <br>붉어지는 내 얼굴 위로 <br>눈물이 흐르나 봐 <br>정말 많이 궁금했는데 보고 싶었는데 <br>그렇게 널 보낸 내가 다 미웠는데 <br>하루하루 쌓인 시간 속에 그런 <br>내 모습조차도 희미해졌나 봐 <br>나의 기억 속에 그때의 너는 <br>어떤 모습으로 살고 있을까 <br>이렇게 쉽게 널 잊어버린 <br>내 모습이 원망돼서 <br>너를 보냈던 그날보다 <br>많이 울고 울었던 그때보다 <br>지금의 내 모습이 <br>훨씬 슬프고 쓸쓸해져 <br>너도 가끔은 이곳에 찾아오니 <br>아니면 나보다 훨씬 더 먼저 편해졌을까 <br>그때 헤어진 우리도 <br>한참을 힘겹던 내 모습도 <br>결국엔 오늘에서야 우리 이별 인건 가봐 <br>너의 기억 속에 그때의 나는 <br>어떤 모습으로 살고 있을까 <br>삶의 무게에 지친 <br>지금의 내 모습관 다르겠지 <br>취해가는 내 모습 위로 <br>그때 기억들이 자꾸 살아나 <br>붉어지는 내 얼굴 위로 <br>눈물이 흐르나 봐 <br>]]></content><category term="강타 (KANGTA)" label="강타 (KANGTA)"/><category term="단골식당 (Diner)" label="단골식당 (Diner)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강타_KANGTA/말했더라면_If_I_Told_Ya/</id><title>강타 (KANGTA) - 말했더라면 (If I Told Ya) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%ED%83%80_KANGTA/%EB%A7%90%ED%96%88%EB%8D%94%EB%9D%BC%EB%A9%B4_If_I_Told_Ya/" title="강타 (KANGTA) - 말했더라면 (If I Told Ya) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[늘 기다려 달라고 했어 <br>난 좀 느린 사람이라서 <br>시간이 더 필요해 <br>가줄래 <br>네게 상처만 줬던 <br>이제야 I'm sorry 용서 안되겠지 <br>이제야 뚜렷해져 <br>오늘 내 앞의 시간이 끝이란 걸 <br>If I told ya 여기 머물게 <br>If I told ya 허락해줄래 <br>조금만 더 먼저 말했더라면 <br>If I told ya 난 달라졌어 <br>If I told ya 포기하지 마 <br>이런 말할 자격 있었을 텐데 <br>이별인 걸까 You and I <br>그런 말하지 마 Goodbye <br>늘 원해왔던 <br>사람이 될게 <br>조금 더 먼저 너에게 <br>말해줬더라면 <br>네 손에 잡히지 않는 힘든 사람이라 <br>이런 날 이해하는 게 불가능했겠지 <br>항상 날아 가려만 <br>떠나려만 <br>했던 바보였기에 <br>비겁한 I'm sorry 용서 안되겠지 <br>나의 끝은 너인데 <br>어리석었던 나라서 몰랐던 걸 <br>If I told ya 여기 머물게 <br>If I told ya 허락해줄래 <br>조금만 더 먼저 말했더라면 <br>If I told ya 난 달라졌어 <br>If I told ya 포기하지 마 <br>이런 말할 자격 있었을 텐데 <br>이별인 걸까 You and I <br>그런 말하지 마 Goodbye <br>늘 원해왔던 <br>사람이 될게 <br>조금 더 먼저 너에게 <br>말해줬더라면 <br>뒤돌아 보게 돼 <br>바보 같지 그래 <br>왜 사람들은 모두 지난 후에야 후회할까 <br>차라리 너를 미워할 수 있다면 <br>쉬웠을까 <br>이젠 알아 <br>널 사랑해 <br>말했더라면 <br>If I told ya 여기 머물게 <br>If I told ya 허락해줄래 <br>조금만 더 먼저 말했더라면 <br>If I told ya 난 달라졌어 <br>If I told ya 포기하지 마 <br>이런 말할 자격 있었을 텐데 <br>이별인 걸까 You and I <br>그런 말 하지마 Goodbye <br>늘 원해왔던 <br>사람이 될게 <br>조금 더 먼저 너에게 <br>말해줬 말했더라면 <br>]]></content><category term="강타 (KANGTA)" label="강타 (KANGTA)"/><category term="말했더라면 (If I Told Ya)" label="말했더라면 (If I Told Ya)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양다일/그땐_알_수_없었던_것_Feat_백지웅/</id><title>양다일 - 그땐 알 수 없었던 것 (Feat. 백지웅) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EB%8B%A4%EC%9D%BC/%EA%B7%B8%EB%95%90_%EC%95%8C_%EC%88%98_%EC%97%86%EC%97%88%EB%8D%98_%EA%B2%83_Feat_%EB%B0%B1%EC%A7%80%EC%9B%85/" title="양다일 - 그땐 알 수 없었던 것 (Feat. 백지웅) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[매일 아침에는 <br>무뎌진 내 모든 기억이 <br>서두르듯 날 깨우고 <br>딱히 별 볼일 없어도 <br>나 혼자서 정신 없는 <br>긴 하루를 돌아보면 <br>어느새 하나 둘씩 <br>멀어져 간 조금은 <br>아팠던 내 지난 날들 <br>함께 올 수는 없었던 걸까 <br>그땐 알 수 없었던 것 <br>멀어질 줄 몰랐던 때 <br>가끔 미워도 마냥 좋았던 <br>조금은 혼자이고 싶었던 <br>날들은 어디로 <br>이제 더는 돌아갈 수 <br>없음에 오늘은 <br>멀어질 줄 몰랐음에 <br>미안하단 한마디를 전하고 <br>조금도 혼자이기는 싫다고 <br>서투른 말들을 <br>이제서야 알 것 같은데 <br>귀찮았던 건 맞아 <br>솔직히 나도 그땐 어렸으니까 <br>한두 번을 미루다 보니 <br>다 잊은 듯이 대할 순 없었고 <br>더 많은 것이 쌓인 것 같아서 <br>미안한 마음도 잊혀져 <br>남은 건 내 서운함이 <br>더 커졌단 것 <br>그땐 알 수 없었던 것 <br>멀어질 줄 몰랐던 때 <br>가끔 미워도 마냥 좋았던 <br>조금은 혼자이고 싶었던 <br>날들은 어디로 <br>이제 더는 돌아갈 수 <br>없음에 오늘은 <br>멀어질 줄 몰랐음에 <br>미안하단 한마디를 전하고 <br>조금도 혼자이기는 싫다고 <br>서투른 말들을 <br>이제서야 알 것 같은데 <br>멀어질 줄 몰랐어 나 <br>가끔씩 지쳐 외로울 때면 <br>함께였을 때 좋았었다고 <br>말들을 떠올려 <br>이제 더는 돌아갈 수 <br>없겠지 오늘도 <br>멀어진 이유를 찾고 <br>비슷한 일들에 다시 차이면 <br>그때로 돌아갈 수는 없다고 <br>서투른 사람들 <br>이제서야 알 것 같은데 <br>]]></content><category term="양다일" label="양다일"/><category term="그땐 알 수 없었던 것 (Feat. 백지웅)" label="그땐 알 수 없었던 것 (Feat. 백지웅)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양다일/나를_깨워주는/</id><title>양다일 - 나를 깨워주는 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EB%8B%A4%EC%9D%BC/%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EA%B9%A8%EC%9B%8C%EC%A3%BC%EB%8A%94/" title="양다일 - 나를 깨워주는 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나를 깨우듯 속삭이며 <br>웃는 너를 볼 때면 <br>피곤했던 날들이 <br>비로소 지나감을 느끼고 <br>날 일깨우는 한마디로 <br>다시 너를 볼 때면 <br>잠시 지나갔던 날들을 <br>돌아보게 만들고 <br>이젠 새로운 누군가에게 <br>그런 사람이 되었을 너 <br>왜 이제서야 네가 그리워서 <br>매일 아침 눈을 뜰까 <br>왜 너는 나를 떠나고 나서도 <br>나를 깨워주는 걸까 <br>한 때는 오랜 습관 탓에 <br>너무 버거웠는데 <br>나를 잃어가는 줄 알았는데 <br>홀로 남아 외로운 건지 <br>이젠 네가 없이도 <br>지난 나를 돌아보려 하곤 해 <br>이젠 나 아닌 누군가에게 <br>그런 사람이 되었겠지 <br>왜 이제서야 네가 그리워서 <br>매일 같이 눈을 뜰까 <br>왜 너는 나를 떠나고 나서도 <br>날 일깨워주는 걸까 <br>지나간 날들에 <br>늘 아쉬움만 남아 <br>아무것도 남은게 없던 내 맘에 <br>무뎌졌던 감정들이 <br>늦은 후회를 할때면 <br>이런 나를 알고 바라봐주던 <br>그때의 네가 그리워 <br>왜 이제서야 네가 그리워서 <br>매일 아침 눈을 뜰까 <br>왜 너는 나를 떠나고 나서도 <br>나를 깨워주는 걸까 <br>왜 이제서야 네가 그리워서 <br>매일 같이 눈을 뜰까 <br>왜 너는 나를 떠나고 나서도 <br>날 일깨워주는 걸까 <br>]]></content><category term="양다일" label="양다일"/><category term="나를 깨워주는" label="나를 깨워주는"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양다일/떠나지마/</id><title>양다일 - 떠나지마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EB%8B%A4%EC%9D%BC/%EB%96%A0%EB%82%98%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88/" title="양다일 - 떠나지마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[처음관 다르다고 <br>내게 미안해하는 것도 <br>더는 아니라고 <br>많은게 달라졌다고 <br>걱정하지 말라며 <br>다시 잊혀질 거라고 <br>모두 같을 거라고 <br>왜 나만 힘든 거냐고 <br>나를 떠나지마 더는 말하지마 <br>꽤 많이 늦었지만 날 두고 가지마 <br>오랜 시간 오랜 감정에 <br>다 전하지 못한 말 <br>익숙해져 그랬었는지 되려 <br>상처받기 두려웠는지 늦은 <br>후회를 전한다면 <br>나를 떠나지마 더는 말하지마 <br>꽤 많이 늦었지만 날 두고 가지마 <br>woo woo woo woo <br>조급했던 처음 서툰 우리처럼 <br>잊혀졌던 맘 속에서 <br>날 버리고 떠나가지마 <br>나를 떠나지마 더는 말하지마 <br>돌이킬 순 없다 해도 <br>날 두고 가지마 <br>다시 설렐 순 없어도 돌아와줘 <br>나를 떠나지마 날 두고 가지마 <br>나를 떠나지마 <br>]]></content><category term="양다일" label="양다일"/><category term="떠나지마" label="떠나지마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양다일/우리_같이_The_Fault_In_Our_Stars/</id><title>양다일 - 우리, 같이 (The Fault In Our Stars) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EB%8B%A4%EC%9D%BC/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%B4_The_Fault_In_Our_Stars/" title="양다일 - 우리, 같이 (The Fault In Our Stars) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 같이 추워진 날이면 <br>우리 같이 조용한 바람에 <br>말도 없이 차가워진 <br>손을 잡지 <br>지쳐버린 감정에 <br>문득 널 바라보면 <br>어쩜 그리 <br>외로워 보이는지 <br>어찌 나와 같은지 <br>baby you <br>아직 날 사랑하는지 <br>괜히 불안한지 왜 이렇게 <br>woo <br>어느새 멀어진 것만 같은지 <br>왜 외로운 건지 또 말 없이 <br>woo <br>우린 마치 잊혀져 버린 <br>옛 상처같이 말도 없이 <br>서로를 바라보지도 않지 <br>지루한지 <br>언젠가 말했었던 <br>그때와 같지만 <br>누구의 탓도 아닌 걸 <br>baby <br>조금 변해버린 건 우리 <br>같이 <br>baby you <br>아직 날 사랑하는지 <br>괜히 불안한지 왜 이렇게 <br>woo <br>어느새 멀어진 것만 같은지 <br>왜 외로운 건지 또 말 없이 <br>woo <br>내게 처음 그랬던 것처럼 <br>아직까진 <br>우리 사랑이라 말해줘 <br>조금만 더 <br>baby you <br>아직 날 사랑하는지 <br>괜히 불안한지 왜 이렇게 <br>woo <br>어느새 멀어진 것만 같은지 <br>왜 외로운 건지 또 말 없이 <br>woo <br>]]></content><category term="양다일" label="양다일"/><category term="우리, 같이 (The Fault In Our Stars)" label="우리, 같이 (The Fault In Our Stars)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양다일/가만히_아파_Feat_강민희/</id><title>양다일 - 가만히 아파 (Feat. 강민희) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EB%8B%A4%EC%9D%BC/%EA%B0%80%EB%A7%8C%ED%9E%88_%EC%95%84%ED%8C%8C_Feat_%EA%B0%95%EB%AF%BC%ED%9D%AC/" title="양다일 - 가만히 아파 (Feat. 강민희) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 하루도 <br>꽤 길었는지 <br>아무 말 없이 <br>바라보기만 해도 <br>내 맘을 덮을 듯 <br>흐르는 너의 한숨에 <br>아려와 그저 널 <br>바라볼 수밖에 없다는게 <br>말하지 말아 <br>널 보고 있으면 <br>내가 다 알 순 없어도 <br>네 손을 잡고 있으면 <br>가만히 아파 괜히 아파 <br>oh no <br>내일 널 바라볼 땐 <br>조금 덜 아파하길 <br>생각보단 빠른 <br>아니 아픔보단 조금 <br>느린 것 같아 잊혀진다는 건 <br>행복할 시간조차 벅차 <br>무슨 말을 할지조차 <br>힘겹던 하루일 것 같아 <br>미안한 맘에 바라보기만 oh <br>아무 말 말아 <br>널 보고 있으면 <br>내게 다 전해지는게 <br>표현할 수도 없음에 <br>가만히 아파 그저 아파 <br>oh no <br>이 아픔이 지나면 <br>다시 웃을 수 있길 예 <br>우 워어어어 우 워어어어 <br>babe <br>혹 나 없이 어디선가 널 <br>울리진 않을까 <br>잠을 설치고 <br>속절없이 긴 밤을 지새면 <br>한결같이 baby <br>늘 곁에 있겠다고 <br>아무 걱정 말고 you <br>아무 말 말아 <br>널 보고 있으면 <br>내게 다 전해지는게 <br>네 손을 잡고 있으면 <br>가만히 아파 그저 아파 <br>oh no <br>이 아픔이 지나면 <br>다시 웃을 수 있길 <br>]]></content><category term="양다일" label="양다일"/><category term="가만히 아파 (Feat. 강민희)" label="가만히 아파 (Feat. 강민희)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/토마스_쿡/졸업/</id><title>토마스 쿡 - 졸업 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%86%A0%EB%A7%88%EC%8A%A4_%EC%BF%A1/%EC%A1%B8%EC%97%85/" title="토마스 쿡 - 졸업 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[도망치듯 달려가는 <br>숲 속에 잠이 드는 <br>다시 새롭게 태어나는 <br>난 그런 꿈을 꿨어 <br>불꽃처럼 타오르는 <br>영원히 함께하는 <br>너와 같은 그런 꿈을 꿨어 <br>난 그런 꿈을 꿨어 <br>우린 또 어디에서 <br>그 어떤 무엇이 되나 <br>다시 그때처럼 <br>서로 웃을 수 있을까 <br>불꽃처럼 타오르는 <br>영원히 함께하는 <br>너와 같은 그런 꿈을 꿨어 <br>난 그런 꿈을 꿨어 <br>우린 또 어디에서 <br>그 어떤 무엇이 되나 <br>다시 그때처럼 <br>서로 웃을 수 있을까 <br>도망치듯 달려가는 <br>숲 속에 잠이 드는 <br>다시 새롭게 태어나는 <br>난 그런 꿈을 꿨어 <br>다 벗어던지고 헤엄치는 <br>난 그런 꿈을 꿨어 <br>]]></content><category term="토마스 쿡" label="토마스 쿡"/><category term="졸업" label="졸업"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/토마스_쿡/별과_나_그리고_우리_사이/</id><title>토마스 쿡 - 별과 나 그리고 우리 사이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%86%A0%EB%A7%88%EC%8A%A4_%EC%BF%A1/%EB%B3%84%EA%B3%BC_%EB%82%98_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EA%B3%A0_%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EC%82%AC%EC%9D%B4/" title="토마스 쿡 - 별과 나 그리고 우리 사이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아주 잔잔한 <br>적도의 밤바다 <br>파도 한 점도 없는 <br>꿈결 같은 바다 <br>끝도 없는 <br>은빛 물결 위에 <br>달빛이 비치네 <br>사랑이 비쳐오네 <br>간다 우린 어디론가 <br>시간을 거슬러 <br>놓치기 싫은 이 순간 <br>이대로 멈췄으면 <br>한눈에 다 담을 수 없어서 <br>기억에 새겨놓은 <br>그날 밤 그 바다 <br>믿을 수 없던 수많은 별들 <br>넋을 잃고 바라보던 우리 둘 <br>커다란 우주 그 안의 우리 <br>아름다웠던 그때의 너와 나 <br>그저 멍하니 바라보다가 <br>아주 천천히 알 수 있었지 <br>느낄 수 있어 지금 이 순간 <br>별과 나 그리고 우리 둘 사이 <br>간다 우린 어디론가 <br>시간을 거슬러 <br>놓치기 싫은 이 순간 <br>이대로 멈췄으면 <br>믿을 수 없던 수많은 별들 <br>넋을 잃고 바라보던 우리 둘 <br>커다란 우주 그 안의 우리 <br>아름다웠던 그때의 너와 나 <br>그저 멍하니 바라보다가 <br>아주 천천히 알 수 있었지 <br>느낄 수 있어 지금 이 순간 <br>별과 나 그리고 우리 둘 사이 <br>믿을 수 없던 수많은 별들 <br>넋을 잃고 바라보던 우리 둘 <br>커다란 우주 그 안의 우리 <br>아름다웠던 그때의 너와 나 <br>그저 멍하니 바라보다가 <br>아주 천천히 알 수 있었지 <br>느낄 수 있어 지금 이 순간 <br>별과 나 그리고 우리 둘 사이 <br>]]></content><category term="토마스 쿡" label="토마스 쿡"/><category term="별과 나 그리고 우리 사이" label="별과 나 그리고 우리 사이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/토마스_쿡/둘만의_노래/</id><title>토마스 쿡 - 둘만의 노래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%86%A0%EB%A7%88%EC%8A%A4_%EC%BF%A1/%EB%91%98%EB%A7%8C%EC%9D%98_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="토마스 쿡 - 둘만의 노래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[빙빙빙 내 곁을 맴도는 <br>부드러운 너의 호기심 <br>넌 항상 그 어디에서든 <br>변치 않는 모습이 있어 <br>아는 사람도 부르는 사람도 <br>우리 둘뿐인 노래 <br>그 안에 웃고 있을 거야 <br>나와 영원히 <br>노래 속에 춤을 출 거야 <br>여전히 우린 사랑할 거야 <br>언제나 어떤 계절에나 <br>따뜻함을 잃지 않았던 <br>조용히 내 곁에 잠들던 <br>그 모습이 눈에 아련해 <br>아는 사람도 부르는 사람도 <br>우리 둘뿐인 노래 <br>그 안에 웃고 있을 거야 <br>나와 영원히 <br>노래 속에 춤을 출 거야 <br>여전히 우린 사랑할 거야 <br>그 안에 웃고 있을 거야 <br>나와 영원히 <br>노래 속에 춤을 출 거야 <br>여전히 우린 사랑할 거야 <br>그 안에 너랑 나랑 함께 할 거야 <br>잊지 마 사랑해 영원히 <br>]]></content><category term="토마스 쿡" label="토마스 쿡"/><category term="둘만의 노래" label="둘만의 노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/토마스_쿡/어둠의_왕/</id><title>토마스 쿡 - 어둠의 왕 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%86%A0%EB%A7%88%EC%8A%A4_%EC%BF%A1/%EC%96%B4%EB%91%A0%EC%9D%98_%EC%99%95/" title="토마스 쿡 - 어둠의 왕 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[문득 날 마주친 그들의 일상은 <br>웃고 있지 않았네 <br>사랑하는 사람들 곁에서 <br>소중한 친구를 틈에서 <br>문득 날 마주친 그들의 일상은 <br>웃고 있지 않았네 <br>뜨는 아침 해를 바라보며 <br>사랑하는 사람의 손을 잡고서 <br>아무도 없는 방안에 <br>용서를 빌고 있었지 <br>눈물이 방을 적시고 <br>머리에 왕관을 쓰고서 <br>웃고 있지 않았네 <br>문득 날 마주친 그들의 일상은 <br>웃고 있지 않았네 <br>심을 곳 없는 기름진 씨앗을 <br>양손에 가득 쥐고서 <br>아무도 없는 방안에 <br>용서를 빌고 있었지 <br>눈물이 방을 적시고 <br>머리에 왕관을 쓰고서 <br>웃고 있지 않았네 <br>웃고 있지 않았네 <br>웃고 있지 않았네 <br>]]></content><category term="토마스 쿡" label="토마스 쿡"/><category term="어둠의 왕" label="어둠의 왕"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/토마스_쿡/그래_안녕/</id><title>토마스 쿡 - 그래 안녕 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%86%A0%EB%A7%88%EC%8A%A4_%EC%BF%A1/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%98_%EC%95%88%EB%85%95/" title="토마스 쿡 - 그래 안녕 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가슴이 무언가로 가득 찬 것처럼 <br>난 숨이 가빠와 그리고 벅차올라 <br>넓은 들판 위에 서있는 것처럼 <br>저 높은 산위에 오른 것처럼 말야 <br>good bye good bye good bye <br>good bye good bye good bye <br>하나둘씩 떠올라 <br>잊고 있던 얼굴들이 <br>슬프지 않은 추억 <br>그래서 아름다워 <br>good bye good bye good bye <br>good bye good bye good bye <br>생각 없는 그런 <br>하루하루가 익숙해질 때 <br>다시 나를 찾아올 쫓기듯이 <br>너를 찾아 헤매는 <br>나를 다시 보게 될까 두려워 <br>난 생각해 내가 왜 이럴까 <br>그러다가 다시 맘이 편해져 <br>발뒤꿈치를 난 들고 있어 <br>홀가분해 이젠 다 끝이야 <br>]]></content><category term="토마스 쿡" label="토마스 쿡"/><category term="그래 안녕" label="그래 안녕"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/토마스_쿡/사라진_불빛/</id><title>토마스 쿡 - 사라진 불빛 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%86%A0%EB%A7%88%EC%8A%A4_%EC%BF%A1/%EC%82%AC%EB%9D%BC%EC%A7%84_%EB%B6%88%EB%B9%9B/" title="토마스 쿡 - 사라진 불빛 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[따뜻하게 언제나 나를 비추고 <br>날 그렇게 주인공을 만들었지 <br>아무도 없는 아무것도 없이 <br>혼자 이렇게 서있는 날 <br>다시 비추네 <br>내게 없는 걸 갖고 있는 사람 <br>웃으면서 바라보다가 <br>모든 걸 다 주어도 <br>아깝지 않다가 <br>대책 없이 속은 걸 알게 되지 <br>길모퉁이 한순간 불이 꺼지고 <br>벌거벗은 나를 보게 만들었지 <br>아무도 없는 아무것도 없이 <br>아무것도 없이 <br>혼자 이렇게 서있는 날 <br>다시 비추네 <br>내게 없는 걸 갖고 있는 사람 <br>웃으면서 바라보다가 <br>모든 걸 다 주어도 <br>아깝지 않다가 <br>대책 없이 속은 걸 알게 되지 <br>첨부터 다 속은 걸 알게 되지 <br>눈부시게 타오르다가 <br>모든 걸 다 주어도 <br>아깝지 않다가 <br>사라져버린 그 빛을 알게 되지 <br>내게 없는 걸 갖고 있는 사람 <br>웃으면서 바라보다가 <br>모든 걸 다 주어도 <br>아깝지 않다가 <br>대책 없이 속은 걸 알게 되지 <br>첨부터 다 속은 걸 알게 되지 <br>눈부시게 타오르다가 <br>모든 걸 다 주어도 <br>아깝지 않다가 <br>사라져버린 그 빛을 알게 되지 <br>]]></content><category term="토마스 쿡" label="토마스 쿡"/><category term="사라진 불빛" label="사라진 불빛"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/토마스_쿡/두_번째_인생/</id><title>토마스 쿡 - 두 번째 인생 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:52:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:52:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%86%A0%EB%A7%88%EC%8A%A4_%EC%BF%A1/%EB%91%90_%EB%B2%88%EC%A7%B8_%EC%9D%B8%EC%83%9D/" title="토마스 쿡 - 두 번째 인생 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무렇게나 끌려가듯이 <br>허우적대며 <br>항상 반대로 반대로 <br>그저 도망쳤지 <br>이리 저리 바보처럼 기웃대다 <br>벌써 절반이 지났음을 알게 되지 <br>두 번째 인생 두 번째 인생 <br>두 번째 인생 두 번째 인생 <br>걸음을 더는 멈추지 말아 <br>돌아보지 마 <br>마치 처음처럼 <br>만나게 되는 내일처럼 <br>조금씩 보이는데 이제 내 삶이 <br>불안했던 청춘은 다 지나갔다 <br>두 번째 인생 두 번째 인생 <br>두 번째 인생 두 번째 인생 <br>두 번째 인생 두 번째 인생 <br>두 번째 인생 두 번째 인생 <br>두 번째 인생 두 번째 인생 <br>두 번째 인생 두 번째 인생 <br>]]></content><category term="토마스 쿡" label="토마스 쿡"/><category term="두 번째 인생" label="두 번째 인생"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Aint_Nobody_Breakages_Suck_It_Up_Mix/</id><title>Clare Maguire - Ain`t Nobody (Breakage`s Suck It Up Mix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Aint_Nobody_Breakages_Suck_It_Up_Mix/" title="Clare Maguire - Ain`t Nobody (Breakage`s Suck It Up Mix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br><br>Meet me in the red sky and dance with me <br>Let the valley change you and the night set you free <br>It's dusk in the dessert, it's heaven at the gates <br>You were my desire, you were my escape <br><br>Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br><br>Open up this moment and bury me inside <br>I can see us changing, like a season over time <br>It's silver on the river, reflections of your love <br>Drown me in the silence, we'll never come undone <br><br>Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br><br>Shadows are falling, tomorrow's closing in <br>Stay with me till morning, open up your wings <br>I can hear your whispers, they're calling out my name <br>Will you promise me that we'll steal the night again 'cause <br><br>Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody can love me like you do <br><br>Meet me in the red sky and dance with me <br>Let the valley change you and the night set you free <br>It's dusk in the dessert, it's heaven at the gates <br>You were my desire, you were my escape]]></content><category term="Clare Maguire" label="Clare Maguire"/><category term="Ain`t Nobody (Breakage`s Suck It Up Mix)" label="Ain`t Nobody (Breakage`s Suck It Up Mix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Burn/</id><title>Clare Maguire - Burn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Burn/" title="Clare Maguire - Burn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Set you out on a course <br>Draw the line and say it is yours <br>Now you wonder who's boss <br>But do you really have to be sure <br><br>Do you ever feel, through the night <br>We light up, we ignite <br><br>We still have time to burn, you and I <br>We still have time to burn, you and I <br>We can try an an an and keep on holding o o on <br>We still have time to burn, you and I <br><br>Now we're making new laws <br>But the day is mine and it's yours <br>Will you open the door <br>I will not say anything else, nothing more <br><br>And still I feel, through the night <br>We light up, we ignite <br><br>We still have time to burn, you and I <br>We still have time to burn, you and I <br>We can try an an an and keep on holding o o on <br>We still have time to burn, you and I <br><br>Hey, oh, eh, oh you can hold onto it <br>Hey, oh, eh, oh run right through this <br>Hey, oh, eh, oh go on, hold on to it <br><br>We still have time to burn, you and I <br>We still have time to burn, you and I <br><br>We still have time to burn, you and I <br>We still have time to burn, you and I <br>We can try an an an and keep on holding o o on <br>We still have time to burn, you and I]]></content><category term="Clare Maguire" label="Clare Maguire"/><category term="Burn" label="Burn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Lucky/</id><title>Clare Maguire - Lucky - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Lucky/" title="Clare Maguire - Lucky - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're too blind to realize you are lucky <br>So untrue, these sweet, sweet lies, you are lucky <br><br>Are you afraid <br>You're talking tougher every day <br>But under the night <br>You're iron smile shows it's a fight <br><br>I can see inside, your eyes are sharp <br>Your head is drunk, and your heart is dark <br>Let me tell you something, it's not working, no <br><br>You're too blind to realize you are lucky <br>So untrue, these sweet, sweet lies, you are lucky <br><br>Is it a haze <br>Can you talk to fortune or feel fame <br>Cause you seem alone <br>You talk too much or don't talk at all <br><br>Yes, you're outside a golden glow <br>A fearless face, and shaking bones <br>And let me tell you something, it's not working, no <br><br>You're too blind to realize you are lucky <br>So untrue, these sweet, sweet lies, you are lucky <br>Now that you've got what you want, you are lucky <br>Now that you've got what you want, you are lucky <br><br>You just can't complain <br>You better understand <br>When you're feeling down <br>It makes nobody sad <br><br>You've got it all <br>You are the lucky one <br>You've got it all <br>You are the lucky one <br><br>You're too blind to realize you are lucky <br>So untrue, these sweet, sweet lies, you are lucky <br>Now that you've got what you want you are lucky <br>Now that you've got what you want you are lucky]]></content><category term="Clare Maguire" label="Clare Maguire"/><category term="Lucky" label="Lucky"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/This_Is_Not_The_End/</id><title>Clare Maguire - This Is Not The End - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/This_Is_Not_The_End/" title="Clare Maguire - This Is Not The End - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If it be your will to speak <br>Of memories we often shared <br>Talk to me of days gone by <br>Think of love and not despair <br><br>And when I'm gone <br>We'll meet again <br>As often do the closest friends <br>So dry your eyes <br>And lay me down <br>I tell you this is not the end <br><br>And if someone else <br>Must take my place <br>For I'll be gone the longest time <br>I'll wait and I will understand <br>A heart of thorns must <br>Leave the mind <br><br>But when in time I see your face <br>The scars will fade <br>The heart will mend <br>So dry your eyes <br>And lay me down <br>I tell you this is not the end <br><br>And from today I wish you joy <br>From this day I wish you peace <br>I hope that life will pass you by <br>As softly as the falling leaves <br><br>And when your heart is full again <br>Raise a glass for me my friend <br>And dry your eyes <br>And lay me down <br>I tell you this is not the end <br>Oh dry your eyes <br>And lay me down <br>I tell you this is not the end]]></content><category term="Clare Maguire" label="Clare Maguire"/><category term="This Is Not The End" label="This Is Not The End"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Light_After_Dark/</id><title>Clare Maguire - Light After Dark - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Light_After_Dark/" title="Clare Maguire - Light After Dark - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We're in one mind <br>We're in this together <br>And we're facing a fight <br>We're not trying to be clever no <br>We're not trying to be cool <br>Sometimes it feels like it's just me and you <br><br>We have one life <br>To find higher ground <br>It can take us up <br>It won't bring us down <br>It's forever we're forever <br><br>We'll change it all <br>We'll rise then we'll fall <br>We'll love then get lost <br>In the light after dark <br><br>We're not alone now <br>You are the reason I am <br>Walking so tall <br>We're in the spotlight <br>We're on the floor <br>Wrapped in arms that make <br>Us feel secure <br><br>We have one chance <br>To go where we go <br>You have shown me <br>And now I have seen it I know <br>It's forever oh we're forever <br><br>You and me <br>We're the light after dark <br>You and me <br>We're the light after dark]]></content><category term="Clare Maguire" label="Clare Maguire"/><category term="Light After Dark" label="Light After Dark"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Aint_Nobody/</id><title>Clare Maguire - Ain`t Nobody - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Aint_Nobody/" title="Clare Maguire - Ain`t Nobody - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br><br>Meet me in the red sky <br>And dance with me <br>Let the valley change you <br>And the night set you free <br>It's dusk in desert <br>It's heaven at the gates <br>You are my desire <br>You are my escape <br><br>Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br><br>Open up this moment <br>And bury me inside <br>I can see us changing <br>Like the seasons over time <br>It's silver on the river <br>Reflections of your love <br>Drown me in this silence <br>We'll never come undone <br><br>Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br><br>Oh hey <br>Shadows are falling <br>Tomorrow's closing in <br>Stay with me 'till morning <br>Open up your wings <br>I can hear your whispers <br>Calling out my name <br>Will you promise me that <br>You'll steal the night again <br>Cause <br><br>Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br>Ain't nobody <br>Can love me like you do <br><br>Meet me in the red sky <br>And dance with me <br>Let the valley change you <br>And the night set you free <br>It's dusk in desert <br>It's heaven at the gate <br>You are my desire <br>You are my escape]]></content><category term="Clare Maguire" label="Clare Maguire"/><category term="Ain`t Nobody" label="Ain`t Nobody"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Youre_Electric/</id><title>Clare Maguire - You`re Electric - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Youre_Electric/" title="Clare Maguire - You`re Electric - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lately I've been facing a fall <br>Holding onto something that means nothing but war <br>I've been cutting connections <br>Causing the walls <br>To build up around me <br>And faces to fade <br>Into blue blue colours <br>I walk in shallow waters <br><br>Should have gone my own way <br>But I didn't run just to hide <br>I ran for a better life <br>For a better life <br><br>You're electric <br>You know you light up my world when it's hard to take <br>So let's run away <br>Although I know you're electric <br>I know that lightening won't strike twice in the same place <br>So let's run away <br><br>I want you to know this love <br>I don't regret what we've done <br>Or who we are <br>No need to look for protection <br><br>Should have gone my own way <br>But I didn't run just to hide <br>I ran for a better life <br>For a better life <br><br>You're electric <br>You know you light up my world when it's hard to take <br>So let's run away <br>Although I know you're electric <br>I know that lightening won't strike twice in the same place <br>So let's run away <br><br>I would fly but you're standing here <br>Fixing my broken wings <br>Try to mend try to mend <br>This mess I'm in <br><br>You're electric <br>You know you light up my world when it's hard to take <br>So let's run away <br>Although I know you're electric <br>I know that lightening won't strike twice in the same place <br>So let's run away <br><br>You're electric you light up my world when it's hard to take <br>So let's run away]]></content><category term="Clare Maguire" label="Clare Maguire"/><category term="You`re Electric" label="You`re Electric"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Break_These_Chains/</id><title>Clare Maguire - Break These Chains - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Break_These_Chains/" title="Clare Maguire - Break These Chains - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I just don't believe <br>I'm ready for today <br>This paranoid pain is coming back again <br>Oh that picture Momma placed <br>By the window how I hate my face <br><br>And there's people all outside <br>Behind the curtains silver lines <br>With all their lies <br>They're all like mine all like mine <br>But when the wind blows <br>I'll go I'll go <br><br>And I will be released <br>Break these chains set me free <br>And I will be released <br>Break these chains <br><br>I can think of brighter days <br>They were golden in a way <br>Words were not this grey <br>But now prices will be paid <br>When I walk in the path <br>Of all you guilty ones someday <br><br>Cause I cannot help my heart <br>When it's beating in the dark <br>Afraid next time I won't cry <br>I won't cry <br>And when the times change <br>I'll go away I'm away <br><br>And I will be released <br>Break these chains set me free <br>And I will be released <br>Break these chains <br><br>Like a pilot I will fly <br>Way up in the sky <br>I'll be free I'll be high high high <br><br>And I will be released <br>Break these chains <br>Break these chains <br>So I can be released <br>Praying on my knees <br>That I can be released <br>I will be released oh <br>I can be released <br>Praying on my knees <br>That I will be released <br>I will be released <br><br>And I will be released <br>Break these chains set me free <br>And I will be released <br>Break these chains <br>Set me free <br><br>Like a pilot I will fly <br>Way up in the sky <br>I'll be free I'll be high high high <br><br>And I will be released <br>Break these chains <br>Break these chains <br><br>I can think of brighter days <br>They were golden in a way <br>Words were not this grey <br>But I can break these chains]]></content><category term="Clare Maguire" label="Clare Maguire"/><category term="Break These Chains" label="Break These Chains"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Sweet_Lie/</id><title>Clare Maguire - Sweet Lie - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Sweet_Lie/" title="Clare Maguire - Sweet Lie - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If I see you again <br>Will you remember me <br>If I see you again <br>Will you paint memories <br><br>Three long years never fly away <br>Three small words speak again <br><br>Out of sight out of mind <br>What a sweet lie what a sweet lie <br>Out of sight out of mind <br>What a sweet lie what a sweet lie <br><br>If I see you again <br>Will you understand <br>If I see you again <br>This was not my plan <br><br>Three long years never fly away <br>Three small words speak again <br><br>Out of sight out of mind <br>What a sweet lie what a sweet lie <br>Out of sight out of mind <br>What a sweet lie what a sweet lie <br><br>Three long years never fly away <br>Three small words please speak again <br><br>Out of sight out of mind <br>What a sweet lie what a sweet lie <br>Out of sight out of mind <br>What a sweet lie what a sweet lie <br><br>If I see you again <br>Will you remember me]]></content><category term="Clare Maguire" label="Clare Maguire"/><category term="Sweet Lie" label="Sweet Lie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/The_Happiest_Pretenders/</id><title>Clare Maguire - The Happiest Pretenders - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/The_Happiest_Pretenders/" title="Clare Maguire - The Happiest Pretenders - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[He licks the paper turns the page <br>He writes the spoken word again <br>Releases pools of untrapped blood <br>To camouflage what's understood <br>Wrapped up in a golden throne <br>He undresses overloads <br>Walks quietly to a distant place <br>Honest lies in washed out grace <br><br>Oh oh oh indicate we're locked in <br>Oh oh oh with the kings and queens <br><br>We are the happiest pretenders <br>And we are the happiest pretenders <br><br>Dressed down towards the Tyne <br>He chases evening's wonder whys <br>Then misses hours time again <br>Sweeps him underneath its wings <br><br>Oh oh oh indicate we're locked in <br>Oh oh oh with the kings and queens <br><br>We are the happiest pretenders <br>And we are the happiest pretenders <br><br>And if they try to catch us out <br>We'll chase them down <br>We're gonna chase them down <br>Cause we are the happiest pretenders <br><br>He wipes the crystal from his eyes <br>He hits the lights and leaves them dry <br>Undoes tomorrows unknown will <br>Let's it slide <br>Tastes the thrill <br>x2 <br><br>Cause we are the happiest pretenders <br>And we are the happiest pretenders <br><br>And if they try to catch us out <br>We'll chase them down <br>We're gonna chase them down <br>Cause we are the happiest pretenders <br><br>He wipes the crystal from his eyes <br>He hits the lights and leaves them dry <br>Undoes tomorrows unknown will <br>Let's it slide <br>Tastes the thrill]]></content><category term="Clare Maguire" label="Clare Maguire"/><category term="The Happiest Pretenders" label="The Happiest Pretenders"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Bullet/</id><title>Clare Maguire - Bullet - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Bullet/" title="Clare Maguire - Bullet - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was told that loneliness was like <br>Spaces between the stars <br>Well it's empty between these <br>Starry eyes <br>I was told a dead man was heavier than a broken heart <br>Am I dead now <br>My heart sure feels heavy <br><br>And I try not to feel it <br>Yeah I try not to feel it <br>So hard to believe it <br><br>I was told that time tiptoes by <br>Well I can hear his footsteps <br>Running past me <br>I was told I had a face <br>With nothing to fear <br>That's not the first thing <br>To scare me <br><br>And I try not to feel it <br>Oh I try not to feel it <br>It's so hard to believe it <br>But at the end of it all it's true <br><br>You shot this bullet <br>Through my bones <br>You shot this bullet <br>Through my bones <br><br>You shot me down <br>Down down I go <br>You shot me down <br>Down down I go <br><br>I get up take the phone from my hands <br>The glass from my lips <br>The pictures from my fingertips <br>I stand up I walk round and round <br>And I don't hear no sound <br>Only the words that you spoke to me <br><br>And I try not to feel it <br>Oh I try not to feel it <br>It's so hard to believe it <br>But at the end of it all it's true <br><br>You shot this bullet <br>Through my bones <br>You shot this bullet <br>Through my bones <br><br>You shot me down <br>Down down I go <br>You shot me down <br>Down down I go <br>You shot me down <br>Down down I go <br>You shot me down <br>Down down I go]]></content><category term="Clare Maguire" label="Clare Maguire"/><category term="Bullet" label="Bullet"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/I_Surrender/</id><title>Clare Maguire - I Surrender - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/I_Surrender/" title="Clare Maguire - I Surrender - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Watching a fire <br>Skipping under thunder <br>Crossing a wire <br>Connecting undercover <br>Be mine <br>It's a physical thing <br>I wanna give you <br>All the love I can give <br>The love I can give <br><br>Cause you make me surrender <br>With you I'm forced to surrender <br><br>Burying rivers <br>Drowning all our fears <br>Burning the bridges <br>Pushing all the gears <br>Be mine <br>It's a physical thing <br>I wanna give you <br>All the love I can give <br>The love I can give <br><br>Cause you make me surrender <br>With you I'm forced to surrender <br><br>I'm letting go waving this <br>White flag <br>I've given up the fight <br>Given up the fight <br>Cause you make me surrender <br>Losing a battle <br>Head into the shallow <br>Let go of the handle <br>Let us be alone now <br>Let us be alone now <br>Let us be alone now <br><br>Cause you make me surrender <br>With you I'm forced to surrender <br><br>I'm letting go waving this <br>White flag <br>I've given up the fight <br>Given up the fight <br>Cause you make me surrender <br><br>Cause you make me surrender <br>With you I'm forced to surrender]]></content><category term="Clare Maguire" label="Clare Maguire"/><category term="I Surrender" label="I Surrender"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Freedom/</id><title>Clare Maguire - Freedom - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/Freedom/" title="Clare Maguire - Freedom - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Makes me sit and wonder <br>How you're never bothered <br>When I say I wanna be free <br>I was rushing ahead <br>How could you not see that <br>Guess you won't miss <br>What you don't need <br><br>I promised with every word <br>That I would tell you the truth <br>Maybe it went unheard <br>You could have told me so <br>I would've never known <br><br>You're not here <br>You're not here with me <br>I guess that means I'm free <br><br>In and out <br>I'd rather go without <br>I can't defend you now <br>You would have let me down <br><br>If you find another <br>Maybe you'll discover <br>True love just won't get up <br>And leave <br><br>I promised with every word <br>That I would tell you the truth <br>Maybe it went unheard <br>You could have told me so <br>I would've never known <br><br>You're not here <br>You're not here with me <br>I guess that means I'm free <br>x3 <br><br>You're not here <br>You're not here with me <br>I guess I just run free]]></content><category term="Clare Maguire" label="Clare Maguire"/><category term="Freedom" label="Freedom"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/The_Last_Dance/</id><title>Clare Maguire - The Last Dance - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/The_Last_Dance/" title="Clare Maguire - The Last Dance - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Today I feel the mood <br>And I don't feel like talking oh I <br>I wasn't ready to lose you <br>You're the first man to move me, yeah <br>You helped me feel alive <br>Got me up from 9 to 5 oh I <br>I could get through those days <br>With you on my mind, yeah <br><br>Got to try move on but I promise you <br>I will kiss your crown when life takes me down <br><br>I'll save my last dance <br>For you my friend <br>I'll save my last dance <br>For you my friend <br><br>Another face in the crowd <br>Oh people love to move now oh I <br>I just can't feel the beat <br>'Cause my heart's fallen out <br><br>Got to try move on but I promise you <br>I will kiss your crown when life takes me down <br><br>I'll save my last dance <br>For you my friend <br>I'll save my last dance <br>For you my friend <br><br>I've got my life in my hands <br>And your love in my heart <br>I've got my life in my hands <br>And your love in my heart <br>I'll save my last dance <br>For you my friend <br><br>And it seems I've lived my life <br>With you as my rhythm, yeah <br>And I know I'll find my feet after dreaming <br><br>I'll save my last dance <br>For you my friend <br>I'll save my last dance <br>For you my friend <br><br>I've got my life in my hands <br>And your love in my heart <br>I've got my life in my hands <br>And your love in my heart <br>I'll save my last dance <br>For you my friend <br><br>I've got my life in my hands <br>And your love in my heart <br>x4 <br><br>Today I feel the mood <br>I wasn't ready to lose you <br>Today I feel the mood <br>I wasn't ready to lose you]]></content><category term="Clare Maguire" label="Clare Maguire"/><category term="The Last Dance" label="The Last Dance"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/The_Shield_And_The_Sword/</id><title>Clare Maguire - The Shield And The Sword - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clare_Maguire/The_Shield_And_The_Sword/" title="Clare Maguire - The Shield And The Sword - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You and I <br>Felt so good to begin with didn't we <br>Well now it seems there's far too many adverts in between <br>And we don't speak <br>So we're left in constant silence <br>It's haunting me <br>So I'm ready now to fight this <br><br>You have the shield <br>I'll take the sword <br>I no longer love you <br>No longer love you <br>I'm not afraid of danger in the dark <br>I no longer love you <br>No longer love you <br><br>You and I aren't working <br>Burning on the bridges now <br>We're trapped inside <br>Screaming won't somebody get me out <br><br>You have the shield <br>I'll take the sword <br>I no longer love you <br>No longer love you <br>I'm not afraid of danger in the dark <br>I no longer love you <br>No longer love you <br><br>I no longer love you <br>No longer love you <br>No longer love you <br>No longer love you <br><br>And we don't speak <br>So we're left in constant silence <br>And it's haunting me <br>So I'm ready now to fight this <br><br>You have the shield <br>I'll take the sword <br>I no longer love you <br>No longer love you <br>I'm not afraid of danger in the dark <br>I no longer love you <br>No longer love you <br>x2 <br><br>You and I <br>Felt so good to begin with didn't we <br>But now it seems these shields and swords are haunting me]]></content><category term="Clare Maguire" label="Clare Maguire"/><category term="The Shield And The Sword" label="The Shield And The Sword"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Martin_Masarov/Du_Dansar_Som_En_Idiot/</id><title>Martin Masarov - Du Dansar Som En Idiot - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:55:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:55:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Martin_Masarov/Du_Dansar_Som_En_Idiot/" title="Martin Masarov - Du Dansar Som En Idiot - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Du dansar som en idiot <br>Sa hon och dansade lite narmre <br>Du dansar som en idiot <br><br>Sa jag och dansade lite narmre <br>Strax efter kvart i tva <br>Nar timman tranger pa <br>Vet inte vart jag ar <br>Och mitt i allt ar du <br>Kan inte fega ur <br>Nu ar jag anda har <br>Om jag gor bort mig nu <br>Skit i det, jag bjuder <br>Jag var den enda har som rorde mig fult <br>Och sen kom du <br>Och sen kom du <br><br>Du dansar som en idiot <br>Sa hon och dansade lite narmre <br>Du dansar som en idiot <br>Sa jag och dansade lite narmre <br>Och nu sitter vi i taxin, taxin <br>Sa jag ar ganska kaxig, kaxig <br>Nu sitter vi i taxin, taxin <br>Och ater upp varandra, andra <br>For jag dansar som en <br>Du ar typ 10 poang <br>Jag ar val helt okej <br>Jag har en etta pa soder <br>Det var natt med min charm <br>Som fick dig ur balans <br>Har allting du behover <br>Hade ingen chans forut <br>Men man blir snygg nar man har kul <br>Jag var den enda har som rorde mig fult <br>Och sen kom du <br>Och sen kom du <br><br>Du dansar som en idiot <br>Sa hon och dansade lite narmre <br>Du dansar som en idiot <br>Sa jag och dansade lite narmre <br>Och nu sitter vi i taxin, taxin <br>Sa jag ar ganska kaxig, kaxig <br>Nu sitter vi i taxin, taxin <br>Och ater upp varandra, andra <br>For jag dansar som en <br>For jag dansar som en <br>Du dansar som en <br>Idiot <br>Du dansar som en idiot <br>Sa hon och dansade lite narmre]]></content><category term="Martin Masarov" label="Martin Masarov"/><category term="Du Dansar Som En Idiot" label="Du Dansar Som En Idiot"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Maty_Noyes/Falling_Out_Of_LovE/</id><title>Maty Noyes - Falling Out Of LovE - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:57:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:57:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Maty_Noyes/Falling_Out_Of_LovE/" title="Maty Noyes - Falling Out Of LovE - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I think I'm falling <br>I think I'm falling <br>Out of love with you <br>My stumach's turning <br>My eyes are watering <br>I don't know what to do <br><br>Well I keep tryna wait, oh wait <br>It out and ignore the truth <br>But I think it's time to say, oh say <br>Say goodbye to you <br><br>I think I'm falling out of love, oh, oh <br>Falling out of love with you <br>I think I'm falling out of love, oh, oh <br>Falling out of love with you <br>Oh oh oh oh oh, oh, oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh, oh, oh, oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh, oh, oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh, oh, oh, oh <br><br>Want me to fix you <br>Want me to fix you <br>I don't know what to do <br>I tried to love you <br>I tried to kiss you <br>I couldn't heal your wounds <br><br>Well if you don't need change, oh change <br>But then you won't be you <br>I guess I'll be on my way, oh way <br>And this was all I knew <br><br>I think I'm falling out of love, oh, oh <br>Falling out of love with you <br>I think I'm falling out of love, oh, oh <br>Falling out of love with you <br>Oh oh oh oh oh, oh, oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh, oh, oh, oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh, oh, oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh, oh, oh, oh <br><br>And when I try to say your name <br>The words don't sound the same <br>So you're feeling all this pain <br>Well, I don't feel a thing <br>Oh oh oh oh oh, oh, oh, oh <br>Falling out of love with you <br><br>I think I'm falling out of love, oh, oh <br>Falling out of love with you <br>I think I'm falling out of love, oh, oh <br>Falling out of love with you <br>Oh oh oh oh oh, oh, oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh, oh, oh, oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh, oh, oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh, oh, oh, oh <br><br>I think I'm falling <br>I think I'm falling <br>Out of love with you]]></content><category term="Maty Noyes" label="Maty Noyes"/><category term="Falling Out Of LovE" label="Falling Out Of LovE"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Maty_Noyes/Lil_Bit_WrOng/</id><title>Maty Noyes - Lil` Bit WrOng - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:57:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:57:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Maty_Noyes/Lil_Bit_WrOng/" title="Maty Noyes - Lil` Bit WrOng - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A little bit wrong than you like it <br>A little too broke to buy it <br>A little too great to hide it <br>I'm a little bit wrong <br>I'm a little bit wrong <br><br>But I've been gone back from the dead <br>And you do really understand <br>Never in love, love despairs <br>Say you're with me, say you're with me <br>But I'm not hurt by what she said <br>May I live life from their hands <br>Heart to heart, color me red <br>Color me red, color me red <br><br>All across the world <br>All the boys and girls <br>If you feel the noise <br>Sing it, sing it along <br><br>A little bit wrong than you like it <br>A little too broke to buy it <br>A little too great to hide it <br>I'm a little bit wrong <br>A little too bent to fix it <br>A little jam on that biscuit <br>Lipstick's like love, I'll kiss it <br>I'm a little bit wrong <br>I'm a little bit wrong <br><br>Oh, my body has feng shui <br>I'm not just a pretty face <br>Every piece in perfect place <br>Pick your places, work your faces <br>Can't disguise a masterpiece <br>People like what people see <br>Here I am just being me <br>They can taste it, just can't make it <br><br>All across the world <br>All the boys and girls <br>If you feel the noise <br>Sing it, sing it along <br><br>A little bit wrong than you like it <br>A little too broke to buy it <br>A little too great to hide it <br>I'm little bit wrong <br>A little too bent to fix it <br>A little jam on that biscuit <br>Lipstick's like love, I'll kiss it <br>I'm a little bit wrong <br><br>These things are not meant for you <br>These things are not meant for you <br>These things are not meant for you <br>Not meant not meant not not meant for you <br>These things are not meant for you <br>These things are not meant for you <br>These things are not meant for you <br>They're not meant not not meant for you <br><br>A little bit wrong than you like it <br>A little too broke to buy it <br>A little too great to hide it <br>I'm a little bit wrong <br>A little too bent to fix it <br>A little jam on that biscuit <br>Lipstick's like love, I'll kiss it <br>I'm a little bit wrong <br>I'm a little bit wrong]]></content><category term="Maty Noyes" label="Maty Noyes"/><category term="Lil` Bit WrOng" label="Lil` Bit WrOng"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Maty_Noyes/In_My_Mind/</id><title>Maty Noyes - In My Mind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T09:57:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T09:57:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Maty_Noyes/In_My_Mind/" title="Maty Noyes - In My Mind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know I messed it up with every other guy <br>I swear you're different and this time I'm gonna try <br>We can start fresh if you'd just let go of the past yeah <br>I don't I don't I don't get it cause I don't judge you like that <br>Can't just love me in pieces gotta love it all <br>You try to make me feel like being humans wrong <br>You got a lot to say about me and my past <br>Well I don't, I don't, I don't get it cause I don't judge you like that <br><br>Got me runnin' other places in my mind in my mind <br>How could you even say I never try never try <br>And you're acting like I been around with every single guy <br>Got me running other places in my mind in my mind yeah <br>Da da da da da da da da da da yeah <br>Da da da da da da da da da da <br>You're acting like I been around with every single guy <br>Got me running other places in my mind in my mind, yeah <br><br>I know that I could be with any other man <br>But none of them can do it quite the way you can <br>Thought we were stronger why you doubting all the time <br>Well I don't, I don't, I don't get it cause I'm so sweet all the time <br>Our love is effortless, stop acting like you're scared <br>I get down on my knees but you're not playing fair <br>My heart breaks down when you question if you're mine <br>When I don't, I don't, I don't get it <br>Cause I'm so sweet all the time <br><br>Got me running other places in my mind, in my mind <br>How could you even say I never tried, never tried <br>And you acting like I been around with every single guy <br>Got me running other places in my mind, in my mind, yeah <br>Da da da da da da da da da da yeah <br>Da da da da da da da da da da <br>And you acting like I been around with every single guy <br>You got me running other places in my mind, in my mind, yeah <br><br>Got me running to places where no body else has gone <br>And I tried to take you with me baby then it went all wrong <br>And I said, I'm here to stay but I need to get away <br>So I'm running other places in my mind, in my mind, yeah <br><br>Da da da da da da da da da da yeah <br>Da da da da da da da da da da <br>And you acting like I been around with every single guy <br>You got me running other places in my mind, in my mind, yeah <br>Da da da da da da da da da da yeah <br>Da da da da da da da da da da <br>And you acting like I been around with every single guy <br>You got me running other places in my mind, in my mind, yeah]]></content><category term="Maty Noyes" label="Maty Noyes"/><category term="In My Mind" label="In My Mind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LSD_Ape_Machine/You_Only_Live_Once_Original_Mix/</id><title>LSD Ape Machine - You Only Live Once (Original Mix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:01:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:01:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LSD_Ape_Machine/You_Only_Live_Once_Original_Mix/" title="LSD Ape Machine - You Only Live Once (Original Mix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Looking Breaking Arrive <br>but what we want seems <br>in sickness kind <br>But know we were already knows <br>what’s going on <br>The understanding wrong <br>The Ain’t Place before <br>In seems serenity serenity <br>Looking Breaking Arrive <br>but what we want seems <br>in sickness kind <br>But know we were already knows <br>what’s going on <br>The understanding wrong <br>The Ain’t Place before <br>In seems serenity serenity <br>]]></content><category term="LSD Ape Machine" label="LSD Ape Machine"/><category term="You Only Live Once (Original Mix)" label="You Only Live Once (Original Mix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Maggie_Rogers/Dog_Years/</id><title>Maggie Rogers - Dog Years - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:01:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:01:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Maggie_Rogers/Dog_Years/" title="Maggie Rogers - Dog Years - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I count my time in dog years <br>Swimming in sevens <br>Slow dancing in seconds <br>Oh and I'm the one that loves you <br>Oh and I'm the one that loves you <br>I spend my time daydreaming <br>As sure as the sea <br>It's just you and me <br>Oh and I'm the one that loves you <br>Oh and I'm the one that loves you <br>And if you had a bad week <br>Just let me touch your cheek <br>Oh and I'll be there waiting <br>When you get frustrated <br>I know things are changing <br>But darling I'm saying <br>I'll be singing you <br>in all of my songs <br>Come what may <br>I'll still stay <br>Inside your mind <br>For all of time <br>Singing ooh <br>We will be alright <br>In the afterlife <br>Of all that is shifting <br>And shaking my system <br>I know your rhythm <br>And I know I know <br>I know I know I know <br>That I'm the one that loves you <br>Oh and I'm the one that loves you <br>And if you had a bad week <br>Then I'll sing you to sleep <br>Oh and I'll be there waiting <br>If you start to get jaded <br>I know things are changing <br>But darling I'm saying <br>I've been here all along <br>Come what may <br>I'll still stay <br>Inside your mind <br>For all of time <br>Singing ooh <br>We will be alright <br>Not in vain <br>We'll still stay the same <br>Inside your mind <br>For all of time <br>Singing ooh <br>We will be alright <br>In the afterlife <br>In the afterlife <br>I count my time in dog years <br>dog years dog years <br>dog years dog years <br>We will be alright <br>Dog years dog years <br>We will be alright <br>Dog years dog years <br>In the afterlife Dog years <br>dog years dog years dog years <br>Singing baby <br>we will be alright <br>Dog years dog years <br>We will be alright <br>We will be alright <br>]]></content><category term="Maggie Rogers" label="Maggie Rogers"/><category term="Dog Years" label="Dog Years"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fickle_Friends/Brooklyn/</id><title>Fickle Friends - Brooklyn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:02:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:02:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fickle_Friends/Brooklyn/" title="Fickle Friends - Brooklyn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wake up with worry <br>Nothing fills me up <br>He follows me daily <br>He knows how to love <br>No true end inside me <br>I won't ever say it enough <br>You're a Brooklyn baby <br>You know how to love <br>I know what can rule me <br>Sink me with the sand <br>Oh I can be the warden <br>And I will never crave it <br>I won't ever say it enough <br>You're a Brooklyn baby <br>You know how to love <br>You are someone else <br>There's something I can't define <br>You are not mine <br>You are someone <br>You are someone else <br>Worrying in my head <br>That's what she said <br>You are someone else <br>You you you are not my <br>You are like the honey <br>I am not allowed <br>Oh I won't go without <br>Show me in a movie <br>You can tell me what you're about <br>Oh I'm in Brooklyn baby <br>I'm a long way out <br>You are someone else <br>There's something I can't define <br>You are not mine <br>You are someone <br>You are someone else <br>Worrying in my head <br>That's what she said <br>You are someone else <br>You you are not my <br>You are someone else <br>Swear I go <br>Does he know <br>That we're different I <br>You you are not my <br>And I still say <br>Each new day <br>I got this one <br>you are not my you are not my <br>You are someone else <br>There's something I can't define <br>You are not mine <br>You are someone <br>You are someone else <br>Worrying in my head <br>That's what she said <br>You are someone else <br>You you you are not my <br>You are someone else <br>You you you are not my <br>You are someone else <br>]]></content><category term="Fickle Friends" label="Fickle Friends"/><category term="Brooklyn" label="Brooklyn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Marx_And_Engels/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - Marx And Engels - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:03:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:03:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Marx_And_Engels/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - Marx And Engels - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's misery in all I hear and see <br>From the people on TV <br>After their tea when life begins again <br>They'll be happier than me <br>There are a thousand meals being made on Saturday <br>From the view I saw today <br>I took a bet inside the launderette <br>With a girl from Wallasey <br><br>She spoke in dialect I could not understand <br>But one thing she made clear <br>There was no coming on to her <br>There was no way <br><br>There's misery in all I hear and see <br>From the people on TV <br>After their tea when life begins again <br>They'll be happier than me <br>There are a thousand meals being made on Saturday <br>From the view I saw today <br>I took a bet inside the launderette <br>With a girl from Wallasey <br><br>She spoke in dialect I could not understand <br>But one thing she made clear <br>There was no coming on to her <br>There was no way <br>That she could respect <br>If it couldn't see <br>That the girl just wants to be <br>Left alone with Marx and Engels for a while <br>She's writing in the style <br>Of any riot girl <br><br>The bourgeoisie, historically, has played a revolutionary part to all feudal, idyllic relationships <br>It has resolved personal worth and in place of freedom is exploitation for profit alone <br>There is a spectre of the past in my bold assertion <br>We could learn much from the past]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="Marx And Engels" label="Marx And Engels"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/I_Love_My_Car/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - I Love My Car - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:03:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:03:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/I_Love_My_Car/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - I Love My Car - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I love my car <br>I'll admit today I've gone too far <br>To enamour myself of my little motor car <br>I love my dog <br>I love my pussy cat, I love the rat <br>That lives under the floor and makes his bed from novelettes <br><br>I wish I could say the same for you <br>The day will come soon when I look in your eyes but <br>I won't see you <br><br>I've got a head like a soaking sponge <br>I've got a tongue like a little slug <br>I won't be bugged by trivia <br><br>I love my Carl <br>I love my Brian my Dennis and my Al <br>I could even find it in my heart to love Mike Love <br><br>I wish I could say the same for you <br>The day will come soon when I look in your eyes to <br>see you smiling]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="I Love My Car" label="I Love My Car"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Im_Waking_Up_To_Us/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - I`m Waking Up To Us - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:03:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:03:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Im_Waking_Up_To_Us/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - I`m Waking Up To Us - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I need someone to take some joy in something I do <br>You need a man who's either rich or losing a screw <br>You know I love you here's the irony <br>You're going to walk away intact <br>I think you never liked me anyway <br>You like yourself and you like <br>Men to kiss your arse <br>Expensive clothes <br>Please stop me there <br>I think I'm waking up to us <br>We're a disaster <br>You don't want to know me <br>'Cause you move in circles of the brave <br>Where art defines their lives <br><br>She was the one love of my life, and I let her go <br>And if I look like death today <br>then please let her know <br>I never wanted to do harm to her <br>I only wanted her to see <br>The beauty of the world surrounding her <br>But when she opened up her eyes <br>It's much too late <br>Our chance has gone <br>She's with a guy <br>Who takes the prize for everything I ever showed her <br>Digging all the fun <br>Because she's older <br>I fed her with a spoon <br>I made her mother smile <br>I helped the kid survive <br><br>She was the one love of my life <br>she showed me the road <br>I loved her dog, her steady gaze, the chapter is closed <br>I always wanted all the best for her <br>The best thing was to stay away <br>She grew up and she left the rest of us <br>And now the understanding's gone <br>I haven't changed, how could I <br>I'm pretty much the same person <br>I cannot keep the anger hidden anymore <br>But lucky for you, you are not around <br>My anger turns to pity and to love <br>The season has arrived]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="I`m Waking Up To Us" label="I`m Waking Up To Us"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/The_Loneliness_Of_A_Middle_Distance_Runner/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - The Loneliness Of A Middle Distance Runner - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:03:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:03:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/The_Loneliness_Of_A_Middle_Distance_Runner/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - The Loneliness Of A Middle Distance Runner - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll take a second of the day to think about the things that we have Done this year <br>The dog lies down, the pouring rain <br>I'm underneath the smoker's railway arch again <br>The future's looking colourful <br>It's the colour of blood, chaos and corruption of a happy soul <br>A happy soul will <br>Ride in the field <br>Till the rain dies down <br><br>The railway ticket states a destination <br>But it doesn't mean that we will show <br>There's a fork upon the line <br>We paid the guard to switch the sign, and off we go <br>The future's looking wonderful <br>It's the wonder of a businessman's conspiracy to sell your wares <br>And no one cares <br>Oh you care, I know <br>You care, I forgot for a while <br><br>On a sulky afternoon spent in dispute <br>You'll give yourself a headache, boy <br>So I take revenge in stories and dreaming of the time when <br>We're on stage <br>Have you seen The Loneliness Of A Middle Distance Runner <br>When he stops the race and looks around <br>I left the stage <br>You've seen it now <br>I walked to the station <br>I wish you follow me tonight]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="The Loneliness Of A Middle Distance Runner" label="The Loneliness Of A Middle Distance Runner"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Take_Your_Carriage_Clock_And_Shove_It/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - Take Your Carriage Clock And Shove It - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:03:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:03:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Take_Your_Carriage_Clock_And_Shove_It/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - Take Your Carriage Clock And Shove It - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In the board room the quiet man takes a <br>Second to think what to do <br>He's out of his seat and he's starting to speak <br>And he hears his own voice <br>For years and years he's done nothing but bow down and put up with all their demands <br>She sits like a viper and offers the clock <br>Without giving a damn <br>He takes it <br><br>Honour forbids me but honour be damned <br>You have whined till you got what you want <br>I did the work and when things were going badly <br>You left us to rot <br><br>He locked the door or the boardroom <br>And turned like the scene from the old country song <br>Towering over the table he's lost <br>He is drunk with it all <br><br>You only <br>Came back to us when we'd turned it around <br>When we'd rescued your arse from the fire <br>Your contribution to all that we did was to say <br>it was dire <br><br>Night after day after night I've been working <br>Despite of you fucking us all <br>Now I'm going to die I don't care if you cry <br>Just please leave me alone <br>And spare your tears from yourself <br>We've had those till we're sick <br>You should leave while you still have the chance <br><br>The others were shocked at this shameless disgrace <br>At the end of an honoured career <br>He paused in the silence to pull down his tie <br>And observe the melee]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="Take Your Carriage Clock And Shove It" label="Take Your Carriage Clock And Shove It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Jonathan_David/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - Jonathan David - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:03:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:03:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Jonathan_David/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - Jonathan David - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know you like her <br>Well I like her too <br>I know she likes you <br>It's not as if I'm being sent off to War <br>There are worse things in this world <br><br>There's still room on my wooden horse for two <br>I was Jonathan to your David <br>You're still King <br><br>Well, I'd thought about her <br>I dreamed she'd come, I'd make my escape <br>I thought she liked me but somehow I was wrong <br>I know you don't want it this way <br>But it's OK <br><br>It's not like we'll be parted <br>It's not like we never know love <br><br>And she'll smile for you <br>She'll hold your hand <br>You'll be in love there's no other way <br>And I will make it some day <br><br>I know you like her <br>Well I like her too <br>I know she likes you <br>It's not as if I'm being sent off to War <br>There are worse things in this world <br><br>There's still room on my wooden horse for two <br>I was Jonathan to your David <br>You're still King <br><br>Visions of love recollected <br>Have we ever been true <br>I know that I have, it's time for you to go <br>It's all in the stones that you throw <br>I want you to know <br><br>It's not like we'll be parted <br>It's not like we never know love <br><br>And she'll smile for you <br>She'll hold your hand <br>You'll be in love there's no other way <br><br>People say that <br>We'll never change <br>We'll never change <br>But I have <br><br>You and her in the local newspaper <br>You will be Married and you'll be gone <br><br>Married and you'll be gone]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="Jonathan David" label="Jonathan David"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/The_Gate/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - The Gate - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:03:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:03:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/The_Gate/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - The Gate - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In the hope I'll forget I'll wait <br>It's a chance I'll take oh yeah <br>In the hope I'll forget I'll wait <br>For the time <br><br>In the spring I'll watch my step <br>While the night time passes by <br>When a smile suits me all alone <br>I'll be fine <br><br>There's got to be a better song to sing <br>Before I hang upon your shoulder <br>Telling the truth it may be bolder this time <br>There's got to be a better song to sing <br>That makes a lonely one less cold oh <br>Before I hang upon your shoulder and cry <br><br>Watching friends playing in the dirt <br>Feeling hard but feeling hurt <br>By the sadness that wastes my time <br>It's a crime <br><br>Counting acts which I must add <br>To collect sad memories <br>From a past I'd soon forget <br>Swap or leave <br><br>There's got to be a better song to sing <br>Before I hang upon your shoulder <br>Telling the truth it may be bolder this time <br>There's got to be a better song to sing <br>That makes a lonely one less cold oh <br><br>Before I hang upon your shoulder and cry <br>At the gate I'll wave goodbye <br>To the friends that were my lies <br>And I'll see them off at dawn <br>Feeling wise <br>Feeling wise <br>Feeling wise]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="The Gate" label="The Gate"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/I_Know_Where_The_Summer_Goes/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - I Know Where The Summer Goes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:03:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:03:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/I_Know_Where_The_Summer_Goes/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - I Know Where The Summer Goes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know where the summer goes <br>When you're having no fun <br>When you're under the thumb <br>I know where the summer dwells <br>If your underarm smells <br>And your kitchen looks like hell <br><br>I know where the summer goes <br>If you're scraping a pot, and your head is hot <br>Put your head down, put your thumbs up girl <br>With the smell of hot desk <br>And the glitter of your step <br>He was right, he's the upcoming guru of the city <br>No one told the city councillors <br><br>I know, you can tell me again <br>I've got my mobile phone <br>Full of silicon chips <br>No one likes a smart arse <br>But I've seen a pattern emerge <br>I will race you up the hill <br>Where the boy who made records out of postcard messages <br>And flowering cherries rain on kids like you <br><br>Look twice at the kid with the crimped <br>And overheated hair <br>They ran a book on his looks <br>Odds on was the noble pose and <br>The denim hard riff of the Irish Troubadour <br>But the boy came from nowhere to <br>Steal the hearts of lassies in the lavvies of the club tonight]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="I Know Where The Summer Goes" label="I Know Where The Summer Goes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/This_Is_Just_A_Modern_Rock_Song/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - This Is Just A Modern Rock Song - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:03:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:03:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/This_Is_Just_A_Modern_Rock_Song/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - This Is Just A Modern Rock Song - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Emma tried to run away <br>I followed her across the city <br>She went out to the Easterhouse <br>Because she liked the sound of it <br><br>She didn't have a single penny <br>She stuck a finger in the air <br>She tried to flag down an aeroplane <br>I suppose she needs a holiday <br><br>I put my arm around her waist <br>She put me on the ground with Judo <br>She didn't recognise my face <br>She wasn't even looking <br><br>Laura's feeling just ideal <br>Her horoscope was nearly perfect <br>She's thinking of something to do <br>Because she is The Birthday Girl <br><br>She walked out to the edge of town <br>She saw me lying in the park <br>She took Emma by the hand <br>They've got a lot in common <br><br>I'll leave them to do what they want <br>I'll leave them to do what they need to <br>I'll go and play with words and pictures <br>I'll admit I'm feeling strange <br><br>I'm not as sad as Doestoevsky <br>I'm not as clever as Mark Twain <br>I'll only buy a book for the way it looks <br>And then I stick it on the shelf again <br><br>Now I could tell you what I'm thinking <br>But it never seems to do you good <br>It's beyond me what a girl can see <br>I'm only lucid when I'm writing songs <br><br>This is just a modern rock song <br>This is just a sorry lament <br>We're four boys in corduroys <br>We're not terrific but we're competent <br><br>Stevie's full of good intentions <br>Richards into rock 'n' roll <br>Stuart's staying in and he thinks it's a sin <br>That he has to leave the house at all <br><br>This is just a modern rock song <br>This is just a tender affair <br>I count three, four and then we start to slow <br>Because a song has got to stop somewhere]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="This Is Just A Modern Rock Song" label="This Is Just A Modern Rock Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Put_The_Book_Back_On_The_Shelf/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - Put The Book Back On The Shelf - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:03:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:03:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Put_The_Book_Back_On_The_Shelf/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - Put The Book Back On The Shelf - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sebastian you're in a mess <br>You had a dream, they called you king <br>Of all the hipsters, is it true <br>Or are you still the queen <br><br>Like getting blood out of a stone <br>The city left you all alone <br>You came to dance, but there's no poignancy <br>When they all leave you standing alone <br><br>The wider issues of the day <br>Don't interest you, you'll have to pay <br>For looking at the floor <br>When people talk to you <br><br>You wrote a book about yourself <br>The people left it on the shelf <br>You'll write another one <br>Now you've got a story that's worth talking about <br><br>Are you happy with yourself <br>Are you talking to yourself <br>Are you happy with yourself <br>Put the book back on the shelf <br><br>I know the company you keep <br>You're on the sofa hidden deep <br>While on the telly Sid James speaks <br>To you like God <br><br>You're always looking for a sign <br>But boy you blow it every time <br>You hear a voice begin to speak <br>You ignore it and go softly to sleep]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="Put The Book Back On The Shelf" label="Put The Book Back On The Shelf"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Beautiful/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - Beautiful - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:03:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:03:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Beautiful/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - Beautiful - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She lay in bed all night watching the colours change <br>She lay in bed all night watching the morning change <br>She lay in bed all night watching the morning change into green and gold <br><br>The doctor told her years ago that she was ill <br>The doctor told her years ago to take a pill <br>The doctor told her years ago that she'd go blind if she wasn't careful <br><br>They let Lisa go blind <br>The world was at her feet and she was looking down <br>They let Lisa go blind <br>And everyone she knew thought she was beautiful <br>Only slightly mental <br>Beautiful, only temperamental <br>Beautiful, only slightly mental <br>Beautiful <br><br>She thought it would be fun to try photography <br>She thought it would be fun to try pornography <br>She thought it would be fun to try most anything <br>She was tired of sleeping <br><br>They let Lisa go blind, let Lisa go blind, let Lisa go blind <br>They let Lisa go blind <br>She's looking like a queen <br>But if you knew what's going on in her life <br>There'd be a thousand barren mothers there to talk to her <br>If you knew what's going on in her life <br>There'd be two hundred troubled teenagers to sit with her <br>And to talk to her <br>If you knew what's going on in her life <br>What's going on in her life <br>There would be a documentary on Radio 4 <br><br>She made herself a pair of orthopaedic shoes <br>She thought it was the answer to the fashion blues <br>She thought it was the answer to the fashion blues <br>But she walked with a limp <br><br>They let Lisa go blind, let Lisa go blind, let Lisa go blind]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="Beautiful" label="Beautiful"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Le_Pastie_De_La_Bourgeoisie/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - Le Pastie De La Bourgeoisie - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:03:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:03:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Le_Pastie_De_La_Bourgeoisie/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - Le Pastie De La Bourgeoisie - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sunbeam shone, mousy girl on the end pew <br>You'd stay home, oh if only they let you <br>Le Pastie de la Bourgeoisie <br><br>Municipal pool, you're a junior life saver <br>But you're friends are all serious ravers <br>Le Pastie de la Bourgeoisie <br>Reading Judy Blume <br>But you came too soon <br><br>You're too tall, much too tall for a boyfriend <br>They run and hide, from your buck tooth and split ends <br>Don't be scared, like the books you've read <br>You're the heroine <br>You'll be doing fine <br><br>Wouldn't you like to get away <br>Bestowing the memory of good and evil <br>On the ones you left behind <br>The heartless swine <br><br>And you love like nobody around you <br>How you love, and a halo surrounds you <br>Le Pastie de la Bourgeoisie <br>In the Autumn cool <br>Say cheerio to school <br><br>Listen Dear, I've been watching you lately <br>If I said all these things you would hate me <br>Le Pastie de la Bourgeoisie <br>At the church bazaar <br>I nearly went too far <br><br>Wouldn't you like to get away <br>Give yourself up to the allure of <br>Catcher In The Rye <br>The future's swathed in Stars and Stripes <br><br>Wouldn't you like to get away <br>Kerouac's beckoning with open arms <br>And open roads of eucalyptus <br>Westward bound]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="Le Pastie De La Bourgeoisie" label="Le Pastie De La Bourgeoisie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/A_Century_Of_Fakers/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - A Century Of Fakers - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:04:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:04:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/A_Century_Of_Fakers/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - A Century Of Fakers - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There are people going hungry far away <br>They've got nothing on their plates <br>And you're filling your fat face with every different kind of cake <br>And if you ever go lardy, or go lame <br>I will drop you straight away <br>That's the price you have to pay <br>For every stupid thing you say <br><br>There are people going lonely, and they'll stay <br>Lonely fay into the year <br>Because you're making blinkers fashionable <br>And fashionably you'll say <br>All is equal in love and war and <br>I'm sorry, but I've got some things to do <br>And you pretend to read a book you'll never finish till the day <br><br>That the author dedicates it <br>To A Century Of Fakers <br>They took your mould and they burned it on the fire in history today <br>Yeah, the author dedicates it <br>To A Century Of Fakers <br>He was an anarchist, he tried his best but it wasn't good enough <br><br>Did I say I would see you soon <br>Well I'm sorry, but i just came off my bike <br>And my face is scarred <br>And chance has barred me seeing you tonight <br>I was over the other side of the city <br>And if the truth be known I'd say <br>That you look great from there before you shaved your golden hair today <br><br>Everybody's trying to make us <br>Another century of fakers <br>They took you mould and burned it on the fire of history today <br>Everybody's trying to make us <br>Another cool decade of fakers <br>Another century of fakers]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="A Century Of Fakers" label="A Century Of Fakers"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/A_Century_Of_Elvis/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - A Century Of Elvis - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:04:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:04:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/A_Century_Of_Elvis/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - A Century Of Elvis - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We were sitting in the living room on the sofa, the wrong way round, looking out the window <br>It was quiet, and then in the car park across the road we saw Elvis look, there beside the postman's van <br>and he was walking round the postman's van, looking in the open door <br>He looked as if he was thinking about getting in, but then the postman came back, and he swaggered off <br>walked past the window and down the stairs, and then at the bottom of the stairs right by the caretaker's office <br>he started licking the pavement <br>Every night now since we moved in that new house there's this noise outside the door at just about half seven or eight o' clock every night <br>And if we go and look outside the door, Elvis'll be standing there waiting to be let in <br>And then he wanders into the living room, maybe sits down on one of the chairs or even lies down on the floor <br>He doesn't say much, he just stays there for an hour or two, watching the TV <br>We talk to him a bit, and then around ten o' clock, he'll go away again, and not come back until the next night <br>There's a lot of lanes and stuff around here, around the house although it's right in the middle of the city <br>it seems quite like the country, it's dead hidden safe I suppose, made for night living <br>There's a lot of squirrels and birds, and Stuart says he's seen about nine foxes there <br>when he's jumped over the fence on his way to Prior's Road <br>Sometimes you can go out walking, and when you've been out for a wee while even you don't know where you are anymore <br>so it would be pretty hard for anyone else to find you <br>I suppose that's why he spends so much time there, that's why he's come to live there, or maybe it's just the squirrels <br>I read about somewhere that he likes squirrels quite a lot <br>There's these two videos that we got for wedding presents called the e files <br>e files one and e files two about how Elvis is supposed to be still alive <br>And one time when he came round we were watching one of those, but he didn't say anything he just sat on the armchair <br>He was playing with his collar a bit, and we watched it right through and then when it finished <br>he just got up and walked off into the mist and didn't say anything <br>The first few times he came round I didn't speak to him at all, I wasn't really sure what to say <br>And Karen spoke to him quite a lot she seemed to know what to do more than I do <br>He had quite a strange manner though, he'd go into your stuff and look through it <br>then he'd maybe pick something up and play with it for a wee while, but he'd never make any comment about any of it <br>Seemed pretty rude to me <br>I just watched whatever Karen did, and listened to how she talked to him and then <br>after a while I started to copy that, and tell him a few things <br>not really bothered about whether he responded or said anything back or not <br>I think the first time I spoke to him we were sitting up on the mezzanine and I said that I would tell him about me and wee Karen <br>and how it was that we'd come to be living there <br>I thought he probably liked the fact that we were living there because he came round so much <br>so I thought he might want to know how it was that it came about <br>We did it all over backwards, I told him <br>First of all we got to know each other, and then a while after that we met <br>and when we'd known each other for about seven years we decided to have an anniversary <br>and that went quite well, so after the anniversary we had a honeymoon, and that went well too <br>so after that we decided that we would get married <br>That's why we're living there now I used to think my dad was Elvis, but I haven't told him that yet <br>I haven't told my dad either]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="A Century Of Elvis" label="A Century Of Elvis"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Photo_Jenny/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - Photo Jenny - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:04:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:04:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Photo_Jenny/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - Photo Jenny - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm in a mess, I'm in a dress <br>There's nothing from here till tomorrow morning <br>How will I get there <br>I don't do drugs <br>All my friends are on their holidays <br><br>I go outside, it's not so bad <br>I saw my friend and he couldn't believe that <br>The girls were holding hands <br>The girls are holding hands <br>Don't be a fool <br>It's 1995, the girls are just friends <br><br>They got the drugs I could use but then I don't need any <br>All that I want is a photograph of Photo Jenny <br>How will I get one I don't know <br>How will I get one I don't know <br>How will I get her to strike a pose <br><br>It's getting cold, I'll catch the bus <br>I saw my friend when she's finished working <br>Get some fish and chips <br>What's on the box <br>'Man about the house' with Paula Wilcox <br><br>You see the boy girl's at the bar <br>Everyone thinks she's really ugly <br>But I shut my eyes <br>And the star of it is Photo Jenny]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="Photo Jenny" label="Photo Jenny"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/You_Made_Me_Forget_My_Dreams/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - You Made Me Forget My Dreams - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:04:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:04:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/You_Made_Me_Forget_My_Dreams/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - You Made Me Forget My Dreams - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You made me forget my dreams <br>When I woke up to you sleeping <br>We had peace for a night at least <br>But the trouble starts today <br>This morning you'll say <br>I'll see you sometime, maybe and I <br>Fall back to uneasy sleep <br><br>You made me forget my dreams <br>I was building a space rocket <br>With the boy who played bass guitar <br>With the boy who's wearing flares <br>He didn't care <br>He lit the fuse and ran for a mile <br>The space rocket went up in style <br>The space rocket went up in style <br><br>I'll lend you two hundred quid <br>For a flight across the ocean <br>Maybe things will look better there <br>Because they couldn't be much worse <br>Than tears and a curse <br>For men with guns, maturing in age <br>Will always pay a shitty wage <br>They'll always pay a shitty wage <br><br>You made me forget my dreams <br>When I woke up to you sleeping <br>There was blood on the sheets again <br>And the view outside the window <br>Of gardens in bloom <br>Obscured by all the trouble we had <br>I think I better make a move <br>I think I better make a move]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="You Made Me Forget My Dreams" label="You Made Me Forget My Dreams"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Lazy_Line_Painter_Jane/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - Lazy Line Painter Jane - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:04:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:04:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Lazy_Line_Painter_Jane/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - Lazy Line Painter Jane - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Working the village shop <br>Putting a poster up <br>Dreaming of anything <br>Dreaming of the time when you are free from all the trouble you're in <br>In the mud, on your knees <br>Trying hard not to please <br>Anyone, all the time <br>Being a rebel's fine <br>But you go all the way to being brutal <br><br>You will have a boy tonight <br>You will have a boy tonight <br>On the first bus out of town <br>On the first bus out of town <br><br>Let's see your kit for games <br>All the girls look the same <br>You are challenging style for running miles <br>You're running miles in some boys jumper <br><br>Boo to the business world <br>You know a girl who's tax free on her back and making <br>Plenty cash <br>While you are working for the joy of giving <br><br>You will have a boy tonight <br>You will have a boy tonight <br>And you hope that she will see <br>And you hope that she will see <br><br>You will have a boy tonight <br>Or maybe you will have a girl tonight <br>And you hope that she will see <br>And you hope that she will see <br><br>You are in two minds <br>Tossing a coin to decide whether you should tell your mum <br>About a dose of thrush you got while you were licking railings <br><br>But you read in a book <br>That you got free in Boots <br>There are lotions, there are potions <br>You can take to hide your shame from all those prying eyes <br><br>Lazy Jane, all the time <br>Painting lines <br>You are sleeping at bus stops <br>Wondering how you got your name <br>And what you're going to do about it <br><br>You will have a boy tonight <br>You will have a boy tonight <br>And you hope that she will see <br>And you hope that she will see]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="Lazy Line Painter Jane" label="Lazy Line Painter Jane"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Belle__Sebastian/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - Belle &amp; Sebastian - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:04:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:04:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Belle__Sebastian/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - Belle &amp; Sebastian - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I left the school I left my job <br>You saw me looking like a slob <br>When I was young you were the only fun in town <br><br>Everyone thought it was a shame <br>For Belle and the boy Sebastian <br>Belle was ok but oh Sebastian <br>Went too far again <br>Crashed his car in the rain <br><br>He wants to love and he wants to care <br>But when the boys are queuing up to tell her she's a star <br>Poor Sebastian is heading for a fall <br><br>Everyone thought it was a shame <br>For Belle and the boy Sebastian <br>Everyone thought it was a shame <br>Belle was ok but oh Sebastian <br>Went too far again <br>Crashed his car in the rain <br>Oh Sebastian wrote his diary that <br>He would never be young again <br>But you will <br>Fellow, you are ill <br>You'd better take a weight off of your mind and listen <br>To what other people say <br>Cause things are going wrong your own way]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/String_Bean_Jean/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - String Bean Jean - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:04:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:04:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/String_Bean_Jean/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - String Bean Jean - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I got my fingers dirty at the school of rock <br>Yeah I got my fingers dirty so I took a walk <br>I went up to the country park and hung around till after dark <br>Till the girls got home <br>Till the girls got home <br><br>Did I tell you 'bout the one I know, she's on the rag <br>She spent the summer day inside her sleeping bag <br>Yeah she spent the summer day inside until it's time to work <br>And she works all night <br>Cause the girl's all right <br><br>The girls have got a house that's like a caravan <br>And it's like your holidays whenever you go round <br>And we always have a laugh and then we all get in the bath <br>To save on the leccy bill <br>Me and Jo and Phil' <br><br>I had to leave them in the morning <br>I left the keys around the way <br>I had to catch a bus <br>I had to leave them in the morning <br>I left the keys down in the caf' <br>I had to go to work <br><br>And when Jo was short of cash I had to give her some <br>But I didn't really mind cause I was fit for once <br>So she paid the leccy bill and got the shopping and she still had <br>Some for the cinema <br>So we all went out <br><br>She asked me Do I need to lose a bit of weight <br>And I told her Don't be stupid 'cause you're looking great <br>And I call her String Bean Jean because the label on her jeans says <br>Seven to eight years old well that's pretty small <br>Seven to eight years old that's pretty small <br>Seven to eight years old that's pretty small <br>Seven to eight years old]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="String Bean Jean" label="String Bean Jean"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Dog_On_Wheels/</id><title>Belle &amp; Sebastian - Dog On Wheels - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:04:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:04:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Belle__Sebastian/Dog_On_Wheels/" title="Belle &amp; Sebastian - Dog On Wheels - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I was a boy I was confounded by you <br>Now I'm still a boy I am indebted to you <br>Every song I ever wrote was written for you <br>Written for you <br><br>Now I'm feeling flat you seem mile away <br>I'm so tired that down on the pavement I'll lay <br>Till the blossom on the tree comes falling on me <br>Fall on me <br><br>From my window I can see the mountains in snow <br>From my window I will shut my eyes and let go <br>Promise me you'll always be around when I call <br>And when I fall <br><br>On the river bridge up on the wall, looking down <br>On the river bridge, to me a vision was shown <br>If I could hold on to things till I was full grown <br>Peace would I know <br><br>To my dog on wheels I'll tell my pleasures and woes <br>To my dog on wheels I'll tell my secrets and more <br>Then one day in spring I'll take him down to the road <br>Anything goes]]></content><category term="Belle &amp; Sebastian" label="Belle &amp; Sebastian"/><category term="Dog On Wheels" label="Dog On Wheels"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신사점/어디_갔어/</id><title>신사점 - 어디 갔어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:04:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:04:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%82%AC%EC%A0%90/%EC%96%B4%EB%94%94_%EA%B0%94%EC%96%B4/" title="신사점 - 어디 갔어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어디 갔어 내 월급은 <br>어디 갔어 내 월급이 <br>흑흑 하아 <br>내 한숨의 절반은 <br>다가오는 카드결제일 <br>뗄래야 뗄 수 없는 <br>야근은 필수가 되고 <br>가끔씩은 나도 남들처럼 <br>기분을 또 내면서 <br>항상 빚으로 물드는 <br>내가 너무나 무서워 <br>오늘도 지갑을 열고 <br>허세만 남고 남아서 <br>현금은 없어 <br>영수증만 남아서 흑흑 <br>어디 갔어 내 월급은 <br>어디 갔어 내 월급이 <br>있었는데 있었는데 <br>없잖아 내 돈 네 돈 <br>어디 갔어 내 월급은 <br>어디 갔어 내 월급이 <br>있었는데 체크카드에 <br>없잖아 잔액부족 <br>안 되겠다 엄카찬스 하아 <br>나와라 엄카찬스 <br>왜 힘들게 돈 벌어 <br>나를 위해 쓰지도 못해 <br>뺄래야 뺄 수 없는 <br>약속은 늘어만 가고 <br>내 품 안에 깊이 간직해둔 <br>사직서 하얀 봉투 <br>매일 눈치만 보면서 <br>다시 천 번은 참아 난 <br>멀고 먼 월급날까지 <br>쓸 일이 많고 많아서 <br>자존심 없어 <br>할부금만 남아서 흑흑 <br>어디 갔어 내 월급은 <br>어디 갔어 내 월급이 <br>있었는데 있었는데 <br>없잖아 내 돈 네 돈 <br>어디 갔어 내 월급은 <br>어디 갔어 내 월급이 <br>있었는데 체크카드에 <br>없잖아 잔액부족 <br>또 습관처럼 <br>가장 먼저 생각나는 건 <br>어디어디 나가야하는지 <br>하루를 견뎌내고 <br>또 하루를 살고 <br>왜 나는 하루를 지워내고 <br>또 하루를 버텨야해 <br>언제나 눈가리고 아웅 <br>이렇게 사는 삶이 <br>얼마나 값진 삶인가요 <br>걱정만 가득해 늘어만 <br>가는 메세지 속 카드값 <br>uh 먼저 차분하게 정리해둬 <br>가득한 내 머릿속에 마굿간 <br>쓸데없이 말만 많아 <br>난 또 겁을 내지만 여전해 <br>미안해서 내 월급이 <br>미안해져 내 월급이 <br>다 컸는데 다 컸는데 <br>알잖아 엄마 마음 <br>모자라서 내 월급이 <br>부족해서 내 월급이 <br>다 컸는데 손 내밀 수가 <br>없잖아 창피해져 <br>안 되겠다 엄카찬스 하아 <br>넣어둬 엄마카드 <br>]]></content><category term="신사점" label="신사점"/><category term="어디 갔어" label="어디 갔어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/무지개오락실/낮잠/</id><title>무지개오락실 - 낮잠 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B4%EC%A7%80%EA%B0%9C%EC%98%A4%EB%9D%BD%EC%8B%A4/%EB%82%AE%EC%9E%A0/" title="무지개오락실 - 낮잠 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자 이제 말해봐 <br>무슨 일이 있었는지 <br>너를 내 무릎위에 앉히고 <br>할 일을 미뤄두지 <br>커튼을 쳐 밤을 <br>끌어 당기지 <br>머리 위엔 <br>우리가 함께 붙인 <br>별들이 불을 밝히지 <br>너의 주위에 <br>많은 사람들이 <br>널 괴롭힌데 <br>왜 그러는데 <br>글쎄 이유는 <br>잘 모르겠는데 <br>한참을 같이 욕을 해 <br>그 사람들을 <br>얼굴도 본 적 없지만 <br>아무튼 맘에 안 드는 <br>난 니편 그만 바깥에 <br>기억들은 지워 <br>니 얼굴을 상하게 <br>만드는 것들이 너무 싫어 <br>이제 낮잠을 자 <br>널 눕히고 안은 다음 <br>손으로 니 등을 <br>천천히 두드려 잘 자 <br>take a nap <br>take a nap <br>take a nap <br>take a nap <br>take a nap <br>take a nap <br>take a nap <br>take a nap <br>아직 날도 <br>덜 풀린것 같아 <br>나가는 건 좀 그렇고 <br>방 안에서 우린 <br>이야기나 하다가 <br>낮잠을 자기 시작했지 <br>나지막한 숨소리 <br>내 품 속이 <br>편하다고 말하는 듯 <br>보여지는 표정이 <br>손길을 불러 <br>볼을 만지다 <br>안겨서 잠든 <br>너의 모습이 귀여워 <br>벅차 오르지 <br>팔이 아파 저려도 <br>잠이 행여 깰 까봐 <br>참지 일어날 시간이 <br>되어도 깨우기가 싫어 <br>이대로가 좋아서 <br>몇 시간을 더 <br>가만히 너를 보았어 <br>take a nap <br>take a nap <br>take a nap <br>take a nap <br>take a nap <br>take a nap <br>take a nap <br>take a nap <br>]]></content><category term="무지개오락실" label="무지개오락실"/><category term="낮잠" label="낮잠"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/무지개오락실/노래나_부르자/</id><title>무지개오락실 - 노래나 부르자 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B4%EC%A7%80%EA%B0%9C%EC%98%A4%EB%9D%BD%EC%8B%A4/%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98%EB%82%98_%EB%B6%80%EB%A5%B4%EC%9E%90/" title="무지개오락실 - 노래나 부르자 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그러니까 너를 봤대 <br>클럽에서 남자랑 같이 <br>스테이지 위에 <br>비비적 거리는 꼴보고 <br>기가 차서 너거 뒤에 <br>서서 가만히 쳐다보고 <br>있던 애들이 <br>내 친구 더 할말있나 니 <br>그때 잠 온다고 <br>먼저 잔다고 했던 <br>너의 그 연기도 확실히 <br>수준급이었고 <br>그런 장기 가지고 <br>몇 번이나 속였을꼬 <br>그런 줄도 모르고 <br>일 년을 만났고 <br>너의 과거부터 알아 볼 껄 <br>두터운 너의 철판 <br>개 버릇 남 못 준다는데 <br>어딜 가겠나 <br>클럽에서 딴 남자랑 <br>놀아난 그 날의 night time <br>더 이상 안 속아 <br>이제 너에게 없는 단어 다음 <br>라라라라라 노래나 부르자 <br>라라라라라 노래나 부르자 <br>라라라라라 노래나 부르자 <br>라라라라라 노래나 부르자 <br>야 아까부터 <br>배 고프다고 말했잖아 <br>왜 자꾸 젓가락 질을 <br>막냐 좀 놔 봐 <br>사진을 또 찍어 제껴 <br>올리기에 바빠 망할 <br>내가 산 밥을 <br>내가 못 먹고 있는 상황 <br>넌 항상 이런 식이지 <br>뭘 하든 니 중심이지 <br>내가 따지려고 들기만 해도 <br>곧바로 삐지지 <br>굳이 듣지 않더라도 <br>그 다음 질문이 무지 <br>뻔해 오빤 내가 <br>싫으냐고 묻지 이미 <br>싫어지는 중 니 사진 <br>찢어 버리는 중 <br>이해심 많은 오빠 <br>이미지 잊어 버리는 중 <br>자의식 과잉과 셀카성형 <br>중독 그거 병이지 <br>지가 이쁜 줄 알어 <br>병신이 다 엿 엿 엿이지 <br>받아 주기도 지겨워 <br>다 다 때려치고 싶어져 <br>야 사과 하지마 필요 없어 <br>니가 바뀐다고 일 없어 <br>넌 이제 내말 들을 필요 없어 <br>니 맘대로 살어 <br>나도 아주 신경 끌거야 <br>그렇게 알어 뿅 <br>라라라라라 노래나 부르자 <br>라라라라라 노래나 부르자 <br>라라라라라 노래나 부르자 <br>라라라라라 노래나 부르자 <br>속이 후련해 이런 말을 <br>내가 다 하네 <br>딱 너 같은 남자 <br>만나길 바라네 <br>너가 단물 빨아낸 <br>수 많은 캬라멜같은 <br>남자들 대신해서 <br>내가 말할게 <br>그래 속이 후련해 <br>이런 말을 내가 다 하네 <br>딱 너 같은 남자 <br>만나길 바라네 <br>소리 지를거면 질러 <br>이제 상관 안 할게 <br>이건 내 커피값이야 <br>나 먼저 나갈게 <br>라라라라라 노래나 부르자 <br>라라라라라 노래나 부르자 <br>라라라라라 노래나 부르자 <br>라라라라라 노래나 부르자 <br>]]></content><category term="무지개오락실" label="무지개오락실"/><category term="노래나 부르자" label="노래나 부르자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/무지개오락실/어른이/</id><title>무지개오락실 - 어른이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B4%EC%A7%80%EA%B0%9C%EC%98%A4%EB%9D%BD%EC%8B%A4/%EC%96%B4%EB%A5%B8%EC%9D%B4/" title="무지개오락실 - 어른이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[미안하단 너의 말 <br>굳이 듣고파서 <br>마음에 없어도 돼 <br>입으로 나오기만 해 <br>땡깡피는 나는 <br>어른인 척 하는 어른이 <br>그래서 떠난거니 <br>계속 연락 안받니 <br>미안하다고 <br>니 말은 다 맞고 <br>내 말은 다 틀려 <br>인정할게 할테니 <br>오빠 그만 전화 끊어 <br>뚝 뚝 끊어진 전화기 속 액정 <br>예의없는 걸로 치면 너는 백점 <br>황당해서 폰만 가 <br>만히 바라보는 <br>내 표정은 누가 봐도 개 쩖 <br>이래서 어린애랑 <br>연애하면 안된다며 <br>친구들 앞에서 치는 손사래 <br>집에 가는 길 불 꺼진 가게 <br>유리창에 비친 건 <br>익숙치 않은 내 모습 혼자네 <br>너무했나 내가 아냐 <br>잘못된 걸 말해준 건데 <br>지가 뭔데 괜히 <br>나에게 화를 내 <br>혼자 씩씩 거리다가도 <br>내일이면 분명 후회할 걸 <br>뻔히 아는데 <br>미안하단 너의 말 <br>굳이 듣고파서 <br>마음에 없어도 돼 <br>입으로 나오기만 해 <br>땡깡피는 나는 <br>어른인 척 하는 어른이 <br>그래서 떠난거니 <br>계속 연락 안받니 <br>사실 문제가 발생하거나 <br>싸움이 벌어지면 <br>늘 말을 많이 하는 것은 <br>내 쪽이었지 <br>꼴에 난 랩퍼에다가 <br>또 국문학과잖아 <br>아주 신나게 따졌지 <br>너를 몰아 세우면서 <br>아마 그때 니가 먼저 <br>사과를 했던 건 <br>더 잘못해서가 아니라 <br>우리 관계를 <br>더 생각해서 였단 걸 몰랐어 <br>멍청하게 굴다가 <br>혼자 남겨져서 <br>유치한 방식으로 <br>잘잘못을 따지고 <br>어른인 척 굴던 것들이 <br>창피하게 느껴지고 <br>지금은 삭제목록의 속 <br>니 얼굴들을 <br>엄지로 쓰다듬으며 <br>후회하고 있지 모든 걸 <br>조금 더 괜찮은 내가 될게 <br>너에게 불편한 <br>인간으로 남는 게 <br>너무 싫어 일단 너 <br>일 끝나고 나서 <br>정리해서 다시 말할게 <br>그땐 받어 <br>미안하단 너의 말 <br>굳이 듣고파서 <br>마음에 없어도 돼 <br>입으로 나오기만 해 <br>땡깡피는 나는 <br>어른인척 하는 어른이 <br>그래서 떠난거니 <br>계속 연락 안받니 <br>난 그냥 어른이고 <br>싶은 어린이었지 <br>난 그냥 어른이고 <br>싶은 어린이었지 <br>니가 잘못한 거니까 <br>빨리빨리 사과해 <br>너무 잘난 나머지 <br>이렇게 혼자 남았네 <br>난 그냥 어른이고 <br>싶은 어린이 <br>난 그냥 어른이고 <br>싶은 어린이 <br>애들은 제대로 된 <br>어른이 필요해 <br>넌 지금 어디니 <br>넌 지금 어디니 <br>미안하단 너의 말 <br>굳이 듣고파서 <br>마음에 없어도 돼 <br>입으로 나오기만 해 <br>땡깡피는 나는 <br>어른인척 하는 어른이 <br>그래서 떠난거니 <br>계속 연락 안받니 <br>]]></content><category term="무지개오락실" label="무지개오락실"/><category term="어른이" label="어른이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/무지개오락실/장마/</id><title>무지개오락실 - 장마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B4%EC%A7%80%EA%B0%9C%EC%98%A4%EB%9D%BD%EC%8B%A4/%EC%9E%A5%EB%A7%88/" title="무지개오락실 - 장마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너가 새로 샀다던 장화 <br>결국 보지못했어 <br>예쁜 노란색이랬는데 <br>아 완전 궁금했는데 <br>어제부터 시작된 장마 <br>티비보며 혼자 보냈어 <br>영활봐도 안 빠져 <br>천장이 새나 봐 <br>방이 물에 잠겨 <br>여느 때와 같이 일하러 가는 길 <br>비가 많이 오는데 넌 <br>어떻게 사는지 <br>묻고 싶은 맘을 입안에 박음질 <br>수화기 속 울고있던 <br>넌데 이젠 편하게 자는지 <br>나 너 없으니까 girl <br>감옥 안에 사는 것 같어 <br>입 속에 레몬 있는 것 같아서 <br>자꾸만 코 끝이 찡해져 <br>침을 칵 뱉어 <br>너가 새로 샀다던 장화 <br>결국 보지못했어 <br>예쁜 노란색이랬는데 <br>아 완전 궁금했는데 <br>어제부터 시작된 장마 <br>티비보며 혼자 보냈어 <br>영활봐도 안 빠져 <br>천장이 새나봐 <br>방이 물에 잠겨 <br>비나 왔음 좋겠다 <br>비나 내렸음 좋겠다 <br>데이트하는 애들 신발 <br>싹 다 배렸음 좋겠다 <br>눈물나게 우울한데 <br>우산 좀 챙겨 출근할때마다 <br>연락이 오던 누구한테 <br>소식을 듣고파 궁금한데 <br>퇴근 할 때면 친구들은 <br>날 가만두질 않아 <br>이놈들은 장마가 <br>반가운가봐 <br>딱 딱 한잔만 그래 <br>막걸리 한 사발 <br>먹다 보니까 니가 또 <br>생각이 나지만 알아 <br>늦었지 그 수없이 <br>많은 기횐 다 흩어지고 <br>차가 밟고 지나간 <br>웅덩이처럼 난 덩그러니 <br>아프고 또 차갑게 <br>남겨져 있어 주변이 <br>온통 날 비웃는 기분 <br>그래서 울었지 <br>여름휴가 계획은 <br>제주도보다 멀리 <br>날아갔지 난 가만히 <br>술집 달력을 바라봤지 <br>장마는 이제 시작이고 <br>난 계속 이럴 거니까 <br>너라도 잘 지냈음 좋겠다 <br>그런 거짓말 <br>너가 새로 샀다던 장화 <br>결국 보지못했어 <br>예쁜 노란색이랬는데 <br>아 완전 궁금했는데 <br>어제부터 시작된 장마 <br>티비보며 혼자 보냈어 <br>영활봐도 안 빠져 <br>천장이 새나봐 <br>방이 물에 잠겨 <br>아침에 왈칵했어 <br>나 이제 작은우산 <br>하나만 있음 되니까 <br>같이 쓸 필요가 없으니까 <br>화장실과 내 방 두 개만 <br>왔다갔다 하다가 또 하루가 <br>나 배탈났나 봐 <br>나 속이 비었나 봐 <br>허전해서 우나 봐 <br>너가 새로 샀다던 장화 <br>결국 보지못했어 <br>예쁜 노란색이랬는데 <br>아 완전 궁금했는데 <br>어제부터 시작된 장마 <br>티비보며 혼자 보냈어 <br>영활봐도 안 빠져 <br>천장이 새나봐 <br>방이 물에 잠겨 <br>똑 똑 똑 <br>그만 좀 나오라고 <br>똑 똑 똑 <br>엄마 배 아프다고 <br>똑 똑 똑 <br>난 대답도 못하고 <br>똑 똑 똑 <br>세면대를 꽉 붙잡고 <br>]]></content><category term="무지개오락실" label="무지개오락실"/><category term="장마" label="장마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/무지개오락실/동네_친구/</id><title>무지개오락실 - 동네 친구 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B4%EC%A7%80%EA%B0%9C%EC%98%A4%EB%9D%BD%EC%8B%A4/%EB%8F%99%EB%84%A4_%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC/" title="무지개오락실 - 동네 친구 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[머리를 감지 않아도 만날 수 있는 <br>아무거나 입어도 <br>보러 나갈 수 있는 <br>그러다 내가 거의 <br>잠옷 같은 걸 입고 나가면 <br>웃으며 이건 좀 <br>아니라고 말할 수 있는 <br>30분 정도는 걸을 수 있는 <br>순대 곱창 닭발을 먹을 수 있는 <br>연애얘기 연예인얘기 연예인이 <br>연애하는 얘기 없이 떠들 수 있는 <br>담배는 피던 안 피던 상관 없지만 <br>술은 적당히 곱게 마실 수 있는 <br>매일 클럽에서 <br>밤 새는 타입은 아니지만 <br>동네에선 늦게 돌아 다닐 수 있는 <br>영화나 음악 책 취향이 비슷해 <br>같이 욕하거나 좋아 할 수 있는 <br>그런 거 마땅히 할 거 없는 주말 <br>불러내서 그런 것들을 <br>같이 할 수 있는 <br>ay Good morning 너에게 톡을 보내고 <br>오늘은 왠지 술이 땡긴다고 <br>아주 가끔씩은 산책도 하고 <br>시간이 흘러가도 <br>그렇게 잘 지내자고 <br>일 마치고 슬리퍼 갈아신고 <br>술 마시고 서로 진상 부리고 <br>일 마치고 슬리퍼 갈아신고 <br>술 마시고 서로 진상 부리고 <br>매일 화장기 없는 얼굴하고 <br>자긴 원래 쌩얼이 더 예쁘다고 해 <br>난 어이 없다고 <br>말하지만 왠지 기분 좋아져 <br>마냥 친구는 아닌가 봐 <br>항상 짓궂은 말이 나와 <br>안 그러면 <br>내 맘을 들킬까봐 <br>그러니까 말은 좋지만 <br>친구는 아니야 <br>사실 너도 알지 다 남녀 사이가 <br>어떻게 친구가 돼 말이 돼 <br>출발을 친구로 <br>하긴 하더라만 안 그래 <br>물론 난 이대로 있을거야 <br>고백 했다가 차이면 <br>니가 미울거야 <br>이렇게 니 옆에 <br>친구로 남아 있으면 <br>이 좋은 것들을 <br>계속 같이 할 수 있는 걸 <br>ay Good morning 너에게 톡을 보내고 <br>오늘은 왠지 술이 땡긴다고 <br>아주 가끔씩은 산책도 하고 <br>시간이 흘러가도 <br>그렇게 잘 지내자고 <br>일 마치고 슬리퍼 갈아신고 <br>술 마시고 서로 진상 부리고 <br>일 마치고 슬리퍼 갈아신고 <br>술 마시고 서로 진상 부리고 <br>]]></content><category term="무지개오락실" label="무지개오락실"/><category term="동네 친구" label="동네 친구"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/무지개오락실/다시_아침/</id><title>무지개오락실 - 다시, 아침 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B4%EC%A7%80%EA%B0%9C%EC%98%A4%EB%9D%BD%EC%8B%A4/%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C_%EC%95%84%EC%B9%A8/" title="무지개오락실 - 다시, 아침 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다시 아침 <br>삶을 이어가지 나의 나침반이 <br>제 위치를 가르키는지를 확인 한 뒤 <br>잠시 기분좋은 것들을 <br>떠올리다가 이내 손잡이를 꺾어 <br>문을 열어 점점 벌어지는 <br>세상의 입 속으로 나를 집어넣어 <br>길 <br>매일 똑같이 걷는 그 위 <br>쏟아 지는 빛 혹은 비 <br>그것들을 맞으면서 <br>걸어가는 느낌 <br>밤새 싸늘히 식어있던 풍경 <br>태양의 더운 숨으로 물들면 <br>깨어나 크게 움직여 <br>아주 천천히 기지개를 키며 <br>어깨를 스치며 지나치는 <br>수백 수천 수만가지 이야기들 <br>그 속에 내가 있고 당신이 있지 <br>오늘은 어떤 표정일지 <br>긴 골목과 골목 <br>사이를 빠져나가서 <br>큰 길에 나와있는 사람들을 만나 <br>저마다의 꿈을 품은 그 눈들 <br>각자의 춤을 출 무대로 향하는 중 <br>다시 아침 <br>삶을 이어가지 나의 나침반이 <br>제 위치를 가르키는지를 확인 한 뒤 <br>잠시 기분좋은 것들을 <br>떠올리다가 이내 손잡이를 꺾어 <br>문을 열어 점점 벌어지는 <br>세상의 입 속으로 나를 집어넣어 <br>다시 아침 다시 아침 <br>다시 아침 다시 아침 <br>저마다 폰을 보며 <br>웃고 있는 사람들 <br>한 손엔 커피와 신문 <br>서류 가방든 아저씨 <br>가방에 같은 인형 걸어 둔 <br>같은 교복입은 남녀 어린 학생들 <br>작은 손 거울에 비친 <br>얼굴을 보며 화장을 하는 아가씨 <br>역 앞 택시를 잡는 대학생과 <br>짧은 치마 입고 <br>버슬 향해 뛰는 여자 <br>줄을 맞춰 올라가는 지하도 계단 <br>그 모든 곳에 녹아있어 변함없이 <br>매일 아침이면 우린 <br>같은 해를 바라 봐 <br>자신만의 빛을 향해 <br>조금씩 걸어가 <br>자신만의 빛을 향해 <br>조금씩 걸어가 <br>다시 아침 <br>삶을 이어가지 나의 나침반이 <br>제 위치를 가르키는지를 확인 한 뒤 <br>잠시 기분좋은 것들을 <br>떠올리다가 이내 손잡이를 꺾어 <br>문을 열어 점점 벌어지는 <br>세상의 입 속으로 나를 집어넣어 <br>다시 아침 다시 아침 <br>다시 아침 다시 아침 <br>]]></content><category term="무지개오락실" label="무지개오락실"/><category term="다시, 아침" label="다시, 아침"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sing_Street/Up/</id><title>Sing Street - Up - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sing_Street/Up/" title="Sing Street - Up - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's two o'clock on the edge of the morning <br>She's running magical circles around my head <br>I head to ride on a dream she's driving <br><br>She turns to kiss me, I crash back into bed <br>Across the street on a grayed out Monday <br>I see the girl with the eyes I can't describe <br>And suddenly it's a perfect Sunday <br>And everything is more real than life <br><br>I think I'm back in the dream <br>I think I'm back on the ceiling <br>It's such a beautiful feeling <br><br>Going up <br>She lights me up <br>She breaks me up <br>She lets me up <br><br>You find a mixture of bounding perfection <br>You've gotta read but you don't wanna reach the end <br>'Cause what if everything beautiful's fiction <br>And this reality's just pretend <br><br>And then I'm back in the dream <br>I'm looking up at the ceiling <br>It's such a beautiful feeling <br><br>Going up <br>She lights me up <br>She breaks me up <br>She lets me up <br><br>Up to the stars, she shows me <br>Dame Street, George's Street, miles below me <br>Up and the world won't let us down <br>Oh oh oh oh <br><br>Going up <br>It's two o'clock on the edge of the morning <br>She lights me up <br>She's running magical circles around my head <br>She breaks me up <br>I head to ride on a dream she's driving <br>She lets me up]]></content><category term="Sing Street" label="Sing Street"/><category term="Up" label="Up"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tove_Lo/Cool_Girl/</id><title>Tove Lo - Cool Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tove_Lo/Cool_Girl/" title="Tove Lo - Cool Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You can run free <br> I won't hold it against ya <br>You do your thing <br>never wanted a future <br>Fuck if I knew how to <br>put it romantic <br>Speaking my truth <br>there's no need to panic <br>No let's not put a label on it <br>Let's keep it fun <br>We don't put a label on it <br>So we can run free yeah <br>I wanna be free like you <br>I'm a I'm a I'm a cool girl <br>I'm a I'm a cool girl <br>Ice cold <br>I roll my eyes at you boy <br>I'm a cool girl <br>I'm a I'm a cool girl <br>Ice cold <br>I roll my eyes at you boy <br>Rules you don't like <br>but you still wanna keep 'em <br>Said you want fines <br>for whatever reason <br>Show we can chill <br>try and keep it platonic <br>Now you can't tell <br>if I'm really ironic <br>No let's not put a label on it <br>Let's keep it fun <br>We don't put a label on it <br>So we can run free yeah <br>I wanna be free like you <br>I'm a I'm a I'm a cool girl <br>I'm a I'm a cool girl <br>Ice cold <br>I roll my eyes at you boy <br>I'm a cool girl <br>I'm a I'm a cool girl <br>Ice cold <br>I roll my eyes at you boy <br>I'm a cool girl <br>I'm a I'm a cool girl <br>Ice cold <br>I roll my eyes at you boy <br>I'm a cool girl <br>I'm a I'm a cool girl <br>Ice cold <br>I roll my eyes at you boy <br>I got fever highs <br>I got boiling blood <br>I'm that fire kind <br>We could burn together <br>I'm a I'm a cool girl <br>I'm a I'm a cool girl <br>Ice cold <br>I roll my eyes at you boy <br>I'm a cool girl <br>I'm a I'm a cool girl <br>Ice cold <br>I roll my eyes at you boy <br>I'm a cool girl <br>I'm a I'm a cool girl <br>Too cool for you <br>I'm a cool girl <br>I'm a I'm a I'm a I'm a <br>I'm a I'm a cool girl <br>I'm a I'm a cool girl <br>Ice cold <br>I roll my eyes at you boy <br>]]></content><category term="Tove Lo" label="Tove Lo"/><category term="Cool Girl" label="Cool Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kungs/This_Girl_Kungs_Vs_Cookin_On_3_Burners/</id><title>Kungs - This Girl (Kungs Vs. Cookin` On 3 Burners) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kungs/This_Girl_Kungs_Vs_Cookin_On_3_Burners/" title="Kungs - This Girl (Kungs Vs. Cookin` On 3 Burners) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Money rains from the sky above <br>But keep the change <br>'cause I've got enough <br>A little time and some tenderness <br>You'll never buy my love <br>No other thing that's as precious to <br>No other There's no other <br>Than a heart that feel <br>and a heart that's true <br>Somethin' that you've got <br>to know this girl <br>Woh <br>Take my hand <br>Or them over Take my hand you <br>O or them over <br>Take my hand you <br>Or them over <br>Take my hand <br>Or them over <br>His presents don't really <br>come for free <br>Your paychecks don't mean <br>that much to me <br>Just take my hand <br>and hold me tight <br>You'll never buy my love <br>You buy me this <br>and you buy me that <br>To win over Win me over <br>You got me wrong and that's a fact <br>Somethin' that you've got <br>to love this <br>Will you realize when I'm gone <br>That I dance to a different song <br>Will you realize when I'm gone <br>That I dance to a different song <br>It's a shame but I've got to go <br>Woh <br>Take my hand <br>Or them over <br>Take my hand you <br>O or them over <br>Take my hand you <br>Or them over <br>Take my hand <br>Or them over <br>]]></content><category term="Kungs" label="Kungs"/><category term="This Girl (Kungs Vs. Cookin` On 3 Burners)" label="This Girl (Kungs Vs. Cookin` On 3 Burners)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hailee_Steinfeld/Rock_Bottom_Feat_DNCE/</id><title>Hailee Steinfeld - Rock Bottom (Feat. DNCE) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hailee_Steinfeld/Rock_Bottom_Feat_DNCE/" title="Hailee Steinfeld - Rock Bottom (Feat. DNCE) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What are we fighting for <br>Seems like we do it just for fun <br>In this this stupid war <br>We play hard with our plastic guns <br>Breathe deep bottle it up <br>So deep until it's all we got <br>Don't speak just use your touch <br>Don't speak before we say too much <br>That you hate me now <br>and I feel the same way <br>You love me now <br>and I feel the same way <br>Scream and we shout <br>And make up the same day <br>the same day <br>Oh we're on the right side <br>of rock bottom <br>And I hope that we keep falling <br>We're on the good side <br>of bad karma <br>Cause we keep on coming back <br>for more <br>We're on the right side <br>of rock bottom <br>And to you I just keep crawling <br>You're the best kind <br>of bad something <br>Cause we keep on coming back <br>for more <br>You get under my skin <br>More than anyone's ever been <br>But when we lay in bed <br>You hold me harder 'til I forget <br>That you hate me now <br>and I feel the same way <br>You love me now <br>and I feel the same way <br>Scream and we shout <br>And make up the same day <br>the same day <br>Oh we're on the right side <br>of rock bottom <br>And I hope that we keep falling <br>We're on the good side <br>of bad karma <br>Cause we keep on coming back <br>for more <br>We're on the right side <br>of rock bottom <br>And to you I just keep crawling <br>You're the best kind <br>of bad something <br>Cause we keep on coming back <br>for more <br>Keep on coming back for more <br>Cause we keep on coming back <br>for more <br>What are we fighting for <br>Seems like we do it just for fun <br>In this this just stupid war <br>We play hard with our plastic guns <br>Oh we're on the right side <br>of rock bottom <br>And I hope that we keep falling <br>We're on the good side <br>of bad karma <br>Cause we keep on coming back <br>for more <br>We're on the right side <br>of rock bottom <br>And to you I just keep crawling <br>You're the best kind <br>of bad something <br>Cause we keep on coming back <br>for more <br>Keep on coming back for more <br>Cause we keep on coming back <br>for more <br>Keep on coming back for more <br>Cause we keep on coming back <br>for more <br>]]></content><category term="Hailee Steinfeld" label="Hailee Steinfeld"/><category term="Rock Bottom (Feat. DNCE)" label="Rock Bottom (Feat. DNCE)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jonas_Blue/Perfect_Strangers_Feat_JP_Cooper/</id><title>Jonas Blue - Perfect Strangers (Feat. JP Cooper) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jonas_Blue/Perfect_Strangers_Feat_JP_Cooper/" title="Jonas Blue - Perfect Strangers (Feat. JP Cooper) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You were looking at me <br>like you wanted to stay <br>When I saw you yesterday <br>I'm not wasting your time <br>I'm not playing no games <br>I see you <br>Who knows the secret <br>tomorrow will hold <br>We don't really need to know <br>Cause you're here with me now <br>I don't want you to go <br>You're here with me now <br>I don't want you to go <br>Maybe we're perfect strangers <br>Maybe it's not forever <br>Maybe the night will change us <br>Maybe we'll stay together <br>Maybe we'll walk away <br>Maybe we'll realize <br>We're only human <br>Maybe we don't need no reason <br>Maybe we're perfect strangers <br>Maybe it's not forever <br>Maybe the night will change us <br>Maybe we'll stay together <br>Maybe we'll walk away <br>Maybe we'll realize <br>We're only human <br>Maybe we don't need no reason <br>Why <br>Come on come on come over <br>Maybe we don't need no reason <br>Why <br>Come on come on come over <br>No one but you got me <br>feeling this way <br>There's so much <br>we can't explain <br>Maybe we're helping <br>each other escape <br>I'm with you <br>Who knows the secret <br>tomorrow will hold <br>We don't really need to know <br>Cause you're here with me now <br>I don't want you to go <br>You're here with me now <br>I don't want you to go <br>Maybe we're perfect strangers <br>Maybe it's not forever <br>Maybe the night will change us <br>Maybe we'll stay together <br>Maybe we'll walk away <br>Maybe we'll realize <br>We're only human <br>Maybe we don't need no reason <br>Maybe we're perfect strangers <br>Maybe it's not forever <br>Maybe the night will change us <br>Maybe we'll stay together <br>Maybe we'll walk away <br>Maybe we'll realize <br>We're only human <br>Maybe we don't need no reason <br>Why <br>Come on come on come over <br>Maybe we don't need no reason <br>Why <br>Come on come on come over <br>Come on come on come over <br>Maybe we don't need no reason <br>Why <br>Come on come on come over <br>]]></content><category term="Jonas Blue" label="Jonas Blue"/><category term="Perfect Strangers (Feat. JP Cooper)" label="Perfect Strangers (Feat. JP Cooper)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Desiigner/Panda/</id><title>Desiigner - Panda - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Desiigner/Panda/" title="Desiigner - Panda - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This what they all been <br>waitin' for <br>I guess so <br>Panda Panda <br>Panda Panda Panda Panda Panda <br>I got broads in Atlanta <br>Twistin' dope lean and the Fanta <br>Credit cards and the scammers <br>Hittin' off licks in the bando <br>Black X6 Phantom <br>White X6 look like a panda <br>Goin' out like I'm Montana <br>Hundred killas hundred hammers <br>Black X6 Phantom <br>White X6 panda <br>Pockets swole Danny <br>Sellin' bar candy <br>Man I'm the macho like Randy <br>The choppa go Oscar for Grammy <br>Bitch nigga pull up ya panty <br>Hope you killas understand me <br>I got broads in Atlanta <br>Twistin' dope lean and the Fanta <br>Credit cards and the scammers <br>Hittin' off licks in the bando <br>Black X6 Phantom <br>White X6 look like a panda <br>Goin' out like I'm Montana <br>Hundred killas hundred hammers <br>Black X6 Phantom <br>White X6 panda <br>Pockets swole Danny <br>Sellin' bar candy <br>Man I'm the macho like Randy <br>The choppa go Oscar for Grammy <br>Bitch nigga pull up ya panty <br>Hope you killas understand me <br>Hey <br>Panda Panda <br>Panda Panda Panda Panda <br>Panda Panda Panda Panda <br>I got broads in Atlanta <br>Twistin' dope lean and shit <br>sippin' Fanta <br>Credit cards and the scammers <br>Wake up Versace shit <br>life Desiigner <br>Whole bunch of lavish shit <br>They be askin' 'round town <br>who be clappin' shit <br>I be pullin' up stuff <br>in the Phantom ship <br>I got plenty of stuff of Bugatti <br>whip look how I drive this shit <br>Black X6 Phantom <br>White X6 killin' on camera <br>Pop a Perc I can't stand up <br>Gorilla they come <br>and kill you with bananas <br>Four fillas they finna pull up <br>in the Phantom <br>Know niggas they come <br>and kill you on the camera <br>Big Rollie it dancin' bigger <br>than a Pandie <br>Go Oscar for Grammy <br>bitch pull up ya panty <br>Fill up I'ma flip it <br>I got bitches pull up <br>and they get it <br>I got niggas <br>that's countin' for digits <br>Say you make you <br>a lot of new money <br>Know some killas pull off <br>and they in the Wraith <br>CTD pull up in the killa Bape <br>Call up Phillip Phillip <br>gon' fill the bank <br>Niggas up in the bank <br>we gon' drill the bank <br>Fuck we gon' kill the bank get it <br>I got broads yea I get it <br>I get cards yea I shitted <br>This how I live it <br>Did it all for a ticket <br>Now Flex drop bombs <br>when he spin it <br>And Bobby gon' trend it <br>Jeff The Don doin' business <br>Zana Ray fuckin' up shit <br>and she doin' her business <br>I be gettin' to the chicken <br>Countin' to the chicken <br>And all of my niggas gon' split it <br>Panda Panda <br>Panda Panda Panda Panda Panda <br>I got broads in Atlanta <br>Twistin' dope lean and the Fanta <br>Credit cards and the scammers <br>Hittin' off licks in the bando <br>Black X6 Phantom <br>White X6 look like a panda <br>Goin' out like I'm Montana <br>Hundred killas hundred hammers <br>Black X6 Phantom <br>White X6 panda <br>Pockets swole Danny <br>Sellin' bar candy <br>Man I'm the macho like Randy <br>The choppa go Oscar for Grammy <br>Bitch nigga pull up ya panty <br>Hope you killas understand me <br>I got broads in Atlanta <br>Twistin' dope lean and the Fanta <br>Credit cards and the scammers <br>Hittin' off licks in the bando <br>Black X6 Phantom <br>White X6 look like a panda <br>Goin' out like I'm Montana <br>Hundred killas hundred hammers <br>Black X6 Phantom <br>White X6 panda <br>Pockets swole Danny <br>Sellin' bar candy <br>Man I'm the macho like Randy <br>The choppa go Oscar for Grammy <br>Bitch nigga pull up ya panty <br>Hope you killas understand me <br>Panda Panda <br>Panda Panda Panda Panda Panda <br>Panda Panda Panda Panda <br>]]></content><category term="Desiigner" label="Desiigner"/><category term="Panda" label="Panda"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alessia_Cara/Here/</id><title>Alessia Cara - Here - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alessia_Cara/Here/" title="Alessia Cara - Here - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I guess right now <br>you've got the last laugh <br>I'm sorry if I seem uninterested <br>Or I'm not listenin' <br>or I'm indifferent <br>Truly I ain't got no business here <br>But since my friends are here <br>I just came to kick it but really <br>I would rather be at home <br>all by myself not in this room <br>With people who don't even care <br>about my well being <br>I don't dance don't ask <br>I don't need a boyfriend <br>So you can go back <br>please enjoy your party <br>I'll be here <br>somewhere in the corner <br>under clouds of marijuana <br>With this boy <br>who's hollering I can hardly hear <br>Over this music <br>I don't listen to <br>and I don't wanna get with you <br>So tell my friends <br>that I'll be over here <br>Oh oh oh here <br>oh oh oh here oh oh oh <br>I ask myself <br>what am I doing here <br>Oh oh oh here oh oh oh here <br>And I can't wait till <br>we can break up outta here <br>Excuse me if <br>I seem a little <br>unimpressed with this <br>An anti social pessimist <br>but usually I don't mess with this <br>And I know you <br>mean only the best and <br>Your intentions aren't to bother me <br>But honestly I'd rather be <br>Somewhere with my people <br>we can kick it and just listen <br>To some music <br>with the message like we usually do <br>And we'll discuss our big dreams <br>How we plan to take over the planet <br>So pardon my manners <br>I hope you'll understand it <br>That I'll be here <br>Not there in the kitchen <br>with the girl <br>Who's always gossiping <br>about her friends <br>So tell them I'll be here <br>Right next to the boy <br>who's throwing up 'cause <br>He can't take <br>what's in his cup no more <br>Oh God why am I here <br>Oh oh oh here <br>oh oh oh here oh oh oh <br>I ask myself <br>what am I doing here <br>Oh oh oh here oh oh oh here <br>And I can't wait till <br>we can break up outta here <br>Hours later congregating <br>next to the refrigerator <br>Some girl's talking 'bout <br>her haters <br>She ain't got none <br>How did it ever come to this <br>I shoulda never come to this <br>So holla at me <br>I'll be in the car when you're done <br>I'm standoffish <br>don't want what you're offering <br>And I'm done talking <br>Awfully sad it had to be that way <br>So tell my people <br>when they're ready that I'm ready <br>And I'm standing by the TV <br>with my beanie low <br>Yo I'll be over here <br>Oh oh oh here <br>oh oh oh here oh oh oh <br>I ask myself what am I doing here <br>Oh oh oh here oh oh oh here <br>And I can't wait till <br>we can break up outta here <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>]]></content><category term="Alessia Cara" label="Alessia Cara"/><category term="Here" label="Here"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Bay/Let_It_Go/</id><title>James Bay - Let It Go - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Bay/Let_It_Go/" title="James Bay - Let It Go - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[From walking home <br>and talking loads <br>To seeing shows in <br>evening clothes with you <br>From nervous touch <br>and getting drunk <br>To staying up <br>and waking up with you <br>But now we're slipping at the edge <br>Holding something we don't need <br>All this delusion in our heads <br>Is gonna bring us to our knees <br>So come on let it go <br>Just let it be <br>Why don't you be you <br>And I'll be me <br>Everything that's broke <br>Leave it to the breeze <br>Why don't you be you <br>And I'll be me <br>And I'll be me <br>From throwing clothes <br>across the floor <br>To teeth and claws <br>and slamming doors at you <br>If this is all we're living for <br>Why are we doing it <br>doing it doing it anymore <br>I used to recognize myself <br>It's funny how reflections change <br>When we're becoming <br>something else <br>I think it's time to walk away <br>So come on let it go <br>Just let it be <br>Why don't you be you <br>And I'll be me <br>Everything that's broke <br>Leave it to the breeze <br>Why don't you be you <br>And I'll be me <br>And I'll be me <br>Trying to fit your hand <br>inside of mine <br>When we know it <br>just don't belong <br>There's no force on earth <br>Could make it feel right no <br>Whoa <br>Trying to push this problem <br>up the hill <br>When it's just too heavy to hold <br>Think now's the time to let it slide <br>So come on let it go <br>Just let it be <br>Why don't you be you <br>And I'll be me <br>Everything that's broke <br>Leave it to the breeze <br>Let the ashes fall <br>Forget about me <br>Come on let it go <br>Just let it be <br>Why don't you be you <br>And I'll be me <br>And I'll be me <br>]]></content><category term="James Bay" label="James Bay"/><category term="Let It Go" label="Let It Go"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Calum_Scott/Dancing_On_My_Own/</id><title>Calum Scott - Dancing On My Own - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Calum_Scott/Dancing_On_My_Own/" title="Calum Scott - Dancing On My Own - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Somebody said you got a new friend <br>Does she love you better than I can <br>There's a big black sky over my town <br>I know where you're at I bet she's around <br>And yeah I know it's stupid <br>But I just got a see it for myself <br><br>I'm in the corner watching you kiss her <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>And I'm right over here why can't you see me <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>And I'm givin it my all <br>But I'm not the guy you're taking home <br>Oooooh <br>I keep dancing on my own <br><br>I just wanna dance all night <br>I'm all messed up I'm so out of line <br>Stilettos and broken bottles <br>I'm spinnin around in circles <br><br>And I'm in the corner watching you kiss her <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>And I'm right over here why can't you see me <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>And I'm givin it my all <br>But I'm not the guy you're taking home <br>Ooooo <br>I keep dancing on my own <br>And ohh, no noo <br><br>So far away <br>But still so near <br>The lights come on <br>The music dies <br>But you don't see me standing here <br>I just came to say goodbye <br><br>And I'm in the corner watching you kiss her <br>Ohhhhhhh <br>And I'm givin it my all <br>But I'm not the guy you're taking home <br>Oooooo <br>I keep dancing on my own <br>And ohh, noo <br><br>And I'm in the corner watching you kiss her <br>Oh no <br>And I'm right over here why can't you see me <br>Oh no <br>And I'm givin it my all <br>But I'm not the guy you're taking home <br>Oooooh <br>I keep dancing on my own <br><br>So far away <br>But still so near <br>The lights come on <br>The music dies <br>But you don't see me standing here]]></content><category term="Calum Scott" label="Calum Scott"/><category term="Dancing On My Own" label="Dancing On My Own"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ellie_Goulding/Love_Me_Like_You_Do_영화_그레이의_50가지_그림자_OST_From_Fifty_Shades_Of_Grey/</id><title>Ellie Goulding - Love Me Like You Do (영화 `그레이의 50가지 그림자` OST) (From `Fifty Shades Of Grey`) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ellie_Goulding/Love_Me_Like_You_Do_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EC%9D%98_50%EA%B0%80%EC%A7%80_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%BC%EC%9E%90_OST_From_Fifty_Shades_Of_Grey/" title="Ellie Goulding - Love Me Like You Do (영화 `그레이의 50가지 그림자` OST) (From `Fifty Shades Of Grey`) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're the light you're the night <br>You're the colour of my blood <br>You're the cure you're the pain <br>You're the only thing I wanna touch <br>Never knew that it <br>could mean so much so much <br>You're the fear I don't care <br>'Cause I've never been so high <br>Follow me to the dark <br>Let me take you past our satellites <br>You can see the world you <br>brought to life to life <br>So love me like you do <br>la la love me like you do <br>Love me like you do <br>la la love me like you do <br>Touch me like you do <br>ta ta touch me like you do <br>What are you waiting for <br>Fading in fading out <br>On the edge of paradise <br>Every inch of your skin <br>is a holy grail I've got to find <br>Only you can set <br>my heart on fire on fire <br>Yeah I'll let you set the pace <br>'Cause I'm not thinking straight <br>My head's spinning around <br>I can't see clear no more <br>What are you waiting for <br>Love me like you do <br>la la love me like you do like you do <br>Love me like you do <br>la la love me like you do <br>Touch me like you do <br>ta ta touch me like you do <br>What are you waiting for <br>Love me like you do <br>la la love me like you do like you do <br>Love me like you do <br>la la love me like you do yeah <br>Touch me like you do <br>ta ta touch me like you do <br>What are you waiting for <br>I'll let you set the pace <br>'Cause I'm not thinking straight <br>My head's spinning around <br>I can't see clear no more <br>What are you waiting for <br>Love me like you do <br>la la love me like you do like you do <br>Love me like you do <br>la la love me like you do yeah <br>Touch me like you do <br>ta ta touch me like you do <br>What are you waiting for <br>Love me like you do <br>la la love me like you do like you do <br>Love me like you do <br>la la love me like you do oh <br>Touch me like you do <br>ta ta touch me like you do <br>What are you waiting for <br>]]></content><category term="Ellie Goulding" label="Ellie Goulding"/><category term="Love Me Like You Do (영화 `그레이의 50가지 그림자` OST) (From `Fifty Shades Of Grey`)" label="Love Me Like You Do (영화 `그레이의 50가지 그림자` OST) (From `Fifty Shades Of Grey`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Weeknd/The_Hills/</id><title>The Weeknd - The Hills - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Weeknd/The_Hills/" title="The Weeknd - The Hills - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah yeah yeah <br>Your man on the road <br>he doin' promo <br>You said Keep our business <br>on the low low <br>I'm just tryna get you <br>out the friend zone <br>Cause you look even better <br>than the photos <br>I can't find your house <br>send me the info <br>Drivin' through <br>the gated residential <br>Found out I was comin' <br>sent your friends home <br>Keep on tryna hide it <br>but your friends know <br>I only call you <br>when it's half past five <br>The only time <br>that I'll be by your side <br>I only love it when you touch me <br>not feel me <br>When I'm fucked up <br>that's the real me <br>When I'm fucked up <br>that's the real me yeah <br>I only call you <br>when it's half past five <br>The only time I'd ever <br>call you mine <br>I only love it when you touch me <br>not feel me <br>When I'm fucked up <br>that's the real me <br>When I'm fucked up <br>that's the real me babe <br>I'ma let you know <br>and keep it simple <br>Tryna keep it up <br>don't seem so simple <br>I just fucked two bitches <br>'fore I saw you <br>And you gon' have <br>to do it at my tempo <br>Always tryna send me <br>off to rehab <br>Drugs started <br>feelin' like it's decaf <br>I'm just tryna live life <br>for the moment <br>And all these motherfuckers <br>want a relapse <br>I only call you <br>when it's half past five <br>The only time <br>that I'll be by your side <br>I only love it when you touch me <br>not feel me <br>When I'm fucked up <br>that's the real me <br>When I'm fucked up <br>that's the real me yeah <br>I only call you <br>when it's half past five <br>The only time I'd ever <br>call you mine <br>I only love it when you touch me <br>not feel me <br>When I'm fucked up <br>that's the real me <br>When I'm fucked up <br>that's the real me babe <br>Hills have eyes <br>the hills have eyes <br>Who are you to judge <br>who are you to judge <br>Hide your lies girl <br>hide your lies <br>Only you to trust <br>only you <br>I only call you <br>when it's half past five <br>The only time <br>that I'll be by your side <br>I only love it when you touch me <br>not feel me <br>When I'm fucked up <br>that's the real me <br>When I'm fucked up <br>that's the real me yeah <br>I only fuck you <br>when it's half past five <br>The only time I'd ever call you mine <br>I only love it when you touch me <br>not feel me <br>When I'm fucked up <br>that's the real me <br>When I'm fucked up <br>that's the real me babe <br>Ewedihalehu <br>Yene konjo ewedihalehu <br>Yene fikir fikir fikir fikir <br>Yene fikir fikir fikir fikir <br>]]></content><category term="The Weeknd" label="The Weeknd"/><category term="The Hills" label="The Hills"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Years__Years/Desire_Feat_Tove_Lo/</id><title>Years &amp; Years - Desire (Feat. Tove Lo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:05:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:05:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Years__Years/Desire_Feat_Tove_Lo/" title="Years &amp; Years - Desire (Feat. Tove Lo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I must be tough <br>I must behave <br>I must keep fighting <br>Don't give it up <br>I want to keep us compromising <br>Open your arms and pray <br>To the truth that you're denying <br>Give in to the game <br>To the sense that you've been hiding <br>Where are you taking me <br>I can't be blamed <br>I want you to want me again <br>Is it desire <br>Or is it love that I'm feeling for you <br>I want desire <br>Cause your love only gets me abused <br>Chasing that rush <br>I need to show you <br>what you've been missing <br>And give me your touch <br>All of your love is not forbidden <br>Where are you taking me <br>I can't be blamed <br>I want you to want me again <br>Is it desire <br>Or is it love that I'm feeling for you <br>I want desire <br>Cause your love only gets me abused <br>Is it desire <br>Or is it love that I'm feeling for you <br>I want desire <br>I wanna see <br>what you're willing to lose <br>Taking pretending <br>you're nothing but giving <br>Making me lose my cool <br>Faking my love game <br>baby we're the same <br>Heart turned from good to cruel <br>You know that you've got me <br>You've loved me down <br>You tell me you want me now <br>Is it desire <br>Or is it love that I'm feeling for you <br>I want desire <br>Cause your love only gets me abused <br>Is it desire <br>Or is it love that I'm feeling for you <br>I want desire <br>I wanna see <br>what you're willing to lose <br>what you're willing to lose <br>what you're willing to lose <br>Is it desire <br>]]></content><category term="Years &amp; Years" label="Years &amp; Years"/><category term="Desire (Feat. Tove Lo)" label="Desire (Feat. Tove Lo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mike_Posner/I_Took_A_Pill_In_Ibiza_Seeb_Remix/</id><title>Mike Posner - I Took A Pill In Ibiza (Seeb Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:06:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:06:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mike_Posner/I_Took_A_Pill_In_Ibiza_Seeb_Remix/" title="Mike Posner - I Took A Pill In Ibiza (Seeb Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I took a pill in Ibiza <br>To show Avicii I was cool <br>And when I finally got sober <br>felt ten years older <br>But fuck it it was something to do <br>I'm living out in LA <br>I drive a sports car just to prove <br>I'm a real big baller <br>cause I made a million dollars <br>And I spend it on girls and shoes <br>But you don't wanna be high like me <br>Never really knowing why like me <br>You don't ever wanna step off <br>that roller coaster and be <br>All alone <br>You don't wanna ride <br>the bus like this <br>Never knowing who to trust like this <br>You don't wanna be stuck up <br>on that stage singing <br>Stuck up on that stage singing <br>All I know <br>Are sad songs sad songs <br>Darling all I know <br>Are sad songs sad songs <br>I know are sad songs <br>I know are sad songs <br>I know are sad songs <br>I know are sad songs <br>I'm just a singer <br>Who already blew his shot <br>I get along with old timers <br>cause my name's a reminder <br>Of a pop song people forgot <br>And I can't keep a girl no <br>Cause as soon as the sun comes up <br>I cut 'em all loose <br>and work's my excuse <br>But the truth is I can't open up <br>And you don't wanna be high like me <br>Never really knowing why like me <br>You don't ever wanna step off <br>that roller coaster and be <br>All alone <br>You don't wanna ride <br>the bus like this <br>Never knowing who to trust like this <br>You don't wanna be stuck up <br>on that stage singing <br>Stuck up on that stage singing <br>All I know <br>Are sad songs sad songs <br>Darling all I know <br>Are sad songs sad songs <br>I know are sad songs <br>I know are sad songs <br>Sad songs <br>I know are sad songs <br>Sad songs <br>I know are sad songs <br>]]></content><category term="Mike Posner" label="Mike Posner"/><category term="I Took A Pill In Ibiza (Seeb Remix)" label="I Took A Pill In Ibiza (Seeb Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DJ_Snake/Middle_Feat_Bipolar_Sunshine/</id><title>DJ Snake - Middle (Feat. Bipolar Sunshine) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:06:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:06:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DJ_Snake/Middle_Feat_Bipolar_Sunshine/" title="DJ Snake - Middle (Feat. Bipolar Sunshine) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Staring at two different <br>views on your window ledge <br>Coffee has gone cold <br>it's like time froze <br>There you go wishing <br>floating down our wishing well <br>It's like I'm always <br>causing problems <br>causing hell <br>I didn't mean to <br>put you through this <br>I can tell <br>We're gonna sweep <br>this under the carpet <br>I hope that I can <br>turn back the time <br>To make it all alright <br>all alright for us <br>I'll promise to build <br>a new world for us two <br>With you in the middle <br>you in the middle <br>you in the middle <br>Lying down beside you <br>What's going through your head <br>The silence in the air <br>felt like my soul froze <br>Am I just overthinking <br>feelings I conceal <br>This gut feeling <br>I'm tryna get off me as well <br>I hope we find our missing <br>pieces and just chill <br>We're gonna sweep it <br>under the carpet <br>I hope that I can <br>turn back the time <br>To make it all alright <br>all alright for us <br>I'll promise to build <br>a new world for us two <br>With you in the middle <br>you in the middle <br>you in the middle <br>with you <br>you <br>thank the children <br>just thank the children <br>you <br>thank the children <br>just thank the children <br>]]></content><category term="DJ Snake" label="DJ Snake"/><category term="Middle (Feat. Bipolar Sunshine)" label="Middle (Feat. Bipolar Sunshine)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DNCE/Cake_By_The_Ocean/</id><title>DNCE - Cake By The Ocean - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:06:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:06:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DNCE/Cake_By_The_Ocean/" title="DNCE - Cake By The Ocean - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh no <br>See you walking 'round <br>like it's a funeral <br>Not so serious <br>girl why those feet cold <br>We just getting started <br>don't you tip toe tip toe <br>Ah <br>Waste time with a masterpiece <br>don't waste time <br>with a masterpiece huh <br>You should be rolling with me <br>you should be rolling with me ah <br>You're a real life fantasy <br>you're a real life fantasy huh <br>But you're moving <br>so carefully let's start <br>living dangerously <br>Talk to me baby <br>I'm going blind from this sweet <br>sweet craving whoa <br>Let's lose our minds <br>and go fucking crazy <br>Ah ya ya ya ya I keep on hoping <br>we'll eat cake by the ocean <br>Walk for me baby <br>I'll be Diddy <br>you'll be Naomi whoa <br>Let's lose our minds <br>and go fucking crazy <br>Ah ya ya ya ya I keep on hoping <br>we'll eat cake by the ocean huh <br>God damn <br>See you licking frosting <br>from your own hands <br>Want another taste <br>I'm begging Yes ma'am <br>I'm tired of all this candy <br>on the dry land dry land oh <br>Waste time with a masterpiece <br>don't waste time <br>with a masterpiece huh <br>You should be rolling with me <br>you should be rolling with me ah <br>You're a real life fantasy <br>you're a real life fantasy huh <br>But you're moving <br>so carefully let's start <br>living dangerously <br>Whoa <br>Talk to me baby <br>I'm going blind from this sweet <br>sweet craving whoa <br>Let's lose our minds <br>and go fucking crazy <br>Ah ya ya ya ya I keep <br>on hoping we'll eat cake by the ocean <br>Walk for me baby walk for me now <br>I'll be Diddy you'll be Naomi whoa <br>Let's lose our minds <br>and go fucking crazy <br>Ah ya ya ya ya I keep on hoping <br>we'll eat cake by the ocean <br>Oh ah <br>Ah ya ya ya ya I keep on hoping <br>we'll eat cake by the ocean <br>Oh ah <br>Ah ya ya ya ya I keep on hoping <br>we'll eat cake by the ocean huh <br>You're fucking delicious <br>Talk to me girl <br>Talk to me baby <br>I'm going blind from this sweet <br>sweet craving whoa <br>Let's lose our minds <br>and go fucking crazy <br>Ah ya ya ya ya I keep on hoping <br>we'll eat cake by the ocean <br>Walk for me baby walk for me now <br>I'll be Diddy you'll be Naomi whoa <br>Let's lose our minds <br>and go fucking crazy <br>Ah ya ya ya ya I keep on hoping <br>we'll eat cake by the ocean huh <br>Red velvet vanilla chocolate <br>in my life <br>Funfetti I'm ready <br>I need it every night <br>Red velvet vanilla chocolate <br>in my life <br>Ah ya ya ya ya I keep on hoping <br>we'll eat cake by the ocean huh <br>]]></content><category term="DNCE" label="DNCE"/><category term="Cake By The Ocean" label="Cake By The Ocean"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Katy_Perry/Rise/</id><title>Katy Perry - Rise - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:06:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:06:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Katy_Perry/Rise/" title="Katy Perry - Rise - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I won't just survive <br>Oh you will see me thrive <br>Can write my story <br>I'm beyond the archetype <br>I won't just conform <br>No matter how <br>you shake my core <br>Cause my roots <br>they run deep oh <br>Oh ye of so little faith <br>Don't doubt it don't doubt it <br>Victory is in my veins <br>I know it I know it <br>And I will not negotiate <br>I'll fight it I'll fight it <br>I will transform <br>When when the fire's <br>at my feet again <br>And the vultures <br>all start circling <br>They're whispering <br>you're out of time <br>But still I rise <br>This is no mistake <br>no accident <br>When you think the final <br>nail is in think again <br>Don't be surprised <br>I will still rise <br>I must stay conscious <br>Through the madness and chaos <br>So I call on my angels <br>They say <br>Oh ye of so little faith <br>Don't doubt it don't doubt it <br>Victory is in your veins <br>You know it you know it <br>And you will not negotiate <br>Just fight it just fight it <br>And be transformed <br>'Cause when <br>when the fire's <br>at my feet again <br>And the vultures <br>all start circling <br>They're whispering <br>you're out of time <br>But still I rise <br>This is no mistake <br>no accident <br>When you think the final <br>nail is in think again <br>Don't be surprised <br>I will still rise <br>Don't doubt it don't doubt it <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>You know it you know it <br>Still rise <br>Just fight it just fight it <br>Don't be surprised <br>I will still rise <br>]]></content><category term="Katy Perry" label="Katy Perry"/><category term="Rise" label="Rise"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shawn_Mendes/Treat_You_Better/</id><title>Shawn Mendes - Treat You Better - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:06:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:06:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shawn_Mendes/Treat_You_Better/" title="Shawn Mendes - Treat You Better - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I won't lie to you <br>I know he's just not right for you <br>And you can tell me if I'm off <br>But I see it on your face <br>When you say <br>that he's the one that you want <br>And you're spending all your time <br>In this wrong situation <br>And anytime you want it to stop <br>I know I can treat you <br>better than he can <br>And any girl like you <br>deserves a gentleman <br>Tell me why are we wasting time <br>On all your wasted crying <br>When you should be with me instead <br>I know I can treat you better <br>Better than he can <br>I'll stop time for you <br>The second you say you'd like me to <br>I just wanna give you <br>the loving that you're missing <br>Baby just to wake up with you <br>Would be everything <br>I need and this could be so different <br>Tell me what you want to do <br>'Cause I know <br>I can treat you better than he can <br>And any girl like you <br>deserves a gentleman <br>Tell me why are we wasting time <br>On all your wasted crying <br>When you should be with me instead <br>I know I can treat you better <br>Better than he can <br>Better than he can <br>Give me a sign <br>Take my hand we'll be fine <br>Promise I won't let you down <br>Just know that you don't <br>Have to do this alone <br>Promise I'll never let you down <br>'Cause I know <br>I can treat you better than he can <br>And any girl like you <br>deserves a gentleman <br>Tell me why are we wasting time <br>On all your wasted crying <br>When you should be with me instead <br>I know I can treat you better <br>Better than he can <br>Better than he can <br>Better than he can <br>]]></content><category term="Shawn Mendes" label="Shawn Mendes"/><category term="Treat You Better" label="Treat You Better"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ariana_Grande/Into_You/</id><title>Ariana Grande - Into You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:06:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:06:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ariana_Grande/Into_You/" title="Ariana Grande - Into You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm so into you <br>I can barely breathe <br>And all I wanna do <br>is to fall in deep <br>But close ain't close enough <br>'til we cross the line hey yeah <br>So name a game to play <br>and I'll roll a dice hey <br>Oh baby look what you started <br>The temperature's rising in here <br>Is this gonna happen <br>Been waiting and waiting <br>for you to make a move <br>woo oh oh oh <br>Before I make a move <br>woo oh oh oh <br>So baby come light me up <br>and maybe I'll let you on it <br>A little bit dangerous but <br>baby that's how I want it <br>A little less conversation <br>and a little more touch my body <br>'Cause I'm so into you <br>into you into you <br>Got everyone watchin' us <br>so baby let's keep it secret <br>A little bit scandalous but <br>baby don't let them see it <br>A little less conversation <br>and a little more touch my body <br>'Cause I'm so into you <br>into you into you oh yeah <br>This could take some time hey <br>I made too many mistakes <br>Better get this right right baby <br>Oh baby look what you started <br>The temperature's rising in here <br>Is this gonna happen <br>Been waiting and waiting <br>for you to make a move <br>woo oh oh oh <br>Before I make a move <br>woo oh oh oh <br>So baby come light me up <br>and maybe I'll let you on it <br>A little bit dangerous but <br>baby that's how I want it <br>A little less conversation <br>and a little more touch my body <br>'Cause I'm so into you <br>into you into you <br>Got everyone watchin' us so <br>baby let's keep it secret <br>A little bit scandalous but <br>baby don't let them see it <br>A little less conversation <br>and a little more touch my body <br>'Cause I'm so into you <br>into you into you <br>Tell me what you came here for <br>'Cause I can't <br>I can't wait no more <br>I'm on the edge with no control <br>And I need I need you to know <br>You to know oh <br>So baby come light me up <br>and maybe I'll let you on it <br>A little bit dangerous but <br>baby that's how I want it <br>A little less conversation <br>and a little more touch my body <br>'Cause I'm so into you <br>into you into you <br>Got everyone watchin' us so <br>baby let's keep it secret <br>A little bit scandalous but <br>baby don't let them see it <br>A little less conversation <br>and a little more touch my body <br>'Cause I'm so into you <br>into you into you <br>So come light me up <br>so come light me up my baby <br>A little dangerous <br>a little dangerous my baby <br>A little less conversation <br>and a little more touch my body <br>'Cause I'm so into you <br>into you into you <br>]]></content><category term="Ariana Grande" label="Ariana Grande"/><category term="Into You" label="Into You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Troye_Sivan/Youth/</id><title>Troye Sivan - Youth - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:06:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:06:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Troye_Sivan/Youth/" title="Troye Sivan - Youth - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What if <br>What if we run away <br>What if <br>What if we left today <br>What if <br>We said goodbye to safe and sound <br>What if <br>What if we're hard to find <br>What if <br>What if we lost our minds <br>What if <br>We let them fall behind <br>and they're never found <br>And when the lights start <br>flashing like a photo booth <br>And the stars exploding <br>We'll be fireproof <br>My youth <br>My youth is yours <br>Trippin' on skies <br>sippin' waterfalls <br>My youth <br>My youth is yours <br>Run away now and forevermore <br>My youth <br>My youth is yours <br>The truth so loud you can't ignore <br>My youth my youth my youth <br>My youth is yours <br>What if <br>What if we start to drive <br>What if <br>What if we close our eyes <br>What if <br>We're speeding <br>through red lights into paradise <br>'Cause we've no time <br>for getting old <br>Mortal bodies timeless souls <br>Cross your fingers here we go <br>Oh oh oh <br>And when the lights start <br>flashing like a photo booth <br>And the stars exploding <br>We'll be fireproof <br>My youth <br>My youth is yours <br>Trippin' on skies sippin' <br>waterfalls <br>My youth <br>My youth is yours <br>Run away now and forevermore <br>My youth <br>My youth is yours <br>The truth so loud you can't ignore <br>My youth my youth my youth <br>My youth is yours <br>My youth is yours <br>My youth <br>My youth is yours <br>Trippin' on skies <br>sippin' waterfalls <br>My youth <br>My youth is yours <br>Run away now and forevermore <br>My youth <br>My youth is yours <br>The truth so loud you can't ignore <br>My youth my youth my youth <br>My youth is yours <br>Oh oh oh <br>My youth is yours <br>Oh oh oh <br>My youth is yours <br>]]></content><category term="Troye Sivan" label="Troye Sivan"/><category term="Youth" label="Youth"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Justin_Bieber/Sorry/</id><title>Justin Bieber - Sorry - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:06:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:06:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Justin_Bieber/Sorry/" title="Justin Bieber - Sorry - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You gotta go and get angry <br>at all of my honesty <br>You know I try <br>but I don't do too well <br>with apologies <br>I hope I don't run out of time <br>Could someone call a referee <br>'Cause I just need one more <br>shot at forgiveness <br>I know you know <br>that I made those mistakes <br>maybe once or twice <br>And by once or twice <br>I mean maybe a couple <br>of hundred times <br>So let me <br>oh let me redeem <br>oh redeem <br>oh myself tonight <br>'Cause I just need one more shot <br>second chances <br>Yeah <br>Is it too late now to say sorry <br>'Cause I'm missing more <br>than just your body oh <br>Is it too late now to say sorry <br>Yeah I know oh oh <br>that I let you down <br>Is it too late to say <br>I'm sorry now <br>I'm sorry yeah <br>Sorry yeah <br>Sorry <br>Yeah I know that I let you down <br>Is it too late to say <br>I'm sorry now <br>I'll take every single piece <br>of the blame <br>if you want me to <br>But you know <br>that there is no innocent one <br>in this game for two <br>I'll go I'll go and then you go <br>you go out and spill the truth <br>Can we both say the words <br>and forget this <br>Yeah <br>Is it too late now to say sorry <br>'Cause I'm missing more <br>than just your body oh <br>Is it too late now to say sorry <br>Yeah I know oh oh <br>that I let you down <br>Is it too late to say <br>I'm sorry now <br>I'm not just trying to get you <br>back on me oh no no <br>'Cause I'm missing more <br>than just your body your body oh <br>Is it too late now to say sorry <br>Yeah I know oh oh <br>that I let you down <br>Is it too late to say <br>I'm sorry now <br>I'm sorry yeah <br>Sorry oh <br>Sorry <br>Yeah I know oh oh <br>that I let you down let you down <br>Is it too late to say <br>I'm sorry now <br>I'm sorry yeah <br>Sorry oh <br>Sorry <br>Yeah I know oh oh <br>that I let you down <br>Is it too late to say <br>I'm sorry now <br>]]></content><category term="Justin Bieber" label="Justin Bieber"/><category term="Sorry" label="Sorry"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Allan_Rayman/2522_Drum_Edit/</id><title>Allan Rayman - 25.22 (Drum Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:06:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:06:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Allan_Rayman/2522_Drum_Edit/" title="Allan Rayman - 25.22 (Drum Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I love to love you, baby <br>I love to love you <br>I love to love you, baby <br>I love to love you <br><br>I never wanna let you go <br>And I am the reason that you let me go <br>I am the lover, I'm the undertow <br>I never wanna let you go <br>And I am the reason that you let me go <br>I am the lover, I'm the undertow <br>I ain't got time no more <br><br>25, a quarter to, I ain't through diggin' you yet <br>I'm crushing you, 22, memories <br>I ain't got time no more <br>I got all the love with no time no more <br>I got all the love with no time no more <br><br>Sweet teen burn, it's you that's giving me sweat <br>Well, my love learning all the moves and all the right steps <br>I ain't got time no more <br>I got all the love, but with no time no more <br>Said I got all the love with no time no more]]></content><category term="Allan Rayman" label="Allan Rayman"/><category term="25.22 (Drum Edit)" label="25.22 (Drum Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤지현/눈부셨어요/</id><title>윤지현 - 눈부셨어요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:06:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:06:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A7%80%ED%98%84/%EB%88%88%EB%B6%80%EC%85%A8%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="윤지현 - 눈부셨어요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너무 걱정하지 말아요 <br>이 밤 동안만 울다 잘께요 <br>미련스레 참으니까 <br>더 먹먹하고 <br>없던 원망이 생겨서요 <br>내가 잘못한것 아니고 <br>그대의 잘못도 아닌데 <br>미워할 수는 없죠 <br>서로 계절이 다른 <br>너무 먼 언덕에서 <br>꿈을 꾸듯 사랑을 원한거죠 <br>사람 마음이야 <br>때론 변할 수도 있죠 <br>사람 마음 어떻게 <br>다 알수 있을까요 <br>다만 내가 더 많이 좋아 해서 <br>미안할 뿐인거죠 <br>눈부셨어요 <br>나는 너무 작았고 <br>그댄 너무 반짝였어요 <br>그대 내게 들려주던 노래 <br>그 노랫소리가 <br>귓가에 맴돌곤 해요 <br>그럴땐 두 손으로 귀를 꼭 막고 <br>다른 생각을 하면 곧 괜찮아져요 <br>사람 마음이야 <br>때론 변할 수도 있죠 <br>사람 마음 어떻게 <br>다 알 수 있을까요 <br>다만 내가 더 많이 좋아 해서 <br>미안할 뿐인 거죠 <br>눈부셨어요 <br>나는 너무 작았고 <br>그댄 너무 반짝였어요 <br>창문을 꼭 닫고 커튼도 내려서 <br>별님도 볼 수가 없게 <br>짐작도 못하게 <br>밤고양이도 알아 챌 수 없도록 <br>아무도 모르게 잠시 울다 갈께요 <br>사람 마음이야 <br>때론 변할 수도 있죠 <br>사람 마음 어떻게 <br>다 알 수 있을까요 <br>다만 내가 더 많이 좋아 해서 <br>미안할 뿐인 거죠 <br>눈부셨어요 <br>나는 너무 작았고 <br>그댄 너무 반짝였어요 <br>]]></content><category term="윤지현" label="윤지현"/><category term="눈부셨어요" label="눈부셨어요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Edo_G/Trending/</id><title>Edo. G - Trending - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:09:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:09:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Edo_G/Trending/" title="Edo. G - Trending - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You could fight the power <br>Or light the sour <br>From your darkest days to your brightest hours <br>Edo and Tren homie we twins like towers <br>This boom bap rap you keep that trap with Baauer <br>Lost my self in to the beat started dreaming to it <br>I spit that real shit <br>And got meaning to it <br>These are the words to live by <br>Knock it over and get by <br>Chest and head shots to the meat I call em rib eyes <br>I had to learn to forgive guys <br>That's how we became street wise <br>And beat wise shit banging <br>Stop looking for death we leave you hanging <br>In a world that is ever changing <br>Complicated you so lame an, plus you ya'll blaming <br>And I ain't talking about fire <br>Its time to spit truth to liars <br>Do the booth and wires <br>Clean records cause we have no priors <br><br>Bonjour I'm so confident you ain't sure <br>Spit the pure staying flying like a condor <br>While you descending we ascending it's never ending <br>Trend on the beat home boy <br>Now we trending <br>We trending <br>I say we trending <br>I I I say we trending <br><br>Attention goes where attention grows <br>You rappers talk shit but never mention flows <br>I'm inching close <br>To the goals of my fore fathers <br>And Ferguson we heard again we all martyrs <br>90s re union to my alma mater <br>Take it back to the 80s Afrika Bambaataa <br>No panic talk I spit that volcanic rock its organic ock <br>That's how i make this planet rock <br>The shooters sin is concealed <br>Boston to Lynnfield <br>You been pen wheeled <br>We all hurt and we get healed <br>Life's not a big deal <br>Today you're they bug <br>Tomorrow you're the windshield <br>I use my mouth as a vessel <br>Breach the gap with a trestle <br>Keep you up like espresso <br>With life we all wrestle <br>Boston accent like <br><br>Bonjour I'm so confident you ain't sure <br>Spit the pure staying flying like a condor <br>While you descending we ascending it's never ending <br>Trend on the beat home boy <br>Now we trending <br>We trending <br>I say we trending <br>I I I say we trending]]></content><category term="Edo. G" label="Edo. G"/><category term="Trending" label="Trending"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Edo_G/Last_Man_Standing_Cuts_By_DJ_Netik/</id><title>Edo. G - Last Man Standing (Cuts By DJ Netik) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:09:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:09:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Edo_G/Last_Man_Standing_Cuts_By_DJ_Netik/" title="Edo. G - Last Man Standing (Cuts By DJ Netik) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, Yo <br>It's Edo Edo, Edo <br>Aha, Street Wyze <br>Let's get it <br><br>From the outhouse to the penthouse to the halfway house <br>Five stars <br> itself <br>Bein' rich, it don't compare to wealth, prepare yourself <br><br>Out the fame you name, you are lame <br>Smash your frame and money is funny, change is strange <br>Stop braggin', stop swaggin', I spit flames like ten dragons <br>Hard shit, you spit the beauty pageants <br><br>You niggas can't imagine <br>Cause y'all are passengers ridin' on a band waggon <br>I got it, you hold it, we control it <br>Edo gon' drive it like you stole it <br><br>You tell bad lies, I see your bullshit with bad eyes <br>We had ties Act wise <br>Don't be surprised that good fellas are now bad guys <br><br>It ain't just rap <br>I teach it well, speak it well <br>Edo's the last man standin' <br>To kick the truth to the youth <br><br>It ain't just rap <br>I teach it well, speak it well <br>Edo's the last man standin' <br>Put together meaningful words that really unite, come on <br><br>Yo, what I seen blind ya sight like hi beam <br>When I dream all I hear is sirenes <br>Another murder, ambulance, cop cars <br>It's so dark, it's hard for me to see stars <br><br>I see liquor stores, I see bars <br>Prison rate higher, all I see is bars <br>No brotherhood for my brothers <br>White sheet undercovers, black babies, young mothers <br><br>March to beat of funeral drums <br>More people get shot and killed by guns <br>In fear, how we raise our sons <br>I hit the stage with rage, so I can raise my funds <br><br>Conscious rap could never ever bore people <br>We gain more people speakin' for the poor people <br>The workin' woman and workin' man <br>Who bust they ass without a helping hand <br><br>It ain't just rap <br>I teach it well, speak it well <br>Edo's the last man standin' <br>To kick the truth to the youth <br><br>It ain't just rap <br>I teach it well, speak it well <br>Edo's the last man standin' <br>Put together meaningful words that really unite, come on <br><br>Edo's the last man standin' <br>Come on <br><br>One bullet, one shot, one spark <br>One dog bark, all dogs bark <br>My people feel hopeless, they feel cursed <br>But we at our best, when things get worse <br><br>One bullet, one shot, one spark <br>One dog bark, all dogs bark <br>My people feel hopeless, they feel cursed <br>But we at our best, when things get worse <br><br>We at our best, when things get worse 4x]]></content><category term="Edo. G" label="Edo. G"/><category term="Last Man Standing (Cuts By DJ Netik)" label="Last Man Standing (Cuts By DJ Netik)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Krankland/In_The_Realms_Of_The_Unreal/</id><title>Krankland - In The Realms Of The Unreal - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T10:10:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T10:10:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Krankland/In_The_Realms_Of_The_Unreal/" title="Krankland - In The Realms Of The Unreal - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Deep into the darkened woods <br>There I found myself halfway <br>Oh to think of those dark days <br>It fills my mind with fear and fright <br><br>Now I go there every night <br>The lion wears a handsome suit <br>And when it does not back off <br>You try to tell me a line to soothe <br><br>Your hand into mine and we'll be good <br><br>In the realms of the unreal <br>With rocky roads and barren fields <br>There I gaze at the fierce beast <br>And in the east mist starts to clear <br><br>Your hand into mine and we'll be good <br>Your head into the light and we'll be fine <br><br>In the realms of the unreal <br>In the realms of the unreal <br>In the realms of the unreal <br>In the realms of the unreal <br><br>Your hand into mine and we'll be good <br>Your head into the light and we'll be fine]]></content><category term="Krankland" label="Krankland"/><category term="In The Realms Of The Unreal" label="In The Realms Of The Unreal"/></entry></feed>