<feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:53:43+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ovenz/Fiance/</id><title>O.venz - Fiance - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:53:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:53:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ovenz/Fiance/" title="O.venz - Fiance - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보석이 담겨진 너의 눈 속을 <br>쭉 헤엄치며 <br>칵테일 몇 잔을 마시는 <br>상상을 해봐 내 피앙새여 <br>니 향기는 선율 위 춤추고 <br>있어 우주 속 별빛처럼 <br>미소를 보여줘 나 천국을 <br>다시 또 느낄 수 있게 <br>석양이 지고 있지 <br>너에게 향하는 길에 <br>시간이 흘러서 도착한 미래는 <br>과거가 되네 <br>갈대들 사이로 보이는 실루엣 <br>너 역시나 너 <br>꿈속의 조각을 모았어 <br>손을 뻗어주길 날 위해서 <br>또 다른 이념이 공간을 만들어 <br>서로의 존재를 만났고 <br>주연의 모습처럼 <br>온전히 흐르는 단막에 <br>우리는 무일한 운명으로 휘었지 <br>밤하늘 은하수를 닮은 <br>너에 손을 잡을 때 <br>온전함을 느끼지 <br>오직 그녀에서 예 <br>흑영이 자리 잡아 <br>세상이 어두워져도 <br>너의 빛과 향기는 <br>무엇도 감추지 못해 <br>will praise you true <br>everything baby <br>take this love oh yeah yeah <br>기차에 올라타 우주로 떠나자 <br>꽉 잡아 내 손을 yeah yeah <br>will praise you true <br>everything baby <br>forever young love yeah yeah <br>창문 넘어 보이는 그녀의 모습 <br>대천사를 봤지 yeah yeah <br>너가 있다면 너가 있다면 <br>너만 있으면 <br>죽음이 절대 난 두렵지 않지 <br>이제 네가 없이는 아무것도 나 <br>느낄 수 없어 너 아닌 그 무엇도 난 <br>오직 나를 비추는 건 너 하나야 <br>i feel it in my mind <br>i used to say we ride we ride <br>i used to say we ride we ride <br>i believe in we can start can start <br>i wanna give you the stars in the sky <br>will praise you true <br>everything baby <br>take this love oh yeah yeah <br>기차에 올라타 우주로 떠나자 <br>꽉 잡아 내 손을 yeah yeah <br>will praise you true <br>everything baby <br>forever young love yeah yeah <br>창문 넘어 보이는 그녀의 모습 <br>대천사를 봤지 yeah yeah <br>will praise you true <br>everything baby <br>take this love oh yeah yeah <br>기차에 올라타 우주로 떠나자 <br>꽉 잡아 내 손을 yeah yeah <br>will praise you true <br>everything baby <br>forever young love yeah yeah <br>창문 넘어 보이는 그녀의 모습 <br>대천사를 봤지 yeah yeah <br>]]></content><category term="O.venz" label="O.venz"/><category term="Fiance" label="Fiance"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/3_x_Coke/Beautiful_World/</id><title>3 x Coke - Beautiful World - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:53:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:53:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/3_x_Coke/Beautiful_World/" title="3 x Coke - Beautiful World - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[막연하게 멀게만 느껴지던 것들은 <br>이젠 선명하게 보여 <br>우중충한 날씨도 내리쬐는 햇빛도 <br>이젠 아름답게 보여 <br>it's a beautiful world <br>it's a beautiful <br>it's a beautiful world <br>it's a beautiful <br>여긴 beautiful world <br>난 그렇게 느끼지 do you agree <br>다들 뭐그리 피곤하게 살아요 <br>걍 즐기면서 가보자고 like to party <br>난 가끔 이런 생각을 하곤 해 <br>내가 인정받고 지갑 분실했을 때 <br>초록 상자에 검색하면 주민 등록증 <br>없이도 들어갈텐데 술집 <br>요즘의 내겐 날 증명할 게 넘 많아 <br>그건 준비하는 시간은 아깝잖아 <br>그래선지 다들 빨라 <br>근데 중요한 건 몰라 <br>그저 성공에 목매잖아 <br>다 제껴놓을래 거기 뭘 그렇게 <br>다들 목숨 건데 i don't <br>understand 그냥 하고보는 거지 뭐 <br>주어진 환경에서 <br>200% 성괄 내자고 꼭 <br>막연하게 멀게만 느껴지던 것들은 <br>이젠 선명하게 보여 <br>우중충한 날씨도 내리쬐는 햇빛도 <br>이젠 아름답게 보여 <br>it's a beautiful world <br>it's a beautiful <br>it's a beautiful world <br>it's a beautiful <br>뭐 하나 쉬운 게 없네 <br>그렇다고 쫄 필요는 없네 <br>원래 그래 모든 게 다 <br>맘 먹기에 달렸데 <br>당연히 구라지만 나는 그걸 믿을래 <br>쉽게 생각해 it's so simple <br>되든 안 되든 둘 중 하나일뿐 <br>분명 밝은 생각과 행동은 좋은 꿈을 <br>데려올 게 확실해 <br>비록 지금은 아니지만 <br>난 말야 내가 만약에 유명세를 타도 <br>지금과 다를 바 없이 살 것 같애 아마도 <br>있게 살아본 적 없어선진 몰라도 <br>사치부리면서 사는 삶은 나완 안맞어 <br>내가 변한다면 서슴없이 욕해 <br>올챙이적 생각 못해 don't care <br>근데 또 이런 상상은 해 그런 소릴 <br>들을 만큼 유명해져 있길 바래 <br>막연하게 멀게만 느껴지던 것들이 <br>이젠 선명하게 보여 <br>우중충한 날씨도 내리쬐는 햇빛도 <br>이젠 아름답게 보여 <br>it's a beautiful world <br>it's a beautiful <br>it's a beautiful world <br>it's a beautiful <br>it's a beautiful <br>it's a beautiful <br>it's a beautiful <br>it's a beautiful <br>Beautiful beautiful beautiful <br>beautiful beautiful beautiful <br>beautiful beautiful beautiful <br>beautiful beautiful <br>it's a beautiful <br>막연하게 멀게만 느껴지던 것들이 <br>이젠 선명하게 보여 <br>우중충한 날씨도 내리쬐는 햇빛도 <br>이젠 아름답게 보여 <br>it's a beautiful world <br>it's a beautiful <br>it's a beautiful world <br>it's a beautiful <br>선명하게 보여 <br>아름답게 보여 <br>선명하게 보여 <br>아름답게 보여 <br>it's a beautiful world <br>it's a beautiful <br>it's a beautiful world <br>it's a beautiful <br>]]></content><category term="3 x Coke" label="3 x Coke"/><category term="Beautiful World" label="Beautiful World"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/3_x_Coke/T_or_T_Throne_or_Thorn_Feat_PRIZMOLIQ/</id><title>3 x Coke - T or T (Throne or Thorn) (Feat. PRIZMOLIQ) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:53:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:53:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/3_x_Coke/T_or_T_Throne_or_Thorn_Feat_PRIZMOLIQ/" title="3 x Coke - T or T (Throne or Thorn) (Feat. PRIZMOLIQ) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[i don't know 내 앞에 뭐가 있는지 <br>걍 내 입에 기름칠 좀 <br>하고파서 난 rollin' <br>순수하게 뱉던 놈이 돈이 보인 순간 <br>눈도 가린체로 뱉어 경주마 flowing <br>이건 뭐 호구짓 당했던 것 부터 <br>말하자면 존나 많지 난 턱 붙여 <br>I'm spit on that <br>띠껍게 날 보던 놈들 기억해 real <br>fuck that shit <br>할 일이 많아지고 있어 17년 <br>지금 까지 했던게 <br>허공에 씹질이 아니란게 <br>이제 보여 뒤지란 법 없어 <br>난 빙의 이 비트 위 <br>예술가 코스프레 아니고 창작해 <br>you can't see me <br>이 감각은 존나 빡빡해 <br>오늘도 농구 끝나고 난 studio <br>하루에 두곡을 쓰고 샤워하고 누워 <br>이 느낌을 곱 씹지 츄잉껌 <br>고통없인 절대로 성공을 믿지마 <br>고난없인 멋대로 왕관을 쓰지마 <br>가시밭을 걸어 두 발이 다 까져도 <br>누구도 막을 수가 없어 <br>두 손에 못 박을 때도 <br>no pain no gain <br>no cross no crown <br>for my mothafuckin crown <br>mo pain mo gain <br>mo cross mo crown <br>for my mothafuckin crown <br>a-yo 난 십잘 지지 않아도 <br>손 가락질을 받던 놈 <br>쟤네는 절대 원치 않지 <br>이런 나의 성공 <br>모두 이해하지 위대한 그분 같이 <br>그래서 날 이렇게 부르나봐 <br>신이 난 놈 <br>god's son 아니길 <br>바랬겠지만 축복받은 태생 <br>은 어쩔 수없는 내 재능 <br>이 제는 그걸 지혜롭게 써 보려 해 <br>내 인생은 지금부터가 begin again <br>아 직도 많지 비난과 손사레 <br>그건 내 스무살에 자르지 못한 할례 <br>안해 gimmick <br>보여준 적 없지 나는 아직 <br>내 적들이 뭐라고 하던 난 just do it <br>대본따윈 없는 삶에도 난 배우신 분 <br>날 조연으로만 봤던 <br>애들과의 정면승부 <br>여태 내 삶이 계속 깨져왔어도 <br>계속 맞서갈테니 <br>i got cross i get crown <br>고통없인 절대로 성공을 믿지마 <br>고난없인 멋대로 왕관을 쓰지마 <br>가시밭을 걸어 두 발이 다 까져도 <br>누구도 막을 수가 없어 <br>두 손에 못 박을 때도 <br>no pain no gain <br>no cross no crown <br>for my mothafuckin crown <br>mo pain mo gain <br>mo cross mo crown <br>for my mothafuckin crown <br>내 안에 yo 모든걸 <br>여기 다 털기전에 <br>잡생각부터 싹 비워 <br>raw 한것만 이번엔 <br>식혀 내 머리솎 날 본능적 감각에 <br>맡겨 내 의식을 따라 <br>뱉는 랩 실감나게 또 <br>뱉어낸뒤 받아내 사람들 <br>엄지 이젠 좀 여유있게 <br>박자 타고 보는 경치 <br>매일 챙기는 신보 허나 여전히 철지난 <br>음악에 반응하는 세포 선입견은 없지 <br>난 밤새 리듬에 빠져 <br>무알콜 취권하는 재키춘 <br>더 Groovy 하게 박자를 <br>갖고 놀아 애기처럼 <br>이 놀이에 미쳐 매일 세웠지 <br>내안의 기준을 <br>이 무대위 숨쉬던 <br>영웅들과 함께 춤을 춰 <br>이 춤을 통해 숨을 셔 <br>수많은 겁쟁이들 <br>다 숨어서 보네 죽은척 <br>달콤한 꿈에 취한듯 <br>웃고있는 얼굴 위로 <br>침뱉고 가는거지 믿어 <br>내 방식과 내 시도 <br>고통없인 절대로 성공을 믿지마 <br>고난없인 멋대로 왕관을 쓰지마 <br>가시밭을 걸어 두 발이 다 까져도 <br>누구도 막을 수가 없어 <br>두 손에 못 박을 때도 <br>no pain no gain <br>no cross no crown <br>for my mothafuckin crown <br>mo pain mo gain <br>mo cross mo crown <br>for my mothafuckin crown <br>]]></content><category term="3 x Coke" label="3 x Coke"/><category term="T or T (Throne or Thorn) (Feat. PRIZMOLIQ)" label="T or T (Throne or Thorn) (Feat. PRIZMOLIQ)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/3_x_Coke/Ball_0_Feat_Zenah_GRoovy/</id><title>3 x Coke - Ball (0) (Feat. Zenah G.Roovy) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:53:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:53:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/3_x_Coke/Ball_0_Feat_Zenah_GRoovy/" title="3 x Coke - Ball (0) (Feat. Zenah G.Roovy) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Keep it up <br>I'm on my way I think <br>My ball is rollin' rollin' rollin' <br>I don't take anyone's own way <br>I don't give a shit <br>2 chainz &amp; rollies <br>그딴 건 필요 없지 나의 길에 <br>이미 더한 가치거리들이 나의 뒤에 <br>단단하게 자리잡아 <br>날 서있게 만들기에 <br>나는 더 갈 수 있단 자신감을 얻어 <br>비록 내 어제는 끝도 없이 <br>비틀거렸어도 <br>그 속에서 내 할 일에 중심을 둬 <br>비로소 앞으로에 대한 <br>의심을 거둬 <br>아직도 갈 길은 한참 멀었지 <br>확신을 갖고 난 뒤에 <br>더 똑바로 걷고 <br>팔잘 고쳤지 바닥을 쳤어도 <br>이게 끝이 아니란 걸 알지 <br>야 똑바로 봐 <br>니가 쉽게 물로 봤던 그때 걔야 <br>니 말대로 되지 않아 미안하지만 <br>삐끗하지 않고 결국 여까지 왔어 <br>Keep it up <br>I'm on my way I think <br>My ball is rollin' rollin' rollin' <br>I don't take anyone's own way <br>I don't give a shit <br>지금의 난 baller <br>내가 가진 공은 계속해서 굴러 <br>내가 해야 할 건 <br>늘어나고 시간은 부풀어 <br>그 무게를 체감하기에는 <br>아직 나는 어려 <br>그니까 더 더욱 키워가는 거야 <br>다른 것보다 훨씬 더 크게 <br>한참 멀었다는 건 <br>누구보다 잘 알아 but <br>걸어온 길 쉽게 <br>등 돌릴 순 없잖아 <br>기구한 팔자 또는 기울어진 삶 <br>별 신경 안 쓰지만 <br>오히려 다른 애들이 <br>상관하고 참견할 땐 <br>무척 화가 나 <br>내겐 필요 없으니까 <br>싹 다 떠나가길 바래 <br>왜냠 난 아직 갈 길이 남았거든 <br>지체할 맘은 단 1초도 없네 <br>아까워 실패에 대해 <br>논의하는 때에도 <br>난 차라리 한발자국이라도 <br>더 걸을래 <br>Keep it up <br>I'm on my way I think <br>My ball is rollin' rollin' rollin' <br>I don't take anyone's own way <br>I don't give a shit <br>WOO HOO <br>My ball is priceless <br>My ball is <br>WOO HOO <br>My ball is priceless <br>My ball is priceless <br>Keep it up <br>I'm on my way I think <br>on my way that I think <br>My ball is rollin' rollin' <br>I don't take anyone's own way <br>I don't give a shit <br>Time is tickin' now <br>Time is tickin' now <br>]]></content><category term="3 x Coke" label="3 x Coke"/><category term="Ball (0) (Feat. Zenah G.Roovy)" label="Ball (0) (Feat. Zenah G.Roovy)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/3_x_Coke/Memento_Feat_LAKTA_Rolo/</id><title>3 x Coke - Memento (Feat. LAKTA, Rolo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:53:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:53:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/3_x_Coke/Memento_Feat_LAKTA_Rolo/" title="3 x Coke - Memento (Feat. LAKTA, Rolo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[oh shit <br>여긴 어둠으로 가득한 도시 <br>like gotham <br>내가 또 어떤 일을 저질렀는지 <br>모르는 채 시작되는 <br>hide and seek <br>who am i 나도 잘 몰라 <br>내가 누군지 조차 <br>근데 날 계속 쫓아 오는 자식들은 <br>심상치가 않아 <br>i can still remember nutthin' <br>이런 적이 벌써 꽤 됐지 <br>눈을 감고 난 뒤 다시 뜰 때마다 <br>내겐 낯선 공기 낯선 느낌 <br>이건 매번 겪는 빌어먹을 amnesia <br>lay back 난 못할 걸 절대 <br>가만있음 잡아 먹혀 <br>내 상탠 pan cake <br>no matter what i've done 어차피 <br>오늘 밤이 지나고 나면 i just let it go <br>나도 내가 누군지 기억 나질 않아 <br>텅 빈 백지와도 같지 아마 <br>Where am i Who am i 또 rewind <br>지겹게 돌고 도네 <br>깊은 한숨 후회만 <br>눈에 보이는 상황은 <br>늘 적응 안돼 <br>생각을 해보자고 <br>이 자와 나와의 관계 <br>아는 사람은 아니고 <br>트루먼 쇼처럼 <br>모든 건 다 나 몰래 꾸며진 간계 <br>온몸엔 피와 땀 <br>누구의 짓인진 몰라도 <br>정말 기가 차 <br>몽롱한 상태의 원인은 <br>drug caffeine alcohol <br>근데 범인이 나란 건 모두 알 걸 <br>그렇다면 없애 그 누구도 모르게 <br>누가 봤다면 그 눈을 뽑아 두 개 <br>익숙한 듯 빨리 치우는 현장 <br>등뒤로 흩어진 모습 경찰 <br>옅은 미소 전부 영화인 듯 <br>나조차 모르게 다시 한번 더 액션 <br>나도 내가 누군지 기억 나질 않아 <br>텅 빈 백지와도 같지 아마 <br>Where am i Who am i 또 rewind <br>지겹게 돌고 도네 <br>깊은 한숨 후회만 <br>who am i 나조차도 내가 <br>낯설어지는 밤 where is my mind <br>who am i 나조차도 내가 <br>낯설어지는 밤 where is my mind <br>who am i 나조차도 내가 <br>낯설어지는 밤 where is my mind <br>who am i 나조차도 내가 <br>낯설어지는 밤 where is my mind <br>나도 내가 누군지 기억 나질 않아 <br>텅 빈 백지와도 같지 아마 <br>Where am i Who am i 또 rewind <br>지겹게 돌고 도네 <br>깊은 한숨 후회만 <br>나도 내가 누군지 기억 나질 않아 <br>텅 빈 백지와도 같지 아마 <br>Where am i Who am i 또 rewind <br>지겹게 돌고 도네 <br>깊은 한숨 후회만 <br>]]></content><category term="3 x Coke" label="3 x Coke"/><category term="Memento (Feat. LAKTA, Rolo)" label="Memento (Feat. LAKTA, Rolo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/3_x_Coke/Fxxk_That/</id><title>3 x Coke - Fxxk That - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:53:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:53:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/3_x_Coke/Fxxk_That/" title="3 x Coke - Fxxk That - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 돌아봤네 꿈 꾸던 날을 <br>지난 몇년전부터 오늘까지 나는 <br>내가 지나온 것 들이 나를 더 크게 <br>만들거라 믿고 쭉 달려왔었지 <br>그게 내 발목에 족쇈줄도 모르고 <br>i been on my grind <br>껍데기 뿐인 빈 음악과 <br>날 절대로 동일선상에 두지마 <br>난 언제나 비교 대상은 기분 나빠 <br>유일무이 monopoly <br>이건 살아남기 위한 생존심리 <br>식어버린 싸늘한 주검들로 만든 <br>산을 밟고 넘어가는 길 <br>wake up 눈을 떠 <br>바라 본 세상엔 아무도 없어 <br>내가 직접 만들어 <br>보여줄게 많단 말야 신처럼 <br>이게 나를 드러내는 첫번째 Fact <br>너 잘 들어 이건 내가 가져올 <br>butterfly effect <br>do my thang i believe in myself <br>bitch ass 좇는 건 절대로 안 해 <br>내가 내 길을 개척해갈 <br>시간도 아까워서 난 정면 돌파 <br>one micro phone 내가 겪어왔던 <br>모든 것들을 죽이는 <br>단어들로 뱉어 내 <br>스스로 날 대표하고 <br>더 확실히 알려 like batman <br>어떤 래퍼들의 언행불일치 <br>이미 대다수가 지 무덤파고 있지 <br>real한 척 깨달은 척 하지마라 <br>대중들은 벌써 다 알고 있어 <br>제 삼의 눈은 무슨 <br>모두 대충 대충 <br>뱉고 그걸 랩이라 해 Third eye들 <br>남의 가사 유행처럼 따라할 시간에 <br>갈고 닦고 좀 더 탓해 니들 <br>motherfuckin' idle <br>motherfuckin' idle <br>이겨내고 벌려 너와 나의 차이를 <br>인정 하지 못한다면 너는 꼰대 <br>패배자가 어울리는 title <br>기억해 내 이름 <br>j u a n i made it <br>이제 더 크게 그 이름을 부르고 <br>Everybody signz up put'em up <br>내가 뿌려놓은 말들의 무게 <br>다 가뿐하게 수확할 차례 <br>맨날 방구석에서 망부석처럼 <br>서서 구속만을 기다리는건 내게 <br>많이 지루한 일이지 그래서 <br>새까만 밤을 새 생각과 맘을 계속 <br>새롭게 다잡았네 <br>이게 그에 해당되는 결과물 <br>어떤 애들은 계속 <br>내 실패를 점치고 날 <br>괴롭게 해 그런 반응들을 뒤엎고 <br>난 계속 해 <br>빡세게 내 청사진을 가능케 <br>만들 계획을 실현중 <br>작품 그 이상의 기록갱신 <br>이걸 비롯해서 비내리며 삐걱대던 <br>지난날의 과오는 다 지워 <br>넘보지마 나의 level <br>갈 곳은 내가 정해 mo'fuckin heaven <br>내가 나고 자란 한국 땅에 <br>몸으로 깨운 my vibe ride with it <br>여길 찢어내고 있는 <br>가위 앞 난 바위지 <br>stared from the bottom <br>꿈을 데려와서 살아 <br>take it to the next level <br>갖게 될 거야 지금보다 <br>더 더 나은 걸 <br>안주하지 않아 절대로 anymore <br>]]></content><category term="3 x Coke" label="3 x Coke"/><category term="Fxxk That" label="Fxxk That"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/3_x_Coke/I_Am/</id><title>3 x Coke - I Am - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:53:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:53:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/3_x_Coke/I_Am/" title="3 x Coke - I Am - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[첫번째 막이 열리면 <br>두 손엔 비가 내려 <br>두 번짼 점점 더 퍼지는 소리에 <br>눈을 뜬 뒤 <br>세번째 mic check <br>이건 나를 알리는 최선책 <br>이자 내 인생의 선택쯤 <br>yeah that's mine <br>yeah that's mine <br>마지막은 내가 해온 그대로 <br>변함없이 계속 지켜내는 것 <br>나는 믿어 그간 매번 미뤄왔던 <br>잠에 대해 보상받는 걸 <br>몇 번의 기회에선 삐끗한 적 있지만 <br>난 거기에 더 큰 뜻이 있음을 알어 <br>I am Who i am 내가 곧 나야 <br>누가 날 대신해서 내 꿈을 이뤄 <br>bitch 잘 들어 열등병자 코스프레는 <br>끝났어 mo money mo problem <br>난 늘 다르게 변화해 <br>other colors my flow <br>J u an 이게 내 이름인 걸 <br>니들 머리속에다 기억해둬 <br>먼 길로 돌아왔지만 내 존재는 <br>확실하게 드러내고 있어 <br>No.1 자린 관심 없어 <br>나는 내 시간이 더 중요해 <br>야망이 다른 간지 <br>그걸 내 현실로 대입해 <br>i am who i am wanna be the man <br>i am who i am wanna be the man <br>i am who i am wanna be the man <br>J u a n yeah that's my name <br>i am who i am <br>i am who i am <br>i am who i am <br>i am who i am <br>oh plz 제발 간섭마 <br>내 앞가림은 내가 잘해 근데 <br>쓸데 없는 걱정하지 난 <br>어지간해선 절대 안넓히는 <br>오지랖 쟤넨 안그런가봐 <br>없는 취미 관심 밖 <br>피곤한 삶을 늘 스스로 만들고 <br>맨날 키보드 앞에서 쎈척 <br>하는 애들관 안맞는 vibe <br>이제 난 현실을 똑바로 보네 <br>이건 내 성공의 lottery <br>지금 내게 필요한 건 동전이야 <br>꽝은 없어 반은 왔어 시작한 만큼 <br>아직 갈 길은 더 남았어 <br>지금 내 위친 밑바닥 <br>그래서 더 원해 앞 마당이 <br>달린 집과 모두의 자랑 <br>거리가 되는 걸 여차하면 모든 걸 <br>걸 준비가 되있어 비좁은 방에서 <br>꿈꿨던 미랠 가져오기 위해 <br>i am who i am wanna be the man <br>i am who i am wanna be the man <br>i am who i am wanna be the man <br>J u a n yeah that's my name <br>i am who i am <br>i am who i am <br>i am who i am <br>i am who i am <br>]]></content><category term="3 x Coke" label="3 x Coke"/><category term="I Am" label="I Am"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royalroad/Beach_Night/</id><title>Royalroad - Beach Night - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:54:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:54:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royalroad/Beach_Night/" title="Royalroad - Beach Night - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[when you got blessed <br>didn't give a shit bout ma life <br>이제와서 날 찾아 <br>you don't have to go back <br>this is best <br>we faced with matter <br>that I don't wanna <br>I just vibe with it on the loop <br>I feel like lookin <br>at The Cebu ocean view <br>지금까지 감췄던 내 모든걸 <br>여기서 쏟고 가야겠어 난 <br>hihat 한번 때려주고 <br>걸어가지 비트윌 <br>바닷속 헤엄쳐다니고 나와서는 비틀 <br>거리게 돌아다녀 <br>여긴 아무 신경 안쓰니까 <br>좋아 난생 처음 보는 <br>여자랑도 drinkin <br>니가 뒤진 서랍 안엔 <br>이젠 없어 내가 휑 <br>하니 너도 느껴보니 <br>이젠 어때 지금 bang <br>아무 생각 없이 걸어 <br>on the beach I wanna bitch <br>니가 뭐를 하던 간에 <br>I don't fuck with turn up pitch <br>바로 원해 나는 오늘만큼 <br>속에 담아 두지 않아 <br>꺼내봐 니 원래 느낌 살아 <br>생전 관에 담어 <br>내가 보는 다른 사람 <br>귀가 아퍼 깔아 음악 <br>후회할 껀 없어 <br>다른 사람과는 달라 나는 <br>바로 원해 나는 오늘만큼 <br>속에 담아 두지 않아 <br>꺼내봐 니 원래 느낌 살아 <br>생전 관에 담어 <br>내가 보는 다른 사람 <br>귀가 아퍼 깔아 음악 <br>후회할 껀 없어 <br>다른 사람과는 달라 나는 <br>내가 죽기전에 <br>Fuckin till i die 쓸래 <br>담배같은 중독성 쩌는 곡과 라임 <br>이건 나의 사명과 같은 라임이야 <br>다음 앨범표지 내가 만든 순간 <br>I'm a real art <br>일단 술들어 술 <br>지금 예술은 무슨 소리 <br>복잡한 생각들은 저리치워 모조리 <br>시원한 바람 쐬고 날려버려 개소리 <br>짖거려도 되는 오늘 밤은 모두 <br>can do it <br>머리속에 매일 bamm 하고 <br>떠다니는 game <br>우린 절대 <br>don't break to ma life 절대 후횐 <br>없어 그냥 막가 막차타고 확간 <br>애들과는 달라 우리 즐겨보자 bling <br>더 즐길 수있음 와봐 <br>오늘 밤이 갈때까지 <br>너의 두 눈의 동공이 <br>그냥 확풀릴 때까지 <br>대낮의 아침이 <br>내 두눈을 쏘아댈때까지 <br>술이 안들어 갈 정도로 <br>마시고 갈 때까지 <br>바로 원해 나는 오늘만큼 <br>속에 담아 두지 않아 <br>꺼내봐 니 원래 느낌 살아 생전 <br>관에 담어 <br>내가 보는 다른 사람 <br>귀가 아퍼 깔아 음악 <br>후회할 껀 없어 <br>다른 사람과는 달라 나는 <br>바로 원해 나는 오늘만큼 <br>속에 담아 두지 않아 <br>꺼내봐 니 원래 느낌 살아 <br>생전 관에 담어 <br>내가 보는 다른 사람 <br>귀가 아퍼 깔아 음악 <br>후회할 껀 없어 <br>다른 사람과는 달라 나는 <br>]]></content><category term="Royalroad" label="Royalroad"/><category term="Beach Night" label="Beach Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/RONY/너여서_Only_You_Vocal_by_부소정/</id><title>RONY - 너여서 (Only You) (Vocal by 부소정) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:54:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:54:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/RONY/%EB%84%88%EC%97%AC%EC%84%9C_Only_You_Vocal_by_%EB%B6%80%EC%86%8C%EC%A0%95/" title="RONY - 너여서 (Only You) (Vocal by 부소정) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무 소리도 들리지 않는 곳에 <br>홀로 남겨져 텅 빈 이 세상 속에 <br>많이 외롭고 지쳐 있는 나를 <br>니가 없다면 무너졌겠지 <br>아무것도 없는 것 같았어 <br>하루에도 수십 번은 더 울었어 <br>이제야 내게 너라는 <br>사랑을 알게 해준 그런 사람이 있어 <br>It's Only You <br>살아 숨쉬는 이유 그건 바로 너야 <br>It's Only You <br>내겐 너라는 선물 그 뿐이면 돼 <br>It's Only you <br>아무것도 할 수 없었던 <br>지친 내게 용기를 준 그건 너였어 <br>이제는 내가 너에게 <br>사랑을 함께 나눌 그런 사람이 될게 <br>It's Only You <br>살아 숨쉬는 이유 그건 바로 너야 <br>It's Only You <br>내겐 너라는 선물 그 뿐이면 돼 <br>It's Only you <br>바람에 흩어진 기억처럼 <br>그대와 함께 간다면 <br>그 무엇도 두렵지 않아 <br>It's Only You <br>너만 함께 있다면 그걸로 행복해 <br>It's Only You <br>내겐 너라는 선물 그 뿐이면 돼 <br>It's Only you <br>]]></content><category term="RONY" label="RONY"/><category term="너여서 (Only You) (Vocal by 부소정)" label="너여서 (Only You) (Vocal by 부소정)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/에이아_EIA/뚝뚝_Inst/</id><title>에이아 (EIA) - 뚝뚝 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:54:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:54:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%84_EIA/%EB%9A%9D%EB%9A%9D_Inst/" title="에이아 (EIA) - 뚝뚝 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어두운 밤에 <br>조용히 스며드는 <br>음악 소리에 취해 <br>수줍게 꺼내본 <br>지난 날의 너와 내 모습이 <br>창가에 비친 마른 입술이 <br>모든 걸 말해 주는 것 같아 <br>밤공기가 차가워 이불에 <br>몸을 감싼 채 <br>그저 핸드폰만 바라봐 <br>뚝 뚝 <br>너에게로 가고 싶은데 <br>뚝 뚝 <br>그게 내 맘 같지 않아서 <br>유유 유우 <br>유우우우우우우 <br>uh huh <br>작은 방 네가 남기고 간 <br>흔적들이 너무나도 많아서 <br>정리가 안돼 <br>맘에 담아두었던 그런 그리움이 <br>저 하늘 위에서 내리는 <br>빗방울처럼 <br>뚝 뚝 <br>너에게로 가고 싶은데 <br>뚝 뚝 <br>그게 내 맘 같지 않아서 <br>유유 유우 <br>유우우우우우우 <br>uh huh <br>오늘만 지나면 늘 그래왔듯이 <br>괜찮아질 것 같아 <br>비가 오는 밤이면 <br>니 생각에 젖어 <br>촛불을 환히 밝힐래 <br>뚝 뚝 <br>너에게로 가고 싶은데 <br>뚝 뚝 <br>그게 내 맘 같지 않아서 <br>유유 유우 <br>유우우우우우우 <br>uh huh <br>뚝 뚝 <br>너에게로 가고 싶은데 <br>뚝 뚝 <br>그게 내 맘 같지 않아서 <br>유유 유우 <br>Oh you <br>유우우우우우우 <br>uh huh <br>]]></content><category term="에이아 (EIA)" label="에이아 (EIA)"/><category term="뚝뚝 (Inst.)" label="뚝뚝 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/에이아_EIA/뚝뚝/</id><title>에이아 (EIA) - 뚝뚝 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:54:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:54:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%84_EIA/%EB%9A%9D%EB%9A%9D/" title="에이아 (EIA) - 뚝뚝 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어두운 밤에 <br>조용히 스며드는 <br>음악 소리에 취해 <br>수줍게 꺼내본 <br>지난 날의 너와 내 모습이 <br>창가에 비친 마른 입술이 <br>모든 걸 말해 주는 것 같아 <br>밤공기가 차가워 이불에 <br>몸을 감싼 채 <br>그저 핸드폰만 바라봐 <br>뚝 뚝 <br>너에게로 가고 싶은데 <br>뚝 뚝 <br>그게 내 맘 같지 않아서 <br>유유 유우 <br>유우우우우우우 <br>uh huh <br>작은 방 네가 남기고 간 <br>흔적들이 너무나도 많아서 <br>정리가 안돼 <br>맘에 담아두었던 그런 그리움이 <br>저 하늘 위에서 내리는 <br>빗방울처럼 <br>뚝 뚝 <br>너에게로 가고 싶은데 <br>뚝 뚝 <br>그게 내 맘 같지 않아서 <br>유유 유우 <br>유우우우우우우 <br>uh huh <br>오늘만 지나면 늘 그래왔듯이 <br>괜찮아질 것 같아 <br>비가 오는 밤이면 <br>니 생각에 젖어 <br>촛불을 환히 밝힐래 <br>뚝 뚝 <br>너에게로 가고 싶은데 <br>뚝 뚝 <br>그게 내 맘 같지 않아서 <br>유유 유우 <br>유우우우우우우 <br>uh huh <br>뚝 뚝 <br>너에게로 가고 싶은데 <br>뚝 뚝 <br>그게 내 맘 같지 않아서 <br>유유 유우 <br>Oh you <br>유우우우우우우 <br>uh huh <br>]]></content><category term="에이아 (EIA)" label="에이아 (EIA)"/><category term="뚝뚝" label="뚝뚝"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헷세/그랬네요/</id><title>헷세 - 그랬네요 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:54:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:54:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%B7%EC%84%B8/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%AC%EB%84%A4%EC%9A%94/" title="헷세 - 그랬네요 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 전부라던 그 사람 <br>늘 주기만했던 사람 <br>언제나 웃어주던 그대라서 <br>그댄 행복할거라 난 믿었죠 <br>기쁜 날엔 친굴 찾았고 <br>힘든 날엔 그댈 찾았죠 <br>아무 말 없이 안아주던 사람 <br>나보다 나를 걱정해준 사람 <br>언제나 괜찮다던 그대 <br>늘 웃어주었던 <br>따스하기만 했던 얼굴 <br>그 흔한 위로 한 마디도 못한 채 <br>그저 나만 힘들다 나만 아프다 <br>그랬네요 <br>내가 그대에게 무심코 <br>내려놓은 내 아픔들에 <br>그대 맘은 점점 시들어갔겠죠 <br>텅 빈 방 홀로 남은 화분처럼 <br>언제나 괜찮다던 그대 <br>늘 지쳐있었던 난 외면한 그대 얼굴 <br>그 흔한 위로 한 마디도 못한 채 <br>그저 나만 힘들다 나만 아프다 <br>그랬네요 <br>이해할 수 없었죠 그대 한숨과 눈물 <br>아프다 힘들단 말 조차 <br>못했던 그대이니까 <br>행여 내 마음 다칠 까봐 <br>눈물까지도 감췄던 그대이니까 <br>나보다 그댄 더 힘들었을 텐데 <br>그런 줄도 모르고 내가 그댈 아프게 <br>그랬네요 <br>]]></content><category term="헷세" label="헷세"/><category term="그랬네요" label="그랬네요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍영구/나를_위해서_오신_주_The_Lord_Came_For_Me/</id><title>홍영구 - 나를 위해서 오신 주 (The Lord Came For Me) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:55:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:55:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%98%81%EA%B5%AC/%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9C%84%ED%95%B4%EC%84%9C_%EC%98%A4%EC%8B%A0_%EC%A3%BC_The_Lord_Came_For_Me/" title="홍영구 - 나를 위해서 오신 주 (The Lord Came For Me) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주님 나와 함께 계시며 <br>나와 동행하시네 <br>그는 나와 언제나 같이 있고 싶다 하네 <br>그는 나의 선한 목자요 나의 길 비추네 <br>어두운 세상에 나의 앞길 비춰주시네 <br>그 나라와 하늘 보좌 버리고 <br>나를 위해서 오신 주 <br>날 만족시키고 날 구원하신 분 <br>나 그분을 위해 노래 하리 <br>나는 가진 것이 없어서 <br>드릴 것도 없어서 <br>당신을 기쁘게 하지 못합니다 <br>그는 이런 마음 아시고 괜찮다 하시네 <br>전능하신 주 <br>너 말곤 필요한 것 없다 하시네 <br>그 나라와 하늘 보좌 버리고 <br>나를 위해서 오신 주 <br>날 만족시키고 날 구원하신 분 <br>나 그분을 위해 노래하리 <br>두려움과 슬픔 속에서 <br>내 힘이 되신 여호와 <br>오랜 방황 모두 끝내고 <br>날 사랑하신 그분과 함께 하리 <br>하늘보좌 버리고 나를 위해서 오신주 <br>날 만족시키고 날 구원하신 분 <br>나 그분을 위해 노래 하리 <br>나 그분을 위해 노래 하리 <br>]]></content><category term="홍영구" label="홍영구"/><category term="나를 위해서 오신 주 (The Lord Came For Me)" label="나를 위해서 오신 주 (The Lord Came For Me)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/샤넌/Love_Dont_Hurt_Feat_Amber_Of_fx/</id><title>샤넌 - Love Don`t Hurt (Feat. Amber Of f(x)) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:55:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:55:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%83%A4%EB%84%8C/Love_Dont_Hurt_Feat_Amber_Of_fx/" title="샤넌 - Love Don`t Hurt (Feat. Amber Of f(x)) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know that you've been broken <br>It's easy to see easy to see <br>Let me keep you in the moment <br>Baby just give it to me <br>I see the way you acting <br>Up in your mind wondering <br>if I'm worth the ride <br>It's a natural reaction <br>But we gon' be takin our time <br>If you don't try <br>then you ain't gonna ever know <br>If you don't try baby <br>If it takes all night let's do it <br>I just wanna show you the way <br>I'm gonna love ya <br>Like you never been loved <br>never never been loved before <br>And I'm gonna give ya <br>All of all of my heart baby you <br>the one I adore <br>I see the way <br>that you been feeling <br>And I know exactly <br>what you needing <br>I'm gonna love ya <br>Till love don't hurt anymore <br>You’ve been trying <br>to dry those tears so long <br>Maybe in time you’ll be alright <br>Staring in my eyes baby <br>you can’t deny <br>What you keep inside <br>We might be the perfect score <br>So here I’m waiting <br>at your shores <br>Oh baby please open up your doors <br>it’s you that I’m fighting for <br>If you don't try <br>then you ain't gonna ever know <br>If you don't try baby <br>If it takes all night let's do it <br>I just wanna show you the way <br>I'm gonna love ya <br>Like you never been loved <br>never never been loved before <br>And I'm gonna give ya <br>All of all of my heart baby you <br>the one I adore <br>I see the way <br>that you been feeling <br>And I know exactly <br>what you needing <br>I'm gonna love ya <br>Till love don't hurt anymore <br>Heartbreak won't break what we got <br>It's all in the feeling <br>I'm gonna be showing you good love <br>This ain't nothing <br>like all those other ones <br>I'm gonna I'm gonna love ya <br>Like you never been loved <br>never never been loved before <br>And I'm gonna give ya <br>All of all of my heart baby you <br>the one I adore <br>I see the way <br>that you been feeling <br>And I know exactly <br>what you needing <br>I'm gonna love ya <br>Till love don't hurt anymore <br>love don't hurt anymore <br>]]></content><category term="샤넌" label="샤넌"/><category term="Love Don`t Hurt (Feat. Amber Of f(x))" label="Love Don`t Hurt (Feat. Amber Of f(x))"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/샤넌/눈물이_흘러_Feat_Lil_Boi/</id><title>샤넌 - 눈물이 흘러 (Feat. Lil Boi) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:55:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:55:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%83%A4%EB%84%8C/%EB%88%88%EB%AC%BC%EC%9D%B4_%ED%9D%98%EB%9F%AC_Feat_Lil_Boi/" title="샤넌 - 눈물이 흘러 (Feat. Lil Boi) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다 식어 버린 커피 <br>넌 이런 느낌 모르겠지 예 <br>또 떠올리기 싫어 <br>더 차갑던 너의 눈빛 <br>언제 깨져버린 건지 <br>남아있는 작은 유리 파편 <br>다시 마음이 찔려도 <br>괜찮을까 이젠 정말 <br>달콤하게 먼저 왜곡된 추억도 <br>지우려해 Baby <br>힘들지않아 또 하루가 너없이도 <br>반복되고 <br>눈물이 흘러 <br>모두 지나가고 <br>이제 끝난 걸 알지만 <br>또 추억이 흘러 <br>계속 숨을 쉬고 <br>잠도 잘자고 있는걸 <br>너 없이도 화려한 거리 <br>너 없이도 따스한 공기 <br>눈물이 흘러 오늘도 <br>Oh Don't Hurt Anymore <br>연락 없는 phone <br>아마도 넌 아무것도 <br>아닌듯 보낼거 같아보여 uh <br>Baby I just wanna know <br>너도 나와 같은 길에서 <br>똑같이 힘들어 하고 있는 지 <br>wait wait <br>목이 말러 <br>What’s the problem <br>물론 말론 괜찮지만 <br>벌써 너의 집 앞까지 왔어 <br>문틈 사이 전해오는 너의 향기에 <br>금방이라도 문이 열릴것만 같지 왜 <br>Baby I’ll be there <br>마음속에 깊이 박혔던 상처도 <br>어루만져줘 Baby <br>슬프지 않아 또 하루가 흘러가고 <br>예전처럼 <br>눈물이 흘러 <br>모두 지나가고 <br>이제 끝난 걸 알지만 <br>또 추억이 흘러 <br>계속 숨을 쉬고 <br>잠도 잘자고 있는걸 <br>너 없이도 화려한 거리 <br>너 없이도 따스한 공기 <br>눈물이 흘러 오늘도 <br>Oh Don't Hurt Anymore <br>Heart break 다 겪는 일이야 <br>내 눈물처럼 번지는건 싫어 <br>이 모습대로 시간이 흘러도 <br>다 지나가는거야 <br>눈물이 흘러 <br>모두 지나가고 <br>이제 끝난 걸 알지만 <br>또 추억이 흘러 <br>계속 숨을 쉬고 <br>잠도 잘자고 있는걸 <br>너 없이도 화려한 거리 <br>너 없이도 따스한 공기 <br>눈물이 흘러 오늘도 <br>Oh Don't Hurt Anymore <br>시간이 흘러 아무렇지 않게 <br>시간이 흘러 아무렇지 않게 <br>시간이 흘러 아무의미 없게 <br>Oh Don't Hurt Anymore <br>]]></content><category term="샤넌" label="샤넌"/><category term="눈물이 흘러 (Feat. Lil Boi)" label="눈물이 흘러 (Feat. Lil Boi)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스터몽/Peterpan_Feat_Bumby_JinLee/</id><title>스터몽 - Peterpan (Feat. Bumby, JinLee) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:55:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:55:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B0%EB%AA%BD/Peterpan_Feat_Bumby_JinLee/" title="스터몽 - Peterpan (Feat. Bumby, JinLee) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[still a young <br>앞으로 더 많은걸 바래도 <br>나는 여전하길 바래 <br>still a young <br>어른처럼 살라고 말해도 <br>나는 어리기만 할게 <br>still a young <br>앞으로 더 많은걸 바래도 <br>나는 여전하길 바래 <br>still a young <br>어른처럼 살라고 말해도 <br>나는 어리기만 할게 <br>약 두달정도 뒤면 <br>나는 어른이 되는데 별거없이 <br>나이만 늘었네 <br>라고 생각하는 친구들이 많아 <br>I don't wanna <br>GUCCI나 PRADA <br>I just wanna be another one <br>얘들아 받아적어 <br>평범한 어른관 달러 <br>내 10년 뒤 모습은 <br>지금 날 보고 잘 기억해 <br>계속 찾으러 다니지 내 팅커벨 <br>벌써 새벽에 닿았다고해도 <br>여유롭게 동심을 담았지 <br>앞으로도 많은걸 바란다고해도 <br>여전하길 바래 눈을 감았지 <br>멀리서 보면 다 풍경이란 말 <br>와닿지도 않아 젊음이 아까워 <br>라고 말한 또래친구들은 이제 <br>성숙함에 대해 <br>멀어지고 있는것만 같애 <br>시간이 지나고 나서도 <br>느끼고 있는건 아직 어리단 걸 <br>내게 동화를 들려줬던 그때에 <br>기억까지도 아직 남아있네 <br>어른의 무게에 대해 <br>지불하라면 난 내 나이 만큼만 <br>너네들을 내게 대입해 <br>봐도 남는 건 없지 이런 내겐 <br>still a young <br>앞으로 더 많은걸 바래도 <br>나는 여전하길 바래 <br>still a young <br>어른처럼 살라고 말해도 <br>나는 어리기만 할게 <br>still a young <br>앞으로 더 많은걸 바래도 <br>나는 여전하길 바래 <br>still a young <br>어른처럼 살라고 말해도 <br>나는 어리기만 할게 <br>]]></content><category term="스터몽" label="스터몽"/><category term="Peterpan (Feat. Bumby, JinLee)" label="Peterpan (Feat. Bumby, JinLee)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/형우/거쳐간다/</id><title>형우 - 거쳐간다 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:55:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:55:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%98%95%EC%9A%B0/%EA%B1%B0%EC%B3%90%EA%B0%84%EB%8B%A4/" title="형우 - 거쳐간다 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 또 다른 사람을 만나고 <br>너는 또 다른 사람을 만나고 <br>한 때의 시간을 머물렀다가 <br>또 다른 사람에게 비켜주었네 <br>세상이 그래야 한다고 해서 <br>그래서 다른 사람을 만나면 <br>반드시 나는 니가 생각나고 <br>그 사실을 숨긴 채로 <br>다른 사람을 만나게 되지 <br>나는 언제까지 <br>다른 사람을 만나야 해 <br>만나지 않고선 <br>절대 살 순 없는 걸까 <br>그래 우리는 그렇게 <br>잠시 서로 거쳐간다 <br>다른 사람을 만나러 <br>또 다른 사람을 거쳐서 간다 <br>내 삶도 바보처럼 <br>잠시 너를 거쳐가서 <br>다른 사람 따위는 더 <br>필요가 없음을 뒤늦게 알았다 <br>나는 또 다른 사랑에 빠지고 <br>너는 또 다른 사랑에 빠지고 <br>우리가 하나였던 시간들을 <br>다른 사람에게 비켜주고 <br>나도 다음을 찾아가더라 <br>어디로 가는지 <br>모른 채로 그냥 가는데 <br>돌고 도는 그 반복이 <br>지겨워질 법도 한데 <br>우리는 그렇게 <br>잠시 서로 거쳐간다 <br>다른 사람을 만나러 <br>또 다른 사람을 거쳐서 간다 <br>내 삶도 바보처럼 <br>잠시 너를 거쳐가서 <br>다른 사람 따위는 더 <br>필요가 없음을 뒤늦게 알았다 <br>그래 사실 난 지금도 <br>너를 다 지나진 못했어 <br>여전히 그대로 너라는 사람을 <br>거쳐가는 길에 있었어 <br>때로는 잘 된 거라 생각을 해 <br>때로는 미치도록 후회를 해 <br>다음 사람을 만나기 위해 <br>거쳐가야 할 사이였나 <br>내 삶은 그렇게 <br>잠시 너를 거쳐갔다 <br>다음 사람 따위는 더 <br>필요가 없음을 뒤늦게 알고 <br>이대로 니가 없이 <br>한 번의 삶을 거쳐가면 <br>다음 세상 따위는 더 <br>있지도 않음을 뒤늦게 알았다 <br>]]></content><category term="형우" label="형우"/><category term="거쳐간다" label="거쳐간다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/금잔디/그랬었구나/</id><title>금잔디 - 그랬었구나 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:56:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:56:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%88%EC%9E%94%EB%94%94/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%AC%EC%97%88%EA%B5%AC%EB%82%98/" title="금잔디 - 그랬었구나 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그랬었구나 내가 그랬었구나 <br>마음에 상처 주었었구나 <br>그랬었구나 내가 그랬었구나 <br>깊은 실망을 안겨 주었었구나 <br>미안하다 미안해 정말 미안해 <br>나 혼자의 욕심을 부렸었구나 <br>미안하다 미안해 정말 미안해 <br>너에 대한 배려를 못했었구나 <br>오오 <br>그랬었구나 내가 그랬었구나 <br>나의 사랑이 많이 부족했구나 <br>미안하다 미안해 정말 미안해 <br>나 혼자의 욕심을 부렸었구나 <br>미안하다 미안해 정말 미안해 <br>너에 대한 배려를 못했었구나 <br>오오 <br>그랬었구나 내가 그랬었구나 <br>나의 사랑이 많이 부족했구나 <br>그래 그래 그래 그래 <br>내가 그랬었구나 <br>그래 그래 그래 그래 그랬었구나 <br>그랬었구나 내가 그랬었구나 <br>너를 더 많이 아껴줘야겠구나 <br>너를 더 많이 사랑해야겠구나]]></content><category term="금잔디" label="금잔디"/><category term="그랬었구나" label="그랬었구나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/금잔디/보라빛_엽서/</id><title>금잔디 - 보라빛 엽서 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:57:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:57:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%88%EC%9E%94%EB%94%94/%EB%B3%B4%EB%9D%BC%EB%B9%9B_%EC%97%BD%EC%84%9C/" title="금잔디 - 보라빛 엽서 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보라빛 엽서에 실어온 향기는 <br>당신의 눈물인가 이별의 아픔인가 <br>한숨속에 묻힌 사연 지워보려해도 <br>떠나버린 당신 마음 붙잡을 수 없네 <br>오늘도 가버린 당신의 생각엔 <br>눈물로 써내려간 얼룩진 일기장엔 <br>다시 못 올 그대 모습 기다리는 사연 <br><br>오늘도 가버린 당신의 생각엔 <br>눈물로 써내려간 얼룩진 일기장엔 <br>다시 못 올 그대 모습 기다리는 사연 <br>다시 못 올 그대 모습 기다리는 사연]]></content><category term="금잔디" label="금잔디"/><category term="보라빛 엽서" label="보라빛 엽서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코드쿤스트/Dont_shoot_me_MAMA_Feat_Car_the_garden_온스테이지_Ver/</id><title>코드쿤스트 - Don`t shoot me MAMA (Feat. Car, the garden) (온스테이지 Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:58:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:58:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%93%9C%EC%BF%A4%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/Dont_shoot_me_MAMA_Feat_Car_the_garden_%EC%98%A8%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80_Ver/" title="코드쿤스트 - Don`t shoot me MAMA (Feat. Car, the garden) (온스테이지 Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[삶은 짧고 갈등은 깊어가 <br>나는 아주 작은 빛이 고파 <br>모든 것은 선택으로 길들여져 <br>It's so beautiful <br>It's so beautiful <br>손을 들어 내가 원하는 걸 <br>닿을 수가 있기를 기도해 <br>나는 아주 작은 꽃을 피우려 <br>내일을 열어 <br>희망을 봐 <br>When we were young <br>We burned the highway skyline <br>Don't shoot me MAMA <br>I can't believe the things <br>I'm going through <br>Tell me mama <br>Maybe I'm thinking of this wrong way <br>Don't shoot me MAMA <br>I can't believe the things <br>I'm going through <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>It's so beautiful day <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>It's so beautiful day <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>It's so beautiful day <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>It's so beautiful day <br>삶은 짧고 갈등은 깊어가 <br>나는 아주 작은 빛이 고파 <br>모든 것은 선택으로 길들여져 <br>It's so beautiful <br>It's so beautiful <br>손을 들어 내가 원하는 걸 <br>닿을 수가 있기를 기도해 <br>나는 아주 작은 꽃을 피우려 <br>내일을 열어 <br>희망을 봐 <br>When we were young <br>We burned the highway skyline <br>Don't shoot me MAMA <br>I can't believe the things <br>I'm going through <br>Tell me mama <br>Maybe I'm thinking of this wrong way <br>Don't shoot me MAMA <br>I can't believe the things <br>I'm going through <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>It's so beautiful day <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>It's so beautiful day <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>It's so beautiful day <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>It's so beautiful day <br>]]></content><category term="코드쿤스트" label="코드쿤스트"/><category term="Don`t shoot me MAMA (Feat. Car, the garden) (온스테이지 Ver.)" label="Don`t shoot me MAMA (Feat. Car, the garden) (온스테이지 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코드쿤스트/Born_from_the_Blue_Feat_JUSTHIS_온스테이지_Ver/</id><title>코드쿤스트 - Born from the Blue (Feat. JUSTHIS) (온스테이지 Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:58:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:58:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%93%9C%EC%BF%A4%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/Born_from_the_Blue_Feat_JUSTHIS_%EC%98%A8%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80_Ver/" title="코드쿤스트 - Born from the Blue (Feat. JUSTHIS) (온스테이지 Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Can we get a little break <br>Can we get a little <br>Can we get a little break <br>24/7 365 <br>노력하면 뭐든 이뤄낼 수 있다를 <br>믿은 사람들이 24시 일 해 <br>거기서 나온 세금으로 <br>누군가는 비행 <br>영어로는 fly <br>서울이란 의사는 과잉 처방해 <br>카페인 과다복용 <br>24시 편의점과 카페가 <br>학생들의 첫 drug dealer <br>Let me make sense to you check it <br>불안장애 공황장애 <br>불면증 우울증 <br>허나 한국 사람한테 <br>정신병원으로 들어간다는 것은 <br>이력서에 빨간 줄 긋기 <br>결국 나도 발작이 오고 나서야 <br>발을 옮겼지 <br>의사들은 약을 줘 설명도 없이 <br>부작용 생기거든 약을 바꿔 <br>여전히 설명 없이 <br>Now what you see <br>I see the lack of justice <br>got us disgusted <br>You don't even know <br>I'm so high right now <br>Look at the streets <br>What you see <br>난 사람들이 무시하려는 <br>악마가 보이지 <br>We're not born to be blue <br>We're just born from the blue <br>Look at the earth <br>What you see <br>Is it white is it green <br>To me it is blue <br>I'm not born to be blue <br>I'm just born from the blue <br>We're not born to be blue <br>We're just born from the blue <br>Wake up wake up <br>Hold up hold up <br>오늘 할 일이 뭐였지 <br>스케줄 애플리케이션을 켜 <br>미팅과 공연 연습 피처링 앨범 <br>제일 모르는 사람이 됐어 <br>내가 나에 대해서 <br>I need 30-minute mediation <br>눈 감고 내게 물어 <br>너는 지금 어딨어 <br>보이네 내가 밟고 간 동료들이 <br>보이냐 내가 맞았지 <br>fuck your guessin' <br>네가 망할 거랬던 공연과 앨범 <br>존나 blow up <br>개인적인 건 아냐 상처받았어 <br>마데카솔 발라 <br>혼자 다 한 게 자랑까진 <br>아니어도 자부심 <br>날 과소평가하는 deal <br>설명할 시간 없어 <br>내 가치에 대해 <br>어차피 내 전례들처럼 <br>니네도 다 믿게 돼 <br>난 내 자신을 믿으니 <br>너도 날 믿으라고 안 해 <br>너도 너 자신을 믿어 I'm blue <br>You don't even know <br>I'm so high right now <br>Look at the streets <br>What you see <br>난 사람들이 무시하려는 <br>악마가 보이지 <br>We're not born to be blue <br>We're just born from the blue <br>Look at the earth <br>What you see <br>Is it white is it green <br>To me it is blue <br>I'm not born to be blue <br>I'm just born from the blue <br>We're not born to be blue <br>We're just born from the blue <br>You don't even know <br>I'm so high right now <br>That's why I watch these things <br>They don't even know <br>We're so god damn high now <br>One more time one more time <br>I'm not born to be blue <br>I'm just born from the blue <br>We're not born to be blue <br>We're just born from the blue <br>I'm not born to be blue <br>I'm just born from the blue <br>We're not born to be blue <br>We're just born from the blue <br>]]></content><category term="코드쿤스트" label="코드쿤스트"/><category term="Born from the Blue (Feat. JUSTHIS) (온스테이지 Ver.)" label="Born from the Blue (Feat. JUSTHIS) (온스테이지 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코드쿤스트/Lounge_Feat_화지_온스테이지_Ver/</id><title>코드쿤스트 - Lounge (Feat. 화지) (온스테이지 Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:58:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:58:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%93%9C%EC%BF%A4%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/Lounge_Feat_%ED%99%94%EC%A7%80_%EC%98%A8%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80_Ver/" title="코드쿤스트 - Lounge (Feat. 화지) (온스테이지 Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[히피 같은 내 방랑을 <br>다 받아줄 집시같은 너 내 여왕 <br>아침이 밝으면 가방을 싸 <br>저녁 전에 이미 활주로 떠나 <br>같이 도망가자 바다 파랗고 <br>저 데모 소리 안 들리는 곳 <br>사람들 chill 한 곳 시간이 <br>돈이고 내 돈이고 여권이자 통역 <br>쟤네는 여행객 우린 탈주범 <br>여기저기 싸돌아다닐 여권 <br>네개 채운 도장들 <br>LP 둘에 EP와 믹스테잎 <br>여기까진 부족해 가자 <br>거기 말 좀 안 통한들 뭐 어때 <br>사람 사는데는 다 비슷해 <br>무대에서 라운지에서 바로 비행기 <br>손잡이 걷어올려 너랑 붙어 쉬겠지 <br>눈 뜨면 바로 딴 나라 딴 바닷 바람 <br>근데 거기 네가 없다면 버릴 여행지 <br>손가락 둘씩 합쳐서 <br>두 쌍에 피스아웃 <br>너랑 볼 태양 얼마든 안 비싸 <br>여기 별 없는 하늘 경적소리 뒷담 <br>전부 두고 폰 꺼 인생 짧으니까 <br>세상이 어지러워 갈 데가 더 줄어가 <br>더 늦기 전에 잘라내자 우리 무력감 <br>인간의 때가 덜 묻은 해안 위에 <br>내게 취해 밤새워 헤엄치게 <br>yeah baby 너랑 나 코치 말고 1등 <br>라운지에서 라운지에서 라운지 yeah <br>날씨가 싫거나 별 보고 싶음 말해줘 <br>다 데려갈게 <br>yeah baby 너랑 나 <br>게이트에서 게이트 <br>라운지에서 라운지에서 라운지 yeah <br>라운지에서 라운지에서 라운지 yeah <br>라운지에서 라운지 <br>닫을 괄호들이 너무 많은 <br>통빡 굴리는 애들 사이 <br>숨쉬기 힘들어졌네 <br>저 톱니들의 삐걱거림 사이 소름 <br>신경 곤두서 <br>눈 뜨고 걷기 피곤한 상태 <br>난 지금 세상의 잣대 다 피해 <br>가책 없이 취할 내 도피처를 찾네 <br>야자나무 사이 빼꼼히 보이는 <br>너의 그 실루엣과 그 뒤태에 <br>그 비전을 봤네 <br>대통령이 사이비랑 놀아나서 <br>나라 팔아 먹었지 <br>바다 건너 저긴 피부색이 <br>다름 엿 먹지 <br>저긴 폭탄 저긴 빚더미 <br>저긴 종교 핍박에 아기들도 <br>총을 들지 겁 없이 <br>시대는 어지럽고 갈 데는 줄어가 <br>더 늦기 전에 보러 가자 <br>별이 수놓은 밤 <br>인류의 때가 덜 묻은 해안 위에 <br>내게 취해 밤 세워 헤엄치게 <br>yeah baby 너랑 나 코치 말고 1등 <br>라운지에서 라운지에서 라운지 yeah <br>날씨가 싫거나 별 보고 싶음 말해줘 <br>다 데려갈게 <br>yeah baby 너랑 나 <br>게이트에서 게이트 <br>라운지에서 라운지에서 라운지 yeah <br>라운지에서 라운지에서 라운지 yeah <br>라운지에서 라운지 <br>히피같은 내 방랑을 <br>다 받아줄 집시같은 너 내 여왕 <br>아침이 밝으면 가방을 싸 <br>저녁 전에 이미 활주로 떠나 <br>같이 도망가자 바다 파랗고 <br>저 데모 소리 안 들리는 곳 <br>사람들 chill 한 곳 시간이 <br>돈이고 내 돈이고 여권이자 통역 <br>쟤네는 여행객 우린 탈주범 <br>yeah baby 너랑 나 코치 말고 1등 <br>라운지에서 라운지에서 라운지 yeah <br>날씨가 싫거나 별 보고 싶음 말해줘 <br>다 데려갈게 <br>yeah baby 너랑 나 <br>게이트에서 게이트 <br>라운지에서 라운지에서 라운지 yeah <br>라운지에서 라운지에서 라운지 yeah <br>라운지에서 라운지 <br>Deep <br>]]></content><category term="코드쿤스트" label="코드쿤스트"/><category term="Lounge (Feat. 화지) (온스테이지 Ver.)" label="Lounge (Feat. 화지) (온스테이지 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sound_Offering/오직_성령이/</id><title>Sound Offering - 오직 성령이 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:58:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:58:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sound_Offering/%EC%98%A4%EC%A7%81_%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9%EC%9D%B4/" title="Sound Offering - 오직 성령이 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[알기원해 <br>나의 삶의 참된 의미를 <br>가기원해 <br>내가 가야 할 그 어딘가로 <br>보기원해 <br>어두움을 물리치는 빛 <br>듣기원해 <br>자유 얻은 내 친구의 웃음소리 <br>오직 성령이 임하시면 <br>너희가 권능을 받아 <br>예루살렘과 온 유대 사마리아 <br>저 땅 끝까지 이르러 <br>내 증인 되리라 <br>알기원해 <br>나의 삶의 참된 의미를 <br>가기원해 <br>내가 가야 할 그 어딘가로 <br>보기원해 <br>어두움을 물리치는 빛 <br>듣기원해 <br>자유 얻은 내 친구의 웃음소리 <br>오직 성령이 임하시면 <br>너희가 권능을 받아 <br>예루살렘과 온 유대 사마리아 <br>저 땅 끝까지 이르러 <br>오직 성령이 임하시면 <br>너희가 권능을 받아 <br>예루살렘과 온 유대 사마리아 <br>저 땅 끝까지 이르러 <br>내 증인 되리라 <br>]]></content><category term="Sound Offering" label="Sound Offering"/><category term="오직 성령이" label="오직 성령이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sound_Offering/미문에서/</id><title>Sound Offering - 미문에서 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T15:58:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T15:58:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sound_Offering/%EB%AF%B8%EB%AC%B8%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C/" title="Sound Offering - 미문에서 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 안에 그 누구도 <br>빼앗을 수 없는 그 이름 <br>그 이름 의지하여 나아갑니다 <br>세상에 그 무엇도 <br>대신 할 수 없는 그 이름 <br>그 이름 믿음으로 선포합니다 <br>은과 금은 내게 없으나 <br>내게 있는 이것을 주노라 <br>나사렛 예수 그리스도의 이름으로 <br>이제 일어나 걸어라 <br>내 안에 그 누구도 <br>빼앗을 수 없는 그 이름 <br>그 이름 의지하여 나아갑니다 <br>세상에 그 무엇도 <br>대신 할 수 없는 그 이름 <br>그 이름 믿음으로 선포합니다 <br>은과 금은 내게 없으나 <br>내게 있는 이것을 주노라 <br>나사렛 예수 그리스도의 이름으로 <br>이제 일어나 걸어라 <br>은과 금은 내게 없으나 <br>내게 있는 이것을 주노라 <br>나사렛 예수 그리스도의 이름으로 <br>이제 일어나 걸어라 <br>]]></content><category term="Sound Offering" label="Sound Offering"/><category term="미문에서" label="미문에서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Faas/Shouldve_Seen_It/</id><title>Luke Faas - Should`ve Seen It - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:04:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:04:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Faas/Shouldve_Seen_It/" title="Luke Faas - Should`ve Seen It - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I waited for an hour <br>Before I drove to see you <br>The very worst of feelings <br><br>The interval that we grew <br>and every time that I would wanna get some space <br>You'd put on that angry face you know I hate <br>To make you sad and angry <br>But now you've drained all my empathy <br><br>Now its time for me to go and catch a brake <br>And seek some, loud places <br>Forget time and space, and relieve all the weight <br>Just run from, our location <br><br>Hearing your voice for hours <br>I'm sick of tears and crying <br>Don't wanna see you suffer <br>But now I need some silence <br>I don't wanna stay because it's practical <br>I don't wanna be over adaptable <br>I'll admit I'm failing <br>Assuming this was plain sailing <br><br>Now its time for me to go and catch a brake <br>And seek some, loud places <br>Forget time and space, and relieve all the weight <br>Just run from, our location <br><br>Should've of seen it <br>Should've of seen it <br>Should've of seen it coming]]></content><category term="Luke Faas" label="Luke Faas"/><category term="Should`ve Seen It" label="Should`ve Seen It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Faas/Why_Bother/</id><title>Luke Faas - Why Bother - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:04:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:04:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Faas/Why_Bother/" title="Luke Faas - Why Bother - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Why bother <br>Why bother stretch my hand <br>Why bother <br>Why bother <br>You for your demand <br>My brother <br><br>Your reputations sticks to you as glue <br>You had a none trust <br>Not only a few <br>Now your returning <br>Could this be my clue <br>Do I go away and never bother <br>Why bother <br><br>I won't waste the gravel energy on you <br>Why would I bother <br>Why bother <br>I won't spread the rest with sympathy <br>Why would I bother <br>Why bother <br><br>Why bother <br>Why would I even care <br>Why bother <br>Why bother <br>The anything but fail <br>Why bother <br><br>Your reputations sticks to you as glue <br>You had a none trust <br>Not only a few <br>Now your returning <br>Could this be my clue <br>Do I go away and never bother <br>Why bother <br><br>I won't waste the gravel energy on you <br>Why would I bother <br>Why bother <br>I won't spread the rest with sympathy <br>Why would I bother <br>Why bother <br><br>I won't waste the gravel energy on you <br>Why would I bother <br>Why bother <br>I won't spread the rest with sympathy <br>Why would I bother <br>Why bother]]></content><category term="Luke Faas" label="Luke Faas"/><category term="Why Bother" label="Why Bother"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Faas/Apathy/</id><title>Luke Faas - Apathy - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:04:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:04:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Faas/Apathy/" title="Luke Faas - Apathy - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Can you take it <br>I haven't made my mind <br>I hope you own chapter <br>So you can stay aligned <br>So little balance <br>Haven't been at ease <br>Ever since that year <br>Of your first breeze <br><br>I'm no magician <br>I have no power of being friends <br>I doubt it will help you with flower bouquets <br><br>I'm much lazy <br>Like imagination too <br>Should I try even harder <br>Or be aversive <br>You suffer in through a personality your conflict <br>I'm afraid of apathy <br>Your affection should be heard <br>You suffer in through a personality your conflict <br>I'm afraid of apathy <br>Your affection should be heard <br><br>Can you take it <br>I thought I'll escape <br>To another planet <br>When your in better shape <br>When you find balance <br>In an ice and cool <br>Even when I fuck up <br>Acting fool <br><br>I'm no magician <br>I have no power of being friends <br>I doubt it will help you with flower bouquets <br><br>I'm not just lazy <br>Like imagination too <br>Should I try even harder <br>Or be aversive <br>Just suffer in through a personality your conflict <br>I'm afraid of apathy <br>Your affection should be heard <br>Just suffer in through a personality your conflict <br>I'm afraid of apathy <br>Your affection should be heard <br>And suffer in through a personality your conflict]]></content><category term="Luke Faas" label="Luke Faas"/><category term="Apathy" label="Apathy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도시수족관/미끼/</id><title>도시수족관 - 미끼 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:04:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:04:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%EC%8B%9C%EC%88%98%EC%A1%B1%EA%B4%80/%EB%AF%B8%EB%81%BC/" title="도시수족관 - 미끼 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[실 끝에 바늘에 욕망을 꾄다 <br>언제든 빠져나갈 수 있게 <br>내 끝에 욕망에 너로 사로잡을 때 <br>내 끝에 사랑에 너로 사로잡을 때 <br>행복하게 너도 웃고 있지 <br>비겁하게 너도 웃고 있지 <br>그 고운 살결에 상처를 입혀도 <br>웃으며 핥는 건 너 그래 너 <br>깨끗한 숨결에 <br>악의를 넣는 것 또한 너 <br>난 너를 사랑해 정말로 사랑해 <br>너를 위해 나는 미끼가 되었고 <br>영원히 있을게 니 곁에 있을게 <br>내 더러운 사랑엔 니가 있겠지 <br>실 끝에 바늘에 환상을 꾄다 <br>언제든 집어 삼킬 수 있게 <br>내 끝에 욕망에 너로 사로잡을 때 <br>내 끝에 사랑에 너로 사로잡을 때 <br>행복하게 너도 웃고 있지 <br>비겁하게 너도 웃고 있지 <br>그 고운 살결에 상처를 입혀도 <br>웃으며 핥는 건 너 그래 너 <br>깨끗한 숨결에 <br>악의를 넣는 것 또한 너 <br>난 너를 증오해 너무나 증오해 <br>너로 인해 나는 악인이 되었고 <br>영원히 없을게 니 곁에 없을게 <br>니 깨끗한 증오엔 내가 있겠지 <br>약에 취한 듯한 너를 묶고선 <br>잔혹한 사랑을 보여줄게 <br>거짓말쟁이의 혀를 잘라서 <br>풀려버린 눈을 도려냈지 <br>그 고운 살결에 상처를 입혀도 <br>웃으며 핥는 건 너 <br>깨끗한 숨결에 <br>악의를 넣는 것 또한 너 <br>그 고운 살결에 상처를 입혀도 <br>웃으며 핥는 건 너 <br>깨끗한 숨결에 <br>악의를 넣는 것 또한 너 <br>난 너를 사랑해 정말로 사랑해 <br>너를 위해 나는 미끼가 되었고 <br>영원히 있을게 니 곁에 있을게 <br>내 더러운 사랑엔 니가 있겠지 <br>난 너를 증오해 너무나 증오해 <br>너로 인해 나는 악인이 되었고 <br>영원히 없을게 니 곁에 없을게 <br>니 깨끗한 증오엔 내가 있겠지 <br>]]></content><category term="도시수족관" label="도시수족관"/><category term="미끼" label="미끼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도시수족관/켠김에_왕까지/</id><title>도시수족관 - 켠김에 왕까지 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:04:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:04:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%EC%8B%9C%EC%88%98%EC%A1%B1%EA%B4%80/%EC%BC%A0%EA%B9%80%EC%97%90_%EC%99%95%EA%B9%8C%EC%A7%80/" title="도시수족관 - 켠김에 왕까지 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[배고픔에 시달리는 작은 노예여 <br>어찌하여 너는 계속 여기 남았나 <br>꿈이 너무 짙어 못 떠나는 노예여 <br>언제까지 너는 꿈을 뜨지 못하나 <br>부르튼 입술을 확인하며 <br>어찌도 그리 슬피 울었나 <br>그대는 하루도 쉬지 않고 <br>아침 해부터 달이 뜰 때까지 <br>외로움에 시달리는 작은 노예여 <br>어찌하여 너는 계속 여기 남았나 <br>꿈이 안전해서 못 떠나는 노예여 <br>언제까지 너는 꿈을 뜨지 못하나 <br>포기란 주변에 손가락질 <br>귀를 막고 계속 난 모른 척 <br>그대는 눈물을 닦아내며 <br>두 눈에 반짝 별이 뜰 때까지 <br>외로움에 시달리는 작은 노예여 <br>어찌하여 너는 계속 여기 남았나 <br>꿈이 안전해서 못 떠나는 노예여 <br>언제까지 너는 꿈을 뜨지 못하나 <br>어두운 감옥에 갇힌 노예 <br>무거운 쇠고랑 철컹대며 <br>저 높은 태양이 추락할 때 <br>날개를 훔쳐 날아날 때까지 <br>외로움에 시달리는 작은 노예여 <br>어찌하여 너는 계속 여기 남았나 <br>꿈이 안전해서 못 떠나는 노예여 <br>언제까지 너는 꿈을 뜨지 못하나 <br>외로움에 시달리는 작은 노예여 <br>어찌하여 너는 계속 여기 남았나 <br>꿈이 안전해서 못 떠나는 노예여 <br>언제까지 너는 꿈을 뜨지 못하나 <br>실패라 해도 씹어주겠어 <br>끝이 없다면 끝내주겠어 <br>시련이라면 밟아주겠어 <br>그곳에 나는 노예가 되어 <br>아픔을 모두 안고 <br>불행을 모두 맞고 <br>해가 뜰 때를 위해 <br>이곳에 왕이 되겠어 <br>]]></content><category term="도시수족관" label="도시수족관"/><category term="켠김에 왕까지" label="켠김에 왕까지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도시수족관/해파리/</id><title>도시수족관 - 해파리 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:04:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:04:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%EC%8B%9C%EC%88%98%EC%A1%B1%EA%B4%80/%ED%95%B4%ED%8C%8C%EB%A6%AC/" title="도시수족관 - 해파리 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새파란 물위에 투명한 사람 하나 <br>바다를 둥둥둥 하염없이 떠다니지 <br>그런 너나 이런 나나 <br>살아있는 시체나 같아 <br>그런 너는 내겐 나는 <br>너무나도 편안해 <br>차가운 유리 속 투명한 사람 하나 <br>심해 속 빛나는 우아한 발레리나 <br>그런 너나 이런 나나 <br>살아있는 시체나 같아 <br>그런 너는 내겐 나는 <br>너무나도 편안해 <br>바다에 뛰어들래 너를 보기 위해 <br>차라리 내게 안겨 고통 받을래 <br>저 먼 새하얀 빛이 나를 찾아들 때 <br>그땐 너에게 감사해할게 <br>뇌도 없고 생각 없고 <br>머리 없고 꼬리 없어 <br>옆구리엔 긴치마를 <br>둘러싸고 춤을 추지 <br>그런 너나 이런 나나 <br>살아있는 시체나 같아 <br>그런 너는 내겐 나는 <br>너무나도 편안해 <br>바다에 뛰어들래 너를 보기 위해 <br>차라리 내게 안겨 고통 받을래 <br>저 먼 새하얀 빛이 나를 찾아들 때 <br>그땐 너에게 감사해할게 <br>바다에 뛰어들래 너를 보기 위해 <br>차라리 내게 안겨 고통 받을래 <br>저 먼 새하얀 빛이 나를 찾아들 때 <br>그땐 너에게 감사해할게 <br>바다에 뛰어들래 너를 보기 위해 <br>차라리 내게 안겨 고통 받을래 <br>저 먼 새하얀 빛이 나를 찾아들 때 <br>그땐 너에게 감사해할게 <br>그땐 너에게 감사해할게 <br>그땐 너에게 감사해할게 <br>]]></content><category term="도시수족관" label="도시수족관"/><category term="해파리" label="해파리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도시수족관/손을_잡아주세요/</id><title>도시수족관 - 손을 잡아주세요 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:04:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:04:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%EC%8B%9C%EC%88%98%EC%A1%B1%EA%B4%80/%EC%86%90%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%A1%EC%95%84%EC%A3%BC%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94/" title="도시수족관 - 손을 잡아주세요 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[손을 잡아주세요 꼭 잡아주세요 <br>제 두근대는 심장이 <br>당신의 마음에 문을 <br>두드려도 괜찮을까요 <br>눈을 감아주세요 꼭 감아주세요 <br>제 간절한 목소리를 <br>당신의 귓가에 속삭여 <br>보아도 괜찮을까요 <br>이봐요 이젠 얼굴을 <br>내밀어봐요 내 손을 잡아줘요 <br>나이렇게 문앞에 <br>세워 두지만 말아요 <br>두지만 말아요 <br>정말 천국같은 이곳이 <br>당신에 맘속이 맞던가요 <br>눈이 부신 이곳이 <br>당신에 맘속이 맞던가요 <br>눈을 감아주세요 꼭 감아주세요 <br>제 간절한 목소리를 <br>당신의 귓가에 속삭여 <br>보아도 괜찮을까요 <br>이봐요 이젠 얼굴을 <br>내밀어봐요 내 손을 잡아줘요 <br>나이렇게 문앞에 <br>세워 두지만 말아요 <br>두지만 말아요 <br>정말 천국같은 이곳이 <br>당신에 맘속이 맞던가요 <br>눈이 부신 이곳이 <br>당신에 맘속이 맞던가요 <br>어쩜이리도 아름다운가요 <br>당신이하는 모든 말들이 <br>나를 바라보는 그마음이 <br>내겐 정말 행복이었던가요 <br>정말 천국같은 이곳이 <br>당신에 맘속이 맞던가요 <br>눈이 부신 이곳이 <br>당신에 맘속이 맞던가요 <br>]]></content><category term="도시수족관" label="도시수족관"/><category term="손을 잡아주세요" label="손을 잡아주세요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도시수족관/고백_그리움/</id><title>도시수족관 - 고백, 그리움 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:05:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:05:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%EC%8B%9C%EC%88%98%EC%A1%B1%EA%B4%80/%EA%B3%A0%EB%B0%B1_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9B%80/" title="도시수족관 - 고백, 그리움 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 품에서 떠났던 너를 <br>잠시도 잊은 적 없다 <br>니곁에서 너를 찾아도 <br>더는 찾을 수 없다 <br>그리워 하면 <br>내가 널 미워할까봐 <br>널 향한 내 마음이 <br>나를 아프게 만든다 <br>내안을 비춘 그대는 <br>흩날린 꽃이 되고 <br>멀리서 온 그 향기에 <br>그만 취해버리고 <br>내안을 비춘 그대는 <br>빛날린 햇살 되고 <br>그빛에 그대 얼굴이 <br>더욱 선명해지고 <br>내안을 비춘 그대는 <br>흩날린 꽃이 되고 <br>멀리서 온 그 향기에 <br>그만 취해버리고 <br>내안을 비춘 그대는 <br>빛날린 햇살 되고 <br>그빛에 그대 얼굴이 <br>더욱 선명해지고 <br>]]></content><category term="도시수족관" label="도시수족관"/><category term="고백, 그리움" label="고백, 그리움"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도시수족관/Deep_Dream/</id><title>도시수족관 - Deep Dream - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:05:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:05:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%EC%8B%9C%EC%88%98%EC%A1%B1%EA%B4%80/Deep_Dream/" title="도시수족관 - Deep Dream - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리는 새벽달이 뜨면 <br>그때 다시 만나 <br>포근한 하얀 안개속을 <br>멍하니 걸었지 <br>우 깊은 잠에 들어야 <br>만날 수가 있나 <br>사라진 그대를 그대를 찾아 <br>나는 잠에 든다 <br>One deepdream again <br>One deepdream again <br>한번만 만날 수 있다면 <br>정말 좋을텐데 <br>이곳에 나는 너무나도 <br>간절한데 제발 <br>우 깊은 잠에 들어야 <br>만날 수가 있나 <br>못잊을 그대를 그대를 찾아 <br>나는 잠에 든다 <br>One deepdream again <br>One deepdream again <br>그대는 날 떠나갔고 <br>나는 그대 흔적을 찾아 <br>그대는 다 사라졌고 <br>나는 그대 환상을 찾아 <br>이제는 깨어나서 <br>다시 안녕이라 말하려하네 <br>One deepdream again <br>One deepdream again <br>One deepdream again <br>One deepdream again <br>]]></content><category term="도시수족관" label="도시수족관"/><category term="Deep Dream" label="Deep Dream"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도시수족관/마음의_소리/</id><title>도시수족관 - 마음의 소리 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:05:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:05:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%EC%8B%9C%EC%88%98%EC%A1%B1%EA%B4%80/%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C%EC%9D%98_%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC/" title="도시수족관 - 마음의 소리 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마음에도 없는 소릴 계속 하고 <br>시계초침이 바쁜걸음 걷고있을때 <br>나의 심장박동은 자꾸 멈추려해 <br>색깔조차 없고 빈틈하나 <br>찾을 수 없는 <br>네 말들속에는 거짓들이 <br>좀 있었으면 해 <br>또 투정부리고 또 짜증내다 <br>그냥 그렇게 <br>또다시 다정히 내게 말을 <br>붙여줬으면 해 <br>시작과 끝을 알고싶어 한 건 아니야 <br>단지 넌 아픈게 두렵고 많이 무서워 <br>눈을 감고 조용히 주위소릴 <br>한번 들어봐 <br>네 말들속에는 거짓들이 <br>좀 있었으면 해 <br>또 투정부리고 또 짜증내다 <br>그냥 그렇게 <br>또 다시 다정히 내게 말을 <br>붙여줬으면 해 <br>시작과 끝을 알고싶어 한 건 아니야 <br>단지 넌 아픈게 두렵고 많이 무서워 <br>눈을 감고 조용히 주위소릴 <br>한번 들어 <br>또 다시 다정히 내게 말을 <br>붙여줬으면 해 <br>시작과 끝을 알고싶어 한 건 아니야 <br>단지 넌 아픈게 두렵고 많이 무서워 <br>눈을 감고 조용히 주위소릴 <br>한번 들어봐 <br>]]></content><category term="도시수족관" label="도시수족관"/><category term="마음의 소리" label="마음의 소리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도시수족관/기억/</id><title>도시수족관 - 기억 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:05:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:05:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%EC%8B%9C%EC%88%98%EC%A1%B1%EA%B4%80/%EA%B8%B0%EC%96%B5/" title="도시수족관 - 기억 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 기억 나지 않아 <br>그날 하늘이 참 눈부셨는지 <br>그땐 오직 너만을 <br>바라보고 있었으니까 <br>나는 너만을 오직 너만을 <br>바라보고만 있었으니까 <br>이순간 지금 당신이 <br>아주 슬펐으면 좋겠어 <br>문득 내 생각이 나서 <br>펑펑 울었으면 좋겠어 <br>인연에 매혹에 끝이 <br>기나긴 상처뿐이 남질 않음에도 <br>끝나지 않는 만남에 <br>황홀해 하는 것일까 <br>영원한 관계에 끝이 지속되길 <br>불가능한걸 알면서도 <br>너무 잘 알고 있지만 <br>계속해서 반복하고 있을까 <br>이순간 지금 당신이 <br>아주 슬펐으면 좋겠어 <br>문득 내 생각이 나서 <br>펑펑 울었으면 좋겠어 <br>인연에 매혹에 끝이 <br>기나긴 상처뿐이 남질 않음에도 <br>끝나지 않는 만남에 <br>황홀해 하는 것일까 <br>영원한 관계에 끝이 지속되길 <br>불가능한걸 알면서도 <br>너무 잘 알고 있지만 <br>계속해서 반복하고 있을까 <br>반복하고 있을까 <br>]]></content><category term="도시수족관" label="도시수족관"/><category term="기억" label="기억"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도시수족관/불면증/</id><title>도시수족관 - 불면증 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:05:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:05:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%EC%8B%9C%EC%88%98%EC%A1%B1%EA%B4%80/%EB%B6%88%EB%A9%B4%EC%A6%9D/" title="도시수족관 - 불면증 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[영원히 꿈꾸며 살 줄 알았지 <br>하지만 한풀 한풀 꽃들은 시들고 <br>먼지 쌓인 계단을 내려가다가 <br>어른이 된 나를 봤을 때 <br>첨으로 술을 먹고 담밸 펴봤지 <br>이걸로 나는 다 큰 어른인척 했지 <br>하지만 캄캄한 밤이 되면 <br>미래가 무서워 떨었지 <br>난 불안해 힘들어해 <br>너무 지금 또 난 다시 <br>후회를 하겠지 계속 하겠지 <br>또 반복되겠지 <br>세상이 너무해서 <br>이젠 결국 또 난 다시 <br>후회를 하겠지 계속 하겠지 <br>또 반복되겠지 <br>억지로 현실을 뒤쫓아 갔지 <br>하지만 한층 한층 꿈들을 접었고 <br>남길 수 없는 나의 기적들 <br>어른이 된 나를 봤을 때 <br>난 불안해 힘들어해 <br>너무 지금 또 난 다시 <br>후회를 하겠지 계속 하겠지 <br>또 반복되겠지 <br>세상이 너무해서 <br>이젠 결국 또 난 다시 <br>후회를 하겠지 계속 하겠지 <br>또 반복되겠지 <br>아직은 아직은 아직은 <br>아직은 아직은 아직은 <br>난 불안해 힘들어해 <br>너무 지금 또 난 다시 <br>후회를 하겠지 계속 하겠지 <br>또 반복되겠지 <br>세상이 너무해서 <br>이젠 결국 또 난 다시 <br>후회를 하겠지 계속 하겠지 <br>또 반복되겠지 <br>아직은 아직은 아직은 <br>아직은 아직은 아직은 <br>]]></content><category term="도시수족관" label="도시수족관"/><category term="불면증" label="불면증"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도시수족관/멀었어/</id><title>도시수족관 - 멀었어 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:05:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:05:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%EC%8B%9C%EC%88%98%EC%A1%B1%EA%B4%80/%EB%A9%80%EC%97%88%EC%96%B4/" title="도시수족관 - 멀었어 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자그마치 하루하루가 <br>이렇게나 지나가고 <br>오늘 내일에 모든 날이 <br>나와 당신의 날일 때엔 <br>아무 소리 들리지 않아도 <br>그래서 누군간 몰라도 <br>나와 그대만 아는 얘기 <br>지난 마음이 하는 얘기 <br>언제나 항상 <br>어느 곳에나 서로에게 <br>하고 있는 이야기가 있죠 <br>한참 멀었어 <br>그것은 아직 끝을 내기엔 <br>계속 되는 소리가 들려 <br>무슨 말이 더 필요하겠어 <br>나는 멀었어 <br>너의 모든 것을 느끼기엔 <br>알아가야 할 우리 관계에 <br>무슨 말이 더 필요하겠어 <br>언제나 항상 <br>어느 곳에나 서로에게 <br>하고 있는 이야기가 있죠 <br>한참 멀었어 <br>그것은 아직 끝을 내기엔 <br>계속 되는 소리가 들려 <br>무슨 말이 더 필요하겠어 <br>나는 멀었어 <br>너의 모든 것을 느끼기엔 <br>알아가야 할 우리 관계에 <br>무슨 말이 더 필요하겠어 <br>]]></content><category term="도시수족관" label="도시수족관"/><category term="멀었어" label="멀었어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도시수족관/너의_목소리/</id><title>도시수족관 - 너의 목소리 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:05:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:05:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%EC%8B%9C%EC%88%98%EC%A1%B1%EA%B4%80/%EB%84%88%EC%9D%98_%EB%AA%A9%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC/" title="도시수족관 - 너의 목소리 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘밤 널 꿈꾼 밤 <br>부스럭 소리에 잠이 그만 깨었다 <br>문턱에 기대고 엿들을 땐 <br>아무런 기척도 없었는데 <br>다시 누으면 들리는 너의 목소리 <br>오늘밤 널 찾은 밤 잠결에 <br>나도 모르게 널 불렀다 <br>꿈속을 느끼고 떠올릴 땐 <br>너무도 생생히 남아있는데 <br>눈뜨면 들을 수 없는 너의 목소리 <br>눈뜨면 들을 수 없는 너의 목소리 <br>다시 누으면 들리는 너의 목소리 <br>지척에 들린 너의 발소리 <br>바람에 스쳐간 <br>너의 그 소매 깃 소리들도 <br>눈감으면 다정하게 다가와 <br>눈뜨면 사라질 내 목소리 <br>머릿속 되뇌어 버려진 <br>너의 그 소리들도 <br>흔적도 없이 <br>바람 속으로 사라지네 <br>지척에 들린 너의 발소리 <br>바람에 스쳐간 <br>너의 그 소매 깃 소리들도 <br>눈감으면 다정하게 다가와 <br>눈뜨면 사라질 내 목소리 <br>머릿속 되뇌어 버려진 <br>너의 그 소리들도 <br>흔적도 없이 <br>바람 속으로 사라지네 <br>]]></content><category term="도시수족관" label="도시수족관"/><category term="너의 목소리" label="너의 목소리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/우재호/Fly_High/</id><title>우재호 - Fly High - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:05:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:05:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9A%B0%EC%9E%AC%ED%98%B8/Fly_High/" title="우재호 - Fly High - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리가 서있는 이 땅의 사람들과 <br>저 높은 하늘이 손에 닿으려 할 때 <br>두 팔을 벌려서 하늘과 손을 잡고 <br>이젠 모든 걱정은 던져버려 <br>지루한 일상을 떠나 <br>네가 원하는 그곳으로 <br>이젠 모든 걱정은 던져 버리고서 <br>모두 함께 세상을 즐겨 보는 거야 <br>나 만의 꿈들이 모두다 이뤄질 수 있어 <br>모든걸 잊고 우리들의 노랠 들어봐 <br>우리가 서있는 이 땅의 사람들과 <br>투명한 하늘이 손을 스치고 갈 때 <br>두 팔을 벌려서 하늘과 손을 잡고 <br>이젠 모든 걱정은 던져버려 <br>지루한 일상을 떠나 <br>네가 원하는 그곳으로 <br>이젠 모든 걱정은 던져 버리고서 <br>모두 함께 세상을 즐겨 보는 거야 <br>나 만의 꿈들이 모두다 이뤄질 수 있어 <br>모든걸 잊고 우리들의 노랠 들어봐 <br>이젠 모든 걱정은 던져 버리고서 <br>모두 함께 세상을 즐겨 보는 거야 <br>나 만의 꿈들이 모두다 이뤄질 수 있어 <br>모든걸 잊고 우리들의 노랠 들어봐 <br>이젠 모든 걱정은 던져 버리고서 <br>모두 함께 세상을 즐겨 보는 거야 <br>나 만의 꿈들이 모두다 이뤄질 수 있어 <br>모든걸 잊고 우리들의 노랠 들어봐 <br>이젠 모든 걱정은 던져 버리고서 <br>모두 함께 세상을 즐겨 보는 거야 <br>나 만의 꿈들이 모두다 이뤄질 수 있어 <br>우리들의 노랠 들어봐 <br>나만의 꿈들이 나만의 꿈들이 <br>Yeah Yeah <br>모두다 이뤄 질 수 있어 <br>]]></content><category term="우재호" label="우재호"/><category term="Fly High" label="Fly High"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/성우/지긋지긋/</id><title>성우 - 지긋지긋 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:05:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:05:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%B1%EC%9A%B0/%EC%A7%80%EA%B8%8B%EC%A7%80%EA%B8%8B/" title="성우 - 지긋지긋 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모든 게 시시해 <br>너 없는 클럽 같이 <br>어떻게 이게 하루 이틀 일이겠니 <br>실증이 났어 이제 모든 게 다 <br>이불을 개고 또 <br>빨래를 하는 일 까지도 <br>기분 탓은 아닌 듯해 <br>머리가 무거워 생각이 많아서 <br>이렇게 살 바엔 <br>차라리 뭐라도 하는 게 낫겠어 <br>뭐 어쩌겠어 난 또 혼자가 됐고 <br>가끔 걸려오는 전화는 참 <br>지긋지긋해 <br>머리가 지끈지끈해 <br>지긋지긋해 <br>지긋지긋해 <br>머리가 지끈지끈해 <br>지긋지긋해 <br>지긋지긋해 <br>텅 빈 내 방 안에 <br>퍼지는 체리향 같이 <br>건조한 내 맘에 <br>오늘은 비가 내렸지 <br>익숙해 질 때도 된 것 같은데 왜 <br>혼자인 이 밤은 <br>외롭고 어둡기만 한지 <br>이건 좀 아닌 듯해 <br>하루를 마무리할 때 <br>꼭 이를 닦아야 해 <br>모든 게 다 씻겨 나가게 <br>다시 누워 내일을 위해서 <br>잠을 자야만 해 <br>또 같은 꿈을 꾸겠지만 <br>지긋지긋해 <br>머리가 지끈지끈해 <br>지긋지긋해 <br>지긋지긋해 <br>머리가 지끈지끈해 <br>지긋지긋해 <br>지긋지긋해 <br>]]></content><category term="성우" label="성우"/><category term="지긋지긋" label="지긋지긋"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/성우/절레절레/</id><title>성우 - 절레절레 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:05:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:05:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%B1%EC%9A%B0/%EC%A0%88%EB%A0%88%EC%A0%88%EB%A0%88/" title="성우 - 절레절레 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[굳이 말 안 해도 <br>알 수 있잖아 <br>널 보는 내 눈빛이 <br>어떤 걸 원하는지 <br>내가 원래 성격이 <br>좀 급한 사람이라서 <br>남들이 다 했던 <br>뻔한 질문은 생략 할게 <br>하이웨스트 검은 청바지에 <br>배가 보이는 티가 잘 어울리네 <br>그건 너도 잘 아는 것 같애 <br>눈을 떼지 못하게 <br>눈을 떼지 못하게 <br>시간낭비 하지마 <br>우리 인생은 짧아 <br>이제 어쩔래 절레절레 <br>오늘은 집에 못 들어간다고 전해 <br>이제 어쩔래 절레절레 <br>딴 생각 하지마 난 너의 맘을 원해 <br>이제 어쩔래 절레절레 <br>이제 어쩔래 절레절레 <br>다 좋은 게 좋은 거잖아 <br>넌 다른 애들관 차원이 달라 <br>자꾸 숨기려 하지마 <br>그럴수록 더 알고 싶잖아 <br>네가 어디 사는지 <br>내일 뭐 하는지 <br>흐르는 땀 위로 <br>검은색 끈 이 목을 조이네 <br>풀어줄게 조금만 더 가까이 <br>내가 닿을 수 있게 <br>쉴 새 없이 내 맘에 불을 질러 <br>우린 멈추지 않고 <br>새벽을 헤엄쳐 <br>이제 어쩔래 절레절레 <br>오늘은 집에 못 들어간다고 전해 <br>이제 어쩔래 절레절레 <br>딴 생각 하지마 난 너의 맘을 원해 <br>이제 어쩔래 절레절레 <br>이제 어쩔래 절레절레 <br>]]></content><category term="성우" label="성우"/><category term="절레절레" label="절레절레"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/RAMZI/힐링/</id><title>RAMZI - 힐링 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:05:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:05:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/RAMZI/%ED%9E%90%EB%A7%81/" title="RAMZI - 힐링 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너무나도 햇살 좋은 날의 오후야 <br>난 조금 부지런히 일어나려 해 <br>우릴 기다리는 바람과 햇살이 <br>언제 다시 올지 몰라 <br>커다란 맘은 점점 더 흐릿해져서 <br>사라져 버린 나를 찾아가려 해 <br>난 미쳐 알지못했지만 <br>그저 바라보겠다고 했어 <br>아무런 말도 할 필요가 없이 <br>and 주는대로 맘이 이끄는대로 <br>느끼고 싶은대로 하나가 되는 듯한 <br>기분에 취하면 돼 <br>언제나 이것만 기억하면 돼 <br>아무런 말 필요가 없이 <br>기분에 취해 오로지 나만 생각해 <br>작아져만 가 이제 더는 볼 수 없어서 <br>바람결에 날아가 니 손을 잡아 <br>이제 기다리는 사람들 <br>너에게 다시 다가가는거야 <br>오늘같은 날에 취해 나 달려가는게 <br>너무 좋은 아침을 맞는게 <br>이제는 익숙해져 <br>나만의 나로 다시 태어나는걸 <br>나 기다리고 있을게 나 <br>기다리고 있을게 나 <br>기다리고 있을게 나 <br>아무런 말도 할 필요가 없이 <br>and 주는대로 맘이 이끄는대로 <br>느끼고 싶은대로 하나가 되는 듯한 <br>기분에 취하면 돼 <br>언제나 이것만 기억하면 돼 <br>아무런 말 필요가 없이 <br>기분에 취해 오로지 나만 생각해 <br>가려졌던 내 그리움에 <br>그래서 사라졌던 기억이 <br>아직 남아있어서 <br>다시 날 깨웠어 너와 함께야 <br>이 모든 것을 사랑해 <br>언제나 이것만 기억하면 돼 <br>아무런 말 필요가 없이 <br>기분에 취해 오로지 나만 생각해 <br>]]></content><category term="RAMZI" label="RAMZI"/><category term="힐링" label="힐링"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OTHANKQ_오땡큐/Awesome/</id><title>OTHANKQ (오땡큐) - Awesome - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:06:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:06:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OTHANKQ_%EC%98%A4%EB%95%A1%ED%81%90/Awesome/" title="OTHANKQ (오땡큐) - Awesome - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여행 떠나기 전 준비할 게 많아 <br>많은 걸 가진 사람 아니었잖아 난 <br>떠나기 전엔 뭐 이렇게 챙겨가 <br>왜 이래야 해 <br>그냥 떠나고 보는 거야 <br>Let's just go now <br>Let's just leave now <br>언제부터 준비했다고 그래 <br>Let's just go now <br>Let's just leave now <br>안 될게 뭐가 있겠어 <br>i feel like pretty awesome <br>바다와 산과 여유 <br>늦잠을 자고 <br>한껏 지저분해도 좋아 <br>i feel like pretty awesome <br>마음껏 술도 마셔 <br>먹고 싶은 걸 먹어 <br>i feel like pretty awesome <br>이미 설레고 있어 일상을 뒤로해 <br>내려놔 버려둬 쩌든 모든 것들을 <br>어디가 중요해 떠나는 게 좋을 뿐 <br>이 기분 그대로 <br>그곳을 향해 무조건 가 <br>Let's just go now <br>Let's just leave now <br>언제부터 준비했다고 그래 <br>Let's just go now <br>Let's just leave now <br>안 될게 뭐가 있겠어 <br>i feel like pretty awesome <br>바다와 산과 여유 <br>늦잠을 자고 <br>한껏 지저분해도 좋아 <br>i feel like pretty awesome <br>마음껏 술도 마셔 <br>먹고 싶은 걸 먹어 <br>i feel like pretty awesome <br>I wanna I hope so <br>I wanna I hope so <br>I wanna I hope so <br>Just go just leave now <br>I wanna I hope so <br>I wanna I hope so <br>I wanna I hope so <br>Just go just leave now <br>i feel like pretty awesome <br>바다와 산과 여유 <br>늦잠을 자고 <br>한껏 지저분해도 좋아 <br>i feel like pretty awesome <br>마음껏 술도 마셔 <br>먹고 싶은 걸 먹어 <br>i feel like pretty awesome <br>i feel like pretty awesome <br>바다와 산과 여유 <br>늦잠을 자고 <br>한껏 지저분해도 좋아 <br>i feel like pretty awesome <br>마음껏 술도 마셔 <br>먹고 싶은 걸 먹어 <br>i feel like pretty awesome <br>]]></content><category term="OTHANKQ (오땡큐)" label="OTHANKQ (오땡큐)"/><category term="Awesome" label="Awesome"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/류지인/어항_Feat_유인아/</id><title>류지인 - 어항 (Feat. 유인아) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:06:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:06:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%98%EC%A7%80%EC%9D%B8/%EC%96%B4%ED%95%AD_Feat_%EC%9C%A0%EC%9D%B8%EC%95%84/" title="류지인 - 어항 (Feat. 유인아) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 작은 어항에 <br>끝이 없는 길을 새긴 <br>멍청한 물고기 <br>그게 바로 나야 <br>이 작은 어항에 <br>물방울을 타고 맴도는 <br>멍청한 물고기 <br>그게 바로 나야 <br>눈을 감지 않은 채로 <br>빛이 스며드는 때를 기다린다 <br>헤엄쳐 널 그리다 <br>그만 유리 벽에 부딪힌 대도 <br>난 한참 너를 보다 <br>한 없이 나를 가두네 <br>헤엄쳐 널 그리다 <br>그만 유리 벽에 부딪힌 대도 <br>난 한참 너를 보다 <br>한 없이 나를 가두네 <br>이 작은 어항에 <br>끝이 없는 길을 새긴 <br>멍청한 물고기 <br>그게 바로 나야 <br>]]></content><category term="류지인" label="류지인"/><category term="어항 (Feat. 유인아)" label="어항 (Feat. 유인아)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rainbow99/PM_8_Narr_배우_윤광희/</id><title>Rainbow99 - PM 8 (Narr. 배우 윤광희) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:06:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:06:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rainbow99/PM_8_Narr_%EB%B0%B0%EC%9A%B0_%EC%9C%A4%EA%B4%91%ED%9D%AC/" title="Rainbow99 - PM 8 (Narr. 배우 윤광희) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사실 하나 칠 년간 연애를 했다 <br>문제 하나 그녀는 이제 떠났다 <br>사실 둘 사 년간 회사를 다녔다 <br>문제 둘 오늘 브리핑을 망쳤다 <br>사실 셋 운동을 시작했다 <br>문제 셋 생각이 멈추질 않는다 <br>사실 넷 저 여자는 내 여자가 아니다 <br>문제 넷 저 여자가 내 여자가 아니라고 <br>확신할 수가 없다 <br>사실 다섯 내일도 출근을 해야 한다 <br>문제 다섯 잠을 잘 수가 없다 <br>사실 여섯 불면증이다 불면증이 왔다 <br>문제 여섯 왔으면 떠나야 되는데 <br>떠나지를 않는다 <br>]]></content><category term="Rainbow99" label="Rainbow99"/><category term="PM 8 (Narr. 배우 윤광희)" label="PM 8 (Narr. 배우 윤광희)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rainbow99/PM_2_Narr_배우_윤광희/</id><title>Rainbow99 - PM 2 (Narr. 배우 윤광희) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:06:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:06:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rainbow99/PM_2_Narr_%EB%B0%B0%EC%9A%B0_%EC%9C%A4%EA%B4%91%ED%9D%AC/" title="Rainbow99 - PM 2 (Narr. 배우 윤광희) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아 눈부시다 <br>그냥 남들이 하니까 <br>아무 말도 하지 않았어 <br>그게 무슨 소리야 <br>여기 내 자리잖아 <br>니가 앉혀줬잖아 <br>민정아 민정아 민정아 <br>나아질 수 있습니다 <br>나아져야 하니까요 <br>언젠가 흔들려 무언가 <br>갑자기 폭탄 맞듯 <br>모른 체 하고 있었는데 <br>그럴 때 오는 거야 <br>안녕하십니까 <br>마치 도시의 밤이 바다처럼 <br>제품으로 넘쳐났습니다 <br>모델의 헤어스타일 <br>의상이 유행했고 <br>프랜차이즈 커피를 <br>들고 다니는 것처럼 <br>저희 제품을 들고 다녔습니다 <br>민정아 민정아 민정아 <br>언젠가 흔들려 무언가 <br>갑자기 폭탄 맞듯 <br>모른 체 하고 있었는데 <br>그럴 때 오는 거야 <br>언젠가 흔들려 무언가 <br>갑자기 폭탄 맞듯 <br>모른 체 하고 있었는데 <br>그럴 때 오는 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="Rainbow99" label="Rainbow99"/><category term="PM 2 (Narr. 배우 윤광희)" label="PM 2 (Narr. 배우 윤광희)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Breathe_Carolina/Glue/</id><title>Breathe Carolina - Glue - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:12:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:12:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Breathe_Carolina/Glue/" title="Breathe Carolina - Glue - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No matter what I do, do <br>No matter what I say ey yay yay e <br>I'm frozen here with you, you <br>Wish I could melt away ey yay yay e <br><br>Am livin' in the life I <br>Thought that I'll be holdin' on to you to like I do right now <br>Am livin' in the life I <br>Thought that I'll be holdin' on to you to like I do right now <br>You got me all in my mind spending all of my time searchin' 'bout you <br>We come back every time no matter how hard that we try <br>So together like glue <br>So together like glue <br>So together like glue <br>Glue glue <br>So together like glue, glue <br><br>Got nothing left to prove, prove <br>Got nothing in the way ey yay yay e <br>Like sunlight in the room, room <br>You take away the shay ey yay yay d <br><br>Am livin' in the life I <br>Thought that I'll be holdin' on to you to like I do right now <br>Am livin' in the life I <br>Thought that I'll be holdin' on to you to like I do right now <br>You got me all in my mind spending all of my time searchin' 'bout you <br>We come back every time no matter how hard that we try <br>So together like glue <br>So together like glue <br>So together like glue <br>Glue glue <br>So together like glue, glue <br><br>I just can't let go of you <br>I just can't let go of you <br>You got me all in my mind spending all of my time searchin' 'bout you <br>We come back every time no matter how hard that we try <br>So together like glue <br>So together like glue <br>So together like glue <br>Glue glue <br><br>So together like glue, glue <br>So together like glue <br>So together like glue <br>Glue glue <br>So together like glue, glue <br>I just can't let go of you]]></content><category term="Breathe Carolina" label="Breathe Carolina"/><category term="Glue" label="Glue"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ㄹ2dom_리덤/벚꽃과그대_Feat_신가은/</id><title>ㄹ2dom (리덤) - 벚꽃과그대 (Feat. 신가은) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:12:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:12:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%E3%84%B92dom_%EB%A6%AC%EB%8D%A4/%EB%B2%9A%EA%BD%83%EA%B3%BC%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80_Feat_%EC%8B%A0%EA%B0%80%EC%9D%80/" title="ㄹ2dom (리덤) - 벚꽃과그대 (Feat. 신가은) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하얀 백지 위에 잉크가 번지듯 <br>내 마음이란 백지에 <br>너라는 잉크가 <br>번져 던져 놨던 <br>사랑이라는 감정 <br>다시 피어 오르는 듯해 <br>이 말도 한번 했었지만 <br>믿을지는 모르지만 <br>널 처음 본 순간 되게 떨렸어 <br>설렘이란 감정을 가져다준 <br>넌 신이 주신 선물 <br>그때 난 이해했어 <br>기적이란 말뜻 <br>믿진 않았는데 <br>넌 내게 믿음을 줬어 <br>그래 넌 내게 믿음을 줬어 <br>두 번 다신 오지 않을 거라 믿었던 <br>이 설렘의 감정 <br>너와 손을 잡고 공원을 걸을 때 <br>공원을 걸을 때 <br>너의 손을 붙잡고 <br>벚꽃이 가득한 길을 <br>그냥 아무 말없이 걷고 싶어 <br>너의 손을 붙잡고 <br>벚꽃이 가득한 길을 <br>그냥 아무 말없이 걷고 싶어 <br>친구들에게 한번도 해본 적 없던 <br>널 여자친구라고 소개해주고 싶고 <br>그동안 찾아 헤맸던 <br>내 반쪽을 찾았다고 <br>소리 지르고 싶은 내 맘을 아는지 <br>넌 처음이었거든 <br>내 마음에 문을 열고 <br>영혼을 가져간 사람 <br>사랑 이 단어 <br>몸으로 느끼게 해준 사람 <br>그 사람 너라는 걸 <br>아침에 눈을 뜨는 순간부터 <br>잠이 드는 순간까지 <br>넌 무슨 생각하는지 <br>나처럼 보고 싶진 않은지 <br>혹시나 들이대면 <br>넌 떠나진 않을지 <br>널 소중하게 생각했어 <br>너무나 조심했어 <br>마치 때묻지 않은 <br>아이 같은 니 마음 <br>나 때문에 상처받진 않을지 <br>걱정돼 조금 <br>너의 손을 붙잡고 <br>벚꽃이 가득한 길을 <br>그냥 아무 말없이 걷고 싶어 <br>너의 손을 붙잡고 <br>벚꽃이 가득한 길을 <br>그냥 아무 말없이 걷고 싶어 <br>그렇게 너에 대한 마음이 <br>커져가면 커져갈수록 <br>난 네게 집착을 했나 봐 <br>영원히 내 옆에만 <br>있어주길 바랬나 봐 <br>몸도 약한 니가 <br>술자리를 가질 때면 <br>내 맘은 모래성이 <br>부서지듯 무너져 <br>이런 맘을 아는지 모르는지 <br>넌 자꾸 날 초조하게 만드네 <br>널 사랑하는 마음에 <br>네게 짜증도 내고 화도 냈어 <br>나도 이런 내가 너무 싫어 <br>뜸해지는 연락 <br>굽힐 줄 모르는 자존심 땜에 <br>우리가 멀어져 가는 게 <br>하루에도 니 연락을 기다리며 <br>애꿎은 핸드폰만 만지작거리며 <br>널 기다리는 모습이 <br>너를 사랑하는 나의 마음은 <br>꽃보다 그대가 술보다 그대가 <br>마치 이 노래 같아 <br>너를 사랑하는 나의 마음은 <br>꽃보다 그대가 술보다 그대가 <br>마치 이 노래 같아 <br>]]></content><category term="ㄹ2dom (리덤)" label="ㄹ2dom (리덤)"/><category term="벚꽃과그대 (Feat. 신가은)" label="벚꽃과그대 (Feat. 신가은)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피데이_PDAY/그렇게/</id><title>피데이 (PDAY) - 그렇게 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:12:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:12:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4_PDAY/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A0%87%EA%B2%8C/" title="피데이 (PDAY) - 그렇게 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[늘 같은 하루 위에 몸을 싣고 <br>모든 게 다 잘 되기를 비는 기도 <br>어쩌면 우린 지금껏 탈출의 시도 <br>없이 시간에 삶을 떠맡긴지도 <br>점점 익숙해져 가는 일상의 리듬 <br>하지만 뭔가 놓치는 기분 <br>잡힐 듯 아니 보이지도 않아 <br>사실은 아직 눈도 안 떴지 <br>지금 그 찰나를 떠도는 부유물 <br>그게 우리들의 또 다른 이름 no <br>이 순환을 깨버릴 꿈을 꾼 <br>내일의 주인은 너이기를 <br>그렇게 흘러가라고 <br>보낸 게 후회되더라고 <br>다시 돌아오길 원할 땐 화살이 돼 <br>내 가슴 깊은 곳에 처절하게 박히네 <br>오 왜 오 왜 대체 왜 왜 <br>오 왜 오 왜 대체 왜 왜 <br>늦었다고 생각할 땐 <br>이미 늦은 거더군 <br>내 안에 마지막에 <br>꼭 꺼내겠다고 걸어 둔 <br>약속은 보란 듯이 낡아 있었고 <br>돌릴 틈도 없이 날이 밝아 있었어 <br>그렇게 후회가 수놓은 밤을 지나 <br>상처는 후에 어떻게든 아물지만 <br>안고 살아갈 흉터가 <br>생겼다는 것을 알아 <br>이게 날 바꿀 수 있을지는 <br>확실하지 않아 <br>다만 배운 게 있다면 <br>순간의 소중함인 듯 <br>많은 시간 망설임 뒤에 가린 뜻 <br>꺼내지 못한 감정의 퇴색된 의미 <br>할머니를 보내드렸을 때 그랬듯이 <br>아직 남은 나의 사람과 또 나의 삶이 <br>지금마저도 지나가는 걸 아니까 <br>사랑 분노 감사 혹은 미안함 <br>이제 더 이상은 놓치고 싶지 않아 <br>그렇게 흘러가라고 <br>보낸 게 후회되더라고 <br>다시 돌아오길 원할 땐 화살이 돼 <br>내 가슴 깊은 곳에 처절하게 박히네 <br>오 왜 오 왜 대체 왜 왜 <br>오 왜 오 왜 대체 왜 왜 <br>그는 돌아오지 않아 돌아오지 않아 <br>알 수 있는 것은 하나 <br>우린 죽어있지 않아 <br>그는 돌아오지 않아 돌아오지 않아 <br>알 수 있는 것은 하나 <br>우린 죽어있지 않아 <br>그렇게 흘러가라고 <br>보낸 게 후회되더라고 <br>다시 돌아오길 원할 땐 화살이 돼 <br>내 가슴 깊은 곳에 처절하게 박히네 <br>오 왜 오 왜 대체 왜 왜 <br>오 왜 오 왜 대체 왜 왜 <br>]]></content><category term="피데이 (PDAY)" label="피데이 (PDAY)"/><category term="그렇게" label="그렇게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피데이_PDAY/얼굴/</id><title>피데이 (PDAY) - 얼굴 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:12:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:12:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4_PDAY/%EC%96%BC%EA%B5%B4/" title="피데이 (PDAY) - 얼굴 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[얼마나 많은 날이 지났는지 <br>또 얼마나 많은 다짐을 했는지 <br>기억 속의 날 난 <br>여전히 그때 처음과 같은 <br>마음이고만 싶은데 왜 이렇게 <br>너무 많은 것이 변해버렸어요 <br>나도 모르게 <br>어느새 이렇게 자라 각자의 <br>삶을 사는 아들딸을 바라보는 게 <br>어떤 기분인가요 엄마 아빠 <br>꼭 자랑스러운 아들이 될 거란 말 <br>지켜지는 건지 <br>아님 그저 버틸 뿐인지 <br>모르겠어요 난 또 당신들 앞에 <br>어떤 표정을 지을지 <br>안개가 핀 것 같아 <br>얼굴 위로 뿌옇게 더 하얗게 <br>난 숨어 내 두려움과 악몽 가지고 <br>이게 걷힌 후엔 웃고 있길 빌어 <br>정말 그랬으면 좋겠어 <br>괜찮은 척을 하고 웃음 지어 보여도 <br>실은 아냐 난 거꾸로 뒤집혀 있거든 <br>걱정 마 내 사람아 다만 널 위해서 <br>다시 환하게 웃는 것 정도는 거뜬 <br>그래도 가끔 이길 수 없는 기분 <br>계속 이렇게 라면 어떡하나 싶은 <br>철들지 않길 원해도 <br>훨씬 무거운 현실 <br>살아있다면 들게 되는 건가 봐 <br>어쩔 수 없이 <br>어쩔 수 없이 벌써 수없이 <br>되풀이된 걱정 <br>이 끝엔 남는 게 없어 <br>알기에 꾸역꾸역 잊고 <br>두 발을 옮겨 문 밖으로 향하지 또 <br>찬 공기를 머금은 사람들의 틈 <br>누구 하나 내게 <br>어떤 요구도 하지 않는 <br>그래서 난 또 지금 얼어붙나 봐 <br>그렇게 얼어붙어 난 무표정인가 봐 <br>안개가 핀 것 같아 <br>얼굴 위로 뿌옇게 더 하얗게 <br>난 숨어 내 두려움과 악몽 가지고 <br>이게 걷힌 후엔 웃고 있길 빌어 <br>정말 그랬으면 좋겠어 <br>]]></content><category term="피데이 (PDAY)" label="피데이 (PDAY)"/><category term="얼굴" label="얼굴"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피데이_PDAY/벽_With_SIXT/</id><title>피데이 (PDAY) - 벽 (With. SIXT) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:12:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:12:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4_PDAY/%EB%B2%BD_With_SIXT/" title="피데이 (PDAY) - 벽 (With. SIXT) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[벽이 있다고 믿었던 아이 <br>느끼는 건 벽 너머 그들과의 차이 <br>그 아이는 너무 어렸고 할 수 있었던 <br>거라곤 오직 그들로 꽉꽉 채운 벽화를 <br>그려대는 것 <br>매일같이 play 버튼을 눌러대는 것 <br>그들이 가진 모습을 훔쳐내는 것 <br>조차도 맘대로 안 돼 울어대는 것 <br>어쩜 그건 그에게 불가능한 미션 <br>공부나 해야지 그럼 중간은 가 있어 <br>어른들 말씀 잘 들어야 <br>훗날 잘 먹고 살어 <br>그게 전부가 아닐 거란 <br>생각이 자라났던 <br>그 때 처음 들었어 날 그리기 위한 붓 <br>벽을 채워 나가 자신의 얼굴로 가득 <br>소박했지만 큰 행복을 가져다 준 것 <br>왜 그걸 표현하는 말이 있잖아 꿈 <br>꿈을 적어봤지 <br>가진 생각들을 종이 위에 털어놨지 <br>마음 깊이 그 모든 기쁨 설움까지 <br>표현한 후 얼굴은 더 선명해져 갔지 <br>이젠 목소릴 내 봐 <br>비록 작다고 말해도 누구에겐 닿을 <br>하루하루 필요한 건 음악 몇 개와 <br>자신을 느낄 수 있는 약간의 무게감 <br>떠 있어 마치 날아갈 것 같이 <br>막혀있던 벽 너머가 보여 <br>떠 있어 지금 느끼는 이 기분 <br>난 보란 듯 벽을 넘어 보여 <br>더 나아질 거라 믿어 어렸던 생각이 더 <br>자란 듯한 어느 밤 아이는 제 자리로 <br>더 나아질 거라 믿어 어렸던 생각이 더 <br>자란 듯한 어느 밤 나는 내 갈 길로 <br>넘어 넘어 넘어 넘어 <br>넘어 가 넘어 가 <br>I'm a I'm a 90's kid <br>여전히 정신은 거기 멈춰있지 <br>난 늘 어설펐던 어린애 <br>평범하게 살길 강요 받았던 그 시절 <br>내가 원했던 꿈은 거기 담기엔 <br>너무 컸어 <br>모든 게 내 손 안에 그 책임은 <br>어깨 위에 <br>짊어지고서 갈게 따가운 <br>시선도 동시에 <br>솔직해지기로 했어 <br>날 꿈꾸게 했던 그들처럼 <br>뱉은 말을 다 현실로 바꾸려 했어 <br>어느덧 같은 꿈을 꿨던 애들과 <br>나는 여기로 <br>우리가 함께 그리려 했던 <br>그림은 아직도 going on <br>그 시절과는 다른 곳이 <br>이젠 날 반겨주지 <br>성공한 이들이 모여있다 <br>믿고 있던 도시 <br>위에 난 서있어 아니 달려 <br>dream chaser <br>그 이유는 아마도 어렸을 적 <br>나를 위해서 <br>지금 날 가로막은 모든 걸 다 <br>전부 넘어서 <br>결국엔 네가 옳았다고 <br>말해주기 위해서 I'll chase <br>넘어 넘어 넘어 넘어 <br>넘어 가 넘어 가 <br>]]></content><category term="피데이 (PDAY)" label="피데이 (PDAY)"/><category term="벽 (With. SIXT)" label="벽 (With. SIXT)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피데이_PDAY/믿어/</id><title>피데이 (PDAY) - 믿어 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:12:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:12:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4_PDAY/%EB%AF%BF%EC%96%B4/" title="피데이 (PDAY) - 믿어 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잘하고 있단 말을 들으면 <br>잠깐 나를 내려놓게 돼 <br>아직까지 혼자서는 제대로 된 <br>걸음마조차도 못 뗀 채 <br>왜 자꾸 뛰어갈 생각을 해 <br>마음만 앞서고 있다는 걸 <br>알고 있지만 <br>그래도 나를 자극하는 건 <br>그 이상의 것들 그 이상의 것들 <br>나는 원해 더 나은 나와 <br>더 많은 것들을 가졌으면 해 <br>한계란 말을 지우고 I'm runnin' <br>부족한 날 인정하기까지의 <br>시간 안 아까워지게 <br>나는 발을 굴러야만 해 <br>그래야만 해 <br>오 나의 어제여 숨지마 <br>우린 멈추지 않았잖아 <br>오 나의 어젠 어둡지 않아 <br>여전히 여기 있잖아 <br>그만 생각해 now is the time <br>그럼 가 just go <br>머리가 가득 찼어 제발 <br>이제는 죽은 생각은 turn off <br>How I live how I live how I live <br>그저 믿어 날 믿어 날 난 살아있지 <br>때론 맞지 않는 옷을 입기도 했어 <br>타인의 시선과 의견에 동해서 <br>악취가 나는 듯했어 내 몸에서 <br>그럴 때마다 새 가사들로 <br>날 씻어내도 <br>확실해지는 건 지워지지 <br>않는다는 사실 <br>부정할수록 더럽혀지는 게 많지 <br>수없이 적혀왔던 <br>나의 단어들엔 아직 <br>포기란 말이 절대 들어있지 않지 <br>새삼 깨닫고 난 뒤에 터지는 탄식 <br>오 중요한 건 그 시간의 탓이 <br>아닌 마음가짐임을 다시 확인하지 <br>이젠 다 끌어안아 지난 과오까지 <br>그만 생각해 now is the time <br>그럼 가 just go <br>머리가 가득 찼어 제발 <br>이제는 죽은 생각은 turn off <br>How I live how I live how I live <br>그저 믿어 날 믿어 날 난 살아있지 <br>다른 소린 들리지 않게 <br>볼륨을 더 올려 yeah yeah <br>볼륨을 더 올려 yeah yeah <br>Keep my mind free yeah <br>다른 소린 들리지 않게 <br>볼륨을 더 올려 yeah yeah <br>볼륨을 더 올려 yeah yeah <br>Keep my mind free yeah <br>그만 생각해 now is the time <br>그럼 가 just go <br>머리가 가득 찼어 제발 <br>이제는 죽은 생각은 turn off <br>How I live how I live how I live <br>그저 믿어 날 믿어 날 난 살아있지 <br>]]></content><category term="피데이 (PDAY)" label="피데이 (PDAY)"/><category term="믿어" label="믿어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피데이_PDAY/Somewhere/</id><title>피데이 (PDAY) - Somewhere - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:12:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:12:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4_PDAY/Somewhere/" title="피데이 (PDAY) - Somewhere - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[정글 같은 세상 속의 너와 나 <br>나는 아직 너무 어려서 겁이 많아 <br>가끔 이대로 모든 게 멈출 것 같아 <br>넌 더 세게 날 안아줘 <br>지금 너의 온기도 <br>언젠가는 식겠지만 <br>난 여전히 준비도 <br>덜된 어린애 같아 <br>그게 조금 분해 분해 <br>어쩔 수 없는 이 기분에 너에게 <br>또 투정해버려 바보처럼 <br>너 아니면 난 갈 곳 없어 <br>가만히 내 곁에 있어 <br>잠깐 기다려 달란 말도 <br>내겐 너무 길어 <br>그냥 내게는 너 말곤 <br>어느 것도 싫어 <br>난 원해 원해 원해 원해 <br>애원해 원해 원해 <br>Somewhere somewhere <br>Somewhere somewhere <br>어차피 우리는 죽어가니까 <br>그렇게 먼저 떠나는 게 아닐까 <br>결국 끊어져버릴 관계 가치와 <br>내 바람 사이에 <br>난 이토록 시달릴까 <br>꺼져버려 다 그런 거라면 <br>꺼져버려 다 그런 거라면 <br>난 어디쯤 어디쯤 <br>어디쯤인지 모르겠어 <br>이러다가 정말로 <br>난 너의 목을 조르겠어 <br>그걸 원하지 않는데 난 <br>아니 그걸 원하고 있나 난 <br>널 아프게 하고 싶지 않아 <br>널 아프게 하고 싶지 않아 <br>널 아프게 하고 싶지 않아 <br>널 아프게 하고 싶지 <br>외로운 지금을 <br>지나고 있어 너와 함께 <br>자꾸만 우울해 <br>또 울어서 내 코가 빨개 <br>끝을 향해서 가는 것 같아 <br>미칠 것 같아 <br>난 미칠 것 같은데 <br>넌 날 보며 웃어 밝게 <br>있을까 너와 나 <br>함께 추구할 행복 <br>그게 우리 둘 중 하날 <br>철저히 파괴한대도 <br>우린 닿을 수가 있을까 <br>정말 그런 곳이 있을까 <br>Somewhere somewhere <br>Somewhere somewhere <br>Somewhere somewhere <br>Somewhere <br>]]></content><category term="피데이 (PDAY)" label="피데이 (PDAY)"/><category term="Somewhere" label="Somewhere"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피데이_PDAY/Underwater/</id><title>피데이 (PDAY) - Underwater - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:12:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:12:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4_PDAY/Underwater/" title="피데이 (PDAY) - Underwater - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 깊은 물 속에 녹아있어 <br>깊은 물 속에 너와 있어 <br>우린 헤엄을 쳐 발을 디뎌 <br>내 모든 걸 너와 <br>함께 할 수 있다 믿어 <br>이 땅에서 우리 함께 <br>설 수 있는 곳에 <br>닿을 때까지 그때까지 <br>Somewhere somewhere <br>Somewhere hmmumm <br>]]></content><category term="피데이 (PDAY)" label="피데이 (PDAY)"/><category term="Underwater" label="Underwater"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김용임/묻지마세요/</id><title>김용임 - 묻지마세요 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:14:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:14:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9A%A9%EC%9E%84/%EB%AC%BB%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94/" title="김용임 - 묻지마세요 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[묻지마세요 물어보지마세요 내 나이 묻지마세요 <br>흘러간 내청춘 잘한것도 없는데 요놈의 숫자가 따라오네요 <br>여기까지 왔는데 앞만보고 왔는데 지나간 세월의 서러운 눈물 <br>사산너머 가는 청춘 너 가는 줄 몰랐구나 세월아 가지를 말아라]]></content><category term="김용임" label="김용임"/><category term="묻지마세요" label="묻지마세요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서은미/너를_지우개/</id><title>서은미 - 너를 지우개 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:15:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:15:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EC%9D%80%EB%AF%B8/%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC_%EC%A7%80%EC%9A%B0%EA%B0%9C/" title="서은미 - 너를 지우개 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑한다 말에 속아 <br>내 청춘 다 바쳤는데 <br>그댄 왜 그렇게 변해버렸나요 <br>서러워 눈물만 나네 <br>그때의 당신 내게 말했죠 <br>영원할 거라고 <br>언제나 널 웃게만 하겠다고 <br>약속했었죠 <br>이제는 당신 내게 말하죠 <br>차가운 눈빛으로 <br>마르지 않는 서러운 눈물 <br>그대가 너무 미워요 <br>이제는 미련 두지 않아 <br>변한 그 사랑 따윈 <br>어젯밤 흘려 보낸 빗물처럼 <br>그대를 떠나가겠어 <br>사랑한다 말에 속아 <br>내 청춘 다 바쳤는데 <br>그댄 왜 그렇게 변해버렸나요 <br>서러워 눈물만 나네 <br>이제는 당당하게 널 버리고 <br>내 인생 찾아갈 거야 <br>변해버린 그 사랑 따윈 <br>깨끗이 지워내겠어 <br>이제는 미련 두지 않아 <br>변한 그 사랑 따윈 <br>어젯밤 흘려 보낸 빗물처럼 <br>그대를 떠나가겠어 <br>사랑한다 말에 속아 <br>내 청춘 다 바쳤는데 <br>그댄 왜 그렇게 변해버렸나요 <br>서러워 눈물만 나네 <br>이제는 당당하게 널 버리고 <br>내 인생 찾아갈 거야 <br>변해버린 그 사랑 따윈 <br>깨끗이 지워내겠어 <br>]]></content><category term="서은미" label="서은미"/><category term="너를 지우개" label="너를 지우개"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/가야금영재/바람아_전해주오/</id><title>가야금영재 - 바람아 전해주오 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:16:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:16:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%80%EC%95%BC%EA%B8%88%EC%98%81%EC%9E%AC/%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C%EC%95%84_%EC%A0%84%ED%95%B4%EC%A3%BC%EC%98%A4/" title="가야금영재 - 바람아 전해주오 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 님 따라서 갈까보다 <br>정든 님 따라서 갈까보다 <br>구름도 쉬어가는 저 고개 넘어서면 <br>그리운 그대 볼 수 있을까 <br>나는 아니 쉬어 넘으련만 <br>산 고개 넘다가 <br>잠시 쉬어가던 바람아 <br>어찌하여 못오는고 <br>이다지도 못보는고 <br>내 바람도 전해주오 <br>갈까보다 갈까보다 <br>내 님 따라서 갈까보다 <br>구름도 쉬어 넘는 저 고개 <br>넘어로 갈까보다 <br>내 님 따라서 갈까보다 <br>정든 님 따라서 갈까보다 <br>머나먼 천리라도 저 넘어 만리라도 <br>그리운 그대 볼 수 있다면 <br>나는 삼월동풍 제비되어 님 계신 <br>처마 끝 찾아 집을 짓고 노닐까 <br>무정하여 아주 잊고 <br>영영 이별 되려는가 <br>내 바람을 전해주오 <br>갈까보다 갈까보다 <br>내 님 따라서 갈까보다 <br>갈까보다 갈까보다 <br>내 님 따라서 갈까보다 <br>]]></content><category term="가야금영재" label="가야금영재"/><category term="바람아 전해주오" label="바람아 전해주오"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Angelika_Dusk/Catfight/</id><title>Angelika Dusk - Catfight - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:16:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:16:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Angelika_Dusk/Catfight/" title="Angelika Dusk - Catfight - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Silhouette in the doorway <br>Smell the smoke in the air <br>You walk the room like a runway <br>High heels and long brown hair <br><br>Don't you know that I've started over <br>Since there was a me and you <br>What makes you think you can come around here <br>Saying shit that isn't true <br><br>Cat fight, scratch, bite, wanna take it outside <br>Gonna make you wish you never messed with me at all <br><br>Get out the way I'm the queen of this city <br>Shut up your mouth take your eyes off my crown <br>Get out my face you ain't even that pretty <br>you better run 'cause I'm taking you down <br><br>Get out, out, out, out <br>Get out, out, out, out <br><br>Used to be intoxicating <br>Now you're just cheap perfume <br>It's only your time you're wasting <br>The way you working the room <br><br>Cat fight, scratch, bite, wanna take it outside <br>Gonna make you wish you never messed with me at all <br><br>This town ain't big enough now <br>For the both of us, for the both of us]]></content><category term="Angelika Dusk" label="Angelika Dusk"/><category term="Catfight" label="Catfight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Noah_Bartfield/Lie_To_Me/</id><title>Noah Bartfield - Lie To Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:16:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:16:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Noah_Bartfield/Lie_To_Me/" title="Noah Bartfield - Lie To Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lonely sleep is something I’ll endure <br>Restless hands are under sheets and praying <br>Come back home, come home <br>You’ll be here soon <br>So goodnight, goodnight <br>When you come back home <br>You’ll lie to me, you’ll lie to me <br>Come back home <br>and Lie, Lie to me <br>Lonely days spent open eyed and dreaming of <br>Memories, the memories are why I still <br>Want you home, come home <br>You’ll be here soon <br>I’ll dream on, dream on <br>When you come back home <br>You’ll lie to me, you’ll lie to me <br>Come back home <br>and Lie, Lie to me <br>Days you’re gone <br>You find other love to share <br>and I’m aware <br>When you come back home <br>You’ll lie to me, you’ll to me <br>When you come back home <br>You’ll be here but insincere <br>And days you’re gone, I’ll be alone with no love to share <br>So come back home <br>And Lie, Lie to me <br>Just Lie, Lie to me]]></content><category term="Noah Bartfield" label="Noah Bartfield"/><category term="Lie To Me" label="Lie To Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Noah_Bartfield/Walls/</id><title>Noah Bartfield - Walls - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:16:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:16:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Noah_Bartfield/Walls/" title="Noah Bartfield - Walls - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You just watch while she’s hurt by a lover <br>Try to break, break her walls down <br>You can’t help cause she’s bound to another <br>Try to break, break her walls down <br>Tell her all 'bout the ways you can love her <br>Help her break, break her walls down <br>And let her feel love like she’s meant to <br>Help her break, break her walls down <br>When you think that you’ve done enough <br>She her more let her know she’s everything <br>Tell her all the times she made you fall <br>She made you fall <br>Now it’s you who gets to hold her heart <br>Keep her safe, keep her safe and sound <br>When it’s hard, when it starts to fall apart <br>Don’t forget how her walls came down]]></content><category term="Noah Bartfield" label="Noah Bartfield"/><category term="Walls" label="Walls"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Noah_Bartfield/Real_Love/</id><title>Noah Bartfield - Real Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:16:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:16:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Noah_Bartfield/Real_Love/" title="Noah Bartfield - Real Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You tell me when I’m not myself <br>You’re there to catch me when I fall <br>We go up, come down <br>Lose ourselves to be found <br>More than a daydream <br>More than a red bouquet <br>Open and weightless <br>Past our thrill of the chase <br>Real Love isn’t just skin in the dark <br>Real Love isn’t just a skip of the heart <br>It’s a deeper thing <br>It’s deeper <br>Maybe time will tell it all <br>But love can’t run until crawls <br>We fall short, reach out <br>Bring our feet to the ground <br>Sometime’s I hurt you <br>Sometime’s I pull away <br>Fragile but callused <br>You’ll forgive my mistakes <br>Real Love isn’t just skin in the dark <br>Real Love isn’t just a skip of the heart <br>It’s a deeper thing <br>It’s deeper <br>If the fruit of this old tree <br>Grows bittersweet <br>With too many seasons <br>Not enough reasons left to stay <br>I wish you well, I wish you well <br>While my tired heart swells <br>Real Love isn’t just skin in the dark <br>Real Love isn’t just a skip of the heart <br>It’s a deeper thing <br>It’s deeper]]></content><category term="Noah Bartfield" label="Noah Bartfield"/><category term="Real Love" label="Real Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Noah_Bartfield/Ill_Still_Be_Here_Tomorrow/</id><title>Noah Bartfield - I`ll Still Be Here Tomorrow - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:16:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:16:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Noah_Bartfield/Ill_Still_Be_Here_Tomorrow/" title="Noah Bartfield - I`ll Still Be Here Tomorrow - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We wake up with the sun <br>Pouring on our feet <br>You lie still, I don’t breath <br>Pretend we’re still asleep <br>Drifting peacefully <br>While you kiss my cheek <br>You’re sighing in relief <br>Even though I tell you every day <br>I’ll still be here tomorrow <br>You’ll wake up in my arms <br>Nothing’s gonna change, I’ll love you the same <br>I’ll still be here tomorrow <br>Morning’s gone, we go out <br>Never have a plan <br>We just walk and you glow <br>Wearing my right hand <br>It’s so effortless <br>Growing happiness <br>All I want is more <br>Hoping that you want me to say <br>I’ll still be here tomorrow <br>You’ll wake up in my arms <br>Nothing’s gonna change, I’ll love you the same <br>I’ll still be here tomorrow <br>The sun goes down <br>We count the stars as they come out <br>Just close your eyes <br>Everything’s alright, babe <br>I’ll still be here tomorrow <br>You’ll wake up in my arms <br>Nothing’s gonna change, I’ll love you the same <br>I’ll still be here tomorrow <br>I’ll still be here tomorrow]]></content><category term="Noah Bartfield" label="Noah Bartfield"/><category term="I`ll Still Be Here Tomorrow" label="I`ll Still Be Here Tomorrow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Noah_Bartfield/Let_It_Be_Love/</id><title>Noah Bartfield - Let It Be Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:16:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:16:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Noah_Bartfield/Let_It_Be_Love/" title="Noah Bartfield - Let It Be Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday you asked me, “Is it worth it?” <br>I told you it was, I told you it was <br>You thought that I would leave you any moment <br>I told you, “That’s not what love does, That’s not what love does” <br>You’ve gotta let it rise, let it fall <br>Let it grow on it’s own for a while <br>Let it do what it please, let it rest when it needs <br>Let it be love, Let it be love, Let it be, love <br>You thought that i would pass by like the others <br>You were wrong, You were wrong <br>I know that you've been hurt bad and I’m sorry <br>But that’s not what love does, that’s not what love does <br>If you let it rise, let it fall <br>Let it grow on it’s own for a while <br>Let it do what it please, let it rest when it needs <br>Let it be love, Let it be love, Let it be, love <br>I know it’s hard <br>To let your guard down <br>But trust me <br>Let it rise, let it fall <br>Let it grow on it’s own for a while <br>Let it do what it please, let it rest when it needs <br>Let it be love, Let it be love, Let it be, love <br>Let it be love, Let it be love, Let it be, love <br>Let it be love, Let it be love, Let it be, love]]></content><category term="Noah Bartfield" label="Noah Bartfield"/><category term="Let It Be Love" label="Let It Be Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meeka_Kates/Empire_Feat_Allen_Ginsberg/</id><title>Meeka Kates - Empire (Feat. Allen Ginsberg) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:16:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:16:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meeka_Kates/Empire_Feat_Allen_Ginsberg/" title="Meeka Kates - Empire (Feat. Allen Ginsberg) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've seen the best minds <br>of my generation <br>Packaged shipped and sold <br>Numbers change color <br>As the young become old <br>And I can see why <br>but I don't know how <br>Thousands can bury <br>Their brains in the ground <br>I've seen the best minds <br>of my generation <br>Packaged shipped and sold <br>Numbers change color <br>As the young become old <br>And I can see why <br>but I don't know how <br>Thousands can bury <br>Their brains in the ground <br>I've seen the best minds <br>of my generation <br>Packaged shipped and sold <br>Numbers change color <br>As the young become old <br>And I can see why <br>but I don't know how <br>Thousands can bury <br>Their brains in the ground <br>]]></content><category term="Meeka Kates" label="Meeka Kates"/><category term="Empire (Feat. Allen Ginsberg)" label="Empire (Feat. Allen Ginsberg)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Orisa_Stand_Your_Ground/</id><title>Dan Bull - Orisa, Stand Your Ground - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:17:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:17:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Orisa_Stand_Your_Ground/" title="Dan Bull - Orisa, Stand Your Ground - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Orisa oh <br>Orisa go <br><br>Orisa oh <br>Stand your ground <br>Now Orisa go <br>Pull their defences down <br>Orisa oh <br>Watch over the team <br>Now Orisa hold <br>Us together in victory <br><br>Listen to me, Sir <br>There's a new individual feature <br>On the scene that's pleased to meet you <br>Greet Orisa <br>She treats you like a piece of meat <br>On greasy pizza <br>I don't mean she feeds you <br>She eats you <br>And leaves the left over pieces in the freezer <br>You're frozen in the spot <br>Call it immediate anaesthesia <br>Controlling gravity to make you halt, stay <br>Throwing ammo in your face <br>As casually as salt bae <br>A babe aged but a month <br>That does it the old way <br>She holds you in place before you're fucked <br>Call it foreplay <br>Practicing safe sex <br>She brought a protective barrier <br>Being beat isw a disease <br>And you're the carrier <br>She's a tank that <br>Leaves you anchored <br>You wanker <br>You'll need to flank her <br>For any chance to outrank her <br>How long will it need for you finally to learn <br>Leaving you burned is her primary concern <br><br>Orisa oh <br>Stand your ground <br>Now Orisa go <br>Pull their defences down <br>Orisa oh <br>Watch over the team <br>Now Orisa hold <br>Us together in victory <br><br>With the gun on her waist <br>She'll blow your blooming face off <br>Then drop her drum in your base <br>Call it a drum and bass drop <br>M8 wot <br>She's got this game locked <br>It's too late to stop <br>Rage quit and blame a frame rate drop <br>You ought to be sure not to ignore the order to halt <br>Or she'll pull you forward <br>With the force of a horns of a bull <br>A portable fortress of awesomeness <br>Brought in to cause an unfortunate fall <br>With the force of a fork lift truck <br>That's falling off a waterfall <br>And crushing all your balls to mush <br>So if you know what's good for you <br>Then you ought to shush <br>She'll take on stampedes <br>The size of a pre order rush <br>She'll impede and then stamp on each and all of us <br>Nothing breaches through when losers shoot her armour <br>Because it's as amusingly futuristic as Futurama <br>Fortify <br>Halt <br>Fusion driver <br>Supercharger <br>She looks rather like a bull <br>I wonder who's the father <br><br>Orisa oh <br>Stand your ground <br>Now Orisa go <br>Pull their defences down <br>Orisa oh <br>Watch over the team <br>Now Orisa hold <br>Us together in victory]]></content><category term="Dan Bull" label="Dan Bull"/><category term="Orisa, Stand Your Ground" label="Orisa, Stand Your Ground"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Dawn_Zero_Horizon_Zero_Dawn_Horizon_Dawn_Zero_Horizon_Dawn_Horizon_Zero/</id><title>Dan Bull - Dawn Zero Horizon Zero Dawn Horizon Dawn Zero Horizon Dawn Horizon Zero - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:17:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:17:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Dawn_Zero_Horizon_Zero_Dawn_Horizon_Dawn_Zero_Horizon_Dawn_Horizon_Zero/" title="Dan Bull - Dawn Zero Horizon Zero Dawn Horizon Dawn Zero Horizon Dawn Horizon Zero - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A <br>Ruined world <br>Hey <br>What you doing girl <br>Looking for answers <br>You look a bit anxious <br><br>You're far from shelter <br>It's harmful out there <br>Fighting violence and terror <br>Is trial and error <br>Grab a vine or a fibre <br>A wire and tie them together <br>So you're flying <br>As light as a feather <br>Climbing whatever <br>Climate or weather <br>'Til you're finding the treasure <br>Head straight to Meridian <br>What a place to create a city in <br>Chasing Elysium <br>Like an idiot taking the lithium <br>Aim for oblivion <br>I may be rephrasing an idiom <br>Saying the same thing again <br>Just to make it fit in <br>But i'm taking you primitive places <br>You may never visit <br>And making it <br>SSSIIZZLING <br><br>Every minute there's a hero born <br>At the beginning of the Zero Dawn <br>Got a premonition and I fear those swarms <br>Will be here with no warning <br>Hear those horns <br>Don't pour scorn <br>On those that forewarn <br>Of snowstorms <br>Or you could go home forlorn <br>Every minute there's a hero born <br>At the beginning of the Zero Dawn <br><br>Trudging through the over growth <br>The hunt's a drug i do <br>I'm floating close to overdose <br>My toes, my bones, my chromosomes <br>The moment's over, focus <br>Slowly sober, roaming over zones <br>Showing signs of tribes of old <br>Like roman roads are <br>Eroded <br>A ronin rode a rodeo <br>Rewrote the rule, we rowed a rowboat <br>Over rows of rapid river flows <br>Until it froze <br>The tiller throws us <br>And it goes off <br>'Til our goal just isn't close <br>This isn't supposed to be <br>The way the wind it blows <br>But when it blows, It leaves a breeze <br>That tends to throw the leaves of trees <br>To the extent we only see <br>In fevered dreams <br>See, believe <br>These machines <br>Steel beasts <br>When we beat them we'll feast <br>On meals of real meat again <br>We'll meet again <br>When he's deceased <br><br>Every minute there's a hero born <br>At the beginning of the Zero Dawn <br>Got a premonition and i fear those swarms <br>Will be here with no warning <br>Hear those horns <br>Don't pour scorn <br>On those that forewarn <br>Of snowstorms <br>Or you could go home forlorn <br>Every minute there's a hero born <br>At the beginning of the Zero Dawn <br><br>I've <br>Got something to say <br>Don't take it in a sensitive way <br>There's no sense in taking offense <br>I'm saving a friend when i say <br>Pray <br>What kind of brave hunter is chased <br>Running away <br>To the hub of the cave <br>Thinking you're going to be safe <br>Nah <br>They're coming to take <br>Everything you're loving away <br>Whether humble or great <br>Man, it'll crumble and fade <br>Succumbing unto the grave <br>So come on under whether you're <br>Pulling a gun or a blade <br>Going to make the blood in my veins <br>Run at a pace that's unsafe <br>In an untamed rugged domain <br>What could it mean <br>I'm wondering who my mother could be <br>Was she <br>The same kind of woman as me <br>There's some kind of beast <br>Drumming a beat <br>I'm a machine <br>Like those steel beasts <br>When we beat them we'll feast <br>On meals of real meat again <br>We'll meet again when he's deceased <br>When he's been blessed with death <br>When east is east <br>And west is west <br>North is north <br>And south is south <br>I'm going in <br>Out and out <br><br>Every minute there's a hero born <br>At the beginning of the Zero Dawn <br>Got a premonition and i fear those swarms <br>Will be here with no warning <br>Hear those horns <br>Don't pour scorn <br>On those that forewarn <br>Of snowstorms <br>Or you could go home forlorn <br>Every minute there's a hero born <br>At the beginning of the Zero Dawn]]></content><category term="Dan Bull" label="Dan Bull"/><category term="Dawn Zero Horizon Zero Dawn Horizon Dawn Zero Horizon Dawn Horizon Zero" label="Dawn Zero Horizon Zero Dawn Horizon Dawn Zero Horizon Dawn Horizon Zero"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Home_Is_Where_The_Hate_Is/</id><title>Dan Bull - Home Is Where The Hate Is - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:17:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:17:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Home_Is_Where_The_Hate_Is/" title="Dan Bull - Home Is Where The Hate Is - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ah, greetings, you're right on time <br>Wipe your feet, you're invited inside <br>Your arrival is quite a surprise <br>You're ripe for the ride of your life <br>Right <br>Let me take your coat, you're welcome <br>Have a browse through the photo album <br>It's only seldom we host any guests <br>The rest of the family are home, I'll tell them <br>Come and join us for vittles <br>It'll satiate those cravings a little <br>Put some meat on those brittle bones <br>We insist, you must have a nibble <br>It's something we hunted, one for the road <br>Here's a clue it's right under your nose <br>If you refuse, you'll be stunting the growth <br>Of your welcome to our humble abode <br>Those lonely country roads are so remote that no one'll know <br>You're overdue home, there's no bloody phone <br>Now go to your room or I'll go for your throat <br>When you're under my roof, you'll heed my rules <br>Succumb to my truth, do I need my tools <br>Should I fetch my pliers Should I come for your tooth <br>It's your fault, I don't want to remove it <br><br>Home <br>Home is where the hate is <br>Home <br>Your relatives are waiting <br>Home <br>Everyone's related <br>Home <br>They who immigrate or natives <br>Home <br>Look what we've created <br>Satanist, sadist <br>Home is where the hate is <br><br>Butcher, baker, candlestick maker <br>You can't get away from your animal nature <br>Try as you might and the anger will take you <br>Now sample the cake that grandmother's made you <br>That's a family favorite, passed through generations of Bakers inhabiting the plantation <br>Eraserhead X Fantasia <br>It's fun and games, son, let Dad chase you <br>Here I come, ready or not <br>I hear a gun, bloody belly all shot <br>Don't you try to pee on my fun <br>We've barely begun and there's many more shocks in store for you <br>But you know that already <br>Of course you do, keep both hands steady <br>Adrenaline, what a hell of a drug <br>I'm getting a buzz from killing and peeling the skin of a corpse <br>I'm yearning for more <br>It isn't enough 'cause I've seen it before <br>I've been in a war within in my thoughts <br>The insects are wriggling from under the floor <br>You're injured, your innards are spilling <br>There's chunder and gore and blood on the walls <br>It's pungent and raw <br>That's the warm welcome I give out for someone who comes through my door <br>And into my <br><br>Home <br>Home is where the hate is <br>Home <br>Your relatives are waiting <br>Home <br>Everyone's related <br>Home <br>They who immigrate or natives <br>Home <br>Look what we've created <br>Satanist, sadist <br>Home is where the hate is]]></content><category term="Dan Bull" label="Dan Bull"/><category term="Home Is Where The Hate Is" label="Home Is Where The Hate Is"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Oh_No_Mario/</id><title>Dan Bull - Oh No Mario! - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:17:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:17:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Oh_No_Mario/" title="Dan Bull - Oh No Mario! - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well <br>Why are video games so bloody violent <br>Mindless <br>Man, it's time to rewind <br>To a time where the action was colorful and innocent <br>Moms and Dads didn't have to be diligent <br>Didn't have to panic for the kids becoming militant <br>Mario's back and it's brilliant <br>I'm a wholesome character that is suitable for children <br>A real role model when I'm leaping off a building <br>Come on kids follow me, follow me <br>One, two, three jump off and weeeeee <br>Dash through traffic shouting tally ho <br>Can you run down the road as fast as Mario <br>I'ma show you pipes a variety of types <br>Hash pipes, crack pipes pass me a light <br>I'm jacked up on mushrooms, listening to Rush tunes <br>Puff, puff, pass me the carrot <br>Motherfuck you <br><br>Fuck Yeah <br>Oh no Mario <br>Fuck Yeah <br>Oh no Mario <br><br>Fucking listen <br><br>Roll up to the club and I jump on the table <br>Engage in R rated behavior that's shameful <br>Fuck the haters straight up mate <br>You can jump on a turtle, and make it painful <br>I'm only saving Princess Peach <br>To get a piece and pinch her peaches <br>Preach <br>I'm going to break that bum when I get her home <br>But I've got the shakes man, I'm coming off the methadone <br>So I scoff another plate full of Goombas <br>Make her suck me off on the rug like a roomba <br>Ooh rah <br>Rebel rabble rouser <br>That'll yank down Bowser's trousers <br>And I sell drugs, plumbing is a front <br>I'm addressing every woman as a cunt <br>Roughing up a punk while I'm puffing on a blunt <br>Duppy motherfuckers and I stuff them in the trunk <br><br>Fuck finishers in Mortal Kombat <br>Oh no Mario <br>Mario's already been there, done that <br>Oh no Mario <br>Fuck Carmageddon and fuck Manhunt <br>Oh no Mario <br>Mario's worse, he's a god damn cunt <br>Oh no Mario <br><br>Spin my hat front to back then back to front <br>I bet you can't do that, you cunt <br>I'm a little fucking fat fucking plumber <br>Fucking taking on fucking any fucking comer <br>I'm a <br>Loose cannon on the loose <br>With an appetite for animal abuse <br>Don't like Jews, I don't like you <br>Don't like anybody, hang them from a noose <br>Enacting atrocities, cruelty of all kinds <br>Bloodbaths, massacres, slaughter, and war crimes <br>Napalming your jungle leaves <br>When I'm shaking the junk in my dungarees <br>But you won't get a crumb from me <br>Because I'm from the streets of New Donk City <br>Out the barrio and I'm heading for Hell <br>It's a me Mario beheading infidels <br><br>Fuck Saints Row, fuck Grand Theft Auto <br>Oh no Mario <br>Mario's going to come and cut your throat <br>Oh no Mario <br>Fuck Doom, fuck Hatred <br>Oh no Mario <br>Mario's raping all that is sacred <br>Oh no Mario <br><br>Nintendo Fun for all the family]]></content><category term="Dan Bull" label="Dan Bull"/><category term="Oh No Mario!" label="Oh No Mario!"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/The_Last_Guardian_Feat_Miracle_of_Sound/</id><title>Dan Bull - The Last Guardian (Feat. Miracle of Sound) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:17:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:17:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/The_Last_Guardian_Feat_Miracle_of_Sound/" title="Dan Bull - The Last Guardian (Feat. Miracle of Sound) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We spoke unspoken things <br>We rode on broken wings <br>We wrote a symphony with broken bows and broken strings <br>We harmonized to bring each other simple hope from hymns <br>We spoke unspoken things <br>We rode on broken wings <br><br>I still remember the day that I met you <br>To begin with, I didn't quite get you <br>And I bet you didn't get me <br>When you sneezed and I said bless you <br>Remember the days of getting acquainted <br>We were chained together with pain <br>But yet its the same tether that made a friendship <br>That no oppressor could tame <br>We severed the chain <br>Shedding the weight <br>And made a clever escape <br>Through terrible weather and flame <br>Frayed fur and feathers never the same <br>Together we celebrate <br>Commiserate <br>Share treasure and blame <br>By any given measure you make <br>We're the best the better the best of mates <br><br>We spoke unspoken things <br>We rode on broken wings <br>We wrote a symphony with broken bows and broken strings <br>We harmonized to bring eachother simple hope from hymns <br>Akin to lonely folk and kings sharing a token drink <br>Opening a link once closed <br>To simply sit like bros and sing <br>We broke the mould <br>And showed the whole world what we both can bring <br>But a pin that's soaked in ink <br>And poked in skin can only sting <br>Like broken bones, broken oaths or broken wings <br><br>So just carry me and I'll lead you <br>Shelter me and I'll feed you <br>Hear me and I'll see you through <br>Together we do whatever we need to do <br><br>I still remember the day that I met you <br>To begin with, I didn't quite get you <br>And I bet you didn't get me <br>When I leaned in with an attempt to pet you <br>But with you I'm not scared to share the real me <br>Just knowing you care can heal me <br>I swear fealty <br>Can you feel me <br>I'll be a sword if you shield me <br>Might never get a chance to say goodbye <br>When its too late you're gone <br>We two may be separated <br>But it's you that made me one <br>When I'm away please stay strong <br>Remember what it takes to break these bonds <br>Place oceans and seas between us <br>They'll seem like lakes and ponds <br>I care about your whereabouts <br>I'm bare without you <br>Share yourself with me <br>Feel free to dare to doubt <br>I swear I'm there to help <br>My prayers go out to thee <br>You're tearing down the scary towers <br>Bearing down <br>And staring out <br>And glaring down at me <br>There's no bounds to what were amounting to <br>To what you and a pal can do <br>Insurmountable mountains <br>Become minuscule mounds <br>When we meld as two <br>I keep the principles you held us to <br>And they help us through <br>Still here when I'm out of view <br>That chill you felt I felt it too <br>That chill you felt I felt it too <br>So <br><br>Carry me and I'll lead you <br>Shelter me and I'll feed you <br>Hear me and I'll see you through <br>Together we do whatever we need to do <br>Together we do whatever we need to do]]></content><category term="Dan Bull" label="Dan Bull"/><category term="The Last Guardian (Feat. Miracle of Sound)" label="The Last Guardian (Feat. Miracle of Sound)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Red_Dead_Resentment/</id><title>Dan Bull - Red Dead Resentment - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:17:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:17:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Red_Dead_Resentment/" title="Dan Bull - Red Dead Resentment - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh for 1911, you suckas <br>Listen, I got a story to tell <br><br>His name was John Marston, a hard un former outlaw <br>Taken by the FBI, so what they let him out for <br>They wanted him to scout where his old gang hanged <br>And help them to see that his old gang hanged <br>They were a rag tag band ravaging the badlands <br>There was only one way that this'd end Bang Bang <br>Found Bill Williamson at Fort Mercer <br>Met the wrong end of his gun, could call it murder <br>But Marston was found, dying parched on the ground <br>By the bonniest farmer around Bonnie MacFarlane and now <br>John in his honour did odd jobs with her father and helped <br>Looped lassos lobbed and fires put out <br>Riding the finest mount, got to explore <br>Living the life that he liked in the great outdoors <br>Ambushing, hunting, trapping, interrupting public hangings <br>Such a bunch of random encounters and misunderstandings <br>But I'm not done with rambling, and John's not done with gambling <br>Dueling, looking out for bounties, pulling plants and fully handling <br>Any damn business this district could imagine witnessing <br>Hanging with Dickens, Harold, Landon Ricketts <br>Attacking antagonists from henchmen to the head, the boss <br>From van der Linde, Allende to Edgar Ross <br>Enter Dead Eye, whereby time kinda stops <br>Then many enemies get shot, a lot <br>Guns cocked and locked, one shot could stop an ox <br>Options Not a lot they've got to drop <br>'Cos they're chock a block with bullet holes like dot to dot <br>Those watching are like What the fock <br>Got their attention, that's audience retention <br>Enemies left red and dead redemption <br>Got your attention, that's audience retention <br>Enemies left red and dead redemption <br><br>Red Dead Redemption <br>Red Dead Redemption <br>Red Dead Redemption <br>Red Dead Redemption]]></content><category term="Dan Bull" label="Dan Bull"/><category term="Red Dead Resentment" label="Red Dead Resentment"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Return_To_Skyrim_Feat_Harry_Partridge/</id><title>Dan Bull - Return To Skyrim (Feat. Harry Partridge) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:17:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:17:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Return_To_Skyrim_Feat_Harry_Partridge/" title="Dan Bull - Return To Skyrim (Feat. Harry Partridge) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[By the nine, it's been five long years since I've come here <br>So I think I'm perfectly entitled to cry one tear <br>And now I want beer <br>And I need a mead and thanks to this bucket we don't have to buy one here <br>I've just baked up a fresh batch of sweetrolls, would you like one dear <br>I should head back to my Hearthfire before the Dawnguard start lecturing <br>But my belly's full and inventory's empty so we'd better get adventuring <br>Pick up a weapon <br>Then pick a direction <br>Then pick a dungeon that we're entering <br>No fast travel, just treasuring every texture that's rendering <br>Quest <br>Reliving our memories and carving out some new ones <br>With newer and shinier hardware you can do whatever you want <br>Is it just me or have mods made this world change in odd ways <br>My frosty droplets of snot are thawed under the God rays <br>They drip in the mountain water, glistening <br>Trickling sounds are sort of twinkling <br>Rippling out I'm sure if you're listening <br>Your hair's on end and your pores are tingling <br>My legacy, odyssey, elegy, prophecy's better than ever <br>You're probably getting euphoric and wobbly <br>In bed in pyjamas <br>But it feels like ebony armor <br>It's Godly <br>I am the Dragonborn and thus I'm dragging you back to my birthplace <br>I've got unfinished business, I never did the main quest in the first place <br>So many side missions, civil wars, guilds and factions <br>How can I ever 100% a game that filled with distractions <br>Refractions and reflections <br>Weapon sets and plant collections <br>Never ending <br>Harry uh, Harry <br>Pants <br>Erection]]></content><category term="Dan Bull" label="Dan Bull"/><category term="Return To Skyrim (Feat. Harry Partridge)" label="Return To Skyrim (Feat. Harry Partridge)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Dishonoured/</id><title>Dan Bull - Dishonoured - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:17:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:17:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Dishonoured/" title="Dan Bull - Dishonoured - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Left to fester in a prison cell <br>This is living hell <br>But i've never been a fellow to just sit and dwell <br>On how they set me up <br>Said I killed the empress <br>My will for vengance <br>Somewhat similar to my skills it's endless <br>Distill the tension <br>Build momentum <br>'til the thrill's tremendous <br>I'm going to bring a world of pain to them <br>That's real relentless <br>They'll feel horrendous in their final living seconds <br>A cold breath on their shoulder as death beckons <br>And shows them in this most fleeting of moments <br>There's no grave <br>Their remains are feeding the rodents <br>Now those close to them <br>Are grieving and broken <br>I leave the bereaved <br>With my deepest condolence <br>That's one more completed atonement <br>Closer to the Lord Regent <br>My meanest opponent <br>He's a treasonous Caesarless Brutus <br>Jesus, he's the evilest elitist Judas <br>He is leaving us deseased <br>I don't believe it's Lupus <br>These streets are heaving with the Weepers <br>Who are really ruthless <br>The old boys' club in an all boys school <br>They control all of Dunwall <br>The Tallboys rule <br>I'm after Lady Boyle <br>So pass the Baby oil <br>You need your nappy changing, man <br>My rapping made you soil <br>Defacation <br>From a blend of dread and veneration <br>Of an assassinating rapper's devastation <br>A declaration <br>Destination desolation <br>Defamation of your delegation <br>Desecration <br>Desparation <br>A dedication <br>To the deprivating <br>Deformating <br>Depredation of your nation <br>Detonation <br>My reputation precedes me <br>Like I was played in a demonstration at E3 <br>You couldn't easily beat me <br>I rake in loads of bone charms <br>Believe me, I'm beastly <br>I'll break your bones in both arms <br><br>Tonight <br>I'm bringing dunwall to life <br>As I walk on water <br>Through walls of light <br>You heard the king <br>As the urchins sing <br>Revenge solves everything]]></content><category term="Dan Bull" label="Dan Bull"/><category term="Dishonoured" label="Dishonoured"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Family_68_Feat_NemRaps/</id><title>Dan Bull - Family `68 (Feat. NemRaps) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:17:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:17:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Family_68_Feat_NemRaps/" title="Dan Bull - Family `68 (Feat. NemRaps) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Brother <br>While you were here playing beer pong <br>I was dealing with the viet cong <br>Me and my familia, we are strong <br>A real bond <br>So string along, I'm gonna sing a song <br>Now bring it on <br>Who are you Hey, hey, who are you <br>Clay I'm just a boy from the Bayou <br>There's a battle raging, man and nature <br>But if you can navigate the salivating alligators <br>Hell awaits you <br>See you at Sammy's place an hour later <br>And do a man a favour 'cause I'm outta paper <br>Grab the tab and pay the round <br>And get yourself a drink to drown your sorrows and a chaser <br>Down it straight and then head out onto the town for capers <br>My knuckles got a couple scars from scuffles in bars <br>Over shuffled cards, I hustle hard <br>There's a shovel in the trunk of my muscle car for when the trouble starts <br>Some dogs are only loyal 'till you pull the muzzle off <br>Visibly twitchy, there's a reason you're fidgety <br>Must be the midges, heat and humidity, breeding stupidity <br>Bitch <br>We've no need for your sympathy <br>Concealing your bigotry beneath a sheet of duplicity <br>And revealing your inner beast <br>Down in the deep south we do it differently <br>I mean if you're feeling me <br>Dead in the middle of river row, little did we know, that we riddled two middlemen who didn't do diddily <br>Oh <br>This is New Bordeaux Bordeaux <br>So what's a few more schmoes <br>Asking for their ass kicked <br>That's their last trick <br>How'd you like the bottom of a swamp for a casket <br><br>Until you've had it all taken away, you'll never know <br>The meaning of family <br>Once you've had it all taken away, then all you'll want's <br>To be in a family <br><br>The new black mob, courtesy of Bourbon Street <br>Might not know me but you heard of me, certainly <br>The Marcanos tried to murder me, but when I pull the heat <br>My people started rising like mercury <br>The Italian Mafia, killed without mercy <br>So now it's time to turn this town topsy turvy <br>If you in the family, then you getting amnesty <br>We plan to bleed these heathens from the city like a damn disease <br>New Bordeaux, my residency <br>And I can't control what the residents see <br>So me and my conglomerates, shall remain anonymous <br>I'm out for dead presidents to represent me <br>Put you in a coma not induced medically <br>Feed you to the creates not leaving a shred of evidence <br>Evidently I need to break it down, so lemme see <br>If you keep messing with me, you'll be a swamp delicacy <br>The only cocktail you drink is molotov <br>There'll be a few scorched men in New Orleans when we catch 'em nodding off <br>Bullets will be tossed across ya noggin <br>Keep on talking and we'll pop you like a bottle top <br>And transport you out of state <br>We dump bodies before they can draw the chalk lines <br>You can vanish without a trace <br>Safe to say, my serrated blade'll ruin y'all <br>Stabbed so many times, I got you looking like a voodoo doll <br>War is what it's time for, go and grab a knife or <br>Turn a sight for sore eyes into an eye sore <br>Got your body floating downstream towards the 9th ward <br>Family isn't who you're born with it's who you die for <br><br>Until you've had it all taken away, you'll never know <br>The meaning of family <br>Once you've had it all taken away, then all you'll want's <br>To be in a family]]></content><category term="Dan Bull" label="Dan Bull"/><category term="Family `68 (Feat. NemRaps)" label="Family `68 (Feat. NemRaps)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Not_A_Player/</id><title>Dan Bull - Not A Player - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:17:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:17:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Not_A_Player/" title="Dan Bull - Not A Player - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not a player I just suck a lot <br>I couldn't give a shucking fit whether we win the cup or not <br>In real life I can't even kick it <br>I've never been to a match let alone bought a season tickethuh <br>There's no denying my skill though <br>I can dribble All over my pillow <br>I can't do a scissor kick but I can kick scissors <br>And sue whoever manufactured them for six figures <br>I'm a man on a mission with ambition <br>To be the sickest soccer kickist in my position <br>At school I liked playing defender a bit <br>So I could have a chit chat down the end of the pitch <br>With my friend who was sht we used to collect stickers but we'd get suspicious even at the scent of a kit <br>But now Im gonna make it in the premire ship and if you don't have faith in me It'll offend me you prick <br>I'm the son of a bitch <br>That'll run on the pitch <br>So awkward you'd think there was some kind of glitch <br>And within a couple of minutes I'll have stitch <br>I don't wanna put the effort in I just wanna be rich <br>I'm the son of a bitch <br>That'll run on the pitch <br>So awkward you'd think there was some kind of glitch <br>And within a couple of minutes I'll have stitch <br>I don't wanna put the effort in I just wanna be rich <br>Im not a player cos I suck a lot <br>Im not a player cos I suck a lot <br>Im not a player cos I suck a lot <br>Im not a player cos I suck a lot <br>Im not a player cos I suck a lot <br>I tripped over my laces and nearly grazed my knuckle off <br>I can't even recall a time my side won <br>My keepy uppy record is like none <br>By gum my chum <br>Why try when I can hide inside sat on my bum <br>Twiddle my thumbs on the Joypad <br>I'd enjoy that <br>Taped over the final to annoy dad <br>So call the boy bad <br>I call it fair play <br>I'm not a good sport <br>Or good at sport <br>Im bare bait <br>Stuck kicking a snare across the airwaves <br>Better at Rap than football I dare say <br>Though get in the way of my goal <br>And get battered <br>Your reputation wrecked, tattered <br>Sepp Blatter <br>I'm a proffesional Athlete <br>'Cept fatter <br>You'll never get me to a track meet <br>Im already knackered <br>Yeah <br>Im not a player cos I suck a lot <br>Im not a player cos I suck a lot <br>Im not a player cos I suck a lot <br>Im not a player cos I suck a lot]]></content><category term="Dan Bull" label="Dan Bull"/><category term="Not A Player" label="Not A Player"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Deadpool_Song_Deadpool_Song/</id><title>Dan Bull - Deadpool Song (Deadpool Song) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:17:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:17:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Deadpool_Song_Deadpool_Song/" title="Dan Bull - Deadpool Song (Deadpool Song) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Intro <br>Forced Laughter <br>Declaration of excitement <br>Build up <br>Build up, build up, build up, build up, build up, build up <br>Build up, build up, build up, build up, build up, build up <br>Build up, build up, build up, build up, build up, build up <br>Drop <br><br>MAHH <br>This is a song that's self referential <br>By Dan Bull about a fellow called Deadpool <br>Both dead cool, both mental <br>Both use terms that are frowned on in general <br>We're giving you a heart attack <br>The proper medical term for that is cardiac <br>We put in 200% <br>You're probably only doing about half of that <br>Who's this beautiful dude doing martial arts <br>Hey, where's Ms Marvel at <br>I'm the marvelous marvel of marvel you marvel at <br>Throwing marbles at marmosets <br>Wearing a tight black and red pajama set <br>Nomming marmalade because I'm Marvin, mate <br>And now I've got to dash because I'm rather late <br>For the hook in which I lazily chant my name <br><br>Dead to the Pool to the Pool to the Dead <br>If it doesn't make sense, well, it's all in your head <br>Pool to the Dead to to Dead to the Pool <br>Ooh, bikinis, head to the pool <br>Dead to the Pool to the Pool to the Dead <br>If it doesn't make sense, well, it's all in your head <br>Impressed mildly be you'll backwards this read <br>Bro, story cool <br><br>So scratch that Deadpool itch <br>Livestream it all on Twitch <br>Self referential kitsch <br>Auto tuned to perfect pitch <br>Call women ho and bitch <br>Then repeat until you're rich <br>It's pronounced niche not nich <br>Oh no, YouTube just glitched <br>There's too much anger <br>Give me a chimichanga <br>I'm a chubby wanker <br>I can't read the signs well enough to see the danger <br>Oh, hang on, cheeky banter <br>And I'm fidgety, rowdy, skittish <br>Inexplicably sounding British <br>Round up critics that downvote this <br>And skip their life story to the finish <br>With so many fates to save the world from <br>Who will step to the plate <br>Wade will, son <br>I make you disappear from the net like your name was <br>I was running out of rhymes for Wilson <br>Even though I just had the opportunity to change it <br>I still said Wilson <br>And now I've done it again, we should probably bring the fills in <br><br>Dead to the Pool to the Pool to the Dead <br>If it doesn't make sense, well, it's all in your head <br>Pool to the Dead to to Dead to the Pool <br>Ooh, bikinis, head to the pool <br>Dead to the Pool to the Pool to the Dead <br>If it doesn't make sense, well, it's all in your head <br>Impressed mildly be you'll backwards this read <br>Bro, story cool <br><br>This song is for sale <br>You have money <br>Go on <br>Treat Yourself <br>Have you noticed how many of Dan Bull's end really suddenly on the final word]]></content><category term="Dan Bull" label="Dan Bull"/><category term="Deadpool Song (Deadpool Song)" label="Deadpool Song (Deadpool Song)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Rapture/</id><title>Dan Bull - Rapture - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:17:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:17:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Rapture/" title="Dan Bull - Rapture - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I am Andrew Ryan <br>And I'm here to ask you a question <br><br>Is a man not entitled to the sweat of his brow <br>The Man in Moscow would spread it to the rest of the crowd <br>The Man in Washington would offer it to the lazy and the poor <br>He in the Vatican would proffer as he prays to the Lord <br>I rejected those philosophies as backward <br>They squandered men's prospects, economies were fractured <br>I shunned detractor's ideologies, shrugged off the Atlas <br>Adapted Adam's Eden for the man who manufactures <br>I chose what was impossible to capture <br>I chose Rapture <br>Where artists can work free from controversial quarrels <br>And scientists can pioneer beyond the world of morals <br>And with the sweat of your brow <br>Rapture can become your city as well <br>Join me, Andrew Ryan <br>Follow my dream <br>Find me, finally <br>Join me, would you kindly <br><br>Rapture is coming back to life <br>Her lungs fill with the will to survive <br>Rapture is coming back to life <br>Finding truth between the lines in a book full of lies <br>Rapture is coming back to life <br>Shops and schools humming with the thoughts of young minds <br>Rapture is coming back to life <br>My city will live, my city will thrive <br><br>Being restricted by minor men was tiring to me <br>If no land was fit to witness the might of Ryan Industries <br>Then I'd find a ship to fit my vision, try it in the deep <br>Besides, you can build towers higher from the sea <br>With Ayn Rand guiding my hand, our divine plan <br>Transcended flights of fancy or lines in the sand <br>Deep, deep beneath the waves, under untold bars of pressure <br>A dark castle full of Art Deco architecture <br>Part venture capitalist investor, part art director <br>Hard Objectivism's the correct decision, disregard the lecture <br>I'm part card shark, part card collector <br>Part father figure, part protector, part corrector <br>Part confessor, part professor, dot connector, lie detector <br>Part Tsar, projector of a spark, settler, tower erector <br>A man chooses, a slave obeys <br>So would you kindly Powerful phrase <br><br>Rapture is coming back to life <br>Her lungs fill with the will to survive <br>Rapture is coming back to life <br>Finding truth between the lines in a book full of lies <br>Rapture is coming back to life <br>Shops and schools humming with the thoughts of young minds <br>Rapture is coming back to life <br>My city will live, my city will thrive <br><br>Would you kindly subscribe to this channel <br>Would you kindly buy the MP3 <br><br>Rapture is coming back to life <br>Her lungs fill with the will to survive <br>Rapture is coming back to life <br>Finding truth between the lines in a book full of lies <br>Rapture is coming back to life <br>Shops and schools humming with the thoughts of young minds <br>Rapture is coming back to life <br>My city will live, my city will thrive]]></content><category term="Dan Bull" label="Dan Bull"/><category term="Rapture" label="Rapture"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/멜랑꼴리트_MelancholyT/걸어가/</id><title>멜랑꼴리트 (Melancholy.T) - 걸어가 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:20:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:20:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A9%9C%EB%9E%91%EA%BC%B4%EB%A6%AC%ED%8A%B8_MelancholyT/%EA%B1%B8%EC%96%B4%EA%B0%80/" title="멜랑꼴리트 (Melancholy.T) - 걸어가 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[걸어가 그저 발길닿는 대로 <br>어디로 향하는지는 나도 모르지 <br>걸어가 그저 발길닿는 대로 <br>어디를 향하는지는 나도 모르지 <br>그저 마음 흘러가는 대로 <br>날 맡길 뿐 <br>이런 날 보며 누군가 말하지 <br>어쩌려고 그러냐고 <br>세상살이 그리 쉽지 않다고 <br>그런 그대에게 난 묻고 싶어 <br>내가 뭐 어때서 <br>그저 내 가슴이 뛰고 <br>내 맘이 이끄는 방향으로 그저 <br>돛을 단 배가 바람에 흘러가듯 <br>그저 맡길뿐 <br>머리로 이해하려 하기보다 <br>가슴이 느끼는대로 걷다보면 <br>알 수 있지 않을까 <br>그저 마음흘러가는 대로 <br>날 맡길 뿐 <br>단 한번도 쉽게 본적 없다고 <br>그저 내 자신을 알 뿐 <br>그저 내게 솔직하고 싶은 맘 <br>내 맘이 이끄는 방향으로 그저 <br>돛을 단 배가 바람에 흘러가듯 <br>그저 맡길뿐 <br>걸어가 그저 발길 닿는 대로 <br>내가 숨쉬고 있음을 <br>내가 살아있음을 <br>그저 내 가슴이 뛰고 <br>내 맘이 이끄는 방향으로 그저 <br>돛을 단 배가 바람에 흘러가듯 <br>그저 맡길뿐 <br>그저 내 가슴이 뛰고 <br>내 맘이 이끄는 방향으로 <br>돛을 단 배가 바람에 흘러가듯 <br>그저 맡길뿐 <br>]]></content><category term="멜랑꼴리트 (Melancholy.T)" label="멜랑꼴리트 (Melancholy.T)"/><category term="걸어가" label="걸어가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안수/고향생각/</id><title>안수 - 고향생각 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:21:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:21:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%88%98/%EA%B3%A0%ED%96%A5%EC%83%9D%EA%B0%81/" title="안수 - 고향생각 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1절 <br>아지랑이 철길위에 <br>쌍나비가 춤춘다 <br>파란하늘 실바람에 <br>하얀구름 둥실 떠간다 <br>붉게타는 꽃노을에 <br>산새들 짝을 지어 <br>둥지찾는 사랑노래소리 <br>저멀리 기적소리 밤이 <br>늦어 울어대면 밤열차 <br>길떠나던 첫사랑 님이 <br>생각나 달뜨는 저녁이면 <br>사랑 노래를 불러본다 <br>고향노래를 <br>후렴: <br>달뜨는 저녁이면 <br>사랑 노래를 불러본다 <br>고향노래를 <br>1.2절 가사]]></content><category term="안수" label="안수"/><category term="고향생각" label="고향생각"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tora/Never_With_Me_Feat_Merryn_Jeann__Meals/</id><title>Tora - Never With Me (Feat. Merryn Jeann &amp; Meals) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:21:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:21:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tora/Never_With_Me_Feat_Merryn_Jeann__Meals/" title="Tora - Never With Me (Feat. Merryn Jeann &amp; Meals) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hold on through the year <br>Don't be shocked that <br>I want you here <br>I missed my calling <br>so darn boring <br>As it's been way too fucking long <br>since you came over <br>And shook my coma deep <br>Broke my loners streak <br>And you put earth beneath my feet <br>My dreams were sweet <br>I can't just believe no rumours <br>No evidence <br>your vultures came <br>and cleaned up <br>Love <br>Just believe no <br>no evidence <br>Your vultures came <br>and cleaned <br>You're the reason <br>but you're never in season <br>Much to keeping my promises <br>You're the reason <br>by you're never with me <br>Shocking how much I be wonder <br>If blocking a crush is a blunder <br>Tucking up under the covers <br>Fucking a touch I'm asunder <br>Mucking around <br>Or stuck in a grounded state <br>Fate would have it Escape is tragic <br>Blame the static <br>So I'm carrying on <br>Into the days <br>I long for peace in a song <br>Six in the morn <br>airport waits a yawn <br>Call shakes up my conscience <br>Your late words are nonsense <br>Though we fornicate <br>with the memories <br>All the same it's ephemeral <br>Cause You're the reason <br>but you're never in season <br>Much to keeping my promises <br>You're the reason <br>by you're never with me <br>]]></content><category term="Tora" label="Tora"/><category term="Never With Me (Feat. Merryn Jeann &amp; Meals)" label="Never With Me (Feat. Merryn Jeann &amp; Meals)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tora/Eat_The_Sun/</id><title>Tora - Eat The Sun - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:21:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:21:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tora/Eat_The_Sun/" title="Tora - Eat The Sun - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Under my feet <br>An heirloom Illuminates <br>And I can only try to warn ahead <br>Particles don't lie to your eyes <br>But the articles <br>in your mind might try <br>Won't you try on your lucky side <br>Or is it so finite <br>that it just don't fit you right <br>Won't you dive <br>into the depths and back <br>So you know <br>why we all still wear our smiles <br>I know where you get that from <br>Get that from <br>You were lying in-accused so long <br>All we might have missed <br>in a sense is gone <br>But you're a buyer in a tin foil suit <br>and you eat the sun <br>]]></content><category term="Tora" label="Tora"/><category term="Eat The Sun" label="Eat The Sun"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tora/Surround/</id><title>Tora - Surround - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:21:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:21:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tora/Surround/" title="Tora - Surround - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I could be around 'round <br>'round you <br>And it could be now now now ohh <br>We could be surround <br>'round sounded <br>But we're not <br>I could be around you <br>It could be now now <br>I could be around you <br>It could be now now <br>I could be around you <br>It could be now now <br>I could be around you <br>It could be now now <br>Now Ahh Now Ahh Now <br>Ahh Now Ahh <br>It might just swallow me whole <br>That I can be around <br>It might just swallow me whole <br>It might just swallow <br>It might just swallow me <br>It might just swallow <br>It might just swallow me <br>It might just swallow <br>It might just swallow me <br>It might just follow me home <br>I could be around 'round <br>'round you <br>And it could be now now now ohh <br>We could be surround <br>'round sounded <br>But we're not <br>]]></content><category term="Tora" label="Tora"/><category term="Surround" label="Surround"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tora/My_Place/</id><title>Tora - My Place - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tora/My_Place/" title="Tora - My Place - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't you wanna go back <br>to my place <br>Don't you wanna go back <br>to my place <br>Don't you wanna go back <br>to my place <br>Won't you give at all <br>you're a disgrace <br>I'm silly you're dumb dumb girl <br>I know <br>Cause usually you're down down <br>You silly you're dumb dumb girl <br>I know <br>Cause usually you're down down oh <br>Cradle your thoughts <br>and swallow your pride <br>I'm easily worth <br>the time you waste <br>Belated of course <br>you tell me you're crying <br>And I'm easily worth your time <br>but you waste mine <br>I'm easily worth your time <br>I'm easily worth your time <br>I'm easily worth your time <br>I'm easily worth your time <br>You're a disgrace <br>I'm silly you're dumb dumb girl <br>I know Cause usually <br>you're down down <br>You silly you're dumb dumb girl <br>I know Cause usually <br>you're down down oh <br>I'm silly you're dumb dumb girl <br>I know Cause usually <br>you're down down <br>You silly you're dumb dumb girl <br>I know Cause usually <br>you're down down oh <br>You silly you're dumb dumb <br>Cause usually you're down down <br>You silly you're dumb dumb girl <br>I know Cause usually <br>you're down down <br>]]></content><category term="Tora" label="Tora"/><category term="My Place" label="My Place"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tora/Jaigantic/</id><title>Tora - Jaigantic - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tora/Jaigantic/" title="Tora - Jaigantic - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I even changed my name this time <br>I followed you up the hill <br>where you're frozen <br>and I filled you in <br>when the force came <br>up to inspect your home <br>yeah your neighbor <br>came back to save ya <br>Those times we've had I felt you <br>I want it back <br>and I'm sure you do oh oh oh <br>Oh you only you i think about <br>I'm not over you <br>I'm so confused god knows <br>who we're all floating over you <br>it's only you i think about <br>I'm not over you <br>I'm so confused god knows <br>who we're all floating <br>we're falling <br>Those times we've had I felt you <br>I want it back <br>and I'm sure you do oh oh oh <br>oh oh <br>I'm not necessarily overjoyed <br>your false appearances <br>don't be brave <br>beyond that lonely cutaway <br>the same as you've began <br>are all influenced <br>you search yourself <br>when you get home <br>and close your eyes <br>]]></content><category term="Tora" label="Tora"/><category term="Jaigantic" label="Jaigantic"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tora/Admire/</id><title>Tora - Admire - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tora/Admire/" title="Tora - Admire - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's all the time in the world <br>I'm not letting go that easy <br>I admire you girl <br>How you're getting on don't need me <br>Could be a breaker braker breaker mm <br>A breaker braker breaker of me <br>Refusing to believe <br>You're letting go that easy <br>High inspire me now <br>I'm getting all of my choices wrong <br>Could be a breaker braker breaker mm <br>A breaker braker breaker of me <br>You're brave Breaker braker mm <br>A brave Breaker braker ooh <br>You're brave Breaker braker mm <br>A brave Braker breaker of me <br>I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not <br>I'm not Letting go <br>I'm not I'm not <br>I'm letting go <br>I'm not I'm not <br>I'm not letting go <br>I'm not <br>I'm not letting go <br>I'm not I'm not I'm not <br>]]></content><category term="Tora" label="Tora"/><category term="Admire" label="Admire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tora/Sugar_Snap/</id><title>Tora - Sugar Snap - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tora/Sugar_Snap/" title="Tora - Sugar Snap - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Only kissing only keeps you <br>knowing the gates been open up <br>enough for you to give it up <br>Lonely mister smokin <br>in the big smoke <br>Courtesy of one half hearted girl <br>I can hear ya <br>I Have a feeling I know too well <br>I can hear ya <br>I Have a feeling <br>I know too much about you <br>to get caught in your sugar trap <br>I can hear ya <br>Only kissing only keeps you <br>knowing the gates been open up <br>enough for you to give it up <br>Lonely mister smoking <br>in the big smoke <br>Courtesy of one half hearted <br>It's true <br>Two innocent lovers <br>Are just two <br>But you make me wait <br>Until I'm patient <br>I can hear ya <br>I Have a feeling I know too well <br>I can hear ya <br>I Have a feeling <br>I know too much about you <br>I can hear ya <br>Have a feeling I know too well <br>I can hear ya <br>I Have a feeling <br>I know too much about you <br>to get caught in your sugar trap <br>]]></content><category term="Tora" label="Tora"/><category term="Sugar Snap" label="Sugar Snap"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/여유와_설빈/먼_훗날_당신과_나_Bonus_Track/</id><title>여유와 설빈 - 먼 훗날 당신과 나 (Bonus Track) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%AC%EC%9C%A0%EC%99%80_%EC%84%A4%EB%B9%88/%EB%A8%BC_%ED%9B%97%EB%82%A0_%EB%8B%B9%EC%8B%A0%EA%B3%BC_%EB%82%98_Bonus_Track/" title="여유와 설빈 - 먼 훗날 당신과 나 (Bonus Track) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[먼 훗날 당신과 나 <br>나란히 앉아 <br>하루가 이틀 같던 날 <br>그리며 노래하네 <br>정태춘과 박은옥 또는 <br>존 레논과 오노 요코 <br>따라 걸으려 발 맞추다 <br>다른 걸음으로 집을 짓네 <br>난 당신과 나의 그날을 기대해 <br>그동안 타인의 삶에 스민 <br>난 당신과 나를 안아주고파 <br>모든 어울린 삶에 대하여 <br>난 당신과 나의 그날을 기대해 <br>그동안 타인의 삶에 스민 <br>난 당신과 나를 안아주고파 <br>모든 어울린 삶에 대하여 <br>난 당신과 나의 그날을 기대해 <br>그동안 타인의 삶에 스민 <br>난 당신과 나를 안아주고파 <br>모든 어울린 삶에 대하여 <br>먼 훗날 당신과 나 <br>]]></content><category term="여유와 설빈" label="여유와 설빈"/><category term="먼 훗날 당신과 나 (Bonus Track)" label="먼 훗날 당신과 나 (Bonus Track)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/여유와_설빈/모두_잠든_새벽/</id><title>여유와 설빈 - 모두 잠든 새벽 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%AC%EC%9C%A0%EC%99%80_%EC%84%A4%EB%B9%88/%EB%AA%A8%EB%91%90_%EC%9E%A0%EB%93%A0_%EC%83%88%EB%B2%BD/" title="여유와 설빈 - 모두 잠든 새벽 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모두 잠든 새벽 <br>나는 잠에서 깨어 <br>눈 앞에 보인 건 <br>전등뿐이지만 <br>모두 잠든 새벽 <br>나는 방문을 열어 <br>내 앞에 있는 건 <br>어둠뿐이지만 <br>나는 불빛을 별빛을 <br>햇빛을 따라간다 <br>찾아간다 <br>모두 잠든 새벽 <br>나는 거리를 걸어 <br>지나가는 건 <br>바람뿐이지만 <br>모두 잠든 새벽 <br>나는 시동을 걸어 <br>켜져 있는 건 <br>가로등뿐이지만 <br>나는 불빛을 별빛을 <br>햇빛을 따라간다 <br>나는 불빛을 별빛을 <br>햇빛을 따라간다 <br>찾아간다 <br>모두 잠든 새벽 <br>나는 기억을 걸어 <br>남아있는 건 <br>상처뿐이지만 <br>모두 잠든 새벽 <br>나는 이름을 불러 <br>돌아오는 건 <br>메아리뿐이지만 <br>나는 불빛을 별빛을 <br>햇빛을 따라간다 <br>나는 불빛을 별빛을 <br>햇빛을 따라간다 <br>나는 불빛을 별빛을 따라 <br>햇빛을 따라간다 <br>난 찾아간다 <br>모두 잠든 새벽 <br>나는 잠에서 깨어 <br>너는 잠에서 깨어 <br>우린 꿈에서 <br>]]></content><category term="여유와 설빈" label="여유와 설빈"/><category term="모두 잠든 새벽" label="모두 잠든 새벽"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/여유와_설빈/꿈속의_그곳/</id><title>여유와 설빈 - 꿈속의 그곳 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%AC%EC%9C%A0%EC%99%80_%EC%84%A4%EB%B9%88/%EA%BF%88%EC%86%8D%EC%9D%98_%EA%B7%B8%EA%B3%B3/" title="여유와 설빈 - 꿈속의 그곳 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 강을 건너본 적 없네 <br>나는 산을 넘어본 적도 없었네 <br>그곳 <br>아무도 없는 곳 <br>천국이라면 이런 곳일까 <br>행복이라면 이런 것일까 <br>손 닿을 수 없고 <br>아직도 먼 곳을 <br>바라보네 <br>잊어도 괜찮아 <br>덧없는 아픔들은 <br>모든 건 사라져 <br>영원할 순 없지 <br>저 황홀한 곳으로 <br>언제쯤 난 <br>갈 수나 있을까 <br>꿈 속의 그곳 <br>천국이라면 이런 곳일까 <br>행복이라면 이런 것일까 <br>손을 잡아주고 <br>내게로 온 사랑 <br>입 맞추네 <br>잊어도 괜찮아 <br>덧없는 아픔들은 <br>모든 건 사라져 <br>영원할 순 없지 <br>저 황홀한 곳으로 <br>언제쯤 난 <br>갈 수나 있을까 <br>꿈 속의 그곳 <br>꿈 속의 그곳 <br>]]></content><category term="여유와 설빈" label="여유와 설빈"/><category term="꿈속의 그곳" label="꿈속의 그곳"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/여유와_설빈/바보/</id><title>여유와 설빈 - 바보 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%AC%EC%9C%A0%EC%99%80_%EC%84%A4%EB%B9%88/%EB%B0%94%EB%B3%B4/" title="여유와 설빈 - 바보 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그 어떤 강물도 그 어떤 사람도 <br>똑바로 흐르지 걸어가지 않아요 <br>거칠게 나에게 파도가 쳐도 <br>사람 사는 세상이 될 수 있도록 <br>강물은 바다를 포기하지 않아요 <br>우리는 당신을 잊지 않아요 <br>강물은 바다를 포기하지 않듯 <br>바다는 강물을 마다하지 않아요 <br>힘들고 지칠 때 너무 아플 때 <br>사랑하는 사람들 함께 있다면 <br>강물은 바다를 포기하지 않아요 <br>우리는 당신을 잊지 않아요 <br>강물은 바다를 포기하지 않아요 <br>우리 우리는 당신을 잊지 않아요 <br>]]></content><category term="여유와 설빈" label="여유와 설빈"/><category term="바보" label="바보"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/여유와_설빈/상자/</id><title>여유와 설빈 - 상자 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%AC%EC%9C%A0%EC%99%80_%EC%84%A4%EB%B9%88/%EC%83%81%EC%9E%90/" title="여유와 설빈 - 상자 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈 뜨고 살아도 안 보이면 <br>어떻게 해야 해 <br>귀 기울여 들어도 안 들리면 <br>어떻게 해야 해 <br>어떻게 해 <br>불 꺼진 방안에 몸을 뉘어 <br>나는 돌아가네 <br>커다란 상자에 몸을 실어 <br>나는 돌아가네 <br>나는 돌아가 <br>눈 내린 창밖이 하얘지면 <br>나는 떠나갈래 <br>비 개인 하늘이 반짝이면 <br>나는 떠나 <br>여길 떠나 <br>나는 떠나갈래 <br>]]></content><category term="여유와 설빈" label="여유와 설빈"/><category term="상자" label="상자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/여유와_설빈/개미마을/</id><title>여유와 설빈 - 개미마을 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%AC%EC%9C%A0%EC%99%80_%EC%84%A4%EB%B9%88/%EA%B0%9C%EB%AF%B8%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%84/" title="여유와 설빈 - 개미마을 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[서울에 몇 남지 않은 <br>달동네 중 하나 <br>개미마을에 사는 <br>베짱이라고 합니다 <br>가슴 아픈 일도 많고 <br>배고픔과 함께 <br>슬픔까지 찾아와 <br>날 괴롭힐 때 <br>노래하면 된다고 <br>춤을 추면 된다고 <br>꿈을 꾸면 된다고 <br>사랑하면 된다고 <br>연탄재를 차지 않고 <br>뜨거운 사람이 되려 <br>개미마을에 사는 <br>베짱이라고 합니다 <br>노래하면 된다고 <br>춤을 추면 된다고 <br>꿈을 꾸면 된다고 <br>사랑하면 된다고 합니다 <br>뜨거운 사람 <br>뜨거운 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="여유와 설빈" label="여유와 설빈"/><category term="개미마을" label="개미마을"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/여유와_설빈/사람과_사람_사이/</id><title>여유와 설빈 - 사람과 사람 사이 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%AC%EC%9C%A0%EC%99%80_%EC%84%A4%EB%B9%88/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C%EA%B3%BC_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C_%EC%82%AC%EC%9D%B4/" title="여유와 설빈 - 사람과 사람 사이 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 너를 보았고 <br>너도 나를 봤지만 <br>그냥 지나쳐버리고 말아 <br>사람과 사람 사이 <br>눈에 보이지 않는 <br>마음의 벽이 너무나 높아 <br>왜 그렇게 가면을 쓰고 있니 <br>뭐가 그렇게 문을 <br>걸어 잠그게 하는지 <br>나는 너에게 다가갈 거야 <br>그럼 너도 나에게 <br>한 발짝 다가와줄래 <br>나를 두려워하지마 <br>나는 그런 사람이 아냐 <br>너도 알잖아 <br>희미한 너의 미소에 <br>내가 가야 할 길이 보여 <br>꿈이 보여 <br>이제 우리 서로를 보여줘 <br>]]></content><category term="여유와 설빈" label="여유와 설빈"/><category term="사람과 사람 사이" label="사람과 사람 사이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/여유와_설빈/할아버지/</id><title>여유와 설빈 - 할아버지 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%AC%EC%9C%A0%EC%99%80_%EC%84%A4%EB%B9%88/%ED%95%A0%EC%95%84%EB%B2%84%EC%A7%80/" title="여유와 설빈 - 할아버지 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[할아버지는 살아계실 때 <br>지금 내가 앉은 소파에 앉아 <br>신호가 잘 잡히지 않는 <br>라디오를 즐겨 들으셨다 <br>얼마나 많은 소식을 들고 <br>어린 나를 옆에 앉히고 <br>감히 헤아릴 수가 없는 <br>시간 두고 가시는구나 <br>할아버지는 돌아가실 때 <br>누구에게도 알리지 않고 <br>뒷산 오르시는 길에서 <br>경운기와 눈 감으셨다 <br>얼마나 많은 농사를 짓고 <br>어린 나를 뒤에 태우고 <br>감이 헤아릴 수가 없는 <br>사랑 주고 가시는구나 <br>나 이 담에 커서 돈 많이 벌면 <br>삐까뻔쩍 라디오 사 드려야지 <br>나 이 담에 커서 어른이 되면 <br>부릉부릉 경운기 사 드려야지 <br>감히 헤아릴 수가 없는 <br>먼 곳으로 가시는구나 <br>]]></content><category term="여유와 설빈" label="여유와 설빈"/><category term="할아버지" label="할아버지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/여유와_설빈/풍경/</id><title>여유와 설빈 - 풍경 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%AC%EC%9C%A0%EC%99%80_%EC%84%A4%EB%B9%88/%ED%92%8D%EA%B2%BD/" title="여유와 설빈 - 풍경 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[굳게 닫힌 창문 너머로 <br>비가 오나 눈이 내리나 <br>따뜻한 이 내 방 안에선 <br>모든 것이 풍경이지요 <br>창 밖으로 <br>문 밖으로 <br>세상으로 <br>나가야지 삶이 되는데 <br>언젠가 사라질 당신과 나 <br>우리가 함께할 수많은 날 <br>서로 사랑해줘요 <br>꿈을 꾸게 해줘요 <br>삶이 되게 해줘요 <br>나와 함께 해줘요 <br>서로 사랑해줘요 <br>꿈을 꾸게 해줘요 <br>노래하게 해줘요 <br>춤을 추게 해줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="여유와 설빈" label="여유와 설빈"/><category term="풍경" label="풍경"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/여유와_설빈/바다를_보내주는_사람/</id><title>여유와 설빈 - 바다를 보내주는 사람 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%AC%EC%9C%A0%EC%99%80_%EC%84%A4%EB%B9%88/%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%A4%EB%A5%BC_%EB%B3%B4%EB%82%B4%EC%A3%BC%EB%8A%94_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C/" title="여유와 설빈 - 바다를 보내주는 사람 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언제나 눈을 뜨면 회색 하늘 탁한 공기 <br>사랑을 믿지 않는 사람이 살아가죠 <br>바다를 보여줘요 바다를 들려줘요 <br>그대가 절망하면 이렇게 대답했죠 <br>바다를 보내주는 사람이 있다구요 <br>바다를 보여줘요 바다를 들려줘요 <br>그대가 재촉하면 무너진 나의 마음 <br>바다는 어디 있죠 바다는 언제 오죠 <br>그대가 체념하면 이렇게 되뇌이죠 <br>이것만 기억해요 이것만 기억해요 <br>바다를 보내주는 사람이 있다구요 <br>그대를 사랑하는 사람이 있다구요 <br>사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="여유와 설빈" label="여유와 설빈"/><category term="바다를 보내주는 사람" label="바다를 보내주는 사람"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/여유와_설빈/생각은_자유/</id><title>여유와 설빈 - 생각은 자유 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%AC%EC%9C%A0%EC%99%80_%EC%84%A4%EB%B9%88/%EC%83%9D%EA%B0%81%EC%9D%80_%EC%9E%90%EC%9C%A0/" title="여유와 설빈 - 생각은 자유 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생각은 자유예요 상상해봐요 <br>천국도 지옥도 국가도 종교도 없는 <br>존 레논의 노래처럼 꿈을 꿀래요 <br>몽상일지라도 꿈을 꿀래요 <br>엄마 엄마 천국의 문을 두드려요 <br>내게서 이 뱃지와 총을 가져가세요 <br>밥 딜런의 노래처럼 시를 쓸래요 <br>바람에 날려갈 시를 쓸래요 <br>물 좀 줘요 목 말라요 사랑을 주세요 <br>아무리 원해도 비는 안 와요 <br>한대수의 노래처럼 살고 싶어요 <br>행복의 나라에 살고 싶어요 <br>긴 밤 지새우고 풀잎마다 맺힌 <br>진주보다 고운 아침이슬처럼 <br>김민기의 노래처럼 걸어갈래요 <br>서러움 버리고 걸어갈래요 <br>다시는 못 볼 님이라도 <br>원망하지 않아요 <br>내 사랑 그대여 내 곁에 머물러줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="여유와 설빈" label="여유와 설빈"/><category term="생각은 자유" label="생각은 자유"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/여유와_설빈/구름에_가려진_달에게/</id><title>여유와 설빈 - 구름에 가려진 달에게 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:22:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:22:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%AC%EC%9C%A0%EC%99%80_%EC%84%A4%EB%B9%88/%EA%B5%AC%EB%A6%84%EC%97%90_%EA%B0%80%EB%A0%A4%EC%A7%84_%EB%8B%AC%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C/" title="여유와 설빈 - 구름에 가려진 달에게 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[구름에 가려진 달에게 <br>어둠에 갇혀버린 빛에게 <br>안개가 걷히면 보일까 <br>아침이 밝아오면 보일까 <br>어두워 아무것도 안 보여 <br>흐려져 똑바로 갈 수 없어 <br>그늘에 가려진 너에게 <br>마음의 안식을 주려 해 <br>바람에 흔들리던 나 이제 <br>당당히 내 길을 가려 해 <br>외로워 하나 둘 곁에 없어 <br>두려워 혼자선 갈 수 없어도 <br>난 가 나의 길을 <br>너와 함께라면 <br>어두워도 흐려져도 <br>불안해도 결국 넘어져도 <br>]]></content><category term="여유와 설빈" label="여유와 설빈"/><category term="구름에 가려진 달에게" label="구름에 가려진 달에게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태사비애/집에_가기싫어/</id><title>태사비애 - 집에 가기싫어 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:23:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:23:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%82%AC%EB%B9%84%EC%95%A0/%EC%A7%91%EC%97%90_%EA%B0%80%EA%B8%B0%EC%8B%AB%EC%96%B4/" title="태사비애 - 집에 가기싫어 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 집에 <br>나 가기가 싫어 <br>텅 빈 집에 <br>나 가기가 싫어 <br>우리 매일 떨어지기 이렇게 힘든데 <br>손을 잡고 절대 놓고 싶지 않잖아 <br>집에 가기 싫어 정말 <br>집에 정말 가기 싫어 <br>우리 같이 살까 <br>집에 혼자 <br>나 가기가 싫어 <br>너 없는 집 <br>나 가기가 싫어 <br>매일매일 떨어지기 이렇게 힘든데 <br>손을 잡고 절대 놓고 싶지 않잖아 <br>집에 가기 싫어 정말 <br>집에 정말 가기 싫어 <br>우리 그냥 살자 <br>하루하루 시간 지나 몇 년이 지나도 <br>손을 잡고 절대 평생 놓지 않을게 <br>같이 살자 우리 정말 <br>우리 정말 같이 살자 <br>행복하게 오래 <br>]]></content><category term="태사비애" label="태사비애"/><category term="집에 가기싫어" label="집에 가기싫어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시와_바람/아_미운사람/</id><title>시와 바람 - 아! 미운사람 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:23:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:23:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EC%99%80_%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C/%EC%95%84_%EB%AF%B8%EC%9A%B4%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C/" title="시와 바람 - 아! 미운사람 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑에 아픔이 많은 남자 <br>이별에 아쉬움이 남은 여자 <br>대낮에 길에서 만난 두 사람 <br>앗 이럴 수가 <br>그때는 왜 그렇게 떠났냐고 <br>내 맘을 그렇게 몰랐냐고 <br>못했던 말들이 너무 많아 <br>아 어떡하나 <br>한걸음 한걸음 다가가서 <br>참았던 눈물을 흘려볼까 <br>당신의 마음도 아직 뜨거운지 <br>한 번 물어볼까 <br>아직도 내 맘 속엔 니가 있다고 <br>아 미운 사람 <br>사랑에 아픔이 많은 남자 <br>이별에 아쉬움이 남은 여자 <br>대낮에 길에서 만난 두 사람 <br>아 이럴 수가 <br>아직도 마음이 남았는데 <br>어떻게 그리 쉽게 떠나가나 <br>함께한 날들이 너무 길어 <br>아 못 잊겠네 <br>한걸음 한걸음 다가가서 <br>참았던 눈물을 흘려볼까 <br>당신의 마음도 아직 뜨거운지 <br>한번 물어볼까 <br>아직도 내 맘 속에 니가 있다고 <br>아 미운사람 <br>너와 함께한 거리에 <br>더 이상 갈 수가 없어 <br>너 없는 하늘 찾아 <br>여기까지 왔는데 <br>너도 나를 생각하다 <br>이 길 위에 온 건지 <br>그래서 우린 오늘 <br>마주치게 된 건지 <br>아직도 내 맘 속엔 니가 있다고 <br>아 미운사람 <br>아 미운사람 <br>]]></content><category term="시와 바람" label="시와 바람"/><category term="아! 미운사람" label="아! 미운사람"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시와_바람/허수아비/</id><title>시와 바람 - 허수아비 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T16:23:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T16:23:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EC%99%80_%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C/%ED%97%88%EC%88%98%EC%95%84%EB%B9%84/" title="시와 바람 - 허수아비 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[당신은 허수아비야 <br>당신은 허수아비야 <br>예쁘지만 안 예쁘고 <br>화려하지만 촌스러워 <br>당신은 허수아비야 <br>당신은 허수아비야 <br>내 맘을 가지고 놀지마 <br>당신이 나를 바라볼 때 <br>그윽한 미소로 유혹하고 <br>내가 마음을 고백하려할 땐 <br>친구가 좋다 말하네 <br>세상에 가장 슬픈 눈으로 <br>위로의 눈빛을 건네주고 <br>내가 어깨에 기대려할 땐 <br>구속이 싫다 말하네 <br>당신은 허수아비야 <br>당신은 허수아비야 <br>예쁘지만 안 예쁘고 <br>화려하지만 촌스러워 <br>당신은 허수아비야 <br>당신은 허수아비야 <br>내 맘을 가지고 놀지마 <br>아무래도 당신에겐 <br>없는 게 있어요 <br>그것은 따뜻한 인간미야 <br>어장관리 백날해도 <br>당신만 허무해질 뿐이야 <br>당신은 허수아비야 <br>당신은 허수아비야 <br>예쁘지만 안 예쁘고 <br>화려하지만 촌스러워 <br>당신은 허수아비야 <br>당신은 허수아비야 <br>내 맘을 가지고 놀지마 <br>내 맘을 가지고 놀지마 <br>내 맘을 가지고 놀지마 <br>]]></content><category term="시와 바람" label="시와 바람"/><category term="허수아비" label="허수아비"/></entry></feed>