<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:14:33+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Brown/Papas_Got_A_Brand_New_Bag_Live/</id><title>James Brown - Papa`s Got A Brand New Bag (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Brown/Papas_Got_A_Brand_New_Bag_Live/" title="James Brown - Papa`s Got A Brand New Bag (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come here sister... Papa's in the swing <br>He ain't too hip... about that new breed babe <br>He ain't no drag <br>Papa's got a brand new bag <br><br>Come here mama... and dig this crazy scene <br>He's not too fancy... but his line is pretty clean <br>He ain't no drag. <br>Papa's got a brand new bag <br><br>He's doing the Jerk... <br>He's doing the Fly <br>Don't play him cheap 'cause you know he ain't shy <br>He's doing the Monkey, the Mashed Potatoes, Jump back Jack, See you later <br>alligator. <br><br>Come here sister <br>Papa's in the swing <br>He ain't too hip now <br>but I can dig that new breed babe; <br>He ain't no drag <br>He's got a brand new bag <br><br>Oh papa! He's doing the Jerk <br>Papa... he's doing the Jerk <br>He's doing the twist ... just like this <br>He's doing the Fly ev'ry day and ev'ry night <br>The thing's... like the Boomerang. <br>Hey... come on <br>Hey! Hey... come on <br>Hey! Hey... he's pu tight... out of sight... <br>Come on. Hey! Hey!]]></content><category term="James Brown" label="James Brown"/><category term="Papa`s Got A Brand New Bag (Live)" label="Papa`s Got A Brand New Bag (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Everly_Brothers/Cathys_Clown_Live/</id><title>The Everly Brothers - Cathy`s Clown (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Everly_Brothers/Cathys_Clown_Live/" title="The Everly Brothers - Cathy`s Clown (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't want your love anymore <br>Don't want your kisses, that's for sure <br>I die each time <br>I hear this sound: <br>"Here he comes. That's Cathy's clown." <br><br>I've gotta stand tall <br>You know a man can't crawl <br>But when he knows you’re tellin’ lies <br>And he hears them passing’ by <br>He's not a man at all <br><br>Don't want your love anymore <br>Don't want your kisses, that's for sure <br>I die each time <br>I hear this sound: <br>"Here he comes. That's Cathy's clown." <br><br>When you see me shed a tear <br>And you know that it’s sincere <br>Don’t you think it’s kind of sad <br>That you’re treating me so bad <br>Or don’t you even care? <br><br>Don't want your love anymore <br>Don't want your kisses, that's for sure <br>I die each time <br>I hear this sound: <br>"Here he comes. <br>That's Cathy's clown <br>That's Cathy's clown <br>That's Cathy's clown."]]></content><category term="The Everly Brothers" label="The Everly Brothers"/><category term="Cathy`s Clown (Live)" label="Cathy`s Clown (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gladys_Knight__The_Pips/Come_See_About_Me/</id><title>Gladys Knight &amp; The Pips - Come See About Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gladys_Knight__The_Pips/Come_See_About_Me/" title="Gladys Knight &amp; The Pips - Come See About Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been crying <br>'Cause I'm lonely (for you) <br>Smiles have all turned to tears <br>But tears won't wash away the fears <br>That you're never ever gonna return <br>To ease the fire that within me burns <br><br>It keeps me crying baby for you <br>Keeps me sighin' baby for you <br>So won't you hurry ? <br>Come on boy, see about me <br>(Come see about me) <br>See about you baby <br><br>I've given up my friends just for you <br>My friends are gone <br>And you have too <br>No peace shall I find <br>Until you come back <br>And be mine <br>No matter what you do or say <br>I'm gonna love you anyway <br><br>Keep on crying baby for you <br>I'm gonna keep sighin' baby for you <br>So come on hurry <br>Come on and see about me <br>(Come see about me) <br>See about you baby <br><br><br><br><br><br>Sometime's up <br>Sometime's down <br>My life's so uncertain <br>With you not around <br>From my arms you maybe out of reach <br>But my heart says you're here to keep <br><br>Keeps me crying baby for you <br>Keep on, keep on crying baby for you <br>So won't you hurry <br>Come on boy, see about me (Come see about me) <br>See about you baby (Come see about me) <br>You know I'm so lonely (Come see about me) <br>I love you only (Come see about me) <br>See about your baby (Come see about me) <br>Hurry, hurry]]></content><category term="Gladys Knight &amp; The Pips" label="Gladys Knight &amp; The Pips"/><category term="Come See About Me" label="Come See About Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joey_Dee_And_The_Starliters/What_Kind_Of_Love_Is_This_Rerecorded/</id><title>Joey Dee And The Starliters - What Kind Of Love Is This (Rerecorded) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joey_Dee_And_The_Starliters/What_Kind_Of_Love_Is_This_Rerecorded/" title="Joey Dee And The Starliters - What Kind Of Love Is This (Rerecorded) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What kind of love is this that makes me want to jump and shout? <br>I want to know what kind of love is this that turns my heart inside out? <br>It's that itchy-twitchy feelin' that I have inside <br>Something overwhelming that I just can't hide <br>I want to know (oh, yeah) whoa, yeah (oh, yeah) whoa, tell me (oh, yeah) <br>(What kind of love is this?) <br>What kind of love is this? <br><br>What kind of love is this that haunts me every day? <br>I want to know what kind of love is this that makes me say the things I say? <br>Well, I'm walkin' around and grinnin' with my head in the air <br>The people think I'm crazy but I just don't care <br>I want to know (oh, yeah) whoa, yeah (oh, yeah) whoa, tell me (oh, yeah) <br>(What kind of love is this?) <br>What kind of love is this? <br><br>Well, I feel like a man in outer space <br>I'm actin' like a psycho case <br>Hey, girl, stop this feelin' <br>Look at me, you've got me rockin' and a-reelin'! <br><br>Yeah, what kind of love is this, aw, that shakes me up so bad? <br>I want to know what kind of love is this?, yeah, my situation is sad <br>Well, I just can't understand it, it just ain't real <br>I know no one has ever felt the way I feel <br>I want to know (oh, yeah) whoa, yeah (oh, yeah) whoa, tell me (oh, yeah) <br>(What kind of love is this?) <br>What kind of love is this? <br><br>(What kind of love is this?) <br>(What kind of love is this?) <br>(What kind of love is this?)]]></content><category term="Joey Dee And The Starliters" label="Joey Dee And The Starliters"/><category term="What Kind Of Love Is This (Rerecorded)" label="What Kind Of Love Is This (Rerecorded)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Miracles/Shop_Around_Rerecorded/</id><title>The Miracles - Shop Around (Rerecorded) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Miracles/Shop_Around_Rerecorded/" title="The Miracles - Shop Around (Rerecorded) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I became of age, my mother called me to her side <br>She said, son, you're growing up now, pretty soon you'll take a bride <br>And then she said <br><br>Just because you've become a young man now <br>There's still some things that you don't understand now <br>Before you ask some girl for her hand now <br>Keep your freedom for as long as you can now <br>My mama told me, you better shop around <br>Whoa, yeah, you better shop around <br><br>Ah, there's some things that I want you to know now <br>Just as sure as the wind's gonna blow now <br>The women come and the women gonna go now <br>Before you tell 'em that you love 'em so now <br>My mama told me, you better shop around <br>Whoa, yeah, you better shop around <br><br>Try to get yourself a bargain, son <br>Don't be sold on the very first one <br>Pretty girls come a dime a dozen <br>Try to find you one who's gonna give you true loving <br><br>Before you take a girl and say I do now <br>Make sure she's in love with you now <br>My mama told me, you better shop around <br><br><br><br><br><br>Oh, yeah <br>Try to get yourself a bargain, son <br>Don't be sold on the very first one <br>Pretty girls come a dime a dozen <br>Try to find you one who's gonna give you true loving <br><br>Before you take a girl and say I do now <br>Make sure she's in love with you now <br>Make sure that her love is true now <br>I'd hate to see you feeling sad and blue now <br>My mama told me, you better shop around <br><br>Oh, don't let the first one getcha <br>Oh no, cause I don't want to see her with ya <br>Uh huh, before you let 'em hold you tight <br>Ah, yeah, yeah, make sure she's all right <br>Uh huh, before you let her take your hand, my son <br>Understand, my son <br>Be a man, my son <br>I know you can, my son <br>I love you <br>Shop around]]></content><category term="The Miracles" label="The Miracles"/><category term="Shop Around (Rerecorded)" label="Shop Around (Rerecorded)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Merseybeats/I_Think_Of_You_Rerecorded/</id><title>The Merseybeats - I Think Of You (Rerecorded) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Merseybeats/I_Think_Of_You_Rerecorded/" title="The Merseybeats - I Think Of You (Rerecorded) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When the night is cold <br>And my arms want someone to hold <br>I think of you <br>When the rain is falling <br>I hear you calling to me <br>I think of you <br><br>I think of you every minute <br>I lie awake each lonely night <br>I think of you, yeah that day <br>You walked away and out of sight <br><br>Well now my arms just long to hold you <br>Like they used to do oo before <br>I'm a broken man <br>Now you don't love me no o more <br><br>Now the night is cold <br>And my arms want someone to hold <br>I think of you <br>Now the rain is falling <br>I hear you calling to me <br>I think of you <br><br>I think of you every minute <br>I lie awake each lonely night <br>I think of you, yeah that day <br>You walked away and out of sight <br><br>Well now my arms just long to hold you <br>Like they used to do oo before <br>I'm a broken man <br>Now you don't love me no o more <br><br>When the night is cold <br>And my arms want someone to hold <br>I think of you <br>When the rain is falling <br>I hear you calling to me <br>I think of you <br>I think of you]]></content><category term="The Merseybeats" label="The Merseybeats"/><category term="I Think Of You (Rerecorded)" label="I Think Of You (Rerecorded)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Delfonics/La_-_La_Means_I_Love_You_Live/</id><title>The Delfonics - La - La Means I Love You (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Delfonics/La_-_La_Means_I_Love_You_Live/" title="The Delfonics - La - La Means I Love You (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Many guys have come to you <br>With a line that wasn't true <br>And you passed them by passed them by <br>Now you're in the center ring <br>And their lines don't mean a thing <br>Why don't you let me try let me try <br>Now I don't wear a diamond ring <br>I don't even have a song to sing <br>All I know is <br><br>La la la la la la la la la means <br>I love you <br>Oh, baby please now <br>Oh baby <br>La la la la la la la la la means <br>I love you <br><br>If I ever saw a girl <br>That I needed in this world <br>You are the one for me one for me <br>Let me hold me in my arms <br>Girl, and thrill you with my charms <br>I'm sure you will see you will see <br>The things I am sayin' are true <br>And the way I explain them to you <br>Listen to me <br><br>The things I am sayin' are true <br>And the way I explain them to you, yes to you <br>Listen to me <br><br>La la la la la la la la la means <br>I love you <br>Oh, you'll have to understand <br>Come on and take my hand]]></content><category term="The Delfonics" label="The Delfonics"/><category term="La - La Means I Love You (Live)" label="La - La Means I Love You (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brook_Benton/Kiddio_Live/</id><title>Brook Benton - Kiddio (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brook_Benton/Kiddio_Live/" title="Brook Benton - Kiddio (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I told you, baby, how I feel <br>One word can close this deal <br>Baby, be my queen of hearts <br>Please gimme that love you've got <br>A won'tcha say yes, don'tcha say no <br>Make me feel good, kiddio <br><br>Maybe I'm just wastin' time <br>Can't get you off my mind <br>You could make me feel so good <br>I know you could if you only would <br>A won'tcha say yes, don'tcha say no <br>Make me feel good, kiddio <br><br>I wrote you a six page letter <br>I called you on the phone <br>But you started talkin' 'bout the weather <br>Kiddio, don'tcha know that's wrong <br><br>I can't stand this playin' 'round <br>Help me up, don't let me down <br>Kiss me baby, tell me so <br>If you love me, let me know <br>A won'tcha say yes don'tcha say no <br>Make me feel good, kiddio <br><br>I wrote you a six page letter <br>I even called you on the phone <br>But you started talkin' 'bout the weather <br>Kiddio, don'tcha know that's wrong <br><br>I can't stand this playin' 'round <br>Help me up, don't let me down <br>A kiss me baby, tell me so <br>If you love me, let me know <br>a won'tcha say yes, don'tcha say no <br>Make me feel good, kiddio <br><br>Make me feel so uh oh oh good, so, so good, kiddio]]></content><category term="Brook Benton" label="Brook Benton"/><category term="Kiddio (Live)" label="Kiddio (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Drifters/Save_The_Last_Dance_For_Me_Rerecorded/</id><title>The Drifters - Save The Last Dance For Me (Rerecorded) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Drifters/Save_The_Last_Dance_For_Me_Rerecorded/" title="The Drifters - Save The Last Dance For Me (Rerecorded) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You can dance <br>Every dance with the guy <br>Who gave you the eye <br>Let him hold you tight <br><br>You can smile <br>Every smile for the man <br>Who held your hand <br>'Neath the pale moonlight <br><br>But don't forget who's taking you home <br>And in whose arms you're gonna be <br>So darlin' <br>Save the last dance for me, mmm <br><br>Oh I know <br>That the music is fine <br>Like sparkling wine <br>Go and have your fun <br><br>Laugh and sing <br>But while we're apart <br>Don't give your heart <br>To anyone <br><br>But don't forget who's taking you home <br>And in whose arms you're gonna be <br>So darlin' <br>Save the last dance for me, mmm <br><br>Baby don't you know I love you so <br>Can't you feel it when we touch <br>I will never, never let you go <br>I love you oh so much <br><br>You can dance <br>Go and carry on <br>Till the night is gone <br>And it's time to go <br><br>If he asks <br>If you're all alone <br>Can he take you home <br>You must tell him no <br><br>'Cause don't forget who's taking you home <br>And in whose arms you're gonna be <br>So darlin' <br>Save the last dance for me <br><br>'Cause don't forget who's taking you home <br>And in whose arms you're gonna be <br>So darlin' <br>Save the last dance for me, mmm <br><br>Save the last dance for me, mmm <br>Save the last dance for me]]></content><category term="The Drifters" label="The Drifters"/><category term="Save The Last Dance For Me (Rerecorded)" label="Save The Last Dance For Me (Rerecorded)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Coasters/Little_Egypt_Rerecorded/</id><title>The Coasters - Little Egypt (Rerecorded) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Coasters/Little_Egypt_Rerecorded/" title="The Coasters - Little Egypt (Rerecorded) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I went and bought myself a ticket and <br>I sat down in the very first row, wo wo <br>They pulled the curtain but then when <br>They turned the spotlight way down low, wo wo <br>Little Egypt came out strutting <br>Wearing nothing but a button and a bow, wo wo <br>Singing, Yeah yeah Yeah yeah Yeah yeah Yeah yeah'' <br><br>She had a ruby on her tummy and <br>A diamond big as Texas on her toe, wo wo <br>She let her hair down and <br>She did the hoochie koochie real slow, wo wo <br>When she did her special number on a zebra skin <br>I thought she'd stop the show, wo wo <br>Singing, Yeah yeah Yeah yeah Yeah yeah Yeah yeah <br><br>She did a triple somersault and when she hit the ground <br>She winked at the audience and then she turned around <br>She had a picture of a cowboy tattooed on her spine <br>Saying Phoenix, Arizona, nineteen forty nine <br><br>Yeah, but let me tell you people <br>Little Egypt doesn't dance there anymore, wo wo <br>She's too busy mopping and <br>A taking care of shopping at the store, wo wo <br>Cause we got seven kids and <br>All day long they crawl around the floor, wo wo <br>Singing, Yeah yeah Yeah yeah Yeah yeah Yeah yeah]]></content><category term="The Coasters" label="The Coasters"/><category term="Little Egypt (Rerecorded)" label="Little Egypt (Rerecorded)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Little_Richard/Whole_Lotta_Shakin_Live/</id><title>Little Richard - Whole Lotta Shakin` (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Little_Richard/Whole_Lotta_Shakin_Live/" title="Little Richard - Whole Lotta Shakin` (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I said come on over baby, a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br>Yeah I said come on over baby, a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br>Well we ain't fakin', a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br><br>Mmm, I said come on over baby, we got chickens in the barn <br>Whose barn, what barn, my barn <br>I said come on over baby, we got the bull by the horns <br>Yeah, we ain't fakin', a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br><br>Well, I said shake baby, shake <br>I said shake, baby shake now <br>I said shake it baby, shake <br>I said shake it baby, shake <br>We ain't fakin', a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br><br>Well, I said come on over baby, a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br>I said come on over baby, a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br>We ain't fakin', a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br><br>Well my mom mom mom, I said shake baby, shake <br>I said shake baby, shake it <br>I said shake baby, shake all right <br>I said shake baby, shake <br>We ain't fakin', a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br><br>Well, I said come on over baby, a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br>I said come on over baby, a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br>We ain't fakin', a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br><br>Easy now <br><br>I said shake baby, shake <br>I said shake, baby shake now <br>I said shake it baby, shake uh huh <br>I said shake it baby, shake, bop bop <br>We ain't fakin', a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br>Yeh <br><br>Well, I said come on over baby, a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br>I said come on over baby, a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br>We ain't fakin', a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br><br>I said shake baby, shake <br>I said shake, baby shake now <br>I said shake it baby, shake uh huh <br>I said shake it baby, shake, bop bop <br>We ain't fakin', a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br><br>I said shake baby, shake <br>I said shake, baby shake now <br>I said shake it baby, shake uh huh <br>I said shake it baby, shake, bop bop <br>We ain't fakin', a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br><br>I said shake baby, shake <br>I said shake baby, shake <br>We ain't fakin', a whole lot ta shakin' goin' on <br><br>Shake it out]]></content><category term="Little Richard" label="Little Richard"/><category term="Whole Lotta Shakin` (Live)" label="Whole Lotta Shakin` (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hank_Ballard/Lets_Go_Lets_Go_Lets_Go_Rerecorded/</id><title>Hank Ballard - Let`s Go, Let`s Go, Let`s Go (Rerecorded) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hank_Ballard/Lets_Go_Lets_Go_Lets_Go_Rerecorded/" title="Hank Ballard - Let`s Go, Let`s Go, Let`s Go (Rerecorded) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a thrill upon the hill <br>Let's go, let's a go, let's go <br>There's a thrill upon the hill <br>Let's go, let's a go, let's go <br><br>There's a house honey, way across town <br>People coming from miles around <br>Put on your pretty red dress <br>Let's go see about this mess <br>That's it, baby let's git <br>And go way far upon the hill <br><br>We're gonna have a whole lotta fun <br>We gonna greet the risin' sun <br>All night long we gonna ball <br>Until we hear yo mama call <br>That's it, baby let's git <br>And go way far upon the hill <br><br>There's a thrill upon the hill <br>Let's go, let's a go, let's go <br>There's a thrill upon the hill <br>Let's go, let's a go, let's go <br><br>Let's go <br><br>Eee yeah <br>Everybody's gonna be there <br>My friends and yours from everywhere <br>Oh, what a time it's gonna be <br>Come on baby, let's go see <br>That's it, baby let's git <br>And go way far upon the hill <br><br>There's a thrill upon the hill <br>Let's go, let's a go, let's go <br><br>There's a thrill upon the hill <br>A let's go, let's a go, let's go]]></content><category term="Hank Ballard" label="Hank Ballard"/><category term="Let`s Go, Let`s Go, Let`s Go (Rerecorded)" label="Let`s Go, Let`s Go, Let`s Go (Rerecorded)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Crystals/And_Then_He_Kissed_Me_Rerecorded/</id><title>The Crystals - And Then He Kissed Me (Rerecorded) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Crystals/And_Then_He_Kissed_Me_Rerecorded/" title="The Crystals - And Then He Kissed Me (Rerecorded) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, he walked up to me <br>And he asked me if I wanted to dance <br>He looked kinda nice <br>And so I said, I might take a chance <br><br>When he danced, he held me tight <br>And when he walked me home that night <br>All the stars were shinin' bright <br>And then he kissed me <br><br>Each time I saw him <br>I couldn't wait to see him again <br>I wanted to let him know <br>That he was more than a friend <br><br>I didn't know just what to do <br>So I whispered, I love you <br>And he said that he loved me too <br>And then he kissed me <br><br>He kissed me in a way <br>That I've never been kissed before <br>He kissed me in a way <br>That I wanna be kissed forever more <br><br>I knew that he was mine <br>So I gave him all the love that I had <br>And one day he took me home <br>To meet his mom and his dad <br><br>Then he asked me to be his bride <br>And always be right by his side <br>I felt so happy, I almost cried <br>And then he kissed me <br><br>Then he asked me to be his bride <br>And always be right by his side <br>I felt so happy, I almost cried <br>And then he kissed me, and then he kissed me <br>And then he kissed me]]></content><category term="The Crystals" label="The Crystals"/><category term="And Then He Kissed Me (Rerecorded)" label="And Then He Kissed Me (Rerecorded)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jerry_Lee_Lewis/Sweet_Little_Sixteen_Live/</id><title>Jerry Lee Lewis - Sweet Little Sixteen (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jerry_Lee_Lewis/Sweet_Little_Sixteen_Live/" title="Jerry Lee Lewis - Sweet Little Sixteen (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They're really rockin' in Boston <br>In Pittsburgh, Pa <br>Deep in the heart of Texas <br>And round the 'Frisco Bay <br>All over StLouis <br>And down in New Orleans <br>All the cats wanna dance with <br>Sweet Little Sixteen <br><br>Sweet Little Sixteen <br>She's just got to have <br>About half a million <br>Famed autographs <br>Her wallet filled with pictures <br>She gets them one by one <br>Becomes so excited <br>Watch her, look at her run <br><br>Oh Mommy, Mommy <br>Please may I go <br>It's such a sight to see <br>Somebody steal the show <br>Oh Daddy, Daddy <br>I beg of you <br>Whisper to Mommy <br>It's alright with you <br><br>'Cause they'll be rockin' on Bandstand <br>In Philadelphia, Pa <br>Deep in the heart of Texas <br>And round the 'Frisco Bay <br>All over StLouis <br>Way down in New Orleans <br>All the cats wanna dance with <br>Sweet Little Sixteen <br><br>'Cause they'll be rockin' on Bandstand <br>In Philadelphia, Pa <br>Deep in the heart of Texas <br>And round the 'Frisco Bay <br>All over StLouis <br>Way down in New Orleans <br>All the cats wanna dance with <br>Sweet Little Sixteen <br><br>Sweet Little Sixteen <br>She's got the grown up blues <br>Tight dresses and lipstick <br>She's sportin' high heel shoes <br>Oh but tomorrow morning <br>She'll have to change her trend <br>And be sweet sixteen <br>And back in class again <br><br>Well the'll be rockin' in Boston <br>Pittsburgh, Pa <br>Deep in the heart of Texas <br>And round the 'Frisco Bay <br>Way out in StLouis <br>Way down in New Orleans <br>All the cats wanna dance with <br>Sweet Little Sixteen]]></content><category term="Jerry Lee Lewis" label="Jerry Lee Lewis"/><category term="Sweet Little Sixteen (Live)" label="Sweet Little Sixteen (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joey_Dee_And_The_Starliters/Peppermint_Twist_Part1_Rerecorded/</id><title>Joey Dee And The Starliters - Peppermint Twist Part.1 (Rerecorded) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joey_Dee_And_The_Starliters/Peppermint_Twist_Part1_Rerecorded/" title="Joey Dee And The Starliters - Peppermint Twist Part.1 (Rerecorded) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Got a new dance and it goes like this <br>Hupp di da pep pep pep pep pep <br>The Name of this dance is the Peppermint Twist <br>Hupp di da pep pep pep pep pep <br>You'll like it like this <br>The Peppermint Twist <br>Hupp di da pep pep pep pep pep <br><br>'Round and 'round <br>Up and down <br><br>'Round and 'round <br>Up and down <br>It's 'round and 'round and up and down <br><br>One two three kick One two tree jump <br><br>All the girls yeah we go the twist <br>Hey Pepe <br>The Peppermint Twist <br>Do the plane the same it's the Peppermint Twist <br>Hey Pepe <br>The Peppermint Twist <br>You will what <br>What is the Peppermint Twist <br>Hey Pepe <br>The Peppermint Twist <br><br>'Round and 'round <br>Up and down <br><br>It's goes 'round and 'round <br>And up and down <br>One two tree good one ha ha ha ha <br>One two tree good one ha ha ha ha <br>One two tree good one ha ha ha ha <br>One two tree good one ha ha ha ha <br>You wanna love than do this the Peppermint Twist]]></content><category term="Joey Dee And The Starliters" label="Joey Dee And The Starliters"/><category term="Peppermint Twist Part.1 (Rerecorded)" label="Peppermint Twist Part.1 (Rerecorded)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brook_Benton/Baby_YouVe_Got_What_It_Takes_Rerecorded/</id><title>Brook Benton - Baby You`Ve Got What It Takes (Rerecorded) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brook_Benton/Baby_YouVe_Got_What_It_Takes_Rerecorded/" title="Brook Benton - Baby You`Ve Got What It Takes (Rerecorded) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well now, it takes more than a robin to make the winter go <br>And it takes two lips of fire to melt away the snow <br>Well, it takes two hearts a cookin' to make a fire grow <br>And baby, you've got what it takes <br><br>You know it takes a lot of kissin' <br>Tell me about it <br>To make a romance sweet <br>Ooh, it takes a lot of lovin' to make my life complete <br>Mmm, and it takes a lot of woman to knock me off my feet <br>And baby, you've got what it takes <br><br>I said, mmm, mmm, mmm, uh huh, mmm, mmm, mmm <br>Ah, ah, hah mmm, mmm <br>You know you've got just what it takes <br><br>Because it takes more than an effort to stay away from you <br>It'd take more than a lifetime to prove that I'll be true <br>But it takes somebody special to make me say, I do <br>Oh, yeah <br>And baby, you've got what it takes <br><br>Ah, ah, hah mmm, mmm, uh huh, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm <br>You know you've got just what it takes <br><br>Because it takes, oh yeah <br>You're back in my spot again, honey <br>I like your spot <br>To stay away from you <br>I can't stay away from you <br><br>It takes more than a lifetime, daddy <br>To prove that I'll be true <br>Now it's you <br>But it takes somebody special <br>Like me, baby <br>To make me say, I do <br>And baby, you've got what it takes <br><br>C'mon, let's play it again, huh <br>C'mon, let's do it one more time, all right <br>And baby, you've got what it takes <br><br>One more time, Brook <br>Ah ha, okay, ah ha <br>And baby, you've got what it takes]]></content><category term="Brook Benton" label="Brook Benton"/><category term="Baby You`Ve Got What It Takes (Rerecorded)" label="Baby You`Ve Got What It Takes (Rerecorded)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gladys_Knight__The_Pips/Letter_Full_Of_Tears/</id><title>Gladys Knight &amp; The Pips - Letter Full Of Tears - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:03:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:03:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gladys_Knight__The_Pips/Letter_Full_Of_Tears/" title="Gladys Knight &amp; The Pips - Letter Full Of Tears - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here comes the mailman walking up the street <br>And it looks like he has a letter today for me <br>Wait a minute let me look inside <br>No, it couldn't be from my guy <br><br>Because he, he brought me <br>I said, he, he brought me <br>A letter full of tears <br><br>I thought we had a love so strong <br>It would take a lifetime to break us apart <br>Oh yeah, but I found out today I was wrong <br>And my reward was a broken heart my my heart <br><br>Oh, here comes the teardrops <br>Welcome a welcome to my eyes <br>And I couldn't hold 'em back <br>No matter if I tried <br><br>You know it hurt me so inside <br>Won't you pardon me while I cry <br><br>Because he brought me <br>I said, he brought me <br>A letter full of tears <br><br>Those aren't drip drop tears <br>Can't you see them falling <br>I thought we had a love so strong <br>But I found, I was wrong]]></content><category term="Gladys Knight &amp; The Pips" label="Gladys Knight &amp; The Pips"/><category term="Letter Full Of Tears" label="Letter Full Of Tears"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Everly_Brothers/Walk_Right_Back_Live/</id><title>The Everly Brothers - Walk Right Back (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:04:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:04:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Everly_Brothers/Walk_Right_Back_Live/" title="The Everly Brothers - Walk Right Back (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want you to tell me why you walked out on me <br>I'm so lonesome every day <br>I want you to know that since you walked out on me <br>Nothing seems to be the same old way <br><br>Think about the love that burns within my heart for you <br>The good times we had before you went away, oh please <br>Walk right back to me this minute <br>Bring your love to me, don't send it <br>I'm so lonesome every day <br><br>I want you to tell me why you walked out on me <br>I'm so lonesome every day <br>I want you to know that since you walked out on me <br>Nothing seems to be the same old way <br><br>Think about the love that burns within my heart for you <br>The good times we had before you went away from me <br>Walk right back to me this minute <br>Bring your love to me, don't send it <br>I'm so lonesome every day]]></content><category term="The Everly Brothers" label="The Everly Brothers"/><category term="Walk Right Back (Live)" label="Walk Right Back (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Miracles/Youve_Really_Got_A_Hold_On_Me_Rerecorded/</id><title>The Miracles - You`ve Really Got A Hold On Me (Rerecorded) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:04:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:04:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Miracles/Youve_Really_Got_A_Hold_On_Me_Rerecorded/" title="The Miracles - You`ve Really Got A Hold On Me (Rerecorded) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't like you <br>But I love you <br>See that I'm always <br>Thinking of you <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>You treat me badly <br>I love you madly <br>You've really got a hold on me <br>You've really got a hold on me <br>You've really got a hold on me <br>You've really got a hold on me <br>Baby <br><br>I don't want you <br>But I need you <br>Don't want to kiss you <br>But I need you <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>You do me wring now <br>My love is strong now <br>You've really got a hold on me <br>You've really got a hold on me <br>You've really got a hold on me <br>You've really got a hold on me <br>Baby <br><br>I love you and all I want you to do <br>Is just hold me, hold me, hold me, hold me <br>Tider <br>Tider <br><br>I want to leave you <br>Don't want to stay here <br>Don't want to spend <br>Another day here <br>Oh, oh, oh, I want to split now <br>I just can quit now <br>You've really got a hold on me <br>You've really got a hold on me <br>You've really got a hold on me <br>You've really got a hold on me <br>Baby <br><br>I love you and all I want you to do <br>Is just hold me, hold me, hold me, hold me <br><br>You've really got a hold on me <br>You've really got a hold on me <br>I said You've really got a hold on me <br>You've really got a hold on me <br>You know, you've really got a holdon me]]></content><category term="The Miracles" label="The Miracles"/><category term="You`ve Really Got A Hold On Me (Rerecorded)" label="You`ve Really Got A Hold On Me (Rerecorded)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Brown/I_Got_You_I_Feel_Good_Live/</id><title>James Brown - I Got You (I Feel Good) (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:04:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:04:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Brown/I_Got_You_I_Feel_Good_Live/" title="James Brown - I Got You (I Feel Good) (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wo I feel good, I knew that I would, now <br>I feel good, I knew that I would, now <br>So good, so good, I got you <br><br>Wo I feel nice, like sugar and spice <br>I feel nice, like sugar and spice <br>So nice, so nice, I got you <br><br>When I hold you in my arms <br>I know that I can do no wrong <br>and when I hold you in my arms <br>My love won't do you no harm <br><br>and I feel nice, like sugar and spice <br>I feel nice, like sugar and spice <br>So nice, so nice, I got you <br><br>When I hold you in my arms <br>I know that I can't do no wrong <br>and when I hold you in my arms <br>My love can't do me no harm <br><br>and I feel nice, like sugar and spice <br>I feel nice, like sugar and spice <br>So nice, so nice, well I got you <br><br>Wo I feel good, I knew that I would, now <br>I feel good, I knew that I would <br>So good, so good, 'cause I got you <br>So good, so good, 'cause I got you <br>So good, so good, 'cause I got you <br><br>Hey Oh yeah a]]></content><category term="James Brown" label="James Brown"/><category term="I Got You (I Feel Good) (Live)" label="I Got You (I Feel Good) (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Drifters/Under_The_Boardwalk_Rerecorded/</id><title>The Drifters - Under The Boardwalk (Rerecorded) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:04:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:04:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Drifters/Under_The_Boardwalk_Rerecorded/" title="The Drifters - Under The Boardwalk (Rerecorded) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, when the sun beats down and burns the tar up on the roof <br>And your shoes get so hot, you wish your tired feet were fireproof <br>Under the boardwalk, down by the sea <br>On a blanket with my baby is where I'll be <br><br>Under the boardwalk Out of the sun <br>Under the boardwalk We'll be havin' some fun <br>Under the boardwalk People walking above <br>Under the boardwalk We'll be falling in love <br>Under the boardwalk, boardwalk <br><br>From the park you hear the happy sound of a carousel <br>Mmm, you can almost taste the hot dogs and French fries they sell <br>Under the boardwalk, down by the sea, yeah <br>On a blanket with my baby is where I'll be <br><br>Under the boardwalk Out of the sun <br>Under the boardwalk We'll be havin' some fun <br>Under the boardwalk People walking above <br>Under the boardwalk We'll be falling in love <br>Under the boardwalk, boardwalk <br><br>Oh, under the boardwalk, down by the sea, yeah <br>On a blanket with my baby is where I'll be <br><br>Under the boardwalk Out of the sun <br>Under the boardwalk We'll be havin' some fun <br>Under the boardwalk People walking above <br>Under the boardwalk We'll be falling in love <br>Under the boardwalk, boardwalk]]></content><category term="The Drifters" label="The Drifters"/><category term="Under The Boardwalk (Rerecorded)" label="Under The Boardwalk (Rerecorded)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Merseybeats/Wishin_And_Hopin_Rerecorded/</id><title>The Merseybeats - Wishin` And Hopin` (Rerecorded) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:04:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:04:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Merseybeats/Wishin_And_Hopin_Rerecorded/" title="The Merseybeats - Wishin` And Hopin` (Rerecorded) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wishin and hopin and thinkin and prayin <br>Plannin and dreamin each night of his charms <br>That wont get you into his arms <br>So if youre lookin to find love you can share <br>All you gotta do is <br>Hold him and kiss him and love him <br>And show him that you care <br>Show him that you care just for him <br>Do the things he likes to do <br>Wear your hair just for him cause <br>You wont get him <br>Thinkin and a prayin <br>Wishin and hopin <br>just wishin and hopin and thinkin and prayin <br>Plannin and dreamin his kiss is the start <br>That wont get you into his heart <br>So if youre thinkin how great true love is <br>All you gotta do is <br>Hold him and kiss him and squeeze him and love him <br>Yeah just do it and after you do you will be his <br>you gotta <br>Show him that you care just for him <br>Do the things he likes to do <br>Wear your hair just for him cause <br>You wont get him <br>Thinkin and a prayin <br>Wishin and hopin <br>Just wishin and hopin and thinkin and prayin <br>Plannin and dreamin his kiss is the start <br>That wont get you into his heart <br>So if youre thinkin how great true love is <br>All you gotta do is <br>Hold him and kiss him and squeeze him and love him <br>Yeah just do it and after you do you will be his <br>You will be his you will be his]]></content><category term="The Merseybeats" label="The Merseybeats"/><category term="Wishin` And Hopin` (Rerecorded)" label="Wishin` And Hopin` (Rerecorded)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Crystals/Da_Doo_Ron_Ron_Rerecorded/</id><title>The Crystals - Da Doo Ron Ron (Rerecorded) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:04:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:04:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Crystals/Da_Doo_Ron_Ron_Rerecorded/" title="The Crystals - Da Doo Ron Ron (Rerecorded) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Met him on a Monday and my heart stood still <br>Da doo ron ron ron <br>Da doo ron ron <br>Somebody told me that his name was Bill <br>Da doo ron ron ron <br>Da doo ron ron <br><br>Yes, my heart stood still <br>Yes, his name was Bill <br>And when he walked me home <br>Da doo ron ron ron <br>Da doo ron ron <br><br>Knew what he was doing when he caught my eye <br>Da doo ron ron ron <br>Da doo ron ron <br>He looked so quiet but my oh my <br>Da doo ron ron ron <br>Da doo ron ron <br><br>Yes, he caught my eye <br>Yes, my oh my <br>And when he walked me home <br>Da doo ron ron ron <br>Da doo ron ron <br><br>Picked me up at seven and he looked so fine <br>Da doo ron ron ron <br>Da doo ron ron <br>Someday soon I'm gonna make him mine <br>Da doo ron ron ron <br>Da doo ron ron <br><br>Yes, he looked so fine <br>Yes, I'll make him mine <br>And when he walked me home <br>Da doo ron ron ron <br>Da doo ron ron]]></content><category term="The Crystals" label="The Crystals"/><category term="Da Doo Ron Ron (Rerecorded)" label="Da Doo Ron Ron (Rerecorded)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marvin_Gaye/I_Heard_It_Through_The_Grapevine_Live/</id><title>Marvin Gaye - I Heard It Through The Grapevine (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:04:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:04:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marvin_Gaye/I_Heard_It_Through_The_Grapevine_Live/" title="Marvin Gaye - I Heard It Through The Grapevine (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I bet you're wonderin' how I knew <br>'Bout your plans to make me blue <br>With some other guy you knew before <br>Between the two of us guys <br>You know I loved you more <br>It took me by surprise I must say <br>When I found out yesterday <br>Don't you know that I heard it through the grapevine <br>Not much longer would you be mine <br>Oh I heard it through the grapevine <br>Oh I'm just about to lose my mind <br><br>Honey, honey yeah <br>I heard it through the grapevine <br>Not much longer would you be mine baby <br><br>I know a man ain't supposed to cry <br>But these tears I can't hold inside <br>Losin' you would end my life you see <br>'Cause you mean that much to me <br>You could have told me yourself <br>That you loved someone else <br>Instead I heard it through the grapevine <br>Not much longer would you be mine <br>Oh, I heard it through the grapevine <br>And I'm just about to lose my mind <br><br>Honey, honey yeah <br>I heard it through the grapevine <br>Not much longer would you be mine, baby <br><br>People say believe half of what you see <br>Son and none of what you hear <br>But I can't help but be confused <br>If it's true please tell me dear <br>Do you plan to let me go <br>For the other guy you loved before <br><br>Don't you know I heard it through the grapevine <br>Not much longer would you be mine, baby yeah <br>I heard it through the grapevine <br>I'm just about to lose my mind <br>Honey, honey, yeah <br>I heard it through the grapevine <br>Not much longer would you be mine, baby yeah <br><br>Honey, honey, yeah <br>I heard it through the grapevine <br>Not much longer would you be mine, baby yeah yeah <br>I heard it through the grapevine <br>Not much longer would you be mine, baby yeah yeah]]></content><category term="Marvin Gaye" label="Marvin Gaye"/><category term="I Heard It Through The Grapevine (Live)" label="I Heard It Through The Grapevine (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Samir_Badran/Vet_Att_Du_Vill_Ha_Mig_Feat_Kevin/</id><title>Samir Badran - Vet Att Du Vill Ha Mig (Feat. Kevin) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:04:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:04:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Samir_Badran/Vet_Att_Du_Vill_Ha_Mig_Feat_Kevin/" title="Samir Badran - Vet Att Du Vill Ha Mig (Feat. Kevin) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Vi har snackat ett tag <br>pa facebook appen <br>bilder pa snapchat hela natten <br>lajkat alla bilder pa instagram <br>dina vanner dem vet att <br>vi gillar varandra <br>Pratat flera timmar i telefon <br>Problemen dem startar nar <br>vi har lagt pa <br>for du vet du behover inte leka svar <br>Jag tror att du vet att <br>jag vill ha dig anda <br>Saa Baby du behover inte backa <br>For att jag ska vilja ha dig <br>vill ha dig anda <br>Jag vill ha dig anda <br>Jag vill ha dig anda <br>Jag sa baby du behover inte backa <br>for att jag ska vilja ha dig <br>vill ha dig anda <br>Jag vill ha dig anda <br>Jag vill ha dig anda <br>Saaa kan du visa <br>mig vart du star <br>Babyyyyy <br>jag vet att du vill ha mig ohhh <br>Sag babyyyy <br>jag vet att du vill ha mig <br>VaGA BARA FALLA NU <br>FALLA NU <br>VaGA BARA FALLA NU <br>Du vill inte vara forst med ett sms <br>du ar ute pa klubben sen efterfest <br>visar inget intresse <br>du tror jag ska backa <br>jag ser dina blickar <br>du gillar att stanna <br>Men du grater inombords <br>du vet inte <br>sjalv vad du tror <br>Men jag lovar dig vagar du falla <br>sa ar jag dar tar emot nar du ramlar <br>Baby du behover inte backa <br>for att jag ska vilja ha dig <br>vill ha dig anda <br>jag vill ha dig anda <br>jag vill ha dig anda <br>Jag sa baby du behover inte backa <br>for att jag ska vilja ha dig <br>vill ha dig anda <br>Jag vill ha dig anda <br>Jag vill ha dig anda <br>Sa kan du visaaaa <br>vart du star <br>Mhmm babyyy <br>jag vet att du vill ha mig <br>Ahhaa sag babyyy <br>jag vet att du vill ha mig <br>VaGA BARA FALLA NU <br>Vaga bara falla nu <br>Vaga bara falla nu <br>Snalla vaga <br>falla ha dig har dig <br>Snalla vaga <br>bara falla <br>jag vill vara med nar du ramlar <br>]]></content><category term="Samir Badran" label="Samir Badran"/><category term="Vet Att Du Vill Ha Mig (Feat. Kevin)" label="Vet Att Du Vill Ha Mig (Feat. Kevin)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이지우/걷다가도/</id><title>이지우 - 걷다가도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:04:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:04:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80%EC%9A%B0/%EA%B1%B7%EB%8B%A4%EA%B0%80%EB%8F%84/" title="이지우 - 걷다가도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 니가 없는 하루하루가 <br>어찌 흘러가는지도 몰라 <br>넌 내가 없는 하루들이 <br>아무렇지 않니 <br>난 너의 작은 습관마저도 <br>흔하지 않은 너의 <br>말투하나까지도 <br>가슴에 박혀있어 <br>이렇게 아직까지 널 그려 <br>아무래도 난 내 생각보다 <br>널 많이 사랑했나봐 <br>너 없는 것 말고 <br>달라진 게 아닌데 <br>난 사는게 사는게 아냐 <br>걷다가도 너의 기억을 찾아 <br>걷다가도 항상 난 <br>아직도 날 보던 <br>너의 눈빛과 추억이 <br>나를 떠나질 않아 <br>이럴 줄 알았더라면 <br>끝까지 널 잡았을텐데 <br>아무리 봐도 난 <br>내 생각보다 널 많이 <br>사랑했나봐 <br>너 없는 것 말고 <br>달라진 게 아닌데 <br>난 사는게 사는게 아냐 <br>우리 함께했던 모든 게 <br>의미 없이 사라지는데 <br>나마저 널 잊으면 <br>나마저 널 잊으면 <br>아무리 봐도 난 <br>내 생각보다 널 많이 <br>사랑했나봐 <br>너 없는 것 말고 <br>달라진 게 아닌데 <br>난 사는게 사는게 아냐 <br>걷다가도 너의 흔적을 <br>찾아 걷다가도 <br>]]></content><category term="이지우" label="이지우"/><category term="걷다가도" label="걷다가도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/컬스/넌_씨_눈/</id><title>컬스 - 넌 씨 눈 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:04:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:04:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BB%AC%EC%8A%A4/%EB%84%8C_%EC%94%A8_%EB%88%88/" title="컬스 - 넌 씨 눈 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Its yo boy KIRS <br>smarten up boys <br>눈치가 없는지 <br>생각도 없는지 <br>센스는 개줬니 <br>넌 씨 눈 챙겼니 <br>Monday 처럼 긴장하자 <br>foreplay <br>정신차려 각박한 세상속에 <br>오케이 여자 생각뿐인 <br>너는 뭔데 <br>근데 얘네들 생각달라 <br>그냥 꼰대 <br>남자들아 눈치를 어쨌니 <br>여자들이 눈치주면 못보니 <br>전신거울 집안에다 못두니 <br>잡지안에 나온 답도 <br>보면서 못 고치니 <br>고쳐 떠나가기전에 번쩍 <br>달래줘 자꾸 단답하면 <br>여잔 빡쳐 <br>붙잡어 피곤하다 해도 <br>그냥 잡고 <br>해달라는대로 해주면 넌 <br>healing doctor <br>넌 씨 눈 시키는대로 그냥해 <br>넌 씨 눈 이길수 없어 포기해 <br>넌 씨 눈 사랑한다고 말만해 <br>넌 씨 눈 니들은 눈치가 필요해 <br>너는 씨알 눈치가 없네 넌 씨 눈 <br>너는 씨알 눈치가 없네 넌 씨 눈 <br>넌 씨 눈 너는 씨알 눈치가 없네 <br>넌 씨 눈 너는 씨알 눈치가 없네 <br>넌 씨 눈 너는 씨알 눈치가 없네 <br>넌 씨 눈 너는 씨알 눈치가 없네 <br>차려놓은 밥상도 못 먹어 <br>앞에 놓인 수저 하나 못 들어 <br>잘 들어 이 세상은 안바껴 <br>금수저 아니면 니들 <br>두손을 다 벌려 <br>눈치가 발바닥 이라면 <br>니들 발곱 <br>내 여친은 난 괜찮데 <br>이제 발톱 <br>눈치가 형사라면 니들 병자 <br>내가 너희 기소할게 <br>이제 난 검사 <br>a yo 눈치를 사 먹고 <br>돌아 다닌거니 <br>a yo 개밥주다 개념도 <br>줘버렸니 <br>눈을 떠야 떡 이라도 얻어먹지 <br>모든해야 답 이라도 알아내지 <br>넌 씨 눈 시키는대로 그냥해 <br>넌 씨 눈 이길수 없어 포기해 <br>넌 씨 눈 사랑한다고 말만해 <br>넌 씨 눈 니들은 눈치가 필요해 <br>너는 씨알 눈치가 없네 넌 씨 눈 <br>너는 씨알 눈치가 없네 넌 씨 눈 <br>넌 씨 눈 너는 씨알 눈치가 없네 <br>넌 씨 눈 너는 씨알 눈치가 없네 <br>넌 씨 눈 너는 씨알 눈치가 없네 <br>넌 씨 눈 너는 씨알 눈치가 없네 <br>]]></content><category term="컬스" label="컬스"/><category term="넌 씨 눈" label="넌 씨 눈"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/컬스/Fake_Feat_DAMI/</id><title>컬스 - Fake (Feat. DAMI) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:04:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:04:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BB%AC%EC%8A%A4/Fake_Feat_DAMI/" title="컬스 - Fake (Feat. DAMI) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 모를거야 아무 것도 몰라 <br>그냥 화도 안나 <br>우린 멀어지나봐 <br>넌 모를거야 사랑해서 그래 <br>그냥 화도 안나 <br>우린 헤어지나봐 <br>I I 키 작으면 난 Lose <br>너 너 보이는게 좋은 Poser <br>너 너 계산 안 할거면 <br>밖에 나가 <br>어쩌면 니 코는 <br>내가 세운거야 <br>환경을 생각하길 바래 <br>Recycle <br>세상이 힘들다고 <br>Survival <br>어딜가도 너가 <br>아까워 보인다고 <br>그래 이쁘지만 <br>내 스탈도 아니라고 <br>근데 왜 너 친구말에 <br>흔들리는데 <br>걔네들은 신경쓰지 <br>않아도 돼 <br>세상이 아닌 다른 <br>사람들이 미쳤나봐 <br>왜 가짜가 진짜를 찾는걸까 <br>넌 모를거야 아무 것도 몰라 <br>그냥 화도 안나 <br>우린 멀어지나봐 <br>넌 모를거야 사랑해서 그래 <br>그냥 화도 안나 <br>우린 헤어지나봐 <br>썸 탈 땐 너무 좋데 <br>Full make up <br>섬 들어갔다 오면 <br>No make up <br>정말 넌 사기치네 <br>Who are you <br>오늘도 츄리닝 차림 <br>WHO A U <br>I don’t know baby yo <br>모르겠다 <br>나도 변했지만 <br>넌 다른 사람같아 <br>처음엔 그런거 <br>싫어하는 여자라고 <br>다른 여자들과는 <br>정말 다르다고 <br>근데 왜 너 친구말에 <br>흔들리는데 <br>개내들은 신경쓰지 <br>않아도 돼 <br>세상이 아닌 다른 <br>사람들이 미쳤나봐 <br>왜 가짜가 진짜를 찾는걸까 <br>넌 모를거야 아무 것도 몰라 <br>그냥 화도 안나 <br>우린 멀어지나봐 <br>넌 모를거야 사랑해서 그래 <br>그냥 화도 안나 <br>우린 헤어지나봐 <br>Yo 보기보다는 달라 <br>You are a liar <br>볼 때는 C <br>ayo 진짜는 A <br>지금부터 너 가식은 yo <br>적당히 해 <br>다음을 위해 처음부터 <br>이젠 솔직해야 해 <br>Ayo shorty do you know <br>who I’m banging today <br>might be you or your sister <br>but you got nothing to say <br>이 말이 뭔지 모르면서 <br>왜케 고르는데 <br>먼저 너 자신에게 <br>솔직해 지길 바래 <br>hey <br>You so fake <br>You fake <br>You so fake <br>Fake <br>you so fake <br>]]></content><category term="컬스" label="컬스"/><category term="Fake (Feat. DAMI)" label="Fake (Feat. DAMI)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/컬스/Hook/</id><title>컬스 - Hook - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:04:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:04:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BB%AC%EC%8A%A4/Hook/" title="컬스 - Hook - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Its yo boy KIRS baby <br>Hook Hook 들어가 Hook <br>Hook 너도 모르게 <br>들어가 Hook <br>Hook Hook 나도 <br>모르게 Hook Hook <br>언제왔네 미치겠네 Hook <br>Hook <br>let me get it in this mother uh uh <br>Hook 들어가는 나를 봐라 <br>Hook 들어가도 너는 몰라 <br>니 밥그릇 지키고 싶으면 <br>가서 연습해라 <br>uh Rapper들 그냥 so so <br>니들 형한테 까불다가 <br>다쳐 no no <br>get a good look 랩과 <br>flow를 보고 <br>KIRS swag 배운다면 <br>맞았네 loco <br>yo ayo what’s up <br>ayo you be messing <br>with that real veteran dude <br>and you know I don’t listen to <br>you <br>싱글들을 드럽게 계속 내도 <br>yo 다들 깝치다 내가 들어가 Hook <br>what you know bout HIP HOP <br>내 맘대로 들어가 Hook <br>I don’t mess wit lil suckas <br>Hook Hook 들어가 Hook <br>Hook 너도 모르게 들어가 Hook <br>Hook Hook 나도 모르게 Hook Hook <br>언제왔네 미치겠네 Hook <br>Hook Hook 들어가네 <br>Hook Hook 아무도 모르게 <br>Hook Hook 언제왔네 <br>Hook Hook 미치겠네 <br>and you know <br>맨날 음악이 똑같해 uh huh <br>돈 벌라고 음악하는 애들 uh huh <br>그래서 얼마를 모았는데 uh huh <br>그 정도론 절대 안돼 HA HA <br>oh yea you don’t know me <br>유명하지 않은데 <br>왜 나만 우뚝서니 <br>yo it aint funny yo if it its <br>money <br>옆에서 hook 들어갈텐데 <br>왜 뒤만보니 <br>욕하기 바쁠 땐 언제고 <br>이제와서 붙어대니 <br>고향이 그립네 <br>내 총은 어디있니 <br>그대로 깝쳐 여긴 <br>미국이 아니니 <br>나 진짜 처음이자 <br>마지막으로 말할테니 <br>추방당하게 하지마 <br>내가 변할테니 <br>yo 다들 깝치다 <br>나 들어가 hook <br>HIP HOP <br>내 맘대로 들어가 hook <br>I don’t mess wit lil suckas <br>Hook Hook 들어가 Hook <br>Hook 너도 모르게 들어가 Hook <br>Hook Hook 나도 모르게 Hook Hook <br>언제왔네 미치겠네 Hook <br>Hook Hook 들어가네 <br>Hook Hook 아무도 모르게 <br>Hook Hook 언제왔네 <br>Hook Hook 미치겠네 <br>check it <br>Imma bang that chick <br>and yo other chick <br>cause yo shorties <br>they be on my thick <br>now go and watch out fellas <br>we be realer than Manilla <br>till we remember <br>Nice Brothers we forever <br>Yo All these rappers wack <br>come on and make bet <br>so that I can make a stack <br>like yo mama fat <br>if you don’t get it oh well <br>so sad oh damn <br>Here we go again <br>KIRS ignorant again <br>Yo I aint messing <br>wit these kids no more <br>No squares in my circle <br>ya heard <br>Hook Hook 들어가 Hook <br>Hook 너도 모르게 들어가 Hook <br>Hook Hook 나도 모르게 Hook Hook <br>언제왔네 미치겠네 Hook <br>Hook Hook 들어가네 <br>Hook Hook 아무도 모르게 <br>Hook Hook 언제왔네 <br>Hook Hook 미치겠네 <br>]]></content><category term="컬스" label="컬스"/><category term="Hook" label="Hook"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/컬스/DC_Feat_DJ_RizOne/</id><title>컬스 - D.C. (Feat. DJ RizOne) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:04:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:04:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BB%AC%EC%8A%A4/DC_Feat_DJ_RizOne/" title="컬스 - D.C. (Feat. DJ RizOne) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nice Beatz <br>In the 80’s baby <br>I’m an 80’s baby <br>it’s the hip hop <br>hip hop <br>it’s the hip hop <br>hip hop <br>In the 80’s baby <br>I’m an 80’s baby <br>요즘 어린 꼬맹이들이 <br>모르는 얘기 <br>ha its a wonderful story <br>호랑이들도 담배피던 <br>시절 일 때지 <br>yea uh 니들 아니 서태지 <br>매일 들어 테이프가 <br>쭉 늘어 질 때지 <br>Nike and Jordan shoes <br>got me crazy <br>KIRS 미국에서 <br>좀 놀았을 때 baby <br>아빠가 ghetto에서 <br>총 맞았어 <br>Bang 맞고 미쳤는지 <br>우릴 떠났어 <br>가족보다 친구가 <br>중요하다고 생각했어 <br>공부보단 Gang이 <br>멋있는 줄 알았어 <br>니들은 몰라 94 <br>게임기 Nintendo <br>44 or pretty thick hoes <br>내 학교는 80% <br>검은 Pixel <br>2%만 이슬 좋아하는 <br>노랭이들 HIP HOP <br>In the 80’s baby <br>I’m an 80’s baby <br>its the hip hop hip hop <br>its the hip hop hip hop <br>DC에서 올라가네 <br>New York city <br>나랑 Logos 생각하면 <br>we some locos <br>쇳 덩어리 들고 <br>다니던 Hot 97 <br>하나님이 날 <br>지켜보나봐 heaven <br>Baltimore에서 악마의 Party <br>너무 미치게 논 <br>놈은 심장마비 <br>But can’t nobody be <br>high as I be <br>Come and feel the high <br>and you’ll like me <br>내 사랑 Hip Hop <br>태어난곳 east coast <br>내 첫 사랑 태어난곳 <br>east coast <br>내 첫 키스도 <br>물론 east coast <br>but 내 첫 여자 <br>경험은 대한민국 <br>그땐 나랑 형님들만 <br>문신 있었을 때 <br>삐삐차고 돌아 다녔을 때 <br>97년도쯤에 가출 했을 때 <br>교포 남자들이 <br>여자한테 인기 <br>많을 때 그립네 <br>In the 80’s baby <br>Im an 80’s baby <br>It’s the hip hop hip hop <br>It’s the hip hop hip hop <br>Yea yea you know <br>I got it going on <br>Yea yea bitches know <br>I got it going on <br>MD to DC we got it going on <br>Seoul city baby <br>we got it going on <br>Nice Brotherz baby <br>we got it going on <br>Nice Beatz baby <br>we got it going on <br>KIRS baby yea <br>I got it going on <br>Can’t nobody stop us <br>we got it going on <br>Its the Hip Hop <br>IT THE 80’s BABY <br>Im a THE 80’s BABY <br>Yea it’s the hip hop <br>and you know and you know <br>IT THE 80’s BABY <br>Im a THE 80’s BABY <br>Yea it’s the hip hop <br>and you know and you know <br>]]></content><category term="컬스" label="컬스"/><category term="D.C. (Feat. DJ RizOne)" label="D.C. (Feat. DJ RizOne)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ABC/The_Look_Of_Love_Acoustic/</id><title>ABC - The Look Of Love (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:05:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:05:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ABC/The_Look_Of_Love_Acoustic/" title="ABC - The Look Of Love (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When your world is full of strange arrangements <br>and gravity won't pull you through <br>you know you're missing out on something <br>well that something depends on you <br>All I'm saying it takes a lot to love you <br>all I'm doing you know it's true <br>all I mean now there's one thing <br>yes one thing that turns this grey sky to blue <br><br>That's the look that's the look the look of love <br>that's the look that's the look the look of love <br>that's the look that's the look the look of love <br><br>When your girl has left you out on the pavement Goodbye <br>Then your dreams fall apart at the seams <br>Your reason for living's your reason for leaving <br>Don't ask me what it means <br>Who got the look I don't know the answer to that question <br>Where's the look If I knew I would tell you <br>What's the look Look for your information <br>Yes there's one thing the one thing that still holds true <br>What's that <br><br>That's the look that's the look the look of love <br>that's the look that's the look the look of love <br>that's the look that's the look the look of love <br><br>That's the look that's the look the look of love <br>that's the look that's the look the look of love <br>that's the look that's the look the look of love <br><br>If you judge a book by the cover <br>Then you judge the look by the lover <br>I hope you'll soon recover <br>Me I go from one extreme to another <br><br>And all my friends just might ask me <br>They say 'Martin, maybe, one day you'll find true love' <br>And I say 'Maybe, there must be a solution to <br>The one thing, the one thing, we can't find' <br><br>That's the look that's the look, Sisters and Bothers <br>that's the look that's the look, should help each other <br>that's the look that's the look, oh, oh, oh <br>Heavens above <br>That's the look that's the look, hip hip hooray, ay <br>that's the look that's the look, yippee ai yippee aiay <br>that's the look that's the look, be lucky in love <br>Look of love]]></content><category term="ABC" label="ABC"/><category term="The Look Of Love (Acoustic)" label="The Look Of Love (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ABC/Viva_Love_Acoustic/</id><title>ABC - Viva Love (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:05:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:05:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ABC/Viva_Love_Acoustic/" title="ABC - Viva Love (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You think the world will melt if you whistle <br>There's a certain spring in your stride <br>You face the future like a heat seeking missile <br>You've got yourself a smile a mile wide <br><br>Yes, you have <br><br>Viva love <br>Viva love, viva love, viva love <br>Viva love <br>Viva, viva <br>Viva love <br><br>When lightning strikes you don't look for shelter <br>You're floating free, gravity defied <br>It's hell for leather on a helter skelter <br>Just steel your nerves for a bright white knuckle ride <br><br>Viva love <br>Viva love, viva love, viva love <br>Viva love <br>Viva, viva <br>Viva love <br>Viva love, viva love, viva love <br>Viva love <br>Viva, viva <br>Viva love <br><br>In the battle of the sexes <br>Victory's denied <br>I'm charging your tanks <br>With slingshots and knives <br><br>My troops they retreat <br>And run for their lives <br>I'm facing defeat <br>But somehow love survives <br><br>Viva love <br>Viva love, viva love, viva love <br>Viva love <br>Viva, viva <br>Viva love <br>Viva love, viva love, viva love <br>Viva love <br>Viva, viva <br>Viva love <br><br>Viva love]]></content><category term="ABC" label="ABC"/><category term="Viva Love (Acoustic)" label="Viva Love (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ABC/The_Love_Inside_The_Love_Acoustic/</id><title>ABC - The Love Inside The Love (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:05:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:05:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ABC/The_Love_Inside_The_Love_Acoustic/" title="ABC - The Love Inside The Love (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[More than mad infatuation <br>Much more than mutual attraction <br>Yes, it's all our own creation <br>On a road to satisfaction <br><br>Life keeps revealing <br>A deeper deeper feeling <br>Between you and me <br>Through the years we get to see <br><br>The love inside, the love inside <br>The love inside the love inside the love <br>The love inside, the love inside <br>The love inside the love inside the love <br><br>This world was once a kinder place <br>We'd welcome love in time and space <br>We walked as Gods in a state of grace <br>A smile on your face <br><br>Life keeps revealing <br>A deeper deeper meaning <br>Between you and me <br>Through the years we get to see <br><br>The love inside, the love inside <br>The love inside the love inside the love <br>The love inside, the love inside <br>The love inside the love inside the love <br><br>Take a left at heartache <br>Carry on three blocks <br>Then a right to all the emotions you conceal <br>At the river, take a right then a left then a right <br>To all the things you refuse to feel <br>Across the railway tracks <br>A journey for the soul <br>Avoid the sacks <br>But there you'll find your gold <br>Buried beethere the plastic bags <br>In a box inside a box <br>Inside a box <br><br>The love inside, the love inside <br>The love inside the love inside the love <br>The love inside, the love inside <br>The love inside the love inside the love]]></content><category term="ABC" label="ABC"/><category term="The Love Inside The Love (Acoustic)" label="The Love Inside The Love (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Margaret/Cool_Me_Down_Acoustic/</id><title>Margaret - Cool Me Down (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:05:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:05:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Margaret/Cool_Me_Down_Acoustic/" title="Margaret - Cool Me Down (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ready aim and fire your gun <br>Nothing can cool me down <br>Wine on Venus is hot like the sun <br>Wow nothing can cool me down <br>Got my high stilettos on fleek <br>Nothing can cool me down <br>See the shadows dancing on me <br>No nothing can cool me down <br>And before the night is over <br>Imma light a spark <br>and let the crazy out <br>I'm your goddess on your knees <br>Down down down down <br>down down down <br>I'm hotter than a fire <br>Water can't cool me down <br>Water can't cool me down <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>I'm dancing like flames <br>And nothing can cool me down <br>Watch me I run this town <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>No water can't cool me <br>Down down down down <br>down down down <br>Dow dow dow <br>There's no need to call 911 <br>Nothing can cool me down <br>If you do you spoiling the fun <br>Wow nothing can cool me down <br>And before you're begging please <br>Imma light a spark <br>and let the crazy out <br>I'm your goddess on your knees <br>Down down down down <br>down down down <br>I'm hotter than a fire <br>Water can't cool me down <br>Water can't cool me down <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>I'm dancing like flames <br>And nothing can cool me down <br>Watch me I run this town <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>No water can't cool me <br>Down down down down <br>down down down <br>Dow dow dow <br>No water can't cool me <br>Down down down down <br>down down down <br>I love the way you want it <br>Come get it like you own it <br>Yeah yeah <br>we blaze even brighter <br>When being two <br>I'm hotter than a fire <br>Water can't cool me down <br>Water can't cool me down <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>I'm dancing like flames <br>And nothing can cool me down <br>Watch me I run this town <br>I'm hotter than a fire <br>Water can't cool me down <br>Water can't cool me down <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>No water can't cool me <br>Down down down down <br>down down down <br>Dow dow dow <br>No water can't cool me <br>Down down down down <br>down down down <br>Dow dow dow <br>No water can't cool me <br>Down down down down <br>down down down <br>Dow dow dow <br>No water can't cool me <br>Down down down down <br>down down down <br>Down down down down <br>down down down <br>Down down down down <br>down down down down <br>]]></content><category term="Margaret" label="Margaret"/><category term="Cool Me Down (Acoustic)" label="Cool Me Down (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KPoint/Pamela/</id><title>KPoint - Pamela - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:05:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:05:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KPoint/Pamela/" title="KPoint - Pamela - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh <br>Oh, oh, oh, oh <br>Zombie donc gestu' de cadavre <br>Oh, oh, oh <br><br>J'suis defonce derriere les Casals <br>Zombie, donc gestu' de cadavre <br>La tentation t'a mis le cadenas <br>Maintenant ton ame est en cavale <br>T'as assez suce, maintenant avale <br>T'ecoutes mon son direct tu shazames <br>J'ecoute ce qu'il s'fait direct je <br>J'ai plus d'une cartouche dans le <br><br>Pamela, Pamela, Pamela Anderson, Pamela <br>Ton rappeur est refait comme Pamela <br><br>Chaque ceau mor est un Kameha <br>Sang royal coule dans mes veines <br>Co cocaine coule dans les tiennes <br>Leur projet, bon pour la benne <br>Dans les bails bres som, on est clairs <br>Je detruis tout comme le feu de Hephaistos <br>Nos cicatrices ont fait l'histoire <br>C'est la se cri, on fait avec <br>J'ai catalogue le rap, il m'fait la tete <br>Tu Wanda sur moi, mais c'est quoi gars <br>J'fais ce que j'veux gros, j'ai v'la l'ecart <br>Rien que tu Wanda, rien qu'tu Wanda <br>Roi du 37, rien ne l'arretera <br><br>Pamela, Pamela, Pamela Anderson, Pamela <br>Ton rappeur est refait comme Pamela <br>De mauvaise humeur quand j'ai Pamela <br>Pamela, Pamela, Pamela, Pamela, Pamela Anderson <br>J'ai crash sur la se fe de Pamela <br>Pamela, Pamela, Pamela <br>Pamela, Pamela, Pamela <br>Anderson Pamela <br>Ton rappeur est refait comme Pamela <br>De mauvaise humeur quand j'ai Pamela <br>Pamela, Pamela, Pamela <br>Pamela, Pamela Anderson <br>J'ai crash sur la se fe de Pamela Pamela, Pamela <br><br>Mon accent vous l'avait neglige <br>On va tout remettre au clair, tout rediger <br>La couronne, j'en suis l'heritier <br>T'as mon respect, tu l'as merite <br>J'tourne pas le dos a la verite <br>J'retourne pas ma veste, tu peux verifier <br>Mes yeux refletent ma serenite <br>J'laisserai pas negro me deguiser <br>Ferme ta gueule et pense <br>Mon savoir, c'est mon arme blanche <br>La mort s'vend, elle est blanche <br>La femme et la nuit sont blanches <br>J'veux tout graille, gros j'ai la dalle <br>Kpoint est la, passe a la table <br>Pour les boug qui m'ecoutent au placard <br>Jamais pose genou sur l'asphalte <br>Dans mon hood comme dans Walking Dead <br>Resbi, c'est dans Walt Disney <br>La tete enfoncee dans l'appui tete <br>Fantome embraye fait passer les vitesses <br>Jeune negro keus' qui s'en bat les couilles <br>Quelques inegalites dans les fouilles <br>Deux doigts dans la chatte, un dans le huuh <br>Dans Anderson Pamela, la puta <br><br>Pamela, Pamela, Pamela Anderson, Pamela <br>Ton rappeur est refait comme Pamela <br>De mauvaise humeur quand j'ai Pamela <br>Pamela, Pamela, Pamela, Pamela, Pamela Anderson <br>J'ai crash sur la se fe de Pamela <br>Pamela, Pamela, Pamela <br>Pamela, Pamela, Pamela <br>Anderson Pamela <br>Ton rappeur est refait comme Pamela <br>De mauvaise humeur quand j'ai Pamela <br>Pamela, Pamela, Pamela <br>Pamela, Pamela Anderson <br>J'ai crash sur la se fe de Pamela Pamela, Pamela]]></content><category term="KPoint" label="KPoint"/><category term="Pamela" label="Pamela"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신용재_포맨/그대라서_Inst/</id><title>신용재 (포맨) - 그대라서 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:05:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:05:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9A%A9%EC%9E%AC_%ED%8F%AC%EB%A7%A8/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%9D%BC%EC%84%9C_Inst/" title="신용재 (포맨) - 그대라서 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈 내리는 밤거리를 <br>함께 걷는 이 순간 <br>눈 내리는 하얀 밤을 <br>함께 있는 이 순간 <br>따뜻하게 포근하게 <br>그댈 안아주고 싶어 <br>이 겨울이 따뜻한 건 오 그대라서 <br>한걸음 더 또 한걸음 더 <br>다가갈게요 <br>내 마음이 행복한 건 오 그대라서 <br>사랑해요 또 사랑해요 그댈 Woo <br>어느새 지나간 겨울이 <br>또 다시 우릴 찾아오듯 <br>난 언제나 난 영원히 <br>그댈 사랑할게요 <br>밤하늘이 반짝이는 건 <br>오 그대라서 <br>한걸음 더 또 한걸음 더 <br>다가갈게요 <br>내 마음이 행복한 건 오 그대라서 <br>사랑해요 또 사랑해요 <br>그대를 영원히 <br>]]></content><category term="신용재 (포맨)" label="신용재 (포맨)"/><category term="그대라서 (Inst.)" label="그대라서 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Amity_Affliction/All_Messed_Up_Acoustic/</id><title>The Amity Affliction - All Messed Up (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:05:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:05:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Amity_Affliction/All_Messed_Up_Acoustic/" title="The Amity Affliction - All Messed Up (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I wake up I'm thankful I slept through the night <br>Cause that is the only time I feel alright <br>Keep my eyes closed so I sleep the sadness away <br>When I wake up I'm sure that it won't be the same <br><br>All the panic, depression, the hurt and regret <br>Lying to myself I don't think of death <br>All the ups all the downs, all the petty concerns <br>My whole world's imploding I can't find the words <br>Cause the truth is I'm messed up <br><br>The truth is that I'm all messed up like you <br>Yeah we're all messed up it's true <br>The truth is that I'm all messed up like you <br>Yeah we're all messed up it's true <br>And the truth is they don't hear the words we say <br>Yeah they all just turn away <br>The truth is they don't hear the words we say <br>Yeah they all just turn away <br><br>If I wake up tomorrow just know that I tried <br>To find a way out without saying goodbye <br><br>All the panic, depression, the hurt and regret <br>Lying to myself I don't think of death <br>All the ups all the downs, all the petty concerns <br>My whole world's imploding, I can't find the words <br>Cause the truth is I'm messed up <br><br>The truth is that I'm all messed up like you <br>Yeah we're all messed up it's true <br>The truth is that I'm all messed up like you <br>Yeah we're all messed up it's true <br>And the truth is they don't hear the words we say <br>Yeah they all just turn away <br>The truth is they don't hear the words we say <br>Yeah they all just turn away <br><br>Will you save my life <br>Or just say goodbye <br>Will you save my life <br>Or just say goodbye <br>Will you save my life <br>Or just say goodbye <br>Will you save my life <br>Or just say goodbye]]></content><category term="The Amity Affliction" label="The Amity Affliction"/><category term="All Messed Up (Acoustic)" label="All Messed Up (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marracash/Senza_Dio_RMX_Feat_Luche/</id><title>Marracash - Senza Dio (RMX) (Feat. Luche) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:05:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:05:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marracash/Senza_Dio_RMX_Feat_Luche/" title="Marracash - Senza Dio (RMX) (Feat. Luche) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Gue Pequeno, Marracash, puta que pariu <br><br>Sono solo un altro senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Sono solo un altro anch'io <br>Sono solo un altro senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Sono solo un altro <br>Sono solo un altro senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Sono solo un altro anch'io <br>Sono solo un altro senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Sono solo un altro <br><br>Sono un santo delinquente, Jesus Malverde <br>Col pendente al collo e di reato pendente <br>Sono ancora tutto intero <br>Ora prego non siano dietro <br>Non ci sono atei dove si rischia davvero <br>Il mio verso e Vangelo, servo la messa in camera <br>Ho smarrito il sentiero ma ho preso la panoramica <br>Mi chiedo se c'ho ancora un po' di anima <br>Se me lo chiedo ho ancora un po' di anima <br>I miei eroi son morti, i miei nemici sono forti <br>Leggo preghiere sulle schiene di balordi <br>Sto tra poveri diavoli e ricchi miracoli <br>Il giocatore esperto gioca sempre su piu tavoli <br>La trinita era un duo <br>Passa il 500 sotto luce fluo <br>Venga il mio regno, non il suo <br>Alla mia morte, fra', so che mi attende un altro inferno <br>Lei ingoia la mia storia triste e dopo ingoia il resto <br>Perche <br><br>Sono solo un altro senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Sono solo un altro anch'io <br>Sono solo un altro senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Sono solo un altro <br>Sono solo un altro senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Sono solo un altro anch'io <br>Sono solo un altro senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Sono solo un altro <br><br>Sul telefono il dramma, l'applicazione sgama <br>Nelle vicinanze qua nessuno che mi ama <br>Con il cuore spinato <br>L'odio che ho respirato <br>Mi avvicino a Lui, quei tempi in cui i giorni sono bui <br>Dopo mi succede <br>Che sta gente mi fa perdere ogni fede <br>La tua ragazza crede <br>Che io non sappia cosa faccia per la coca <br>Sta a ruota <br>E tu sei Giuda Iscariota <br>Chiedimi cos'e che nella vita non ho fatto <br>Ho provato tutto tranne il cazzo <br>Ma non ho mai pregato <br>Non ho mai fregato un fratello <br>Per il grano cash caramello <br>Illuminati in blu da un Cristo al neon <br>Un viso triste, si, non ti avevo mai visto il neo <br>Dalla lira all'euro ancora ventimila in tasca <br>E se mi paghi passo da una religione all'altra <br><br>Illusione, delusione, collusione <br>Illusione, delusione, collusione <br><br>Sono solo un altro senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Sono solo un altro anch'io <br>Sono solo un altro senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Sono solo un altro <br>Sono solo un altro senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Sono solo un altro anch'io <br>Sono solo un altro senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Senza Dio <br>Sono solo un altro <br><br>Non ho tempo per segnarti sul mio calendario <br>Il tuo stato e d'emergenza fra il mio stato e leggendario <br>Non puoi capirmi tu non sei della mia razza <br>Senza Dio ma con Cristo e padre Pio in ogni piazza <br>Guardi le vetrine tu vuoi essere alla moda <br>Io le guardavo per contare i buchi di pistola <br>Sei in alto ordino la tua caduta <br>Se, se dico bucagli la nuca e il Vangelo secondo Luca <br>Ho visto la tua ragazza, io la voglio per forza <br>Ho visto tutti 'sti gioielli e li voglio per forza <br>Spari nella folla poi saltiamo sulla moto <br>Brucio soldi, brucio tappe, brucio la sua foto <br>E sono un senza Dio, ieri ho perso un amico <br>E mo' suo figlio e diventato mio figlio, see <br>E io lo vizio con cose firmate <br>Ho lo stigmate ovvero le mani bucate <br><br>Jesus e italiano <br>Porque acha que e Deus <br>Porque pensa que a mae e vergin <br>E com 33 anos vive ainda com os pais <br>Gesu e italiano <br>Perche si sente un Dio <br>Perche pensa che sua madre e vergine e a 33 anni vive ancora con i suoi genitori]]></content><category term="Marracash" label="Marracash"/><category term="Senza Dio (RMX) (Feat. Luche)" label="Senza Dio (RMX) (Feat. Luche)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marracash/Purdi_RMX_Feat_Fabri_Fibra/</id><title>Marracash - Purdi (RMX) (Feat. Fabri Fibra) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:05:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:05:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marracash/Purdi_RMX_Feat_Fabri_Fibra/" title="Marracash - Purdi (RMX) (Feat. Fabri Fibra) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Non faccio il purista <br>Pero di gente che pur di star <br>Pur di far la star, ce n'e un'assurdita <br>Questo paese fra e il Purdistan <br>Mi sono svegliato che era il medioevo <br>Non ci resta che piangere <br>La tua pagina e il museo del tuo ego <br>Con la musica a margine <br>Quanto rido con i post che fai <br>Strappalacrime, strappa like <br>Tra un link al tubo e uno a Spotify <br>E un petto nudo alla Sporty Spice <br>Senza aver mai fatto una canna parli anche di droga e riabilitazione Sei serio <br>Pero c'e di peggio, chi si droga per dirlo dentro le canzoni no comment <br>Dici talmente cazzate che secondo me qua tra poco ti candidi <br>Con un bicchiere di capacita diluito in un mare di marketing <br>Finto impegnato, musica che non richiede l'impegno all'ascolto, il colmo <br>Se ti crescesse un cazzo li su non farebbe di te un unicorno <br>Babbo <br><br>Pur di attirare l'attenzione <br>Cambieresti sesso, cambieresti religione <br>Pur di, ti venderesti la madre <br>E ormai sei piu di la che di qua <br><br>Oh, ah, facce balla <br>Facce sballa Ahahah <br>Ah <br><br>Non voglio dissare nessuno <br>Il dissing non va piu di moda <br>Dovrei fare un corso di yoga <br>E tingermi i capelli viola <br>Non voglio fare quello che Parla parla <br>In macchina mica ascolto Panda, Panda <br>La jolla che brucia, dici Passa, passa <br>Nelle cuffie c'e Santeria Alza, alza <br>Alle donne se sei un VIP <br>Gli fai fare cio che vuoi <br>Ho pippato con Lou Reed <br>Ho scopato con Naomi <br>Non saprei cosa aggiungere a questo argomento <br>Il mondo sa come la penso <br>Tutti vogliono fare successo, io pure <br>Politicamente scorretto <br>Non capisci la svolta <br>Coi soldi del rap ci pagavo l'affitto <br>Questa roba scotta come il nero nascosto nel contro soffitto <br>Raga sto per uscire col disco <br>Non immagini quello che ho scritto <br>Ogni evento si incastra preciso <br>Ora cantiamo tutti l'inciso <br><br>Pur di attirare l'attenzione <br>Cambieresti sesso, cambieresti religione <br>Pur di, ti venderesti la madre <br>E ormai sei piu di la che di qua <br><br>Dimmi dimmi per la fama cosa sei disposto a fare <br>Quanto puoi scavare, pur di <br><br>I soldi non dormono mai <br>Chiamami Gordon Guekko <br>Quindi se mi paghi rappo <br>Ma sai qual e l'unica cosa che lecco <br>Conosco un milione di tipe bro tipo l'ex moglie di Tyson <br>Che pur di far soldi ti fanno morire come fanno i pusher col taglio <br>Non contano piu le canzoni, ma se le bambine fanno gli acquazzoni <br>Le tue uniche poche erezioni le hai quando fai le visualizzazioni <br>Pur di stare nelle news, uccideresti per fare piu views <br>Morti di fama, morti di follower, molti sui social raccontano frottole <br>Pur di restare in pista 'sta gente l'ho vista fingersi artista <br>Opinionista, pure attivista, quanto mi rattrista il tuo insta <br>Tu ti suicidi se non ti confermano <br>Muori se spengo lo schermo 'mo <br>E se pensi che venda il transgender <br>Tu te lo tagli come Caitlyn Jenner <br><br>Pur di attirare l'attenzione <br>Cambieresti sesso, cambieresti religione <br>Pur di, ti venderesti la madre <br>E ormai sei piu di la che di qua <br><br>Ripensando ai tempi della scuola quando eri un mito <br>Come sei finito, pur di <br><br>La vita non e fatta di quello che guadagni <br>Ma soprattutto di cio che perdi <br>Pur di stare sulla barca annegheresti gli altri <br>E ora non hai piu a fianco fratelli <br><br>Pur di attirare l'attenzione <br>Cambieresti sesso, cambieresti religione <br>Pur di, ti venderesti la madre <br>E ormai sei piu di la che di qua <br>Pur di attirare l'attenzione <br>Cambieresti sesso, cambieresti religione <br>Pur di, ti venderesti la madre <br>E ormai sei piu di la che di qua]]></content><category term="Marracash" label="Marracash"/><category term="Purdi (RMX) (Feat. Fabri Fibra)" label="Purdi (RMX) (Feat. Fabri Fibra)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marracash/Scooteroni_RMX_Feat_Sfera_Ebbasta/</id><title>Marracash - Scooteroni (RMX) (Feat. Sfera Ebbasta) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:05:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:05:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marracash/Scooteroni_RMX_Feat_Sfera_Ebbasta/" title="Marracash - Scooteroni (RMX) (Feat. Sfera Ebbasta) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, Milano <br>Coppia di campioni, coppa dei campioni <br>Vrooom vrooom <br>Scooteroni <br>Scoo scoo scoo scooteroni <br><br>Dentro i marsupi di Gucci hanno quattro telefoni <br>E la medicina Yah <br>A uno come te dovrebbero proibire internet <br>Come in Cina Yah <br>E addosso una figa sicuro <br>Se lo sto cercando e non trovo il mio cap Yah <br>Tu smetti di scrivere, smetti di vivere, se ti sequestro l'iPad <br><br>Vrooom vrooom scooteroni <br>Scoo scooteroni <br>Vrooom scooteroni <br>Scoo scooteroni <br>Sgaso sopra di te, rispetta i campioni <br>Vrooom vrooom scooteroni <br>Scoo scooteroni <br><br>In Barona, fra, dove sto, mi hanno dato la baronia <br>Ho una mia Maria Salvador che e di Salvador di Bahia <br>e piu sprint di Higuain, piu street cred di Creed <br>In posti della tua citta dove non sei mai stato tu che sei di li <br>Non sono di strada, io sono la strada <br>Quindi attento ad attraversarmi <br>Vedendo poi quanto e profondo il tuo impatto sul mondo <br>Tua madre poteva ingoiarti <br>50 al dettaglio, 70 di taglio <br>Saldi, soldi da Silicon Valley <br>Il lupo si veste da pecora, frate, mi vesto dagli stessi sarti <br>G dalle buone maniere, Maniero <br>Si mi son fatto di tutto, mai ero <br>Puntello a Piazza Tirana che sembra di stare a Tirana davvero <br>King Marracash, sofisticato, Hermann Hesse <br>H di Hermes nella cinta <br>Ho cosi palle che fra potrei mettere incinta una tipa gia incinta <br><br>Dentro i marsupi di Gucci hanno quattro telefoni <br>E la medicina <br>A uno come te dovrebbero proibire internet <br>Come in Cina <br>E addosso una figa sicuro <br>Se lo sto cercando e non trovo il mio cap <br>Tu smetti di scrivere, smetti di vivere, se ti sequestro l'iPad <br><br>Vrooom vrooom scooteroni <br>Scoo scooteroni <br>Vrooom scooteroni <br>Scoo scooteroni <br>Sgaso sopra di te, rispetta i campioni <br>Vrooom vrooom scooteroni <br>Scoo scooteroni <br><br>G capo dei capi, vai in tachicardia per la rima <br>La tua tipa mi prende per via orale bro come la Tachipirina <br>Tu ti fai un colpo, io faccio un golpe <br>Il flow e sulla luna <br>Per questo cammino per strada in moonwalker <br>Veni vidi vici, Muse Beatrici son pute meretrici <br>Gratta sperando che vinci, King G <br>Spingi finche il bilanciere vola <br>Omozigota gemella <br>Che mi sbarella sul zzoca, Eva Herzigova <br>Giu dalla Bosnia Erzegovina <br>Donne importate, piu di un cognome importante <br>Mega impennate, 'sta vita che ti fa pensare in piccolo <br>Frate sei grande <br>Fossi un cartello sarei Sinaloa <br>Sto sulla street, Constrictor Boa <br>La merce da Mauri e i contanti da Salvo <br>Per fare cash programmati da cyborg <br>Babbo con te non mi aggrego <br>Duri un minuto come con McGregor <br>Ritorna la G, si festeggia l'avvento mo <br>Sparando da sopra un'Aventador <br><br>Dentro i marsupi di Gucci hanno quattro telefoni <br>E la medicina Yah <br>A uno come te dovrebbero proibire internet <br>Come in Cina Yah <br>E addosso una figa sicuro <br>Se lo sto cercando e non trovo il mio cap Yah <br>Tu smetti di scrivere, smetti di vivere, se ti sequestro l'iPad <br><br>Vrooom vrooom scooteroni <br>Scoo scooteroni <br>Vrooom scooteroni <br>Scoo scooteroni <br>Sgaso sopra di te, rispetta i campioni <br>Vrooom vrooom scooteroni <br>Scoo scooteroni <br><br>Billion Headz Money Gang <br>Gang <br><br>Fumo ganja olandese Hey <br>Senza uscire dal mio quartiere Yah <br>Usain Bolt certe sere Hey <br>Quattro secondi da quelle sirene Yah <br>Uuhh, Uuuhhh <br>Nel locale mandaci da bere Bu, bu <br>O manda i tuoi amici se non ti sta bene Yah <br>Per mano va bene, le buste nei Booster <br>Fra in tre sugli scooter T Max, lei mi trova bello <br>Fulvio Testi, 180 in sorpasso Vrooom <br>Tu su un motorello <br>In quattro ore uno stipendio intero <br>Stampa il sorriso in faccia a mio fratello <br>In quattro ore, si, un mazzetto intero <br>Stampa il sorriso in faccia a mio fratello, yaaah <br>Yaaahh]]></content><category term="Marracash" label="Marracash"/><category term="Scooteroni (RMX) (Feat. Sfera Ebbasta)" label="Scooteroni (RMX) (Feat. Sfera Ebbasta)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marracash/Piazza_Rossa/</id><title>Marracash - Piazza Rossa - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:05:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:05:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marracash/Piazza_Rossa/" title="Marracash - Piazza Rossa - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Alla nostra, urlo come il quadro alla mostra <br>Questa vodka vale quel che costa <br>Con l'ansia nella borsa <br>Freddo nelle ossa come a Mosca <br>Piazza rossa, Piazza rossa <br>Alla nostra, a una notte che andrebbe rimossa <br>Una storia dentro a una piu grossa come una matrioska <br>Freddo nelle ossa come a Mosca <br>Piazza rossa, Piazza rossa <br><br>La vita e una troia ed e breve <br>La strofa e per te la scrivo sulla neve <br>Perche sei fredda come l'Antartide <br>Una replicante come Blade Runner <br>Perche sei fredda come il sashimi <br>I tuoi occhi freddi come assassini <br>I miei occhi rossi sotto questo parka <br>Rotto dall'asma, ossigeno al plasma <br>Perche sei fredda come l'Alaska <br>Vorrei rubarti come Vallanzasca <br>Tu sei un piranha nella mia vasca <br>Fredda la canna puntata in testa <br>Io che impazzisco vengo internato <br>Rime ghiacciato vengo ibernato <br>Siamo Sub Zero come Mortal Kombat <br>C'e solo il gelo che ci circonda <br><br>Alla nostra, urlo come il quadro alla mostra <br>Questa vodka vale quel che costa <br>Con l'ansia nella borsa <br>Freddo nelle ossa come a Mosca <br>Piazza rossa, Piazza rossa <br>Alla nostra, a una notte che andrebbe rimossa <br>Una storia dentro a una piu grossa come una matrioska <br>Freddo nelle ossa come a Mosca <br>Piazza rossa, Piazza rossa <br><br>Il mio cuore e ormai di pietra come quel cartello appeso a bar di Bruno <br>Che alla fine per colpa di pochi non si fa piu credito a nessuno <br>Lei dorme truccata come se nei sogni spera di incontrare uno <br>La capisco, sono un uomo oscuro, un uomo che proietta ombre al buio <br>E ho solo scambi da cui sganciarmi con uno schiocco di dita <br>La donna giusta rende duro il tuo cazzo, non la tua cazzo di vita <br>Cercavi una persona onesta, beh, ne e pieno al metro la mattina <br>Piu grosso questo mal di testa, beh, piu grossa sara l'aspirina, quindi <br><br>Alla nostra, urlo come il quadro alla mostra <br>Questa vodka vale quel che costa <br>Con l'ansia nella borsa <br>Freddo nelle ossa come a Mosca <br>Piazza rossa, Piazza rossa <br>Alla nostra, a una notte che andrebbe rimossa <br>Una storia dentro a una piu grossa come una matrioska <br>Freddo nelle ossa come a Mosca <br>Piazza rossa, Piazza rossa <br><br>Una canzone triste suona soltanto per me <br>La pace non esiste cerco soltanto un perche <br>Ma non sai che freddo fa <br>Che fredda e la realta <br>Dio c'e ma non e qua]]></content><category term="Marracash" label="Marracash"/><category term="Piazza Rossa" label="Piazza Rossa"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marracash/Cahmere/</id><title>Marracash - Ca$hmere - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:06:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:06:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marracash/Cahmere/" title="Marracash - Ca$hmere - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Marra Gue <br>Dogozilla Empire <br>Cashmere <br>Cash mere <br><br>Ero gia Young Pope prima di Jude Law <br>Un metro e novanta di rime e di flow <br>Gli amici che ho, gli amici che ho <br>Supercriminali, siamo Suicide Squad <br>Bella e Cara come Hadid e Delevingne <br>Non ha dentro un cazzo a parte il mio na mean <br>Montagne di coca fanno fiumi di <br>Euro, euro la mia vita, Euro Disney <br>Compro oro piu di un Compro Oro <br>Tu cambia lavoro che ti vedo giu <br>Che di questo passo fra li fai a sessanta <br>Quando il cazzo non ti tira piu <br>Ci scambiamo questa Wanda Nara <br>Che si scopa quelli della stessa squadra <br>Spendo, spendo come una puttana <br>Che il mio portafogli scappera di casa <br><br>Penso a 500mila euro fa <br>Ho giocato bene, quindi level up <br>Senti il materiale e dici Serieta <br>Faccio altre due serie, niente ferie fra <br>Cashmere nell'armadio, cash alla roulette <br>Lei col culo che non entra nei Balmain <br><br>Cashmere Cashmere <br>Cashmere, cashmere, cashmere <br>Cashmere Cashmere <br>Cashmere, cashmere, cashmere <br><br>Fratello mio, anche un milione e iniziato da uno <br>Sono leggenda frate come Zelda <br>Cavalco una zebra, Guepek papi chulo <br>Sotto 'ste Nike c'e solo l'inferno <br>Sopra di me c'e solo il paradiso <br>Il flow e garanzia frate senza l'avviso <br>Innamorato di me e me, Narciso <br>E c'ho una tipa che e un'opera d'arte <br>Tipo Monnalisa, solo piu figa <br>Darling, io penso solo a dei modi per farli <br>E poi metterli dentro una Platino VISA <br>Non ho pieta frate se sei Caino <br>Giro con vari sicari schizzati che sembra che han la cocaina <br>Dentro al barattolo di proteina <br>Quante persone mantengo <br>Tu non capisci, dai gioca al Nintendo <br>Che sei un junior, Boca <br>E quando parli di me devi sciacquarti la bocca <br>Oggi e arrivata 'sta qua dalle Hawaii <br>Bravo, tu tienimi un po' il suo chihuahua <br>Mentre la bombo in una suite allo Ushuaia <br>I miei fra col metallo piu di Tom Araya <br><br>Penso a 500mila euro fa <br>Ho giocato bene, quindi level up <br>Senti il materiale e dici Serieta <br>Faccio altre due serie, niente ferie fra <br>Cashmere nell'armadio, cash alla roulette <br>Lei col culo che non entra nei Balmain <br><br>Cashmere Cashmere <br>Cashmere, cashmere, cashmere <br>Cashmere Cashmere <br>Cashmere, cashmere, cashmere <br><br>Marra cashmere, Guepek <br>Yeah Santeria, cashmere everything]]></content><category term="Marracash" label="Marracash"/><category term="Ca$hmere" label="Ca$hmere"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marracash/Ninja/</id><title>Marracash - Ninja - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:06:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:06:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marracash/Ninja/" title="Marracash - Ninja - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[La mia strada e maestra, l'asfalto palestra <br>Come un dojo le Gescal, qui che doso la mesca <br>Siamo ombre sui tetti di un impero finito <br>Sono solo interessi, non c'e amico o nemico <br>No valori, non piu <br>Noi ronin senza shogun <br>Con la M di money in fronte come Majin Bu <br>Il disprezzo e in eterno, il mio polso e piu fermo <br>Giro lame all'interno, organi di ogni governo <br>Senza fare rumori sveglio la verita <br>C'ho una lista di nomi come Arya Stark <br>Da come rispondi gia prevedo dei guai <br>Tu da come li conti io so gia come li fai <br>Fango per questi schiavi e sangue per chi fa il bandito <br>Cio che sporca le mani rende il lavoro pulito <br>Sbuffo soffio del drago <br>Grosso guaio a Milano <br>Ora sai cosa siamo <br>Mostrami cio che hai imparato <br><br>Ehi brotha <br>Saro la tua via e la tua spada <br>Come la tua ombra in strada <br>Tu sei nel mio clan, clan, clan <br>Clan, clan, clan <br>Oh mama <br>Ora che ti sei addestrata <br>Pronta per il brrr ratatata <br>Lotta per il clan, clan, clan <br>Siam, siam, siam <br><br>Ninja, ninja, ninja <br>Ninja, ninja, ninja <br>Ninja, ninja, ninja <br>Ninja, ninja, ninja <br><br>Siamo nati per far sempre l'alba <br>Per non trovare calma <br>La vita vera e farla, no parla parla <br>Nel fumo denso nel silenzio io mi muovo svelto <br>Se non alzi il mento vai sul pavimento <br>E poi sarai scomparso in gabbia con due sacchi di sabbia <br>Tu confida in me <br>Come Don Pablo con La Quica <br>e il mondo dei grandi <br>La strada si tinge, e scarlatta <br>Non c'e pace, non c'e Mahatma Gandhi <br>Siamo affiliati nella stessa family <br>Se si scaldano gli animi siamo affilati <br>La mia tecnica e shinobi <br>Rima poetica, cammino al buio <br>Il cuore e avvolto dai rovi <br>E qua non accettiamo tradimenti, se stai con me non menti <br>Controllo gli elementi <br>La terra sotto i piedi se ti manca <br>Il fuoco quando hai freddo nella stanza <br>L'acqua se avrai sete e questa aria <br><br>Ehi brotha <br>Saro la tua via e la tua spada <br>Come la tua ombra in strada <br>Tu sei nel mio clan, clan, clan <br>Clan, clan, clan <br>Oh mama <br>Ora che ti sei addestrata <br>Pronta per il brrr ratatata <br>Lotta per il clan, clan, clan <br>Siam, siam, siam <br><br>Ninja, ninja, ninja <br>Ninja, ninja, ninja <br>Ninja, ninja, ninja <br>Ninja, ninja, ninja]]></content><category term="Marracash" label="Marracash"/><category term="Ninja" label="Ninja"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stephanie_Rainey/100_Like_Me_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>Stephanie Rainey - 100 Like Me (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:06:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:06:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stephanie_Rainey/100_Like_Me_Acoustic_Ver/" title="Stephanie Rainey - 100 Like Me (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I hide it when I try to speak <br>She holds me like a dog on a leash <br>I'm running <br>she won't let me breathe <br>If I'm honest <br>she's making me cold <br>A demon she's stripping my soul <br>I'm feeling the people see <br>but nobody knows <br>There must be another hundred <br>like me <br>There must be another hundred <br>like me <br>There must be another hundred <br>like me <br>Tell me tell me tell me <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>An army won't keep her away <br>Who are we without all the pain <br>She's bringing me down <br>but I can get back up <br>A mirror that holds all the cracks <br>I've asked it <br>but it won't talk back <br>I'm feeling people only see <br>what I lack <br>There must be another hundred <br>like me <br>There must be another hundred <br>like me <br>There must be another hundred <br>like me <br>Tell me tell me tell me <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>oh oh oh oh oh <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>oh oh oh oh oh <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>oh oh oh oh oh <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>oh oh oh oh oh <br>I'm not the only one <br>There must be another hundred <br>like me <br>There must be another hundred <br>like me <br>There must be another hundred <br>like me <br>Tell me tell me tell me <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>]]></content><category term="Stephanie Rainey" label="Stephanie Rainey"/><category term="100 Like Me (Acoustic Ver.)" label="100 Like Me (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stephanie_Rainey/100_Like_Me/</id><title>Stephanie Rainey - 100 Like Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:06:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:06:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stephanie_Rainey/100_Like_Me/" title="Stephanie Rainey - 100 Like Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I hide it when I try to speak <br>She holds me like a dog on a leash <br>I'm running she won't let me breathe <br>If I'm honest she's making me cold <br>A demon she's stripping my soul <br>I'm feeling the people see <br>but nobody knows <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>There must be another <br>hundred like me oh oh oh <br>There must be another <br>hundred like me oh oh oh <br>There must be another <br>hundred like me <br>Tell me tell me tell me <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>An army won't keep her away <br>Who are we without all the pain <br>She's bringing me down <br>but I can get back up <br>A mirror that holds all the cracks <br>I've asked it but it won't talk back <br>I'm feeling people <br>only see what I lack <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>There must be another <br>hundred like me oh oh oh <br>There must be another <br>hundred like me oh oh oh <br>There must be another <br>hundred like me <br>Tell me tell me tell me <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>oh oh oh oh oh <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>oh oh oh oh oh <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>oh oh oh oh oh <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>oh oh oh oh oh <br>I'm not the only one <br>There must be another <br>hundred like me oh oh oh <br>There must be another <br>hundred like me oh oh oh <br>There must be another <br>hundred like me <br>Tell me tell me tell me <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>I'm not the only one hiding <br>]]></content><category term="Stephanie Rainey" label="Stephanie Rainey"/><category term="100 Like Me" label="100 Like Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스윗빈/파닥파닥파파닥/</id><title>스윗빈 - 파닥파닥파파닥 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:06:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:06:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%EC%9C%97%EB%B9%88/%ED%8C%8C%EB%8B%A5%ED%8C%8C%EB%8B%A5%ED%8C%8C%ED%8C%8C%EB%8B%A5/" title="스윗빈 - 파닥파닥파파닥 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꽁냥 꽁냥 꽁냥 꽁냥 <br>막 이래 <br>귓속이 막이래 <br>가슴이 콩닥콩닥 <br>퐁당 퐁당 퐁당 퐁당 <br>막 이래 <br>니가 던진 멘트가 <br>내 맘속에 쑉 <br>파닥파닥 <br>벌써 난 낚였어 <br>이미 난 틀렸어 <br>영혼이 빠졌어 <br>삐뽀삐뽀 <br>너에게 뿅 갔어 <br>답도 없이 너만 생각나 <br>너는 나의 꽁냥이 <br>콩닥이 퐁당이 <br>나는 너의 파닥이 <br>파닥 파닥 파파닥 <br>핫둘 핫둘 핫둘 핫둘 <br>막 이래 <br>널 따라 막이래 <br>심장이 쿵쾅쿵쾅 <br>뒤뚱 뒤뚱 뒤뚱 뒤뚱 <br>막 이래 <br>날보고 놀려대는 <br>니 어깨에 <br>툭다다 툭탁툭 <br>깡총깡총 <br>어떡해 귀여워 <br>강아지 같은 너 <br>푸들이 같은 너 <br>우쮸쮸쮸 <br>널 보면 내 눈이 <br>반짝반짝 반짝이가 돼 <br>너는 나의 꽁냥이 <br>콩닥이 퐁당이 <br>나는 너의 파닥이 <br>파닥파닥 파파닥 <br>너의 손을 잡으니 <br>영화 속 판타지 <br>소곤소곤 살며시 <br>속삭여줄래 <br>너는 나의 꽁냥이 <br>콩닥이 퐁당이 <br>나는 너의 파닥이 <br>파닥 파닥 파파닥 <br>너는 나의 꽁냥이 <br>콩닥이 퐁당이 <br>나는 너의 파닥이 <br>파닥 파닥 파파닥 <br>파닥 파닥 파파닥 <br>]]></content><category term="스윗빈" label="스윗빈"/><category term="파닥파닥파파닥" label="파닥파닥파파닥"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스윗빈/알람/</id><title>스윗빈 - 알람 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:06:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:06:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%EC%9C%97%EB%B9%88/%EC%95%8C%EB%9E%8C/" title="스윗빈 - 알람 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지금은 그대가 일어날 시간 <br>살짝 눈을 떠요 <br>조금은 일어나기 힘들어도 <br>기지개를 켜요 <br>알아요 조금 더 자고 싶은 맘 <br>나도 그런걸요 <br>그래도 그대를 깨워주는 게 <br>나의 일이에요 <br>아직 해도 안 떴는데 <br>하루는 시작되고 <br>늦은 밤까지 그대 <br>오늘도 바쁘겠지만 <br>나 언제나 그대 곁에 있을게요 <br>날 믿고 오늘도 힘차게 보내요 <br>그대 잠든 모습 보면 <br>너무나 지쳐 보여 <br>조금 더 잘 수 있게 <br>놔두고 싶긴 하지만 <br>나 언제나 그대 곁에 있을게요 <br>날 믿고 오늘도 힘차게 보내요 <br>나 그대가 행복하기를 바래요 <br>날 믿고 오늘도 힘차게 보내요 <br>그대를 믿어요 <br>이제 일어나요 <br>]]></content><category term="스윗빈" label="스윗빈"/><category term="알람" label="알람"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스윗빈/슈퍼_히어로_Super_Hero/</id><title>스윗빈 - 슈퍼 히어로 (Super Hero) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:06:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:06:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%EC%9C%97%EB%B9%88/%EC%8A%88%ED%8D%BC_%ED%9E%88%EC%96%B4%EB%A1%9C_Super_Hero/" title="스윗빈 - 슈퍼 히어로 (Super Hero) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어릴 적 날 꿈꾸게 하던 <br>슈퍼 히어로들 <br>그런 건 어린 시간 속 <br>상상 같았는데 <br>이렇게 시간이 흐른 후에도 <br>나는 여전히 <br>초능력 슈퍼 히어로가 넘 좋아 <br>맘대로 하늘을 날아서 <br>어디든 여행 하고 <br>나쁜 일 하는 악당 잡아서 <br>혼도 내주고 <br>이 별 저 별 자유롭게 <br>다니며 멋진 <br>일들 많이 많이 하고 싶은 <br>나의 이름은 <br>오 슈퍼히어로 <br>예쁘고 힘도 쌘 <br>난 슈퍼 히어로가 <br>되보고 싶어 <br>초능력 에너지 <br>머리도 똑똑한 <br>멋있는 슈퍼히어로 <br>Let's be the one <br>더 높은 하늘로 올라가 <br>더 멀리 바라보고 <br>나쁜 주문 거는 마법사들 <br>혼도 내주고 <br>이곳 저곳 자유롭게 <br>다니며 멋진 <br>일들 많이 많이 하고 있는 <br>나의 이름은 <br>오 슈퍼히어로 <br>예쁘고 힘도 쌘 <br>난 슈퍼 히어로가 <br>되보고 싶어 <br>초능력 에너지 <br>머리도 똑똑한 <br>멋있는 슈퍼히어로 <br>Let's be the one <br>달빛의 염원으로 <br>태양의 희망으로 <br>바다와 대지 위의 <br>모든 힘을 모아서 <br>널 용서치 않아 <br>lampas benediction <br>오 슈퍼히어로 <br>예쁘고 힘도 쌘 <br>난 슈퍼 히어로가 <br>되보고 싶어 <br>초능력 에너지 <br>머리도 똑똑한 <br>멋있는 슈퍼히어로 <br>슈퍼 히어로 <br>오 슈퍼히어로 <br>예쁘고 힘도 쌘 <br>난 슈퍼 히어로가 <br>되보고 싶어 <br>초능력 에너지 <br>머리도 똑똑한 <br>멋있는 슈퍼히어로 <br>Let's be the one <br>]]></content><category term="스윗빈" label="스윗빈"/><category term="슈퍼 히어로 (Super Hero)" label="슈퍼 히어로 (Super Hero)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/두아들/나_믿노라_Solo_김규남/</id><title>두아들 - 나 믿노라 (Solo 김규남) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:06:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:06:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%91%90%EC%95%84%EB%93%A4/%EB%82%98_%EB%AF%BF%EB%85%B8%EB%9D%BC_Solo_%EA%B9%80%EA%B7%9C%EB%82%A8/" title="두아들 - 나 믿노라 (Solo 김규남) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그 참혹한 십자가에 <br>주 달려 흘린 피 <br>샘물같이 늘 흘러서 <br>내 죄 씻어주시네 <br>값 없이 주신 그 은혜 <br>나 어찌 갚으리 <br>십자가 사랑 대속의 은혜 <br>나를 살리셨네 <br>나 믿노라 <br>나 믿노라 <br>보혈의 공로 <br>나 믿노라 <br>나 믿노라 <br>주 날 구했네 <br>온 백성의 죄사하신 <br>하나님 어린양 <br>우리를 향한 영원한 사랑 <br>이제 나 전하리 <br>예수의 보혈 능력 있네 <br>예수 피 믿으오 <br>할렐루야 찬양하세 <br>우릴 구원한 그 이름 <br>오직 예수 <br>나 믿노라 <br>나 믿노라 <br>보혈의 공로 <br>나 믿노라 <br>나 믿노라 <br>주 날 구했네 <br>믿노라 <br>나 믿노라 <br>보혈의 공로 <br>나 믿노라 <br>나 믿노라 <br>주 날 구했네 <br>우릴 구원했네 <br>우릴 구원했네 <br>나 믿노라 <br>]]></content><category term="두아들" label="두아들"/><category term="나 믿노라 (Solo 김규남)" label="나 믿노라 (Solo 김규남)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/두아들/그_어디나_하늘나라_Solo_김규남/</id><title>두아들 - 그 어디나 하늘나라 (Solo 김규남) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:06:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:06:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%91%90%EC%95%84%EB%93%A4/%EA%B7%B8_%EC%96%B4%EB%94%94%EB%82%98_%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98%EB%82%98%EB%9D%BC_Solo_%EA%B9%80%EA%B7%9C%EB%82%A8/" title="두아들 - 그 어디나 하늘나라 (Solo 김규남) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 영혼이 은총입어 <br>중한 죄짐 벗고 보니 <br>슬픔 많은 이 세상도 <br>천국으로 화하도다 <br>할렐루야 찬양하세 <br>내 모든 죄 사함 받고 <br>주 예수와 동행하니 <br>그 어디나 하늘나라 <br>주의 얼굴 뵙기 전에 <br>멀리 뵈던 하늘나라 <br>내 맘 속에 이뤄지니 <br>날로 날로 가깝도다 <br>할렐루야 찬양하세 <br>내 모든 죄 사함 받고 <br>주 예수와 동행하니 <br>그 어디나 하늘나라 <br>높은 산이 거친들이 <br>초막이나 궁궐이나 <br>내 주 예수 모신 곳이 <br>그 어디나 하늘나라 <br>할렐루야 찬양하세 <br>내 모든 죄 사함 받고 <br>주 예수와 동행하니 <br>그 어디나 하늘나라 <br>]]></content><category term="두아들" label="두아들"/><category term="그 어디나 하늘나라 (Solo 김규남)" label="그 어디나 하늘나라 (Solo 김규남)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/두아들/가장_귀한_선물/</id><title>두아들 - 가장 귀한 선물 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:06:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:06:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%91%90%EC%95%84%EB%93%A4/%EA%B0%80%EC%9E%A5_%EA%B7%80%ED%95%9C_%EC%84%A0%EB%AC%BC/" title="두아들 - 가장 귀한 선물 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대 나를 바라보아요 <br>나의 손을 잡아요 <br>하나님의 사랑 속에서 <br>우리 영원히 함께해요 <br>아름다운 나의 그대여 <br>웃음 지어보아요 <br>꿈만 같은 일이 내 앞에 <br>지금 펼쳐지고 있네요 <br>사랑해요 <br>우리 잡은 두손 이제는 <br>영원히 놓치 말아야 해요 <br>주님이 주신 <br>나의 가장 귀한 선물 <br>바로 당신이에요 <br>힘겨운 시련이 몰려와도 <br>우리는 이겨낼 수 있죠 <br>서로를 향한 믿음 <br>주님의 약속 <br>함께 바라보면서 <br>사랑해요 <br>우리 잡은 두손 이제는 <br>영원히 놓치 말아야 해요 <br>주님이 주신 <br>나의 가장 귀한 선물 <br>바로 당신이에요 <br>바로 당신이에요 <br>]]></content><category term="두아들" label="두아들"/><category term="가장 귀한 선물" label="가장 귀한 선물"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/두아들/광야에_외치는_자의_소리/</id><title>두아들 - 광야에 외치는 자의 소리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:06:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:06:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%91%90%EC%95%84%EB%93%A4/%EA%B4%91%EC%95%BC%EC%97%90_%EC%99%B8%EC%B9%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%9E%90%EC%9D%98_%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC/" title="두아들 - 광야에 외치는 자의 소리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[광야에 외치는 자의 <br>소리가 있어 <br>가로되 너희는 <br>주의 길을 예비하라 <br>그의 첩경을 평탄케 하라 <br>모든 골짜기 메워지고 <br>모든 산들이 낮아지고 <br>굽은 것이 곧아지고 <br>험한 길 평탄해 질 것이라 <br>모든 육체가 하나님의 <br>구원하심을 보리라 <br>모든 육체가 하나님의 <br>구원하심을 보리라 <br>광야에 외치는 자의 <br>소리가 있어 <br>가로되 너희는 <br>주의 길을 예비하라 <br>그의 첩경을 평탄케 하라 <br>모든 골짜기 메워지고 <br>모든 산들이 낮아지고 <br>굽은 것이 곧아지고 <br>험한 길 평탄해 질 것이라 <br>모든 육체가 하나님의 <br>구원하심을 보리라 <br>모든 육체가 하나님의 <br>구원하심을 보리라 <br>모든 육체가 하나님의 <br>구원하심을 보리라 <br>모든 육체가 하나님의 <br>구원하심을 보리라 <br>보리라 <br>]]></content><category term="두아들" label="두아들"/><category term="광야에 외치는 자의 소리" label="광야에 외치는 자의 소리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리치케이/니가_스며든_밤/</id><title>리치케이 - 니가 스며든 밤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:07:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:07:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EC%B9%98%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4/%EB%8B%88%EA%B0%80_%EC%8A%A4%EB%A9%B0%EB%93%A0_%EB%B0%A4/" title="리치케이 - 니가 스며든 밤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그냥 그냥 당연한 듯 <br>니가 생각이나 잠 못 이루는 밤 <br>저 달빛에 젖어 난 기억에 젖어 <br>소리 없는 눈물만 날 위로해 <br>이 밤 이 밤이 지나면 <br>내일은 잊을까 너와 한 시간들 <br>흐르는 눈물에 내리는 기억에 <br>나도 모르게 녹아 내릴까 <br>니가 생각나 매일 <br>그냥 이러다 말겠지 <br>이별이 다 그렇잖아 <br>또 참다 보면 지울 수 있을까 <br>사랑이 그게 뭐라고 <br>난 하루하루 미쳐가 <br>그게 뭔데 Oh <br>오늘 오늘이 지나면 <br>잊혀져 있을까 이미 끝난 사랑 <br>흐르는 시간에 모든 기억 싣고 <br>멀리 떠나 보낼 순 없을까 <br>니가 생각나 매일 <br>그냥 이러다 말겠지 <br>이별이 다 그렇잖아 <br>또 참다 보면 지울 수 있을까 <br>사랑이 그게 뭐라고 <br>난 하루하루 미쳐가 <br>그게 뭔데 Oh <br>그까짓 게 뭐라고 <br>이렇게도 이렇게도 아플까 <br>이별 후엔 왜 이래 <br>좋았던 그때 그 기억들만 떠올라 <br>자꾸 이러면 어떻게 잊어 <br>말처럼 쉽지 않잖아 <br>다 잊을 수 가 없잖아 <br>니가 생각나 매일 <br>그냥 이러다 말겠지 <br>이별이 다 그렇잖아 <br>또 참다 보면 지울 수 있을까 <br>사랑이 그게 뭐라고 <br>난 하루하루 미쳐가 <br>그게 뭔데 <br>]]></content><category term="리치케이" label="리치케이"/><category term="니가 스며든 밤" label="니가 스며든 밤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아이노스_밴드_Ainos_Band/His_Name/</id><title>아이노스 밴드 (Ainos Band) - His Name - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:07:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:07:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8%EC%8A%A4_%EB%B0%B4%EB%93%9C_Ainos_Band/His_Name/" title="아이노스 밴드 (Ainos Band) - His Name - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[His name His name <br>His name His name <br>네 모든 슬픔을 <br>주님께 다 맡기라 <br>네 모든 염려를 <br>주님께 다 맡기라 <br>주가 너의 곁에서 <br>너를 지켜주시며 <br>네게 새 힘 늘 주시리라 <br>내 모든 슬픔을 <br>주님께 다 맡기리 <br>내 모든 염려를 <br>주님께 다 맡기리 <br>주가 나의 곁에서 <br>나를 지켜주시며 <br>내게 새 힘 늘 주시리라 <br>His name His name <br>이 세상의 소망이요 <br>His name His name <br>또 천국의 기쁨이라 <br>거룩한 주 이름 <br>나의 방패삼고서 <br>환란 시험 당할 때 <br>기도하리 <br>주가 나의 곁에서 <br>나를 지켜주시며 <br>내게 새 힘 늘 주시리라 <br>His name His name <br>이 세상의 소망이요 <br>His name His name <br>또 천국의 기쁨이라 <br>내 모든 슬픔들 <br>기쁨의 춤이 되었네 <br>주의 놀라운 사랑 <br>내게 소망주시네 <br>Precious name <br>O how sweet <br>Joy of earth and heaven <br>I believe in you <br>Precious name <br>O how sweet <br>Joy of earth and heaven <br>I believe in you <br>Precious name <br>O how sweet <br>Joy of earth and heaven <br>I believe in you <br>Precious name <br>O how sweet <br>Joy of earth and heaven <br>I believe in you <br>Precious name <br>O how sweet <br>Joy of earth and heaven <br>I believe in you <br>Precious name <br>O how sweet <br>Joy of earth and heaven <br>I believe in you <br>Precious name <br>O how sweet <br>Joy of earth and heaven <br>I believe in you <br>Precious name <br>O how sweet <br>Joy of earth and heaven <br>I believe in you <br>Jesus Jesus <br>이 세상의 소망이요 <br>Jesus Jesus <br>또 천국의 기쁨이라 <br>예수의 Jesus 이름은 Jesus <br>이 세상의 소망이요 <br>예수의 Jesus 이름은 Jesus <br>또 천국의 기쁨이라 <br>또 천국의 기쁨이라 <br>우리의 기쁨이라 <br>예수의 이름은 <br>세상의 소망이요 <br>예수의 이름은 <br>천국의 기쁨이라 <br>예수의 이름은 <br>세상의 소망이요 <br>예수의 이름은 <br>천국의 기쁨이라 <br>Rejoice Rejoice <br>Rejoice Rejoice <br>His name <br>]]></content><category term="아이노스 밴드 (Ainos Band)" label="아이노스 밴드 (Ainos Band)"/><category term="His Name" label="His Name"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아이노스_밴드_Ainos_Band/나의_죄를_씻기는/</id><title>아이노스 밴드 (Ainos Band) - 나의 죄를 씻기는 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:07:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:07:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8%EC%8A%A4_%EB%B0%B4%EB%93%9C_Ainos_Band/%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%A3%84%EB%A5%BC_%EC%94%BB%EA%B8%B0%EB%8A%94/" title="아이노스 밴드 (Ainos Band) - 나의 죄를 씻기는 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[예수의 흘린 피 <br>날 희게 하오니 <br>귀하고 귀하다 <br>예수의 피밖에 없네 <br>나의 죄를 씻기는 <br>예수의 피밖에 없네 <br>다시 정케 하기도 <br>예수의 피밖에 없네 <br>예수의 흘린 피 <br>날 희게 하오니 <br>귀하고 귀하다 <br>예수의 피밖에 없네 <br>나를 정케 하기도 <br>예수의 피밖에 없네 <br>사죄하는 증거도 <br>예수의 피밖에 없네 <br>예수의 흘린 피 <br>날 희게 하오니 <br>귀하고 귀하다 <br>예수의 피밖에 없네 <br>예수의 피 <br>날 희게 하오니 <br>귀하고 귀하다 <br>예수의 피 <br>날 희게 하오니 <br>귀하고 귀하다 <br>예수의 피 예수의 피 <br>예수의 피 예수의 피 <br>예수의 피 예수의 피 <br>예수의 피 예수의 피 <br>예수의 피 예수의 피 <br>예수의 피 예수의 피 <br>예수의 피 <br>날 희게 하오니 <br>귀하고 귀하다 <br>예수의 피 <br>날 희게 하오니 <br>귀하고 귀하다 <br>예수의 피 <br>날 희게 하오니 <br>귀하고 귀하다 <br>예수의 피 <br>날 희게 하오니 <br>귀하고 귀하다 <br>예수의 피 <br>날 희게 하오니 <br>귀하고 귀하다 <br>예수의 피 <br>날 희게 하오니 <br>귀하고 귀하다 <br>예수의 흘린 피 <br>날 희게 하오니 <br>귀하고 귀하다 <br>예수의 피밖에 없네 <br>예수의 피밖에 없네 <br>예수의 피밖에 없네 <br>예수의 피밖에 없네 <br>예수의 피밖에 없네 <br>예수의 피밖에 없네 <br>]]></content><category term="아이노스 밴드 (Ainos Band)" label="아이노스 밴드 (Ainos Band)"/><category term="나의 죄를 씻기는" label="나의 죄를 씻기는"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mind182/Magnet_Feat_IsA_B/</id><title>Mind182 - Magnet (Feat. I$sA B) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:07:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:07:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mind182/Magnet_Feat_IsA_B/" title="Mind182 - Magnet (Feat. I$sA B) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't bother me <br>Yeah I'd rather be alone <br>no promising on everything <br>I'm gone <br>It drives me crazy <br>when you keep me waiting <br>Stay pulling on my heart strings <br>and then you send my head <br>to different places <br>Are we looking at the same thing <br>Hanging mid air <br>It's like a light went on <br>and you did no wrong <br>Tell me <br>Can we play fair <br>It's a long way up <br>If you want my love <br>Cuz every time we try <br>Every time we try <br>I end up back in your paradise <br>Holding on for life <br>No I can't shake you <br>out of my life <br>Everytime I try <br>I end up back <br>in your paradise holding <br>on for life <br>One look <br>then I'm crashing with the waves <br>There's no escaping you <br>When all of the crazy <br>starts to fade <br>I find my way back <br>into your arms <br>It's an electric kinda love <br>that cuts right through <br>when it's running low <br>it's never done <br>Guess I'm just electric for you <br>Did you mean everything <br>that you said <br>Can we build it back up <br>from what's left <br>Hey <br>Since I can't get away from you <br>I'll meet you right over my bed <br>Hanging mid air <br>It's like a light went on <br>and you did no wrong <br>Tell me <br>Can we play fair <br>It's a long way up <br>If you want my love <br>If you want my love <br>Cuz every time we try <br>Every time we try <br>I end up back in your paradise <br>Holding on for life <br>No I can't shake you <br>out of my life <br>Everytime I try <br>I end up back <br>in your paradise holding <br>on for life <br>oh <br>How did we end up here <br>Fell to the lowest <br>we've ever been <br>Then back up again <br>Like a magnet <br>Always pull me in like <br>Oh <br>Maybe we'll never know <br>How we fell to the lowest <br>we've ever been <br>Then back up again <br>like a magnet <br>I'm a magnet to you <br>I'm a magnet <br>One look <br>then I'm crashing with the waves <br>There's no escaping you <br>When all of the crazy starts to <br>fade <br>I find my way back into your arms <br>It's an electric kinda love <br>that cuts right through <br>when it's running low <br>it's never done <br>Guess I'm just electric for you <br>]]></content><category term="Mind182" label="Mind182"/><category term="Magnet (Feat. I$sA B)" label="Magnet (Feat. I$sA B)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/케이윌/그게_뭐라고/</id><title>케이윌 - 그게 뭐라고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:07:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:07:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4%EC%9C%8C/%EA%B7%B8%EA%B2%8C_%EB%AD%90%EB%9D%BC%EA%B3%A0/" title="케이윌 - 그게 뭐라고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하늘을 보고 누군가 <br>그리워지면 <br>가을이 온 거고 그즈음 <br>매년 손님이 와 <br>마치 똑똑 누군가 <br>두드리는데 <br>알면서도 어쩔 수 없이 <br>문을 열어놔 <br>넌 늘 멋대로였어 <br>헤어진 후에도 <br>몰래 왔다 가네 <br>그리움만 둔 채로 <br>추억은 맴도는데 <br>우리는 흔적이 없어 <br>넌 내게 영원히 <br>반복되는 계절이었어 <br>니가 생각나 이맘때쯤에 <br>웃고 있던 너와 내가 <br>생각 나는데 <br>니 무릎을 베고 하늘을 보며 <br>먼 훗날 우리 얘길 했는데 <br>사랑한다고 내 귓가에 <br>말해주던 너의 목소리 <br>그게 뭐라고 또 생각나 <br>하나 둘씩 떠오르지 <br>함께한 추억들이 <br>그리워지네 <br>하나 둘 어 <br>나쁜 쪽이 누구인진 <br>이제 더는 상관없어지고 <br>우린 그저 어리고 <br>미숙했다고 여기며 <br>어쩔 수 없는 일들에 대해 <br>그래 그땐 어쩔 수 없었지 <br>라고 받아들이게 돼 <br>내 마음이 아깝게 <br>느껴질 때가 있었어 <br>미치도록 니가 미웠던 <br>때가 있었어 <br>시간 지나니 그냥 내 <br>심술이더라 <br>뱉는 말마다 진심과 <br>반대였더라고 <br>게임 밤새 하지마 <br>밥 좀 챙겨먹어 <br>별 거 아닌 잔소리가 <br>사실 제일 그리워 <br>청승이야 청승 <br>전화 걸 뻔했네 <br>잠도 안 와 맥주 한 캔 <br>사러 가야겠네 <br>사랑한다고 내 귓가에 <br>말해주던 너의 목소리 <br>그게 뭐라고 또 생각나 <br>하나 둘씩 떠오르지 <br>함께한 추억들이 <br>그리워지네 <br>그 누군가 내게 말을 했지 <br>세월이 곧 약일꺼라고 <br>널 많이 사랑했나봐 그랬나봐 <br>이젠 잊을 때도 됐는데 <br>사랑한다고 좋아한다고 <br>매일 같이 말해주던 <br>네 목소리 잊지 못하고 <br>하나 둘씩 떠오르지 <br>함께한 추억들이 <br>그리워지네 <br>너는 대책 없이 기억나 <br>속 또 헤집어놓고 맘에 훅 <br>하고 들어왔어 <br>그러면 나는 또 <br>후 하고 숨을 쉬네 <br>산책이나 나가야지 <br>뭐 밤이 기네 <br>]]></content><category term="케이윌" label="케이윌"/><category term="그게 뭐라고" label="그게 뭐라고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유승우/내가_니편이_되어줄게/</id><title>유승우 - 내가 니편이 되어줄게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:07:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:07:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EC%8A%B9%EC%9A%B0/%EB%82%B4%EA%B0%80_%EB%8B%88%ED%8E%B8%EC%9D%B4_%EB%90%98%EC%96%B4%EC%A4%84%EA%B2%8C/" title="유승우 - 내가 니편이 되어줄게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[누가 내 맘을 위로할까 <br>누가 내 맘을 알아줄까 <br>모두가 나를 비웃는 것 같아 <br>기댈 곳 하나 없네 <br>이젠 괜찮다 했었는데 <br>익숙해진 줄 알았는데 <br>다시 찾아온 이 절망에 <br>나는 또 쓰러져 혼자 남아있네 <br>내가 니 편이 되어줄게 <br>괜찮다 말해줄게 <br>다 잘 될 거라고 넌 빛날 거라고 <br>넌 나에게 가장 소중한 사람 <br>이젠 괜찮다 했었는데 <br>익숙해진 줄 알았는데 <br>다시 찾아온 이 절망에 <br>나는 또 쓰러져 혼자 남아있네 <br>내가 니 편이 되어줄게 <br>괜찮다 말해줄게 <br>다 잘 될 거라고 넌 빛날 거라고 <br>넌 나에게 소중하다고 <br>모두 끝난 것 같은 날에 <br>내 목소릴 기억해 <br>괜찮아 다 잘 될 거야 <br>넌 나에게 가장 소중한 사람 <br>다 잘 될 거라고 넌 빛날 거라고 <br>넌 나에게 소중하다고 <br>모두 끝난 것 같은 날에 <br>내 목소릴 기억해 <br>괜찮아 다 잘 될 거야 <br>넌 나에게 <br>가장 소중한 사람 <br>]]></content><category term="유승우" label="유승우"/><category term="내가 니편이 되어줄게" label="내가 니편이 되어줄게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/기리보이/소란했던_시절에/</id><title>기리보이 - 소란했던 시절에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:07:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:07:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4/%EC%86%8C%EB%9E%80%ED%96%88%EB%8D%98_%EC%8B%9C%EC%A0%88%EC%97%90/" title="기리보이 - 소란했던 시절에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 기억하고 있는지 <br>모두 잊은 듯 지내는지 <br>비 내리는 그 날이면 <br>널 떠올리곤 해 <br>널 떠올려봐 <br>너무 사소했던 것들까지 <br>소란했던 일들 덕에 <br>지금 허무하지 <br>너무 커버린 추억은 <br>이별에 담을 수가 없어 <br>내 머릿속은 비어버려 <br>멍청해져 버렸어 <br>이 뻔하디 뻔한 상황 <br>울고 불고 난리 쳐 <br>제발 전화 좀 받아 <br>난 끝까지 시끄러웠지 <br>넌 끝까지 시끄러웠지 <br>지나온 우리 날들이 <br>조금씩 사라져 가도 <br>되돌릴 수가 없는 걸 <br>너무 잘 알고 있기에 <br>단 한 순간의 기억도 <br>다 버릴 수가 없어서 <br>기억 속에서 여전히 <br>헤매이고 있는 나 <br>한참을 생각해 봤어 <br>우리의 날들을 <br>소음들에게 맞서던 <br>우리의 지난 날들을 <br>세상에 너의 그런 소리를 <br>난 들은 적이 없는데 <br>나는 무서워 <br>귀를 막아 버렸지 <br>어디서든 잘 살고 <br>아무쪼록 몸 조심해 <br>난 괜찮아 지금 <br>이 소린 꽤 조신해 <br>퍼즐 같은 우리 <br>추억은 조각이 났지 <br>넌 그걸 들고 대체 <br>어디서 또 뭐를 하니 <br>모든걸 틀어막고 <br>정적뿐인 이 방에서 <br>청승맞게 이상한 <br>감정을 이입 하고 있어 <br>거긴 어떤 <br>소리들로 가득 차있니 <br>나만 빠진 너의 삶은 <br>어디까지 가있니 <br>너는 갈 때까지 갔고 <br>돌아갈 순 없어 <br>넌 나만 놓고 갔고 <br>난 너만큼이 없어 <br>모든걸 잃고서 <br>기억들로만 살아 숨쉬네 <br>흩어져버린 추억과 <br>조각나 버린 마음이 <br>뒤늦게 너를 데려와 <br>마치 손에 닿을 만큼 <br>후회로 물든 순간도 <br>다 버릴 수가 없어서 <br>기억 속에서 여전히 <br>헤매이고 있는 나 <br>그 소란했던 시절에 <br>그대라는 이름 <br>]]></content><category term="기리보이" label="기리보이"/><category term="소란했던 시절에" label="소란했던 시절에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/솔비/손모아_장갑/</id><title>솔비 - 손모아 장갑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:07:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:07:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%94%EB%B9%84/%EC%86%90%EB%AA%A8%EC%95%84_%EC%9E%A5%EA%B0%91/" title="솔비 - 손모아 장갑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[조금만 더 기다려줄래 <br>내가 지금 가고 있어 <br>차가운 겨울바람은 또 <br>우릴 질투하는 거겠지 <br>따뜻한 손모아 장갑 끼고 <br>어디든 달려볼까 <br>밤 하늘은 또 <br>우리를 어디로 데려갈지 <br>이 겨울에 끝은 너와 함께 있어 <br>설렘이 가득한 거리 <br>여기저기 들리는 종소리 <br>저 불빛들은 <br>우리들의 선물로 가득하고 <br>시간이 다가오는 걸 <br>손꼽아 기다리던 <br>우리만의 겨울의 이야기들 <br>조금만 더 기다려줄래 <br>내가 지금 가고 있어 <br>차가운 겨울바람은 또 <br>우릴 질투하는 거겠지 <br>따뜻한 손모아 장갑 끼고 <br>어디든 달려볼까 <br>밤 하늘은 또 <br>우리를 어디로 데려갈지 <br>이 겨울에 끝은 너와 함께 있어 <br>따듯한 너의 손끝에 <br>내 마음은 녹아 내리고 <br>하얀 눈송이 사뿐히 <br>머리 위 내려앉아 <br>이렇게 아름다운 날 <br>추억은 쌓여가고 <br>녹지 않을 우리의 이야기들 <br>조금만 더 기다려줄래 <br>내가 지금 가고 있어 <br>차가운 겨울바람은 또 <br>우릴 질투하는 거겠지 <br>따뜻한 손모아 장갑 끼고 <br>어디든 달려볼까 <br>밤 하늘은 또 <br>우리를 어디로 데려갈지 <br>이 겨울에 끝은 너와 함께 있어 <br>하늘은 또 우리를 위해 <br>하얀 선물을 내리고 <br>함께 있는 것만으로도 난 <br>온 세상 다 가진 것 같은데 <br>하고픈 말 천 가지 넘지만 <br>정말로 널 사랑해 <br>소중한 우리 기적은 <br>오늘 밤 일어날까 <br>이 겨울에 끝은 너와 함께 있어 <br>]]></content><category term="솔비" label="솔비"/><category term="손모아 장갑" label="손모아 장갑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이어스_Ears/비밀/</id><title>이어스 (Ears) - 비밀 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:07:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:07:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%96%B4%EC%8A%A4_Ears/%EB%B9%84%EB%B0%80/" title="이어스 (Ears) - 비밀 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그때 넌 눈으로 이미 <br>말하고 있었어 <br>너무 힘든 일이니 이제 <br>그만 하자고 <br>지쳐보이는 네 모습과 <br>다른 내 마음에 <br>니가 아플 걸 알면서도 <br>멈추지 못 하네 <br>너에게 늘 특별한 <br>사람이고 싶어 난 <br>혹시 예전 그대로 돌아 <br>갈 수 있을까 <br>네 환한 미소와 내가 준 <br>목걸이까지 <br>지금 이대로 널 보내면 <br>안될 것 같아서 <br>니가 아플 걸 알면서도 <br>그만하자 못해 <br>너에게 늘 특별한 <br>사람이고 싶어 난 <br>그만하자 말 못해 <br>]]></content><category term="이어스 (Ears)" label="이어스 (Ears)"/><category term="비밀" label="비밀"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/메이다니_MAYDONI/아프지말아요_For_you_Inst/</id><title>메이다니 (MAYDONI) - 아프지말아요 (For you) (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:07:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:07:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%A4%EB%8B%88_MAYDONI/%EC%95%84%ED%94%84%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%90%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94_For_you_Inst/" title="메이다니 (MAYDONI) - 아프지말아요 (For you) (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대를 바라봅니다 <br>따뜻했던 그 손을 더 <br>잡고 싶은데 <br>괜찮아 이제 잊어야 해 <br>우리의 사랑했던 기억 <br>아프지말아요 날 위해 <br>약속해요 무리 하지 않기 <br>흔들리지마요 날 위해 <br>떠나간 시간일 뿐 이니까 <br>우 그대를 그려 <br>행복한 순간들 잊지 않도록 <br>우 우리의 추억을 <br>지난날에 가려 지지 않게 <br>아프지말아요 날 위해 <br>약속해요 잠시 쉬어가기 <br>흔들리지마요 날 위해 <br>그대의 행복을 바라니까 <br>우 그대를 그려 <br>사랑한 순간들 잊지 않도록 <br>우 우리의 아름다운 <br>추억들이 가려 지지 않게 <br>더 환하게 <br>다 잊고 웃으며 <br>행복하길 바래 <br>이제는 다 <br>흘러가버린거니까 <br>멀어져 내 손을 잡던 <br>너의 온기가 <br>이제는 모든 게 무뎌져 <br>아프지말아요 나의 그대 <br>기억해요 무리 하지 않기 <br>돌아보지마요 나의 그대 <br>난 그려요 행복했던 우리 <br>늘 그려요 행복했던 우리]]></content><category term="메이다니 (MAYDONI)" label="메이다니 (MAYDONI)"/><category term="아프지말아요 (For you) (Inst.)" label="아프지말아요 (For you) (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/메이다니_MAYDONI/아프지말아요_For_you/</id><title>메이다니 (MAYDONI) - 아프지말아요 (For you) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:07:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:07:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%A4%EB%8B%88_MAYDONI/%EC%95%84%ED%94%84%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%90%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94_For_you/" title="메이다니 (MAYDONI) - 아프지말아요 (For you) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대를 바라봅니다 <br>따뜻했던 그 손을 더 <br>잡고 싶은데 <br>괜찮아 이제 잊어야 해 <br>우리의 사랑했던 기억 <br>아프지말아요 날 위해 <br>약속해요 무리 하지 않기 <br>흔들리지마요 날 위해 <br>떠나간 시간일 뿐 이니까 <br>우 그대를 그려 <br>행복한 순간들 잊지 않도록 <br>우 우리의 추억을 <br>지난날에 가려 지지 않게 <br>아프지말아요 날 위해 <br>약속해요 잠시 쉬어가기 <br>흔들리지마요 날 위해 <br>그대의 행복을 바라니까 <br>우 그대를 그려 <br>사랑한 순간들 잊지 않도록 <br>우 우리의 아름다운 <br>추억들이 가려 지지 않게 <br>더 환하게 <br>다 잊고 웃으며 <br>행복하길 바래 <br>이제는 다 <br>흘러가버린거니까 <br>멀어져 내 손을 잡던 <br>너의 온기가 <br>이제는 모든 게 무뎌져 <br>아프지말아요 나의 그대 <br>기억해요 무리 하지 않기 <br>돌아보지마요 나의 그대 <br>난 그려요 행복했던 우리 <br>늘 그려요 행복했던 우리 <br>]]></content><category term="메이다니 (MAYDONI)" label="메이다니 (MAYDONI)"/><category term="아프지말아요 (For you)" label="아프지말아요 (For you)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vicetone/Landslide/</id><title>Vicetone - Landslide - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:07:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:07:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vicetone/Landslide/" title="Vicetone - Landslide - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Black waves where we used to stand <br>Go on, give yourself a chance <br>Rush away like an avalanche <br>Look down on a lonely flame <br>A few steps till the view has changed <br>Broken eyes never see the same <br><br>I never saw it coming, landslide <br>Carry us away, away, away <br>In a landslide, in a landslide <br>I disappear into a landslide <br>Never be the same, the same, the same <br>In a landslide, in a landslide <br><br>In a landslide, in a landslide <br>In a landslide, in a landslide <br><br>Soaked up in a bloodshot haze <br>Woke up with you in my veins <br>I don't know how to let you fade <br>Look down on a lonely flame <br>A few steps till the view has changed <br>Broken eyes never see the same <br><br>I never saw it coming, landslide <br>Carry us away, away, away <br>In a landslide, in a landslide <br>I disappear into a landslide <br>Never be the same, the same, the same <br>In a landslide, in a landslide <br><br>In a landslide, in a landslide <br>In a landslide, in a landslide <br><br>We're falling, we're falling, we're falling all the way <br>We're falling, we're falling, we're falling all the way <br><br>I never saw it coming, landslide <br>Carry us away, away, away <br>In a landslide, in a landslide <br>I disappear into a landslide <br>Never be the same, the same, the same <br>In a landslide, in a landslide <br><br>In a landslide, in a landslide <br>In a landslide, in a landslide <br><br>We're falling, we're falling, we're falling all the way <br>In a landslide, in a landslide <br>We're falling, we're falling, we're falling all the way <br>In a landslide, in a landslide <br>We're falling, we're falling <br>In a landslide, in a landslide]]></content><category term="Vicetone" label="Vicetone"/><category term="Landslide" label="Landslide"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이지드/EVILHAZARD/</id><title>이지드 - EVILHAZARD - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:08:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:08:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80%EB%93%9C/EVILHAZARD/" title="이지드 - EVILHAZARD - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 얼굴엔 하얀 분칠 <br>THIS FEEL LIKE A LEATHERFACE <br>어릴 때부터 나쁜 짓 <br>많이 했었지 <br>그런 의미로 우리동네는 <br>질이 안 좋지 <br>난 그런 데서 자라서 <br>안 좋은 말들을 뱉지 <br>이제 난 EVILHAZARD <br>그래 내 맘대로 해석 <br>다른 가짜들은 애써 <br>부정하지 못 본 척 <br>돈은 필요 없어 <br>내 얘기나 들어줘 <br>지저분한 느낌 <br>너는 헤어나올 수 없어 <br>DIRTY VIBE ON MY CRACKCHAIN <br>I BELIVE NEW FUTURE WITH ME <br>잘 봐 내 이름 EZD <br>더는 벗어날 수 없지 <br>내가 자라며 배워 온 모든 것 들이 <br>나의 음악 그 자체로 너네 귀를 <br>함락하러 왔지 나는 악당 <br>얕은 거짓없이 꽉 채운 타임라인 <br>기다릴 것 없이 보여줘 <br>우리 팀은 죽지 않아 좀비 같애 <br>썩어버린 대부분은 싹 다 없어져 <br>나와 공통점은 없지 <br>이걸 듣고 느껴 BIXXHES <br>보여줄 테니까 받아먹어 <br>SWALLOW <br>이 느낌 내 방식 전부 다 <br>SWALLOW <br>아직 많이 남았으니까 <br>SWALLOW <br>I CUM MY SPERM <br>쏟아질 테니 <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>누군가 정해 놓은 건 아니였지만 <br>내 인생은 하류 <br>어쨌든 선택해야 했지 <br>다 걸어 버렸다고 <br>이 말이 어떤 의미인지 <br>정확히 알아 <br>내 주변을 지키지 <br>이건 가볍지 않아 <br>YE I'M BLAZIN' <br>내 미랜 벌써 보여 <br>장담해 이건 ROYAL <br>그 무엇도 날 죽이진 못한다면 <br>더욱 강하게 만들 뿐 <br>여전히 살아 숨쉬어 <br>속도를 더 내지 <br>발등에 불을 붙여 <br>이게 나의 방식 <br>다들 동참해 내 뒤로 줄 서 <br>독 오른 놈의 영웅심리 <br>머릿수를 채워 넣고 나는 뒷짐 <br>바이러스처럼 퍼져 개처럼 짓지 <br>온몸으로 느껴지는 공포심 <br>니가 내가 아니라면 못 보지 <br>모든 건 설계돼있어 오직 <br>목표를 위해서 <br>준비해왔지 조용히 <br>결과야 뭐가 어찌됐던 <br>나는 끝을 봐야 되는 성격 <br>모르는 일이지 아직 안 졌어 <br>먼저 내껄 받아 먹어 <br>SWALLOW <br>보여줄 테니까 받아먹어 <br>SWALLOW <br>이 느낌 내 방식 전부 다 <br>SWALLOW <br>아직 많이 남았으니까 <br>SWALLOW <br>I CUM MY SPERM <br>쏟아질 테니 <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>다 SWALLOW <br>]]></content><category term="이지드" label="이지드"/><category term="EVILHAZARD" label="EVILHAZARD"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JZ/그_손으로/</id><title>JZ - 그 손으로 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:08:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:08:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JZ/%EA%B7%B8_%EC%86%90%EC%9C%BC%EB%A1%9C/" title="JZ - 그 손으로 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[칠흙같은 어두움 속에 <br>헤메이던 나의 모습 <br>넘어지고 쓰러져 <br>일어 날 힘조차 없을때 <br>희미하게 내게 들리는 <br>따스한 주님의 음성 <br>나의 사랑 <br>나의 어여쁜 자야 <br>나와 함께 가자 <br>말씀 하실 때 <br>내 생각이 <br>주님 생각보다 앞서서 <br>그 음성 외면하려 <br>미련하게 몸부림쳤네 <br>그런 내 모습조차 <br>변함없는 사랑으로 <br>어둡던 내 안에 <br>새 빛 비춰주시네 <br>그 손으로 <br>내 손 잡아주시네 <br>영광의 못자국 난 <br>주님의 손으로 <br>그 손으로 내 마음 <br>만져주시는 주님 <br>주님의 손 놓지 않으리 <br>영원히 주님과 <br>함께 걸으리 <br>내 생각이 <br>주님 생각보다 앞서서 <br>그 음성 외면하려 <br>미련하게 몸부림쳤네 <br>그런 내 모습조차 <br>변함없는 사랑으로 <br>어둡던 내 안에 <br>새 빛 비춰주시네 <br>그 손으로 <br>내 손 잡아주시네 <br>영광의 못자국 난 <br>주님의 손으로 <br>그 손으로 내 마음 <br>만져주시는 주님 <br>주님의 손 놓지 않으리 <br>영원히 주님과 <br>함께 걸으리 <br>그 손으로 <br>내 손 잡아주시네 <br>영광의 못자국 난 <br>주님의 손으로 <br>그 손으로 내 마음 <br>만져주시는 주님 <br>주님의 손 놓지 않으리 <br>영원히 주님과 <br>함께 걸으리 <br>]]></content><category term="JZ" label="JZ"/><category term="그 손으로" label="그 손으로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/채은옥/미소를_띄우며_나를_보낸_그_모습처럼_Feat_장기섭/</id><title>채은옥 - 미소를 띄우며 나를 보낸 그 모습처럼 (Feat. 장기섭) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:08:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:08:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B1%84%EC%9D%80%EC%98%A5/%EB%AF%B8%EC%86%8C%EB%A5%BC_%EB%9D%84%EC%9A%B0%EB%A9%B0_%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EB%B3%B4%EB%82%B8_%EA%B7%B8_%EB%AA%A8%EC%8A%B5%EC%B2%98%EB%9F%BC_Feat_%EC%9E%A5%EA%B8%B0%EC%84%AD/" title="채은옥 - 미소를 띄우며 나를 보낸 그 모습처럼 (Feat. 장기섭) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날 위해 울지 말아요 <br>날 위해 슬퍼 말아요 <br>그렇게 바라보지 말아요 <br>의미를 잃어버린 그 표정 <br>날 위해 울지 말아요 <br>날 위해 슬퍼 말아요 <br>그렇게 바라보지 말아요 <br>의미를 잃어버린 그 표정 <br>날 사랑하지 말아요 <br>너무 늦은 얘기잖아요 <br>애타게 기다리지 말아요 <br>사랑은 끝났으니까 <br>그대 왜 나를 그냥 <br>떠나가게 했나요 <br>이렇게 다시 <br>후회할 줄 알았다면 <br>아픈 시련 속에 <br>방황하지 않았을 텐데 <br>사랑은 이제 내게 <br>남아있지 않아요 <br>아무런 느낌 <br>가질 수 없어요 <br>미소를 띄우며 <br>나를 보낸 그 모습처럼 <br>그대 왜 나를 그냥 <br>떠나가게 했나요 <br>이렇게 다시 <br>후회할 줄 알았다면 <br>아픈 시련 속에 <br>방황하지 않았을 텐데 <br>사랑은 이제 내게 <br>남아있지 않아요 <br>아무런 느낌 <br>가질 수 없어요 <br>미소를 띄우며 <br>나를 보낸 그 모습처럼 <br>나를 보낸 그 모습처럼 <br>]]></content><category term="채은옥" label="채은옥"/><category term="미소를 띄우며 나를 보낸 그 모습처럼 (Feat. 장기섭)" label="미소를 띄우며 나를 보낸 그 모습처럼 (Feat. 장기섭)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/중식이/바닥에_누워/</id><title>중식이 - 바닥에 누워 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:08:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:08:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A4%91%EC%8B%9D%EC%9D%B4/%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%A5%EC%97%90_%EB%88%84%EC%9B%8C/" title="중식이 - 바닥에 누워 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[몇 달 동안 난 <br>누워 있었지 <br>이제 나는 아무것도 몰라 <br>눈만 껌뻑여 천장만 보다 <br>날아가는 쓰레기봉지처럼 <br>새벽이 오면 벌벌 떨다가 <br>숨쉬고 있는 내 모습에 놀라 <br>머리 위에는 파리가 맴돌지 <br>쓰레기 더미에 <br>썩어가는 생선 같은 나 <br>나의 사랑은 오랫동안 <br>냉장고 안에 썩어 있었어 <br>뭐였지 이게 뭐였지 <br>나도 몰라 나도 몰라 <br>갈증을 식히려 목을 적시려 <br>썩은 너를 마셨어 <br>나는 아플 걸 알면서 너를 삼켰어 <br>나는 한 마리의 개가 되어 <br>쓰레길 뒤지고 있었지 <br>나는 왜 살지 나는 왜 살지 <br>나도 몰라 나도 몰라 <br>꿈꾸던 소년은 길을 잃고 <br>서울역 앞에 누워 있었지 <br>명분 없는 삶은 움직이지 않았지 <br>바람이 불어와 하늘을 날았지 <br>이제 나는 아무것도 몰라 <br>날아 가는지 떨어져 가는지 <br>바람에 날린 쓰레기 봉지처럼 <br>겨울이 오면 누가 날 좀 치워줘 <br>차가운 여긴 아무도 날 몰라 <br>눈만 껌뻑여 하늘만 본 다 <br>숨만 헐떡여 새하얀 한숨만 <br>나의 사랑은 오랫동안 <br>냉장고 안에 썩어 있었어 <br>뭐였지 이게 뭐였지 <br>나도 몰라 나도 몰라 <br>갈증을 식히려 목을 적시려 <br>썩은 너를 마셨어 <br>나는 아플 걸 알면서 너를 삼켰어 <br>]]></content><category term="중식이" label="중식이"/><category term="바닥에 누워" label="바닥에 누워"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dangerkids/Blacklist_/</id><title>Dangerkids - Blacklist_ - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:08:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:08:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dangerkids/Blacklist_/" title="Dangerkids - Blacklist_ - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sink your teeth a little deeper <br>Each shot gets a little bit cheaper <br>And I've had it up to here <br>It's like I lose a little piece of me with every decision <br>It's like I draw the dotted line and then you make the incision <br>Before I put you in my rear view, I just came to tell you <br><br>We're not through until I say it's over <br>Not numb, just a little bit colder <br>Do you have what it takes to take us on <br>We are the movement <br>This is the Blacklist <br>Go <br><br>You'd sell your soul if you had it <br>You'd burn a bridge to be king of the ashes <br>And I've seen it all before <br>It's like there's someone taking credit from me as soon as I make it <br>You either fight for what you've got or let them walk up and take it <br>And I know, cause after everything I'm starting to see <br>You better watch your mouth the way you're taking to me, because <br><br>We're not through until I say it's over <br>Not numb, just a little bit colder <br>Do you have what it takes to take us on <br>We are the movement <br>This is the Blacklist <br><br>Yeah, this is the Blacklist <br>Why can't you see <br>You made me this way <br><br>We're not through until I say it's over <br>Not numb, just a little bit colder <br>Do you have what it takes to take us on <br><br>We're not through until I say it's over <br>Not numb, just a little bit colder <br>Do you have what it takes to take us on <br>We are the movement <br>This is the Blacklist <br>Go <br>Yeah, this is the Blacklist]]></content><category term="Dangerkids" label="Dangerkids"/><category term="Blacklist_" label="Blacklist_"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신용재_포맨/그대라서/</id><title>신용재 (포맨) - 그대라서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:08:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:08:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9A%A9%EC%9E%AC_%ED%8F%AC%EB%A7%A8/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%9D%BC%EC%84%9C/" title="신용재 (포맨) - 그대라서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈 내리는 밤거리를 <br>함께 걷는 이 순간 <br>눈 내리는 하얀 밤을 <br>함께 있는 이 순간 <br>따뜻하게 포근하게 <br>그댈 안아주고 싶어 <br>이 겨울이 따뜻한 건 오 그대라서 <br>한걸음 더 또 한걸음 더 <br>다가갈게요 <br>내 마음이 행복한 건 오 그대라서 <br>사랑해요 또 사랑해요 그댈 Woo <br>어느새 지나간 겨울이 <br>또 다시 우릴 찾아오듯 <br>난 언제나 난 영원히 <br>그댈 사랑할게요 <br>밤하늘이 반짝이는 건 <br>오 그대라서 <br>한걸음 더 또 한걸음 더 <br>다가갈게요 <br>내 마음이 행복한 건 오 그대라서 <br>사랑해요 또 사랑해요 <br>그대를 영원히 <br>]]></content><category term="신용재 (포맨)" label="신용재 (포맨)"/><category term="그대라서" label="그대라서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Famous_Dex/Drip_From_My_Walk_Feat_Lil_Yachty_Remix/</id><title>Famous Dex - Drip From My Walk (Feat. Lil Yachty) (Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:08:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:08:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Famous_Dex/Drip_From_My_Walk_Feat_Lil_Yachty_Remix/" title="Famous Dex - Drip From My Walk (Feat. Lil Yachty) (Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, yeah, yeah, everybody keep asking me how I get the drip <br>How I get drip this How I get drippy that How I get drip that <br>How I be fly this How I be fucking bitches that <br>They say how I got all the drip But look <br><br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>Oh Man Goddamn <br>A bad bitch, live up north <br>I'm smoking dope till I exhaust <br>Money coming from the vault <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>Oh Man Goddamn <br>A bad bitch, live up north <br>I'm smoking dope till I exhaust <br>Money coming from the vault <br>Drippy, Drippy <br>I get the drip from my walk <br><br>I get the drip from my walk <br>My baby she come from up north <br>My money, it come from the vault <br>I'm smoking on dope like Young Dolph <br>We touch the plug down for the cough <br>Im sippin' on lean till I fall <br>My diamonds they shine, they Rick Ross <br>I hop in the foreign, get lost <br>Oh Man Goddamn <br>2 bitches they calling me drippy <br>I fuck them and then we get drippy <br>My 30, it shoot, Scottie Pippen <br>Im sippin' on lean till I'm sleepy <br>I pop me 2 pills I get geeky <br>I got a lil bitch her name Kiki <br>I think that lil bitch Puerto Rican <br>She chill at my crib for the weekend <br>3 grams in my Wood like a boss <br>My diamonds they shine with a floss <br>My foreign it float like a ghost <br>I hop in that bitch and get lost <br>My money is starting to get tall <br>I walk in the mall buy it all <br>My drippy it came in the sauce <br>I get the drip from my walk <br><br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>Oh Man Goddamn <br>A bad bitch, live up north <br>I'm smoking dope till I exhaust <br>Money coming from the vault <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>Oh Man Goddamn <br>A bad bitch, live up north <br>I'm smoking dope till I exhaust <br>Money coming from the vault <br>Drippy, Drippy <br>I get the drip from my walk <br><br>Run Ricky <br>Straight neck, I don't do the hickeys <br>Nigga stupid if he try to stick me <br>Leave a pussy nigga drippy drippy <br>Aw man, fuck it up <br>All my young niggas they run it up <br>Can't leave the room till we add it up <br>Bag it up, I get that drip from my sister <br>I get that speed from the fisker <br>Old heads lookin' at Boat like the sinister <br>Young niggas look at Lil Boat like the minister <br>Just made a 30 while fucking on Jennifer <br>Dex and Lil Boat, we go way back <br>Niggas where fools go A Track <br>If I bring you a four I need eight back, drippy drippy <br>Boat so young she had to hit up Ricky <br>Dripping sauce, feel it in your kidneys <br>Young nigga had a real epiphany <br>Before a nigga had a mili <br>And I ball like a player <br>Got a Benz in my lair <br>These niggas want me to flip flop <br>In her throat like a cough drop <br><br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>Oh Man Goddamn <br>A bad bitch, live up north <br>I'm smoking dope till I exhaust <br>Money coming from the vault <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>I get the drip from my walk <br>Oh Man Goddamn <br>A bad bitch, live up north <br>I'm smoking dope till I exhaust <br>Money coming from the vault <br>Drippy, Drippy <br>I get the drip from my walk]]></content><category term="Famous Dex" label="Famous Dex"/><category term="Drip From My Walk (Feat. Lil Yachty) (Remix)" label="Drip From My Walk (Feat. Lil Yachty) (Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/언노운드레스/On_Christmas_Day_English_Ver/</id><title>언노운드레스 - On Christmas Day (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:10:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:10:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%B8%EB%85%B8%EC%9A%B4%EB%93%9C%EB%A0%88%EC%8A%A4/On_Christmas_Day_English_Ver/" title="언노운드레스 - On Christmas Day (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[As countless years have <br>gone by us <br>Winter wind again starts <br>blowing in the snow <br>I wait tonight <br>with you in me <br>Glimpse of you shining <br>warm and bright <br>All I want is to be with you <br>Yes right <br>Our White Christmas <br>Filling my heart <br>yes you've always <br>been the one <br>Although the distance <br>between us is so far <br>I had you but you haven't <br>had me all enough <br>Hear me you will be tonight <br>Bead-light through the <br>windows passes by us <br>Pictures of memories soak <br>deeply in the dark <br>I wait tonight <br>with you in me <br>Glimpse of you shining <br>warm and bright <br>All I want is to be with you <br>Yes right <br>Our White Christmas <br>Filling my heart <br>yes you've always <br>been the one <br>Although the distance <br>between us is so far <br>I had you but you haven't <br>had me all enough <br>Hear me you will be tonight <br>Soothing me <br>You will be with me <br>As countless years have <br>gone by us <br>Winter wind again starts <br>blowing in the snow <br>I wait tonight with you in me <br>Warmth of your heart will <br>melt me down <br>All I want is to be with you <br>Yes right <br>Our White Christmas <br>]]></content><category term="언노운드레스" label="언노운드레스"/><category term="On Christmas Day (English Ver.)" label="On Christmas Day (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/언노운드레스/On_Christmas_Day/</id><title>언노운드레스 - On Christmas Day - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:10:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:10:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%B8%EB%85%B8%EC%9A%B4%EB%93%9C%EB%A0%88%EC%8A%A4/On_Christmas_Day/" title="언노운드레스 - On Christmas Day - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[수 많은 시간들이 우릴 지나고 <br>올해도 어김없이 찾아온 겨울 <br>고마웠던 기억들과 <br>그 기억속에 머물러 준 그대와 <br>오늘밤도 기다려보네 <br>우리의 화이트 크리스마스 <br>언제나 나의 마음 채워준 사람 <br>멀리 있어도 나는 그대였지만 <br>차마 전하지 못한 나의 마음을 <br>그대와 함께 나누죠 <br>차창 밖 불빛들은 우릴 지나고 <br>또 다시 다가온 추억의 그림들 <br>사랑했던 기억들과 <br>그 기억속에 빛나던 그대와 <br>오늘밤도 기다려보네 <br>우리의 화이트 크리스마스 <br>언제나 나의 마음 채워준 사람 <br>멀리 있어도 나는 그대였지만 <br>차마 전하지 못한 나의 마음을 <br>그대와 함께 나누죠 <br>그대는 위로가 되죠 <br>수많은 시간들이 우릴 지나고 <br>올해도 어김없이 찾아온 겨울 <br>다정했던 지금을 <br>기억해줄 그대와 <br>오늘밤도 기다려보네 <br>우리의 화이트 크리스마스 <br>]]></content><category term="언노운드레스" label="언노운드레스"/><category term="On Christmas Day" label="On Christmas Day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_De_Palma/Voila/</id><title>Fred De Palma - Voila - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:10:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:10:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fred_De_Palma/Voila/" title="Fred De Palma - Voila - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Voila <br>Voila <br>Fumo e vado in paranoia, chissa che mi succedera <br>Becco due bastarde senza gloria, me le porto a casa e voila <br>Andiamo tutti in centro, in centro <br>Ale quella canna c'avra 10 grammi dentro <br>il tempo che ti dico Ci sono gli sbirri, attento gia ce li abbiamo attorno, in cerchio, e voila <br>Io e te ci mandavamo mille foto, nudi davanti allo specchio, era il nostro gioco, ma poi la nostra storia, mannaggia, e finita <br>sulla mia storia di Snapchat, e voila <br><br>Voila <br>Voila <br>Sto fuori come un satellite <br>Voila <br>Voila <br>Sto fuori come un satellite <br>Io questa notte, non so, da questo androne chissa dove andro Oooh <br>Io questa notte, non so, non so <br>Molla le tue amiche, vieni a casa mia che <br>ti faccio sentire il mio singolo <br>Molla le tue amiche, vieni a casa mia che <br>ti faccio sentire il mio singolo <br><br>Lo so e una scusa del cazzo ma <br>Esco di casa che fumo e bevo, finche ingoio questa siga e aspiro questo Gin Lemon <br>come lei mette le mani avanti, come lei mette le mani avanti solo quando si piega e io sto dietro e voila <br><br>Voila <br>Voila <br>Sto fuori come un satellite <br>Voila <br>Voila <br>Sto fuori come un satellite <br>Io questa notte, non so, da questo androne chissa dove andro Oooh <br>Io questa notte, non so, non so <br>Molla le tue amiche, vieni a casa mia che <br>ti faccio sentire il mio singolo <br>Molla le tue amiche, vieni a casa mia che <br>ti faccio sentire il mio singolo <br><br>Arriva a casa e voila <br>Voila <br>Voila <br>Sto fuori come un satellite <br>Voila <br>Voila <br>Sto fuori come un satellite <br>Io questa notte, non so, da questo androne chissa dove andro Oooh <br>Io questa notte, non so, non so <br><br>Voila]]></content><category term="Fred De Palma" label="Fred De Palma"/><category term="Voila" label="Voila"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김하은/PRAY/</id><title>김하은 - PRAY - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:11:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:11:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%95%98%EC%9D%80/PRAY/" title="김하은 - PRAY - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[빛이 얼마나 <br>두려웠는지 몰라요 <br>내겐 어둠이 <br>더 익숙했나봐 <br>그 빛이 비치면 <br>다 들킬까봐요 <br>내 부끄러운 상처와 모순 <br>반갑지 않은 그 빛 속에 <br>난 눈이 멀어요 <br>어둠 속에 갇혀버린 날 <br>홀로 무대 위를 <br>비추는 조명 아래 <br>노래를 시작해야만 하던 내게 <br>제발 힘을 달라고 <br>이런 날 안아달라고 <br>나는 주님께 기도했어요 <br>이젠 알아요 <br>내가 울부짖지 않아도 <br>항상 그 품에 <br>내가 있었다는 걸 <br>내 손을 채운 건 <br>마이크가 아니라 <br>그의 손이었다는 것을 <br>잊지마요 <br>잃지마요 <br>빼앗기지마요 <br>내 심장을 <br>뛰게 하는 걸 <br>홀로 무대 위를 <br>비추는 조명 아래 <br>노래를 시작해야만 하던 내게 <br>제발 힘을 달라고 <br>이런 날 안아달라고 <br>나는 주님께 기도했어요 <br>잊지마요 <br>잃지마요 <br>빼앗기지마요 <br>그걸 지켜내야만 해요 <br>홀로 무대 위를 <br>비추는 조명 아래 <br>홀로 무대 위를 <br>비추는 조명 아래 <br>노래를 시작해야만 하던 내게 <br>제발 힘을 달라고 <br>이런 날 안아달라고 <br>오늘도 주님께 기도했어요 <br>그대 손 위엔 <br>무엇이 있나요 <br>무엇이 그댈 빛으로 이끄나요 <br>제발 잊지 말아요 <br>주님이 있다는 것을 <br>오늘도 주님께 기도해봐요 <br>오늘도 주님께 기도해봐요 <br>]]></content><category term="김하은" label="김하은"/><category term="PRAY" label="PRAY"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/다이돌핀/Moonlight_Feat_한수연/</id><title>다이돌핀 - Moonlight (Feat. 한수연) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:11:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:11:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%8C%ED%95%80/Moonlight_Feat_%ED%95%9C%EC%88%98%EC%97%B0/" title="다이돌핀 - Moonlight (Feat. 한수연) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밝아지면 <br>그대는 안보이니까 <br>지나친 하루를 <br>반복하고 또 반복해 <br>아무리 걸어도 <br>나오지 않는 해가 <br>한없이 미울때쯤 <br>그는 꼭 다시 져 <br>Woo <br>다시보니 <br>꽃은 밤에 더 아름다워 <br>그대가 보여 난 <br>하루종일 오늘 밤도 잠 못 이뤄 <br>언제 사라질까 <br>내가 눈감을까 무서워 <br>Where are you moonlight <br>온종일 너만 찾아 떠나갔네 <br>웃음처럼 숨고 보이지 않아 <br>Oh Moonlight <br>오늘마저 짙은 회색이 되어 <br>Please stay the night <br>please stay the night <br>밝아지면 <br>그대는 안보이니까 <br>지나친 하루를 <br>반복하고 또 반복해 <br>아무리 걸어도 <br>나오지 않는 해가 <br>한없이 미울때쯤 <br>그는 꼭 다시 져 <br>Where are you moonlight <br>온종일 너만 찾아 떠나갔네 <br>웃음처럼 숨고 보이지 않아 <br>Oh Moonlight <br>오늘마저 짙은 회색이 되어 <br>Please stay the night <br>please stay the night <br>Where are you moonlight <br>Where are you moonlight <br>]]></content><category term="다이돌핀" label="다이돌핀"/><category term="Moonlight (Feat. 한수연)" label="Moonlight (Feat. 한수연)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/다이돌핀/Stood_Feat_Darin/</id><title>다이돌핀 - Stood (Feat. Darin) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:11:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:11:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%8C%ED%95%80/Stood_Feat_Darin/" title="다이돌핀 - Stood (Feat. Darin) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하얀 손목 위에 핀 라일락은 <br>밤새 두근거리고 <br>손톱 끝이 둥그런게 <br>예쁜 달을 열개나 가졌네 <br>껴안고 자자 <br>아무 말 없어도 좋으니 <br>우리 껴안고 자자 <br>네 목덜미에 얼굴을 묻을래 <br>Every night <br>we stood on the universe <br>And stay with among the stars <br>물 들어가는 곳 <br>손에 닿을 때 <br>눈동자는 빛처럼 <br>언젠가는 <br>지금을 그리워 하겠지 <br>그때 서로를 다시 찾을 수 있게 <br>지금의 너를 잊지마 <br>Every night <br>we stood on the universe <br>And stay with among the stars <br>물 들어가는 곳 <br>손에 닿을때 <br>눈동자는 빛처럼 <br>Every night <br>we stood on the universe <br>Every night <br>we stood on the universe <br>]]></content><category term="다이돌핀" label="다이돌핀"/><category term="Stood (Feat. Darin)" label="Stood (Feat. Darin)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/에이미/떨려/</id><title>에이미 - 떨려 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:11:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:11:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EB%AF%B8/%EB%96%A8%EB%A0%A4/" title="에이미 - 떨려 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너의 곁에 있으면 <br>사랑이 피어나고 <br>정신 못 차리겠어 <br>두근두근 떨려와 <br>네가 옆에 있으면 <br>사랑에 취해버려 <br>너무 매력적인걸 <br>거부할 수 없어 <br>러브 머신 있다면 <br>그게 바로 너인 것 같아 <br>너무 멋진 너의 모습에 <br>난 흠뻑 취해버렸어 <br>너는 러브 머신인 거야 <br>사랑을 자꾸 뿜어내 <br>내 마음을 흔들어 <br>빠져들게 만들어 <br>러브 머신인 거야 <br>사랑이 넘쳐 흐르지 <br>그런 네가 좋아서 <br>내 모든걸 다 줄게 <br>센스 있는 네 성격 <br>너무 매력적이야 <br>항상 즐겁게 하는 <br>특별한 능력 있어 <br>나만 보고 살기를 <br>간절히 기도했어 <br>다른 여자 있으면 <br>내 마음이 아파 <br>러브 머신 바로 너 <br>누가 봐도 멋진 킹카야 <br>너의 품에 안기고 싶어 <br>키스를 하고 싶어져 <br>너는 러브 머신인 거야 <br>사랑을 자꾸 뿜어내 <br>내 마음을 흔들어 <br>빠져들게 만들어 <br>러브 머신인 거야 <br>사랑이 넘쳐 흐르지 <br>그런 네가 좋아서 <br>내 모든걸 다 줄게 <br>나에게는 네가 제일 최고야 <br>나의 사랑 잊지 말고 <br>행복하게 해줘 <br>러브 머신인 거야 <br>사랑을 자꾸 뿜어내 <br>내 마음을 흔들어 <br>빠져들게 만들어 <br>러브 머신인 거야 <br>사랑이 넘쳐 흐르지 <br>그런 네가 좋아서 <br>내 모든걸 다 줄게 <br>러브 머신인 거야 <br>사랑을 자꾸 뿜어내 <br>내 마음을 흔들어 <br>빠져들게 만들어 <br>러브 머신인 거야 <br>사랑이 넘쳐 흐르지 <br>그런 네가 좋아서 <br>내 모든걸 다 줄게 <br>]]></content><category term="에이미" label="에이미"/><category term="떨려" label="떨려"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Yellow/</id><title>Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Yellow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:11:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:11:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Yellow/" title="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Yellow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look at the stars <br>Look how they shine for you <br>And everything you do <br>Yeah, they were all yellow <br>I came along <br>I wrote a song for you <br>And all the things you do <br>And it was called Yellow <br><br>So, then, I took my turn <br>Oh, what a thing to've done <br>And it was all yellow <br><br>Your skin <br>Oh, yeah, your skin and bones <br>Turn it into something beautiful <br>And you know <br>You know I love you so <br>You know I love you so <br>I swam across <br>I jumped across for you <br>Oh, what a thing to do <br>'Cause you were all yellow <br><br>I drew a line <br>I drew a line for you <br>Oh, what a thing to do <br>And it was all yellow <br><br>Your skin <br>Oh, yeah, your skin and bones <br>Turn into something beautiful <br>And you know <br>For you, I'd bleed myself dry <br>For you, I'd bleed myself dry <br>It's true <br>Look how they shine for you <br>Look how they shine for you <br>Look how they shine for <br>Look how they shine for you <br>Look how they shine for you <br>Look how they shine <br><br>Look at the stars <br>Look how they shine for you <br>And all the things that you do]]></content><category term="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers" label="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers"/><category term="Yellow" label="Yellow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Smells_Like_Teen_Spirit_Live/</id><title>Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Smells Like Teen Spirit (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:11:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:11:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Smells_Like_Teen_Spirit_Live/" title="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Smells Like Teen Spirit (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Load up on guns and bring your friends <br>It's fun to lose and to pretend <br>She's over bored and self assured <br>Oh no, I know a dirty word <br><br>Hello, hello, hello, how low <br>Hello, hello <br><br>I'm worse at what I do best <br>And for this gift I feel blessed <br>Our little group has always been <br>And always will until the end <br><br>Hello, hello, hello, how low <br>Hello, hello <br><br>With the lights out, it's less dangerous <br>Here we are now, entertain us <br>I feel stupid and contagious <br>Here we are now, entertain us <br><br>Hello, hello, hello, how low <br>Hello, hello <br><br>With the lights out, it's less dangerous <br>Here we are now, entertain us <br>I feel stupid and contagious <br>Here we are now, entertain us <br>A mulatto <br>An albino <br>A mosquito <br>My libido <br><br>A denial A denial A denial <br>A denial A denial]]></content><category term="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers" label="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers"/><category term="Smells Like Teen Spirit (Live)" label="Smells Like Teen Spirit (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Creep/</id><title>Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Creep - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:11:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:11:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Creep/" title="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Creep - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you were here before <br>Couldn't look you in the eye <br>You're just like an angel <br>Your skin makes me cry <br>You float like a feather <br>In a beautiful world <br>And I wish I was special <br>You're so fuckin' special <br>But I'm a creep I'm a weirdo <br>What the hell am I doing here <br>I don't belong here <br>I don't care if it hurts <br>I want to have control <br>I want a perfect body <br>I want a perfect soul <br>I want you to notice <br>When I'm not around <br>You're so fuckin' special <br>I wish I was special <br>But I'm a creep I'm a weirdo <br>What the hell am I doing here <br>I don't belong here <br>oh oh oh oh <br>She's running out again <br>She's running out <br>She's run run run running out <br>Whatever makes you happy <br>Whatever you want <br>You're so fuckin' special <br>I wish I was special <br>But I'm a creep I'm a weirdo <br>What the hell am I doing here <br>I don't belong here <br>I don't belong here <br>]]></content><category term="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers" label="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers"/><category term="Creep" label="Creep"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Masquerade_Of_Fools/</id><title>Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Masquerade (Of Fools) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:11:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:11:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Masquerade_Of_Fools/" title="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Masquerade (Of Fools) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't be fooled <br>By our looks <br><br>We are no angels <br>With pretty faces <br><br>Oh no <br><br>We sit in darkness <br>But we are watching <br>All of you <br><br>Masquerade of fools <br><br>We've all got secrets <br>We want to keep them <br>From you <br><br>You can't come with us <br>Beneath the surface <br><br>Oh no <br><br>Masquerade 2x <br>Of fools 3x <br><br>The ball commences <br>You feel defenseless <br>Don't you <br><br>We dance in circles <br>We dance with fervor <br>For you <br><br>You try to catch us <br>To take us hostage <br>But we will always disappear before your eyes <br><br>We all are prisoners <br>Of smoke and mirrors <br>And after dark we float away into the night <br><br>Masquerade 2x <br>Of fools 3x]]></content><category term="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers" label="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers"/><category term="Masquerade (Of Fools)" label="Masquerade (Of Fools)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Seashell/</id><title>Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Seashell - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:12:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:12:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Seashell/" title="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Seashell - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Take my hand and come walk with me <br>down towards the enchanting sea <br>I'll run laughing across the sand <br>You'll just smile 'cause you understand <br><br>Watch the sun kiss the rising sea <br>trembling sparkles of ecstasy <br>Waves break, simmer, and then renew <br>just as sometimes a heart can do <br><br>I walked the full length of the beach until <br>I found the most beautiful seashell <br><br>Fragments of all the things you've said <br>smi_le tenderly in my head <br>Beaming sun is still trying to <br>burn the way that I burn for you <br><br>Feel the waves as they fall and rise <br>Breathe in deeply and close my eyes <br>Let me not ever wake from this <br>precious moment of perfect bliss <br><br>I walked the full length of the beach until <br>I found the most beautiful seashell <br><br>Stay here with me <br>down by the sea <br><br>For the others there on that beach <br>ou_r heaven was out of reach <br>They heard only the dolphins' cries <br>We heard music and angels' sighs <br><br>We gazed out to the horizon <br>sea and sky melting into one <br>Whispered line where the blue meets blue <br>Just as vague as where I meet you <br><br>In the wake of that golden day <br>memories still take my breath away <br>I touched heaven when you touched me <br>down beside the enchanting sea <br><br>I walked the full length of the beach until <br>I found the most beautiful seashell, for me <br><br>Sunset glows <br>Come with me <br>One last race <br>to the sea]]></content><category term="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers" label="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers"/><category term="Seashell" label="Seashell"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Our_Last_Fight/</id><title>Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Our Last Fight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:12:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:12:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Our_Last_Fight/" title="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Our Last Fight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Burning with desire and hate <br>Acquiescence sealed our fate <br>Empty rooms and empty eyes <br>Empty promise filled with lies <br><br>I hate you <br>I love you <br>Our last fight, our last fight <br><br>Tortured by the things you said <br>Vice like grip around my head <br>Nothing left to lose or gain <br><br>I abhor <br>I adore <br>Our last fight, our last fight <br><br>I'll grow throns to keep me safe <br>To protect my crumbling faith <br>Bitter, bitter Sweet no more <br>Nothing left worth fighting for <br><br>I loathe you <br>I love you <br>I hate you <br>I loved you <br>Our last fight, our las fight 4x]]></content><category term="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers" label="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers"/><category term="Our Last Fight" label="Our Last Fight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Use_Somebody/</id><title>Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Use Somebody - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:12:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:12:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Use_Somebody/" title="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Use Somebody - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been roaming around <br>Always looking down at all I see <br>Painted faces, fill the places I can't reach <br><br>You know that I could use somebody <br>You know that I could use somebody <br><br>Someone like you, and all you know, and how you speak <br>Countless lovers under cover on the street <br><br>You know that I could use somebody <br>You know that I could use somebody <br>Someone like you <br>Someone like you <br><br>Off in the night, you live it up, while I'm off to sleep <br>Waging wars to shape the poet and the beat <br>I hope it's gonna make you notice <br>I hope it's gonna make you notice <br><br>Someone like me, ooh <br><br>I've been roaming around <br>Always looking down at all I see]]></content><category term="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers" label="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers"/><category term="Use Somebody" label="Use Somebody"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/I_Feel_You/</id><title>Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - I Feel You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:12:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:12:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/I_Feel_You/" title="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - I Feel You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I feel you <br>Your sun it shines <br>I feel you <br>Within my mind <br>You take me there <br>You take me where <br>The kingdom comes <br>You take me to <br>And lead me through Babylon <br><br>This is the morning of our love <br>It's just the dawning of our love <br><br>I feel you <br>Your heart it sings <br>I feel you <br>The joy it brings <br>Where heaven waits <br>Those golden gates <br>And back again <br>You take me to <br>And lead me through oblivion <br><br>This is the morning of our love <br>It's just the dawning of our love <br><br>I feel you <br>Your precious soul <br>And I am whole <br>I feel you <br>Your rising sun <br>My kingdom comes <br><br>I feel you <br>Each move you make <br>I feel you <br>Each breath you take <br>Where angels sing <br>And spread their wings <br>My love's on high <br>You take me home <br>To glory's throne <br>By and by <br><br>This is the morning of our love <br>It's just the dawning of our love]]></content><category term="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers" label="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers"/><category term="I Feel You" label="I Feel You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foo_Fighters/Everlong/</id><title>Foo Fighters - Everlong - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:12:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:12:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foo_Fighters/Everlong/" title="Foo Fighters - Everlong - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[See the stone set in your eyes <br>See the thorn twist in your side <br>I wait for you <br>Sleight of hand and twist of fate <br>On a bed of nails she makes me wait <br>And I wait, without you <br><br>With or without you <br>With or without you <br><br>Through the storm, we reach the shore <br>You gave it all but I want more <br>And I'm waiting for you <br><br>With or without you <br>With or without you <br>I can't live with or without you <br><br>And you give yourself away <br>And you give yourself away <br>And you give, and you give <br>And you give yourself away <br><br>My hands are tied, my body bruised <br>She got me with nothing to win <br>And nothing left to lose <br><br>And you give yourself away <br>And you give yourself away <br>And you give, and you give <br>And you give yourself away <br><br>With or without you <br>With or without you <br>I can't live <br>With or without you <br><br>With or without you <br>With or without you <br>I can't live <br>With or without you <br>With or without you]]></content><category term="Foo Fighters" label="Foo Fighters"/><category term="Everlong" label="Everlong"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Ironic/</id><title>Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Ironic - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:12:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:12:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Ironic/" title="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Ironic - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[An old man turned ninety eight <br>He won the lottery and died the next day <br>It's a black fly in your Chardonnay <br>It's a death row pardon two minutes too late <br>And isn't it ironic don't you think <br><br>It's like rain on your wedding day <br>It's a free ride when you've already paid <br>It's the good advice that you just didn't take <br>And who would've thought it figures <br><br>Mr Play It Safe was afraid to fly <br>He packed his suitcase and kissed his kids good bye <br>He waited his whole damn life to take that flight <br>And as the plane crashed down he thought <br>Well isn't this nice <br>And isn't it ironic don't you think <br><br>It's like rain on your wedding day <br>It's a free ride when you've already paid <br>It's the good advice that you just didn't take <br>And who would've thought it figures <br><br>Well, life has a funny way of sneaking up on you <br>When you think everything's okay and everything's going right <br>And life has a funny way of helping you out when <br>You think everything's gone wrong and everything blows up in your face <br><br>A traffic jam when you're already late <br>A no smoking sign on your cigarette break <br>It's like ten thousand spoons <br>When all you need is a knife <br>It's meeting the man of my dreams <br>And then meeting his beautiful wife, hm <br>And isn't it ironic don't you think <br>A little too ironic and yeah I really do think <br><br>It's like rain on your wedding day <br>It's a free ride when you've already paid <br>It's the good advice that you just didn't take <br>And who would've thought it figures <br><br>Life has a funny way of sneaking up on you <br>Life has a funny, funny way, helping you out <br>Helping you out]]></content><category term="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers" label="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers"/><category term="Ironic" label="Ironic"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Champagne_Supernova/</id><title>Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Champagne Supernova - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:12:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:12:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Champagne_Supernova/" title="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Champagne Supernova - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How many special people change <br>How many lives are living strange <br>Where were you while we were getting high <br>Slowly walking down the hall <br>Faster than a cannonball <br>Where were you while we were getting high <br><br>Someday you will find me <br>Caught beneath the landslide <br>In a champagne supernova in the sky <br>Someday you will find me <br>Caught beneath the landslide <br>In a champagne supernova <br>A champagne supernova in the sky <br><br>Wake up the dawn and ask her why <br>A dreamer dreams she never dies <br>Wipe that tear away now from your eye <br>Slowly walking down the hall <br>Faster than a cannonball <br>Where were you while we were getting high <br><br>Someday you will find me <br>Caught beneath the landslide <br>In a champagne supernova in the sky <br>Someday you will find me <br>Caught beneath the landslide <br>In a champagne supernova <br>A champagne supernova <br><br>'Cause people believe <br>That they're gonna get away for the summer <br>But you and I we live and die <br>The world's still spinning around <br><br>We don't know why <br>Why <br><br>How many special people change <br>How many lives are living strange <br>Where were you while we were getting high <br>Slowly walking down the hall <br>Faster than a cannonball <br>Where were you while we were getting high <br><br>Someday you will find me <br>Caught beneath the landslide <br>In a champagne supernova in the sky <br>Someday you will find me <br>Caught beneath the landslide <br>In a champagne supernova <br>A champagne supernova <br><br>'Cause people believe <br>That they're gonna get away for the summer <br>But you and I we live and die <br>The world's still spinning around <br>We don't know why <br>Why <br><br>How many special people change <br>How many lives are living strange <br>Where were you while we were getting high <br>We were getting high <br>We were getting high <br>We were getting high <br>We were getting high <br>We were getting high <br>We were getting high]]></content><category term="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers" label="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers"/><category term="Champagne Supernova" label="Champagne Supernova"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Solsbury_Hill/</id><title>Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Solsbury Hill - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:12:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:12:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Solsbury_Hill/" title="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Solsbury Hill - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Climbing up on Solsbury Hill <br>I could see the city light <br>Wind was blowing, time stood still <br>Eagle flew out of the night <br>He was something to observe <br>Came in close, I heard a voice <br>Standing, stretching every nerve <br>I had to listen, had no choice <br>I did not believe the information <br>Just had to trust imagination <br>My heart going boom, boom, boom <br>Son, he said, grab your things <br>I've come to take you home <br><br>To keep in silence, I resigned <br>My friends would think I was a nut <br>Turning water into wine <br>Open doors would soon be shut <br>So I went from day to day <br>Though my life was in a rut <br>Till I thought of what I'd say <br><br>Which connection I should cut <br>I was feeling part of the scenery <br>I walked right out of the machinery <br>My heart going boom, boom, boom <br>Hey, he said, Grab your things <br>I've come to take you home <br>Yeah, back home <br><br>When illusion spin her net <br>I'm never where I want to be <br>And liberty, she pirouette <br>When I think that I am free <br>Watched by empty silhouette <br>Who close their eyes but still can see <br>No one taught them etiquette <br>I will show another me <br>Today I don't need a replacement <br>I'll tell them what the smile on my face meant <br>My heart going boom, boom, boom <br>Hey, I said, You can keep my things <br>They've come to take me home]]></content><category term="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers" label="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers"/><category term="Solsbury Hill" label="Solsbury Hill"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Nothing_Else_Matters/</id><title>Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Nothing Else Matters - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:12:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:12:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scala__Kolacny_Brothers/Nothing_Else_Matters/" title="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers - Nothing Else Matters - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So close no matter how far <br>Couldn't be much more from the heart <br>Forever trusting who we are <br>And nothing else matters <br><br>Never opened myself this way <br>Life is ours, we live it our way <br>All these words I don't just say <br>And nothing else matters <br><br>Trust I seek and I find in you <br>Every day for us something new <br>Open mind for a different view <br>And nothing else matters <br><br>Never cared for what they do <br>Never cared for what they know <br>But I know <br><br>So close no matter how far <br>It couldn't be much more from the heart <br>Forever trusting who we are <br>And nothing else matters <br><br>Never cared for what they do <br>Never cared for what they know <br>But I know <br><br>I never opened myself this way hey <br>Life is ours, we live it our way hey <br>All these words I don't just say hey <br>And nothing else matters <br><br>Trust I seek and I find in you <br>Every day for us something new <br>Open mind for a different view <br>And nothing else matters <br><br>Never cared for what they say <br>Never cared for games they play <br>Never cared for what they do <br>Never cared for what they know <br>And I know, yeah yeah <br><br>So close no matter how far <br>Couldn't be much more from the heart <br>Forever trusting who we are <br>No nothing else matters]]></content><category term="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers" label="Scala &amp; Kolacny Brothers"/><category term="Nothing Else Matters" label="Nothing Else Matters"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kpointk/Compte_A_Rebours/</id><title>Kpointk - Compte A Rebours - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:12:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:12:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kpointk/Compte_A_Rebours/" title="Kpointk - Compte A Rebours - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[J'suis bloque comme dans un ascenseur <br>J'attends l'etage de la gloire et je compte les secondes <br>Une fois que j'aurais atteint les sommets, les rageux diront que j'avais tort d'avoir raison <br>J'garde la tete sur les epaules mais j'prefere etre premier que second gardez vos lots de consolation <br>Du fond d'ma banlieue sud j'perds pas le nord et j'pense a mon espece et ma motivation <br><br>Negro moi j'suis pose dans mon ghetto <br>Dis moi qui peux demanteler le reseau <br>Ils veulent tous la part du gateau <br>Et ils veulent fumer sur mon bedo' <br>Un p'tit visser' en bas du ke Blo <br>Il sort le ke Glo si tu cherche les blemes Pro <br>Un frero d'plus en mandat d'depot <br>J'ai but tes soldats sur le te co <br>Wallay billlay j'vais les que cho <br>C'est ma rime qu'ils viendront pe cho <br>J'suis tout seul dans le vaisseau <br>L'arme a la main moi je viens les rechauff' <br>On fait les bay on est reglo <br>Les favos' veulent nous que blo <br>Substance illicite coule dans mes vaisseaux <br>On pense au seille o, on pense au pesos <br>Pour le business on a la releve <br>J'me leve a l'aube et j'le realise <br>Ils ont que du sur leurs levres <br>Marianne j'me barre de ta chatte chez Melanie <br>C'est de mon futur que j'tiens les rennes <br>Mais l'sheitan veut faire ami ami <br>Madame Irma m'a appris <br>Que l'avenir et la vie ont un prix <br><br>J'suis bloque comme dans un ascenseur <br>J'attends l'etage de la gloire et je compte les secondes <br>Une fois que j'aurais atteint les sommets, les rageux diront que j'avais tort d'avoir raison <br>J'garde la tete sur les epaules mais j'prefere etre premier que second gardez vos lots de consolation <br>Du fond d'ma banlieue sud j'perds pas le nord et j'pense a mon espece et ma motivation <br><br>Jamais, jamais, jamais <br>J'n'abandonnerai jamais x4 <br><br>J'suis bloque comme dans un ascenseur <br>J'attends l'etage de la gloire et je compte les secondes <br>Une fois que j'aurais atteint les sommets, les rageux diront que j'avais tort d'avoir raison <br>J'garde la tete sur les epaules mais j'prefere etre premier que second gardez vos lots de consolation <br>Du fond d'ma banlieue sud j'perds pas le nord et j'pense a mon espece et ma motivation <br><br>Negro ouais j'suis pose dans mon repere <br>Et j'vois qu'le temps s'arrete pour sonne per <br>On veut les cles du coffre fort de son pere <br>Et puis la teu cha de la banquiere <br>L'ADN du game sur l'arriere banquette <br>KPoint G j'ecoute pas d'apres les enquetes <br>Cicatrice sur le dos de mes ancetres <br>La vengeance est un plat j'invite Blanchette au banquet <br>Toi qui n'as pas d'imagination n'as pas d'ailes <br>Si t'as pas de savoir t'as pas d'armes <br>J'les vois crier a l'aide, j'vais les rafaler sans etat d'ame <br>C'est de mon futur que j'tiens les rennes <br>Mais l'sheitan veut faire ami ami <br>Le Rap Game est mis a mort <br>J'l'ai baise sans lui dire Mi Amor <br><br>J'suis bloque comme dans un ascenseur <br>J'attends l'etage de la gloire et je compte les secondes <br>Une fois que j'aurais atteint les sommets, les rageux diront que j'avais tort d'avoir raison <br>J'garde la tete sur les epaules mais j'prefere etre premier que second gardez vos lots de consolass' <br>Du fond d'ma banlieue sud j'perd pas le nord et j'pense a mon espece et ma motivass' <br><br>Jamais, jamais, jamais <br>J'n'abandonnerai jamais x4 <br><br>J'suis bloque comme dans un ascenseur <br>J'attends l'etage de la gloire et je compte les secondes <br>Une fois que j'aurais atteint les sommets, les rageux diront que j'avais tort d'avoir raison <br>J'garde la tete sur les epaules mais j'prefere etre premier qu'etre second et vos lots de consolass' <br>Du fond d'ma banlieue sud j'perd pas le nord et j'pense a mon espece et ma motivass']]></content><category term="Kpointk" label="Kpointk"/><category term="Compte A Rebours" label="Compte A Rebours"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이소은/Merry_Christmas/</id><title>이소은 - Merry Christmas - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:12:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:12:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%80/Merry_Christmas/" title="이소은 - Merry Christmas - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘같은 크리스마스에 <br>나는 혼자서 기억을 찾아 <br>지금은 함께 할수 없지만 <br>내 맘이 아프도록 이밤 <br>오늘같은 크리스마스에 <br>나는 혼자서 기도를 드려 <br>혹시나해서 <br>오늘은 그래도 되니까 <br>크리스마스니까 <br>메리 크리스마스 <br>메리 크리스마스 <br>나의 인사 듣고 있니 <br>난 니가 생각나 <br>니가 그리워 <br>지금 이밤 안불 물어 <br>메리 크리스마스 <br>메리 크리스마스 <br>웃으면서 <br>네게 말할께 안녕 <br>안녕 이 노래를 <br>너에게 지금 보내 <br>메리 크리스마스 <br>메리 크리스마스 <br>나의 인사 듣고 있니 <br>난 니가 생각나 <br>니가 그리워 <br>지금 이밤 안불 물어 <br>메리 크리스마스 <br>메리 크리스마스 <br>웃으면서 <br>네게 말할께 안녕 <br>안녕 이 노래를 <br>너에게 지금 보내 <br>]]></content><category term="이소은" label="이소은"/><category term="Merry Christmas" label="Merry Christmas"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/슬리핑/돌아와_줄래/</id><title>슬리핑 - 돌아와 줄래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:12:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:12:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%AC%EB%A6%AC%ED%95%91/%EB%8F%8C%EC%95%84%EC%99%80_%EC%A4%84%EB%9E%98/" title="슬리핑 - 돌아와 줄래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 사랑하니까 <br>아무것도 그 무엇도 <br>난 바라지 않아 <br>그냥 내 옆에 그대로 <br>날 바라보면서 <br>웃어줘 그게 다야 <br>하루를 나 살아도 <br>너만 있으면 난 모든 게 <br>빛나고 또 빛나서 <br>아름다운 걸 <br>너 없이 나는 아무것도 <br>할 수가 없는 걸 <br>그러니까 돌아와 줄래 <br>너 날 떠난 그날도 <br>오늘처럼 바람 불고 <br>참 많이 추웠어 <br>다시 아무 일도 <br>없었던 것처럼 <br>그 길로 내게로 너 <br>걸어오면 돼 <br>하루를 나 살아도 <br>너만 있으면 난 모든 게 <br>빛나고 또 빛나서 <br>아름다운 걸 <br>너 없이 나는 아무것도 <br>할 수가 없는 걸 <br>그러니까 돌아와 줄래 <br>웃으며 나 왔다고 <br>안아주면 돼 <br>그 길로 나에게로 <br>]]></content><category term="슬리핑" label="슬리핑"/><category term="돌아와 줄래" label="돌아와 줄래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이스타아카데미/희망의_빛으로/</id><title>이스타아카데미 - 희망의 빛으로 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:12:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:12:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80%EC%95%84%EC%B9%B4%EB%8D%B0%EB%AF%B8/%ED%9D%AC%EB%A7%9D%EC%9D%98_%EB%B9%9B%EC%9C%BC%EB%A1%9C/" title="이스타아카데미 - 희망의 빛으로 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어느새 차가워진 공기 <br>그만큼 어두운 이 거리엔 <br>수많은 사람들 속에서 <br>조용히 피어난 희망의 별빛 <br>Love 따스한 손을 내밀면 <br>힘겨워도 내일은 웃을 수 있죠 <br>Love 조금만 힘을 낸다면 <br>더 밝게 빛날 수 있어요 <br>I want to be with you with you <br>Forever and ever <br>사랑의 빛으로 영원히 <br>I can fly high with you with you <br>For My Dream For Your Dream <br>우리의 꿈들을 믿어요 <br>아득히 보이지 않아도 <br>서로의 빛이 되어 걸어가요 <br>하늘에 빛나는 별빛도 <br>그대와 나의 길을 비추죠 <br>Love 따스한 손을 내밀면 <br>힘겨워도 내일은 웃을 수 있죠 <br>Love 조금만 힘을 낸다면 <br>더 밝게 빛날 수 있어요 <br>I want to be with you with you <br>Forever and ever <br>사랑의 빛으로 영원히 <br>I can fly high with you with you <br>For My Dream For Your Dream <br>우리의 꿈들을 믿어요 <br>I want to be with you with you <br>Forever and ever <br>사랑의 빛으로 영원히 <br>I can fly high with you with you <br>For My Dream For Your Dream <br>우리의 꿈들을 믿어요 <br>우리의 꿈들을 믿어요 <br>]]></content><category term="이스타아카데미" label="이스타아카데미"/><category term="희망의 빛으로" label="희망의 빛으로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Annabel_Jones/Asking_For_A_Friend_Stripped/</id><title>Annabel Jones - Asking For A Friend (Stripped) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:12:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:12:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Annabel_Jones/Asking_For_A_Friend_Stripped/" title="Annabel Jones - Asking For A Friend (Stripped) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How are you happy <br>I'm asking for a friend <br>Smiling and laughing <br>even when you're feeling bad <br>How do you stay clear <br>I'm asking for a friend <br>Even when you're here <br>you're somewhere else instead <br>When every day is agony <br>it's hard <br>To find somewhere <br>where you can still belong <br>Summer almost came <br>but you left us <br>Things were really bad <br>things got pretty tough <br>Trouble trouble followed you <br>Sadness sadness swallowed you <br>Call to the dark <br>it was broke from the start <br>Love won't fix that part <br>How can you find sleep <br>I'm asking for a friend <br>Quiet still and deep <br>it was simpler back then <br>How do you stay close <br>I'm asking for a friend <br>Stay up sweet recall <br>Maybe you're better off like that <br>When every day is agony <br>it's hard <br>To find somewhere <br>where you can still belong <br>Summer almost came <br>but you left us <br>Things were really bad <br>things got pretty tough <br>Trouble trouble followed you <br>Sadness sadness swallowed you <br>Call to the dark <br>it was broke from the start <br>Love won't fix that part <br>Love won't fix that part <br>]]></content><category term="Annabel Jones" label="Annabel Jones"/><category term="Asking For A Friend (Stripped)" label="Asking For A Friend (Stripped)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박세욱/이별_그리고_1년/</id><title>박세욱 - 이별 그리고 1년 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:12:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:12:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%B1/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EA%B3%A0_1%EB%85%84/" title="박세욱 - 이별 그리고 1년 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어떻게 된 일일까 <br>잠시 자리를 비운 너를 <br>애타게 기다렸을 뿐인데 <br>오늘도 그날처럼 너의 향기를 닮은 <br>라일락 꽃들이 또 활짝 피었네 <br>어떻게 지내는지 아픈 데는 없는지 <br>혹시 길을 잃어서 오고 싶어도 <br>오지 못 하고 있는 건 아닌지 <br><br>나는 오늘도 네가 그리워서 <br>너와 함께 했던 추억들만 떠올리며 살아요 <br>난 괜찮아요 견딜 만해요 살 수 있어요 <br>네가 남겨주고 간 행복했던 <br>기억들이 너무 많아서 <br><br>그날도 오늘처럼 하늘도 함께 울어 <br>미칠것 같은 나를 어루만져 <br>하지만 빗소리에 <br>네가 부르는 소리 못 들을까 봐 <br>걱정만 하고 있어 <br>네가 돌아오는 길 안 보이진 않을까 <br>퍼붓는 빗줄기에 오고 싶어도 <br>오지 못 하고 있는 건 아닌지 <br><br>나는 오늘도 네가 그리워서 <br>너와 함께 했던 추억들만 떠올리며 살아요 <br>난 괜찮아요 견딜 만해요 살 수 있어요 <br>네가 남겨주고 간 행복했던 <br>기억들이 너무 많아서 <br><br>잊지 않을게요 날 사랑해줬던 너를 <br>그 누구보다 최우선으로 날 사랑해줬던 널 <br><br>보고 싶어요 꼭 안고 싶어요 <br>너의 다소곳한 그 손길이 너무나 간절해요 <br>널 기다려요 또 바보처럼 너를 불러요 <br>이런 날 용서해요 아직도 <br>너를보내지 못 하는 나를]]></content><category term="박세욱" label="박세욱"/><category term="이별 그리고 1년" label="이별 그리고 1년"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/키즈캐슬/물거품이_되어_사라진_인어공주/</id><title>키즈캐슬 - 물거품이 되어 사라진 인어공주 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:14:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:14:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%82%A4%EC%A6%88%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/%EB%AC%BC%EA%B1%B0%ED%92%88%EC%9D%B4_%EB%90%98%EC%96%B4_%EC%82%AC%EB%9D%BC%EC%A7%84_%EC%9D%B8%EC%96%B4%EA%B3%B5%EC%A3%BC/" title="키즈캐슬 - 물거품이 되어 사라진 인어공주 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 사랑, 왕자님! 난 당신을 해칠수 없어 <br>다시 인어 공주로 돌아갈 수 없어도 <br>내 사랑, 왕자님! 난 당신을 해칠 수 없어 <br>영원히 당신만을 사랑하고, 기억할게요 <br>]]></content><category term="키즈캐슬" label="키즈캐슬"/><category term="물거품이 되어 사라진 인어공주" label="물거품이 되어 사라진 인어공주"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/키즈캐슬/너의_목소리를_줘야해/</id><title>키즈캐슬 - 너의 목소리를 줘야해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:14:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:14:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%82%A4%EC%A6%88%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/%EB%84%88%EC%9D%98_%EB%AA%A9%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC%EB%A5%BC_%EC%A4%98%EC%95%BC%ED%95%B4/" title="키즈캐슬 - 너의 목소리를 줘야해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 바다 마녀! 못되고 무서운 마녀! <br>사람이 되고 싶다고? 너의 목소리를 줘야 해 <br><br>후회하지 않겠어? 돌이킬 수 없는 약속 <br>마법의 묘약을 마시면, 넌 사람이 될 수 있어 <br>두 다리를 갖게 되는 거야! <br><br>나는 바다 마녀! 못되고 무서운 마녀! <br>사람이 되고 싶다고? 너의 목소리를 줘야 해 <br>]]></content><category term="키즈캐슬" label="키즈캐슬"/><category term="너의 목소리를 줘야해" label="너의 목소리를 줘야해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/키즈캐슬/인어왕국보다_더_멋진_세상/</id><title>키즈캐슬 - 인어왕국보다 더 멋진 세상 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T11:14:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T11:14:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%82%A4%EC%A6%88%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/%EC%9D%B8%EC%96%B4%EC%99%95%EA%B5%AD%EB%B3%B4%EB%8B%A4_%EB%8D%94_%EB%A9%8B%EC%A7%84_%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81/" title="키즈캐슬 - 인어왕국보다 더 멋진 세상 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[인어 왕국보다 더 멋진, 세상이 있을 줄이야 <br>하늘엔 밝은 달이 있고, 달을 보는 예쁜 꽃 있어 <br>인어 왕국보다 더 멋진, 세상이 여기 있다네 <br>꽃과 풀잎의 자장노래, 평화로운 이 밤 <br>]]></content><category term="키즈캐슬" label="키즈캐슬"/><category term="인어왕국보다 더 멋진 세상" label="인어왕국보다 더 멋진 세상"/></entry></feed>