<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:34:24+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양선모/구름이_널_가려서_Vocal_김은비/</id><title>양선모 - 구름이 널 가려서 (Vocal. 김은비) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:04:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:04:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EC%84%A0%EB%AA%A8/%EA%B5%AC%EB%A6%84%EC%9D%B4_%EB%84%90_%EA%B0%80%EB%A0%A4%EC%84%9C_Vocal_%EA%B9%80%EC%9D%80%EB%B9%84/" title="양선모 - 구름이 널 가려서 (Vocal. 김은비) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[구름이 너를 가려 <br>자꾸 보지 못하게 해 <br>참아볼게 하늘의 <br>커튼이 널 가리는 걸 <br>꽃으로 비유하면 <br>뭐가 좋을까 <br>이름을 지었어 <br>다가와줘 꽃 꼭 <br>너의 눈 속 호수안에 <br>깊게 빠진 걸까 <br>너를 자꾸 보지 <br>못하게 하는 <br>이 구름을 걷어 볼까 <br>구름이 널 가려서 <br>너를 보지 못하게 해 <br>다가가지 못하게 하는 <br>이 구름을 걷어 낼래 <br>뭉게뭉게 피어난 <br>부끄럼 쑥스럼 <br>이런 생각을 <br>걷어낼래 구름이 <br>널 가리지 않게 <br>너의 눈 속 호수안에 <br>깊게 빠진 걸까 <br>너를 자꾸 보지 <br>못하게 하는 <br>이 구름을 걷어 볼까 <br>구름이 널 가려서 <br>너를 보지 못하게 해 <br>다가가지 못하게 하는 <br>이 구름을 걷어 낼래 <br>뭉게뭉게 피어난 <br>부끄럼 쑥스럼 <br>이런 생각을 <br>걷어낼래 구름이 <br>널 가리지 않게 <br>구름이 널 가려서 <br>너를 보지 못하게 해 <br>다가가지 못하게 하는 <br>이 구름을 걷어 낼래 <br>뭉게뭉게 피어난 <br>부끄럼 쑥스럼 <br>이런 생각을 <br>걷어낼래 구름이 <br>널 가리지 않게 <br>]]></content><category term="양선모" label="양선모"/><category term="구름이 널 가려서 (Vocal. 김은비)" label="구름이 널 가려서 (Vocal. 김은비)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로건/마음소리/</id><title>로건 - 마음소리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:04:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:04:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EA%B1%B4/%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC/" title="로건 - 마음소리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[네 마음에 소리가 <br>내 마음에 문을 두드려 <br>나에게 전해질 이 설레임 <br>난 기다렸어 <br>첫만남 너에게 <br>어떤말을 전할까 <br>가장 떨리는 이 순간 <br>하늘을 나는 듯한 기분 <br>너와 함께 저 멀리 우주로 <br>끝없이 펼쳐진 세상이 <br>우릴 기다리고 있어 <br>우리에게 올 세상의 빛이 <br>우릴 반기고 있어 <br>우리 둘만의 약속과 <br>우리 둘만의 비밀에 <br>서로의 맘 소리에 <br>너와 함께 그려갈 <br>날들을 상상해 <br>강을 향해 흘러가는 <br>너의 향기를 따라 <br>함께 흘러가는 향기 <br>그때 생각이나 <br>우리가 즐겨 부르던 <br>그 노래가 생각이나 <br>새까만 저 하늘의 별도 <br>너와 나를 비추고 있는걸 <br>끝없이 펼쳐진 세상이 <br>우릴 기다리고 있어 <br>우리에게 올 세상의 빛이 <br>우릴 반기고 있어 <br>우리 둘만의 약속과 <br>우리 둘만의 비밀에 <br>서로의 맘 소리에 <br>너와 함께 그려갈 <br>날들을 상상해 <br>너의 손을 내밀어 <br>나를 놓지 말아줘 <br>어떤 어려움이 있어도 <br>나를 믿고 서로 <br>곁을 지켜준다 약속해줘 <br>네곁에 내가 <br>있다는걸 잊지 마 <br>새로운 나날의 시작이 <br>우릴 기다리고 있어 <br>끝없이 펼쳐진 세상이 <br>우릴 기다리고 있어 <br>우리에게 올 세상이 <br>빛이 우릴 반기고 있어 <br>우리 둘만의 약속과 <br>우리 둘만의 비밀에 <br>서로의 맘 소리에 <br>너와 함께 그려갈 <br>날들을 상상해 <br>너와 함께 그려갈 <br>날들을 상상해 <br>]]></content><category term="로건" label="로건"/><category term="마음소리" label="마음소리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DEAN/넘어와_Feat_백예린/</id><title>DEAN - 넘어와 (Feat. 백예린) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:04:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:04:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DEAN/%EB%84%98%EC%96%B4%EC%99%80_Feat_%EB%B0%B1%EC%98%88%EB%A6%B0/" title="DEAN - 넘어와 (Feat. 백예린) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이런 야심한 밤 <br>그런 걱정을 왜 해 <br>물어볼 뿐이야 <br>오해는 왜 해 <br>TV 드라마로 끝내기엔 <br>저 달이 너무 밝아서 <br>So I just wanna talk <br>about you and me yeah <br>밤하늘 위 잠긴 목소리로 <br>차가워 진 폰을 <br>밤새 달궈 oh no <br>별 말을 안 해도 <br>훌쩍 지나있는 <br>시간 속에 올라타있어 <br>Am I crazy <br>yeah maybe <br>뭘까 어딜까 <br>막 이쁘진 않은데 <br>자꾸만 눈이 가 <br>날 못 살게 구는 게 <br>나도 어지러워 도와줘 <br>밖은 어두워져 <br>Don't you want my love <br>시계 초 소리만 더 커져 <br>거기 멈춰 넘어와 <br>그쯤에서 하고 넘어와 <br>oh baby 넘어와 <br>이 밤을 건너 넘어와 <br>oh baby <br>달처럼 마음도 기우네 <br>할 말은 떨어지고 <br>그 사이를 비집고 <br>정적이 틈을 채우네 <br>밤 새 오늘을 기다렸는데 <br>네 앞에만 서면 <br>난 왜 이리 작아지는지 <br>Oh 왜 <br>길거리 위를 <br>끝없이 서성이며 <br>차가워 진 손을 <br>밤새 달궈 oh no <br>어제처럼 그제처럼 <br>집에 돌아가기엔 <br>I’m so crazy <br>yeah maybe <br>뭘까 어딜까 <br>막 이쁘진 않은데 <br>자꾸만 눈이 가 <br>날 못 살게 구는 게 <br>나도 어지러워 도와줘 <br>밖은 어두워져 <br>Don't you want my love <br>시계 초 소리만 더 커져 <br>너와 나 사이 <br>결론은 없는데 <br>널 보면 이렇게 <br>전부 알 것 같은 게 <br>나도 힘들어 날 도와줘 <br>oh let me into your heart <br>시계 초 소리만 더 커져 <br>바로 그 순간 넘어와 <br>네가 내 쪽으로 넘어와 <br>What should I do baby <br>넘어와 <br>내 맘 속으로 <br>넘어와 <br>]]></content><category term="DEAN" label="DEAN"/><category term="넘어와 (Feat. 백예린)" label="넘어와 (Feat. 백예린)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DEAN/불청객/</id><title>DEAN - 불청객 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:04:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:04:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DEAN/%EB%B6%88%EC%B2%AD%EA%B0%9D/" title="DEAN - 불청객 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 시간에는 <br>비가 오면 안됐어 <br>그 노래를 <br>난 또 틀고 말았어 <br>내 귀에 흥얼거린 <br>기분 좋은 멜로디 <br>날 두드리는 <br>그 기억을 난 못 이겨 <br>그 날 밤 <br>그 눈을 보면 안 됐어 <br>끝내 못 한 <br>몇 마디를 머금은 채로 <br>잠 드는 밤 <br>]]></content><category term="DEAN" label="DEAN"/><category term="불청객" label="불청객"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아기동요/나무송/</id><title>아기동요 - 나무송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:05:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:05:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EA%B8%B0%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/%EB%82%98%EB%AC%B4%EC%86%A1/" title="아기동요 - 나무송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나무는 산소를 뿜어낸대요 <br>깨끗한 공기를 만들어낸대요 <br><br>예쁜 나무를 많이 심어서 <br>공기정화해요 <br>콜록 콜록 매연 싫어 <br>나무를 심어요 <br><br>나무는 종류가 정말로 많아요 <br>열매도 열리고 고무도 만들어 <br><br>나무를 심고 키워보세요 <br>정말로 뿌듯해 <br>공기 좋은 대한민국 <br>나무를 심어요]]></content><category term="아기동요" label="아기동요"/><category term="나무송" label="나무송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/swai_스와이/짝사랑_Feat_폴킴/</id><title>swai_스와이 - 짝사랑 (Feat. 폴킴) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:05:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:05:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/swai_%EC%8A%A4%EC%99%80%EC%9D%B4/%EC%A7%9D%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_Feat_%ED%8F%B4%ED%82%B4/" title="swai_스와이 - 짝사랑 (Feat. 폴킴) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한참을 혼자서 맴돌았지 <br>나만의 생각인 줄 모르고 <br>하루하루가 너의 생각으로 <br>가득한 나만의 날이었어 <br>너를 사랑해선 안될 것 같아 <br>혼자 널 바라보는 일도 <br>너의 사랑 모두 끝난 뒤에 <br>만날 수 있을까 <br>그때까지 널 기다릴거라 <br>말도 못하는 나는 <br>잠들기 전에도 떠오르고 <br>일어나면 생각나는 그 사람 <br>하루하루가 우리 둘만으로 <br>가득할 그 날이 언제 올까 <br>너를 사랑해선 안될 것 같아 <br>혼자 널 바라보는 일도 <br>너의 사랑 모두 끝난 뒤에 <br>만날 수 있을까 <br>그때까지 널 기다릴거라 <br>말도 못하는 나는 <br>혼자 아픔뿐인 난 <br>그 흔한 고백 한번 못하고 <br>너를 이젠 지우려 하고 있어 <br>너를 사랑해선 안될 것 같아 <br>혼자 널 바라보는 일도 <br>너의 사랑 모두 끝난 뒤에 <br>만날 수 있을까 <br>그때까지 널 기다릴거라 <br>말도 못하는 나는 <br>널 사랑해선 안될 것 같아 <br>]]></content><category term="swai (스와이)" label="swai (스와이)"/><category term="짝사랑 (Feat. 폴킴)" label="짝사랑 (Feat. 폴킴)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하룰/시간여행/</id><title>하룰 - 시간여행 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:07:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:07:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EB%A3%B0/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B0%84%EC%97%AC%ED%96%89/" title="하룰 - 시간여행 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그저 스쳐갈 수도 있겠지만 <br>유난히 밝은 햇살에 <br>그만 멈춰 섰던 <br>그때가 우리의 시작이었을까 <br>너와의 기나긴 인연의 시작이 <br>무심한 거리에 눈 녹아 내리고 <br>유난히 낯익은 모습에 <br>그만 멈춰 섰던 <br>우리 흐르는 세월을 품었지만 <br>마음은 그때와 변한 게 없구나 <br>잘 지내니 <br>소리 없이 물어본다 <br>참 오랜만이야 <br>눈빛으로 말해본다 <br>너와 함께한 <br>그리운 추억을 그리며 <br>반갑다 인사를 한다 <br>무심한 거리에 눈 녹아 내리고 <br>유난히 낯익은 모습에 <br>그만 멈춰 섰던 <br>우리 흐르는 세월을 품었지만 <br>마음은 그때와 변한 게 없구나 <br>잘 지내니 <br>소리 없이 불러본다 <br>참 오랜만이야 <br>눈빛으로 말해본다 <br>너와 함께한 <br>그리운 추억을 그리며 <br>반갑다 인사를 한다 <br>잘 지내길 <br>소리 없이 바래본다 <br>잘 가라 내 사랑 <br>이제 정말 안녕이다 <br>긴 시간 찰나에 미소를 지으며 <br>또 한번 이별을 한다 <br>긴 시간 찰나에 미소를 지으며 <br>또 한번 이별을 한다 <br>]]></content><category term="하룰" label="하룰"/><category term="시간여행" label="시간여행"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시우_XIU/Tell_Me_Your_Name/</id><title>시우_XIU - Tell Me Your Name - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:07:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:07:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EC%9A%B0_XIU/Tell_Me_Your_Name/" title="시우_XIU - Tell Me Your Name - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘도 길을 따라 <br>달리고 있어 <br>우연을 기대하는 <br>설렘이 좋아 <br>널 보면 묻고 싶은 <br>질문이 있어 <br>your name your name <br>난 두 번 다시 <br>널 잃고 싶지 않아 <br>망설이지도 않아 <br>너는 내게로 조금씩 <br>나는 네게로 두 손을 잡아 <br>tell me your name <br>my love <br>이 모든 건 우리의 운명 <br>내 목소리를 듣고 <br>니 목소리를 듣고 <br>결국엔 우리 <br>tell me your name <br>my heart <br>이 모든 건 우리의 순간 <br>내 목소리를 듣고 <br>니 목소리를 듣고 <br>결국 만나 지금 <br>tell me your name <br>창가에 기대앉아 <br>너를 기다려 <br>코끝을 스치는 <br>이 바람이 좋아 <br>널 보면 묻고 싶은 <br>질문이 있어 <br>your name your name <br>난 두 번 다시 <br>널 잃고 싶지 않아 <br>망설이지도 않아 <br>너는 내게로 조금씩 <br>나는 내게로 두 손을 잡아 <br>붉은 실의 운명은 <br>너와 나를 감싸고 돌아 <br>스치듯이 내 곁에 <br>숨을 쉬듯 니 곁에 <br>언제나 always <br>tell me your name <br>my love <br>이 모든 건 우리의 운명 <br>내 목소리를 듣고 <br>니 목소리를 듣고 <br>결국엔 우리 <br>tell me your name <br>my heart <br>이 모든 건 우리의 순간 <br>내 목소리를 듣고 <br>니 목소리를 듣고 <br>결국 만나 지금 <br>tell me your name <br>]]></content><category term="시우 (XIU)" label="시우 (XIU)"/><category term="Tell Me Your Name" label="Tell Me Your Name"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Hersey/Everyones_Talking/</id><title>James_Hersey - Everyone`s Talking - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:11:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:11:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Hersey/Everyones_Talking/" title="James_Hersey - Everyone`s Talking - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Came to my place last night <br>For a glass of the only wine I like <br>And everything about you cried out <br>That everyone around you right now <br>Can't see what it is that you need <br>Can't see what it is that you see <br>In me, in me <br>Can't see what it is you see in me <br><br>And everyone's talking now <br>Everyone's talking <br>Everyone's got their own <br>Words of unpaid advice <br>Everyone else knows how <br>Everyone's talking <br>How it could be right this time <br>But could it be right this time <br><br>I'm back from my trip out to sea <br>With a story and more, we could be so close <br>Tide on a coast <br>Tied like the soul of a mind to a ghost <br>I've got too many things on the line <br>To lose what I know I could find <br>I see something in you <br>And I can tell that you do too <br><br>But everyone's talking now <br>Everyone's talking <br>Everyone's got their own <br>Words of unpaid advice <br>Everyone else knows how <br>Everyone's talking <br>How it could be right this time <br>But could it be right this time <br><br>What do they know <br>What do they know <br>What do they know <br>Tell me, what do they know <br>What do they know <br>What do they know <br>Tell me, what do they know <br>What do they know <br>Tell me, what do they know <br>What do they know <br>Tell me, what do they know <br>What do they know <br>Tell me, what do they know <br>What do they know <br>What do they know <br>Tell me, what do they know <br><br>And everyone's talking now <br>Everyone's talking <br>Everyone's got there own <br>Words of unpaid advice <br>Everyone else knows how <br>Everyone's talking <br>How it could be right this time <br>But could it be right this time]]></content><category term="James Hersey" label="James Hersey"/><category term="Everyone`s Talking" label="Everyone`s Talking"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/웨더/졸업_Feat_남지/</id><title>웨더 - 졸업 (Feat. 남지) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:11:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:11:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9B%A8%EB%8D%94/%EC%A1%B8%EC%97%85_Feat_%EB%82%A8%EC%A7%80/" title="웨더 - 졸업 (Feat. 남지) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 졸업식이야 <br>벌써 눈물이 나려 해 <br>처음 버스에서 <br>마주쳤을 때 <br>너 기억하니 <br>우리 좋아한다고 <br>농담처럼 쉽게 하는 말 <br>너가 좋아한 사람도 <br>모르는 것 없는 <br>친구 사이 <br>언제 비가 오던 날 <br>같이 우산 쓰던 날 <br>그때 그때였을까 <br>어색해진 그때는 <br>모른척했지만 너가 <br>설레었던 것 같아 <br>너를 좋아해 <br>너를 바라보고 있어 <br>공부만 아는 넌 <br>너는 모를 수도 있어 <br>너를 좋아해 <br>너를 바라보고 있어 <br>졸업을 하고 <br>어른이 되면 <br>우리 만날 수 있을까 <br>같이 앉던 자리 <br>조그만 낙서들 <br>추억들을 꺼내보며 <br>너를 찾았어 <br>전부터 말하고 싶었어 <br>이제야 조금은 <br>알 것 같아 <br>오늘에서야 너에게 <br>나 고백할게 <br>너를 좋아하고 있어 <br>시간이 흘러도 <br>어디 가지 말고 있어 <br>나 고백할게 <br>너를 좋아한단 말이야 <br>졸업을 하고 <br>어른이 되면 <br>우리 만날 수 있을까 <br>]]></content><category term="웨더" label="웨더"/><category term="졸업 (Feat. 남지)" label="졸업 (Feat. 남지)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이승재/눈동자/</id><title>이승재 - 눈동자 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:12:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:12:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%B9%EC%9E%AC/%EB%88%88%EB%8F%99%EC%9E%90/" title="이승재 - 눈동자 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그날 밤 이슬이 맺힌 <br>눈동자 그 눈동자 <br>가슴에 내가슴에 남아 <br>외롭게 외롭게 울려만주네 <br>안개 안개 <br>자욱한 그날 밤 거리 <br>다시 돌아올 날 <br>기약없는 이별에 <br>뜨거운 이슬 맺혔나 <br>고독이 밀리는 밤이 오면 <br>가슴속에 떠오르는 <br>눈동자 그 눈동자 <br>아 아 그리운 눈동자여 <br><br>안개 안개 <br>자욱한 그날 밤 거리 <br>다시 돌아올 날 <br>기약없는 이별에 <br>뜨거운 이슬 맺혔나 <br>고독이 밀리는 밤이 오면 <br>가슴속에 떠오르는 <br>눈동자 그 눈동자 <br>아 아 그리운 눈동자여]]></content><category term="이승재" label="이승재"/><category term="눈동자" label="눈동자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시클루_Sickloo/모른체/</id><title>시클루_Sickloo - 모른체 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:14:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:14:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%ED%81%B4%EB%A3%A8_Sickloo/%EB%AA%A8%EB%A5%B8%EC%B2%B4/" title="시클루_Sickloo - 모른체 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 시간에 온 <br>이유가 뭔데 <br>밤늦게 이제와서 <br>도대체 뭔데 <br>아무 상관 없지 <br>아무 상관 없지 <br>무슨 말이 <br>더 뭐가 필요해 <br>다 알면서 <br>전혀 모르겠다고 <br>모르겠다고 <br>시치미를 뚝 뗄래 <br>하나도 모른다고 <br>뭔 뜻인지 모른다고 <br>아니면 대놓고 <br>칫솔 하나랑 <br>베게를 더 꺼낼래 <br>아무도 모른다고 <br>아무도 모른다고 <br>뭐 좀 먹을래 <br>이 시간은 <br>조금 출출해 <br>폰 상태는 어때 <br>배터리 조금 충전해 <br>몸 좀 녹일래 <br>날씨가 조금은 춥네 <br>이런 말 뻘쭘해 <br>그냥 비밀번호 알려줄게 <br>이 시간에 온 <br>이유가 뭔데 <br>밤늦게 이제와서 <br>도대체 뭔데 <br>아무 상관없지 <br>아무 상관없지 <br>무슨 말이 <br>더 뭐가 필요해 <br>다 알면서 <br>모른체 해 모른체 해 <br>넌 웃어 말없이 <br>넌 웃어 말없이 <br>무슨 말이 <br>더 뭐가 필요해 <br>모른체 해 <br>모른체 해 <br>넌 웃어 말없이 <br>넌 웃어 말없이 <br>무슨 말이 <br>더 뭐가 필요해 <br>다 알면서 <br>편의점 좀 다녀올게 baby <br>편의점 좀 다녀올게 baby <br>뭔말인지 알지 <br>뭔말인지 알지 babe <br>뭔말인지 알지 <br>모른체 해줘 <br>이 시간에 온 <br>이유가 뭔데 <br>밤늦게 이제와서 <br>도대체 뭔데 <br>아무 상관없지 <br>아무 상관없지 <br>무슨 말이 <br>더 뭐가 필요해 <br>모른체 해 <br>모른체 해 <br>넌 웃어 말없이 <br>넌 웃어 말없이 <br>무슨 말이 <br>더 뭐가 필요해 <br>다 알면서 <br>]]></content><category term="시클루 (Sickloo)" label="시클루 (Sickloo)"/><category term="모른체" label="모른체"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로즈퀸/Hot_In_Here/</id><title>로즈퀸 - Hot In Here - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:15:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:15:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EC%A6%88%ED%80%B8/Hot_In_Here/" title="로즈퀸 - Hot In Here - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[R O S E the queen is back <br>Rose Queen <br>Attention <br>정신차리고 가 <br>이제 거의 다와 가 <br>너와 내 비밀의 방 <br>도착했어 <br>Patience <br>조금 기다려봐 <br>너무 서두르지 마 <br>사랑 할 시간 많아 <br>알아듣겠어 <br>밤 이 아름다운 밤 <br>니 눈은 <br>going down <br>어딜 봐 나의 눈을 <br>바라 봐줘 <br>밤 깊은 한겨울 밤 <br>흰 눈은 <br>going down <br>어딜 봐 나의 맘을 <br>알아 봐줘요 <br>오 그대여 이리 와요 <br>나를 안아줘요 <br>오 그대여 나의 마음 <br>속으로 들어와요 <br>Yes turn me up <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Yes turn me up <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Yes turn me up <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Yes turn me up <br>Why so hot in here <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Why so hot in here <br>Why so hot in here <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Why so hot in here <br>Why so hot in here <br>Temptation <br>내게 눈 맞춰봐 <br>좀 더 가까이 와 봐 <br>손부터 이리 줘 봐 <br>긴장했어 <br>Relaxin' <br>내 옆에 앉아봐 <br>가까이 더 붙어 봐 <br>심장소리 들어봐 <br>확인했어 <br>밤 이 아름다운 밤 <br>니 눈은 <br>going down <br>어딜 봐 나의 눈을 <br>바라 봐줘 <br>밤 깊은 한겨울 밤 <br>흰 눈은 <br>going down <br>어딜 봐 나의 맘을 <br>알아 봐줘요 <br>오 그대여 이리 와요 <br>나를 안아줘요 <br>오 그대여 나의 마음 <br>속으로 들어와요 <br>Yes turn me up <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Yes turn me up <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Yes turn me up <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Yes turn me up <br>Why so hot in here <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Why so hot in here <br>Why so hot in here <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Why so hot in here <br>Why so hot in here <br>날 안아 줘요 부드럽게 <br>왜이리 밝아 부끄럽게 <br>고민하지 말고 내게 말해봐 <br>들어줄게 난 OK <br>Let's do this and I will fly <br>I will fly high <br>hot 너무 핫해 뜨거운 밤 <br>So hot in here <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Why why why so hot in here <br>Why so hot in here <br>Why so hot in here <br>]]></content><category term="로즈퀸" label="로즈퀸"/><category term="Hot In Here" label="Hot In Here"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dia_Frampton/Dead_Man/</id><title>Dia_Frampton - Dead Man - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:15:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:15:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dia_Frampton/Dead_Man/" title="Dia_Frampton - Dead Man - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Thought I felt the water <br>flooding in <br>I fought for hours <br>but then I caved in <br>And I knew the moment that I lost <br>When you held me in your arms <br>And I know you won't <br>let me dare forget you <br>I know that I'll never <br>really want to <br>Look at what you've done <br>Look what I've become <br>You're looking at a dead man <br>You're looking at a dead man <br>I know it's too late <br>I feel good in your chains <br>You're looking at a dead man <br>You're looking at a dead man <br>Never knew <br>that love could feel so torn <br>My arms are heavy <br>They're brick and bone <br>Had I blinked the moment <br>that we met <br>You stopped my heart beat <br>It didn't start again <br>And I know you won't <br>let me dare forget you <br>I know that I'll never <br>really want to <br>Look at what you've done <br>Look what I've become <br>You're looking at a dead man <br>You're looking at a dead man <br>I know it's too late <br>I feel good in your chains <br>You're looking at a dead man <br>You're looking at a dead man <br>Round and round and round <br>and round we fall <br>Never gonna get around your walls <br>Don't you turn away from me <br>don't you turn away from me again <br>Look at what you've done <br>Look what I've become <br>You're looking at a dead man <br>You're looking at a dead man <br>I know it's too late <br>I feel good in your chains <br>You're looking at a dead man <br>You're looking at a dead man <br>]]></content><category term="Dia Frampton" label="Dia Frampton"/><category term="Dead Man" label="Dead Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스킬레토_Skilleto/날_바라봐_Feat_Till_The_Morning/</id><title>스킬레토_Skilleto - 날 바라봐 (Feat. Till The Morning) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:16:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:16:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%82%AC%EB%A0%88%ED%86%A0_Skilleto/%EB%82%A0_%EB%B0%94%EB%9D%BC%EB%B4%90_Feat_Till_The_Morning/" title="스킬레토_Skilleto - 날 바라봐 (Feat. Till The Morning) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이건 내 이야기이자 <br>니 이야기야 우리 이야기야 <br>이건 니 이야기이자 <br>내 이야기야 우리 이야기야 <br>이건 내 이야기이자 <br>니 이야기야 우리 이야기야 <br>이건 니 이야기이자 <br>내 이야기야 우리 이야기야 <br>날 바라봐 <br>야 그때의 날 바라봐 <br>그때의 날 바라봐 <br>야 야 야 날 바라봐 <br>하얀 와이셔츠 또 검은색 마이 <br>뿔테 안경 난 고등학생답지 <br>열 일곱 살에 <br>내가 처음 힙합을 만난 다음에도 <br>변화는 없지 <br>여전히 머리는 반삭임 <br>고등학생답지 <br>난 고등학생 다웠지 <br>회색 바지는 8통 반 <br>내 나름의 반칙 <br>난 계속해 계속 랩 공부 <br>랩 공부 랩 공부 <br>둘 중 하나를 택한대도 <br>공수래공수거네 <br>so 좆 되기 밖에 더하겠어 <br>좆 될 것 같지 않아 그래서 <br>한 우물 파 우물 파 우물 파 <br>수능은 망했어 <br>날 매섭게 죄어댄 <br>앞선 자들의 매연에 <br>속이 메슥거리지 <br>축하는 해줘도 눈이 매웠네 <br>속으로 욕을 게워내 <br>게워내 게워냈지 <br>MANGO Mr. Bulldog <br>NOAH 그리고 210 <br>PJD 싸이 홈피가 <br>그 시절의 자녹게였고 <br>그들은 어느새 어른이 돼서 <br>공장으로 또 군대로 <br>아직도 랩 하는 중이냐 <br>그래 나만 랩 하는 중이고 <br>전에 꿈꾸던 생활 잘 하고 있지 <br>나 잘 살고 있지 <br>사실 잘 살진 못해 <br>알바 두 개 하고 있지 <br>내 가치 싸 보이지 <br>그 면상에 내 랩을 쏴 보이지 <br>일련의 시련이 <br>날 굳건히 만들어 <br>man now I do easy <br>날 바라봐 <br>야 야 이젠 날 바라봐 <br>이젠 지금의 날 바라봐 <br>my fan my fam <br>my friend my Fabrik <br>지금의 날 바라봐 <br>날 바라봐 <br>야 야 이젠 날 바라봐 <br>야 이젠 지금의 날 바라봐 <br>my fan my fam <br>my friend my Fabrik <br>지금의 날 바라봐 <br>이건 내 이야기이자 <br>니 이야기야 우리 이야기야 <br>이건 니 이야기이자 <br>내 이야기야 우리 이야기야 <br>이건 내 이야기이자 <br>니 이야기야 우리 이야기야 <br>이건 니 이야기이자 <br>내 이야기야 우리 이야기야 <br>이건 내 이야기이자 <br>니 이야기야 우리 이야기야 <br>현실의 벽 넘었다고 생각했지만 <br>아직 계란을 깬 삐약이야 <br>시련 맞닥뜨리면 피하기만 <br>나태는 내 정신의 피하지방 <br>전엔 꿈에 고팠지만 나란 새끼는 <br>이젠 포만감에 취하기만 <br>야 씨발 정신차려 <br>개병신같이 뭐하고 다녀 <br>니가 지금 놀 때냐 <br>랩 존나 못 하는 게 <br>왜 그러고 살어 <br>난 벌거벗은 임금 <br>나 빼고 전부 뭘 아는 기분 <br>훤히 드러난 내 치부 <br>이젠 날 바라봐 비웃어 <br>]]></content><category term="스킬레토 (Skilleto)" label="스킬레토 (Skilleto)"/><category term="날 바라봐 (Feat. Till The Morning)" label="날 바라봐 (Feat. Till The Morning)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스킬레토_Skilleto/My_Shit/</id><title>스킬레토_Skilleto - My Shit - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:16:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:16:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%82%AC%EB%A0%88%ED%86%A0_Skilleto/My_Shit/" title="스킬레토_Skilleto - My Shit - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[7년 전 3월쯤이었지 <br>좋은 대학교가 <br>목표가 아니게 돼버린 뒤 <br>내 목소리는 살았어 <br>친구 놈들의 mp3 속에서 <br>달라진 건 없고 <br>난 그대로 커버렸지 <br>이젠 터전의 변화 <br>수원에서 신촌 신촌에서 고양 <br>내 출신은 공책 위 <br>충남 당진은 황승익의 고향 <br>먼 길을 달려야 했기에 <br>매일 밤 손등에 채찍을 쳐왔지만 <br>점차 둥글게 닳아 <br>둥글게 닳아 내 자각의 모양 <br>나태의 원인 <br>꽤나 많은 핑계를 댈 수 있겠지 <br>망쳤다고 자책하던 무대에도 <br>사람들은 That shit crazy <br>내가 배신했지 <br>자만은 노력을 대신했지 <br>이것 또한 내가 음악을 한다고 <br>차마 말을 못하는 <br>이유가 될 수 있겠지 <br>난 내게 당당치 못해도 <br>욕망은 참지 못해서 <br>괴리감에 나를 던져 놓을 때야 <br>비로소 가사를 썼네 <br>이 적성은 내게 너무 가혹해 <br>Sometimes I feel like I'm 오토다케 <br>그 무력감의 조그만 방에 <br>갇힌 채로 나는 또 쥐어짜내 my shit <br>난 음악을 안 해 Just doing my shit <br>부족함에 난 그냥 숨고만 싶지 <br>도 못 할 바에 난 토해내 my shit <br>야 칭찬 다 좆까 난 존나 싫어 my shit <br>난 음악을 못해 Just doing my shit <br>부족함에 난 그냥 죽고만 싶지 <br>도 못 할 바에 난 토해내 my shit <br>my shit my shit my shit <br>랩 못해 실력 없어 <br>가사도 못쓰고 <br>프리스타일도 못해 좆도 없어 <br>날 치켜 올릴수록 <br>더 낮아지는 현실 <br>내 삶이 자이로드롭 <br>그 낙차가 싫어 두렵지 <br>떨어지는 자존감은 <br>안전벨트 하나 없이 <br>붕 떠있었었기에 난 <br>그저 날고 있는 줄만 알았지 <br>허나 지금 하나씩 하나씩 <br>또 닳아 찢겨지는 내 껍질 <br>벗겨진 내 허영심 속 결국 <br>온전한 내 것이 무엇인지 <br>애새끼 같던 나는 <br>칭찬이 고팠으니까 <br>늘 바랬던 환호로 자위해봐도 <br>느껴지는 엄한 이질감 <br>나만 어딘가 <br>동떨어진 기분 <br>이젠 내 치부인 굳어진 입을 <br>벌리고 연습 술로 마취하고 <br>현실에 안치하는 기술 <br>무력해 확신 속의 <br>의문의 실존에 <br>커지고는 싶은데 <br>나아가진 않는 나를 죽이곤 해 <br>난 아무것도 아니지 <br>좀 더 숨어 들어가 깊이 <br>뭐라도 된 것 마냥 하려 한 게 아냐 <br>난 그냥 하고 싶었단 말야 my shit <br>난 음악을 안 해 Just doing my shit <br>부족함에 난 그냥 숨고만 싶지 <br>도 못 할 바에 난 토해내 my shit <br>야 칭찬 다 좆까 난 존나 싫어 my shit <br>난 음악을 못해 Just doing my shit <br>부족함에 난 그냥 죽고만 싶지 <br>도 못 할 바에 난 토해내 my shit <br>my shit my shit my shit <br>]]></content><category term="스킬레토 (Skilleto)" label="스킬레토 (Skilleto)"/><category term="My Shit" label="My Shit"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/슈퍼걸/날나리/</id><title>슈퍼걸 - 날나리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:17:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:17:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%88%ED%8D%BC%EA%B1%B8/%EB%82%A0%EB%82%98%EB%A6%AC/" title="슈퍼걸 - 날나리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[부킹의 여왕 부킹의 여왕 <br>내 별명 되고 말았어 <br>부킹을 하면 언제나 성공 <br>킹카가 내 손안에 들어와 <br>부킹의 여왕 부킹의 여왕 <br>친구들 부러워하지 <br>비법을 알려달라며 <br>매일마다 내게 전화를 걸어 <br>별거 없어 나를 꾸미고 <br>솔직한 이야기 하고 <br>이야길 들어주면서 <br>환하게 웃어주면 돼 <br>나는 부킹의 여왕이 된 거야 <br>타고난 재능인지도 몰라 <br>토요일 클럽에 갈 때면 <br>언제나 자신이 생겨 <br>나는 부킹의 여왕이 된 거야 <br>하지만 고급스럽게 놀아 <br>화끈한 시간을 보내고 <br>평소엔 열심히 일하는 여자 <br>부킹의 여왕 부킹의 여왕 <br>웃기는 별명이지만 <br>그만큼 잘하는 거야 <br>갈 때마다 멋진 남자를 만나 <br>내 매력에 빠져드는걸 <br>적당히 즐기면서 <br>밤새도록 마시고 <br>신나게 춤추는 거야 <br>나는 부킹의 여왕이 된 거야 <br>타고난 재능인지도 몰라 <br>토요일 클럽에 갈 때면 <br>언제나 자신이 생겨 <br>나는 부킹의 여왕이 된 거야 <br>하지만 고급스럽게 놀아 <br>화끈한 시간을 보내고 <br>평소엔 열심히 일하는 여자 <br>부킹의 여왕이 된 거야 <br>타고난 재능인지도 몰라 <br>토요일 클럽에 갈 때면 <br>언제나 자신이 생겨 <br>나는 부킹의 여왕이 된 거야 <br>하지만 고급스럽게 놀아 <br>화끈한 시간을 보내고 <br>평소엔 열심히 일하는 여자 <br>]]></content><category term="슈퍼걸" label="슈퍼걸"/><category term="날나리" label="날나리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하나/Ninano/</id><title>하나 - Ninano - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:17:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:17:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EB%82%98/Ninano/" title="하나 - Ninano - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니나노 니나노 니나노 <br>니나노 니나노 늴리리야 <br>니나노 니나노 니나노 <br>니나노 <br>짜증을 내어서 무엇 하나 <br>니나노 니나노 니나노 <br>니나노 니나노 늴리리야 <br>니나노 니나노 니나노 <br>니나노 <br>짜증을 내어서 무엇 하나 <br>니나노 니나노 니나노 <br>니나노 니나노 늴리리야 <br>니나노 니나노 니나노 <br>니나노 <br>짜증을 내어서 무엇 하나 <br>늴리리야 늴리리야 늴리리야 <br>아니 노지는 못하리라 <br>늴리리야 늴리리야 늴리리야 <br>늴리리야 늴리리야 늴리리야 <br>아니 노지는 못하리라 <br>]]></content><category term="하나" label="하나"/><category term="Ninano" label="Ninano"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김남훈/징징대지마_Feat_Cheshire_김예지/</id><title>김남훈 - 징징대지마 (Feat. Cheshire, 김예지) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:18:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:18:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%82%A8%ED%9B%88/%EC%A7%95%EC%A7%95%EB%8C%80%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88_Feat_Cheshire_%EA%B9%80%EC%98%88%EC%A7%80/" title="김남훈 - 징징대지마 (Feat. Cheshire, 김예지) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다 사줄게 징징대지 좀 마 <br>넌 어떡하려고 그러는데 <br>돈이 없니 왜 <br>나한테만 빌붙어 사는데 <br>너는 아이언맨은 아니지만 <br>낯짝 두꺼운 철판 같은 얼굴 <br>니 가방은 토르 <br>해머보다 무거워 <br>내가 들지 매일 들지 <br>가끔은 헐크로 변해서 나를 <br>못 잡아먹어 안달복달하지만 <br>난 너의 캡틴아메리카가 <br>되어 줄게 <br>다 사줄게 징징대지 좀 마 <br>넌 어떡하려고 그러는데 <br>돈이 없니 왜 <br>나한테만 빌붙어 사는데 <br>다 해줄게 재촉하지 좀 마 <br>난 어떡하라고 그러는데 <br>겁이 없니 왜 <br>뭘 믿고 그리 당돌한 건데 <br>yo guitar solo right <br>야 너 내 눈 보고 말해 <br>사랑한단 말 진심 이길 바래 <br>카운터 앞에서 항상 <br>진실을 보내 <br>이게 가끔 사랑인지 <br>의심이 가네 <br>날 사랑한단 것보다는 <br>내 카들 사랑한다고 보이는 <br>이런 속상한 의심이 싫어 <br>이게 그냥 착각 이길 <br>신에게 빌어 <br>난 믿었어 날 잡은 니 손을 <br>봐버렸어 숨기는 니 손을 <br>난 원하지도 않아 더치페이 <br>베이베 매일매일 <br>내가 사주는데 <br>아보카도 아메리카노 <br>에스프레소 투샷 프라푸치노 <br>빌어먹을 이 딴 게 뭐가 중요해 <br>내가 널 사랑하면 됐지 <br>다 사줄게 징징대지 좀 마 <br>um 안 그래 <br>넌 어떡하려고 그러는데 <br>돈이 없니 왜 <br>나한테만 빌붙어 사는데 <br>다 해줄게 재촉하지 좀 마 <br>난 어떡하라고 그러는데 <br>겁이 없니 왜 <br>뭘 믿고 그리 당돌한 건데 <br>아 이거 사달라고 <br>]]></content><category term="김남훈" label="김남훈"/><category term="징징대지마 (Feat. Cheshire, 김예지)" label="징징대지마 (Feat. Cheshire, 김예지)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/멜로디_정_Melody_Jung/새봄_Feat_김보령/</id><title>멜로디_정_Melody_Jung - 새봄 (Feat. 김보령) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:19:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:19:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A9%9C%EB%A1%9C%EB%94%94_%EC%A0%95_Melody_Jung/%EC%83%88%EB%B4%84_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EB%B3%B4%EB%A0%B9/" title="멜로디_정_Melody_Jung - 새봄 (Feat. 김보령) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[콘크리트 바닥의 차가움 <br>해가 지고 오는 <br>푸르스름한 칼날 같은 저녁 <br>땅밑으로 꺼져가는 <br>내 영혼과 나의 힘 <br>나를 잃어버린 깊은 슬픔과 아픔 <br>그 아픔 상처 그 눈물 때문에 <br>내가 사랑을 알게 되었으니 <br>나에게서 떠나지 말고 머물러라 <br>나에게 머물러 <br>내가 사랑이 되게 하라 <br>어린 아이의 마음속 다락방 <br>그 곳에 살고 있는 귀신 <br>땅밑으로 꺼져가는 <br>내 영혼과 나의 힘 <br>나를 잃어버린 깊은 슬픔과 아픔 <br>그 아픔 상처 그 눈물 때문에 <br>내가 사랑을 알게 되었으니 <br>나에게서 떠나지 말고 머물러라 <br>나에게 머물러 <br>내가 사랑이 되게 하라 <br>그 아픔 상처 그 눈물 때문에 <br>내가 사랑을 알게 되었으니 <br>나에게서 떠나지 말고 머물러라 <br>나에게 머물러 <br>내가 사랑이 되게 하라 <br>긴 겨울을 지나 새봄이 되게 하라 <br>]]></content><category term="멜로디 정 (Melody Jung)" label="멜로디 정 (Melody Jung)"/><category term="새봄 (Feat. 김보령)" label="새봄 (Feat. 김보령)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MTAT/DANG/</id><title>MTAT - DANG...! - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:19:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:19:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MTAT/DANG/" title="MTAT - DANG...! - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나 둘 데려왔지 <br>내 옆에 새워도 <br>될만한 애들로 <br>M T A T gotta get that cake <br>우리 테이블엔 <br>제일 좋은것들로 <br>채워놓지 u see <br>움직이다 보니 조금 이뤄냈지 <br>잠을 못 자서 <br>머리가 매일 아파도 <br>빡세게 뛰려해 <br>더 좋은 내년을 위해 <br>난 다른 카테고리에 <br>설래 어리숙한 애들하고 <br>날 섞지마 baby <br>옷이라도 흉내낸다면 모를까 <br>아가들은 무신사 없으면 <br>옷을 사지도 못해 <br>아주 심각한 문제야 baby <br>그럴거면 다시 <br>학교로 가 baby <br>get ur identity 삶의 방식 <br>역시 챙겨야지 baby <br>팔공산 boys <br>움직이지 매일 <br>january to december <br>매일 창작하지 <br>생각을 굳힐 생각 없으니 <br>또 풀어야지 aye <br>aye aye we gon boomin <br>언제나 빡세게 <br>우린 막 나가지 Dang <br>울려 댕댕 새 소리를 댕 <br>착하지만 우린 <br>막 나가지 Dang <br>울려 댕댕 새 소리를 댕 <br>착하지만 우린 <br>막 나가지 Dang <br>울려 댕댕 새 소리를 댕 <br>착하지만 우린 <br>막 나가지 Dang <br>울려 댕댕 새 소리를 댕 <br>착하지만 우린 <br>막 나가지 Dang <br>너거들의 연기와 정치는 <br>지금은 날 이겼지만 <br>병신들 모두를 <br>만들꺼지 벌집 <br>Trigga Comin at ya <br>행동하지않는 <br>말은 멋이 없지 <br>그러니 걸어 <br>무대를 만들어 노래를 <br>근데 잘 없더라고 <br>날 불러주는데는 <br>자만심에 빠진 허우대들 <br>난 너네 패배를 <br>담을거지 angle에 <br>내려라 고개를 <br>그래 변해야만하지 <br>내가 먼저 <br>세상은 나를 위해 <br>변해주지않어 <br>혼자 헤메일땐 누구도 <br>손 잡아주지않어 <br>오히려 날 만만하게봤어 <br>fuck these rappers <br>이 꼬맹이는 위협하고 <br>니들 입장 난처하게 하지 <br>작업실에서 쩌는 <br>view 볼 때까지 <br>쩌는 view 볼 때까지 <br>난 부질없이 <br>부들거리는게 일인 <br>느그 기분 맞춰주지못해 <br>구린건 무시하지 <br>연락 받지 않어 <br>친절하게 알려주지못해 <br>난 내가 믿는 믿음 믿어 <br>인마 성공은 <br>좋은 기운에서 온데 <br>젊은 전인권의 행진 <br>shout out to M T A T <br>middle finger up and goin up ye <br>우린 막 나가지 Dang <br>울려 댕댕 새 소리를 댕 <br>착하지만 우린 <br>막 나가지 Dang <br>울려 댕댕 새 소리를 댕 <br>착하지만 우린 <br>막 나가지 Dang <br>울려 댕댕 새 소리를 댕 <br>착하지만 우린 <br>막 나가지 Dang <br>울려 댕댕 새 소리를 댕 <br>착하지만 우린 <br>막 나가지 Dang <br>계속 이어 다음 차례 <br>이건 실업 같은 거고 <br>너에게는 해당되는거니 들어 <br>Ice link와 age <br>얼어버린 자식들 <br>땡땡 때려 장도리 민식이 형 <br>확실히 나는 인사부 high한 <br>feel과 흰 사표를 주어 <br>정치는 됐고 100% represent <br>장인 어르신 대 <br>선배 대 선생 <br>대충 내 앞길을 계산하면 <br>뚫린길만 두 눈에 보여 <br>하필 섞이는 불쌍패들은 <br>눈물이 두 눈위 흐르네 <br>자꾸만 고여 <br>grab the mic M T A T <br>came from My D Town <br>with my family Anti 와 trigga <br>We Came from the Top down <br>치밀한 뇌구조 <br>심리학도 팬 굴림의 TOMSSON <br>feel like I'm bad mother fuckin <br>ass <br>탄력이 실려 내 궁둥짝에 <br>이어폰을 타고 <br>너네들도 그려 <br>상상의 나래를 느끼니 <br>나의 몸동작을 <br>한번 말고 두번 <br>두번 말고 세번 새겨 <br>새겨둘 필요가 있지 <br>물론 다음은 <br>내 첫번째 LP와 행보 <br>내 여자와 나의 행복 <br>go shine'em <br>]]></content><category term="M.T.A.T" label="M.T.A.T"/><category term="DANG...!" label="DANG...!"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/촌놈/허수아비/</id><title>촌놈 - 허수아비 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:20:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:20:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%8C%EB%86%88/%ED%97%88%EC%88%98%EC%95%84%EB%B9%84/" title="촌놈 - 허수아비 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[따뜻한 햇살 틈 사이로 <br>그대 뒷모습을 보았죠 <br>부끄러워서 말도 못 하는 <br>고개 숙여서 그대를 보았죠 <br>항상 니 곁에서 <br>니가 쓰러질 까봐 <br>비가 오는 날이면 <br>두팔 벌려 그대를 지켰죠 <br>난 허수아비 같은 사람이 <br>항상 곁에서 지켜주는 나 <br>혹시나 니가 넘어질까봐 <br>지켜봐 주는 나 <br>난 허수아비 같은 사랑을 <br>하고 싶다고 늘 생각하죠 <br>그대가 혹시 떠나갈까봐 <br>지켜만 보는 <br>난 그대만 생각해 <br>어느 그 순간부터 <br>나를 보는 그 시선 <br>자꾸만 신경 쓰여 <br>뛰는 가슴 숨기려고 했죠 <br>난 허수아비 같은 사람이 <br>항상 곁에서 지켜주는 나 <br>혹시나 니가 넘어질까봐 <br>지켜봐 주는 나 <br>난 허수아비 같은 사랑을 <br>하고 싶다고 늘 생각하죠 <br>그대가 혹시 떠나갈까봐 <br>지켜만 보는 <br>난 그대만 생각해 <br>비가 오는 날에는 <br>그대를 지키려 <br>두 팔을 내밀어 <br>노래로 불렀죠 <br>난 허수아비 같은 사람이 <br>항상 곁에서 지켜주는 나 <br>혹시나 니가 넘어질까봐 <br>지켜봐 주는 나 <br>난 허수아비 같은 사랑을 <br>하고 싶다고 늘 생각하죠 <br>그대가 혹시 떠나갈까봐 <br>지켜만 보는 <br>난 그대만 생각해 <br>]]></content><category term="촌놈" label="촌놈"/><category term="허수아비" label="허수아비"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엔트로피_블루_Entropy_blue/어떤_힘/</id><title>엔트로피_블루_Entropy_blue - 어떤 힘 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:21:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:21:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%94%ED%8A%B8%EB%A1%9C%ED%94%BC_%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8_Entropy_blue/%EC%96%B4%EB%96%A4_%ED%9E%98/" title="엔트로피_블루_Entropy_blue - 어떤 힘 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그저 바라보았지 <br>내 맘에 널 새기듯이 <br>오늘이 지나면 널 다신 <br>못 볼 것 같이 <br>우리는 그 상태를 <br>사랑이라고 말하지 <br>계절처럼 변해가는 것 <br>아주 천천히 <br>너를 바라보던 그 사람은 <br>내가 아닌 누군가였는지도 몰라 <br>너를 사랑했던 그 사람은 <br>혹은 내가 아닌 <br>어떤 힘이었는지도 몰라 <br>그저 바라보았지 <br>내 맘에 널 새기듯이 <br>일렁이는 바람 속에도 <br>니가 있었지 <br>우리는 그 감정을 <br>사랑이라고 말했지 <br>다른 어떤 말로도 <br>설명할 수 없는 그 한 마디 <br>너를 바라보던 그 사람은 <br>내가 아닌 누군가였는지도 몰라 <br>너를 사랑했던 그 사람은 <br>혹은 내가 아닌 <br>어떤 힘이었는지도 몰라 <br>어떤 힘이었는지도 몰라 <br>]]></content><category term="엔트로피 블루 (Entropy blue)" label="엔트로피 블루 (Entropy blue)"/><category term="어떤 힘" label="어떤 힘"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KKlim/Fantasy_Feat_M_Jay_Loti/</id><title>KKlim - Fantasy (Feat. M Jay, Loti) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:21:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:21:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KKlim/Fantasy_Feat_M_Jay_Loti/" title="KKlim - Fantasy (Feat. M Jay, Loti) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[길을 잃게 되었을 때 <br>Don't be afraid <br>i'm in my fantasy Yeah eh <br>혼자라고 느껴질 때 <br>Don't be afraid <br>i'm in my fantasy Yeah eh <br>생각처럼 안돼도 <br>I must believe myself <br>And I know the way <br>so can run away Yeah eh <br>매일 밤 봐왔던 <br>My Paradise Whenever <br>절대 잊지 않게 <br>Write up turn on the lighter <br>모든 것이 변해도 <br>변하지 않는 것 <br>And I know the way <br>so can run away Yeah eh <br>매일 밤 봐왔던 <br>My Paradise Whenever <br>절대 잊지 않게 <br>Write up turn on the lighter <br>평소보다 조금 <br>특별할 지 모를 <br>하루가 내일이길 <br>나는 잠들었어 오늘도 <br>똑같은 일들을 <br>똑같이 했지 미친 <br>귀신이 되고 말거야 <br>말하는게 나 진심이야 <br>미안해 난 <br>꿈이있어 어제부터 <br>내게 우선인건 <br>내가 정한게 아냐 줄서 <br>내가 상상한 이상 <br>그 세곈 어딘가 존재하는거야 <br>수백 수천 가지 이상의 이상 <br>내 손에 쥐는 안개같이 내일도 <br>뿌옇게 여전히 안 개지만 <br>잡힐듯 말듯 그 너머 <br>그게 있는곳 말야 <br>상상해봐 현실이 되는 날 <br>무엇이 우리 앞에 있을지 <br>난 떨려 눈이 감기질 않아 <br>어제 따위 더이상 <br>눈에 뵈질 않아 <br>Get the fuck out here <br>전부 내 옆에서 꺼져 <br>내일 일기예보는 <br>맑음이야 Wuh <br>매일 밤 봐왔던 <br>My Paradise Whenever <br>절대 잊지 않게 <br>Write up turn on the lighter <br>매일 밤 봐왔던 <br>My Paradise Whenever <br>One in the million <br>It's me ay <br>One in the million <br>It's me ay <br>One in the million <br>It's me ay <br>One in the million <br>It's me ay <br>One in the million <br>It's me ay <br>]]></content><category term="KKlim" label="KKlim"/><category term="Fantasy (Feat. M Jay, Loti)" label="Fantasy (Feat. M Jay, Loti)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KKlim/Bail__Release_Feat_Dos_Addic/</id><title>KKlim - Bail &amp; Release (Feat. Dos Addic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:21:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:21:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KKlim/Bail__Release_Feat_Dos_Addic/" title="KKlim - Bail &amp; Release (Feat. Dos Addic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[돈이 없는 게 <br>내게 죄가 된다면 <br>감옥 안에 살고 있어 <br>더 나은 날을 <br>창살을 바라보며 꿈꾸지 <br>큰 집 안에 더럽고 <br>무섭기만 한 이 방을 <br>벗어나기를 그런 적이 <br>있었더라면 <br>매일 난 기도 드리고 신을 <br>믿기 위해 무릎이 닳도록 <br>절했겠지만 <br>잊고 있었던 신음 <br>부모님의 얼굴에 먹칠을 하고 <br>나를 가로막기에 바빴던 돈 <br>그 종이 몇 장을 무시하고 <br>동시에 쫓아야 했기에 <br>외다리와 목발로 <br>무게를 버텨 <br>달리는 내게 복잡한 <br>문제는 없어 <br>답 또한 있을 수 없으니 <br>받아드리는 게 맞다고 믿어 <br>Mayday 누군가 배가 부를 때 <br>누군가는 빵 조가리를 구걸해 <br>그게 자신의 아버지의 탓인데 <br>세상은 원망한 새낀 <br>모두 불효래 <br>물론 어떤 아버지든 <br>어깨에 가장 사랑하는 짐을 져 <br>난 단지 그렇게 강하신 분들의 <br>혼자 흘린 눈물이 싫을 뿐야 <br>Bail 종이 몇 장에 <br>바뀌는 내 삶 <br>Bail 언제쯤 이곳을 벗어날까 <br>Bail 내 친구의 눈물은 <br>언제 그칠까 <br>Bail Bail <br>몇 백억도 해쳐먹는 세상에 <br>내 친구는 점심을 굶었네 <br>그 새낀 오히려 <br>밝은 표정으로 <br>나와 나 같은 놈 만나는 게 <br>너무 화가 치밀어 올라 <br>없는 돈으로 술을 마셨지만 <br>술은 깨면서 종이 <br>몇 장 손에 쥐는 <br>꿈에서는 깨지는 못했네 <br>불어 버린 컵라면 같은 <br>나의 청춘 이제는 식어가 <br>누구의 청춘은 밝게 <br>축복을 받으며 혼자 빛나지만 <br>그 사이에 낄 수 조차 없는 <br>우리의 고립된 현실을 쳐다봐 <br>사회가 만든 악순환의 고리 <br>끊으려면 더 단단한 칼을 가져와 <br>주먹 사이에 가시가 끼었다고 <br>화가 안 날 수 가 있을까 <br>피 흘리고 있는 내 손엔 <br>누군가의 땀이나 <br>닦아봤지만 사실 다 <br>눈물 뿐이였다는 걸 <br>알게 된다면 <br>그 사람들이 얼마나 <br>원망스러울까 <br>그저 째려만 봐 고개가 <br>부러질 것 같아도 <br>Mayday 누군가 배가 부를 때 <br>누군가는 빵 조가리를 구걸해 <br>그게 자신의 어머니의 탓인데 <br>세상은 원망한 새낀 <br>모두 불효래 <br>물론 어떤 어머니든 <br>어깨에 가장 사랑하는 짐을 져 <br>난 단지 그렇게 강하신 분들의 <br>혼자 흘린 눈물이 싫을 뿐야 <br>Bail 종이 몇 장에 바뀌는 내 삶 <br>Bail 언제쯤 이곳을 벗어 날까 <br>Bail 내 친구의 눈물은 <br>언제 그칠까 <br>Bail 저 하늘같은 <br>나랏 님들은 뭔가 다를까 <br>내 친구들의 폐에 물이 <br>들어가는 중이라도 <br>누굴 구하려 할 때 <br>누군간 그 상황을 피하려 <br>애쓰지도 않고 눈길을 <br>반대에 돌렸네 <br>그 중에 그 사람의 아들 딸 <br>혹은 아는 사람이 <br>있었더라면 다 <br>살 수 도 있었을 거라고 <br>생각이 든다면 <br>그건 비관적인 생각일까 <br>더 이상 내가 그 분들께 <br>드릴 실망감이 없어 <br>우린 어차피 어릴 때부터 <br>무의식적으로 다 배워왔어 <br>어떻게든 의지 할 곳 없고 <br>혼자 이겨내야 된다는 걸 <br>가난은 피보다 진하다는 것도 <br>Mayday Mayday <br>내가 악순환을 <br>끊기 위해서 <br>종이 몇 장을 쥐어주고 <br>왕을 죽여줘 Yo <br>Mayday Mayday <br>내가 악순환을 <br>끊기 위해서 <br>종이 몇 장을 쥐어주고 <br>왕을 죽여줘 워 <br>Bail 종이 몇 장에 바뀌는 내 삶 <br>Bail 언제쯤 이곳을 벗어날까 <br>Bail 내 친구의 눈물은 <br>언제 그칠까 <br>Bail Bail <br>바깥 공기는 어때 <br>내가 말했던 대로 <br>모두 느끼지 <br>그곳에서 못 본 햇볕에 <br>몸 다 녹이고 <br>자유를 좀 느끼지 <br>바깥 공기는 어때 <br>내가 말했던 대로 <br>모두 느끼지 <br>그곳에서 못 본 햇볕에 <br>몸 다 녹이고 <br>자유를 좀 느끼지 <br>돈이 없는 게 내게 <br>죄가 될 리가 <br>난 여전히 내 할 일을 <br>하고 있을 뿐 <br>그게 돈을 부른다고는 <br>생각 안 해 <br>난 그저 내 노래들을 <br>듣는 게 좋았을 뿐 <br>아무도 몰라주는 <br>나의 노래에 <br>잘 들었다는 친하지도 <br>않은 친구들의 대답에 <br>나 혼자 기분이 <br>좋아서 괜히 미소 <br>짓는 것에 난 다 이뤄냈네 <br>오늘 비운 잔에 미련을 <br>두지 말자 <br>기분 좋게 취했으니 말야 <br>앞으로도 그냥 이렇게만 <br>살고 싶어 <br>돈 없으면 없는 대로 <br>있어본 적은 없어도 <br>나의 이름값에 존재하는 가치가 <br>겨우 종이 몇 장으로 결정될 리가 <br>가능 하다면 난 그런 <br>것들이 없어도 괜찮아 <br>바깥 공기는 어때 <br>내가 말했던 대로 모두 느끼지 <br>그곳에서 못 본 햇볕에 <br>몸 다 녹이고 자유를 좀 느끼지 <br>바깥 공기는 어때 <br>내가 말했던 대로 모두 느끼지 <br>그곳에서 못 본 햇볕에 <br>몸 다 녹이고 자유를 좀 느끼지 <br>돈이 없는 건 절대로 <br>죄가 아니야 <br>우리 자신을 감옥에 <br>가둬놓은 게 죄야 <br>앞에 보이는 기회를 <br>놓치지 않는다면 <br>차례엔 닿을 테니 일단 <br>목표로 두자 <br>신을 믿지는 않겠지만 <br>있다면 그 분들이 <br>내게 준 작지만 <br>커질 수 있는 가능성을 <br>바라보자 <br>시련을 주셔도 이길 수 <br>있을 정도만 <br>존재 할 테니 흘러가는 대로 <br>그 물살은 조금 거칠 <br>수가 있대도 <br>애초부터 그랬다며 <br>위로를 하고 <br>우리가 의지했던 노를 <br>놓치지 말자 <br>누군가 술주정을 부리면서도 <br>했던 얘기 창피하지만 <br>잊어서도 <br>안되니까 입은 막고 <br>머리에 그리고 <br>가슴팍 주머니 정도에다는 <br>넣어둬 <br>바깥 공기는 어때 <br>내가 말했던 대로 <br>모두 느끼지 <br>그곳에서 못 본 햇볕에 <br>몸 다 녹이고 자유를 <br>좀 느끼지 <br>바깥 공기는 어때 <br>내가 말했던 대로 <br>모두 느끼지 <br>그곳에서 못 본 햇볕에 <br>몸 다 녹이고 자유를 <br>좀 느끼지 <br>돈이 없는 게 죄로만 <br>느껴질 거야 <br>너가 하고 있는 일까지도 <br>돈이 되지 않아 <br>꿈 깨고 현실을 또 깼지만 <br>더욱 더 많은 장애물이 <br>보여 눈을 가릴 거야 <br>괜찮다고 말을 해줄 수 <br>없는 내가 <br>위로라고 해주는 게 <br>겨우 힘내자 <br>밖에 안돼서 괜히 <br>미안한 마음이 들어 <br>한다면 너가 더 <br>미안할거잖아 <br>너와 내가 서로 <br>가둬놓은 방에서 <br>전 재산인 젊음들 <br>모두 팔아서 <br>대충 저녁에 두부에 소주한잔 <br>욕하는 사람은 어차피 <br>너의 편이 아냐 <br>돈을 번다고 뭔가 달라질 거 없어 <br>하지만 절대 너가 가난할 리 없어 <br>일단 이 조그만한 방 3 개와 <br>음악 몇 곡 으로도 행복하잖아 <br>]]></content><category term="KKlim" label="KKlim"/><category term="Bail &amp; Release (Feat. Dos Addic)" label="Bail &amp; Release (Feat. Dos Addic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KKlim/399_Feat_Loti_Gando_Mang/</id><title>KKlim - 399 (Feat. Loti, Gando Mang) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:21:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:21:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KKlim/399_Feat_Loti_Gando_Mang/" title="KKlim - 399 (Feat. Loti, Gando Mang) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 돼 있어야 할 건 <br>워커홀릭 <br>내가 만들고 지녀야 하는 <br>지독한 My own thing <br>그래 내가 듣고 <br>싶어하는 것은 <br>Oh shit 내 Music 으로 <br>듣는 거야 <br>그걸 오직 <br>Feeling Lotiful man <br>ya Feeling Lotiful man <br>넌 내걸 듣고 있네 <br>물어 기분이 어때 <br>Does it make shit or you <br>think you can say oh shit <br>할 수 있을지 또 한번 하네 <br>내가 진정 신경 쓴 건 <br>나의 태도였지 <br>시작과 진행 중은 <br>완전하게 다르니 <br>그때의 나랑은 절때로 <br>같을 수 없고 <br>오늘이 옳은 모습일지는 <br>또 모르니까 <br>That day m makes n now <br>It maybe become 399 <br>is shape from the m mine <br>399 is my shape now <br>That day m makes n now <br>It maybe become 399 <br>is shape from the m mine <br>399 is my shape now <br>399 지금 많이 바꼈지만 난 <br>내게 말을 거네 <br>짧기보단 영원해 <br>One lovin' 여전해 <br>내가 좋아하는 거 하고 살지 <br>돈은 꿈에서 맨날 버네 <br>잠깐도 멈추지 못하지 시간은 <br>Gettin' fly <br>앞자리가 바껴도 <br>계속되는 내리막 <br>I fuck it get bigger <br>Maklin' my own shit <br>I welcome my empire <br>it's your emperor <br>남다른 목표 <br>Look up back in the days <br>달라진 건 내 Ambition <br>Stack is on so <br>내 거를 해 <br>시간은 어차피 지나가지 <br>I ballin' on grind now <br>checkin' old shit <br>Originality shit made <br>in my team <br>미랜 모르지만 확인하지 <br>Man I feel like <br>I be still 내 꺼 My shit <br>난 아직 Untill get high <br>시작도 안 했지 <br>가까워지는 느낌 <br>Feelin' close to it <br>close to it close to it <br>close to it close to it <br>That day m makes n now <br>It maybe become 399 <br>is shape from the m mine <br>399 is my shape now <br>That day m makes n now <br>It maybe become 399 <br>is shape from the m mine <br>399 is my shape now <br>내가 돼 있어야 하는 <br>Fuckin 워커홀릭 <br>But 내가 할 수 있는 일은 <br>아직 별로 없지 <br>하지만 나의 작은 한 두 가지 <br>Make my body <br>그걸 만들어내려 또 <br>Make my spirit <br>날 완성하지 <br>내가 듣고 싶어하는 <br>Oh shit 오지 않았지만 <br>아직 멀리 있는 <br>My music but I don't care <br>내 모습 <br>399 is shape from the m mine <br>]]></content><category term="KKlim" label="KKlim"/><category term="399 (Feat. Loti, Gando Mang)" label="399 (Feat. Loti, Gando Mang)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KKlim/난간에_기대어_Feat_Gando_Mang/</id><title>KKlim - 난간에 기대어 (Feat. Gando Mang) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:21:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:21:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KKlim/%EB%82%9C%EA%B0%84%EC%97%90_%EA%B8%B0%EB%8C%80%EC%96%B4_Feat_Gando_Mang/" title="KKlim - 난간에 기대어 (Feat. Gando Mang) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[걔네 무슨 말을 하든지 내비둬 <br>Ready for the big show <br>Gon' better fix yo <br>Don't know a shit about my life <br>따라만하면 돼 That banda na <br>Gettin' that music <br>눈으로 간 보지마 <br>내 음악에 굳지 피가 <br>You wanna sip it one time <br>work hard but so far <br>빨리 가는 시간에 <br>닿기엔 너무 높아 <br>Never maintain <br>it shit culture는 이미 <br>퍼져나갔지 <br>I got me Feelin' me Only me <br>One love I do shit <br>Back to the basic <br>Spit fire 내 불씨 <br>Message는 찾아 볼 수 없지 <br>I can make it <br>니 말의 반은 억지 <br>Gonna run this <br>shit fucka maybe <br>you know ma daily <br>내게 많아 내일이 <br>썩어빠져버리기는 About time <br>그와 상관없는 난 Hot I <br>Be me 내가 돼 Try to be I <br>Do you feel me <br>My shit on fire be sossa <br>썩어빠져버리기는 About time <br>그와 상관없는 난 Hot I <br>Be me 내가 돼 Try to be I <br>Do you feel me <br>My shit on fire be sossa <br>수많은 Fuckin bullshit <br>내 앞을 막았지 <br>네 말이 안 들리지 <br>I beg your pardon me be <br>Hot never freeze <br>on the beat 내 것만 해 <br>All that shit try to fuck me <br>never mind it <br>수많은 Fuckin bullshit <br>내 앞을 막았지 <br>네 말이 안 들리지 <br>I beg your pardon me be <br>Hot never freeze <br>on the beat 내 것만 해 <br>All that shit try to fuck me <br>never mind it <br>]]></content><category term="KKlim" label="KKlim"/><category term="난간에 기대어 (Feat. Gando Mang)" label="난간에 기대어 (Feat. Gando Mang)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KKlim/책상_Feat_Dos_Addic_M_Jay_Ninesix/</id><title>KKlim - 책상 (Feat. Dos Addic, M Jay, Ninesix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:21:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:21:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KKlim/%EC%B1%85%EC%83%81_Feat_Dos_Addic_M_Jay_Ninesix/" title="KKlim - 책상 (Feat. Dos Addic, M Jay, Ninesix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[적당히 해가 지고 <br>어두운 밤에 <br>난 방안에 불을 키고 <br>책상에 위에 올려진 <br>기계들을 두드리고 있어 <br>창작보다는 생산이 더 <br>어울리는 이런 <br>일거리를 난 더욱 <br>찾아야 된다니 <br>내 과거에는 좀 더 <br>자유롭게 하기 <br>싫은 거는 만지기도 싫어서 <br>그만두거나 새 걸로 만들었는데 <br>그게 이제는 힘들까 <br>항상 난 까만 이 책상 앞에 <br>까만 이 방안에서 Mind use mind <br>Bae 원해 Will be perfect <br>잊지마 내 맘을 Remind rewind oh <br>무언가 만들어내야 <br>된다는 부담과 <br>욕심이 존재하는 <br>나의 공간 안 <br>난 서서히 더 죽어가며 <br>좀더 새로운 걸 <br>찾기 위해 정신이 <br>조금은 취한 채로 <br>자리에 앉아 <br>가만히 또 생각만 하다 <br>나온 결과를 <br>보고 나서야 실망을 맞아 <br>괜한 불안감이 <br>조금 몰려 올때쯤 <br>남들의 우월함에 <br>좌절하고 눈을 감아 <br>너무 어려 <br>억울하기까지 했던 시절 <br>젊다는 게 좋아서 <br>흥분한 지금까지도 <br>난 이 자리에 <br>있을 때만이 열정적 <br>이였기에 그런 생각이 <br>나를 괴롭혀 <br>그래도 괜찮다고 <br>생각이 드는 건 <br>아직 그 열정이 식지는 <br>않았다는 증거 <br>영감이 자리한 <br>내 머리 속 보다 더 <br>좁은 이 공간에 <br>나는 또 지기는 싫다고 <br>책상 위에 먼지를 <br>모두 닦아 내고서 <br>의자 위에 앉아 <br>그게 결과물의 복선 <br>난 처절하게 매달려 <br>완성을 해야 해 <br>그게 누군가에 귀에 <br>들리지는 않더라도 <br>이 비좁은 방안에 <br>책상에서부터 <br>내 삶의 가운데 자리한 <br>갈증으로부터 <br>불안한 미래를 위한 <br>욕심으로부터 <br>난 결국에는 이런 음악 <br>위에서 또 숨쉬어 <br>항상 난 까만 이 책상 앞에 <br>까만 이 방안에서 Mind use mind <br>Bae 원해 Will be perfect <br>잊지마 내 맘을 Remind rewind oh <br>Yeah 1996 <br>내가 태어난 시기 <br>또 내 이름의 출처 <br>같은 공간을 살았던 놈들은 <br>알 거야 아마 각자 어깨에 <br>걸린 기대감만큼 <br>무거운 가방을 들던 때 <br>말야 내게 그때는 <br>2012 아마 내 가사에 <br>계속 나올 시기 <br>겠지 참 답 없게도 <br>뭣 같던 때였네 <br>매일 밤과 낮 책상 앞 <br>비트 없이 가사를 <br>끄적여 놔도 박자는 <br>안 맞아 빡이 돌아가 <br>What the fuck is going on <br>답답해도 뭐 어쩌겠어 <br>난 계속 강짜를 놓고 <br>밀어붙였지 계속해서 <br>뱉다 보면 아니 버티다 보면 <br>뭐라도 될 거야 <br>엄마 걱정하지마 <br>그저 앉아만 있던 <br>날들이 아냐 이 밤이 <br>주는 차가움을 <br>모른다고는 말 하지마 <br>너도 분명 느껴봤어 <br>벗어났다고 해서 <br>나 같은 놈의 밤이 <br>무의미하다고 그럼 비켜 <br>Motherfucker 난 <br>큰 그림을 그리지 <br>내 미래에 연결된 <br>모든 것들과 함께 <br>My team CMC <br>또 내 동네친구 <br>지금은 군대 갔어도 꼭 한잔해 <br>모든 게 잘 되길 바래 I got bless <br>그게 부담되던 날들을 <br>안주로 삼게 <br>Gando mang XIX MONDAY <br>To you rap shout <br>to COSMOSCODE 모두 <br>항상 난 까만 이 책상 앞에 <br>까만 이 방안에서 Mind use mind <br>Bae 원해 Will be perfect <br>잊지마 내 맘을 Remind rewind oh <br>]]></content><category term="KKlim" label="KKlim"/><category term="책상 (Feat. Dos Addic, M Jay, Ninesix)" label="책상 (Feat. Dos Addic, M Jay, Ninesix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/애시드콕_Acidcoke/불토밤끝_Feat_Cordu/</id><title>애시드콕_Acidcoke - 불토밤끝 (Feat. Cordu) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:21:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:21:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%A0%EC%8B%9C%EB%93%9C%EC%BD%95_Acidcoke/%EB%B6%88%ED%86%A0%EB%B0%A4%EB%81%9D_Feat_Cordu/" title="애시드콕_Acidcoke - 불토밤끝 (Feat. Cordu) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What's up Saturday night <br>오늘도 어김없이 <br>허무하게 지나간 <br>하루의 끝은 역시 <br>컵라면과 맥주한캔 <br>무한도전을 다시보기로 봐 <br>친구한테 도착한 사진을 <br>보기전까진 기분 좋았지 <br>갑자기 기분 뭣같지 <br>이쁜 girl friend랑 있는걸 <br>왜 내게 보내 <br>뭐 겉으로는 시큰둥 <br>하기 얘기했지만 <br>나 되게 처량해 <br>내 폰에 연락처엔 <br>사내놈만 채워놨네 <br>홀로 alone and lonely 방구석 <br>솔로몬 왕의 권리로 반으로 <br>다 가르고 싶어 내 맘 같아선 <br>오해는 하지마 여자는 만나봤어 <br>그냥 단지 지금 외로울뿐 <br>가슴에 사무치는 혼자라는 울분 <br>지금 만날 사람 없어 <br>제발 연락하면 받아줘 <br>페북 인스타에 업로드 <br>쫌 자랑하지 말아줘 <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>꽤 차갑게 감아오는 날씨 <br>근데도 토요일이라 <br>불타는 밤일 <br>다른 애들과는 달리 <br>난 언제나처럼 <br>나의 좁은 방이지 <br>편의점 햄버거의 무거운 맛 <br>당기는 맥주는 <br>그래도 스물둘 까진 <br>같이 먹을 사람이 <br>있던것 같은데 <br>이제는 혼자 안주를 <br>고르는게 숙제 <br>Rockin 구제 쌀쌀해 <br>움츠리고 뚜벅뚜벅 <br>강제로 여행해 <br>다른이들의 불토 투어 <br>쿨한척 맥주 한캔 <br>골라 계산대로 <br>안주는 없어도 <br>뭐 괜찮겠죠 <br>남들 다 갖는 주말 밤을 <br>want it <br>어느날 네게서 없어졌다면 <br>내가 범인 <br>혼자 적시는 밤이 적응 됐네 <br>혼자 뎁히고 혼자 잠드는 <br>saturday <br>지금 만날 사람 없어 <br>제발 연락하면 받아줘 <br>페북 인스타에 업로드 <br>쫌 자랑하지 말아줘 <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>Hey Hey Saturday <br>Monday Tuesday Wednesday <br>Thursday Friday Saturday <br>Monday Tuesday Wednesday <br>Thursday Friday Saturday <br>Monday Tuesday Wednesday <br>Thursday Friday Saturday <br>Monday Tuesday Wednesday <br>Thursday Friday Saturday <br>뭔가 될 것같은 토요일 밤에 <br>오늘 밤 토요일의 끝에서 <br>뭔가 될 것같은 토요일 밤에 <br>오늘 밤 토요일의 끝에서 <br>]]></content><category term="애시드콕 (Acidcoke)" label="애시드콕 (Acidcoke)"/><category term="불토밤끝 (Feat. Cordu)" label="불토밤끝 (Feat. Cordu)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/위수_WISUE/예쁘다/</id><title>위수_WISUE - 예쁘다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:21:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:21:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%84%EC%88%98_WISUE/%EC%98%88%EC%81%98%EB%8B%A4/" title="위수_WISUE - 예쁘다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[예쁘다 예쁘다 <br>귓가에 조근 조근 속삭여줘요 <br>따뜻한 손 끝으로 <br>내 머리칼을 매만져 주세요 <br>오랜만에 나란히 <br>함께 앉아있는 다락방 카페 <br>나를 품에 안아주는 <br>그대만 있으면 난 행복한 사람 <br>손을 잡고 따뜻한 그대 주머니에 <br>넣어둔 채로 나란히 걸음 해줘요 <br>내가 들떠 한없이 그대 앞에서 <br>조잘대도 지금처럼 <br>하나하나 눈에 담아줘요 <br>귀여운 눈빛으로 <br>날 바라보며 장난을 치네요 <br>조금씩 그대는 <br>따뜻한 햇볕처럼 밝아지네요 <br>멀리서 날 바라보며 <br>따뜻한 미소로 반겨주는 <br>나를 품에 안아주는 <br>그대만 있으면 난 행복한 사람 <br>손을 잡고 따뜻한 그대 주머니에 <br>넣어둔 채로 나란히 걸음 해줘요 <br>내가 들떠 한없이 그대 앞에서 <br>조잘대도 지금처럼 <br>하나하나 눈에 담아줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="위수 (WISUE)" label="위수 (WISUE)"/><category term="예쁘다" label="예쁘다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/에스피나/My_All/</id><title>에스피나 - My All - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%90%EC%8A%A4%ED%94%BC%EB%82%98/My_All/" title="에스피나 - My All - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그댈 처음 만나 <br>너무 따스했던 시간 <br>가슴이 떨리고 <br>눈앞에 아른거려서 <br>지금 이 순간에도 <br>함께할 순 없나요 <br>그대 손을 잡고 <br>함께 쓰고 싶은 얘기 <br>그대는 나만의 사랑 <br>사랑을 알려준 사람 <br>사랑이 뭔지 몰라서 서툴러서 <br>나의 맘 다 알지 못해도 <br>그대는 나만의 사랑 <br>내 맘을 채운 한 사람 <br>난 그대 하나면 돼요 그대예요 <br>내 맘 가득히 <br>마치 무언가에 <br>이끌리듯 그댈 만나 <br>나의 세상 속을 <br>그대로 가득 채웠지 <br>그대가 이 순간을 <br>늘 잊지 말아 주길 <br>시간이 지나도 <br>함께 하고 싶은 사랑 <br>그대는 나만의 사랑 <br>사랑을 알려준 사람 <br>사랑이 뭔지 몰라서 서툴러서 <br>나의 맘 다 알지 못해도 <br>그대는 나만의 사랑 <br>내 맘을 채운 한 사람 <br>난 그대 하나면 돼요 그대예요 <br>내 맘 가득한 단 한사람 <br>너뿐이라는 한마디 <br>내 옆에만 있어주길 <br>내 마지막 사랑이길 함께 하길 <br>지금처럼만 <br>나만의 사랑 <br>나만의 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="에스피나" label="에스피나"/><category term="My All" label="My All"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Holy_Water/</id><title>VANT - Holy Water - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Holy_Water/" title="VANT - Holy Water - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Holy water, holy water <br>Sink to the bottom and out live your daughter <br><br>Holy water, holy water <br>Sink to the bottom and out live your daughter <br><br>Why'd she go, why'd she go <br>I know she says, I know she says, she's trying to get clean??Why'd she go, why'd she go <br>I know she says, I know she says, she's trying to get clean <br><br>After all, after all <br>It wasn't much better when you broke the fall <br>After all, after all <br>It wasn't much better when you broke the fall <br><br>Why'd you go, why'd you go <br>I know he says, I know he says, he's trying to get through <br>Why'd you go, why'd you go <br><br>I know he says, I know he says, he's trying to get through <br>I know he says, I know he says, he's trying to get through <br>I know he says, I know he says, he's trying to get through]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Holy Water" label="Holy Water"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/All_Our_Babies/</id><title>VANT - All Our Babies - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/All_Our_Babies/" title="VANT - All Our Babies - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So what do we do <br>It just seems so likely <br>That we'll always be cruel <br>And our past incites me <br>We're forever in lieu <br>Yeah this shit got heavy <br>Yeah it's true, it's true, it's true <br><br>That all our babies are dying <br>While we're fighting for more <br>Yeah all our babies are crying <br>Keep on smiling off shore <br><br>So what can I say <br>I'll be mocked for speaking <br>Out loud, unashamed <br>And I can't help thinking <br>That I'm not like you <br>Like a boat left sinking <br>In the blue, the blue, the blue <br><br>Cos all our babies are dying <br>While we're fighting for more <br>Yeah all our babies are crying <br>Keep on smiling off shore <br>And all our sermons are cold <br>Cos this gulf has taken it's toll <br><br>So what do we do <br>It just seems unlikely <br>That we'll ever be cool <br>And our past incites me <br><br>Cos all our babies are dying <br>While we're fighting for more <br>Yeah all our babies are crying <br>Keep on smiling off shore <br><br>Yeah all our babies are dying <br>While we're fighting for more <br>Yeah all our babies are crying <br>Keep on smiling off shore <br>Off shore]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="All Our Babies" label="All Our Babies"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Bribe_Me_To_My_Grave/</id><title>VANT - Bribe Me To My Grave - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Bribe_Me_To_My_Grave/" title="VANT - Bribe Me To My Grave - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I will not abide to your system <br>I will not fit in to your vision <br><br>I don't want your money <br>I don't want your money <br><br>I will put a spanner in the works <br>I will hit you where it really hurts <br><br>I don't want your money <br>I don't want your money <br><br>Bribe me to my grave]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Bribe Me To My Grave" label="Bribe Me To My Grave"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Birth_Certificate/</id><title>VANT - Birth Certificate - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Birth_Certificate/" title="VANT - Birth Certificate - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Our legislation is so black and white <br>Immigration laws can't change over night <br>Reminds me that you have to go home <br>Oh my God, you have to go home <br><br>It only takes a second <br>Burn your birth certificate oh <br>If the world's our home <br>Then why's she got to got to go home <br><br>Patriotism is a fucking lie <br>I'll be branded British 'til the day i die <br>I got this label through invasion <br>So maybe one day soon we'll be Korean <br>Cha cha cha <br><br>Oh my God, you have to go home <br>Oh my God, you have to go home <br><br>It only takes a second <br>Burn your birth certificate, oh <br>If the world's our home <br>Then why's she got to, got to go home <br><br>You know we have these borders <br>Built by ancient kings <br>But the names they chose <br>Don't mean a fucking thing to me <br>I'm just as English as i am Chinese <br>I'm Iraqi, Pakistani, Cuban, Japanese <br><br>Oh my God, you have to go home <br>The place you're told you have to call home <br><br>It only takes a second <br>Burn your birth certificate, oh <br>If the world's our home <br>Then why's she got to, got to go home <br><br>Our illegitimate, conniving, fickle Governments will control <br>Who we love and how long <br>We belong in each others arms <br>Who we love and how long <br>We belong in each others arms <br>Who we love and how long <br>We belong in each others arms]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Birth Certificate" label="Birth Certificate"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Mess_Around/</id><title>VANT - Mess Around - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Mess_Around/" title="VANT - Mess Around - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My best friend is a dirty dog <br>He's a smoker, joker, brother, lover, gift from God <br>He's a crazy mother fucker but he's my best friend <br>And we'll waste our time until the very end <br><br>Til the end <br>Til the end <br>Til the end <br>Til the end <br><br>All our time's spent messing around <br>All our time's spent messing around <br>All our time's spent messing around <br>Yeah dumb blood won't bring us down <br>Mess around <br>Mess around <br><br>Our stories keep talking, they're a tour de force <br>The tracks been beaten but we're still on course <br>A ch ch ch change my mind every week or two <br>I la la la love you brother this one's all for you <br><br>All for you <br>All for you <br>All for you <br><br>All our time's spent messing around <br>All our time's spent messing around <br>All our time's spent messing around <br>Yeah dumb blood won't bring us down <br><br>All our time's spent messing around <br>All our time's spent messing around <br>All our time's spent messing around <br>Yeah dumb blood won't bring us down <br><br>Mess around <br>Mess around <br>Mess around <br>Mess around]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Mess Around" label="Mess Around"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Welcome_To_The_Wonderful_World_Of_Berners_Lee/</id><title>VANT - Welcome To The Wonderful World Of Berners Lee - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Welcome_To_The_Wonderful_World_Of_Berners_Lee/" title="VANT - Welcome To The Wonderful World Of Berners Lee - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe she's a lizard <br>Maybe she's a lizard <br>Maybe she's a lizard who knows <br><br>Pink links to the Wizard <br>Pink links to the Wizard <br>Pink links to the Wizard of Oz <br><br>My futile human mind has just been blown <br><br>La la la la la la la la la la <br>Vortex with no core <br>La la la la la la la la la la <br>Window to my soul <br><br>Help me Berners Lee I'm bored <br>Conspiracy I am yours <br><br>The man on the moon shot JFK <br>The man on the moon shot JFK <br>The man on the moon shot JFK <br>While 51 Bermuda kids say hey hey hey hey hey <br><br>My futile human mind has just been blown <br><br>La la la la la la la la la la <br>Vortex with no core <br>La la la la la la la la la la <br>Window to my soul <br><br>Help me Berners Lee I'm bored <br>Conspiracy I am yours <br>It's the legitimacy that I just ignore <br><br>La la la la la la la la la la <br>Vortex with no core <br>La la la la la la la la la la <br>Window to my soul]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Welcome To The Wonderful World Of Berners Lee" label="Welcome To The Wonderful World Of Berners Lee"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Peace__Love_Reprise/</id><title>VANT - Peace &amp; Love (Reprise) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Peace__Love_Reprise/" title="VANT - Peace &amp; Love (Reprise) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We need peace and love all you mother fuckers <br>We need peace and love all you mother fuckers <br><br>Hope how'd you stand so tall <br>You know our love is all <br>Hope how'd you stand so tall <br>You know our love is all <br>You know our love is all <br>You know our love is all <br>You know our love is all <br><br>You're in life for the wrong reasons <br>You're in life for the seasons <br><br>But the seasons will change, nothing remains <br>Now that peace and love have no meaning]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Peace &amp; Love (Reprise)" label="Peace &amp; Love (Reprise)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Time__Money/</id><title>VANT - Time &amp; Money - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Time__Money/" title="VANT - Time &amp; Money - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby blows bubbles of cuss and waves his father's flag on <br>Top of a fire, that fear of God is coming <br>Half of everything we ever loved has gone <br>Equality is free, you see, that's why there is none <br><br>Oil spill, cheap thrill, land fill, blood for honey <br>Trapped on an earth fuelled by time and money, money <br>Tick, tock, time bomb, hope's gone <br>All we've got is time <br><br>Continental drift is breaking every bone and <br>That glimmer we had is now a star exploding <br>Listen please, I didn't mean to burst your bubble <br>It's easy for me, for 1 in 3's no trouble <br><br>New breed, species, old greed I feel funny <br>Trapped on an earth fuelled by time and money, money <br>Tick, tock, time bomb, hope's gone <br>All we've got is time <br><br>There's a hole in my o zone dear Liza, dear Liza <br>There's a hole in my o zone dear Liza, a hole <br>Then nuke it dear Henry, dear Henry, dear Henry <br>Then nuke it dear Henry, dear Henry nuke it <br><br>Oil spill, cheap thrill, land fill, blood for honey <br>Trapped on an earth fuelled by time and money, money <br>Tick, tock, time bomb, hope's gone <br>All we've got is time <br>All we've got is time <br>Time <br>Time]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Time &amp; Money" label="Time &amp; Money"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Karma_Seeker/</id><title>VANT - Karma Seeker - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Karma_Seeker/" title="VANT - Karma Seeker - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Your twisted heartache surrounds me <br>I don't know how you're still standing <br>Down, I convinced you to stay <br>Down, do you need to be free <br><br>Karma seeker don't sway <br>Karma seeker don't sway <br>Karma seeker pure bliss <br>If you search you'll destroy what you miss <br><br>I've never felt so consumed <br>Your pheromones leave me bruised <br>Love, I'm a slave to your game <br>Love, will convince you to stay <br><br>Harrowed, how could he let you go <br>Don't let him swallow, pride that he used to show <br><br>Karma seeker don't sway <br>Karma seeker don't sway <br>Karma seeker pure bliss <br>If you search you'll destroy what you miss <br><br>I used to fear the one you loved <br>I used to see him up above <br>But now he's gone <br>I used to fear the one you loved <br>I used to see him up above <br>But now he's gone <br>But now he's gone <br>I used to fear the one you loved <br>I used to see him up above <br>But now he's gone <br><br>Harrowed, how could he let you go <br>Don't let him swallow, pride that he used to show <br><br>Karma seeker don't sway <br>Karma seeker don't sway <br>Karma seeker pure bliss <br>If you search you'll destroy what you miss <br><br>Down, I convinced you to stay <br>Down, do you need to be free <br>Love, I'm a slave to your game <br>Love, will convince you to stay]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Karma Seeker" label="Karma Seeker"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Are_We_Free_/</id><title>VANT - Are We Free? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Are_We_Free_/" title="VANT - Are We Free? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey baby start a wildfire <br>In the crossfire <br>Don't go home <br><br>Question other earthlings <br>Fellow humans <br>Where's your soul <br><br>I don't wanna give in <br>I don't wanna get out <br>But this air that we breath <br>Has filled me with doubt <br><br>My mama's got an earthquake, got a typhoon, volcano <br>My sister's got a black eye, she got raped by, your first son <br><br>I don't wanna give in <br>I don't wanna get out <br>But this air that we breath <br>Has filled me with <br><br>Why did you decide not to fly anymore <br>Why don't you get high when you dance anymore <br>Where's that flame that ignites your soul anymore <br>Is this all, is this it, when we're gone, are we free <br><br>Don't wanna give in <br>I don't wanna get out <br>But this air that we breath <br>Has filled me with <br><br>Why did you decide not to fly anymore <br>Why don't you get high when you dance anymore <br>Where's that flame that ignites your soul anymore <br>Is this all, is this it, when we're gone, are we free <br><br>I don't wanna give in <br>I don't wanna get out]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Are We Free?" label="Are We Free?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Parasite/</id><title>VANT - Parasite - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Parasite/" title="VANT - Parasite - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby I'm more common than you'll ever believe <br>From Texas, Mississippi to the Evergreens <br>I've been to Asia via Russia, sailed the seven seas <br>I'm a pauper, high roller, earthquake, summer breeze <br><br>I'm a parasite, I'll keep you up at night <br>I'll haunt your dreams <br>I'm a nematode, I can kill you <br>I can set you free <br><br>I'm a present Armageddon on the Fourth of July <br>I'm cold and creamy, toasty, I get down, I get high <br>I'm in every breath you take, every truth, every lie <br>Underground, upside down, in the clouds, in the sky <br><br>I'm a parasite, I'll keep you up at night <br>I'll haunt your dreams <br>I'm a nematode, I can kill you <br>I can set you free <br><br>When everybody's gone baby, I'll still be here <br>You can map the constellations with my own atmosphere <br>I'm ninety of a hundred, I am love, I am fear <br>I'm a prophet, I'm a sailor, I'm a judge, I'm a queer <br><br>I'm a parasite, I'll keep you up at night <br>I'll haunt your dreams <br>I'm a nematode, I can kill you <br>I can set you free <br><br>I'll set you free, free, free, free]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Parasite" label="Parasite"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Headed_For_The_Sun/</id><title>VANT - Headed For The Sun - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Headed_For_The_Sun/" title="VANT - Headed For The Sun - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Deaf, day dreamer open up your pretty eyes <br>We don't approve of your kind around here <br>Your lazy acquisitions lacked ambition and decisions <br>And resulted in this constant state of fear <br><br>I miss the way we used to breathe <br>Remember when we used to hang from all those sycamore trees <br>Why did we all give up <br>It's like we all don't give a fuck <br><br>We're headed straight for the sun <br>It may be where we belong <br>You'll all be gone, when you're gone <br>We're headed straight for the sun <br><br>If you waste all your breath on your predecessors wake <br>You'll soon be gone and we won't even know your name anymore <br>Yellow, red, blue <br>Coward, dead, fool <br><br>We're headed straight for the sun <br>It may be where we belong <br>You'll all be gone, when you're gone <br>We're headed straight for the sun <br><br>We're headed straight for the sun <br>It may be where we belong <br>You'll all be gone, when you're gone <br>We're headed straight for the sun]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Headed For The Sun" label="Headed For The Sun"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Fly-By_Alien/</id><title>VANT - Fly-By Alien - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Fly-By_Alien/" title="VANT - Fly-By Alien - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[That boy's got his sneakers on <br>Got a new guitar <br>Start a cool, cool punk band <br><br>That girl's got a rolling drum <br>Got a snappy tongue <br>Got a cold, cold right hand <br><br>That world's got a few problems <br>Got a dying sun <br>It's a tick tock time bomb <br><br>That race is gonna kill itself <br>There'll be nothing left <br>We can take, take the shell <br><br>I'm just passing by section 85 <br>My observation, let's just take their sun <br><br>That moon is an ugly blister <br>That gravitates around it's obese sister <br><br>That species is a waste of space <br>I hate this place <br>Can I zap my laser <br><br>I'm just passing by section 85 <br>My observation, let's just take their sun <br><br>Tick tock tick tock tick tock tick tock <br>Sun <br><br>You are asleep but won't dream <br>You are a cog in a machine <br>You are a fire with no spark <br>You are the light in the dark <br>You are an animal, follow your instinct <br>You are important, you are extinct <br>You have a meaning, you have a purpose <br>This life is short, make sure it's worth it <br><br>My observation, let's just take their sun]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Fly-By Alien" label="Fly-By Alien"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/I_Dont_Believe_In_God/</id><title>VANT - I Don`t Believe In God - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/I_Dont_Believe_In_God/" title="VANT - I Don`t Believe In God - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Some people dance, some people have fun <br>Some people fuck, some people shoot guns <br>People shoot up just to feel something <br>Some people die, end with up with nothing <br>Some take cocaine to provoke a feeling <br>Out of control, their blood's on the ceiling <br>I put it out of mind <br>Cos I don't trust mankind <br><br>I look to the stars <br>Cos I don't believe in God <br><br>Everybody's praying that there'll be something else <br>But babe I can tell, we just won't be ourselves <br>I see it as beauty that we rot in the ground <br>Our molecules mate and create a new sound <br>We make escapes to deal with our feelings <br>Our ash will burn and turn with the seasons <br>I think I'm in love <br>With the world and what it was <br><br>I look to the stars <br>Cos I don't believe in God, yeah <br><br>I look to the stars <br>Cos I don't believe in God <br><br>I don't believe in God <br>I don't believe in God <br>I look to the stars <br>Cos I don't believe in God, no]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="I Don`t Believe In God" label="I Don`t Believe In God"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Do_You_Know_Me_/</id><title>VANT - Do You Know Me? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Do_You_Know_Me_/" title="VANT - Do You Know Me? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I get this feeling that I'm all alone <br>A suit, a headset and a telephone <br>Pick up, put down, dial tone <br>I'm good for nothing <br><br>If someone picks up then I'm still alone <br>Just another voice on a telephone <br>I'm down, I'm broke, I'm tired <br>I want something more <br><br>So let me hear you say <br><br>You should know me <br>You should know me <br>By now <br>Do you know me <br>Do you know me <br>Do you know me <br><br>Just another waiter in a dead end bar <br>But waiting on nothing don't get you far <br>I pull, I pour, I guess It's good for something <br><br>I'm alcoholic cos' it numbs the pain <br>Everyone I know tends to feel the same <br>They smoke, they drink, they take <br>They want nothing more <br><br>So let me hear you say <br><br>You should know me <br>You should know me <br>You should know <br>By now <br>Do you know me <br>Do you know me <br>Do you know me <br>At all <br><br>So let me hear you say <br><br>You should know me <br>You should know me <br>You should know <br>By now <br>Do you know me <br>Do you know me <br>Do you know me <br>At all <br><br>You should know me <br>Know me, know me <br>Know me, know me <br>Know me by now <br>Do you know me <br>Do you know me <br>At all]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Do You Know Me?" label="Do You Know Me?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Parking_Lot/</id><title>VANT - Parking Lot - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Parking_Lot/" title="VANT - Parking Lot - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a vampire <br>How'd you find her <br><br>Like a gunshot in a parking lot <br>No one heard, no one saw <br>I did nothing wrong, nothing wrong <br>I really wish I did something <br><br>Wait a minute, wait a minute <br>Wait a minute cause your heart's not in it <br>Wait a minute, wait a minute <br>Wait a minute cause your heart's not in it <br><br>When you find her <br>She'll look so pretty, like a kick in the teeth, oh darling <br>Just admire her <br><br>Like a gunshot in a parking lot <br>No one heard, no one saw <br>I did nothing wrong, nothing wrong <br>I really wish I did something <br><br>Wait a minute, wait a minute <br>Wait a minute cause your heart's not in it <br>Wait a minute, wait a minute <br>Wait a minute cause your heart's not in it <br>2x <br><br>If you're not ready then I'm not ready <br>Just keep things steady <br>Just keep things cool <br>If you're not ready then I'm not ready <br>Just keep things steady <br>Just keep things cool <br>If you're not ready then I'm not ready <br>Just keep things steady <br>Just keep things cool]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Parking Lot" label="Parking Lot"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Lampoon/</id><title>VANT - Lampoon - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Lampoon/" title="VANT - Lampoon - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Which gland are you <br>Which will you choose <br>Suzanne, Moll, Oesophageal <br>Tell me which gland are you <br><br>Everything is fun with this generation <br>Everything is dumb with this generation <br>Everything is fun with this generation <br>Everything is dumb with this generation <br><br>Lampoon <br>Which will you choose <br><br>What band are you <br>What do you do <br>Gastric, rubber, thin or thick <br>Tell me what band are you <br><br>Everything is fun with this generation <br>Everything is dumb with this generation <br>Everything is fun with this generation <br>Everything is dumb with this generation <br><br>Lampoon <br>Which will you choose <br><br>Lampoon <br>Everything is fun, yeah it's fun yeah, funny <br>Everything is dumb, yeah it's dumb yeah, dummy <br>Lampoon <br>Everything is fun, yeah it's fun yeah, funny <br>Everything is dumb, yeah it's dumb yeah, dummy <br><br>Everything is fun with this generation <br>Which will you choose <br>Everything is dumb with this generation <br>Which will you choose <br>Everything is fun with this generation <br>Which will you choose <br>Everything is dumb with this generation <br><br>Lampoon <br>Everything is dumb with this generation <br>Lampoon <br>Everything is dumb with this generation <br>Lampoon <br>Everything is dumb with this generation <br>Lampoon <br>Everything is dumb with this generation <br><br>Lampoon <br>Lampoon]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Lampoon" label="Lampoon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Peace__Love/</id><title>VANT - Peace &amp; Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Peace__Love/" title="VANT - Peace &amp; Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Get busy there's a timeline <br>You're not the only one <br>I'll wait for you at the back of the queue <br>I know it's not your fault <br><br>We need peace and love <br>We need mother nature <br>For the same reason <br><br>We want peace and love <br>We want mother nature <br>When they're in season <br><br>Hope, how'd you stand so tall <br>You know our love is all <br><br>Hope, how'd you stand so tall <br>You know our love is all <br><br>Say something that can move me <br>Just say something at all <br>It's so easy to be muted <br>But you chose to stand so tall <br>Baby I'm in awe <br>Everything's so small <br><br>We need peace and love <br>We need mother nature <br>For the same reason <br><br>We want peace and love <br>We want mother nature <br>When they're in season <br><br>Hope, how'd you stand so tall <br>You know our love is all <br><br>Hope, how'd you stand so tall <br>You know our love is all <br><br>You know our love is all <br>You know our love is all <br><br>We need peace and love <br>All you mother fuckers <br>For the same reason <br><br>We want peace and love <br>All you mother fuckers <br>When they're in season <br><br>But the season's will change <br>Nothing remains <br>Now that peace and love have no meaning]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Peace &amp; Love" label="Peace &amp; Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Put_Down_Your_Gun/</id><title>VANT - Put Down Your Gun - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/Put_Down_Your_Gun/" title="VANT - Put Down Your Gun - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Censor me, this is present day <br>We're still shot for being black or gay <br>You know it's law that let's them pull the trigger <br>But seem confused by another dead <br><br>Fear fear fear fear <br>Guns guns guns guns <br><br>Stop living in fear <br>Put down your gun <br>Stop living in fear <br>Put down your gun <br><br>Middle class fools, self centred rich <br>Brainwashed villains that poison the sick <br>We need education, oh we need it bad <br>If we live in a world where God hates <br><br>Fear fear fear fear <br>Guns guns guns guns <br><br>Stop living in fear <br>Put down your gun <br>Stop living in fear <br>Put down your gun <br><br>Let's get married, things can really change <br>I love you all, so wild, so free, so strange <br>There is a future, but it's still unknown <br>So show you care and scream it from your lungs <br><br>Love love love love <br>All all all all <br><br>We're all the same <br>Put down your gun <br>We're all the same <br>Put down your gun <br>Stop living in fear <br>Put down your gun <br>Stop living in fear <br>Put down your gun]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="Put Down Your Gun" label="Put Down Your Gun"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/The_Answer/</id><title>VANT - The Answer - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VANT/The_Answer/" title="VANT - The Answer - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[C C C C C C C C C C C C C C Call me <br>Won't you call me <br>C C C C C C C C C C C Can you inform me <br>What's the story <br>What's the answer <br><br>Won't you give me the answer <br>The answer <br>The answer <br><br>Chemical conflict 1429 die, die <br>400 children just let them lie, lie, lie <br>We can't interfere in case of criticism <br>We need another term, not another Afghanistan <br><br>Won't you give me the answer <br>The answer <br>The answer <br><br>100K is A OK, it'll all blow over, what the hell can I say <br>1000K well Iraq was Iraq, you know the USA will take and never give back <br>You're from England well Hello there my brother <br>Keep sucking my dick, while my friend fucks your mother <br><br>Does that give you the answer <br>The answer <br>The answer <br>The answer]]></content><category term="VANT" label="VANT"/><category term="The Answer" label="The Answer"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엠제로/진심을_노래해_KEEP_ON_MY_WAY/</id><title>엠제로 - 진심을 노래해 (KEEP ON MY WAY) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%A0%EC%A0%9C%EB%A1%9C/%EC%A7%84%EC%8B%AC%EC%9D%84_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98%ED%95%B4_KEEP_ON_MY_WAY/" title="엠제로 - 진심을 노래해 (KEEP ON MY WAY) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[진짜를 논하면서 <br>치마는 짧게 <br>음악 대신 싸구려 <br>웃음을 팔래 <br>기생들이 판을 치는 <br>랩사당패 <br>난 미꾸라지처럼 틀을 <br>깨버리는 왈패 <br>뱀 같은 이들의 <br>기름진 배때기는 <br>순진하고 굶주린 아기 <br>새들의 무덤 <br>간절함이 깃든 <br>처절한 지저귐은 <br>껌보다도 쉽게 뜯어 <br>먹혀지곤 해 <br>울기 바쁘던 어린 <br>시절을 달랜 <br>무채색의 드럼 <br>까만 노래들과 랩 <br>yea yea my friend <br>so I'm still on this track <br>열정을 사고 파는 <br>더러운 세태 속 <br>새빨간 세 치 혀는 <br>레드카펫을 둔갑 <br>꿈들을 잡아먹는 <br>꾼들의 수작 <br>몇이나 될까 <br>희망고문을 팔고 사는 <br>그들 중에 진짜라고 <br>불리우는 수가 <br>추억이 담긴 모든 거리와 <br>사람은 쉽게 변하지만 <br>yeah I keep on my way <br>I keep on my way <br>내 두 발이 담긴 거리가 <br>굽어지고 매끄럽지 않아도 <br>내 발자국이 <br>내 걸음이 <br>똑바르게 길 위에 <br>찍히면 돼 <br>코르셋처럼 꽉막힌 <br>오만과 편견들은 <br>시대가 바꼈어도 <br>여전히 틀에 박힌 <br>시선들로 여자들의 <br>숨통을 조이기 바빠서 <br>고작 삼 분 남짓한 <br>이 노래 한 곡에도 <br>내 입을 막으려 해 <br>뭐 수많은 혜택의 <br>기회비용이라기엔 <br>난 너무 빈손인데 <br>뭐가 타협이고 <br>살아가는 법이야 <br>나도 똑같이 <br>입에 풀칠 좀 하잔 건데 <br>죄다 하나같이 껄끄러운 <br>조밥 취급 <br>열폭과 시기로 빚어내는 <br>헛된 자존심들은 <br>마치 지 밥그릇이라도 <br>뺏긴 개 마냥 <br>거품까지 물고 뭐 같이 <br>짖어대네 <br>그래서 이젠 의미 없는 <br>뒷풀이도 안 가 <br>똑같은 놈들끼리 안주하는 <br>만취 랩 <br>요란히 부딪히는 술잔과 <br>혓바닥 봐 <br>빈수레가 굴러갈 때 <br>이런 소리가 날까 <br>추억이 담긴 모든 거리와 <br>사람은 쉽게 변하지만 <br>yeah I keep on my way <br>I keep on my way <br>내 두 발이 담긴 거리가 <br>굽어지고 매끄럽지 않아도 <br>내 발자국이 <br>내 걸음이 <br>똑바르게 길 위에 <br>찍히면 돼 <br>명예나 돈따위가 <br>전부가 아냐 <br>나를 쥐똥만큼도 모르면서 <br>무슨 투자를 해 <br>그게 의미가 있을 것 같냐 <br>니들이 말하는 <br>진짜라는 게 그런 거냐 <br>병든 개처럼 비틀거리고 <br>빛보단 그늘 밑에서 <br>삶의 반을 지새고 <br>말보다 빠른 눈들이 <br>왜곡한 진실에도 <br>우린 그 누구도 절대 <br>탓하지 않고 <br>버티게 했던 게 rap music <br>you cannot even imagine <br>누구도 미워하지 않고 <br>살아가는 법 <br>사랑하는 법 <br>또 한 번 살아가는 것 <br>아무리 배고파도 스스로는 <br>팔지 않는 것 <br>헐벗지 않고 떳떳히 뱉는 랩 <br>엄마 좀만 버텨 줘 내가 미안해 <br>돌아가는 길엔 두 손이 무겁게 <br>그 속에 바친 세월이 <br>절대 안 무색하게 <br>추억이 담긴 모든 거리와 <br>사람은 쉽게 변하지만 <br>yeah I keep on my way <br>I keep on my way <br>내 두 발이 담긴 거리가 <br>굽어지고 매끄럽지 않아도 <br>내 발자국이 <br>내 걸음이 <br>똑바르게 길 위에 <br>찍히면 돼 <br>]]></content><category term="엠제로" label="엠제로"/><category term="진심을 노래해 (KEEP ON MY WAY)" label="진심을 노래해 (KEEP ON MY WAY)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엠제로/HOW_U_DOIN/</id><title>엠제로 - HOW U DOIN - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:22:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:22:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%A0%EC%A0%9C%EB%A1%9C/HOW_U_DOIN/" title="엠제로 - HOW U DOIN - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How you doin my friends <br>여기는 새벽 세 시 반 <br>지구 반대편에서 <br>안부를 보내 <br>부디 잘 지냈길 바래 <br>재밌는 소식 하나 알려줄게 <br>나는 여전히 가사를 써 <br>아무래도 내 인생 <br>얼마 살아보지는 않았지만 <br>꽤 재밌는 듯 해 <br>Do you remember <br>우리 어렸을 적 <br>매일 같이 올라가던 <br>지붕 위에 안식처 <br>We call it heaven <br>CD가 늘어지도록 <br>듣던 랩들 <br>야 여전히 너는 <br>내가 봤던 애들 중 <br>가장 멋진 댄서 <br>어떻게 추는 거랬지 <br>치킨 파이를 먹고 <br>표현하는 기쁨은 <br>혹시 그것도 기억 나니 <br>날씨가 종종 흐릴 땐 <br>책가방을 내던지고 <br>뛰어갔던 <br>Takapuna beach <br>스파게티보다도 <br>많이 맛봤던 바다의 짠물 <br>누가 걸어 놨는 지도 모를 <br>밧줄을 타고 다이빙 다이빙 <br>그 때가 바로 내 인생 <br>최고의 순간 timing yeah yeah <br>인생은 작은 timing yeah yeah <br>행복은 순간 timing yeah yeah <br>놓치지 말아요 <br>this timing yeah yeah <br>How you doin <br>How you doin <br>먹고 살기 바빠 <br>놓치고 있던 나의 <br>소중함들을 찾아 <br>How you doin <br>How you doin <br>더 멀리 내다 봐 <br>지금 내 손에 내 삶에 <br>내 의미를 찾아 <br>Yall the invader <br>called saviour <br>and I was like a Satan <br>with paranoid <br>끝만 바라보던 나에게 넌 <br>갑자기 나타나 <br>삶의 계기를 줘 <br>넌 말했지 <br>살아가는 법 <br>그건 대체 누가 정해줘 <br>모든 것들은 up to me <br>대신 살아 줄 사람 없으니 <br>행복한 것만 쫓자 <br>초콜렛과 소다 <br>희망을 노래하며 <br>더 넓은 바다로 가자 <br>맨발로 풀과 땅을 밟으며 <br>온기와 용기로 <br>살아가는 거야 <br>사람과 사랑이 사는 거야 <br>그걸 풀어내는 게 <br>우리의 삶인 거야 <br>사람도 돈도 <br>그리고 욕심도 <br>가진만큼 외로워 <br>날 가장 힘들게 만드는 건 <br>다름 아닌 내 자신인 걸 <br>겪어보지 못한 것들에 <br>대한 환상은 <br>겪어보면 같은 일상 <br>아빠의 솜사탕보다도 <br>빠르게 사라지는 게 <br>달콤한 망상 <br>so 내 행복은 단순해 <br>물론 열두 살의 <br>무지함에서 비롯된 <br>순수함은 그립지만 <br>가끔 <br>술 한 잔에 위로받는 <br>기분도 필요해 <br>내겐 그런 사소함 <br>쉽게 놓쳤던 나의 사소한 <br>행복들이 그리워 <br>네게 편지를 써 <br>혹시 너도 그래 <br>오늘 같은 새벽엔 더 <br>How you doin <br>How you doin <br>먹고 살기 바빠 <br>놓치고 있던 나의 <br>소중함들을 찾아 <br>How you doin <br>How you doin <br>더 멀리 내다 봐 <br>지금 내 손에 내 삶에 <br>내 의미를 찾아 <br>How you doin <br>How you doin <br>먹고 살기 바빠 <br>놓치고 있던 나의 <br>소중함들을 찾아 <br>How you doin <br>How you doin <br>더 멀리 내다 봐 <br>지금 내 손에 내 삶에 <br>내 의미를 찾아 <br>]]></content><category term="엠제로" label="엠제로"/><category term="HOW U DOIN" label="HOW U DOIN"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엠제로/101_ONE_NO_ONE/</id><title>엠제로 - 101 (ONE, NO ONE) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:23:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:23:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%A0%EC%A0%9C%EB%A1%9C/101_ONE_NO_ONE/" title="엠제로 - 101 (ONE, NO ONE) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 장담해 내가 답이라고 <br>내가 잘하냐고 그걸 말이라고 <br>나는 갈릴레오 <br>혹은 나폴레옹처럼 <br>이름만으로도 가치를 증명하고 <br>내가 머리채를 <br>안 잡아도 고갤 젖혀 <br>모두 나를 쳐다보며 입을 벌려 <br>나는 다리 대신에 일을 벌려도 <br>남녀노소 불문 아래 위를 적셔 <br>Who da bitches <br>wanna compete with me <br>빛을 쫓는 날파리들의 <br>fake or gimmick 다 가지치기 <br>쓸모 없으니까 <br>Let me show you <br>what the queen do <br>급으로 따지자면 플래티넘 <br>금은동 따위론 재미 없어 <br>Dont you know the challenger <br>wan' bang with us <br>건배를 원한다면 수준 높여 <br>Cause I'm the 101 oh oh oh <br>101 oh oh oh <br>Cause I'm the 101 oh oh oh <br>101 <br>Cause I'm the 101 oh oh oh <br>101 oh oh oh <br>Cause I'm the 101 oh oh oh <br>101 <br>Keep that bass run do that that <br>Kick drum and do the right rap <br>Keep that bass run do that that <br>Kick drum and do the right rap <br>Cause i'm the <br>one no one can be won but me <br>no one can be instead of me <br>Cause i'm the <br>one in 1o1 pick me up baby <br>no one can make you hot like me <br>Cause i'm the <br>one no one can be won but me <br>no one can be instead of me <br>Cause i'm the <br>one in 1o1 pick me up baby <br>no one can make you hot like me <br>내가 흔드는 네 마디의 리듬은 <br>니가 밤새 흔든 힙보다 비싸 <br>니가 기를 쓰고 키우는 볼륨은 <br>목소리가 아닌 슴가니까 <br>We can see the gap <br>어쩔 수 없네 <br>I just do ma rap man <br>recognize recognize <br>탁월한 타고남 타고난 리듬감 <br>눈치보지 말고 너는 follow ma <br>twitter <br>Keep that bass run do that that <br>Kick drum and do the right rap <br>Keep that bass run do that that <br>Kick drum and do the right rap <br>Keep that bass run do that that <br>Kick drum and do the right rap <br>Keep that bass run do that that <br>Kick drum and do the right rap <br>한철 제비 같은 <br>새끼들은 잠깐 <br>혹했다 꺼져버릴 <br>성냥 한 개비야 <br>난 한 살 배기보다 <br>잘 뒤집어 뒤집어 <br>이 씬을 다 <br>내가 원하는 거 모든 것을 <br>다 갖다가 준다 해도 <br>혹하지 않아 꼬까신들아 <br>난 Classic Trap <br>and Boombastic <br>아무거나 들이대도 <br>자체 발광 HIPPIE Baby <br>Cause I'm the 101 oh oh oh <br>101 oh oh oh <br>Cause I'm the 101 oh oh oh <br>101 <br>Cause I'm the 101 oh oh oh <br>101 oh oh oh <br>Cause I'm the 101 oh oh oh <br>101 <br>FEEL MEEE <br>FEEL MEEE <br>난 너의 이상이자 <br>표현할 수 없는 질투야 <br>난 너의 모나리자 <br>기묘한 기분일 거야 <br>I CAN FEEL WHAT U THINKING <br>I CAN READ WHAT U THINKING <br>I CAN FEEL WHAT U THINKING <br>I CAN READ WHAT U THINKING <br>Cause i'm the <br>one no one can be won but me <br>no one can be instead of me <br>Cause i'm the <br>one in 1o1 pick me up baby <br>no one can make you hot like me <br>Cause i'm the <br>one no one can be won but me <br>no one can be instead of me <br>Cause i'm the <br>one in 1o1 pick me up baby <br>no one can make you hot like me <br>]]></content><category term="엠제로" label="엠제로"/><category term="101 (ONE, NO ONE)" label="101 (ONE, NO ONE)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엠제로/BROWN/</id><title>엠제로 - BROWN - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:23:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:23:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%A0%EC%A0%9C%EB%A1%9C/BROWN/" title="엠제로 - BROWN - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Brown hair Brown eyes <br>브라운관에 나올 듯한 <br>너는 prince with the crown <br>Who I was drawn <br>babe 니가 내 눈을 <br>똑바로 쳐다 볼 때면 <br>숨 쉬는 방법도 잊고서 <br>feel drowned <br>Brown hair Brown eyes <br>브라운관에 나올 듯한 <br>너는 prince with the crown <br>Who I was drawn <br>babe 니가 내 눈을 <br>똑바로 쳐다 볼 때면 <br>숨 쉬는 방법도 잊고서 <br>feel drowned <br>잘 참았어 <br>보고 싶은 건 당연해 <br>그래도 꺼버린 폰처럼 <br>언젠간 그리움도 방전 돼 <br>내리는 비처럼 <br>날 젖게 만든 너지만 <br>시간 지나면 <br>바닥에 고인 물처럼 <br>피해다녀야 돼 <br>너가 내 전부고 <br>세상이었단 착각도 <br>이젠 색안경을 벗어 <br>깨달아야만 하고 <br>버릇처럼 추억 얘기도 <br>입 밖에 꺼내지 마 <br>마음은 아니라고 해도 <br>머리가 착각하니까 <br>그냥 쉿 쉿 <br>그리고 쉭 <br>지나가기만을 기다려 <br>상황은 여전히 <br>힘들고 괴롭겠지만 <br>예전보단 나을 거야 <br>그래서 우린 헤어졌고 <br>뒤돌아보면 안 돼 <br>자꾸 넌 <br>내 맘 속에서 <br>계속 자라니까 <br>나는 토끼기 바빠 <br>니가 간을 더 볼까 봐 <br>마주쳐도 그냥 <br>빠르게 지나쳐 가 <br>미련에 속지 마 <br>서로 더 망가질 뿐야 <br>I'm not okay <br>I'm not okay <br>변하지 못하는 나도 <br>변할 수 없는 우리도 <br>I'm not okay <br>I'm not okay <br>사실대로 말을 할 수도 <br>그렇다고 아니랄 수도 없기에 <br>난 할 얘기도 많고 <br>해야 할 일도 많아 <br>근데 정신 못 차리고 <br>아직 네 생각뿐야 <br>시간은 흘러가고 <br>내 맘은 더 조급한데 <br>자꾸 브레이크를 걸어 <br>네게 멈추고 싶게 하네 <br>게다가 <br>발맞춰 걸어갈 땐 <br>아스팔트 위에서도 <br>꽃이 피어나는 기분 <br>넌 그 중에서도 <br>가장 빛나는 꽃이라서 <br>난 신경 써야 했어 <br>딴 라이벌들 <br>그 소모적인 감정 때문에 <br>내가 괜히 초라한 <br>기분 마저 들길래 <br>이유 없이 혼자 <br>울기도 하고 <br>투정도 부리고 <br>별짓 다 해 봤어 <br>니가 알 리도 없는데 <br>근데 돌이켜보면 <br>초라했던 내 모습도 <br>충분히 사랑으로 <br>이겨낼 수 있었음에도 <br>나 꾸준히 <br>그대 곁에서 외로웠던 건 <br>우리 두 사람의 온도가 <br>너무 달랐다는 것 <br>I'm not okay <br>I'm not okay <br>변하지 못하는 나도 <br>변할 수 없는 우리도 <br>I'm not okay <br>I'm not okay <br>사실대로 말을 할 수도 <br>그렇다고 아니랄 수도 없기에 <br>Brown hair Brown eyes <br>브라운관에 나올 듯한 <br>너는 prince with the crown <br>Who I was drawn <br>babe 니가 내 눈을 <br>똑바로 쳐다 볼 때면 <br>숨 쉬는 방법도 잊고서 <br>feel drowned <br>Brown hair Brown eyes <br>브라운관에 나올 듯한 <br>너는 prince with the crown <br>Who I was drawn <br>babe 니가 내 눈을 <br>똑바로 쳐다 볼 때면 <br>숨 쉬는 방법도 잊고서 <br>feel drowned <br>I'm not okay <br>I'm not okay <br>변하지 못하는 나도 <br>변할 수 없는 우리도 <br>I'm not okay <br>I'm not okay <br>사실대로 말을 할 수도 <br>그렇다고 아니랄 수도 없기에 <br>]]></content><category term="엠제로" label="엠제로"/><category term="BROWN" label="BROWN"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Incubus/Nimble_Bastard/</id><title>Incubus - Nimble Bastard - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:23:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:23:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Incubus/Nimble_Bastard/" title="Incubus - Nimble Bastard - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Has it come to this <br>We're stuck in the weeds <br>I get it I'm not perfect <br>I was never trying to be <br>But I'm not long for this earth <br>If we really only ever <br>get one chance to burn <br>I gotta trip <br>before I can see the finish <br>How else would I learn <br>I wanna know <br>how is it you do it <br>When you land on your feet <br>You're a nimble bastard <br>And you don't skip a beat <br>Such a nimble bastard <br>Salt of the earth <br>Such a nimble bastard <br>Yeah won't you show lowly us <br>How do you see the stars <br>from that far down <br>I swing and I miss <br>And then come the creeps <br>It makes me want to faint <br>I wanna know <br>how is it you do it <br>How do you spill the paint <br>And then fit it into a frame <br>When you land on your feet <br>You're a nimble bastard <br>And you don't skip a beat <br>Such a nimble bastard <br>Salt of the earth <br>Such a nimble bastard <br>Yeah won't you show lowly us <br>How do you see the stars <br>from that far down <br>Has it come to this <br>Has it come to this <br>When you land on your feet <br>You're a nimble bastard <br>And you don't skip a beat <br>Such a nimble bastard <br>Salt of the earth <br>Look out <br>Won't you show lowly us <br>How do you see the stars <br>from that far down <br>You're a nimble bastard <br>Salt of the earth <br>Such a nimble bastard <br>Salt of the earth <br>You're a nimble bastard <br>Yeah won't you show lowly us <br>How do you see the stars <br>]]></content><category term="Incubus" label="Incubus"/><category term="Nimble Bastard" label="Nimble Bastard"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jax_Jones/You_Dont_Know_Me_Acoustic_Ver_Feat_RAYE/</id><title>Jax_Jones - You Don`t Know Me (Acoustic Ver.) (Feat. RAYE) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:23:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:23:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jax_Jones/You_Dont_Know_Me_Acoustic_Ver_Feat_RAYE/" title="Jax_Jones - You Don`t Know Me (Acoustic Ver.) (Feat. RAYE) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ooh, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>I am not your homie, not your, hoo, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>You don't know me <br>What you what you gonna do <br><br>Oh yeah, time is money so don't fuck with mine <br>See I'm out with my girls, I'ma have a good time <br>Step back with your chit chat, killin' my vibe <br><br>See, I can't get too much of a good thing <br>S'why me a dressed up in the finest things <br>Well, please hold your tongue, oh, don't say a damn thing <br><br>See your iPhone camera flashin' <br>Please step back, it's my style you're crampin' <br>You here for long Oh no, I'm just passin' <br>Do you wanna drink No, thanks for askin' <br><br>Ooh, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>I am not your homie, not your, hoo, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>You don't know me, fuck yeah <br>Ooh, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>I am not your homie, not your, hoo, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>You don't know me, fuck yeah <br><br>I mean, we could throw shapes together <br>But it doesn't mean you're in my circle, yeah <br><br>Cruise through life and I'm feelin' on track <br>If you can't keep up, then you better fall back <br>'Cause money look better when I see it all stacked up <br><br>See, I can't get too much of a good thing <br>S'why me a dressed up in the finest things <br>Well, please hold your tongue, oh, don't say a damn thing <br><br>See your iPhone camera flashin' <br>Please step back, it's my style you're crampin' <br>You here for long Oh no, I'm just passin' <br>Do you wanna drink No, thanks for askin' <br><br>Ooh, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>I am not your homie, not your, hoo, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>You don't know me, fuck yeah <br>Ooh, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>I am not your homie, not your, hoo, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>You don't know me, fuck yeah <br><br>Come round here, just know though <br>Won't get what you want, what you want, what you want, want <br>Tell you what you don't know <br>I get what I want, what I want, what I want, want <br><br>See your iPhone camera flashin' <br>Please step back, it's my style you're crampin' <br>You here for long Oh no, I'm just passin' <br>Do you wanna drink No, thanks for askin' <br><br>Ooh, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>I am not your homie, not your, hoo, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>You don't know me, fuck yeah <br><br>You don't know me, fuck yeah]]></content><category term="Jax Jones" label="Jax Jones"/><category term="You Don`t Know Me (Acoustic Ver.) (Feat. RAYE)" label="You Don`t Know Me (Acoustic Ver.) (Feat. RAYE)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Blunt/Time_Of_Our_Lives/</id><title>James_Blunt - Time Of Our Lives - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:23:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:23:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Blunt/Time_Of_Our_Lives/" title="James_Blunt - Time Of Our Lives - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't close your eyes dear <br>don't you be nervous <br>You put this whole damn <br>place in a spell <br>I see your friends here <br>and some of them jealous <br>'Cause they know this love <br>don't come off the shelf <br>I saw your mother <br>she looked so beautiful <br>Remember when she didn't <br>think I would stay <br>But all of those late-night <br>brokers-held dinners <br>Led us to where we're <br>standing today <br>I'm feeling time moves slow <br>I'm seeing faces glow <br>None of them shine as bright <br>As you tonight <br>I'm hearing voices hush <br>There's no one else but us <br>Darling there's so much love <br>Under these lights <br>If it's okay <br>Let's just have the time <br>Of our lives <br>I saw your father <br>he wouldn't talk to me <br>Till he could tell that <br>I was here to stay <br>But all of those awkward <br>short conversations <br>Led us to where we're <br>standing today <br>I'm feeling time moves slow <br>I'm seeing faces glow <br>None of them shine as bright <br>As you tonight <br>I'm hearing voices hush <br>There's no one else but us <br>Darling there's so much love <br>Under these lights <br>If it's okay <br>Let's just have the time <br>Of our lives <br>Time of our lives <br>Time of our lives <br>Time of our lives <br>I'm feeling time moves slow <br>I'm seeing faces glow <br>None of them shine as bright <br>As you tonight <br>I'm hearing voices hush <br>There's no one else but us <br>Darling there's so much love <br>Under these lights <br>If it's okay <br>Let's just have the time <br>Let's just have the time <br>Of our lives <br>]]></content><category term="James Blunt" label="James Blunt"/><category term="Time Of Our Lives" label="Time Of Our Lives"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jax_Jones/You_Dont_Know_Me_Piano_Ver_Feat_RAYE/</id><title>Jax_Jones - You Don`t Know Me (Piano Ver.) (Feat. RAYE) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:23:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:23:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jax_Jones/You_Dont_Know_Me_Piano_Ver_Feat_RAYE/" title="Jax_Jones - You Don`t Know Me (Piano Ver.) (Feat. RAYE) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ooh, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>I am not your homie, not your, hoo, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>You don't know me <br>What you what you gonna do <br><br>Oh yeah, time is money so don't fuck with mine <br>See I'm out with my girls, I'ma have a good time <br>Step back with your chit chat, killin' my vibe <br><br>See, I can't get too much of a good thing <br>S'why me a dressed up in the finest things <br>Well, please hold your tongue, oh, don't say a damn thing <br><br>See your iPhone camera flashin' <br>Please step back, it's my style you're crampin' <br>You here for long Oh no, I'm just passin' <br>Do you wanna drink No, thanks for askin' <br><br>Ooh, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>I am not your homie, not your, hoo, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>You don't know me, fuck yeah <br>Ooh, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>I am not your homie, not your, hoo, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>You don't know me, fuck yeah <br><br>I mean, we could throw shapes together <br>But it doesn't mean you're in my circle, yeah <br><br>Cruise through life and I'm feelin' on track <br>If you can't keep up, then you better fall back <br>'Cause money look better when I see it all stacked up <br><br>See, I can't get too much of a good thing <br>S'why me a dressed up in the finest things <br>Well, please hold your tongue, oh, don't say a damn thing <br><br>See your iPhone camera flashin' <br>Please step back, it's my style you're crampin' <br>You here for long Oh no, I'm just passin' <br>Do you wanna drink No, thanks for askin' <br><br>Ooh, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>I am not your homie, not your, hoo, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>You don't know me, fuck yeah <br>Ooh, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>I am not your homie, not your, hoo, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>You don't know me, fuck yeah <br><br>Come round here, just know though <br>Won't get what you want, what you want, what you want, want <br>Tell you what you don't know <br>I get what I want, what I want, what I want, want <br><br>See your iPhone camera flashin' <br>Please step back, it's my style you're crampin' <br>You here for long Oh no, I'm just passin' <br>Do you wanna drink No, thanks for askin' <br><br>Ooh, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>I am not your homie, not your, hoo, na na yeah <br>Don't act like you know me, like you know me, na na yeah <br>You don't know me, fuck yeah <br><br>You don't know me, fuck yeah]]></content><category term="Jax Jones" label="Jax Jones"/><category term="You Don`t Know Me (Piano Ver.) (Feat. RAYE)" label="You Don`t Know Me (Piano Ver.) (Feat. RAYE)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유월/겨울의_끝에서/</id><title>유월 - 겨울의 끝에서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:23:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:23:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EC%9B%94/%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8%EC%9D%98_%EB%81%9D%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C/" title="유월 - 겨울의 끝에서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[겨울의 끝에서 <br>널 찾을 수 있을까 <br>겨울의 끝에서 <br>널 잊기로 했었어 <br>짧지 않았던 그때를 이미 <br>추억하고 있는지 <br>궁금해서 또 궁금해서 <br>너의 흔적을 찾아보곤 해 <br>왜 난 꼭 이렇게 <br>아파하고 또 아파해야 <br>이렇게 또 혼자 남게 되는지 <br>왜 난 꼭 이렇게 <br>슬퍼하고 또 슬퍼해야 <br>이렇게 또 봄이 오게 되는지 <br>헤어지자는 그 말 한마디가 <br>어찌나 슬프던지 <br>어찌나 아프던지 <br>내게 남았던 <br>네 그 향기조차 이젠 <br>사라져서 또 사라져서 <br>더는 맡을 수도 없는데 <br>왜 난 꼭 이렇게 <br>아파하고 또 아파해야 <br>이렇게 또 혼자 남게 되는지 <br>왜 난 꼭 이렇게 <br>슬퍼하고 또 슬퍼해야 <br>이렇게 또 봄이 오게 되는지 <br>그랬는지 <br>]]></content><category term="유월" label="유월"/><category term="겨울의 끝에서" label="겨울의 끝에서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/우은미_Woo_Eun_Mi/수많은_약속도_이별앞에서_모두_거짓말/</id><title>우은미_Woo_Eun_Mi - 수많은 약속도 이별앞에서 모두 거짓말 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:24:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:24:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9A%B0%EC%9D%80%EB%AF%B8_Woo_Eun_Mi/%EC%88%98%EB%A7%8E%EC%9D%80_%EC%95%BD%EC%86%8D%EB%8F%84_%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84%EC%95%9E%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C_%EB%AA%A8%EB%91%90_%EA%B1%B0%EC%A7%93%EB%A7%90/" title="우은미_Woo_Eun_Mi - 수많은 약속도 이별앞에서 모두 거짓말 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무런 준비하지 못했는데 <br>이별을 말하니 <br>창문만 바라보는 차가워진 <br>낯설게 변한 너를 바라만 봐 <br>행복 하라는 그 말 <br>난 뭐라 해야 해 <br>아무 말도 하지 못했어 <br>이렇게 쉽게 날 떠날 거라면 <br>왜 널 사랑하게 했니 <br>그냥 스쳐 지나갈 사람이면 <br>시작조차 안 했어 <br>수많은 약속도 이별 앞에서 <br>모두 거짓말 <br>미처 알지 못했어 <br>변해가는 니 맘 <br>눈치 없이 곁에 있었어 <br>이렇게 쉽게 날 떠날 거라면 <br>왜 널 사랑하게 했니 <br>그냥 스쳐 지나갈 사람이면 <br>시작조차 안 했어 <br>수많은 약속도 이별 앞에서 <br>모두 거짓말 <br>어딜 가야 하나요 <br>이제는 갈 곳 몰라서 <br>헤메이잖아 어떡해요 <br>이렇게 쉽게 날 떠날 거라면 <br>왜 널 사랑하게 했니 <br>그냥 스쳐 지나갈 사람이면 <br>시작조차 안 했어 <br>수많은 약속도 이별 앞에서 <br>모두 거짓말 <br>]]></content><category term="우은미 (Woo Eun Mi)" label="우은미 (Woo Eun Mi)"/><category term="수많은 약속도 이별앞에서 모두 거짓말" label="수많은 약속도 이별앞에서 모두 거짓말"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Parquet_Courts/Captive_of_the_Sun/</id><title>Parquet_Courts - Captive of the Sun - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:29:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:29:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Parquet_Courts/Captive_of_the_Sun/" title="Parquet_Courts - Captive of the Sun - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My misophonia brought the faders up <br>Now she's a military grade <br>In Dolby Surround, around 51 <br>Cue the barking from the baritone <br>Conductor in the pit for the car honk duet <br>Half tone harmony from the sewer <br>Rebel youth choir belt phrases even newer <br>Dump truck man drops the beat with trash cans <br>Call 911 We got therapy demands <br>Philharmonic got a first chair car crash <br>Pan the falsetto to smash the glass <br>It's a drive by lullaby that couldn't get worse <br>A melody abandoned in the key of New York <br><br>Where nothing comes after <br>I'm a passtime streamer <br>Hanging from the rafters <br>I don't get out <br>I don't have fun <br>Living like a captive of the sun <br><br>So I gotta put my shades on <br>Riding through the city as I gets my escalade on <br>Flipping down the streets that my reputation was made on <br>King of the city, the mayor finna put a parade on <br>Drop the confetti from off the rooftop <br>While I come down candy and let my roof drop <br>I got a baddie shotgun in a tube top <br>With some daisy dukes on and some tube socks <br>Listening to 2Pac <br>You ain't know I do rock records <br>I do it all <br>I got my hands in some cookie jars <br>You ain't knew at all <br>I took a chance and threw caution up in the wind <br>Cuz I got nothing to lose but got something to win <br>We throw it up against the wall and see if it sticks <br>It's gon' end up being a bomb or being the shit <br>They said the fix was in, guess we'll know when it's done <br>Until then we'll just be captives of the sun <br><br>Sight read the chart <br>Clap the rocks into sand <br>A 12 pass van on a pot hole band stand <br>Got an oil can hangover by default <br>And trucks pave the roads with amphetamine salt <br>Skull shaking cadence of the J train rolls <br>The rhythm of defeat, repeating like a pulse <br>Marching on and static, lyrics shout a retort <br>To the melody abandoned in the key of New York <br><br>Where nothing comes after <br>I'm a passtime streamer <br>Hanging from the rafters <br>I don't get out <br>I don't have fun <br>Living like a captive of the sun]]></content><category term="Parquet Courts" label="Parquet Courts"/><category term="Captive of the Sun" label="Captive of the Sun"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/4ROSE/All_Kill/</id><title>4ROSE - All Kill - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:30:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:30:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/4ROSE/All_Kill/" title="4ROSE - All Kill - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가지 가지 가지 가지한다 <br>이번엔 소냐 ㅠㅠ <br>도대체 잘하는게 뭡니까 <br>Ai때 그렇게 당해놓고도 <br>대처가 왜 이래 <br>소잃고 외양간도 <br>안 고친 거냐 <br>소 돼지 닭 다 죽겄네 <br>빌어먹을 나라 <br>이쯤 되면 일부러 <br>이러나 싶다 진짜 <br>이것도 주작인 듯 <br>좀 있음 메르스도 <br>다시 나오겄네 <br>잘하는 건 잡아때기 모르쇠 <br>진짜 왜이러냐 <br>정신 안 차릴래 <br>교활한 놈이 <br>마음이 콩밭에 <br>가 있으니까 그렇지 <br>이땅의 모든 가축이 <br>전멸하겠네 <br>ㅋㅋㅋ 이거 좀처럼 <br>보기 드믄 <br>병신국가일세 ㅋㅋ <br>점염병이 창궐하고 <br>백성들의 원성이 드높은데 <br>해외순방 패션쇼밖에 <br>모르던 나랏님은 <br>지 잘못을 모르나니 <br>진짜 한국사 반만년 <br>역대급 최악으로 <br>남을듯하다 ㅋㅋ <br>]]></content><category term="4ROSE" label="4ROSE"/><category term="All Kill" label="All Kill"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bebe_Rexha/Bad_Bitch/</id><title>Bebe_Rexha - Bad Bitch - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:30:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:30:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bebe_Rexha/Bad_Bitch/" title="Bebe_Rexha - Bad Bitch - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're sayin' that your tired of all your empty habits <br>You want something that's deeper, 'cause you're over the generics <br>You're fuckin' with them basics when you really want the baddest <br>So c'mon, baby, get it, 'cause to miss it, it would be tragic <br><br>You say you want a bad bitch <br>Baby, now you have it <br>Now you got a bad bitch <br>Show me you can handle this <br>Say you want a bad bitch <br>Baby, now you have it <br>Now you got the baddest <br>Show me you can handle this <br><br>Bad bitch, bad bitch <br>Bad bitch, bad bitch <br>Show me you can handle this <br>Bad bitch, bad bitch <br>Bad bitch, bad bitch <br>Show me you can handle this <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh, yeah, yeah, yeah <br><br>You know I can handle it <br>You know I can handle it <br>When you throw that thing back <br>Get me like collateral <br>You be goin' all night when you on that adderall <br>We be goin' all night when you on that adderall <br>Bad bitch, bad bitch <br>You ain't never average <br>Kissin' double C's on your back with the basic <br>Bad bitch, bad bitch <br>You ain't never average <br>Center on the jeans with the center on back too <br><br>You say you want a bad bitch <br>Baby, now you have it <br>Now you got a bad bitch <br>Show me you can handle this <br>Say you want a bad bitch <br>Baby, now you have it <br>Now you got the baddest <br>Show me you can handle this <br><br>Bad bitch, bad bitch <br>Bad bitch, bad bitch <br>Bad bitch, bad bitch <br>Bad bitch, bad bitch <br>Show me you can handle this <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh, yeah, yeah, yeah <br><br>I pay my own bills and I pay my own rent <br>'Cause I'm indepe , independent <br>I buy my own rings and I do my own things <br>'Cause I'm indepe , independent <br>I know it really hurts, I know it ain't fair <br>You're not allowed to touch, but you can stare <br>Know it really hurts, know it ain't fair <br>So keep sayin' your prayers <br><br>You say you want a bad bitch <br>Baby, now you have it <br>Now you got a bad bitch <br>Show me you can handle this <br>Say you want a bad bitch <br>Baby, now you have it <br>Now you got the baddest <br>Show me you can handle this <br><br>Bad bitch, bad bitch <br>Bad bitch, bad bitch <br>Bad bitch, bad bitch <br>Bad bitch, bad bitch <br>Show me you can handle this]]></content><category term="Bebe Rexha" label="Bebe Rexha"/><category term="Bad Bitch" label="Bad Bitch"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/G-Eazy/FFF/</id><title>G-Eazy - F.F.F. - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:30:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:30:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/G-Eazy/FFF/" title="G-Eazy - F.F.F. - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[G, Bebe I got ya <br><br>Friends come and go, friends come and go <br>Go like the seasons <br>I never know, I never know what to believe in <br>And it's getting old, it's getting old <br>But no hard feelings <br>'Cause friends come and go, friends come and go without a reason <br>And I, I've been in LA for way too long <br>Can't get this air inside my lungs <br>It feels like I'm suffocatin' from all the lack of the realness here <br><br>Is there anybody real out here <br>Got my middle, middle up while I'm singing <br><br>Fuck fake friends, we don't need 'em <br>Only thing they're good for is leaving <br>Fuck fake friends, we don't need 'em <br>I've had it up to the ceiling <br>Fuck fake friends, we don't need 'em <br>Only thing they're good for is leaving <br>And I ain't got the time, money on my mind <br>I'll say it to your face, fuck fake friends <br><br>And lately I've been dealin' with mad stress <br>Comes with the territory of a Hollywood address <br>Is anybody real here I need some fact checks <br>I need more realness, need you to act less <br>'Cause they deserve Oscars, so many imposters <br>What's up with guest lists Can I come to your concerts <br>We all got demons, I'm dealin' with monsters <br>I've taken every picture, signed titties and signed shirts <br>But at the same time I know I'm blessed to be here <br>So let's just be clear <br>A million kids wish they had the spot I got <br>Success is not a sandy beach chair <br>Be careful with the people you meet here, I'm sayin' <br>Uh, yeah <br><br>Is there anybody real out here G <br>Got my middle, middle up while I'm singing Uh <br><br>Fuck fake friends, we don't need 'em <br>Only thing they're good for is leaving <br>Fuck fake friends, we don't need 'em <br>I've had it up to the ceiling <br>Fuck fake friends, we don't need 'em <br>Only thing they're good for is leaving <br>And I ain't got the time, money on my mind <br>I'll say it to your face, fuck fake friends <br>Yeah We don't need 'em <br>Bebe, you know I feel you <br><br>And I ain't got the time, money on my mind <br>Say it to my face, don't pretend <br>And I ain't got the time, money on my mind <br>I'll say it to your face, fuck fake friends <br>And I ain't got the time, money on my mind <br>Say it to my face, don't pretend <br>And I ain't got the time, money on my mind <br>I'll say it to your face, fuck fake friends <br><br>Is there anybody real out here <br>Got my middle, middle up while I'm singing <br><br>Fuck fake friends, we don't need 'em <br>Only thing they're good for is leaving <br>Fuck fake friends, we don't need 'em <br>I've had it up to the ceiling <br>Fuck fake friends, we don't need 'em <br>Only thing they're good for is leaving <br>And I ain't got the time, money on my mind <br>I'll say it to your face, fuck fake friends]]></content><category term="G-Eazy" label="G-Eazy"/><category term="F.F.F." label="F.F.F."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bebe_Rexha/Atmosphere/</id><title>Bebe_Rexha - Atmosphere - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:31:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:31:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bebe_Rexha/Atmosphere/" title="Bebe_Rexha - Atmosphere - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I feel in the beginning when we're living <br>We were tripping, we were so high <br>When you tell me that you love me were you bluffin' <br>Was it nothing Now you're so dry <br>You can tell me that you're sorry <br>But I know that you don't mean it, baby, don't lie <br>Don't lie, baby, don't lie <br><br>And I can't blame myself <br>For getting lost inside the promise of you <br>And I can't blame you leaving <br>'Cause what's meant to be will always be true <br><br>There isn't enough love in the atmosphere <br>To keep you here, ahh <br>There isn't enough love in the atmosphere <br>Don't leave me here, all alone <br>I ride for my baby <br>I died for my baby <br>I'd die for my baby, no lie <br>There isn't enough love in the atmosphere <br>In the atmosphere <br><br>Remember we were running up and down <br>And getting messy in the hallways <br>Told me that forever was the time we'd be together, baby, always <br>Now you're saying that you're sorry <br>But I know that you don't mean it 'cause you won't stay <br>No you won't stay, you won't stay <br><br>And I can't blame myself <br>For getting lost inside the promise of you <br>And I can't blame you leaving <br>'Cause what's meant to be will always be true <br><br>There isn't enough love in the atmosphere <br>To keep you here, ahh <br>There isn't enough love in the atmosphere <br>Don't leave me here, all alone <br>I ride for my baby <br>I died for my baby <br>I'd die for my baby, no lie <br>There isn't enough love in the atmosphere <br>In the atmosphere <br>If there's winners and losers, then I'll be the loser <br>I'm still here, I choose ya <br>I don't want another, if we can't have each other <br>'Cause baby, I love ya <br>Maybe in a different world, baby, I could be your girl <br>Maybe then I'll be with you <br>If there's winners and losers, then I'll be the loser <br>I'm still here, I choose ya <br><br>There isn't enough love in the atmosphere <br>To keep you here, ahh <br>There isn't enough love in the atmosphere <br>Don't leave me here, all alone <br>I ride for my baby <br>I died for my baby <br>I'd die for my baby, no lie <br>There isn't enough love in the atmosphere <br>In the atmosphere]]></content><category term="Bebe Rexha" label="Bebe Rexha"/><category term="Atmosphere" label="Atmosphere"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/European_Me_Live_Student_Radio_Session/</id><title>Six_By_Seven - European Me (Live Student Radio Session) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:31:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:31:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/European_Me_Live_Student_Radio_Session/" title="Six_By_Seven - European Me (Live Student Radio Session) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's good to be someone <br>It's good to be someone <br>To feel like you belong <br>Change your life today <br>Change your world as well <br>It's better than it sounds <br>European me <br>It's good to be someone <br>Sanitise your mind <br>Leave the past behind <br>Wallow in your pride <br>Drive the tumbrel mile <br>Your friends they are not mine <br>They hold me down <br>They hold me <br>Down where you belong <br>European me <br>It's good to be someone]]></content><category term="Six By Seven" label="Six By Seven"/><category term="European Me (Live Student Radio Session)" label="European Me (Live Student Radio Session)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/Change/</id><title>Six_By_Seven - Change - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:31:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:31:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/Change/" title="Six_By_Seven - Change - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lazy Like I wanna Be <br>I don't need to catch your eye <br>Lazy like I wanna be <br>I don't need to catch a ride <br>Holding on for you to be <br>Everything that I should want <br>Being what I want to be <br>I can't walk if I can't run <br>Being like I want to be <br>I don't need to hold you up <br>I say like I wanna say <br>You don't need to put me down <br>Begging you is not for me <br>I don't wanna make you change <br>No nothing here is right for you <br>I don't wanna make you change <br>I don't wanna make you change <br>But it's the price you have to pay <br>As you brave another day <br>But it's to hard to make out <br>I don't need this either way <br>I don't look back because I'm paranoid <br>I'm still yearning for the day <br>Yes it's all you, and follow <br>Follow you in every way <br>But you can't carry on now <br>It's the game we have to play <br>Yes it's too late to be generous <br>I don't want to find a way <br>Yes it's too late to be generous <br>I don't wanna make you change]]></content><category term="Six By Seven" label="Six By Seven"/><category term="Change" label="Change"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/Oh_Dear/</id><title>Six_By_Seven - Oh! Dear - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:31:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:31:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/Oh_Dear/" title="Six_By_Seven - Oh! Dear - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You are the sweetest thing <br>You're all that I need <br>You lie between my belly and knees <br>When you're gone, I am gone <br>When you're near I can't speak <br>When you leave, I feel left like a fork on a plate <br><br>Oh dear <br>My dear <br>Yeah I'm in love <br><br>Sell me a coat I can wear <br>And a comb for my hair <br>I could dance you to death on a Friday night <br>You leave my mouth open wide <br>Lock my jaw and take me out <br>I could dance you to death on a Saturday night <br><br>Oh dear <br>My dear <br>Yeah I'm in love]]></content><category term="Six By Seven" label="Six By Seven"/><category term="Oh! Dear" label="Oh! Dear"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/Bochum_Light_Up_My_Life/</id><title>Six_By_Seven - Bochum (Light Up My Life) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:31:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:31:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/Bochum_Light_Up_My_Life/" title="Six_By_Seven - Bochum (Light Up My Life) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll let the moment <br>take you away <br>from here <br>I'll let the moment <br>take you away <br>from here <br>were you lonely <br>did you need a friend <br>did you want me <br>to take you away <br>from here <br>were you lonely <br>did you need a friend <br>did you want me <br>to take you away <br>from here <br>You light up my life <br>when you smile <br>I got a love <br>and love <br>I can give it away <br>You light up my life <br>when you smile <br>I got a love <br>and love <br>I can give it away <br>Bochum <br>I don't need you now <br>I don't need your town <br>anymore <br>Bochum <br>I don't need the grime <br>I don't need the grime <br>of the Ruhr <br>You light up my life <br>when you smile <br>I got a love <br>and love <br>I can give it away <br>You light up my life <br>when you smile <br>I got a love <br>and love <br>I can give it away]]></content><category term="Six By Seven" label="Six By Seven"/><category term="Bochum (Light Up My Life)" label="Bochum (Light Up My Life)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/Eat_Junk_Become_Junk/</id><title>Six_By_Seven - Eat Junk Become Junk - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:31:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:31:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/Eat_Junk_Become_Junk/" title="Six_By_Seven - Eat Junk Become Junk - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm living in my life <br>I'm living in my life <br>I saved a nation and I broke no law <br>I'm living in my life <br>I know who put me here <br>I saved a nation and I broke no law <br>So tell me something new <br>Yeah tell me something new <br>Tell me what you got to look so pleased about <br>Yeah tell me something new <br>Just tell me something new <br>Tell me what you got to look so pleased about <br><br>Now listen to this, now listen to this <br>Iif you eat junk you become junk <br>I never broke no law no <br>Now listen to this, now listen to this <br>If you eat junk you become junk <br>I never broke no law no, I saved a nation <br>I saved a nation State of the nation <br><br>I'm living in you <br>I'm living near you <br>A shut mouth never makes no moan <br>I'm living in you <br>I'm living near you <br>This country's dirty and depressing me <br>Nobody can beat me, nobody can beat me <br>I need replacing by a better man <br>Nobody can beat me, nobody can beat me <br>A better lover with a fool plan]]></content><category term="Six By Seven" label="Six By Seven"/><category term="Eat Junk Become Junk" label="Eat Junk Become Junk"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/New_Year/</id><title>Six_By_Seven - New Year - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:31:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:31:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/New_Year/" title="Six_By_Seven - New Year - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Give me something I can live for <br>Give me something to believe in <br>Feed me saline, plasma life line <br>Skinned by sunlight, I'm hiding inside <br><br>I wanna reach out <br>And I wanna stay <br>How can I lose <br>If I refuse to fail <br><br>Broken pavements and bombed out buildings <br>Nothing left but mines for children <br>Right side numb and the left side is useless <br>Oh my world you really can thrill me <br><br>I wanna reach out <br>And I wanna stay <br>How can I lose <br>If I refuse to fail <br><br>Into the new year]]></content><category term="Six By Seven" label="Six By Seven"/><category term="New Year" label="New Year"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/So_Close/</id><title>Six_By_Seven - So Close - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:31:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:31:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/So_Close/" title="Six_By_Seven - So Close - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Last night I thought I heard you <br>Stepping through the door <br>You and me were so beautiful <br>It must have been a dream <br>You know they really screwed you up <br>Before you tumbled down <br>Boy they really screwed you up <br>Before you tumbled down <br><br>So close to being anything <br>So close to being more <br>Than I have ever been <br>So close to being anything <br>So close to being more <br>Than I have ever been <br><br>I adore your conversation <br>I adore just who you are <br>You inspire my imagination <br>I adore just who you are <br><br>So close to being anything <br>So close to being anything <br>So close to being more <br>Than I have ever been]]></content><category term="Six By Seven" label="Six By Seven"/><category term="So Close" label="So Close"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/For_You/</id><title>Six_By_Seven - For You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:31:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:31:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/For_You/" title="Six_By_Seven - For You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Say you want to stay with me <br>Say you want to sail away <br>Say you want to sail today <br>Take me where I want to be <br><br>This is where the truth can never hide <br>Take me where my soul can never die <br><br>I wanna stay alive <br>I wanna stay alive <br>I wanna do it with you <br>I wanna stay alive <br>Wanna do it for you <br>I want to stay alive <br><br>Show me all that I can be <br>This is the oldest that I've ever been <br>A ring to chain us day to day <br>A mistake that every boy should make <br><br>This is where the truth can never hide <br>Take me where my soul can never die]]></content><category term="Six By Seven" label="Six By Seven"/><category term="For You" label="For You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/Crying/</id><title>Six_By_Seven - Crying - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:31:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:31:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/Crying/" title="Six_By_Seven - Crying - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[To say that I warned you <br>Is putting it mildly <br>We can't go back in time <br>Nothing can help us now <br>I favoured the truth yeah <br>I'm running so fast now <br>I searched for alibis <br>No one help me now <br>To say that I warned you <br>I couldn't it do it anyway <br>Than telling the truth yeah <br>My life is here today <br>I'm crying the water <br>I'm crying for your love <br>I don't wanna love <br>I just stumble every time <br>You tell me it's simple <br>I tell you it's fair <br>You'll tell me anything f <br>For this to stay this way <br>You sold ma a truth yeah <br>You did it so sweetly <br>You sold me down the line <br>I followed every time <br>To say that I warned you <br>I couldn't it do it anyway <br>Than telling the truth yeah <br>My life is here today <br>I'm crying the water <br>I'm crying for your love <br>I don't wanna love <br>I just stumble every time]]></content><category term="Six By Seven" label="Six By Seven"/><category term="Crying" label="Crying"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/Candlelight/</id><title>Six_By_Seven - Candlelight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:31:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:31:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/Candlelight/" title="Six_By_Seven - Candlelight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Something broke like an egg in my throat <br>Something stopped beating blood in my chest <br>Forever gone, you are with me when I miss you <br>Candlelight give me time to get things right <br><br>Can you slow down <br>Can you slow down now <br>Slow down, slow down <br>Can you slow down now <br>My candlelight <br><br>I was counting clouds in a clear blue empty sky <br>I was skimming stones on a river the dam made dry <br>Is it fair, you are here when I am long gone <br>Open your eyes, close the door and take what's yours <br><br>Can you slow down <br>Can you slow down now <br>Slow down, slow down <br>Can you slow down now <br>My candlelight <br><br>We die a lot and live a little]]></content><category term="Six By Seven" label="Six By Seven"/><category term="Candlelight" label="Candlelight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/I_O_U_Love_Single_Edit/</id><title>Six_By_Seven - I O U Love (Single Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:31:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:31:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Six_By_Seven/I_O_U_Love_Single_Edit/" title="Six_By_Seven - I O U Love (Single Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You are the atom that started life <br>You are the glue of the universe <br>Every thousand years I've learned to take a breath <br>You are cosmic and I love you <br><br>They brought down the stars and shined them because of you <br>They painted the sky in blue cause you asked them to <br>And all the rewards of life are just simple truths <br>You are reasoning for sure <br><br>I'll never know the secrets of the world <br>I'll never know them, never know them now <br>I O U love <br><br>I remember when you covered the earth in sleep <br>The ebb and flow and touch of your kiss <br>There can't be a better way <br>With my last breath I will call your name <br><br>I'll never know the secrets of the world <br>I'll never know, I'll never know them now <br>I O U love <br>I O U love <br>I O U love <br>I O U love <br>I O U love <br>I O U love <br>I O U love <br>I O U love <br>I O U love <br>I O U love <br>I O U love <br>I O U love <br>I O U love <br>I O U love]]></content><category term="Six By Seven" label="Six By Seven"/><category term="I O U Love (Single Edit)" label="I O U Love (Single Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ellipse/Summer_Sky/</id><title>Ellipse - Summer Sky - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:32:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:32:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ellipse/Summer_Sky/" title="Ellipse - Summer Sky - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[숨가쁘던 지난 날도 <br>웃음 짓게 해 <br>Belong to Seems <br>to be in my heart <br>차가워진 네 모습도 <br>이 도시처럼 <br>There is a knowing <br>to make breaking time <br>Gonna sum sum sum <br>summer sky <br>Gonna keep keep keep <br>keeping high <br>두 눈을 감고 달려봐 <br>Gonna sum sum sum <br>summer sky <br>Gonna keep keep keep <br>keeping high <br>구름 위로 펼친 <br>summer sky <br>순간 순간 느껴지던 <br>작은 설렘도 <br>Cause I know <br>that your heart is true <br>안타까운 기억들은 <br>이제 사라져 <br>Feel like the wind <br>because I can’t see <br>Gonna sum sum sum <br>summer sky <br>Gonna keep keep keep <br>keeping high <br>두 눈을 감고 달려봐 <br>Gonna sum sum sum <br>summer sky <br>Gonna keep keep keep <br>keeping high <br>구름 위로 펼친 <br>summer sky <br>Feel like that life for me <br>Feel like that in the sky <br>Feel like that life for me <br>Feel like that in the sky <br>Feel like that life for me <br>Feel like that in the sky <br>Feel like that life for me <br>Feel like that in the sky <br>]]></content><category term="Ellipse" label="Ellipse"/><category term="Summer Sky" label="Summer Sky"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/R45/보좌에_앉으신_주/</id><title>R45 - 보좌에 앉으신 주 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:32:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:32:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/R45/%EB%B3%B4%EC%A2%8C%EC%97%90_%EC%95%89%EC%9C%BC%EC%8B%A0_%EC%A3%BC/" title="R45 - 보좌에 앉으신 주 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보좌에 앉으신 주 <br>거룩한 전능의 주 <br>존귀한 어린양께 <br>천사들이 경배하네 <br>온 하늘 가득 덮은 <br>빛나는 주의 영광 <br>무지개 둘러싸인 <br>표현 못할 경이로움 <br>주의 영광 보네 <br>주의 영광 보네 <br>위대하신 전능의 <br>주님께 경배하세 <br>모든 영광 <br>합당하신 주님께 <br>보좌에 앉으신 주 <br>거룩한 전능의 주 <br>존귀한 어린양께 <br>천사들이 경배하네 <br>온 하늘 가득 덮은 <br>빛나는 주의 영광 <br>무지개 둘러싸인 <br>표현 못할 경이로움 <br>주의 영광 보네 <br>주의 영광 보네 <br>주의 영광 보네 <br>주의 영광 보네 <br>위대하신 전능의 <br>주님께 경배하세 <br>모든 영광 <br>합당하신 주님께 <br>크신 주의 영광 앞에 <br>모두 엎드리네 <br>경배하세 <br>보좌 위 어린양께 <br>]]></content><category term="R45" label="R45"/><category term="보좌에 앉으신 주" label="보좌에 앉으신 주"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/R45/성령의_바람/</id><title>R45 - 성령의 바람 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:32:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:32:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/R45/%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9%EC%9D%98_%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C/" title="R45 - 성령의 바람 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주의 성령 이곳에 <br>바람처럼 임하시네 <br>하나님의 호흡이 내 영혼 감싸네 <br>성령의 바람 지금 이곳에 <br>불어와 우리를 새롭게 하네 <br>진리의 성령 우릴 이끄네 <br>I’m reaching for Your heart <br>주를 기다립니다 <br>나를 채워주소서 <br>바람처럼 불어와 <br>내 안에 불 태우소서 <br>주의 성령 이곳에 <br>바람처럼 임하시네 <br>하나님의 호흡이 내 영혼 감싸네 <br>성령의 바람 지금 이곳에 <br>불어와 우리를 새롭게 하네 <br>진리의 성령 우릴 이끄네 <br>I’m reaching for Your heart <br>성령의 바람 지금 이곳에 <br>불어와 우리를 새롭게 하네 <br>진리의 성령 우릴 이끄네 <br>I’m reaching for Your heart <br>주를 기다립니다 <br>나를 채워주소서 <br>바람처럼 불어와 <br>내 안에 불 태우소서 <br>주를 기다립니다 <br>나를 채워주소서 <br>바람처럼 불어와 <br>내 안에 불 태우소서 <br>Holy Spirit come <br>in my heart in my life <br>Holy Spirit come <br>welcome in this place <br>Holy Spirit come <br>in my heart in my life <br>Holy Spirit come <br>welcome in this place <br>Holy Spirit come <br>in my heart in my life <br>Holy Spirit come <br>welcome in this place <br>Holy Spirit come <br>in my heart in my life <br>Holy Spirit come <br>welcome in this place <br>]]></content><category term="R45" label="R45"/><category term="성령의 바람" label="성령의 바람"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/R45/King_Jesus/</id><title>R45 - King Jesus - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:32:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:32:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/R45/King_Jesus/" title="R45 - King Jesus - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[예수 모든 만왕의 왕 <br>예수 온 땅을 다스리는 <br>전능하신 나의 주 하나님 <br>모든 만물 다 엎드려 <br>주께 모든 영광 돌리네 <br>위대하신 나의 주 하나님 <br>빛나는 주의 영광 온 땅 덮네 <br>형언할 수 없는 경이로움 난 보네 <br>누가 주와 같으리 비교할 수 없네 <br>높고 위대한 전능의 주 <br>영광의 주님 <br>소리 높여 찬양해 온 맘 다해 찬양 <br>주님의 영광 앞에 선 <br>내 영혼 외치네 <br>예수 모든 만왕의 왕 <br>예수 온 땅을 다스리는 <br>전능하신 나의 주 하나님 <br>모든 만물 다 엎드려 <br>주께 모든 영광 돌리네 <br>위대하신 나의 주 하나님 <br>빛나는 주의 영광 온 땅 덮네 <br>형언할 수 없는 경이로움 난 보네 <br>누가 주와 같으리 비교할 수 없네 <br>높고 위대한 전능의 주 <br>영광의 주님 <br>소리 높여 찬양해 온 맘 다해 찬양 <br>주님의 영광 앞에 선 <br>내 영혼 외치네 <br>모든 찬양 받으시기 합당한 <br>우리 주께 모든 영광 돌리세 <br>모든 찬양 받으시기 합당한 <br>우리 주께 모든 영광 돌리세 <br>모든 찬양 받으시기 합당한 <br>우리 주께 모든 영광 돌리세 <br>누가 주와 같으리 비교할 수 없네 <br>높고 위대한 전능의 주 <br>영광의 주님 <br>소리 높여 찬양해 온 맘 다해 찬양 <br>주님의 영광 앞에 선 <br>내 영혼 외치네 <br>누가 주와 같으리 비교할 수 없네 <br>높고 위대한 전능의 주 <br>영광의 주님 <br>소리 높여 찬양해 온 맘 다해 찬양 <br>주님의 영광 앞에 선 <br>내 영혼 외치네 <br>]]></content><category term="R45" label="R45"/><category term="King Jesus" label="King Jesus"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/R45/죽음_이기신_주/</id><title>R45 - 죽음 이기신 주 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:32:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:32:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/R45/%EC%A3%BD%EC%9D%8C_%EC%9D%B4%EA%B8%B0%EC%8B%A0_%EC%A3%BC/" title="R45 - 죽음 이기신 주 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[죽음 이기신 주의 승리 <br>날 자유케해 <br>부활하신 주 놀라운 영광 <br>나 찬양해 <br>내 모든 죄 <br>주가 다 지셨네 <br>주로 인해 <br>나 자유해 나 자유해 <br>생명의 주 예수 <br>다시 사셨네 <br>무덤도 죽음도 <br>모두 사라져 <br>십자가 승리로 <br>날 살리셨네 <br>영광 높이 계신 <br>주 찬양하리 <br>죽음 이기신 주의 승리 <br>날 자유케해 <br>부활하신 주 놀라운 영광 <br>나 찬양해 <br>내 모든 죄 <br>주가 다 지셨네 <br>주로 인해 <br>나 자유해 나 자유해 <br>생명의 주 예수 <br>다시 사셨네 <br>무덤도 죽음도 <br>모두 사라져 <br>십자가 승리로 <br>날 살리셨네 <br>영광 높이 계신 <br>주 찬양하리 <br>생명의 주 예수 <br>다시 사셨네 <br>무덤도 죽음도 <br>모두 사라져 <br>십자가 승리로 <br>날 살리셨네 <br>영광 높이 계신 <br>주 찬양하리 <br>오 모든 영광 <br>존귀한 어린양께 <br>영원히 또 영원히 <br>오 모든 영광 <br>존귀한 어린양께 <br>영원히 또 영원히 <br>오 모든 영광 <br>존귀한 어린양께 <br>영원히 또 영원히 <br>오 모든 영광 <br>존귀한 어린양께 <br>영원히 또 영원히 <br>생명의 주 예수 <br>다시 사셨네 <br>무덤도 죽음도 <br>모두 사라져 <br>십자가 승리로 <br>날 살리셨네 <br>영광 높이 계신 <br>주 찬양하리 <br>생명의 주 예수 <br>다시 사셨네 <br>무덤도 죽음도 <br>모두 사라져 <br>십자가 승리로 <br>날 살리셨네 <br>영광 높이 계신 <br>주 찬양하리 <br>오 모든 영광 <br>존귀한 어린양께 <br>영원히 또 영원히 <br>오 모든 영광 <br>존귀한 어린양께 <br>영원히 또 영원히 <br>]]></content><category term="R45" label="R45"/><category term="죽음 이기신 주" label="죽음 이기신 주"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/R45/Open_Up/</id><title>R45 - Open Up - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:32:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:32:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/R45/Open_Up/" title="R45 - Open Up - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Open up heaven's glory come <br>Let Your Kingdom come <br>Let Your will be done <br>Open up heaven's glory come <br>Let Your Kingdom come <br>Let Your will be done <br>하늘의 뜻이 <br>이 땅에 이뤄지리라 <br>하늘의 뜻이 <br>이 땅에 이뤄지리라 <br>Your Kingdom forever <br>God He reign <br>Your glory Your power <br>God He reign <br>Open up <br>Open up heaven's glory come <br>Let Your Kingdom come <br>Let Your will be done <br>Open up heaven's glory come <br>Let Your Kingdom come <br>Let Your will be done <br>Open up heaven's glory come <br>Let Your Kingdom come <br>Let Your will be done <br>Open up heaven's glory come <br>Let Your Kingdom come <br>Let Your will be done <br>하늘문 여소서 <br>주 나라 임하네 <br>소망있네 기쁨있네 <br>자유있네 <br>하늘의 뜻이 <br>이 땅에 이뤄지리라 <br>하늘의 뜻이 <br>이 땅에 이뤄지리라 <br>하늘의 뜻이 <br>이 땅에 이뤄지리라 <br>하늘의 뜻이 <br>이 땅에 이뤄지리라 <br>Your Kingdom forever <br>God He reign <br>Your glory Your power <br>God He reign <br>Your Kingdom forever <br>God He reign <br>Your glory Your power <br>God He reign <br>Your Kingdom forever <br>God He reign <br>Your glory Your power <br>God He reign <br>]]></content><category term="R45" label="R45"/><category term="Open Up" label="Open Up"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Horim/TEMP-TON/</id><title>Horim - TEMP-TON - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:32:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:32:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Horim/TEMP-TON/" title="Horim - TEMP-TON - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We should not t e m p t <br>each other other <br>우린 닿을 수 <br>없을 거란 걸 알어 알어 <br>We should not t e m p t <br>each other other <br>오늘 밤 우릴 서로 <br>원하지 말어 말어 <br>깊이 술잔에 술이 따라져 <br>조금의 얘기마저 웃게 하지 <br>오랜 시간 뒤에 만난 <br>것 같지 않게 아주 편한 <br>oh 둘의 얘기는 부드럽지 <br>더 따른 술은 <br>날 더 취하게 하고 <br>닿은 손은 너를 <br>더 만지고 싶어 <br>깊이 알기 원했던 <br>But 가질 수 없었던 <br>지금 조금만 더 날 편해해줘 <br>그때의 그날로 돌아갈 수 있게 <br>생각만 가득한 체 <br>네 두눈에 나를 담네 <br>CUz we know 우리 <br>그래선 안된다는걸 <br>But 안되기에 더 더욱 <br>하고픈 걸 우리 <br>Now we know <br>do we have a good night <br>책임지지 못할 <br>그밤이 다가와 <br>Now we um um um <br>We should not t e m p t <br>each other other <br>우린 닿을 수 <br>없을 거란 걸 알어 알어 <br>We should not t e m p t <br>each other other <br>오늘 밤 우릴 서로 <br>원하지 말어 말어 <br>]]></content><category term="Horim" label="Horim"/><category term="TEMP-TON" label="TEMP-TON"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코인사이드/Silence_침묵/</id><title>코인사이드 - Silence (침묵) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:32:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:32:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EC%9D%B8%EC%82%AC%EC%9D%B4%EB%93%9C/Silence_%EC%B9%A8%EB%AC%B5/" title="코인사이드 - Silence (침묵) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[더 이상 말은 하지 않을게 <br>너의 얘길 들어 줄게 <br>불필요한 말은 하지 않을게 <br>그냥 그저 들어 줄게 <br>내 모든 힘을 쏟아 널 <br>이해 시키는 일도 <br>이젠 지쳐 그만 할게 <br>의미 없는 위로도 <br>내 생각과는 많이 <br>다른 너에게 <br>더 이상 말은 하지 않을게 <br>너의 얘길 들어 줄게 <br>불필요한 말은 하지 않을게 <br>그냥 그저 들어 줄게 <br>내 모든 힘을 쏟아 널 <br>이해 시키는 일도 <br>이젠 지쳐 그만 할게 <br>의미 없는 위로도 <br>내 생각과는 많이 <br>다른 너에게 <br>]]></content><category term="코인사이드" label="코인사이드"/><category term="Silence (침묵)" label="Silence (침묵)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코인사이드/Scab_Off/</id><title>코인사이드 - Scab Off - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:32:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:32:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EC%9D%B8%EC%82%AC%EC%9D%B4%EB%93%9C/Scab_Off/" title="코인사이드 - Scab Off - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[what happened to me <br>what happened to us <br>i'm still confused <br>what should i be <br>what should we be come <br>i had no time to control <br>there's a nothing <br>i can to back again <br>for now just only <br>don't hurt myself <br>oh don't hurt myself <br>even though get hurt <br>from the others <br>don't hurt myself <br>oh don't hurt myself <br>even though get hurt <br>from by myself <br>why always me <br>why always me <br>i need a reason <br>to understand <br>who made me like this <br>who made us like this <br>i need a someone to blame <br>the answer is on me <br>i was wrong about you <br>for now i have to <br>don't hurt myself <br>oh don't hurt myself <br>even though get hurt <br>from the others <br>don't hurt myself <br>oh don't hurt myself <br>even though get hurt <br>from by myself <br>i have to be more stronger <br>for make a wish with you <br>hold my soul hold my hands <br>don't hurt myself <br>oh don't hurt myself <br>even though get hurt <br>from the others <br>don't hurt myself <br>oh don't hurt myself <br>even though get hurt <br>from by myself <br>please don't <br>please don't hurt <br>don't hurt hurt <br>]]></content><category term="코인사이드" label="코인사이드"/><category term="Scab Off" label="Scab Off"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코인사이드/I_Wont_Forget/</id><title>코인사이드 - I Won`t Forget - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:32:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:32:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EC%9D%B8%EC%82%AC%EC%9D%B4%EB%93%9C/I_Wont_Forget/" title="코인사이드 - I Won`t Forget - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Must be hard to talk about it <br>i understand <br>but the thing that's for us <br>i understand <br>if you ever feel alone <br>don't <br>so shine bright <br>you were never on your own <br>so shine bright <br>i hope you are doing well <br>i won't forget us <br>every time on stage <br>i'll think you guys <br>i won't forget us <br>that's right this is song <br>for you <br>now of trying to walk <br>in each way <br>make it better <br>but it's enough to <br>keep me going <br>don't forget the fact that <br>we were together <br>some where beyond <br>the pain must be away <br>you were never on your own <br>so shine bright <br>i hope you are doing well <br>i won't forget us <br>every time on stage <br>i'll think you guys <br>i won't forget us <br>that's right this is song <br>failed to do with the end <br>so sad <br>i never thought i'd be <br>the one that you <br>would break <br>i guess some things <br>never change <br>i hope you are doing well <br>i won't forget us <br>every time on stage <br>i'll think you guys <br>i won't forget us <br>that's right this is song <br>for you <br>that's right this is song <br>for you for you <br>]]></content><category term="코인사이드" label="코인사이드"/><category term="I Won`t Forget" label="I Won`t Forget"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코인사이드/Go_There/</id><title>코인사이드 - Go There - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:32:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:32:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EC%9D%B8%EC%82%AC%EC%9D%B4%EB%93%9C/Go_There/" title="코인사이드 - Go There - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[something i wanna say <br>you doing all right <br>what is what you want <br>you look nervous in my eyes <br>go there <br>than find you <br>i know the way why don't <br>you go there with me <br>something i wanna say <br>you doing all right <br>what is what you want <br>you look nervous in my eyes <br>you don't have to say i do <br>you don't have to smile so sad <br>please don't tell me it's too late <br>we've got to believe it <br>go there <br>than find you <br>i know the way why don't <br>you go there with me <br>we can make it what we like <br>i shouldn't believe in <br>the dreams that i am <br>won't you take me <br>by the hand <br>i've got a brand new <br>cure for lonely <br>what's inside of you head <br>i just might be with you <br>go there <br>than find you <br>i know the way why don't <br>you go there with me <br>we can make it what we like <br>i shouldn't believe in <br>the dreams that i am <br>something i wanna say <br>you doing all right <br>what is what you want <br>please tell me who you are <br>]]></content><category term="코인사이드" label="코인사이드"/><category term="Go There" label="Go There"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Strand_Of_Oaks/Taking_Acid_And_Talking_To_My_Brother/</id><title>Strand_Of_Oaks - Taking Acid And Talking To My Brother - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:33:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:33:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Strand_Of_Oaks/Taking_Acid_And_Talking_To_My_Brother/" title="Strand_Of_Oaks - Taking Acid And Talking To My Brother - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Light in the window <br>Light in your eyes <br>Light in the field <br>We all move in time <br><br>Light shows your heartbeat <br>And light on the sheets <br>Light makes you wake up <br>And drift back to sleep <br>And feel it all again <br><br>Life keeps repeating <br>Day after day <br>I can't stop moving <br>Or it all goes away <br><br>Jon, you are meaning light <br>Jon, you are weak <br>Wake up and see it all <br>Everything <br>And live it all with me <br>All with me <br>All with me <br>I want it all with me <br><br>Oh if I made all the money <br>Oh if I took all the pills <br>Oh, I took you all for granted <br>Oh I left you all amends <br>Oh e oh Oh oh Oh e o Oh ho <br><br>If you want it <br>You got it <br>The sun and the moon <br>Our mother's surrender <br>We're waking up new <br>Why did you want it <br>Why did you cry <br>Lost in the moment <br>The light in your eye <br><br>All again <br><br>Oh <br><br>You want it <br>You got it <br>The sun and the moon <br>You want it <br>You got it]]></content><category term="Strand Of Oaks" label="Strand Of Oaks"/><category term="Taking Acid And Talking To My Brother" label="Taking Acid And Talking To My Brother"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Strand_Of_Oaks/Quit_It/</id><title>Strand_Of_Oaks - Quit It - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:33:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:33:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Strand_Of_Oaks/Quit_It/" title="Strand_Of_Oaks - Quit It - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nevermind the good times <br>Never mind the bad <br>Nevermind the come down <br>Numb it all instead <br>I've been off my reason <br>I've been on the road <br>I keep getting a feeling <br>I need to go home <br><br>Everytime I said that I'd quit <br>Everytime that I miss all things I don't need <br>You went and got it stuck in my head <br>And we're sitting right here <br>Acting like we don't care <br>I give up my best times for some more <br><br>Nevermind the good times <br>Never mind the bad <br>Nevermind the come down <br>Numb it all instead <br>I miss you <br><br>I've been off my reason <br>I went on the road <br>I keep getting a feeling <br>I need to go home <br><br>Everytime I said that I'd quit <br>Everytime that I miss all things I don't need <br>You went and got it stuck in my head <br>And we're sitting right here <br>Acting like we don't care <br>I give up my best times for some more <br><br>Look out for the truck <br>Sliding into the lane <br>Head went through the window <br>I can't get no sleep <br><br>I might have won your war <br>Cuz I'm the one you know <br>You keep me in your hands <br>I'm laying on the road <br><br>Everytime I said that I'd quit <br>Everytime that I miss all things I don't need <br>You went and got it stuck in my head <br>And we're sitting right here <br>Acting like we don't care <br>I give up my best times for some more <br><br>And I'll stop riding my bike <br>Just to show her <br>And I quit <br>I quit <br>It's all right <br>It's all right <br>It's all right <br>It's all right <br>It's all right]]></content><category term="Strand Of Oaks" label="Strand Of Oaks"/><category term="Quit It" label="Quit It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Strand_Of_Oaks/Cry/</id><title>Strand_Of_Oaks - Cry - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:33:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:33:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Strand_Of_Oaks/Cry/" title="Strand_Of_Oaks - Cry - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The way you sweetly abuse me <br>Our love on the line <br>We hope only for magic <br>We live only lies <br><br>Hey, you're making me cry <br>Hey, you're making me cry <br><br>When your lies, so many lies <br>Come back everywhich <br>Lies for keeping the mood <br>And lies that only work on you <br><br>Hey, you're making me cry <br>Hey, you're making me cry <br><br>What are you, what are you doing later <br>What am I doing later <br>Yeah, what are you doing later <br>Um, I'm just chilling, I might go to the store maybe, I don't know <br><br>Wait, what was the point of that conversation <br> Bueno, bueno, You hear that <br>I don't understand what's happening <br>keep their head yeah, yesterday <br>You have adderol <br>Sound so good to my ears]]></content><category term="Strand Of Oaks" label="Strand Of Oaks"/><category term="Cry" label="Cry"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Strand_Of_Oaks/Salt_Brothers/</id><title>Strand_Of_Oaks - Salt Brothers - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:33:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:33:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Strand_Of_Oaks/Salt_Brothers/" title="Strand_Of_Oaks - Salt Brothers - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You broke the silence, I laughed at the moon <br>You talked about James, in a van full of fools <br>So sick of the boring, I held onto your clothes <br>No time for people, who follow the rules <br><br>When you come down, I come up <br>We chased the morning <br><br>Back at the hotel, years might have passed <br>I take off my arms, and swim in the bed <br>Don't go near the mirror, keep playing that song <br>Your best friend can hear you, he's singing along <br><br>When you come down, I come up <br>We'll chase the morning <br><br>Those sad songs are breaking my heart <br><br>We want something new, if it doesn't change now I'll lose <br>We want something new, make it good, make it real, make it true]]></content><category term="Strand Of Oaks" label="Strand Of Oaks"/><category term="Salt Brothers" label="Salt Brothers"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Strand_Of_Oaks/Everything/</id><title>Strand_Of_Oaks - Everything - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:33:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:33:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Strand_Of_Oaks/Everything/" title="Strand_Of_Oaks - Everything - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yah <br><br>I'm on a ledge again <br>Spinning a night away <br>I'm on everything you can give me <br><br>And life is medical <br>Better grab all the medicine <br>You want a love song, right away <br><br>And I swim more and I swim <br>Someone like you would <br>And I swim and I fall and I fall <br>Someone like you would <br>Someone like you <br><br>And you are a lot of things <br>Stealing my energy <br>You are never worse than me, babe <br><br>I'm in love with a waterway <br>Oh man, I can't explain <br>You lift me up with your family <br><br>And I toil in the morning and I toil <br>Someone like you would <br>And I toil and I fall and I fall <br>Someone like you would <br>Someone like you <br><br>And I toil in the morning and I toil <br>Someone like you would <br>And I toil and I fall and I fall <br>Someone like you would <br>Someone like you <br>Someone like you <br>Someone like you <br><br>Boo]]></content><category term="Strand Of Oaks" label="Strand Of Oaks"/><category term="Everything" label="Everything"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Strand_Of_Oaks/Radio_Kids/</id><title>Strand_Of_Oaks - Radio Kids - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:33:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:33:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Strand_Of_Oaks/Radio_Kids/" title="Strand_Of_Oaks - Radio Kids - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Remember how it felt to listen <br>Fumbling to press record <br>Strangest voice I've heard before <br><br>Who the hell is Hippie Johnny <br>Feel like somebody at school I know <br>I need to get to sleep <br>But maybe, maybe, maybe just one more <br>So play it, play it loud on the radio <br><br>I got my headphones on <br>And my parents will never know <br>It's something that we had before we lost control <br>On the radio <br><br>I can't even pay attention <br>It's just talk, talk nobody listens <br>I miss getting lost <br>I miss just making plans <br>And now it' just kids repeating <br>I guess I'm just as bad as them <br><br>I wanna get it back <br>I wanna get it back <br>I'll never get it back I know <br>So play it, play it loud on the radio <br><br>I'm feeling sorry for myself <br>I'm feeling pretty old <br>At least I had that song <br>At least I had that song <br>On the radio <br><br>I want to get it back <br>I want to get it back <br>Oh bring it back <br>I'll never get it back <br>I want to get it back <br>I'll never get it back <br><br>Bring it back <br>Bring it <br>Bring it <br>Bring it <br><br>On the radio <br>Oh on the radio <br><br>Play it on the radio <br>Play it on the radio <br>Play it <br>Play it <br>Play it <br>Play it <br>Play it <br>Play it <br>Play it <br>Play it on the radio]]></content><category term="Strand Of Oaks" label="Strand Of Oaks"/><category term="Radio Kids" label="Radio Kids"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Strand_Of_Oaks/Hard_Love/</id><title>Strand_Of_Oaks - Hard Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:33:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:33:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Strand_Of_Oaks/Hard_Love/" title="Strand_Of_Oaks - Hard Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[He ran away, he went searching <br>He came back, tired of looking <br>You leave me now, give you nothing <br>Fired up, tired of wasting my <br><br>Hard love <br>Hard Love <br><br>Yeah, we know, no other hating <br>Ride up, I went out looking <br>Come back, come back say it <br><br>Hard love, we don't find it enough <br>Your way, I don't take it enough <br>My way, I don't fight it enough <br>Good love, we don't love hold it enough <br><br>Hard love, we don't find it <br>Your way, I don't take it <br>My way, I don't fight it <br>Good love, we don't love hold it at all <br><br>You recognize all the places <br>Faces on the window <br>I keep pacing, locked in my room <br>Calling your name, combing my hair <br>Calling just to get you, get you right over here <br><br>Just to get you down <br>Just to get you down <br><br>Hard love, we don't find it enough <br>Your way, I don't take it enough <br>My way, I don't fight it enough <br>Good love, we don't love hold it enough <br><br>Hard love, we don't find it <br>Your way, I don't take it <br>My way, I don't fight it <br>Good love, we don't love hold it <br><br>Hard love, hard love <br>Hard love, hard love <br>Hard love, hard love <br><br>Hard love, hard love <br>Hard love, hard love <br>Hard love, hard love]]></content><category term="Strand Of Oaks" label="Strand Of Oaks"/><category term="Hard Love" label="Hard Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Orwells/Last_Call_Go_Home/</id><title>The_Orwells - Last Call (Go Home) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:33:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:33:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Orwells/Last_Call_Go_Home/" title="The_Orwells - Last Call (Go Home) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I, I get weary when you're near me, give me space <br>She, she gets dreary when hears me walkin' in <br>Those, those around me when they found me don't talk much <br>When, when I get back you can relapse in my room <br><br>I'm, I'm in between, happy and mean, waiting on time to stop <br>And when you go, please let me know, if I should sit and rot <br>What should I be, when I agree, always the one on top <br>And when you wake, take what you take, I think my mind's made up <br><br>Look, lookin' upset at the sunset, outta sight <br>Girl, made in China, maybe kinda lookin' cheap <br>Walk, walk up to her, try to woo her, not impressed <br>Hang, hang my head and close my tab, I'm takin' off <br><br>I'm, I'm in between, happy and mean, waiting on time to stop <br>And when you go, please let me know, if I should sit and rot <br>What should I be, when I agree, always the one on top <br>And when you wake, take what you take, I think my mind's made uuuuup]]></content><category term="The Orwells" label="The Orwells"/><category term="Last Call (Go Home)" label="Last Call (Go Home)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Orwells/Ring_Pop/</id><title>The_Orwells - Ring Pop - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:33:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:33:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Orwells/Ring_Pop/" title="The_Orwells - Ring Pop - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Queen dream from across that sea <br>Cashing checks from a magazine <br>From the copper to a TV screen <br>The kind of face that's haunting me <br><br>Something about it, something about it <br>Isn't quite right Isn't quite right <br>Livin' without it, livin' without it <br>In plain sight In plain sight <br><br>NBC to the NME <br>To talk shows on the BBC <br>Heathrow to ORD <br>Too busy to drink with me aww <br><br>Something about it, something about it <br>Isn't quite right, isn't quite right <br>Livin' without it, livin' without it <br>In plain sight In plain sight <br><br>Something about it, something about it <br>Isn't quite right, isn't quite right <br>Livin' without it, livin' without it <br>In plain sight In plain sight]]></content><category term="The Orwells" label="The Orwells"/><category term="Ring Pop" label="Ring Pop"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/토리/달달달달달아/</id><title>토리 - 달달달달달아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:33:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:33:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%86%A0%EB%A6%AC/%EB%8B%AC%EB%8B%AC%EB%8B%AC%EB%8B%AC%EB%8B%AC%EC%95%84/" title="토리 - 달달달달달아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너의 걸음걸이가 <br>질끈 묶은 머리가 <br>사르르 입꼬리가 <br>달아 달아 <br>아기 같은 웃음과 <br>녹아 드는 목소리 <br>혀 끝에 닿은 아가베 시럽처럼 <br>넌 <br>달달달달달아 <br>달달달달달아 <br>달달달달달아 <br>누가 <br>니가 <br>우리 같이 걷는 밤 <br>쏟아지는 별들과 <br>마주잡은 손가락 <br>달아 달아 <br>뽀얀 너의 얼굴과 <br>애교 섞인 목소리 <br>꿀 떨어지는 유DJ 멘트처럼 <br>넌 <br>달달달달달아 <br>달달달달달아 <br>달달달달달아 <br>누가 <br>니가 달아 <br>밝은 달아 <br>콕 찍어 먹어보면 <br>Sweeter than chocolate babe <br>난 너란 꿀을 매일 모으는 <br>Honey bee Are you with me <br>달달달달달아 <br>달달달달달아 <br>달달달달달아 <br>누가 <br>달달달달달아 <br>달달달달달아 <br>달달달달달아 <br>누가 <br>니가 <br>]]></content><category term="토리" label="토리"/><category term="달달달달달아" label="달달달달달아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Orwells/Heavy_Head/</id><title>The_Orwells - Heavy Head - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:34:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:34:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Orwells/Heavy_Head/" title="The_Orwells - Heavy Head - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dry mouthed in the hot white sand <br>Duct taped in a big white van <br>Put a bag over their heads <br>Cut a hole and their face turns red <br><br>I got this feeling when you're not around <br>Like a freight train runnin' through town <br>And when they bark at it don't make a sound <br>This whole generation don't make a <br><br>In every wolf <br>There's a dog looking for revenge <br>So take me to the desert <br>And chop off my heavy, heavy head <br><br>Oh and then unleash the basket and <br>Place it down <br>Upon my momma's bed <br>My heavy, heavy head <br><br>Dry mouthed in the hot white sand <br>On the way to the promised land <br>Did you cross that man did you cross that man <br>Did you pay that man you gotta pay that man <br><br>I got this feeling when you're not around <br>Tied up on the Native's ground <br>And when they bark at it don't make a sound <br>This whole generation don't make a <br><br>In every wolf <br>There's a dog looking for revenge <br>So take me to the desert <br>And chop off my heavy, heavy head <br><br>Oh and then unleash the basket and <br>Place it down <br>Upon my momma's bed <br>My heavy, heavy head]]></content><category term="The Orwells" label="The Orwells"/><category term="Heavy Head" label="Heavy Head"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Orwells/Hippie_Soldier/</id><title>The_Orwells - Hippie Soldier - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T18:34:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T18:34:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Orwells/Hippie_Soldier/" title="The_Orwells - Hippie Soldier - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Under the street light, under my skin <br>Sha la la la sha la la la <br>Shouldn't have done that thing that you did <br>Sha la la la sha la la la <br>Wipe up your tears and that bloody nose <br>Sha la la la sha la la la <br>Go buy a record, some discount clothes <br>Sha la la la sha la la <br><br>Just because you took the easy way out <br>Doesn't mean you know what you're talking about <br><br>Your daddy made it home from the war <br>Sha la la la sha la la la <br>Now you're knocking on his best friend's door <br>Sha la la la sha la la la <br>Tell me what to swallow, what to do <br>Sha la la la sha la la la <br>Get off'a your sofa, and turn off the news <br>Sha la la la sha la la <br><br>Just because you took the easy way out <br>Doesn't mean you know what you're talking about <br><br>Just because you took the easy way out <br>Doesn't mean you know what you're talking about]]></content><category term="The Orwells" label="The Orwells"/><category term="Hippie Soldier" label="Hippie Soldier"/></entry></feed>