<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:04:22+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/FYKE/Human/</id><title>FYKE - Human - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:06:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:06:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/FYKE/Human/" title="FYKE - Human - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We're all broken somehow <br>with seperate heartbeats beaten down <br>cuz consequences come around <br>yeah, I know that now <br>yeah, I know that now <br><br>if you can't take the weight <br>you're not alone <br><br>we are, we are the used and broken <br>we are the ones that lost our youth <br>too far from home so we're forgotten <br>but we're still invisible like you <br>invisible like you <br><br>you're not alone <br><br>we've been looking for the missing pieces <br>losing more and more along the way <br>but right now in this moment we're still breathing <br>and our luck could change <br>yeah, our luck could change]]></content><category term="FYKE" label="FYKE"/><category term="Human" label="Human"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Parade_Of_Lights/Touch/</id><title>Parade Of Lights - Touch - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:07:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:07:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Parade_Of_Lights/Touch/" title="Parade Of Lights - Touch - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1] <br>We've been going back in time <br>Underneath the future lights, lately <br>Give it up and come to life <br>Open up your heart tonight, baby <br><br>[Pre-Chorus] <br>You're in or out <br>Right here, right now <br>I won't let <br>You down <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I got one more touch <br>One more touch <br>To get a little bit closer now <br>One more touch <br>One more touch <br>To get a little bit closer now <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>Tell me what you feel inside <br>What if it's our only night, baby? <br>'Cause if and when you're out of sight <br>Doesn't mean your out of mind, lately <br>Uuh, yeah <br><br><br>[Pre-Chorus] <br>You're in or out <br>Right here, right now <br>I won't let <br>You down <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I got one more touch <br>One more touch <br>To get a little bit closer now <br>One more touch <br>One more touch <br>To get a little bit closer now <br><br>[Verse 3] <br>If you really want it that much <br>Stand up, my friend <br>Find love, again <br>Even if it's time for you, love <br>Stand up, my friend <br>Find love, again <br><br>[Bridge] <br>I can stay and wait for you <br>Every single night <br>We can wait a thousand years <br>Won't be long enough to fight it <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I got one more touch <br>One more touch <br>To get a little bit closer now <br>One more touch <br>One more touch <br>To get a little bit closer now <br><br>If you really want it that much <br>Stand up, my friend <br>Find love, again <br>Even if it's time for you, love <br>Stand up, my friend <br>Find love, again]]></content><category term="Parade Of Lights" label="Parade Of Lights"/><category term="Touch" label="Touch"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Prophets_Of_Rage/Unfuck_The_World/</id><title>Prophets Of Rage - Unfuck The World - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:12:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:12:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Prophets_Of_Rage/Unfuck_The_World/" title="Prophets Of Rage - Unfuck The World - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No Hatred <br>Fuck Racists <br>Blank Faces <br>Time's Changin <br>One Nation <br>Unification <br>The Vibration <br>Unfuck the World <br><br>No Hatred <br>Fuck Racists <br>Blank Faces <br>Time's Changin <br>One Nation <br>Unification <br>The Vibration <br>Unfuck the World <br><br>Poverty hit home like a war zone <br>Check America's pulse, heard a death tone <br>Division hittin like a bullet to precision <br>Kill the dream, kill the vision, now listen <br>What the fuck are you waiting for <br>Stand up and rise like the tide <br>And move your ass with the quickness <br>You may live on the hit list <br>No fear, bare witness <br>Where's ya heart at the heartless can't say <br>Bow down, just do what the man say <br>Buy them lie them deny it all day <br>In a box they locked in the dead lay <br>Bombs droppin on cities where kids play <br>Soldiers fallin in the name of freedom hey <br>Civilians buried in the rubble where dreams die <br>Politicians spew lie after fuckin lie <br><br>No Hatred <br>Fuck Racists <br>Blank Faces <br>Time's Changin <br>One Nation <br>Unification <br>The Vibration <br>Unfuck the World <br><br>No Hatred <br>Fuck Racists <br>Blank Faces <br>Time's Changin <br>One Nation <br>Unification <br>The Vibration <br>Unfuck the World <br><br>Hatred lies divided people <br>Gorgeous anger deeds of evil <br>After the fall whom the bell calls <br>Like we all dancing In a ballroom without balls <br>Talk walk look out listen <br>2020 see now <br>Currency is attention <br>Fascism too many cooks in the kitchen <br>Exploding phones <br>Killing drones on a mission <br>I'm elated to get y'all elevated <br>God remains God yeah and they hate it <br>On your knees people <br>Pledge allegiance to the evil <br>Everything changed yet nothing's changed <br>Bold is change, everything looking strange, yeah <br>Engineers got millennials livin in fear <br>Give a damn, evil can't stand yeah <br>When the people take a stand <br><br>No Hatred <br>Fuck Racists <br>Blank Faces <br>Time's Changin <br>One Nation <br>Unification <br>The Vibration <br>Unfuck the World <br><br>No Hatred <br>Fuck Racists <br>Blank Faces <br>Time's Changin <br>One Nation <br>Unification <br>The Vibration <br>Unfuck the World <br><br>Unfuck the world <br><br>Unfuck the world <br><br>Unfuck the world <br><br>Unfuck the world <br><br>I'm the straw that broke the camel's back <br>The gun in the car jack <br>The night stick that keeps crackin down <br>The resistance never backing down]]></content><category term="Prophets Of Rage" label="Prophets Of Rage"/><category term="Unfuck The World" label="Unfuck The World"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/우주히피/우리의_저녁/</id><title>우주히피 - 우리의 저녁 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:13:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:13:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9A%B0%EC%A3%BC%ED%9E%88%ED%94%BC/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EC%9D%98_%EC%A0%80%EB%85%81/" title="우주히피 - 우리의 저녁 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이리 와 내 옆에 나란히 누워봐 <br>같은 곳을 보니 네 맘을 알 듯해 <br>무슨 일 있는지 아무 말 하지 않아도 <br>모두 다 느껴져 가만히 있으면 <br>아무렇지 않게 웃어 보여도 <br>모든 게 쉽지 않았단 걸 <br>잘할 수 없다고 잘하고 싶다고 <br>그 맘을 내가 잘 알잖아 <br>내 맘이 이 밤이 <br>저 별이 너를 향해 빛나지 <br>어두운 밤 너의 눈이 <br>아름답게 빛나지 <br>고맙다 말하는 다정한 너의 <br>손을 살며시 잡고서 <br>네 꿈을 들을래 <br>힘겨운 하루도 우리 둘 <br>함께하는 게 내 꿈이었다고 <br>너에게 말할래 <br>원하는 모든 게 지금 옆에 있다고 <br>날 안아주는 너 때문에 <br>눈부신 모든 게 부럽지 않다고 <br>이런 내 맘을 너는 알까 <br>내 맘이 이 밤이 <br>저 별이 너를 향해 빛나지 <br>어두운 밤 너의 눈이 <br>아름답게 빛나지 <br>]]></content><category term="우주히피" label="우주히피"/><category term="우리의 저녁" label="우리의 저녁"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nickelback/For_The_River/</id><title>Nickelback - For The River - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:15:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:15:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nickelback/For_The_River/" title="Nickelback - For The River - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stuck in a cage. <br>Luck of the draw. <br>Always a way. <br>Gotta get out. <br>Lord i’m gonna find one. <br>Get me a key. <br>Pick me a lock. <br>Gotta be free. <br>Ready or not. <br>Gotta run gotta run. <br>Gotta run gotta run. <br>Gotta run gotta run. <br>Nowhere to hide because someone’s always going to find you. <br>Trying to breathe with everybody right behind you. <br>Scattering leaves to try and cover up my footprints. <br>Water ahead because i can hear it in the distance. <br>I’m running for the river cause the river is running high and there ain’t no going back. <br>They’ll never catch me. I’m runnin’ for the river. <br>You can ride you can fly. <br>You can tell em that you tried, but there ain’t no going back. <br>They’ll never catch me. <br>Tell em that you tried, but they’re never gonna catch me. <br>Let out the hounds. <br>Send out the guards. <br>Never be found. <br>Better than bars and damnit he’s a fast one. <br>Out of the trees, into the swamp. <br>Gotta be free so don’t ever stop. <br>Gotta run gotta run. <br>Gotta run gotta run. <br>God damnit he’s a fast one. <br>Nowhere to hide because someone’s always going to find you. <br>Trying to breathe with everybody right behind you. <br>Scattering leaves to try and cover up my footprints. <br>Water ahead because i can hear it in the distance. <br>I’m running for the river because the river is running high, <br>and there ain’t no going back. <br>They’ll never catch me. I’m runnin’ for the river. <br>You can ride, you can fly, <br>you can tell em that you tried but there ain’t no going back. <br>They’ll never catch me. <br>Tell em that you tried but they’re never gonna catch me.]]></content><category term="Nickelback" label="Nickelback"/><category term="For The River" label="For The River"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nickelback/After_The_Rain/</id><title>Nickelback - After The Rain - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:15:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:15:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nickelback/After_The_Rain/" title="Nickelback - After The Rain - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All your life, scramble and scurry <br>Take your time, rather than hurry <br>Never too late to write the best of your story <br>Remember to breathe or else you're gonna be sorry <br>Life's no race, it's a companion <br>Always face with reckless abandon <br>The ticket to life as my mother once told me <br>Stick with your pride and you're gonna be lonely (gonna be lonely) <br><br>Everybody says that life takes patience <br>But nobody wants to wait <br>Everybody says we need salvation <br>But nobody wants to be saved <br>The light in the tunnel is just another runaway train <br>The blue skies we wait on <br>Are gonna have to come after the rain <br><br>Spend your days happy and grateful <br>Avoid the taste of wanting and wasteful <br>Every good thing will come in moderation <br>Envy and greed will only lead to frustration <br>Choose your friends, carefree and kindly <br>Choose your words, careful and wisely <br>Always be there to lend a comforting shoulder <br>One will be there to share a day when you're older (a day when you're older} <br><br>Everybody says that life takes patience <br>But nobody wants to wait <br>Everybody says we need salvation <br>But nobody wants to be saved <br>The light in the tunnel is just another runaway train <br>The blue skies we wait on <br>Are gonna have to come after the rain <br><br>All mistakes, committed upon us <br>Always take a toll on the conscience <br>Every regret is a debt that you live with <br>Never forget to remember forgiveness <br><br>Everybody says that life takes patience <br>But nobody wants to wait <br>Everybody says we need salvation <br>But nobody wants to be saved <br>The light in the tunnel is just another runaway train <br>The blue skies we wait on <br>Are gonna have to come after the rain (ra-ai-ai-ain) <br><br>Gonna have to come after the rain (ra-ai-ai-ain) <br>Gonna have to come after the rain (ra-ai-ai-ain) <br>Gonna have to come after the rain (ra-ai-ai-ain) <br>Rain, yeah <br>Ra-ai-ai-ain <br>Gonna have to come after the rain]]></content><category term="Nickelback" label="Nickelback"/><category term="After The Rain" label="After The Rain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nickelback/Coin_For_The_Ferryman/</id><title>Nickelback - Coin For The Ferryman - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:15:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:15:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nickelback/Coin_For_The_Ferryman/" title="Nickelback - Coin For The Ferryman - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Flying down the highway like a bat out of hell <br>My buddy Bradley's in the middle <br>Darcy's lookin' out the window <br>We just got high and hopin' no one can tell <br>But with the icky of the sticky <br>It don't matter where the wind blows <br>Lighter in my hand and I've got nothing to burn <br>Except a little turpentine inside of those five paint cans <br>Get grandpa's shotgun and we'll all take turns <br>But don't you ever say a word <br>'Cause you know momma's gonna hate that <br>The dice that we've been rollin' <br>With our lives are better stolen <br>When you're walking through the fire for fun <br>Tidal wave in motion <br>You can't hide from the explosion <br>In 3, 2, 1 <br>We're smokin' dynamite <br>Too many fuses to light <br>(Got kingdom come, on the run) <br>Gonna steal, beg, and borrow <br>A thousand fahrenheit and we're about to ignite <br>So keep the throttle to the bottom <br>We may never see tomorrow <br>If tonight's our time to go, the one thing I know <br>We'll need a coin for the ferryman <br>Leave us a coin for the ferryman <br>Countin' every nickel, dime and five dollar bill <br>So we've been stealin' gasoline and laying low out on the backroads <br>The city lights are glowin' over the hill <br>And we can make it, but we take the chance of never coming back home <br>The dice that we've been rollin' <br>With our lives are better stolen <br>When you're walking through the fire for fun <br>Tidal wave in motion <br>You can't hide from the explosion <br>In 3, 2, 1 <br>We're smokin' dynamite <br>Too many fuses to light <br>(Got kingdom come, on the run) <br>Gonna steal, beg, and borrow <br>A thousand fahrenheit and we're about to ignite <br>So keep the throttle to the bottom <br>We may never see tomorrow <br>If tonight's our time to go, the one thing I know <br>We'll need a coin for the ferryman <br>Leave us a coin for the ferryman <br>One for the road and one for those in heaven <br>One for the lord and take it from the devil <br>Don't even try, 'cause you know you can't hide <br>Better run, better run, better run <br>We're smokin' dynamite <br>Too many fuses to light <br>(Got kingdom come, on the run) <br>Gonna steal, beg, and borrow <br>A thousand fahrenheit and we're about to ignite <br>So keep the throttle to the bottom <br>We may never see tomorrow <br>If tonight's our time to go, the one thing I know (the one thing I know) <br>We're smokin' dynamite <br>(Got kingdom come, on the run) <br>A thousand fahrenheit <br>So keep the throttle to the bottom <br>We may never see tomorrow <br>If tonight's our time to go, the one thing I know <br>We'll need a coin for the ferryman <br>Leave us a coin for the ferryman]]></content><category term="Nickelback" label="Nickelback"/><category term="Coin For The Ferryman" label="Coin For The Ferryman"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amine/Turf/</id><title>Amine - Turf - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:20:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:20:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amine/Turf/" title="Amine - Turf - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Walking on the pavement I check <br>my pride and my teeth on <br>The girl I grew up <br>with lives a couple houses down <br>The 8 Bus run the same <br>dogs howl when the train <br>Comes like my ex girl <br>and next girl <br>Used to rock the S curl <br>Wanted me a Nextel <br>but my momma copped a Razr <br>That's why I couldn't blame her <br>Flippin' through my past <br>like I used to flip the phone <br>They kickin' out the blacks <br>and all the houses getting clones <br>Friends used to do pills <br>and only eat at Du's Grill <br>The food was pretty good <br>but the times was better <br>These are the only days I missed <br>Like the first shawty I kissed <br>I used to have dreams now I dream <br>I look around and I see nothing <br>in my neighborhood <br>Not satisfied don't think <br>I'll ever wanna stay for good <br>Packed up my bags <br>told mom and dad I've gotta go go <br>And once I do they'll finally <br>see the inner me <br>Everybody wanna be a star <br>everybody want a nice car <br>Everybody wanna live great <br>have a good damn time <br>never trip with the law <br>The popo up in PO dirtier than VO <br>Bullies from the past act <br>like I'm they fucking hero <br>Livin' in LA for the weather <br>I FaceTime mom when I miss her <br>I got some homies that'll never <br>leave my hometown <br>When I pull up to the corner <br>it smell like Miley Cyrus <br>I told em' I don't smoke <br>they say boy you fuckin' wildin' <br>Innocent and young <br>Reckless and we dumb <br>Our heart is like our earth <br>and memories the sun <br>I look around and I see nothing <br>in my neighborhood <br>Not satisfied don't think <br>I'll ever wanna stay for good <br>Packed up my bags told mom <br>and dad I've gotta go go <br>And once I do they'll finally <br>see the inner me <br>Mentality the same from my folks <br>Momma wanna see me happy <br>she don't wanna see me broke <br>I said bread wine sauvignon <br>rastafar babylon <br>You can never die if I live it <br>like a prize hey <br>Who knows who I am <br>who knows who I are <br>Most people pretty sketch <br>like a night at Echo Park <br>That's why I just keep it cool <br>but my time is in a leisure <br>Everytime I'm home <br>I catch emotion like a seizure <br>I cut the first night <br>we fuck around <br>I put my finger in her <br>bootyhole 'cause you know you <br>gotta test the water with hoes <br>A-a-and then <br>I slip and slide through <br>the times in my youth <br>What's the age <br>Too young to worry <br>too old to dream <br>What's the age <br>Imagination to me <br>tragedy to some <br>What's the age I guess we'll <br>find out when we're older Touche <br>I look around and I see nothing <br>in my neighborhood <br>Not satisfied don't think <br>I'll ever wanna stay for good <br>Packed up my bags told mom <br>and dad I've gotta go go <br>And once I do they'll finally <br>see the inner me <br>Turf <br>]]></content><category term="Amine" label="Amine"/><category term="Turf" label="Turf"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joywave/Doubt/</id><title>Joywave - Doubt - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:20:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:20:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joywave/Doubt/" title="Joywave - Doubt - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tell me all the things I'm supposed to like <br>What you want to hear, what think is right <br>I'm not present, my thoughts are misaligned <br><br>Cause every time I close my eyes too tight <br>It's the Fall of 1929 <br>A panic, playing out in black and white <br><br>I fill myself with doubt, I feel like I sold out <br>I feel like I am down, I'm down without a doubt <br>I feel like I let down, everyone around <br>I feel like nothing counts, I'm down without a doubt <br>I've filled myself with doubt <br><br>Maybe I was made for normal life <br>Where I'm in at 9 and I'm out by 5 <br>And there's goals, I'd hit them every time <br><br>I could sell plans of different types <br>To wealthy men and their trophy wives <br>And go home, see the kids at night <br><br>I fill myself with doubt, I feel like I sold out <br>I feel like I am down, I'm down without a doubt <br>I feel like I let down, everyone around <br>I feel like nothing counts, I'm down without a doubt <br>I've filled myself with doubt <br><br>Never good enough, never satisfied with nothing <br>Never good enough, never satisfied with nothing <br>Never good enough, never satisfied with nothing <br>Never good enough, never satisfied with nothing <br>Never good enough, never satisfied with nothing <br>Never good enough, never satisfied with nothing <br><br>I fill myself with doubt, I feel like I sold out <br>I feel like I am down, I'm down without a doubt <br>I feel like I let down, everyone around <br>I feel like nothing counts, I'm down without a doubt <br>I've filled myself with doubt]]></content><category term="Joywave" label="Joywave"/><category term="Doubt" label="Doubt"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Audien/Hot_Water_Feat_Victoria_Zaro/</id><title>Audien - Hot Water (Feat. Victoria Zaro) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:20:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:20:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Audien/Hot_Water_Feat_Victoria_Zaro/" title="Audien - Hot Water (Feat. Victoria Zaro) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I deserve it <br>I know I hurt you with the truth <br>I was certain <br>No matter what we make it through <br>I don't mind perfect <br>If I really needed <br><br>Would you le-le-le-le-let me drown <br>Reach your hand and pull me out <br>Would you le-le-le-le-let me drown <br>Reach your hand and pull me out <br><br>I've been drowning in hot water <br>Yeah, I know I let you down <br>And I'll find a way to say I'm sorry <br>But my time is running out <br>But would you le-le-le-le-let me drown <br>Reach your hand and pull me out <br>Would you le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le <br>(I know perfect) <br><br>Le-le-let me drown <br>Reach your hand <br>Would you le-le-le-let me drown <br>(I'm sorry) <br>Le-le-let me drown <br>Reach your hand <br>Would you le-le-le-let me drown <br>(I'm sorry) <br>Le-le-let me drown <br>Reach your hand <br>Would you le-le-le-let me drown <br>(I'm sorry) <br>Le-le-let me drown <br>Reach your hand <br>Would you le-le-le-let me drown <br><br>If you were on your last breath <br>And there was no one else around <br>Despite what I said <br>I swear that I would help you out <br>Like a siren <br>I hear that old familiar sound <br><br>I've been drowning in hot water <br>Yeah, I know I let you down <br>And I'll find a way to say I'm sorry <br>But my time is running out <br><br>Would you le-le-let me drown <br>Reach your hand <br>Would you le-le-le-let me drown <br>(Hot water) <br>Le-le-let me drown <br>Reach your hand <br>Would you le-le-le-let me drown <br><br>Heaven knows you wanna let go <br>Heaven knows we're caught in echoes <br>And I don't know if you will let go of me <br>Like I let go of you <br>And heaven knows that I've got regrets <br>Heaven knows I meant what I said <br>And I don't know if you will let go <br><br>I've been drowning in hot water <br>Yeah, I know I let you down <br>And I'll find a way to say I'm sorry <br>But my time is running out <br>But would you le-le-le-le-let me drown <br>Reach your hand and pull me out <br>Would you le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le <br>(I know perfect) <br><br>Le-le-let me drown <br>Reach your hand <br>Would you le-le-le-let me drown <br>(I'm sorry) <br>Le-le-let me drown <br>Reach your hand <br>Would you le-le-le-let me <br>(Hot water) <br>Le-le-let me drown <br>Reach your hand <br>Would you le-le-le-let me drown <br>(I'm sorry) <br>Le-le-let me drown <br>Reach your hand <br>Would you le-le-le-let me, let me drown]]></content><category term="Audien" label="Audien"/><category term="Hot Water (Feat. Victoria Zaro)" label="Hot Water (Feat. Victoria Zaro)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전유빈/매력없는_여자/</id><title>전유빈 - 매력없는 여자 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:21:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:21:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%9C%A0%EB%B9%88/%EB%A7%A4%EB%A0%A5%EC%97%86%EB%8A%94_%EC%97%AC%EC%9E%90/" title="전유빈 - 매력없는 여자 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 자꾸만 눈을 맞추나요 <br>그대 그 미소는 내게만 주나요 <br>혹시나 하는 내게 이러지마요 <br>나도 날 잘 알아 매력없는 여자 <br>그래 그 일 일어날 수 없는거야 <br>겁이나 자꾸 내게 이러지 마요 <br>여유롭게 날 대하는 그대는 <br>어지럽게 날 녹여 빙빙 <br>화려한 그대가 날 <br>더 자신없게 만들어요 <br>또 착각하지마 또 흔들리지만 <br>너도 알잖아 못난이 매력없는 여자 <br>반짝 빛나는 저 무지개와는 <br>저 멀리 떨어진 <br>먹구름에 피어나는 꽃 <br>한동안 쉽게도 불려지던 <br>그 가사는 내 얘기가 아니야 <br>날 쳐다보지마 나도 날 잘 알아 <br>고개를 돌리면 <br>아주 가까이에 다가온 <br>너에 뺨에 이대로 멈춰서 <br>입을 맞추고 싶어 <br>그래도 될까 <br>나도 날 잘 모르겠어 <br>니가 날 그렇게 <br>다른 내가 되게 만들어서 <br>겁이나 자꾸 내게 이러지 마요 <br>또 착각하지마 또 흔들리지만 <br>너도 알잖아 못난이 매력없는 여자 <br>반짝 빛나는 저 무지개와는 <br>저 멀리 떨어진 <br>먹구름에 피어나는 꽃 <br>한동안 쉽게도 불려지던 <br>그 가사는 내 얘기가 아니야 <br>날 쳐다보지마 나도 날 잘 알아 <br>아닐까 맞을까 다시 한 번 <br>그댄 확실한 눈빛으로 <br>그런 어려운 이야긴 잘 모르겠는걸요 <br>위험해 위험해요 <br>]]></content><category term="전유빈" label="전유빈"/><category term="매력없는 여자" label="매력없는 여자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Terror_Jr/Terrible/</id><title>Terror Jr - Terrible - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:21:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:21:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Terror_Jr/Terrible/" title="Terror Jr - Terrible - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Squeeze my ass like a teddy bear <br>Suck my tongue and make it disappear <br>Dip my lonely days in honey glaze <br>Maple syrup in our lemonade <br><br>Drinkin' wine at the house, thinkin' 'bout rehab <br>Call you up, put some wine in my mouth <br>Call you up, call you up, ooh, ooh <br><br>I know a girl, she's just your type <br>She's educated, her future is bright <br>I went to high school and failed one class twice <br>But it's my time, you're not going, you're living <br><br>I'm so terrible, come pick me off the floor <br>Unrepairable, can't find an open door <br>I've never found somebody who could want me at my low <br>Now I'll never let you go cause you love me when I'm terrible <br>I'm so terrible, come pick me off the floor <br>Unrepairable, can't find an open door <br>I've never found somebody who could want me at my low <br>Now I'll never let you go cause you love me when I'm terrible <br><br>I don't think we're done <br>I feel we've just begun runnin' from the sun <br>I'm a sweet bitch, but if you're on my worst side <br>You can take a hearse ride <br>I can drink the cyanide like it's red wine <br><br>I know a girl, she's just your type <br>She's educated, her future is bright <br>I went to high school and failed one class twice <br>But it's my time, you're not going, you're living <br><br>I'm so terrible, come pick me off the floor <br>Unrepairable, can't find an open door <br>I've never found somebody who could want me at my low <br>Now I'll never let you go cause you love me when I'm terrible <br>I'm so terrible, come pick me off the floor <br>Unrepairable, can't find an open door <br>I've never found somebody who could want me at my low <br>Now I'll never let you go cause you love me when I'm terrible <br><br>I don't think we're done]]></content><category term="Terror Jr" label="Terror Jr"/><category term="Terrible" label="Terrible"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fear_and_Loathing_in_Las_Vegas/Something_to_Gain_After_the_Pain/</id><title>Fear, and Loathing in Las Vegas - Something to Gain After the Pain - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:22:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:22:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fear_and_Loathing_in_Las_Vegas/Something_to_Gain_After_the_Pain/" title="Fear, and Loathing in Las Vegas - Something to Gain After the Pain - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let's get fired up tonight <br>you need more than 6th sense <br>At least use thirteen to feel it <br><br>Wake up <br>Right now <br>and burn it <br>stand up <br>Your heart is dancing <br>dance now <br>more than yesterday <br>throw that stone with <br>full speed <br><br>It isn't easy <br>To link bonds with people <br>To polish definite skills To keep <br>putting yourself into something For the things you want <br><br>It is something that people can not achieve easily yeah <br>that is why it's valuable <br>it's important <br><br>To achieve something important <br>is like building something little by little <br>The strength to not lose against yourself (yourself) <br>and the passion to not lose against others is needed <br><br>It's something that people can't achieve easily, <br>that is why (that is why) it's worth it <br><br>It ain't something you can get in a day or two so <br>skills (that) shakes people's hearts <br>It ain't something you can get in just a day or two so <br>(The) trustable people that are always <br>with you The strong will of running towards <br>your target Do all you can do ah <br><br>hybrid car <br>Like a hybrid car of heart and body, this is how we function <br>It's no doubt for people <br>who try to take the easy way out to be left behind <br>The course that awaits him is a sheer cliff <br>thats what I think, how about you <br><br>don't wanna end up like him <br><br>we are here stand up and let's go ahed <br>doesn't have to be cool, It can look bad <br>we are here stand up and let's go ahed <br>Cuz there is something to gain after the pains <br><br>The sweat you can feel <br>The troubled times <br>you spent will mean something to you oh <br>(The) important thing will be seen before what you crave for <br><br>The important things <br>Aren't easy to gain <br>but your efforts but your efforts will bring them to you <br>(The) irreplaceable things <br>gain as much as you can <br>what will be assets of your life <br><br>The troubled times will have it's meaning (it's meaning) <br>What's important comes before what you crave <br><br>Achieve as much <br>as you can (as you can) <br>what will be the assets of your life]]></content><category term="Fear, and Loathing in Las Vegas" label="Fear, and Loathing in Las Vegas"/><category term="Something to Gain After the Pain" label="Something to Gain After the Pain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fear_and_Loathing_in_Las_Vegas/SHINE/</id><title>Fear, and Loathing in Las Vegas - SHINE - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:22:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:22:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fear_and_Loathing_in_Las_Vegas/SHINE/" title="Fear, and Loathing in Las Vegas - SHINE - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come on Ladies and gentle men <br>Yes thats right <br>Catch me in Japan <br>This is what people call us <br>Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas <br>Yes Sir <br>lets go for it and follow me <br>Don't dirty your clothes <br>with your drivel <br>Do you feel the worth of <br>your existence <br>A question hits your mind <br>on a depressed night <br>Have you ever thought <br>oh if there are things <br>that only you can do <br>you are the only one <br>what is what you can do <br>what thoughts you got now to do it <br>don't wrap yourself <br>inside a blanket you know <br>what is what you can do <br>what thoughts you got now to do it <br>It ain't something you can <br>achieve without trying <br>hi hi hi yeah <br>without knowing without knowing <br>that you are drowning <br>down into the mud <br>Though you diss the ones <br>that have managed to pull it off <br>hey hey <br>you can't admit the fact <br>of yourself fact of yourself <br>being ah so cliche <br>stay in the crowd stay in the crowd <br>yo come on now with your strong will <br>Find yourself your only self <br>with your silent heart <br>You are always the only you <br>that will never change as always <br>wo-o-o-o-o wo-o-o-o-o <br>There sure are things only you can do <br>Cuz you are the only one <br>person <br>wo-o-o-o-o wo-o-o-o-o <br>The ones that don't even know left <br>right or wrong <br>will shine in life <br>Go find the meaning of yourself <br>Do you know your feelings <br>Your hearts will be harder <br>to see as you keep living <br>At least let yourself believe <br>yourself believing that <br>you are the masterpiece <br>God has made <br>Alright <br>You wanna win this Ha <br>like to be praised ha <br>really like being praised let's go <br>You are the best players <br>come on let's get it going on igya <br>Your hearts will be harder <br>to see as you living <br>At least let yourself <br>believe yourself <br>wo-o-o-o-o wo-o-o-o-o <br>To live as yourself <br>It's actually like grabbing <br>like grabbing the sky <br>Bring it down to reality now <br>wo-o-o-o-o wo-o-o-o-o <br>There are no insane circuits <br>So that you can move <br>forward in your way ah <br>Ready <br>Run Dance Go <br>Catch yourself meaning to your life <br>Think tell show <br>Cuz there are things only you can <br>The light will shine as you think <br>your best is further <br>wo-o-o wo-o-yeah <br>]]></content><category term="Fear, and Loathing in Las Vegas" label="Fear, and Loathing in Las Vegas"/><category term="SHINE" label="SHINE"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sam_Bruno/Hello_Hater/</id><title>Sam Bruno - Hello Hater - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:23:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:23:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sam_Bruno/Hello_Hater/" title="Sam Bruno - Hello Hater - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1] <br>Hello <br>Smile, you got to let go <br>No point in being so blue <br>So tell your squad to come through <br>You'll know they happy for you <br>Who cares what jealous mouths say? <br>They all, they all the same way <br>They never, never shut up <br>They all fake us out anyway <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Everybody rolling like the papers <br>Two fingers giving love to all the haters <br>Saying "See you later, alligators" <br>Now rise and grind, it's time to be a gangster <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>Hello <br>Cheers to everyone who ever did you wrong <br>To the losers who lost us and the lucky bastards who took us on <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Everybody rolling like the papers <br>Two fingers giving love to all the haters <br>Saying "See you later, alligators" <br>Now rise and grind, it's time to be a gangster <br><br>[Bridge] <br>I don't wanna play with them haters <br>Gotta tell 'em all see you later <br>I don't wanna play with them haters <br>Gotta turn them down like a fader]]></content><category term="Sam Bruno" label="Sam Bruno"/><category term="Hello Hater" label="Hello Hater"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Terror_Jr/Death_Wish/</id><title>Terror Jr - Death Wish - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:23:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:23:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Terror_Jr/Death_Wish/" title="Terror Jr - Death Wish - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You change me like hair dye <br>Then you leave me like a hair tie <br>I'm pullin' up no jump shot <br>I'm in your mouth like a cumshot <br><br>So swallow that cigarette and follow my silhouette <br>And maybe you can be my last kiss <br>Fuck a Romeo but tonight you can be my Juliet <br>You can be my Juliet you can be my Juliet <br>You can be my Juliet you can be my Juliet <br><br>But baby I can be your death wish <br>Are you ready to die? <br><br>You change me like hair dye <br>Then you leave me like a hair tie <br>I'm Jim Jones in your Kool-Aid <br>We ball together like 2K <br><br>So swallow that cigarette and follow my silhouette <br>And maybe you can be my last kiss <br>Fuck a Romeo but tonight you can be my Juliet <br>You can be my Juliet you can be my Juliet <br>You can be my Juliet you can be my Juliet <br><br>But baby I can be your death wish <br>Baby I can be your death wish <br>Are you ready to die? <br><br>I feel this cocaine is comin' down <br>I probably should stop doin' that shit <br>It really fucks my nose up <br>You're like my leprechaun prostitute <br>I keep usin' and usin' you <br>And I'm runnin' out of fairy dust <br>So swallow that cigarette and follow my silhouette <br>And maybe you can be my last kiss <br>Fuck a Romeo but tonight you can be my Juliet <br><br>Are you ready to die? <br>Baby I can be your <br>Are you ready to die?]]></content><category term="Terror Jr" label="Terror Jr"/><category term="Death Wish" label="Death Wish"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Portugal_The_Man/Live_In_The_Moment/</id><title>Portugal. The Man - Live In The Moment - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:24:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:24:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Portugal_The_Man/Live_In_The_Moment/" title="Portugal. The Man - Live In The Moment - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My home <br>Is a girl with eyes like wishing wells <br>I'm not alone <br>But I'm still lone, lonely <br>When I was young <br>Always go below the midnight sun <br>Those days are done <br>But I'm still glowing <br><br>Ooh la la la la la <br>Let's live in the moment <br>Come back Sunday morning <br>A lie, oh well <br>When you're gone <br>Goodbye, so long, farewell <br><br>Ooh la la la la la <br>Let's live in the moment <br>Come back Sunday morning <br>With that soul to sell <br>When you're gone <br>Goodbye, so long, farewell <br><br>My home <br>Is a girl who can't wait for time to tell <br>God only knows <br>We don't need history <br>When your family <br>Swinging from the branches of a tree <br>God only knows <br>We don't need ghost stories <br><br>Ooh la la la la la <br>Let's live in the moment <br>Come back Sunday morning <br>A lie, oh well <br>When you're gone <br>Goodbye, so long, farewell <br><br>Ooh la la la la la <br>Let's live in the moment <br>Come back Sunday morning <br>With that soul to sell <br>When you're gone <br>Goodbye, so long, farewell <br><br>Ooh I can't believe it <br>Nothing's gonna comfort me now <br><br>Ooh I can't believe it <br>Nothing's gonna comfort me now <br><br>Ooh la la la la la <br>Let's live in the moment <br>Come back Sunday morning <br>A lie, oh well <br>When you're gone <br>Goodbye, so long, farewell <br>Ooh la la la la la <br>Let's live in the moment <br>Come back Sunday morning <br>With that soul to sell <br>When you're gone <br>Goodbye, so long, farewell <br><br>Oh my god I can’t believe my eyes <br>Wake up everybody you know <br>Come and watch the garden grow <br>I’ll see you when you get there <br><br>Oh my god I can’t believe my eyes <br>Wake up everybody you know <br>Come and watch the garden grow <br>I’ll see you when you get there <br>I’ll see you when you get there <br>I’ll see you when you get there]]></content><category term="Portugal. The Man" label="Portugal. The Man"/><category term="Live In The Moment" label="Live In The Moment"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/Sleep/</id><title>Royal Blood - Sleep - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:24:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:24:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/Sleep/" title="Royal Blood - Sleep - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't wanna sleep <br>Cuz I've had enough <br>Of the same ugly dream <br>I just can't switch it off <br><br>Now I don't wanna know <br>Cuz I'm sick of the sound <br>Misery's on repeat <br>Now you're hanging around <br><br>But I need some medication <br>Tell me you've got what I need <br>I know you've got the cure antidote <br>Hidden up your sleeve <br><br>I just can't help myself thinking <br>You're with someone else <br>Sick to the bone <br>I don't wanna sleep <br>I've read the warning sign <br>You said I'll be alright <br>Left on my own I don't wanna sleep <br><br>I've waited so long <br>Forever counting down <br>Thinking of all the ways <br>I could get you back around <br><br>But I need some medication <br>Tell me you've got what I need <br>I know you've got the cure antidote <br>Hidden up your sleeve <br><br>I just can't help myself <br>Thinking you're with someone else <br>Sick to the bone <br>I don't wanna sleep <br>I've read the warning sign <br>You said I'll be alright <br>Left on my own I don't wanna sleep <br><br>I don't wanna sleep <br>I don't wanna sleep <br>I can't switch it off <br>Think I've had enough <br>I can't switch it off <br>I think I've had enough <br><br>I just can't help myself <br>Thinking you're with someone else <br>Sick to the bone <br>I don't wanna sleep <br>I've read the warning sign <br>You said I'll be alright <br>Left on my own I don't wanna sleep <br><br>I don't wanna sleep <br>Cuz I've had enough <br>Of the same ugly dream <br>I just can't switch it off]]></content><category term="Royal Blood" label="Royal Blood"/><category term="Sleep" label="Sleep"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/Hole_In_Your_Heart/</id><title>Royal Blood - Hole In Your Heart - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:24:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:24:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/Hole_In_Your_Heart/" title="Royal Blood - Hole In Your Heart - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Every time I think about it <br>I shiver like I've never shook <br>And all the while we talk about it <br>It never feels exactly like it should <br><br>Even if we turned it around <br>It would only do no good <br><br>So baby don't fake it <br>When you already know <br>You can't shake it <br>And it's starting to show <br>I can't fill that hole in your heart <br>Like I could at the start <br><br>I felt a fire burning long before <br>I even saw the smoke <br>A tragedy just looming over the horizon <br>Still there's a part of me that hopes <br><br>That we could just turn it around <br>But it would only do no good <br>Just remember there's nobody else <br>That could love you like I could <br><br>So baby don't fake it <br>When you already know <br>You can't shake it <br>And it's starting to show <br>I can't fill that hole in your heart <br>Like I could at the start <br><br>Yeah baby don't fake it <br>When you already know <br>You can't shake it <br>And it's starting to show <br>I can't fill that hole in your heart <br>Like I could at the start <br><br>So baby don't fake it <br>When you already know <br>You can't shake it <br>And it's starting to show <br>I can't fill that hole in your heart <br>Like I could at the start <br>I can't fill that hole in your heart <br>Like I could at the start]]></content><category term="Royal Blood" label="Royal Blood"/><category term="Hole In Your Heart" label="Hole In Your Heart"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/Dont_Tell/</id><title>Royal Blood - Don`t Tell - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:25:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:25:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/Dont_Tell/" title="Royal Blood - Don`t Tell - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Everybody saw you get your coat <br>And everybody heard your bad excuse for leaving <br>Say "I'm going out for a smoke" <br>No one has to know about our little secret <br>Meet you there <br>In the dark <br>I won't say anything <br>If you don't <br><br>So don't tell <br>I swear I won't tell on you <br>On you <br>Don't tell <br>I swear I won't tell <br><br>Used to have a heart of gold <br>Now I'm staying up at night <br>Your dirty little dreamer <br>Always ready to reload <br>At your command <br>Wish I could keep you <br>Syncronised on demand <br>As we fantasise what they can't know <br><br>Oh don't tell <br>I swear I won't tell on you <br>On you <br>Don't tell <br>I swear I won't tell <br><br>I know it's hard to bear <br>Hiding everywhere <br>Trying to forget <br>Keeping it on the down-low <br>I wish we'd skip a beat <br>Give up this hide and seek <br>Think I just changed my mind <br>Let's just let everybody know <br><br>Don't tell <br>I swear I won't tell on you <br>On you <br>Don't tell <br>I swear I won't tell on you <br>On you <br>Don't tell <br>I swear I won't tell]]></content><category term="Royal Blood" label="Royal Blood"/><category term="Don`t Tell" label="Don`t Tell"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/Where_Are_You_Now_/</id><title>Royal Blood - Where Are You Now? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:25:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:25:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/Where_Are_You_Now_/" title="Royal Blood - Where Are You Now? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was an honest boy, yeah <br>I was brought up right <br>Fell for an honest girl, yeah <br>We were so tight <br>If only luck was always on our side <br><br>You gave in all your secrets <br>Didn't give in mine <br>Nowhere left to run, no <br>Way left to shine <br>If only love was on your side <br>Now it's just a stranger passing by <br><br>You saw me driving my car <br>Like a dog running wild <br>Oh my hands were shaking <br>Singing, "where are you now?" <br>I wish I could go back somehow <br>Just tell me baby, where are you now? <br>Where are you now? <br><br>I've tasted every potion <br>They don't taste like you <br>You're a teardrop in an ocean <br>I'm still drinking through <br>And I still wonder where you are <br>And who you're talking to <br>When I think about it I get blue <br><br>Where are you now? <br>Where are you now? <br>Yeah!]]></content><category term="Royal Blood" label="Royal Blood"/><category term="Where Are You Now?" label="Where Are You Now?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/Look_Like_You_Know/</id><title>Royal Blood - Look Like You Know - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:25:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:25:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/Look_Like_You_Know/" title="Royal Blood - Look Like You Know - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Say my prayers every night <br>But no one's there to make it right <br>Holding on, nothing's changed <br>Same old love just rearranged <br><br>No, it's not better <br>No, it's not better <br>No, it's not better no <br>No, it's not better <br>No, it's not better <br>No, it's not better, so <br><br>Just look like you know <br>Look like you know something I should <br>I think I should go <br>I really feel like you want me to <br>Don't say that you want me <br>Don't pray the wish you can't make come true <br>Can I be replaced? <br>Cause that look on your face <br>Says baby I never knew <br><br>Happiness on a drip <br>To total bliss running down the drain <br>Losing count of the days <br>Now every kiss just feels the same <br><br>No, it's not better <br>No, it's not better <br>No, it's not better no <br>No, it's not better <br>No, it's not better <br>No, it's not better, so <br><br>Just look like you know <br>Look like you know something I should <br>I think I should go <br>I really feel like you want me to <br>Don't say that you want me <br>Don't pray the wish you can't make come true <br>Can I be replaced? <br>Cause that look on your face <br>Says baby I never knew <br><br>Just look like you know <br>Look like you know something I should <br>I think I should go <br>I really feel like you want me to <br>Don't say that you want me <br>Don't pray the wish you can't make come true <br>Can I be replaced? <br>Cause that look on your face <br>Says baby I never knew]]></content><category term="Royal Blood" label="Royal Blood"/><category term="Look Like You Know" label="Look Like You Know"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fleet_Foxes/Fools_Errand/</id><title>Fleet Foxes - Fool`s Errand - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:25:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:25:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fleet_Foxes/Fools_Errand/" title="Fleet Foxes - Fool`s Errand - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I knew you fine, sight dream of mine <br>But I know my eyes, they've often lied <br>And I move like blood, like fire and flood <br>Despite you <br><br>Blind love couldn't win <br>As the facts all came in <br>But I know I'll again chase after wind <br>What have I got if not a thought? <br><br>I knew, oh I knew <br>I knew <br><br>It was a fool's errand <br>Waiting for a sign <br>But I can't leave until the sight comes to mind <br>A fool's errand <br><br>Life will repeat, vision I see <br>The mouth and the teeth <br>And that's fine with me <br>What have I got if not a thought? <br><br>I knew, oh I knew <br>I knew <br><br>It was a fool's errand <br>Waiting for a sign <br>But I can't leave until the sign comes to mind <br>A fool's errand <br><br>But I can make it through <br>I was thin and I saw all life in you <br>Fool's errand]]></content><category term="Fleet Foxes" label="Fleet Foxes"/><category term="Fool`s Errand" label="Fool`s Errand"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/Shes_Creeping/</id><title>Royal Blood - She`s Creeping - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:25:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:25:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/Shes_Creeping/" title="Royal Blood - She`s Creeping - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She's creeping <br>Into my bloodstream <br>Then crawling <br>Out dead as a battery <br>Then it sinks in <br>I'm not where I'm supposed to be <br>It's so boring <br>Being what you want me to be <br><br>Cause I've stopped listening <br>I'm just waiting for an answer to a question that I already know <br>I'll let you down <br>Words are so cheap <br>But lately I've been feeling like I'm always living in your shadow <br>When you're not around <br><br>So don't miss what <br>Makes you so miserable <br>Did my message send? <br>God knows I'll send it again <br><br>Cause I've stopped listening <br>I'm just waiting for an answer to a question that I already know <br>I'll let you down <br>Words are so cheap <br>But lately I've been feeling like I'm always living in your shadow <br>When you're not around <br>You're not around <br><br>Cause I've stopped listening <br>I'm just waiting for an answer to a question that I already know <br>I'll let you down <br>Words are so cheap <br>But lately I've been feeling like I'm always living in your shadow <br>When you're not around <br><br>Yeah she's creeping <br>Into my bloodstream <br>Yeah she's creeping <br>Into my bloodstream <br>She's creeping <br>Now you're not around <br>You're not around]]></content><category term="Royal Blood" label="Royal Blood"/><category term="She`s Creeping" label="She`s Creeping"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/I_Only_Lie_When_I_Love_You/</id><title>Royal Blood - I Only Lie When I Love You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:25:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:25:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/I_Only_Lie_When_I_Love_You/" title="Royal Blood - I Only Lie When I Love You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I only lie when I love you <br>I only crawl when I hit the ground <br>You only cry when I love you <br>I only lie when I make a sound <br>Go ahead muck about <br>I got my conscience twisted <br>Pull your hair make me shout <br>It's just that you insisted <br>I was good for nothing <br>Like you were onto something <br>I only lie when I love you <br>I only crawl when I hit the ground <br>You only cry when I love you <br>I only lie when I make a sound <br>I only lie when I <br>I only lie when I <br>I only lie when I <br>I only lie when I <br>I only lie when I love you <br>I only crawl when I hit the ground <br>You only cry when I love you <br>I only lie when I make a sound <br>Go ahead pull the plug <br>Broken finger sticky trigger <br>Now I can't get it off my chest <br>And now I'm wishing <br>you were someone else <br>You know I'm up to something <br>Diagnosed no disease <br>Got a suspicion <br>but you just can't find it <br>up your sleeve <br>And now I beg the truth be told <br>from someone else <br>All of that fuss for nothing <br>I only lie when I love you <br>I only crawl when I hit the ground <br>You only cry when I love you <br>I only lie when I make a sound <br>I only lie when I <br>I only lie when I <br>I only lie when I <br>I only lie when I <br>I only lie when I love you <br>I only crawl when I hit the ground <br>You only cry when I love you <br>I only lie when I make a sound <br>]]></content><category term="Royal Blood" label="Royal Blood"/><category term="I Only Lie When I Love You" label="I Only Lie When I Love You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/How_Did_We_Get_So_Dark_/</id><title>Royal Blood - How Did We Get So Dark? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:25:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:25:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Royal_Blood/How_Did_We_Get_So_Dark_/" title="Royal Blood - How Did We Get So Dark? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I saw it coming <br>Like the shadow on the wall <br>You started running <br>When everything turned cold <br>How did I <br>Become a lookalike <br>Of someone you used to love? <br>Someone you used to love <br><br>So dark <br>How did something so sweet tear us apart? <br>Oh <br>On a sinking ship with a heavy heart <br>Oh oh <br>How did we get so dark? <br><br>Nobody warned you <br>The tables would turn <br>I could have told you <br>Everything you've learnt <br>Would burn to dust <br>Now there's no one you can trust <br>Just someone you used to love <br>Someone you used to love <br><br>So dark <br>How did something so sweet tear us apart? <br>Oh <br>On a sinking ship with a heavy heart <br>Oh oh <br>How did we get so dark? <br><br>How'd we get so dark? [x17]]]></content><category term="Royal Blood" label="Royal Blood"/><category term="How Did We Get So Dark?" label="How Did We Get So Dark?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jane_Zhang/Dust_My_Shoulders_Off_Steve_Aoki_Remix/</id><title>Jane Zhang - Dust My Shoulders Off (Steve Aoki Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:28:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:28:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jane_Zhang/Dust_My_Shoulders_Off_Steve_Aoki_Remix/" title="Jane Zhang - Dust My Shoulders Off (Steve Aoki Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Just had a bad day <br>Had car trouble on the highway <br>My stupid boss don't like me <br>Spilled hot coffee on my blue jeans <br>I'm low on money and ain't shit funny <br>But it's still sunny outside <br>So I keep smiling, I won't start wilin' <br>I just keep living my life <br><br>Can't keep me down, me down <br>(It's only temporary) <br>Can't make me frown, me frown <br>(So I ain't even worried) <br>Cause the world keeps spinnin' <br>Life goes on and on <br>I won't cry for long <br>(Won't cry for long long long) <br><br>I dust my shoulders off <br>I don't worry 'bout nothing, just dust it off <br>I dust my shoulders off <br>I don't worry 'bout nothing, just dust it off <br><br>You can't find your girlfriend <br>Your boyfriend left you <br>But the party's still going on <br>Everybody here is saying "Dust your shoulders off" <br>See him kissing in the kitchen by the bathroom <br>But you don't let it phase you <br>Go and hit the bar up, go and key his car up <br>And tell him that it's karma <br><br>Can't keep me down, me down <br>(It's only temporary) <br>Can't make me frown, me frown <br>(So I ain't even worried) <br><br>Cause the world keeps spinnin' <br>Life goes on and on <br>I won't cry for long <br>(Won't cry for long long long) <br><br>I dust my shoulders off <br>I don't worry 'bout nothing, just dust it off <br>I dust my shoulders off <br>I don't worry 'bout nothing, just dust it off]]></content><category term="Jane Zhang" label="Jane Zhang"/><category term="Dust My Shoulders Off (Steve Aoki Remix)" label="Dust My Shoulders Off (Steve Aoki Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Drummer_Lino_Park/Sweet_Memories_Feat_이상욱/</id><title>Drummer Lino Park - Sweet Memories (Feat. 이상욱) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:29:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:29:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Drummer_Lino_Park/Sweet_Memories_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%81%EC%9A%B1/" title="Drummer Lino Park - Sweet Memories (Feat. 이상욱) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[달콤한 멜로디 <br>퍼커션 리듬소리 <br>내맘 녹이는걸 <br>그 어느때보다 <br>날 떠오르게 해 <br>워우워 <br>손 잡은 듯 다시 기억이 날것같아 <br>그때의 기분과 그 감정들 <br>나를 다시 미소짓게 해 <br>Yeah <br>아련한 기억에 <br>두근대던 그 소리 <br>내맘 녹이는걸 <br>그 어느때보다 <br>날 안아주던 널 <br>기억해 <br>잊혀진 듯 아주조금 알것만 같아 <br>그때의 기분과 그 감정들 <br>나를 다시 미소짓게 해 <br>Yeah <br>난 우후후우후후 <br>마음이 어려울때 <br>그때를 생각해 Yeah <br>그 행복했던 날 <br>Music makes me Makes me <br>feel so good <br>달콤한 멜로디 <br>퍼커션 리듬소리 <br>내맘 녹이는걸 <br>그 어느때보다 <br>날 떠오르게 해 <br>이렇게 <br>잊혀진 듯 아주 조금 알것만 같아 <br>Hey 이제 일어나 다 털어놔 <br>Dosen’t matter it is <br>just a melody <br>Yeah <br>]]></content><category term="Drummer Lino Park" label="Drummer Lino Park"/><category term="Sweet Memories (Feat. 이상욱)" label="Sweet Memories (Feat. 이상욱)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/여전히_여전해_Inst/</id><title>6 to 8 - 여전히 여전해 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:29:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:29:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/%EC%97%AC%EC%A0%84%ED%9E%88_%EC%97%AC%EC%A0%84%ED%95%B4_Inst/" title="6 to 8 - 여전히 여전해 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여전히 여전해 잠이 부족할 만큼 <br>일 속에 묻혀 살곤 해 <br>잠시 끊었던 운동도 미뤘던 여행도 <br>다시 또 시작했어 <br>여전히 여전해 친구들의 걱정에 <br>여자도 소개받곤 해 <br>모두 너 같진 않지만 괜찮은 여자와 <br>잘 해보기도 했어 <br>다들 그러잖아 괜찮아지더라 <br>잘 지내는 내가 어색해지더라 <br>이래도 돼 벌써 잊어도 되니 <br>서운하겠지만 <br>너무 잘 지내서 미안해 정말 <br>여전히 여전해 니가 싫어했었던 <br>옷들을 꺼내 입곤 해 <br>듣기 싫던 니 잔소리 화내던 얼굴이 <br>이젠 그립지 않아 <br>다들 그러잖아 괜찮아지더라 <br>잘 지내는 내가 어색해지더라 <br>이래도 돼 벌써 잊어도 되니 <br>서운하겠지만 <br>너무 잘 지내서 미안해 정말 <br>너도 누군가를 만나고 있겠지 <br>나보다 더 내가 준 것보다 <br>더 많은 걸 줄 사람 <br>사랑하고 있겠지 <br>그리움이 지나 오늘이 오더라 <br>많이 울던 내가 창피해지더라 <br>멀쩡해도 이러다 니가 가끔 <br>따끔대긴 해도 <br>그냥 그래 이젠 걱정하지 마 <br>]]></content><category term="6 to 8" label="6 to 8"/><category term="여전히 여전해 (Inst.)" label="여전히 여전해 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/밥_한_번/</id><title>6 to 8 - 밥 한 번 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:29:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:29:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/%EB%B0%A5_%ED%95%9C_%EB%B2%88/" title="6 to 8 - 밥 한 번 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[커피를 마실 때 너와 택실 탈 때 <br>지갑 속을 훔쳐보는 <br>내 모습이 참 싫다 <br>너의 첫 생일 날 구둘 선물하고 <br>주머니 속엔 동전 몇 개 <br>터벅터벅 걸어간다 <br>밥 한 번 사는 게 왜 난 힘이 들까 <br>널 위해 사는 게 맘처럼 쉽지 않다 <br>근사한 옷과 좋은 차로 <br>널 웃게 하고 싶은데 <br>가진 게 없어서 그래서 미안해 <br>식당에 갈 때면 내가 부담될까 <br>난 라면이 제일 좋더라 하며 <br>해맑게 웃어주는 너 <br>밥 한 번 사는 게 왜 난 힘이 들까 <br>널 위해 사는 게 맘처럼 쉽지 않다 <br>근사한 옷과 좋은 차로 <br>널 웃게 하고 싶은데 <br>가진 게 없어서 그래서 미안해 <br>조금만 더 기다려달란 말이 <br>자꾸 염치없어서 너무 비겁해서 <br>널 놔줘야 할까 봐 <br>널 사랑하는 게 왜 안 되는 걸까 <br>널 지켜주는 게 말처럼 쉽지 않다 <br>가진 거라곤 내 몸 하나 <br>그리고 널 사랑해 <br>내가 부족해서 그래서 미안해 <br>]]></content><category term="6 to 8" label="6 to 8"/><category term="밥 한 번" label="밥 한 번"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/우리_사이/</id><title>6 to 8 - 우리 사이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:29:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:29:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EC%82%AC%EC%9D%B4/" title="6 to 8 - 우리 사이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 그러는데 왜 까칠한 건데 내게 <br>비꼬지 좀 마 투덜대지 좀 마 정말 <br>가끔 웃는 모습에 <br>가슴 뛰게 좋을 때도 있지만 <br>우리 사이 정말 왜이러니 <br>어쩌다 연인처럼 <br>좋다가도 제자리야 <br>사탕처럼 달콤해도 잠시뿐야 <br>이게 뭐야 또 투닥투닥 <br>어떻게 할지를 몰라 <br>아직은 사랑한단 말은 <br>이른 우리 사이 <br>좋아한단 말은 듣고 싶은 사이 <br>이봐 날 봐 좀 웃어줄래 <br>어떻게 내 맘을 몰라 참 우리 사이 <br>그러지 좀 마 상처주지 좀 마 내게 <br>니가 아픈 걸 보면 <br>괜히 맘이 가고 걱정되지만 <br>우리 사이 정말 왜이러니 <br>어쩌다 연인처럼 <br>좋다가도 제자리야 <br>사탕처럼 달콤해도 잠시뿐야 <br>이게 뭐야 또 투닥투닥 <br>어떻게 할지를 몰라 <br>아직은 사랑한단 말은 <br>이른 우리 사이 <br>좋아한단 말은 듣고 싶은 사이 <br>이봐 날 봐 좀 웃어줄래 <br>어떻게 내 맘을 몰라 참 우리 사이 <br>우리 정말 이상해 <br>뭐가 그리 복잡해 <br>맘은 그게 아닌데 <br>왜 헷갈리는데 <br>솔직할 때도 됐잖아 <br>내 맘 알 때도 됐잖아 <br>밉다가도 보고 싶은 너란 남자 <br>귀찮아도 생각나는 너란 여자 <br>사실 말야 좋아하나봐 <br>내 입이 맘 같지 않아 참 미치겠어 <br>아직은 사랑한단 말은 <br>이른 우리 사이 <br>좋아한단 말은 듣고 싶은 사이 <br>이봐 날 봐 좀 웃어줄래 <br>어떻게 내 맘을 몰라 참 우리 사이 <br>]]></content><category term="6 to 8" label="6 to 8"/><category term="우리 사이" label="우리 사이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/포스트맨_Postmen/술이_너보다_낫더라/</id><title>포스트맨 (Postmen) - 술이 너보다 낫더라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:29:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:29:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8F%AC%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A7%A8_Postmen/%EC%88%A0%EC%9D%B4_%EB%84%88%EB%B3%B4%EB%8B%A4_%EB%82%AB%EB%8D%94%EB%9D%BC/" title="포스트맨 (Postmen) - 술이 너보다 낫더라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그래 이렇게 또 취해 버렸어 <br>니가 또 그리워서 취해 버렸어 <br>너 땜에 입에도 안대던 그 술인데 <br>니가 떠난 후에 하루도 쉬지 않는걸 <br>그래 이렇게 또 취해 버렸어 <br>니가 또 미워져서 취해 버렸어 <br>너 땜에 한참 동안 끊었던 그 술로 난 <br>니가 없는 가슴을 채우려 해 <br>술이 너보다 낫더라 <br>날 살게 하더라 <br>너만큼 그리워지더라 <br>한잔에 웃다가 한잔에 울다가 <br>하루만이라도 잊고 싶다 <br>어제 마신 술에 가슴이 아파 <br>우리 헤어진 게 거짓말 같아 <br>어떡해 니가 보고 싶으면 난 어떡해 <br>어김없이 너 땜에 취할 텐데 <br>술이 너보다 낫더라 <br>날 살게 하더라 <br>너만큼 그리워 지더라 <br>한잔에 웃다가 한잔에 울다가 <br>하루만이라도 잊고 싶다 <br>보고 싶은 사람아 <br>너도 어디에선가 또 나처럼 <br>술이 널 잊게 한단 말 <br>다 거짓이더라 <br>그만큼 날 울게 하더라 <br>한잔에 웃다가 한잔에 울다가 <br>하루만이라도 잊고 싶다 <br>미치도록 니가 그립다 <br>]]></content><category term="포스트맨 (Postmen)" label="포스트맨 (Postmen)"/><category term="술이 너보다 낫더라" label="술이 너보다 낫더라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/Im_sorry_Feat_민연재/</id><title>6 to 8 - I`m sorry (Feat. 민연재) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:29:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:29:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/Im_sorry_Feat_%EB%AF%BC%EC%97%B0%EC%9E%AC/" title="6 to 8 - I`m sorry (Feat. 민연재) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[미안해 나 정말 쓰레기야 <br>이렇게 될 줄 몰랐어 <br>너와 손을 잡고 있어도 <br>너와 입술을 맞출 때도 <br>머리론 온통 그 여잘 상상해 <br>미쳤나 봐 <br>이젠 전화벨만 울려도 <br>작은 진동만 느껴져도 <br>솔직히 너보다 그 여자이길 <br>바라는 나도 내가 싫은 걸 <br>Baby i'm sorry i'm so dirty <br>미안하게 잘해주지마 <br>이미 난 멀리 니 곁을 떠나 <br>그녈 향해 가고 있어 <br>누가 봐도 착한 널 두고 <br>다른 곳을 보는 나 <br>Baby i'm sorry <br>더럽혀진 나를 용서하지마 <br>특별할 거 하나 없는데 <br>왜 내 맘이 더 끌리는지 <br>오늘도 술김에 전화길 들고 <br>그녀 번호를 누르고 있어 <br>껍질을 깎아내면 썩은 사과처럼 <br>꼬리치며 사랑했던 <br>주인을 무는 개처럼 <br>사랑한다 진짜 결혼하재놓고 <br>제대로 반전 친 내가 뭐 같겠지 <br>how can I say goodbye <br>what more can I give you now <br>나같은 설레발에 속아 넘지 말고 <br>괜찮은 놈 만나 제발 사랑 받고 살어 <br>Baby i'm sorry i'm so dirty <br>미안하게 잘해주지마 <br>이미 난 멀리 니 곁을 떠나 <br>그녀 곁에 살고 있어 <br>누가 봐도 착한 널 두고 <br>다른 곳을 보는 나 <br>Baby i'm sorry <br>더럽혀진 나를 용서하지마 <br>Leave me leave me girl <br>Let me let me go <br>더는 못하겠어 <br>Baby i'm sorry i'm so dirty <br>내 맘이 내 말을 안 들어 <br>그녀가 뭔데 내 맘은 벌써 <br>그녀 곁에 살고 있어 <br>진심 없이 웃고 있는 날 <br>더는 사랑하지마 <br>Baby i'm sorry <br>더럽혀진 나를 용서하지마 <br>Baby i'm sorry i'm so dirty <br>미안하게 잘해주지마 <br>이미 난 멀리 니 곁을 떠나 <br>그녈 향해 가고 있어 <br>누가 봐도 착한 널 두고 <br>다른 곳을 보는 나 <br>Baby i'm sorry <br>더럽혀진 나를 용서하지마 <br>]]></content><category term="6 to 8" label="6 to 8"/><category term="I`m sorry (Feat. 민연재)" label="I`m sorry (Feat. 민연재)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/니가_분다/</id><title>6 to 8 - 니가 분다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:29:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:29:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/%EB%8B%88%EA%B0%80_%EB%B6%84%EB%8B%A4/" title="6 to 8 - 니가 분다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 니가 분다 <br>문득 니가 분다 <br>아무 준비도 없이 <br>I don't know I don't know <br>I don't know I don't know <br>I don't know <br>어느새 어느새 어느새 <br>어느새 어느새 <br>내 가슴에 분다 <br>쉴 새 없이 분다 <br>애써 잘 지냈는데 <br>걷고 또 걸어가다 어느새 우리 <br>그때 그곳으로 데리고 가 <br>어김없이 또 생각 나더라 <br>어이 없이 너 땜에 내가 운다 <br>그저 한숨만 쉰다 하늘만 본다 <br>어떡해 그리워 너 <br>어쩌다 니가 부는 날이면 <br>불러본다 이제는 텅 빈 이름 <br>입술에 걸린 눈물 <br>바람 따라 흩날린다 <br>너도 내가 부니 가끔 내가 부니 <br>혼자 안부를 묻곤 해 <br>너의 향기가 흘러 <br>내 가슴에 찬다 <br>오늘처럼 니가 불면 <br>어김없이 또 생각 나더라 <br>어이 없이 너 땜에 내가 운다 <br>그저 한숨만 쉰다 하늘만 본다 <br>어떡해 그리워 너 <br>어쩌다 니가 부는 날이면 <br>불러본다 이제는 텅 빈 이름 <br>입술에 걸린 눈물 <br>바람 따라 흩날린다 <br>그렇게 좋던 시절이 지나간다 <br>한 순간 문득 바람에 멈춰 선다 <br>내 맘 아니라고 애써 외면해도 <br>이미 가슴이 널 외친다 <br>니가 없이 또 하루가 간다 <br>이러다가 말겠지 하며 산다 <br>한 잔 술에 널 잊다 시간에 묻다 <br>그렇게 살다 보면 <br>변함없이 또 니가 불겠지 <br>준비 없이 너 땜에 또 울겠지 <br>매일 니가 분다면 <br>그리우면 난 어떡해 <br>]]></content><category term="6 to 8" label="6 to 8"/><category term="니가 분다" label="니가 분다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/가비엔제이/사랑하게_해줘요/</id><title>가비엔제이 - 사랑하게 해줘요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:29:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:29:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%80%EB%B9%84%EC%97%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%98%EA%B2%8C_%ED%95%B4%EC%A4%98%EC%9A%94/" title="가비엔제이 - 사랑하게 해줘요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 그냥 놔두세요 <br>사랑하게 놔두세요 <br>우리 사랑 못마땅해도 <br>직업이 뭐 대수라고 <br>집안이 뭐 대수라고 <br>우리 사랑 우리가 해 <br>부디 허락해줘요 <br>내 인생을 내 대신 <br>살거 아니잖아요 <br>우리 그냥 놔두세요 <br>제발 상관말아요 <br>없으면 또 없는대로 <br>사랑하면 되잖아 <br>사랑 난 그것뿐인데 <br>우리 그냥 사랑하게 해줘요 <br>축하까진 안바래요 <br>그냥 지켜봐주세요 <br>부탁해요 그녀가 다쳐요 <br>세상에 여잔 많단 말 <br>사서 고생 말라는 말 <br>뭐라구요 잘 안들려 <br>내게 돌을 던져도 <br>나 끝까지 이 사랑만은 <br>지킬꺼에요 <br>우리 그냥 놔두세요 <br>제발 상관말아요 <br>없으면 또 없는대로 <br>사랑하면 되잖아 <br>사랑 난 그것뿐인데 <br>우리 그냥 사랑하게 해줘요 <br>세상이 우리에게 해준게 <br>뭐가 있다고 <br>나 이 사람 사랑한다구요 <br>우리 그냥 놔두세요 <br>우리 그냥 놔두세요 <br>사랑하게 놔둬요 <br>우리 그냥 잘 살게요 <br>보란듯이 살게요 <br>내겐 이 사람뿐인데 <br>우리 그냥 우리 그냥 <br>우리 그냥 사랑하게 해줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="가비엔제이" label="가비엔제이"/><category term="사랑하게 해줘요" label="사랑하게 해줘요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/친구_to_애인/</id><title>6 to 8 - 친구 to 애인 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:29:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:29:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC_to_%EC%95%A0%EC%9D%B8/" title="6 to 8 - 친구 to 애인 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[더는 못 참겠어 이러다 돌겠어 <br>온통 너만 보여 oh my god <br>친구로만 지내기엔 <br>나에게 넌 여자인걸 <br>I don't wanna just friend <br>오늘은 네게 고백하고 싶어 <br>oh tell me I wanna with you <br>친구 사이 말고 애인 사인 어때 <br>you're so wonderful wonderful <br>좋을 텐데 <br>너만 보면 미쳐 입 맞출지 몰라 <br>you're so beautiful beautiful <br>이젠 내가 다가갈게 <br>뚜루뚜뚜 뚜뚜 <br>뭔가 애매했던 우리 사이 oh babe <br>뚜루뚜뚜 뚜뚜 <br>이젠 둘이서 fallin' in love Yeah <br>말도 잘 통하고 성격도 잘 맞고 <br>잘 어울리잖아 oh babe <br>술 한잔에 빨간 두 볼 <br>너무나도 예뻐 보여 <br>tell me what should I do <br>오늘은 네게 고백하고 싶어 <br>I hold you I wanna with you <br>친구 사이 말고 애인 사인 어때 <br>you're so wonderful wonderful <br>좋을 텐데 <br>너만 보면 미쳐 입 맞출지 몰라 <br>you're so beautiful beautiful <br>이젠 내가 다가갈게 <br>뚜루뚜뚜 뚜뚜 <br>뭔가 애매했던 우리 사이 oh babe <br>뚜루뚜뚜 뚜뚜 <br>이젠 둘이서 fallin' in love Yeah <br>요즘 너도 내게 외롭다고 <br>남자 소개 해달라며 <br>그 말 나는 못 들은 척 할래 <br>나도 좀 바라봐줄래 <br>다른 남자 말고 나란 남잔 어때 <br>I'm your pretty boy pretty boy <br>잘해줄게 <br>손도 잡고 싶고 너를 안고 싶어 <br>I'm your sweety boy sweety boy <br>상상만 해도 좋은걸 <br>뚜루뚜뚜 뚜뚜 <br>뭔가 애매했던 우리 사이 oh babe <br>뚜루뚜뚜 뚜뚜 <br>이젠 둘이서 fallin' in love Yeah <br>뚜루뚜뚜 뚜뚜 <br>뚜루뚜뚜 뚜뚜 <br>이젠 둘이서 fallin' in love Yeah <br>]]></content><category term="6 to 8" label="6 to 8"/><category term="친구 to 애인" label="친구 to 애인"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/결혼한대요/</id><title>6 to 8 - 결혼한대요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:29:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:29:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/%EA%B2%B0%ED%98%BC%ED%95%9C%EB%8C%80%EC%9A%94/" title="6 to 8 - 결혼한대요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[결혼한대요 그런대요 <br>여태 나만 몰랐죠 <br>정말 그런 줄도 모르고 <br>취해 그녀에게 전화했었죠 <br>보고 싶다면서 울었는데 <br>잘 지낸대요 그런대요 <br>되려 내 걱정하죠 <br>정말 그런 줄도 모르고 <br>내가 이젠 잘할게 돌아와줘 <br>내가 눈치 없이 괜한 말 했네요 <br>돌아올 줄 알았죠 oh oh <br>다시 돌아올 줄 알았죠 oh oh <br>내가 바보 같아서 <br>사랑을 놓쳤죠 그녈 <br>마치 내일 돌아올 것만 <br>같던 그녀가 간대요 <br>기다렸대요 그랬대요 <br>내 안불 묻더래요 <br>가끔 궁금하다 했대요 <br>그깟 자존심 따위가 뭐라고 <br>내가 눈치 없이 바쁜 척 살았죠 <br>돌아올 줄 알았죠 oh oh <br>다시 돌아올 줄 알았죠 oh oh <br>내가 바보 같아서 <br>사랑을 놓쳤죠 그녈 <br>마치 내일 돌아올 것만 같던 <br>너무 늦어 버린 거죠 <br>진짜 끝난 거겠죠 <br>하지 말라는 그 말은 <br>너무 염치없겠죠 <br>꼭 행복하길 바래 <br>그 말도 싫은 걸 <br>내가 어떻게 하죠 <br>결혼하자 했었죠 <br>나와 행복하게 <br>살자 했었죠 영영 <br>내가 자격 없어서 <br>기다려 달란 말 못해 <br>그녈 많이 지치게 했나 봐요 <br>돌아올 줄 알았죠 oh oh <br>다시 돌아올 줄 알았죠 oh <br>내가 바보 같아서 <br>사랑을 놓쳤죠 그녈 <br>마치 내일 돌아올 것만 같던 <br>그녀가 간대요 <br>]]></content><category term="6 to 8" label="6 to 8"/><category term="결혼한대요" label="결혼한대요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/여전히_여전해/</id><title>6 to 8 - 여전히 여전해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:29:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:29:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/6_to_8/%EC%97%AC%EC%A0%84%ED%9E%88_%EC%97%AC%EC%A0%84%ED%95%B4/" title="6 to 8 - 여전히 여전해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여전히 여전해 잠이 부족할 만큼 <br>일 속에 묻혀 살곤 해 <br>잠시 끊었던 운동도 미뤘던 여행도 <br>다시 또 시작했어 <br>여전히 여전해 친구들의 걱정에 <br>여자도 소개받곤 해 <br>모두 너 같진 않지만 괜찮은 여자와 <br>잘 해보기도 했어 <br>다들 그러잖아 괜찮아지더라 <br>잘 지내는 내가 어색해지더라 <br>이래도 돼 벌써 잊어도 되니 <br>서운하겠지만 <br>너무 잘 지내서 미안해 정말 <br>여전히 여전해 니가 싫어했었던 <br>옷들을 꺼내 입곤 해 <br>듣기 싫던 니 잔소리 화내던 얼굴이 <br>이젠 그립지 않아 <br>다들 그러잖아 괜찮아지더라 <br>잘 지내는 내가 어색해지더라 <br>이래도 돼 벌써 잊어도 되니 <br>서운하겠지만 <br>너무 잘 지내서 미안해 정말 <br>너도 누군가를 만나고 있겠지 <br>나보다 더 내가 준 것보다 <br>더 많은 걸 줄 사람 <br>사랑하고 있겠지 <br>그리움이 지나 오늘이 오더라 <br>많이 울던 내가 창피해지더라 <br>멀쩡해도 이러다 니가 가끔 <br>따끔대긴 해도 <br>그냥 그래 이젠 걱정하지 마 <br>]]></content><category term="6 to 8" label="6 to 8"/><category term="여전히 여전해" label="여전히 여전해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tank/When_We/</id><title>Tank - When We - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:29:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:29:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tank/When_We/" title="Tank - When We - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Talk:] <br>Come on baby talk to me. <br>You know cause when you feel your body <br>Getting ready to let go just let me know when <br><br>[Verse 1:] <br>Tonight the only thing that I will ever ask of you <br>Tell me when um <br>I'm tring to make you feel it holla at me when you do <br>Tell me when um <br>Don't keep it to yourslef you know I wonna hear from you <br>Tell me when oh <br>And if I hit the spot let me know I'll come to and tell you when <br><br>[Chorus:] <br>When I'm hoping that <br>When your body says when <br>You'll just let go <br>When you're open up <br>When your scream out when <br>Don't stop the show <br>When when when <br>I'm putin this work in so <br>When are you cum'nn oh <br>When when oh when <br>Girl tell me when <br>When we when we when <br><br>[Verse 2:] <br>Girl open up your wall cause let me see who's new in town <br>Meet your friend <br>Been waiting to get started I'm a knock the bottom out <br>Can we begin? <br>I wanna get it <br>I wanna hit it <br>And when I'm gone for a long time I want you to miss it <br>And while we freakin <br>Your barely speakin <br>Let me know oh when <br><br>[Chorus:] <br>When I'm hoping that <br>When your body says when <br>You'll just let go <br>When you're open up <br>When your scream out when <br>Don't stop the show <br>When when when <br>I'm putting this work in so when are you cum'n oh <br>When when when when when <br>When when when when when when <br>Oh oh <br>Girl tell me when <br>When we when we when <br><br>[Climax:] <br>Here comes when <br>Strokes is getting faster <br>Nails is in my back deep oh <br>Here comes when <br>Bodies getting harder <br>The dick is getting harder oh <br>It's shaken it's throbbing just slow down baby breath <br>Hold on <br>Hold on wait a minute um hum <br>Ok now here we go <br>Here we go <br>I'm with you girl lets blow <br>Blow <br>You just gotta let me know <br>Girl tell me when oh <br><br>[Chorus:] <br>I'm hoping that when your body says when <br>Don't stop the show oh <br>When you're open up <br>When your scream out when <br>You open up scream <br>Don't stop the show <br>When when when <br>I'm puting this work in so when are you com'n oh <br>Puting this work in oh oh <br>When when oh when <br>Oh when when when when <br>Girl tell me when <br>Girl When we when we when oh <br>Girl tell me when <br>Said I wanna know when that feeling comes over you <br>When <br>Tell me when it's going down <br>Girl tell me when <br>Make a sound <br>When we when when when <br>Say when <br>Girl tell me when <br>Say when when yeah <br>Let me hear you say when <br>Girl tell me oh <br>Girl tell me when <br>When <br>When]]></content><category term="Tank" label="Tank"/><category term="When We" label="When We"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Icona_Pop/GIRLS_GIRLS/</id><title>Icona Pop - GIRLS GIRLS - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:30:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:30:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Icona_Pop/GIRLS_GIRLS/" title="Icona Pop - GIRLS GIRLS - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't see your name <br>I bet you have a cool one baby <br>You wanna play <br>just whisper in my ear and maybe <br>Some nights I remember <br>some nights I forget <br>There’s boys I like better <br>but there’s no regrets <br>Girls girls wanna feel it <br>Hearts pumping overheating <br>Girls girls live and breathe it <br>Hearts broke a million times around <br>We dance it off <br>Girls girls wanna feel it <br>Never get enough yeah <br>I lose control <br>I spin around in circles baby <br>And if I fall <br>I'll deal with that tomorrow maybe <br>Some nights I remember <br>some nights I forget <br>There’s boys I like better <br>but there’s no regrets <br>Girls girls wanna feel it <br>Hearts pumping overheating <br>Girls girls live and breathe it <br>Hearts broke a million times around <br>We dance it off <br>Girls girls wanna feel it <br>Never get enough yeah <br>Girls girls wanna feel it <br>Hearts pumping overheating <br>Girls girls live and breathe it <br>Hearts broke a million times around <br>We dance it off <br>Girls girls wanna feel it <br>Never get enough yeah <br>Boy you gotta do it right <br>Even if it's for one night <br>Boy you gotta do it right <br>Even if it's for one night <br>]]></content><category term="Icona Pop" label="Icona Pop"/><category term="GIRLS GIRLS" label="GIRLS GIRLS"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phlake/Gone/</id><title>Phlake - Gone - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:31:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:31:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phlake/Gone/" title="Phlake - Gone - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Vers 1 <br>somebody trickled <br>under her skin <br><br>pulled on her trigger <br>now where do we begin <br><br>I wanna blame it on the liquor <br>the smell of innocence <br><br>I didn't wanna trick her <br>I didn't understand <br><br>Pre-chorus <br><br>I could take a trip to Dubai bye <br>I would love to be on your wi-fi <br><br>I´d be your bed shiek - at home <br>not on a blank screen - alone <br>uuh <br><br>all alone alone alone <br>long away-away from home <br><br>all alone alone alone alone <br>you been gone so long <br><br>all alone alone alone <br>long away-away from home <br><br>dont forget the way how you <br><br>do you <br>do you <br><br>Vers 2 <br><br>I heard the signal <br>Calling my name <br><br>Shots had been fired <br>I couldn't stay <br><br>I wanna blame it on your ego <br>I tried to stay afloat <br><br>I wonder where we'd go <br>But we never know <br><br>Pre-chorus <br><br>I could day dream about yesterday <br>But you were the one that let me get away <br><br>Out in the ocean - alone <br>That's just the motion - I'm gone <br><br>all alone alone alone <br>long away-away from home <br><br>all alone alone alone alone <br>you been gone so long <br><br>all alone alone alone <br>long away-away from home <br><br>dont forget the way how you <br><br>do you <br>do you <br><br>all alone alone alone <br>long away-away from home <br><br>all alone alone alone alone <br>you been gone so long <br><br>all alone alone alone <br>long away-away from home <br><br>dont forget the way how you <br><br>do you <br>do you]]></content><category term="Phlake" label="Phlake"/><category term="Gone" label="Gone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PLAZA/Personal/</id><title>PLAZA - Personal - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:31:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:31:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PLAZA/Personal/" title="PLAZA - Personal - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro] <br>Know I can't, know I can't, no <br>Don't know, no, no, no, no, no <br><br>[Verse 1] <br>Not gon' quit you till I have to <br>Not gon' worry bout what her man do <br>And the pain comes in the long run <br>So is better to deserve it woman <br>Lights down, what you worried about <br>There's no love anywhere in this house <br>Got you actin' a way you dream 'bout <br>It's all a haze and I can't get much higher <br>Can't get much higher <br>So woman take the lust outta me <br>Take the soul and the trust outta me <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I told her we don't gotta know nothing personal <br>They don't gotta know nothing at all <br>If you wanna fuck with me, yeah <br>I told her we don't gotta know nothing personal <br>They don't gotta know nothing at all <br>If you wanna fuck with me, yeah <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>She said "it's so wrong" and I know it <br>Still I'm calling back and I don't know how <br>I'mma feel till I roll up <br>And when I roll up you just step out your dress <br>Like that, I said leave on the rest <br>Like that <br>Now woman you bring the lust outta me <br>You bring the best and the worst outta me <br><br><br>[Chorus] <br>I told her we don't gotta know nothing personal <br>They don't gotta know nothing at all <br>If you wanna fuck with me, yeah <br>I told her we don't gotta know nothing personal <br>They don't gotta know nothing at all <br>If you wanna fuck with me, yeah <br><br>[Bridge] <br>You know you can't go back, no, no <br>You know you won't go back, no, no <br>I hope you understand this girl, girl, girl <br>No, you won't go back, no, no <br>And when the high comes on, you can't fake it <br>And every chance you get girl <br>You know you're gonna take it... <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I told her we don't gotta know nothing personal <br>They don't gotta know nothing at all <br>If you wanna fuck with me, yeah <br>I told her we don't gotta know nothing personal <br>They don't gotta know nothing at all <br>If you wanna fuck with me, yeah <br>I told her we don't gotta know nothing personal <br>They don't gotta know nothing at all <br>If you wanna fuck with me, yeah <br>I told her we don't gotta know nothing personal <br>They don't gotta know nothing at all <br>If you wanna fuck with me, yeah <br><br><br>[Outro] <br>I know that you do <br>I know that you do <br>I know that you do <br>I know that you do <br>Yeah <br>I know that you do <br>I know that you do <br>I know that you do <br>I know that you do]]></content><category term="PLAZA" label="PLAZA"/><category term="Personal" label="Personal"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wolf_Alice/Yuk_Foo/</id><title>Wolf Alice - Yuk Foo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:33:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:33:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wolf_Alice/Yuk_Foo/" title="Wolf Alice - Yuk Foo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Am I a bitch to not like you anymore <br>Punch me in my face, I wouldn't even fight you no more <br><br>'Cause you bore me <br>You bore me to death <br>Well, deplore me <br>No, I don't give a shit <br><br>I wanna fuck all the people I meet <br>Fuck all my friends and all the people in the street <br><br>'Cause you bore me <br>You bore me to death <br>Well, deplore me <br>Well, I don't give a shit shit, shit, shit <br><br>I don't wanna be cruel, but you're really grinding <br>I'm not a fool but I have a rage and it's blinding <br>I feel it coming, is it exciting <br>I feel it coming, yeah I'm unwinding <br><br>You bore me <br>You bore me to death <br>Well, deplore me <br>No, I don't give a shit <br>You bore me <br>You bore me to death <br>Well, deplore me <br>No, I don't give a shit <br><br>You bore me to death <br>No, I don't give a shit <br><br>Yeah I have feelings, 'cause I'm a human <br>Totally self destructive, constantly consuming <br>And now I'm fucked, and that fucks you too <br>So fuck the world, and you, and you and you and <br><br>You bore me <br>You bore me to death <br>Well, deplore me <br>No, I don't give a shit <br>You bore me <br>You bore me to death <br>Well, deplore me <br>No, I don't give a shit <br><br>You bore me to death <br>No, I don't give a shit <br>You bore me to death <br>No, I don't give a shit]]></content><category term="Wolf Alice" label="Wolf Alice"/><category term="Yuk Foo" label="Yuk Foo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스키니죠_Skinnyjoe/24_The_Earth/</id><title>스키니죠 (Skinnyjoe) - #24 (The Earth) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:35:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:35:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%82%A4%EB%8B%88%EC%A3%A0_Skinnyjoe/24_The_Earth/" title="스키니죠 (Skinnyjoe) - #24 (The Earth) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stop before I sing again <br>before my world turns blue <br>You'll be alright <br>within this galaxy <br>You'll be alright <br>if you are aware <br>I'm your protector <br>even if the skies turn gray <br>You'll be alright <br>with my sympathy <br>You'll be alright <br>if you get stronger <br>All the small things <br>that make us feel beautiful <br>shed the tears for the lost planet <br>the perfect sphere <br>Each days get better <br>but in the end <br>It's all wasted <br>It's all wasted <br>It's all wasted <br>]]></content><category term="스키니죠 (Skinnyjoe)" label="스키니죠 (Skinnyjoe)"/><category term="#24 (The Earth)" label="#24 (The Earth)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이석훈/욕심_Inst/</id><title>이석훈 - 욕심 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:35:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:35:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%9D%ED%9B%88/%EC%9A%95%EC%8B%AC_Inst/" title="이석훈 - 욕심 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날 향한 너의 마음이 <br>조금씩 작아질 때쯤 <br>여전히 난 아닌 척 <br>난 모른 체 지내왔다고 <br>어디서부터였을까 <br>조금씩 변해가는 니 눈빛 <br>모든 건 나 때문인데 <br>알아 니가 바라던 날들과 <br>조금 다른 모습의 <br>우리라서 참 미안해 <br>그대 내게로 다시 <br>돌아와 줄거라 믿었는데 <br>찬란했던 또 고마웠던 또 따뜻했던 <br>우리 사랑은 다 끝났다고 <br>여기까지라고 <br>시간이 흘러 지나면 <br>모든 건 잊혀지겠지 <br>기억조차 추억조차 <br>모두다 사라지겠지 <br>혹시나 꺼내본다면 <br>우리의 아름다운 사랑에 <br>미소 지을 수 있기를 <br>사실 나는 널 떠날 수 없어 <br>너로 인해 애태운 <br>이 시간도 사랑이야 <br>그대 내게로 다시 <br>돌아와 줄거라 믿었는데 <br>찬란했던 또 고마웠던 또 따뜻했던 <br>우리 사랑은 다 끝난 거니 <br>정말 끝난 거니 <br>그대도 나와 영원한 사랑을 <br>바란 적 있나요 <br>찬란했던 또 고마웠던 또 따뜻했던 <br>우리 사랑을 다 간직해요 <br>애써 잊지 마요 <br>]]></content><category term="이석훈" label="이석훈"/><category term="욕심 (Inst.)" label="욕심 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이석훈/She_Inst/</id><title>이석훈 - She (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:35:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:35:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%9D%ED%9B%88/She_Inst/" title="이석훈 - She (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이렇게 안아줘 <br>그 어떠한 말을 안 해도 <br>너의 감정이 내게 들려 안고 있으면 <br>가끔 너는 내게 물었지 <br>좋아하냐고 아니 널 사랑하냐고 <br>니 눈동자에 비쳐진 <br>내 모습이 모든걸 말해 <br>머리칼 흘러내린 너의 그 모습이 <br>예뻐 보여 너무 좋아 보여 <br>뭐라고 말할까 사랑한다는 <br>흔한 말보다 <br>내가 더 하고 싶었던 말 <br>어디서부터 나의 말을 시작해야 할까 <br>얼마나 널 사랑하는지 <br>니 그림자 곁에 있는 <br>내 모습이 모든 걸 말해 <br>머리칼 흘러내린 너의 그 모습이 <br>예뻐 보여 너무 좋아 보여 <br>뭐라고 말할까 사랑한다는 <br>흔한 말보다 <br>내가 더 하고 싶었던 말 <br>찬란하다 우리 함께 있는 이순간 <br>태양보다 눈이 부신 너 <br>바람에 흩날리는 너의 좋은 향기 <br>퍼질 때면 나는 행복해져 <br>내게는 너만이 새로운 세상이며 <br>하늘의 별 같아 내 영원한 빛이야 <br>너야 <br>]]></content><category term="이석훈" label="이석훈"/><category term="She (Inst.)" label="She (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이석훈/내게_머물러요_Duet_박새별/</id><title>이석훈 - 내게 머물러요 (Duet. 박새별) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:35:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:35:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%9D%ED%9B%88/%EB%82%B4%EA%B2%8C_%EB%A8%B8%EB%AC%BC%EB%9F%AC%EC%9A%94_Duet_%EB%B0%95%EC%83%88%EB%B3%84/" title="이석훈 - 내게 머물러요 (Duet. 박새별) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[햇살 하늘 가득히 <br>내리던 어느 날 마치 기적처럼 <br>어두웠던 내 맘이 조용히 <br>그대 빛으로 환히 채워졌죠 <br>그대와 걸을 때면 <br>사실 내가 얼마나 <br>행복해지는지 모를 거야 <br>지켜주고 싶어요 <br>이렇게 한없이 <br>소중한 사람 내 그대여 <br>그대 내게 머물러요 <br>그대 지친 마음 <br>내가 다 안아주고 싶어 <br>그대 있어줘서 <br>내 곁에 있어줘서 난 <br>모든 게 더없이 감사해요 <br>참 부족한 나라서 <br>떠나가 버릴까 봐 <br>난 두려워지곤 해요 <br>우릴 지켜내고 싶어요 <br>이렇게 한없이 <br>아름다운 나의 그대여 <br>그대 내게 머물러요 <br>그대 지친 하루 <br>내가 위로가 되고 싶어 <br>그대 있어줘서 <br>내 곁에 있어줘서 난 <br>또 하루를 견뎌낼 수 있는 걸 <br>이제 나 약속해요 <br>늘 같은 맘으로 <br>그대 곁을 지킬게요 <br>그대 제발 머물러요 <br>오늘 내일 매일 <br>나와 함께 만들어가요 <br>내 온 마음 담아 <br>나 고백할게요 사랑해요 <br>그대 내 곁에 있어요 <br>그대 내게 머물러요 <br>]]></content><category term="이석훈" label="이석훈"/><category term="내게 머물러요 (Duet. 박새별)" label="내게 머물러요 (Duet. 박새별)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이석훈/여행_Travel/</id><title>이석훈 - 여행 (Travel) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:35:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:35:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%9D%ED%9B%88/%EC%97%AC%ED%96%89_Travel/" title="이석훈 - 여행 (Travel) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나에게 말해 <br>너 어디로든 가고 싶다며 <br>니가 원하면 <br>난 언제든지 준비돼있어 <br>바쁜 이 생활 속에서 <br>너와 떠난다면 <br>난 그곳이 천국일거야 <br>배낭을 메고서 <br>산으로 가도 좋을 것 같아 <br>언덕을 넘어 <br>상쾌한 공기를 마셔도 좋아 <br>숨이 차오르면 쉬어가자 <br>내 손을 꼭 잡아봐 <br>아주 조금 힘을 내면 정상이야 <br>우리가 꿈꿔 왔던 곳 <br>Happy new day <br>Happy new day <br>세상 끝에 가도 난 좋을 것만 같아 <br>Happy new day <br>그게 무엇이든 <br>더 큰 이유는 없을 테니까 <br>함께 떠나자 <br>파도를 보러 <br>바다를 가도 좋을 것 같아 <br>모래알 위에다 <br>너와 나의 사랑을 새기며 <br>너에게 고백하는 말이야 <br>니가 있다면 나는 늘 행복해 <br>내가 꼭 붙어있을게 <br>언제나 곁에 있을게 <br>Happy new day <br>Happy new day <br>세상 끝에 가도 난 좋을 것만 같아 <br>Happy new day <br>그게 무엇이든 <br>더 큰 이유는 없을 테니까 <br>함께 떠나자 <br>거친 파도가 우릴 덮쳐도 <br>높은 산이 우릴 막아서도 <br>함께라면 두렵지 않아 <br>Happy new day <br>Happy new day <br>세상 끝에 가도 난 좋을 것만 같아 <br>둘이라면 <br>그게 무엇이든 <br>더 큰 이유는 없을 테니까 <br>함께 떠나자 <br>]]></content><category term="이석훈" label="이석훈"/><category term="여행 (Travel)" label="여행 (Travel)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이석훈/욕심/</id><title>이석훈 - 욕심 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:35:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:35:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%9D%ED%9B%88/%EC%9A%95%EC%8B%AC/" title="이석훈 - 욕심 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날 향한 너의 마음이 <br>조금씩 작아질 때쯤 <br>여전히 난 아닌 척 <br>난 모른 체 지내왔다고 <br>어디서부터였을까 <br>조금씩 변해가는 니 눈빛 <br>모든 건 나 때문인데 <br>알아 니가 바라던 날들과 <br>조금 다른 모습의 <br>우리라서 참 미안해 <br>그대 내게로 다시 <br>돌아와 줄거라 믿었는데 <br>찬란했던 또 고마웠던 또 따뜻했던 <br>우리 사랑은 다 끝났다고 <br>여기까지라고 <br>시간이 흘러 지나면 <br>모든 건 잊혀지겠지 <br>기억조차 추억조차 <br>모두다 사라지겠지 <br>혹시나 꺼내본다면 <br>우리의 아름다운 사랑에 <br>미소 지을 수 있기를 <br>사실 나는 널 떠날 수 없어 <br>너로 인해 애태운 <br>이 시간도 사랑이야 <br>그대 내게로 다시 <br>돌아와 줄거라 믿었는데 <br>찬란했던 또 고마웠던 또 따뜻했던 <br>우리 사랑은 다 끝난 거니 <br>정말 끝난 거니 <br>그대도 나와 영원한 사랑을 <br>바란 적 있나요 <br>찬란했던 또 고마웠던 또 따뜻했던 <br>우리 사랑을 다 간직해요 <br>애써 잊지 마요 <br>]]></content><category term="이석훈" label="이석훈"/><category term="욕심" label="욕심"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이석훈/She/</id><title>이석훈 - She - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:35:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:35:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%9D%ED%9B%88/She/" title="이석훈 - She - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이렇게 안아줘 <br>그 어떠한 말을 안 해도 <br>너의 감정이 내게 들려 안고 있으면 <br>가끔 너는 내게 물었지 <br>좋아하냐고 아니 널 사랑하냐고 <br>니 눈동자에 비쳐진 <br>내 모습이 모든걸 말해 <br>머리칼 흘러내린 너의 그 모습이 <br>예뻐 보여 너무 좋아 보여 <br>뭐라고 말할까 사랑한다는 <br>흔한 말보다 <br>내가 더 하고 싶었던 말 <br>어디서부터 나의 말을 시작해야 할까 <br>얼마나 널 사랑하는지 <br>니 그림자 곁에 있는 <br>내 모습이 모든 걸 말해 <br>머리칼 흘러내린 너의 그 모습이 <br>예뻐 보여 너무 좋아 보여 <br>뭐라고 말할까 사랑한다는 <br>흔한 말보다 <br>내가 더 하고 싶었던 말 <br>찬란하다 우리 함께 있는 이순간 <br>태양보다 눈이 부신 너 <br>바람에 흩날리는 너의 좋은 향기 <br>퍼질 때면 나는 행복해져 <br>내게는 너만이 새로운 세상이며 <br>하늘의 별 같아 내 영원한 빛이야 <br>너야 <br>]]></content><category term="이석훈" label="이석훈"/><category term="She" label="She"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan_Mitchell_Grey/HAZEL/</id><title>Ryan Mitchell Grey - HAZEL - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:35:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:35:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan_Mitchell_Grey/HAZEL/" title="Ryan Mitchell Grey - HAZEL - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[honey, you're golden <br>anybody coulda told you that <br>mm mm saccharine <br>you're pure you're earth <br>giving life to me <br>like a baby tree in the ground <br>i thought i found, i thought i found an angel <br>you glow a hazel, hazel <br>shade of love when i see you <br>you glow a nice hazel love <br>you shimmer shimmer hazel love <br>you glow a hazel, hazel <br>shade of love when i see you <br>you glow a nice hazel love <br>you shimmer shimmer hazel love <br>honey, you're a star <br>anybody coulda wished on you <br>but i had my wish come true <br>come true like you were the star crashing down <br>down on earth <br>making life complete <br>just you and i <br>ever since you came down from up high <br>you glow a hazel, hazel <br>shade of love when i see you <br>you glow a nice hazel love <br>you shimmer shimmer hazel love <br>you glow a hazel, hazel <br>shade of love when i see you <br>you glow a nice hazel love <br>you shimmer shimmer hazel love <br>in 365 you make me 360 <br>i look alive when you look at me <br>took a dive in my soul, its beyond my control shine <br>to shine a little hazel now <br>ooo I'm free <br>you glow a hazel, hazel <br>shade of love when i see you <br>you glow a nice hazel love <br>you shimmer shimmer hazel love <br>you glow a hazel, hazel <br>shade of love when i see you <br>you glow a nice hazel love <br>you shimmer shimmer hazel love <br>ooo <br>you glow a nice hazel love <br>you shimmer shimmer hazel love <br>you glow a nice hazel love <br>you shimmer shimmer hazel love]]></content><category term="Ryan Mitchell Grey" label="Ryan Mitchell Grey"/><category term="HAZEL" label="HAZEL"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DRAM/The_Uber_Song/</id><title>DRAM - The Uber Song - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:48:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:48:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DRAM/The_Uber_Song/" title="DRAM - The Uber Song - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ain't nothing <br>but a twenty somethin' dollar <br>ride for my baby my baby <br>Ain't nothing <br>but a twenty somethin' dollar <br>ride for my boo <br>Said it ain't nothing <br>but a twenty somethin' dollar <br>ride for my baby my lady <br>And in about <br>twenty-somethin' minutes <br>she'll be coming through <br>Baby let me get you that Uber <br>Just so you can come over and chill <br>I will <br>And baby when I get you that Uber <br>Ima watch it as it drive <br>and maneuver for real <br>I will <br>When I hit your line <br>you seemed surprised <br>Cause usually <br>when you call I don't reply <br>I decline <br>But I got time today <br>okay you crossed my mind <br>Cause you seem real <br>and plus you chill <br>that's hard to find <br>You can find out <br>all the ways I want to do you <br>Soon as you send the addy <br>I'ma call this Uber <br>to you to you <br>Black truck nothing less <br>just select <br>You're the one I select <br>'cause you're so real you ride the X <br>Baby let me get you that Uber <br>Just so you can come over and chill <br>I will <br>And baby when I get you that Uber <br>Ima watch it as it drive <br>and maneuver for real <br>I will <br>Me and you long overdue <br>How many months It's been a few <br>But will we fuck That's up to you <br>When you come through <br>just make a move <br>Just say the word <br>when you tryna skrrt <br>Or I'll call it early <br>if you just tryna flirt <br>Don't waste my time <br>cause I rarely have it <br>I'll call you that Uber <br>have you in rush hour traffic <br>Damn <br>Baby let me get you that Uber <br>Just so you can come over and chill <br>I will <br>And baby when I get you that Uber <br>Ima watch it as it drive <br>and maneuver for real <br>I will <br>Ain't nothing <br>but a twenty somethin' dollar <br>ride for my baby my baby <br>Ain't nothing <br>but a twenty somethin' dollar <br>ride for my boo <br>Ain't nothing <br>but a twenty somethin' dollar <br>ride for my baby my lady <br>And in about <br>twenty-somethin' minutes <br>she'll be coming through <br>]]></content><category term="DRAM" label="DRAM"/><category term="The Uber Song" label="The Uber Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matthew_Koma/Suitcase/</id><title>Matthew Koma - Suitcase - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:49:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:49:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matthew_Koma/Suitcase/" title="Matthew Koma - Suitcase - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You look like Sundays with my ex <br>Sit at breakfast with your arms across your chest <br>Like a cross she wore my trust around her neck <br>Till it hung her <br>My baby she was clinically obsessed <br>Our identity was physical, but less <br>Every now and then her noise inside my head <br>Re-enters <br><br>She said I remember loving you <br>All of the good shit and all the bad shit too <br>Yeah I remember hating you <br>For all the right things you never tried to do <br>And I remember needing you <br>Call me an addict to your elastic moods <br>I'm packing every memory that we made <br>In a suitcase <br><br>You're on a train I used to wreck <br>With the bullets of the least of my respect <br>And I wish there was a shot I could regret <br>But there isn't <br>Yeah there were tongues I spoke in heat <br>That I never meant to say or meant to mean <br>And they're sharper when I see her in my sleep <br>In visions <br><br>She said I remember loving you <br>All of the good shit and all the bad shit too <br>Yeah I remember hating you <br>For all the right things you never tried to do <br>And I remember needing you <br>Call me an addict to your elastic moods <br>I'm packing every memory that we made <br>In a suitcase <br><br>I know you hate it when I say I'm sorry <br>But I'm sorry <br><br>She said I remember loving you <br>All of the good shit and all the bad shit too <br>Yeah I remember hating you <br>For all the right things you never tried to do <br>And I remember needing you <br>Call me an addict to your elastic moods <br>I'm packing every memory that we made <br>In a suitcase <br>In a suitcase <br><br>You look like Sundays with my ex <br>Sit at breakfast with your arms across your chest <br>Like a cross she wore my trust around her neck <br>Till it hung her]]></content><category term="Matthew Koma" label="Matthew Koma"/><category term="Suitcase" label="Suitcase"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MIKExANGEL/Complicated/</id><title>MIKExANGEL - Complicated - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:50:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:50:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MIKExANGEL/Complicated/" title="MIKExANGEL - Complicated - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro:] <br>La-la, la-la-la, la <br><br>[Verse 1:] <br>I don't know what to call it <br>Cause I be doing my own thing <br>And she don't know what to call it <br>Cause I be playing them mind games <br>Telling you, "I need you. It's mine." <br>Knowing that deep down inside <br>You can never handle this life <br>But darling my intentions are right <br><br>[Pre-Chorus:] <br>'Cause once you're in my arms, I'm thinking I'm invincible <br>I love you girl <br>7 in the morning <br>12 in the evening <br>10 at night, I need you by my side <br>I just wanna please you <br>Never want to leave you <br>Baby girl I need you, in my life <br>'Cause once you're in my arms, I'm thinking I'm invincible <br>I love you girl <br><br>[Chorus:] <br>You just tell em that it's complicated <br>It could be simple, but it's complicated <br>Contemplating while intoxicated <br>So glad we're here 'cause girl we hardly made it <br><br><br>[Verse 2:] <br>She rub my back when I want her <br>Know how to twist marijuana <br>She'll always be there for me <br>When there's no one in my corner <br>I keep it real, it's whatever <br>I wanna see us together <br>You think that I'm acting shady <br>This shit's just too complicated <br><br>[Pre-Chorus:] <br>'Cause once you're in my arms, I'm thinking I'm invincible <br>I love you girl <br>7 in the morning <br>12 in the evening <br>10 at night, I need you by my side <br>I just wanna please you <br>Never want to leave you <br>Baby girl I need you, in my life <br>'Cause once you're in my arms, I'm thinking I'm invincible <br>I love you girl <br><br>[Chorus: 2x] <br>You just tell em that it's complicated <br>It could be simple, but it's complicated <br>Contemplating while intoxicated <br>So glad we're here 'cause girl we hardly made it <br><br><br>[Outro:] <br>La-la, la-la-la, la <br>La-la]]></content><category term="MIKExANGEL" label="MIKExANGEL"/><category term="Complicated" label="Complicated"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Fennir_yfir/</id><title>Asgeir - Fennir yfir - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:50:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:50:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Fennir_yfir/" title="Asgeir - Fennir yfir - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Walk along a weary path <br>The weather holds the aftermath <br>Inside his sadness hiding <br>Crying to the cliffs aloud <br>Careless of the hills, it bowed <br>The heavy wind keeps blowing <br><br>Passing over pathless steps <br>And pleading on the ground, oh lord! <br>My soul is in your keeping <br>Forward through the frost and snow <br>Following the northern glow <br>Inside his pain abiding]]></content><category term="Asgeir" label="Asgeir"/><category term="Fennir yfir" label="Fennir yfir"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/New_Day/</id><title>Asgeir - New Day - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:50:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:50:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/New_Day/" title="Asgeir - New Day - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let forgiveness mend the past <br>heal our wounded hearts at last <br>Wait down by the flowing stream <br>Your return into my dream <br>Your return into my dream <br><br>Love so pure and ever true <br>Mends your heart and leads you through <br>Now a fleeting leave of gloom <br>As the sunlight fills the room <br><br>When the flowers grow <br>They lift their heads up to the glow <br>And find a way to make things okay <br><br>Line out to the sleeping sun <br>For a new day has begun <br>Be it false or be it real <br>This is what you made me feel <br>This is what you made me feel <br><br>When the flowers grow <br>They lift their heads up to the glow <br>That clears the day and makes it okay <br><br>When the flowers grow <br>They lift their heads up to the glow <br>For me and you the sun will shine through]]></content><category term="Asgeir" label="Asgeir"/><category term="New Day" label="New Day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Dreaming/</id><title>Asgeir - Dreaming - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:50:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:50:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Dreaming/" title="Asgeir - Dreaming - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1] <br>In an endless spin <br>And without you leaving <br>Flowing over every cup <br>If you know you're dreaming <br>If your worlds are crossing <br>And this dark should fall <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>Look up to the stars <br>In the darkness glowing <br>And when you're out there soaring high <br>Without your body flowing <br>Don't hesitate <br>You're dreaming after all <br><br>[Verse 3] <br>Over fields of green <br>In the sunlight gleaming <br>Leaving all I know behind <br>Now I know I'm dreaming <br>I follow every line that leads to you]]></content><category term="Asgeir" label="Asgeir"/><category term="Dreaming" label="Dreaming"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/I_Know_You_Know/</id><title>Asgeir - I Know You Know - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:50:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:50:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/I_Know_You_Know/" title="Asgeir - I Know You Know - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, how I need you now <br>Want you beside me <br>Oh, How I need you <br>Alone with a heavy heart <br>Why can't you see me? <br><br>Feeling my luck wear thin <br><br>Drive away with me <br>Straight into the rain <br>Never coming back again <br>See the rivers flow <br>Heading for the ocean <br>I know that's where we belong <br><br>Meet me up in the light <br>Now that it's calling <br>Sing to a quiet stream <br>Oh, how I long for light <br>A light that won't leave me <br>Never to go away <br><br>(And I know you know) <br>Let the ocean bathe me <br>(And I know you know) <br>Let the ocean bathe me <br>(And I know you know) <br>Let the ocean bathe me <br>(And I know you know) <br>Let the ocean bathe me <br>(And I know you know) <br>Let the ocean... <br><br>I know there's a love star <br>Shining down on the old house <br>Nowhere near the tried lines <br>I know where the keys are <br>The keys to the old house <br>Nowhere near the guidelines <br><br>And I know you know <br>See the rivers flow <br>And I know you know <br>(And I know you know) <br>Let the ocean bathe me <br>And I know you know <br>See the rivers flow]]></content><category term="Asgeir" label="Asgeir"/><category term="I Know You Know" label="I Know You Know"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Nothing/</id><title>Asgeir - Nothing - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:50:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:50:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Nothing/" title="Asgeir - Nothing - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing breaks our wave, my love <br>Coldest nights are out, my love <br>Voice unearthed, a hurtful truth <br>Somewhere in the clouds <br>So ambiguous, nothing breaks <br>Now <br>Nothing breaks our wave, my love <br>Nothing breaks our wave, my love]]></content><category term="Asgeir" label="Asgeir"/><category term="Nothing" label="Nothing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Underneath_It/</id><title>Asgeir - Underneath It - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:50:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:50:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Underneath_It/" title="Asgeir - Underneath It - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Calm is in the air <br>Leaves are floating by <br>A trickle here and there <br>Home to unify <br><br>Little headwind <br>Try to bring me back <br>Underneath it <br>Underneath it <br>Underneath it <br>Underneath it <br><br>The order of the day <br>Is mend the falling out <br>Let guilt fade away <br>Refinement bring about <br><br>Then we can begin <br>Then my heart can beat <br>Underneath it <br>Underneath it <br>Underneath it <br>Underneath it <br><br>All that tumbles down <br>Things that have gone south <br>Gone from green to brown <br>In the word of mouth <br><br>A reason why we're here <br>Reason can't be far <br>Underneath it <br>Underneath it <br>Underneath it <br>Underneath it <br><br>Hear the whispers of the restless brook <br>And while the shadows fall <br>We can find an answer <br>Getting closer by the hour <br>Closer than we have before]]></content><category term="Asgeir" label="Asgeir"/><category term="Underneath It" label="Underneath It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Here_Comes_the_Wave_In/</id><title>Asgeir - Here Comes the Wave In - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:51:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:51:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Here_Comes_the_Wave_In/" title="Asgeir - Here Comes the Wave In - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Watching shadows dancing on the wall <br>Painting you and me before the fall <br>Time and fate have left me in this place <br>And reality is in my face <br>Is this it? And just how will I know? <br>Hiding under a blanket of snow <br>When tomorrow is another day <br>With bright colours over skies of grey <br>Somewhere high above the timber line <br>Must be some way I can redefine <br>In this atmosphere of discontent <br>Leaving all of this without torment <br>Break the shackles that have kept me down <br>Feel the fresh air, have to leave this town <br>Moving further out, with both arms spread <br>Ever higher up the steps ahead <br>Here comes the wave in <br>Let the water even everything <br>When the morning comes <br>All this you'll find behind you <br>Whispering to me <br>Is the wind that blows, and birds that sing? <br>Dry your tears <br>It's just something we must go through <br>Out with the old and in with the new <br>This is something that we have to do <br>Through the storm, I travel in the night <br>Find my comfort come the morning light <br>Somewhere high above the timber line <br>Must be some way I can redefine <br>In this atmosphere of discontent <br>Leaving everything without torment <br>Here comes the wave in <br>Let the water even everything <br>When the morning comes <br>All this you'll find behind you <br>Whispering to me <br>Is the wind that blows, and birds that sing? <br>Dry your tears <br>It's just something we must go through <br>How will I know? <br>How will I know? <br>How will I know? <br>How will I know?]]></content><category term="Asgeir" label="Asgeir"/><category term="Here Comes the Wave In" label="Here Comes the Wave In"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Stardust/</id><title>Asgeir - Stardust - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:51:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:51:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Stardust/" title="Asgeir - Stardust - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What's the use of reaching <br>for your heart <br>we sail miles apart <br>I gave you tomorrow's <br>useless broken try <br>to make our world alive <br>I'm free from lover's <br>breatheless scream <br>following me <br>Perhaps you could just take one <br>small chance and see <br>maybe you need me <br>I'm the man that stands behind you <br>Real calm while you prove yourself <br>Understand that there is someone <br>Waiting till the curtains close <br>Me I'm a watercolour washing off <br>Into the deepest sea <br>Though my soul may set in darkness <br>it will rise in light <br>I'm the man that stands behind you <br>Real calm while you prove yourself <br>Out beyond your claim to freedom <br>a field wide I can meet you there <br>I shut my eyes and all the world drops <br>I lift them and you are born again <br>Out beyond your claim to freedom <br>a field wide I can meet you there <br>I'm the man that stands behind you <br>Real calm while you prove yourself <br>I will come back here at sunrise <br>A lover who waits all night <br>]]></content><category term="Asgeir" label="Asgeir"/><category term="Stardust" label="Stardust"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Unbound/</id><title>Asgeir - Unbound - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:51:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:51:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Unbound/" title="Asgeir - Unbound - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When the night time is falling <br>I lay down content <br>And the morrow is calling <br>Stick to the present <br>Where my mind is a flowing <br>My body will follow <br>Must be some way of knowing <br>Nothing holds me back now <br>And I will be standing my ground <br>Luck will find me somehow <br>You know that I will be unbound <br>I want you to be <br>Out there with me <br>I need you to be <br>Unbound with me <br>I want you to be <br>Out there with me <br>And then why do I worry <br>Odds are with me <br>I'm upon my journey <br>Untied I will be <br>I have found what I came for <br>Why should I concern <br>Just a taste and I want more <br>I'm on a good turn <br>On a good turn <br>Nothing holds me back now <br>And I will be standing my ground <br>Luck will find me somehow <br>You know that I will be unbound <br>I want you to be <br>Out there with me <br>I need you to be <br>Unbound with me <br>I want you to be <br>Out there with me <br>And then you bring about <br>Open windows to jump through <br>Over to the other side <br>]]></content><category term="Asgeir" label="Asgeir"/><category term="Unbound" label="Unbound"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Afterglow/</id><title>Asgeir - Afterglow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:51:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:51:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asgeir/Afterglow/" title="Asgeir - Afterglow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Afterglow, afterglow <br>Afterglow, magic show <br>Shine across the earth tonight <br>Shimmering over the ocean <br>Glow, it's a glow <br>Glow, it's a magic show <br>Gleaming up on the earth so bright <br>Moving along in slow motion <br><br>River of light <br>I know the afterglow makes it alright <br><br>Wonderland, wonderland <br>Wonderland is at hand <br>Lustre inside this heart of mine <br>Chasing away the shadows <br>Land, wonderland <br>Wonderland is at hand <br>All abiding under your shine <br>Revel in all that you disclose <br><br>River of light <br>I know the afterglow makes it alright <br><br>Afterglow, afterglow <br>Afterglow, magic show <br>Shine across the earth tonight <br>Shimmering over the ocean <br>Glow, it's a glow <br>Glow, it's a magic show <br>Gleaming up on the earth so bright <br>Moving along in slow motion <br><br>River of light <br>I know the afterglow makes it alright <br>River of light <br>I know the afterglow makes it alright]]></content><category term="Asgeir" label="Asgeir"/><category term="Afterglow" label="Afterglow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blondie/Fragments/</id><title>Blondie - Fragments - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:51:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:51:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blondie/Fragments/" title="Blondie - Fragments - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You can't create more time You just make it <br>If you want a new life, just take it <br><br>And if you want to change the world, then speak real clear <br>And make sure someone's listening listening <br>And if you want to break my heart, then stay right here <br>Yeah don't go anywhere <br><br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br><br>Everything comes in pieces <br><br>Do you love me yet <br>Fucking prove it <br>Try to ask yourself <br>Are you really different <br><br>Know that your life is more frightening than writing a song <br>It's an action of fractions you're passing along <br>And these oceans of emotion will crash once they hit the shore I promise you <br><br>And it's the closest I will get to sincerity <br>Every praise I make just looks so fake and crude to me <br>And it's the closest I will come to purity <br>Simulations never follow me <br><br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br><br>My heart is made up of pieces <br><br>Do you get it yet <br>Can't you see through this <br>You know all too well <br>You cannot make things perfect <br><br>No, I'll be shifting through lists of these possible loves <br>With this pain in my brain It feels scattered like doves <br>Though the sky where my eyes have been drifting towards recently <br><br>And it's the closest I can be to egocentricity <br>This overwhelming sense of rejection will sneak behind and tear at me <br>And it'll slam me to the ground into reality <br>And I'll deal with my disparity <br><br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br>Do you love me now <br>Why don't you love me now <br>Why don't you love me now <br><br>This is where I fall down shattered on the floor <br>As I'm swept around with a million pieces more <br>Of myself I once learned to lose <br>Though it never helped me forget the truth <br>The truth <br>The truth <br>The truth <br><br>This is where I fall down shattered on the floor <br>As I'm swept around with a million pieces more <br>Of myself I once learned to lose <br>Though it never helped me forget the truth <br>The truth <br>The truth <br>The truth]]></content><category term="Blondie" label="Blondie"/><category term="Fragments" label="Fragments"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crispi_Crunch/무비자_No_Visa_Feat_김기쁨_VANC_Remix/</id><title>Crispi Crunch - 무비자 (No Visa) (Feat. 김기쁨) (VAN.C Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:52:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:52:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crispi_Crunch/%EB%AC%B4%EB%B9%84%EC%9E%90_No_Visa_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EA%B8%B0%EC%81%A8_VANC_Remix/" title="Crispi Crunch - 무비자 (No Visa) (Feat. 김기쁨) (VAN.C Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll go to you <br>Just wait for me <br>Let's go and fly away <br>We're gonna get drunk <br>We're gonna get so fucked up <br>We're gonna get so hyped-up <br>I'm all prepared for you geared up <br>I'm 무비자 무비자 <br>But now wait I can't be <br>on your side <br>this thing made us divide <br>We're right now same <br>like Romeo and Juliet <br>I can't be on your side <br>No entries no visa <br>So sorry cuz I'm 무비자 oh 무비자 <br>It's a lie a lie <br>All of them excuses <br>You could make visa <br>just come to me <br>Stay I pray <br>I want you to be here <br>Don't you ever leave me <br>Just Fly <br>I'm 무비자 oh 무비자 <br>무비자 oh 무비자 <br>아무 걱정하지마 너 오빠 믿지 <br>곧 갈게 네가 좋아한 울 엄마 김치도 <br>챙겨갈테니 기다려 워아이니 <br>삐지지 말자 우리 사랑스러운 꽈이꽈이 <br>넌 된장찌개 삼겹살에 소주 <br>너와 난 입맛처럼 소박하지만 안 <br>변해 <br>널 사랑하는 마음은 <br>사드 따위로는 막지 못 해 <br>ay 마치 영화 같아 <br>우리 둘을 갈라 놓는 게 <br>국가란 말야 <br>도대체 왜 대체 왜 <br>우리가 뭘 잘 못 했지 <br>단지 사랑한 죄 밖에 <br>내 말 좀 들어줘요 <br>Trump and 시진핑 <br>한국은 정치하는 사람들 다 시치미 <br>꼭 다시 만날 거야 분명 <br>널 보고파서 미쳐 <br>당장 가고 싶어 중국 <br>It's a lie a lie <br>All of them excuses <br>You could make visa <br>just come to me <br>Stay I pray <br>I want you to be here <br>Don't you ever leave me <br>Just Fly <br>I'm 무비자 oh 무비자 <br>무비자 oh 무비자 <br>It's a lie a lie <br>It's a lie a lie <br>]]></content><category term="Crispi Crunch" label="Crispi Crunch"/><category term="무비자 (No Visa) (Feat. 김기쁨) (VAN.C Remix)" label="무비자 (No Visa) (Feat. 김기쁨) (VAN.C Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crispi_Crunch/No_Visa_Feat_김기쁨/</id><title>Crispi Crunch - No Visa (Feat. 김기쁨) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:52:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:52:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crispi_Crunch/No_Visa_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EA%B8%B0%EC%81%A8/" title="Crispi Crunch - No Visa (Feat. 김기쁨) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[거짓말이야 이건 말도 안돼 <br>You could make visa <br>just come to me <br>정말 거짓말 <br>넌 내게 올 수 있어 <br>Don't you ever leave me Just Fly <br>갈 수 있어 <br>잠시 기다려줘 곧 날아갈테니 <br>We're gonna get drunk <br>we're gonna get hung over <br>We're gonna get so hyped-up <br>난 모든 준비 다 끝났어 <br>But now wait <br>I can't be on your side <br>이게 대체 뭔 일이야 <br>우린 지금 마치 Romeo and Juliet <br>I can't be on your side <br>발급불가 중국비자 <br>So sorry cuz I'm No Visa <br>oh No Visa <br>거짓말이야 이건 말도 안돼 <br>You could make visa <br>just come to me <br>정말 거짓말 <br>넌 내게 올 수 있어 <br>Don't you ever leave me Just Fly <br>No Visa oh No Visa <br>oh No Visa oh No Visa <br>아무 걱정하지마 너 오빠 믿지 <br>곧 갈게 네가 좋아한 울 엄마 김치도 <br>챙겨갈테니 기다려 워아이니 <br>삐지지 말자 우리 사랑스러운 꽈이꽈이 <br>넌 된장찌개 삼겹살에 소주 <br>너와 난 입맛처럼 소박하지만 <br>안 변해 <br>널 사랑하는 마음은 <br>사드 따위로는 막지 못 해 <br>ay 마치 영화 같아 <br>우리 둘을 갈라 놓는 게 <br>국가란 말야 <br>도대체 왜 대체 왜 <br>우리가 뭘 잘 못 했지 <br>단지 사랑한 죄 밖에 <br>내 말 좀 들어줘요 <br>Trump and 시진핑 <br>한국은 정치하는 사람들 다 시치미 <br>꼭 다시 만날 거야 분명 <br>널 보고파서 미쳐 <br>당장 가고 싶어 중국 <br>거짓말이야 이건 말도 안돼 <br>You could make visa <br>just come to me <br>정말 거짓말 <br>넌 내게 올 수 있어 <br>Don't you ever leave me Just Fly <br>I'm No Visa oh No Vis <br>oh No Vis oh No Vis <br>Baby when we finally meet <br>don't hesitate find me <br>Just find me <br>I will never let go of your HAND <br>When we finally meet <br>Don't hesitate find me <br>두이부치 <br>Right now I'm No Visa oh No Visa <br>oh No Visa oh No Visa <br>거짓말이야 이건 말도 안돼 <br>You could make visa <br>just come to me <br>정말 거짓말 <br>넌 내게 올 수 있어 <br>Don't you ever leave me Just Fly <br>oh No Visa oh No Visa <br>]]></content><category term="Crispi Crunch" label="Crispi Crunch"/><category term="No Visa (Feat. 김기쁨)" label="No Visa (Feat. 김기쁨)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slushii/Twinbow/</id><title>Slushii - Twinbow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:52:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:52:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slushii/Twinbow/" title="Slushii - Twinbow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I wake I want to fly, high <br>Higher, and higher, and higher <br>Don't wanna risk my life <br>If the only way to make it is to break the rules and take over the world <br>High, higher, and higher, and higher <br>Don't wanna risk my life <br>If the only way to make it is to break the rules and take over the world <br><br>If the only way to make it is to break the rules and take over the world <br><br>When I wake I want to fly, high <br>Higher, and higher, and higher <br>Don't wanna risk my life <br>If the only way to make it is to break the rules and take over the world <br>High, higher, and higher, and higher <br>If the only way to make it is to break the rules and take over the world <br><br>If the only way to make it is to break the rules and take over the world]]></content><category term="Slushii" label="Slushii"/><category term="Twinbow" label="Twinbow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임동희/애상/</id><title>임동희 - 애상 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:52:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:52:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EB%8F%99%ED%9D%AC/%EC%95%A0%EC%83%81/" title="임동희 - 애상 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[또 다시 괴로움에 한 번 서러움에 한 번 <br>눈을 감아 울음을 삼켜본다 <br>아린 가슴 안고 니 이름 또 불러보지만 <br>기다려도 오지 않을 그리운 <br>내 사람아 <br>잊을 수 있다 난 생각했는데 <br>아니 잊혀질 거라 난 생각했는데 <br>나도 모르는 새 이렇게 니 모습 차 올라 <br>멈춰버린 시간 속에 홀로 남겨져 있어 <br>우린 서로감당 할 수 없음 을 몰랐어 <br>좋아 죽고 못 살던 그 날을 이 젠 뒤로해 <br>또 다시 괴로움에 한 번 서러움에 한 번 <br>눈을 감아 울음을 삼켜본다 <br>아린 가슴 안고 니 이름 또 불러보지만 <br>기다려도 오지 않을 그리운 <br>내 사람아 <br>우린 서로 감당 할 수 없음을 몰랐어 <br>애 태우며 보냈던 그 날을 이 젠 뒤로해 <br>또 다시 괴로움에 한 번 서러움에 한 번 <br>눈을 감아 울음을 삼켜본다 <br>아린 가슴 안고 니 이름 또 불러보지만 <br>기다려도 오지 않을 그리운 <br>내 사람아 <br>셀 수 없을 만큼 많은 <br>그 추억들 그 기억들 <br>피할 수 가 없는 난 그댈 보낼 수 없다고 <br>또 다시 괴로움에 한 번 서러움에 한 번 <br>눈을 감아 울음을 삼켜본다 <br>아린 가슴 안고 니 이름 또 불러보지만 <br>기다려도 오지 않을 그리운 <br>내 사람아 <br>다시는 볼 수 없는 내 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="임동희" label="임동희"/><category term="애상" label="애상"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/칸초_KanchO/Wee_Bee_Bee/</id><title>칸초 (KanchO) - Wee Bee Bee - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:52:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:52:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B9%B8%EC%B4%88_KanchO/Wee_Bee_Bee/" title="칸초 (KanchO) - Wee Bee Bee - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No hashtag <br>No Hashtag <br>이 수필은 퍼즐이 돼 <br>피비린내 퍼지는데 <br>펼치는 내 펀치라인에 <br>절대로 편집 없네 Nope <br>Rap Game은 누워있지 관에 <br>다시 꺼내 <br>Ssup bxxxh <br>Rap을 하기 늦은 자는 시간에 <br>Oh ban this savage <br>Damn it this happens <br>when Bad Meets Eve’ <br>뱀이 쓴 very mean Psalm <br>난 사족 못 써 feel me son <br>가지 하필 가시밭길 <br>막힌 귀에 못이 박힌 소리 <br>Old Hiphop Kid <br>Fxxk it But 이 beat도 <br>50 바퀴 째야 <br>다 뻥이야 그냥 재미나는 <br>rhyme puzzle <br>낱말의 살이 날리고 <br>난 더 즐거이 학살해 난도질 <br>No 소리소문 <br>But the best is 물고문 <br>내 wit wheat 젖을 때는 <br>완전 rhyme 반 죽이지 get it <br>뽑아내면 mom’s spaghetti <br>Cream 치즈 맛 살짝 돈 맛 <br>곰팡이 슨 빵에 니 랩 <br>한 토막 얹어 가글이랑 먹어 <br>소화할 동안 또 봐 Scream <br>Hello Syd 니가 죽은들 슬퍼하겠니 <br>Wee Bee Bee <br>Drinkin’ fxxkin’ and <br>chillin’ all night <br>비비기 쉽지 찢지 <br>여기 실어놓은 rhyme <br>죽이는 입질 all right <br>뷔페는 안 식지 all night <br>Wee Bee Bee Wee Bee Bee <br>빨리 먹어 그릇 치울라 <br>‘cuz Wee Bee Bee We B <br>‘cuz Wee Bee Bee We B <br>‘cuz Wee Bee Bee We B <br>Wee Bee Bee We B <br>‘cuz Wee Bee Bee We B <br>‘cuz Wee Bee Bee We B <br>‘cuz Wee Bee Bee We B <br>Wee Bee Bee We B <br>담배 한 가치도 없이 <br>내 입은 연기가 나지 aye <br>시간도 잘 나가는 오늘 <br>내 입은 변기 같지 <br>다 토해내 <br>그냥 싹 다 게워내 <br>난 시간 없어 좀 바빠 <br>그냥 다 내보내고 혼자 틀어박혀 <br>아니 이번엔 K가 왔어 <br>이 형 빼고 내 등은 훨빈해 <br>단 내 곡 이거 하나만 한 짓 <br>좀 가난하다만 shit <br>빼곡해 유복해 비지 않고 <br>단단하지 쉿 <br>Be quiet please <br>입 닥치고 그냥 들어줘 <br>매 순간을 벌리는 입들 <br>망치로 보여서 내가 못 되나봐 <br>잘못되려 하나 가만 <br>이런 소리나 뱉는 <br>나만 못된 아이인 걸까봐 <br>다만 ahh 철지난 소리를 뱉는 <br>거품 못 떼는 애는 됐어 <br>무리 같은 것들 <br>부르르 떠는 무식한 이 부류들 <br>위아래로 낙하를 <br>출구 EXIT <br>그런 철자가 내 마빡에 붙을까 <br>겁나 피해서 탔지 <br>박자 박자 <br>그 친구 같은 강박은 내 곁에 있지 <br>내겐 놀이 같은 <br>play button 같은 것 뿐 <br>물거품 같은 폼 없는 편집들은 <br>Fxxk‘em <br>이 scene의 편집증 <br>찍어둬 찰칵 <br>Long take shot ‘em <br>Wee Bee Bee <br>Drinkin’ fxxkin’ <br>and chillin’ all night <br>비비기 쉽지 찢지 <br>여기 실어놓은 rhyme <br>죽이는 입질 all right <br>뷔페는 안 식지 all night <br>Wee Bee Bee Wee Bee Bee <br>빨리 먹어 그릇 치울라 <br>‘cuz Wee Bee Bee We B <br>‘cuz Wee Bee Bee We B <br>‘cuz Wee Bee Bee We B <br>Wee Bee Bee We B <br>‘cuz Wee Bee Bee We B <br>‘cuz Wee Bee Bee We B <br>‘cuz Wee Bee Bee We B <br>Wee Bee Bee We B <br>내 혀 놀림은 너의 <br>썩은 머리를 노리는 Alien <br>내 피는 No래 <br>난 Ja Rule을 마주한 Hailie야 <br>Like Doe Rae Me <br>난 파의 이카리유이 <br>너희 dummy 참는 건 끝 <br>기다려 줘 내 service service <br>원 모양 Disk 내 필력 Predator <br>정박아 뒤에 숨어 비하 맞아 새끼야 <br>뒷골이 아파 <br>니 뒤쪽 barrier처럼 귀소를 막아 <br>나의 상태는 cloaking <br>꿀 빨러 mic 잡은 벌들을 청소 <br>난 일당백 하지 <br>내 말벌 같은 blocking <br>내 벽에다가 대고 <br>우는 장면은 feel good <br>그 벽을 타고 판을 팔 <br>KanchO’s 싱글 <br>넌 빠른 발걸음을 갖추는 게 <br>가장 시급해 <br>튀어 아님 묻혀 <br>Undertaker 불러 난 Stone Cold <br>’99 First Blood <br>마빡에 피날 때가 피날레 <br>종소리 뒤 TOMSSON의 LP <br>]]></content><category term="칸초 (KanchO)" label="칸초 (KanchO)"/><category term="Wee Bee Bee" label="Wee Bee Bee"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Northern_Ghost/Purge/</id><title>Northern Ghost - Purge - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:55:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:55:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Northern_Ghost/Purge/" title="Northern Ghost - Purge - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Desolation turned into machines <br>But they're too busy watching us from satellites to streets <br>Ignore the warning signs <br>Look the other way <br>There's nothing left to say <br><br>A nation full of narcissists <br>A colony of killers War <br>Society of psychopaths <br>Holding up the pillars War <br><br>They control the surface of our screens <br>Spinning in a carousel of dying hopes and dreams <br>They tell us what to think <br>They tell us what to feel <br>They tell us what to kill <br><br>And we all obey <br>We're all lead astray <br><br>I felt the world halt <br>It's purging us, reverting back to the start <br>I couldn't make out what the symbols meant <br>But I believe this time we've gone too far <br><br>We're having an emergency <br><br>Low <br>A new low <br>A new low for all the parasites that turn us into drones <br>They hide in the shadows <br><br>I see all of the pieces becoming clear <br>I see a bigger picture revealing our toxic atmosphere <br><br>If only we had more time <br>There's no one left to blame <br><br>Sacrifice <br><br>When you look at your life <br>Are you really worth saving <br>When you look at your life <br>Are you really worth saving]]></content><category term="Northern Ghost" label="Northern Ghost"/><category term="Purge" label="Purge"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/George_Ezra/Dont_Matter_Now/</id><title>George Ezra - Don`t Matter Now - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:55:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:55:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/George_Ezra/Dont_Matter_Now/" title="George Ezra - Don`t Matter Now - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you need to be alone <br>It don't matter now <br>Shut the door, unplug the phone <br>It don't matter now <br>Speak in a language they don't know <br>It don't matter now <br><br>Well I don't think about that stuff <br>No, I don't think about that stuff <br>It don't matter now <br><br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo <br><br>Build a castle out of sand <br>It don't matter now <br>Where it won't last and it won't stand <br>It don't matter now <br>With a suitcase in your hand <br>It don't matter now <br><br>Well I don't think about that stuff <br>No, I don't think about that stuff <br>It don't matter now <br><br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo <br><br>Batman running your hometown <br>Serve you well, run through the crowd <br>It don't matter now <br>Change your name, you won't be found <br>It don't matter now <br><br>Well I don't think about that stuff <br>No, I don't think about that stuff <br>It don't matter now <br><br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo <br> Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo <br>It don't matter now <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo <br>It don't matter now <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo <br>It don't matter now <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo <br>Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo, doo-doo <br>No, it don't matter now]]></content><category term="George Ezra" label="George Ezra"/><category term="Don`t Matter Now" label="Don`t Matter Now"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/희원/바라보다/</id><title>희원 - 바라보다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:57:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:57:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9D%AC%EC%9B%90/%EB%B0%94%EB%9D%BC%EB%B3%B4%EB%8B%A4/" title="희원 - 바라보다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오랫동안 남몰래 <br>가득 담겨있던 이 마음 <br>서툰 나의 고백을 <br>이젠 말해볼게 <br>하루하루 지날수록 <br>널 향한 내 맘이 <br>점점 커져가는데 <br>친구 아닌 연인으로 <br>너에게 다가간다면 <br>네가 내게서 멀어질까 봐 <br>오늘도 너의 뒤에서 <br>이렇게 또 <br>바라보고만 있잖아 <br>하루하루 보낼수록 <br>널 향한 욕심이 <br>점점 커져가는데 <br>친구 아닌 연인으로 <br>너에게 다가간다면 <br>네가 내게서 멀어질까 봐 <br>오늘도 너의 뒤에서 <br>이렇게 또 <br>기다리고만 있잖아 <br>이런 내 맘이 들리니 <br>]]></content><category term="희원" label="희원"/><category term="바라보다" label="바라보다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나르빅_Narvik/니가_어질러져_있어/</id><title>나르빅 (Narvik) - 니가 어질러져 있어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:57:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:57:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%A5%B4%EB%B9%85_Narvik/%EB%8B%88%EA%B0%80_%EC%96%B4%EC%A7%88%EB%9F%AC%EC%A0%B8_%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4/" title="나르빅 (Narvik) - 니가 어질러져 있어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[베게에 베어진 니 향기 <br>니가 벗어놓은 늘어난 티 <br>오늘따라 더 유난히 니가 보고 싶다 <br>몇 달이 지나갔는데 <br>하나도 치우지 못해 니 흔적들 <br>니가 내 맘에 어질러져 있어 <br>치우고 또 치워도 제자리에 <br>남아있어 얼룩처럼 니가 내 가슴에 <br>몇 달이 지나갔는데 하나도 <br>치우지 못해 니 흔적들 <br>니가 내 맘에 어질러져 있어 <br>치우고 또 치워도 제자리에 <br>남아있어 얼룩처럼 니가 내 가슴에 <br>]]></content><category term="나르빅 (Narvik)" label="나르빅 (Narvik)"/><category term="니가 어질러져 있어" label="니가 어질러져 있어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최시호/네_머릿속의_지우개/</id><title>최시호 - 네 머릿속의 지우개 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:57:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:57:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%8B%9C%ED%98%B8/%EB%84%A4_%EB%A8%B8%EB%A6%BF%EC%86%8D%EC%9D%98_%EC%A7%80%EC%9A%B0%EA%B0%9C/" title="최시호 - 네 머릿속의 지우개 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잊혀져 간다 <br>괜찮다던 기억은 <br>버거운 현실이었나 <br>그대 돌아가려 해 <br>자꾸만 나를 지우고 <br>추억조차 그댈 떠나 <br>가장 가까운 기억부터 <br>시간에 녹아내리네 <br>멀어져 간다 <br>붙잡고픈 그대는 <br>어느새 아이가 되고 <br>나를 떠나려 하네 <br>자꾸만 나를 지우고 <br>추억조차 그댈 떠나 <br>가장 가까운 기억부터 <br>시간에 녹아내리네 <br>]]></content><category term="최시호" label="최시호"/><category term="네 머릿속의 지우개" label="네 머릿속의 지우개"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/디어클라우드/또한번_사랑해_Inst/</id><title>디어클라우드 - 또한번 사랑해 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:57:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:57:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%94%94%EC%96%B4%ED%81%B4%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B0%EB%93%9C/%EB%98%90%ED%95%9C%EB%B2%88_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4_Inst/" title="디어클라우드 - 또한번 사랑해 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[소리 없이 다가와 줬어 <br>내게 손 내밀며 <br>웃어 주었지 음음 <br>우리가 함께했던 그 시간들 <br>꿈을 꾼 것처럼 멀어져 가네 <br>커져버린 그리움을 <br>이제 견딜 수 없어 <br>왜 몰랐을까 사랑한다는 걸 <br>가고 싶지 않아도 <br>갈 수 밖에 없나요 <br>이젠 알아 나 그대 없이 <br>살 수 없다는 걸 <br>멀리 가지 말아요 <br>다시 만날 수 있게 <br>또 한번 사랑해 그대 <br>시간을 또 거슬러 가면 <br>서로 마주 보며 <br>웃곤 했었지 음음 <br>언젠가 볼 수 없을 거라는 걸 <br>알고 있지만 나 멈출 수 없어 <br>처음 만났던 그 자리에서 <br>나를 기다려 <br>갈 수 없었던 날 용서해줄래 <br>가고 싶지 않아도 <br>갈 수 밖에 없나요 <br>이젠 알아 나 그대 없이 <br>살 수 없다는 걸 <br>멀리 가지 말아요 <br>다시 만날 수 있게 <br>또 한번 사랑해 그대 <br>우리가 나눴던 약속 <br>더 이상 지킬 수 없는 <br>말이 돼버렸나요 <br>알고 있잖아 우리의 운명 <br>그 누구도 막을 수 없다는 걸 <br>단 한번만 돌아봐줘 <br>멀리 있어도 좋아 <br>같은 하늘 아래면 <br>언젠가는 나 그댈 다시 <br>볼 수 있을 거야 <br>이대로 돌아서면 <br>다시 볼 수 없어도 <br>또 한번 사랑해 그대 <br>영원히 영원히 우리 <br>]]></content><category term="디어클라우드" label="디어클라우드"/><category term="또한번 사랑해 (Inst.)" label="또한번 사랑해 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/디어클라우드/또한번_사랑해/</id><title>디어클라우드 - 또한번 사랑해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:57:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:57:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%94%94%EC%96%B4%ED%81%B4%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B0%EB%93%9C/%EB%98%90%ED%95%9C%EB%B2%88_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4/" title="디어클라우드 - 또한번 사랑해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[소리 없이 다가와 줬어 <br>내게 손 내밀며 <br>웃어 주었지 음음 <br>우리가 함께했던 그 시간들 <br>꿈을 꾼 것처럼 멀어져 가네 <br>커져버린 그리움을 <br>이제 견딜 수 없어 <br>왜 몰랐을까 사랑한다는 걸 <br>가고 싶지 않아도 <br>갈 수 밖에 없나요 <br>이젠 알아 나 그대 없이 <br>살 수 없다는 걸 <br>멀리 가지 말아요 <br>다시 만날 수 있게 <br>또 한번 사랑해 그대 <br>시간을 또 거슬러 가면 <br>서로 마주 보며 <br>웃곤 했었지 음음 <br>언젠가 볼 수 없을 거라는 걸 <br>알고 있지만 나 멈출 수 없어 <br>처음 만났던 그 자리에서 <br>나를 기다려 <br>갈 수 없었던 날 용서해줄래 <br>가고 싶지 않아도 <br>갈 수 밖에 없나요 <br>이젠 알아 나 그대 없이 <br>살 수 없다는 걸 <br>멀리 가지 말아요 <br>다시 만날 수 있게 <br>또 한번 사랑해 그대 <br>우리가 나눴던 약속 <br>더 이상 지킬 수 없는 <br>말이 돼버렸나요 <br>알고 있잖아 우리의 운명 <br>그 누구도 막을 수 없다는 걸 <br>단 한번만 돌아봐줘 <br>멀리 있어도 좋아 <br>같은 하늘 아래면 <br>언젠가는 나 그댈 다시 <br>볼 수 있을 거야 <br>이대로 돌아서면 <br>다시 볼 수 없어도 <br>또 한번 사랑해 그대 <br>영원히 영원히 우리 <br>]]></content><category term="디어클라우드" label="디어클라우드"/><category term="또한번 사랑해" label="또한번 사랑해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루크/아직은_아니야/</id><title>루크 - 아직은 아니야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:57:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:57:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%ED%81%AC/%EC%95%84%EC%A7%81%EC%9D%80_%EC%95%84%EB%8B%88%EC%95%BC/" title="루크 - 아직은 아니야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아직은 가지 마 아직은 아니야 <br>조금만 있다가 마지막이잖아 <br>널 붙잡지는 않아 그냥 이대로 그냥 <br>일분이라도 좋아 아니 일초라도 널 <br>가슴에 묻고 싶어 그래 아프지 말고 <br>혹시라도 날 지울 거라면 니맘은 <br>여기 두고 떠나 <br>널 붙잡지는 않아 그냥 이대로 그냥 <br>일분이라도 좋아 아니 일초라도 널 <br>가슴에 묻고 싶어 그래 아프지 말고 <br>혹시라도 날 지울 거라면 니맘은 <br>여기 두고 떠나 <br>]]></content><category term="루크" label="루크"/><category term="아직은 아니야" label="아직은 아니야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sophie_Francis/Lovedrunk/</id><title>Sophie Francis - Lovedrunk - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:57:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:57:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sophie_Francis/Lovedrunk/" title="Sophie Francis - Lovedrunk - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, I struck gold with you you baby <br>Nothing that I wouldn't do for you baby <br>Give me feelings that I've never known, ooh <br>My mama told to be careful what I ask for <br>But you're the reason why my shoes lay at the back door <br>Ooh, my head is going crazy when I think of all that we could do <br><br>I can't get enough Hey <br>I was a ghost without your love Hey <br>Boy you got me lovedrunk <br>Boy you got me lovedrunk, ooh <br><br>Boy you got me lovedrunk Hey <br>Let's go Hey <br><br>Oh, I must confess to you <br>Usually I'm cool but I'm a mess for you <br>I need your love, pour me some more <br>My mama warned me 'bout the drama you could ask for <br>But you're the reason why my shoes lay at the back door <br>Ooh, my head is going crazy when I think of all that we could do <br><br>I can't get enough Hey <br>I was a ghost without your love Hey <br>Boy you got me lovedrunk <br>Boy you got me lovedrunk, ooh <br><br>Boy you got me lovedrunk Hey <br>Let's go Hey <br><br>I can't get enough Hey <br>I was a ghost without your love Hey <br>Boy you got me lovedrunk <br>Boy you got me lovedrunk, ooh <br><br>Boy you got me lovedrunk Hey <br>Let's go Hey <br><br>Boy you got me lovedrunk <br>Boy you got me lovedrunk, ooh]]></content><category term="Sophie Francis" label="Sophie Francis"/><category term="Lovedrunk" label="Lovedrunk"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노마_n_o_m_a/엄마/</id><title>노마 (n o m a) - 엄마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:58:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:58:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EB%A7%88_n_o_m_a/%EC%97%84%EB%A7%88/" title="노마 (n o m a) - 엄마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[안녕히 주무셨나요 <br>식사는 맛나게 하셨나요 <br>손목은 여전히 시리나요 <br>하루 종일 별일은 없었나요 <br>날짜 지난 약은 버리세요 <br>쓰지 않는 저 종이백들도 <br>파마약은 좋은걸 쓰세요 <br>무릎이 아플땐 택시를 타세요 <br>걱정하는 말에 짜증이 나고 <br>스치는 고마움에 눈물나죠 <br>보고싶은 마음에 전화를 걸지만 <br>미안한 마음에 화를 내고 말았죠 <br>혼자 식사하기 외로우시죠 <br>잠들기전 눈물 지으시나요 <br>엄마 그래도 오래만 오래만 <br>건강히 오래만 살아주세요 <br>걱정하는 말에 짜증이 나고 <br>스치는 고마움에 눈물나죠 <br>보고싶은 마음에 전화를 걸지만 <br>미안한 마음에 화를 내고 말았죠 <br>미안해요 고마워요 <br>살아계심에 내 곁에 있음에 <br>그저 미안하고 고마울 뿐이죠 <br>사랑해요 고마워요 <br>살아계심에 내 곁에 있음에 <br>그저 미안하고 고마울 뿐이죠 <br>살아계심에 내 곁에 있음에 <br>그저 미안하고 고마울 뿐이죠 <br>]]></content><category term="노마 (n o m a)" label="노마 (n o m a)"/><category term="엄마" label="엄마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iced_Earth/Clear_the_Way_December_13th_1862/</id><title>Iced Earth - Clear the Way (December 13th, 1862) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:58:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:58:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iced_Earth/Clear_the_Way_December_13th_1862/" title="Iced Earth - Clear the Way (December 13th, 1862) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They came across the ocean <br>In search of liberty <br>Escaping persecution <br>Famine and poverty <br>Signed up for bloodshed <br>New home a battleground <br>Send in the Irish <br>So courageous and renowned <br><br>Sons of Erin <br>Marching gallantly <br>Into a storm of lead <br>Forward Clear the way <br>Sons of Erin <br>Charging valiantly <br>Across that bloody space <br>Forward Clear the way <br><br>The hills alive with murder <br>The sky so cold and grey <br>The general gives the order <br>Irish clear the way <br>Bodies fall like leaves in autumn <br>From the wall at Marye's heights <br>Shot and shell ripping through them <br>A cold horrific sight <br><br>Sons of Erin <br>Marching gallantly <br>Into a storm of lead <br>Forward Clear the way <br>Sons of Erin <br>Charging valiantly <br>Across that bloody space <br>Forward Clear the way <br><br>Intrepid sons with heads held high <br>Go where glory awaits you <br>Your absolution under fire <br>If the lord above takes you <br>Fight, stand tall, prevail <br>Your brothers surround you <br>Fight, stand tall, prevail <br>Your courage defines you <br><br>Charge through the dead and dying <br>No surrender no retreat <br>Their brothers paid the price <br>They'll never smell defeat <br>Raise high the emerald colors <br>For all field to see <br>They charged into the slaughter <br>With faith and dignity <br><br>Sons of Erin <br>Marching gallantly <br>Into a storm of lead <br>Forward Clear the way <br>Sons of Erin <br>Charging valiantly <br>Across that bloody space <br>Forward Clear the way <br><br>Intrepid sons with heads held high <br>Go where glory awaits you <br>Your absolution under fire <br>If the lord above takes you <br>Fight, stand tall, prevail <br>Your brothers surround you <br>Fight, stand tall, prevail <br>Your courage defines you <br><br>Intrepid sons with heads held high <br>Go where glory awaits you <br>Your absolution under fire <br>If the lord above takes you <br>Fight, stand tall, prevail <br>Your brothers surround you <br>Fight, stand tall, prevail <br>Your courage defines all you are]]></content><category term="Iced Earth" label="Iced Earth"/><category term="Clear the Way (December 13th, 1862)" label="Clear the Way (December 13th, 1862)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/INDIIA/Out_of_Love/</id><title>INDIIA - Out of Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T10:58:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T10:58:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/INDIIA/Out_of_Love/" title="INDIIA - Out of Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We're not connecting quite like we used to <br>Gave it the best, lord knows we've tried <br>Fire to smoke, can't even see you <br>We haven't cared enough to realise <br>Now we've grown apart, all that we had is gone <br>Lay in the gavel feeling alone <br>Our winds are fated, stuck in our comfort song <br>Let's flip the switch so we can move it on <br><br><br>We've been running out here for a long time <br>Let's just make the most of what's left tonight <br>Can you bring your body closer to mine <br>It's all out of love <br><br><br>Out of love <br>It's all out of love <br>Out of love <br>It's all out of love <br><br><br>Give me the motion, don't get emotional <br>Forget who we were, that's in the past <br>And it's not the worst thing that we'll fall in <br>Maybe it's what we need to make it back <br><br><br>We've been running out here for a long time <br>Let's just make the most of what's left tonight <br>Can you bring your body closer to mine <br>It's all out of love <br><br><br>Out of love <br>It's all out of love <br>Out of love <br>It's all out of love <br><br><br>I know you know we're running <br>Who knows, maybe we'll make it back? <br>Let's be here in this moment <br>Out of love <br>I know you know we're running <br>Who knows, maybe we'll make it back? <br>Let's be here in this moment <br>Out of love <br>Out of love <br>Out of love <br>It's all out of love <br><br><br>Out of love <br>It's all out of love <br>Out of love <br>It's all out of love <br><br><br>We've been running out here for a long time <br>Let's just make the most of what's left tonight <br>Can you bring your body closer to mine <br>It's all out of love]]></content><category term="INDIIA" label="INDIIA"/><category term="Out of Love" label="Out of Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지지배/다_너_때문이야/</id><title>지지배 - 다 너 때문이야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:00:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:00:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EC%A7%80%EB%B0%B0/%EB%8B%A4_%EB%84%88_%EB%95%8C%EB%AC%B8%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC/" title="지지배 - 다 너 때문이야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[첫눈에 반한단 말따위 <br>나는 믿지 않았어 믿지 않았어 <br>널 처음 보던 날 알았어 <br>You’re My Boy <br>시간이 멈춘 것만 같아 <br>내 심장이 터질 것만 같은데 <br>You’re my everything <br>내가 좀 이상해 Oh Yeah <br>다 너 때문이야 <br>잠을 잘 수가 없는 건 <br>다 너 때문이야 <br>눈앞이 보이지않아 <br>다 너 때문이야 <br>불러도 들리지않아 <br>You’re My Boy <br>하루가 어떻게 갔는지 <br>아무 느낌이 없어 느낌 없어 <br>너만 보면 아무것도 난 할 수가 <br>시간이 멈춘 것만 같아 <br>내 심장이 터질 것만 같은데 <br>You’re my everything <br>내가 좀 이상해 Oh Yeah <br>다 너 때문이야 <br>잠을 잘 수가 없는 건 <br>다 너 때문이야 <br>눈앞이 보이지않아 <br>다 너 때문이야 <br>불러도 들리지않아 <br>You’re My Boy <br>I Want You Love <br>I Want You Love 니가 좋은 걸 <br>Beautiful Lady <br>You’re My Love <br>니 손을 잡고 입 맞추면서 <br>사랑해 좋아해 말하고 싶어 <br>내 손이 너무 떨려와 <br>니 손을 잡을 수 없어 <br>제발 좀 나를 잡아줘 <br>I Want You <br>다 너 때문이야 <br>잠을 잘 수가 없는 건 <br>다 너 때문이야 <br>눈앞이 보이지않아 <br>다 너 때문이야 <br>불러도 들리지않아 <br>You’re My Boy <br>I Want You Love <br>I Want You Love 니가 좋은 걸 <br>Beautiful Lady <br>You’re My Love <br>다 너 때문이야 <br>다 너 때문이야 <br>다 너 때문이야 <br>You’re My Boy <br>]]></content><category term="지지배" label="지지배"/><category term="다 너 때문이야" label="다 너 때문이야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/현진이/추억의_동성로거리/</id><title>현진이 - 추억의 동성로거리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:03:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:03:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%98%84%EC%A7%84%EC%9D%B4/%EC%B6%94%EC%96%B5%EC%9D%98_%EB%8F%99%EC%84%B1%EB%A1%9C%EA%B1%B0%EB%A6%AC/" title="현진이 - 추억의 동성로거리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1절 <br>네온불 하나 거리도 하나 <br>동성로 거리에서 <br>추억에 취해 옛사랑 못잊어 <br>밤비 맞으며 걸어봅니다 <br>그이와 걷던 동성로길 <br>그때는 행복했었네 <br>둘이서 자주간 카페앞 지날때 <br>그사람 생각이 나네 <br>아~~~아~ 잊을수 없는사람 <br>추억의 동성로 거리 <br>2절 <br>네온불 하나 거리도 하나 <br>동성로 거리에서 <br>술잔 속의 담겨진 그추억 <br>밤비 맞으며 걸어봅니다 <br>그이와 걷던 동성로길 <br>그때는 행복했었네 <br>둘이서 자주간 카페앞 지날때 <br>그사람 생각이 나네 <br>아~~아~~ 잊을수 없는사람 <br>추억의 동성로 거리 <br>아~아~~ 잊을수 없는사람 <br>추억의 동성로 거리 (한번더)]]></content><category term="현진이" label="현진이"/><category term="추억의 동성로거리" label="추억의 동성로거리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/현진이/갓바위_가는길/</id><title>현진이 - 갓바위 가는길 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:03:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:03:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%98%84%EC%A7%84%EC%9D%B4/%EA%B0%93%EB%B0%94%EC%9C%84_%EA%B0%80%EB%8A%94%EA%B8%B8/" title="현진이 - 갓바위 가는길 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[일천삼백 육십오 계단 <br>갓바위 가는 길 <br>한 계단이 청춘이고 <br>한 계단이 인생일세 <br>염불하는 저 나그네 <br>돈이 무엇이더냐 <br>명예가 소중하더냐 <br>여보시게 공수래공수거 <br>인생이 아니더냐 <br>속세에 지은 업보 <br>모두 다 내 탓이로다 <br>팔공산아 갓바위야 <br>찬불하는 저 나그네 <br>일천삼백 육십오 계단 <br>갓바위 가는 길 <br>한 계단이 눈물이고 <br>한 계단이 사랑일세 <br>염불하는 저 나그네 <br>사는 게 무엇이더냐 <br>한번 왔다 가는 세상 <br>여보시게 공수래공수거 <br>인생이 아니더냐 <br>속세에 지은 업보 <br>모두 다 내 탓이로다 <br>팔공산아 갓바위야 <br>찬불하는 저 나그네 <br>찬불하는 저 나그네 <br>]]></content><category term="현진이" label="현진이"/><category term="갓바위 가는길" label="갓바위 가는길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초아강/님이_좋아/</id><title>초아강 - 님이 좋아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:03:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:03:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%95%84%EA%B0%95/%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%B4_%EC%A2%8B%EC%95%84/" title="초아강 - 님이 좋아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[님이 좋아 꽃이 좋아 <br>꽃보다 님이 좋지 <br>저 하늘에 꽃구름이 흘러가면 <br><br>님의 향기 그리워져요 <br>돌아와줘요 묻지 않을게 <br>당신 없인 살수가 없어 <br><br>꽃구름 그림자에 맺은 그 사람 <br>지금은 어디로 갔나 <br><br>님이 좋아 꽃이 좋아 <br>꽃보다 님이 좋지 <br>저 하늘에 꽃구름이 <br><br>흘러가면 님의 향기 그리워져요 <br>돌아 와줘요 용서 해줄게 <br>당신 없인 살수가 없어 <br>꽃구름에 그림자에 맺은 그 사람 <br>지금은 어디로 갔나 <br>지금은 어디로 갔나]]></content><category term="초아강" label="초아강"/><category term="님이 좋아" label="님이 좋아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초아강/나무와_새/</id><title>초아강 - 나무와 새 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:03:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:03:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%95%84%EA%B0%95/%EB%82%98%EB%AC%B4%EC%99%80_%EC%83%88/" title="초아강 - 나무와 새 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[진달래가 곱게 피던 날 <br>내 곁에 날아오더니 <br>작은 날개 가만히 접어서 <br><br>내 마음에 꿈을 주었죠 <br>이젠 서로 정이 들어서 <br>떨어져 살수 없을 때 <br><br>외로움을 가슴에 안은 채 <br>우린 서로 남이 된거죠 <br>신록이 푸르던 날도 <br>어느덧 다 지나가고 <br><br>내 모습은 이렇게 <br>내 모습은 이렇게 <br>야위어만 가고 있어요 <br><br>내 마음은 이렇게 <br>내 마음은 이렇게 <br>병이 들어가고 있어요 <br><br>아픈 마음 달래가면서 <br>난 누굴 기다리나요 <br>하염없이 눈물이 자꾸만 <br>잎 새 되어 떨어지는데 <br><br>신록이 푸르던 날도 <br>어느덧 다 지나가고 <br>내 모습은 이렇게 <br>내 모습은 이렇게 <br><br>야위어만 가고 있어요 <br>내 마음은 이렇게 <br>내 마음은 이렇게 <br>병이 들어가고 있어요 <br><br>아픈 마음 달래가면서 <br>난 누굴 기다리나요 <br>하염없이 눈물이 자꾸만 <br>잎 새 되어 떨어지는데 <br><br>*하염없이 눈물이 자꾸만 <br>잎 새 되어 떨어지는데]]></content><category term="초아강" label="초아강"/><category term="나무와 새" label="나무와 새"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초아강/꽃잎편지/</id><title>초아강 - 꽃잎편지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:03:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:03:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%95%84%EA%B0%95/%EA%BD%83%EC%9E%8E%ED%8E%B8%EC%A7%80/" title="초아강 - 꽃잎편지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흐르는 저 강물에 띄워 보낸 꽃잎 편지 <br>고운 사연 적어서 그님에게 띄웁니다 <br><br>아름다운 강마을에 버들잎이 <br>싹이 틀 때 오신다는 그 님을 <br><br>그리워 못 잊어 띄워 보낸 첫사랑의 꽃잎 편지 <br><br>노을 진 저 강물에 띄워 보낸 꽃잎 편지 <br>고운 순정 담아서 그 님에게 보냅니다 <br><br>꽃이 피는 강마을에 뻐꾹새가 다시 오면 오신다던 그님을 <br><br>그리워 못 잊어 띄워 보낸 첫사랑의 꽃잎 편지]]></content><category term="초아강" label="초아강"/><category term="꽃잎편지" label="꽃잎편지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초아강/연분홍_사랑/</id><title>초아강 - 연분홍 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:03:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:03:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%95%84%EA%B0%95/%EC%97%B0%EB%B6%84%ED%99%8D_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="초아강 - 연분홍 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가슴에 싹이 트는 연분홍 사연이 <br>봄맞이 진달래 꽃 처럼 붉게 타네 <br><br>내 님은 어디에 내 님은 어디에 <br>쌓이는 그리움 기다리는 내 마음은 내 마음은 연분홍 사랑 <br><br>가슴에 아로새긴 연분홍 사연이 <br>달맞이 목련같이 아련히 피어나네 <br><br>내 사랑 어디에 내 사랑 어디에 <br>쌓이는 그리움 기다리는 내 마음은 내 마음은 연분홍 사랑]]></content><category term="초아강" label="초아강"/><category term="연분홍 사랑" label="연분홍 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초아강/여자는_눈물인가봐/</id><title>초아강 - 여자는 눈물인가봐 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:04:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:04:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%95%84%EA%B0%95/%EC%97%AC%EC%9E%90%EB%8A%94_%EB%88%88%EB%AC%BC%EC%9D%B8%EA%B0%80%EB%B4%90/" title="초아강 - 여자는 눈물인가봐 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 나는 당신만을 후회 없이 사랑했는지 <br>당신은 나에게 사랑은 주고서 <br><br>눈물을 보고 싶나요 울리지 말아요 울리지 말아요 <br>바보처럼 울리지 말아요 <br><br>그래도 간다면 그래도 간다면 <br>잘 가세요 잘 가세요 여자는 눈물 인가봐 <br><br>왜 나는 당신만을 미련 없이 사랑했는지 <br>당신은 나에게 당신은 나에게 <br><br>과거를 주고 싶나요 울리지 말아요 울리지 말아요 <br>당신 여자 울리지 말아요 <br><br>울리고 간다면 그래도 간다면 <br>잘 가세요 잘 가세요 여자는 눈물 인가봐]]></content><category term="초아강" label="초아강"/><category term="여자는 눈물인가봐" label="여자는 눈물인가봐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초아강/덕수궁_돌담길/</id><title>초아강 - 덕수궁 돌담길 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:04:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:04:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%95%84%EA%B0%95/%EB%8D%95%EC%88%98%EA%B6%81_%EB%8F%8C%EB%8B%B4%EA%B8%B8/" title="초아강 - 덕수궁 돌담길 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비 내리는 덕수궁 돌담장 길을 <br>우산 없이 혼자서 거니는 사람 <br>무슨 사연 있길래 혼자 거닐까 <br>저토록 비를 맞고 혼자 거닐까 <br>밤비가 소리 없이 내리는 밤에도 <br>깊은 덕수궁 돌담장 길을 <br>비를 맞고 말없이 거니는 사람 <br>옛날에는 두 사람 거닐던 길을 <br>지금은 어이해서 혼자 거닐까 <br>밤비가 하염없이 내리는 밤에]]></content><category term="초아강" label="초아강"/><category term="덕수궁 돌담길" label="덕수궁 돌담길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초아강/빙점/</id><title>초아강 - 빙점 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:04:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:04:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%95%84%EA%B0%95/%EB%B9%99%EC%A0%90/" title="초아강 - 빙점 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 몸이 떠나 거든 아주 가거든 <br>쌓이고 쌓인 미움 버려 주세요 <br>못 다 핀 꽃망울이 아쉬움 두고 <br>서럽게 져야 하는 차가운 빙점 <br>눈물도 얼어붙은 차가운 빙점 <br><br>마지막 가는 길을 서러워 않고 <br>모든 죄 나 혼자서 지고 갑니다 <br><br>소중한 첫사랑의 애련한 꿈을 <br>모질게 꺾어버린 차가운 빙점 <br>보람을 삼켜버린 차가운 빙점]]></content><category term="초아강" label="초아강"/><category term="빙점" label="빙점"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초아강/새벽길/</id><title>초아강 - 새벽길 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:04:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:04:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%95%84%EA%B0%95/%EC%83%88%EB%B2%BD%EA%B8%B8/" title="초아강 - 새벽길 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑은 하늘가에 메아리로 흩어지고 <br>그 이름 입술 마다 맴돌아서 아픈데 <br><br>가슴에 멍든 상처 지울 길 없어라 <br>정답던 님의 얼굴 너무나도 무정해 <br>울면서 돌아서는 안개 짙은 새벽길 <br><br>꽃잎이 눈처럼 창가에 내리는 밤 <br>기러기 날개에 부쳐보는 사연은 <br>사랑이 병이되어 <br><br>찾아온 가슴에 뜨겁던 님의 입김 <br>너무나도 차가워 울면서 돌아서는 <br>안개 짙은 새벽길]]></content><category term="초아강" label="초아강"/><category term="새벽길" label="새벽길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초아강/우리_인생디스코/</id><title>초아강 - 우리 인생(디스코) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:04:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:04:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%95%84%EA%B0%95/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9D%B8%EC%83%9D%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%EC%BD%94/" title="초아강 - 우리 인생(디스코) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가는 길이 험하고 편하다 해도 <br>어차피 끝날 곳은 그 길 뿐인데 <br><br>내 마음 욕심 없이 행복을 노래하며 <br>나는 그렇게 살련다 <br><br>부는 저 바람 어디서 왔다 <br>어디론가 또 떠나가네 <br><br>울고 태어났다가 눈물 속에 가는 길 <br>우리 인생 웃으며 살자 <br><br>가는 길이 험하고 편하다 해도 <br>어차피 끝날 곳은 그 길 뿐인데 <br><br>내 마음 아름답게 사랑을 노래하며 <br>나는 그렇게 살련다 <br><br>가는 저 세월 속절도 없이 <br>마음대로 또 흘러가네 <br><br>빈손으로 왔다가 빈손으로 가는 길 <br>우리 인생 정으로 살자 <br><br>*부는 저 바람 어디서 왔다 <br>어디론가 또 떠나가네 <br>울고 태어났다가 눈물 속에 가는 길 <br><br>우리 인생 웃으며 살자 <br>우리 인생 정으로 살자]]></content><category term="초아강" label="초아강"/><category term="우리 인생(디스코)" label="우리 인생(디스코)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초아강/꿈과_사랑디스코/</id><title>초아강 - 꿈과 사랑(디스코) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:04:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:04:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%95%84%EA%B0%95/%EA%BF%88%EA%B3%BC_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%EC%BD%94/" title="초아강 - 꿈과 사랑(디스코) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[저 구름 따라 흘러흘러 <br>가버린 세월 뒤 돌아보니 <br>무언가 잃어버린 미련의 아쉬움이 <br><br>아직도 가슴에 남아있네 <br>인생이란 울다가 웃고 <br>알 수 없는 미로 인 것을 <br><br>저마다 아픈 사연을 안고 <br>내일 위해 잊고 살지만 <br><br>아 꿈과 사랑 찾아 오늘도 <br>세상 파도 속으로 떠나네 <br><br>저 구름 따라 흘러 흘러 <br>가버린 세월 뒤돌아보니 <br><br>무언가 잃어버린 미련의 아쉬움이 <br>아직도 가슴에 남아있네 <br><br>인생이란 행복과 불행 <br>운명이라 생각하면서 <br><br>저마다 아픈 사연을 안고 <br>내일 위해 잊고 살지만 <br><br>아아아 꿈과 사랑 찾아 오늘도 <br>세상 파도 속으로 떠나네 <br><br>*인생이란 울다가 웃고 <br>알 수 없는 미로인 것을 <br><br>저마다 아픈 사연을 안고 <br>내일 위해 잊고 살지만 <br><br>아아아 꿈과 사랑 찾아 오늘도 <br>세상 파도 속으로 떠나네 <br><br>세상 파도 속으로 떠나네 <br>]]></content><category term="초아강" label="초아강"/><category term="꿈과 사랑(디스코)" label="꿈과 사랑(디스코)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초아강/야속한세월/</id><title>초아강 - 야속한세월 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:04:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:04:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%95%84%EA%B0%95/%EC%95%BC%EC%86%8D%ED%95%9C%EC%84%B8%EC%9B%94/" title="초아강 - 야속한세월 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비단길보다 더 아름다운 이 세상에 <br>끌려가지 않으려 발버둥 쳐도 몸부림 쳐도 <br><br>세월이란 이름 앞에 멈출 수가 없더라 <br>강물 따라 흘러온 구름 따라 흘러간 <br><br>종착역 없는 인생 가지 말라고 붙잡아 봐도 <br>소용없는 무정하고 야속한 세월아 <br><br>멈추지 않는 세월아 나 여기 있을게 <br>혼자 가라 세월아 먼저 가라 세월아 <br>]]></content><category term="초아강" label="초아강"/><category term="야속한세월" label="야속한세월"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초아강/연미애/</id><title>초아강 - 연미애 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:04:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:04:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%95%84%EA%B0%95/%EC%97%B0%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%A0/" title="초아강 - 연미애 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[연미애 <br><br>작사 강정숙 <br>작곡 한동한 <br>원곡 가수 이우희 <br><br>호숫가에 퍼지는 아름다운 햇살처럼 <br>꺼져가는 촛불에 숨결을 불어 넣어준 <br>사랑하는 내 당신 둘도 없는 내 당신 <br>보석보다 더 귀한 소중한 당신 <br>오늘이라는 선물에 감사하며 <br>지나치지조 않고 모자람도 없이 <br>사랑하다 눈 감는 그 날 까지 <br>행복 했노라 말 할 수 있는 그런 사랑 엮어 갑시다 <br><br>호숫가에 퍼지는 아름다운 햇살처럼 <br>꺼져가는 촛불에 숨결을 불어 넣어준 <br>사랑하는 내 당신 둘도 없는 내 당신 <br>보석보다 더 귀한 소중한 당신 <br>오늘이라는 선물에 감사하며 <br>지나치지조 않고 모자람도 없이 <br>사랑하다 눈 감는 그 날 까지 <br>행복 했노라 말 할 수 있는 그런 사랑 엮어 갑시다 <br>행복 했노라 말 할 수 있는 그런 사랑 엮어 갑시다 <br>]]></content><category term="초아강" label="초아강"/><category term="연미애" label="연미애"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초아강/은비령/</id><title>초아강 - 은비령 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:04:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:04:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%95%84%EA%B0%95/%EC%9D%80%EB%B9%84%EB%A0%B9/" title="초아강 - 은비령 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이루지 못할 사랑도 <br>사랑해선 안될 사랑도 <br>눈물과 기쁨이 넘나드는 <br>영원한 운명의 시계추처럼 <br>마음속의 소금 짐 벗어 던지고 <br>눈 내리는 은비령에 나는 서있네 <br><br>시간아 멈춰달라고 <br>애타는 이 내 마음 <br><br>은비령아 은비령아 <br>너만은 알고 있겠지 <br>나만은 알고 있겠지 <br><br>*은비령아 은비령아 <br>너만은 알고 있겠지 <br>나만은 알고 있겠지]]></content><category term="초아강" label="초아강"/><category term="은비령" label="은비령"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초아강/백일홍/</id><title>초아강 - 백일홍 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:04:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:04:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%95%84%EA%B0%95/%EB%B0%B1%EC%9D%BC%ED%99%8D/" title="초아강 - 백일홍 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑 찾아 돌아온다던 <br>당신을 기다렸어요 <br>순결한 여자 가슴 불태워 놓고 <br><br>화관 단장하고 절벽 위에 걸터앉아 <br>새 하얀 그리움이 붉은 빛 되어 <br><br>애련한 그 사랑에 가슴이 아파 <br>멀고 먼 산 바라기 되어 웁니다. <br><br>*애련한 그 사랑에 가슴이 아파 <br>멀고 먼 산 바라기 되어 웁니다]]></content><category term="초아강" label="초아강"/><category term="백일홍" label="백일홍"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초아강/실없는_약속/</id><title>초아강 - 실없는 약속 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T11:04:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T11:04:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%95%84%EA%B0%95/%EC%8B%A4%EC%97%86%EB%8A%94_%EC%95%BD%EC%86%8D/" title="초아강 - 실없는 약속 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 세상 끝나는 날까지 <br>영원토록 함께 하자던 <br>사랑의 맹세 잊어버리고 <br><br>야속하게 떠난 그 사람 <br>허물어져가는 이 내 가슴 <br>첫 눈이 오면 돌아 오려나 <br><br>진달래 붉게 피면 돌아 오려나 <br>실없는 약속이면 하지를 말던지 <br><br>어차피 떠날 거면 미움도 가져가지 <br>아~오늘도 이 비를 맞으며 <br><br>하염없이 거니는 발길 <br><br>*아~ 오늘도 이 비를 맞으며 <br>하염없이 거니는 발길 <br>]]></content><category term="초아강" label="초아강"/><category term="실없는 약속" label="실없는 약속"/></entry></feed>