<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:41:34+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Toothless/Palms_Backside_Feat_Marika_Hackman/</id><title>Toothless - Palm`s Backside (Feat. Marika Hackman) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:41:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:41:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Toothless/Palms_Backside_Feat_Marika_Hackman/" title="Toothless - Palm`s Backside (Feat. Marika Hackman) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A table for one set for two <br>And there's a new face beside you <br>And you look happier <br>Than we ever were <br><br>Out for the night <br>You know you've got nothing to hide <br>He looks alright <br>I know you like my palm's backside <br><br>And you look happier <br>Than we ever were <br>And you look happier <br>Than we ever were <br>And you look happier <br>Than we ever were <br><br>Well monkey see, monkey do <br>I'll find a new start <br>Walk a new avenue <br>I'll find a new heart <br><br>The thicker the skin <br>The harder to tell that inside <br>I'm made of tin <br>You know me like your palm's backside <br><br>And you look happier And I look happier <br>Than we ever were Than we ever were <br><br>Look over your shoulder <br>I'm getting older <br>It's just a placeholder <br>An arm on my shoulder <br><br>And you look happier <br><br>Look over your shoulder <br>I'm getting older <br>It's just a placeholder <br>An arm on my shoulder <br><br>Look over your shoulder <br>I'm getting older <br>It's just a placeholder <br>An arm on my shoulder <br><br>Look over your shoulder <br>I'm getting older <br>It's just a placeholder <br>An arm on my shoulder <br>I'll find a new heart <br><br>Well monkey see, monkey do <br>I'll find a new start <br>Walk a new avenue <br>I'll find a new heart]]></content><category term="Toothless" label="Toothless"/><category term="Palm`s Backside (Feat. Marika Hackman)" label="Palm`s Backside (Feat. Marika Hackman)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Toothless/Charon/</id><title>Toothless - Charon - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:41:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:41:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Toothless/Charon/" title="Toothless - Charon - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If only I knew where you grew <br>If only the sea had been planted through <br>My future outline, yet I'm walking blind <br>Just like the sun of our wave we call cool <br><br>Dust lean into the light <br>Now row Charon, row Charon, row <br>Dust lean into the light <br>Now row Charon, row Charon, row <br>Row, row, row, row <br><br>If only I knew where you grew <br>If only the sea had been planted through <br>You've grown on me girl from sand to a pearl <br>Those formative years were so hard to get through <br><br>Just lean into the light <br>Now row Charon, row Charon, row <br>Just lean into the light <br>Now row Charon, row Charon, row <br>Row, row, row, row]]></content><category term="Toothless" label="Toothless"/><category term="Charon" label="Charon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/썬셋파크_Sunset_Park/UI_Feat_민아_광수/</id><title>썬셋파크 (Sunset Park) - U&amp;I (Feat. 민아, 광수) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:42:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:42:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8D%AC%EC%85%8B%ED%8C%8C%ED%81%AC_Sunset_Park/UI_Feat_%EB%AF%BC%EC%95%84_%EA%B4%91%EC%88%98/" title="썬셋파크 (Sunset Park) - U&amp;I (Feat. 민아, 광수) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무말도 하지 말자 우리 둘 <br>그저 지쳐있는 것 뿐야 <br>이젠 알것같아 너와 나 <br>지금도 힘들어 <br>멀게만 느껴지는 둘 사이 <br>우리 사이 답을 찾아야겠지 <br>넌 나를 생각하는지 <br>우린 너무 달라서 서툰 사랑에 <br>지쳐 안아줄수가 없어서 <br>거짓말이라도 난 좋아 <br>네가 원하는걸 말해 뭐든지 <br>다 괜찮으니깐 <br>이젠 알것같아 너 <br>내게 미련조차 없는걸 <br>다시 사랑할거라 다짐하면서 <br>뒤돌아서 울고있겠지 <br>나 혼자서 난 너없이는 <br>멀게만 느껴지는 둘 사이 <br>우린 서로 다른 답을 찾겠지 <br>넌 나를 생각하는지 <br>우린 너무 달라서 서툰 사랑에 <br>지쳐 안아줄 수가 없어서 <br>거짓말이라도 난 좋아 <br>네가 원하는 걸 말해 뭐든지 <br>다 괜찮으니깐 <br>너와 얘길하고 싶은데 <br>멀어지는 뒷모습 <br>난 볼 수 밖에 없어 <br>네가 보고싶다고 <br>넌 여기 내옆에 없는데 <br>우린 한번을 더 볼수록 <br>헛된 바램에 서로 <br>욕심내고 마는건지 <br>나는 너를 사랑하지만 <br>엉켜버린 이 맘이 힘들어 <br>이젠 뭘 어떡해야해 <br>너는 지금 어떤 맘일까 <br>다시 사랑을 할까 <br>]]></content><category term="썬셋파크 (Sunset Park)" label="썬셋파크 (Sunset Park)"/><category term="U&amp;I (Feat. 민아, 광수)" label="U&amp;I (Feat. 민아, 광수)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이향유/고온/</id><title>이향유 - 고온 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:44:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:44:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%96%A5%EC%9C%A0/%EA%B3%A0%EC%98%A8/" title="이향유 - 고온 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[서늘한 온도 쌀쌀한 기운 <br>꿉꿉해진 방 안에 온긴 없고 <br>움츠린 몸과 쓸쓸한 식탁 <br>멈춰버린 시계는 비틀대 <br>하나 둘 피어나는 <br>창 밖의 꽃들은 <br>내게 선 찾을 수 없는 <br>뜨거움이 있을 거야 <br>기다림 속엔 자윤 없나 봐 <br>아쉬움이 나를 더 아프게 해 <br>나아가야 해 움직여야겠지 <br>다시 뜨겁게 <br>This can't go on <br>참 아름다웠던 둘만의 동화 <br>차가워진 그림 <br>이제는 더 이상 꺼내지 않을 <br>오랜 앨범처럼 <br>달아오른 몸이 식기 전까지 <br>계속 달려가 <br>Go on <br>이제는 더 이상 꺼내지 않을 <br>오랜 앨범처럼 <br>내 몸의 온도 뜨거운 기분 <br>두근대는 조금은 홀가분한 <br>마음속 떨림 이상한 기분 <br>찬 바람에 맺힌 따뜻한 <br>햇살이 날 조명하고 <br>바람은 느려져 <br>차갑던 내 뺨의 온돈 <br>따뜻하게 녹아내려 <br>]]></content><category term="이향유" label="이향유"/><category term="고온" label="고온"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ben_Platt/Finale/</id><title>Ben Platt - Finale - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:47:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:47:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ben_Platt/Finale/" title="Ben Platt - Finale - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Evan Hansen,？ <br>Today is going to be a good day. <br>And here's why: because today, <br>today at least you're you and―that's enough.？ <br><br>All we see is sky for forever <br>We let the world pass by for forever <br>Feels like we could go on for forever this way <br>This way <br><br>All we see is light <br>Watch the sun burn bright <br>We could be alright for forever <br>This way <br><br>All we see is sky for forever <br><br>All I see is sky for forever]]></content><category term="Ben Platt" label="Ben Platt"/><category term="Finale" label="Finale"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rachel_Bay_Jones/So_Big___So_Small/</id><title>Rachel Bay Jones - So Big / So Small - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:47:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:47:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rachel_Bay_Jones/So_Big___So_Small/" title="Rachel Bay Jones - So Big / So Small - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It was a February day <br>When your dad came by before going away <br>A U-Haul truck in the driveway <br>The day was suddenly real <br><br>I told you not to come outside <br>But you saw that truck <br>And you smiled so wide <br>A real live truck in your driveway <br>We let you sit behind the wheel <br><br>Good-bye, good-bye <br>Now it's just me and my little guy <br>And the house felt so big, and I felt so small <br>The house felt so big, and I felt so small <br><br>That night I tucked you into bed <br>I will never forget how you sat up and said <br>"Is there another truck coming to our driveway <br>A truck that will take mommy away” <br><br>And the house felt so big, and I felt so small <br>The house felt so big, and I <br>And I knew there would be moments that I'd miss <br>And I knew <br>There would be space I couldn't fill <br>And I knew <br>I'd come up short a million different ways <br>And I did <br>And I do <br>And I will <br><br>But like that February day <br>I will take your hand, squeeze it tightly and say <br>There's not another truck in the driveway <br>Your mom isn't going anywhere <br>Your mom will stay right here <br>Your mom isn't going anywhere <br>Your mom will stay right here <br>No matter what <br>I'll be here <br><br>When it feels so big <br>'til it all feels so small <br>When it feels so big <br>'til it all feels so small <br>’Til it all feels so small]]></content><category term="Rachel Bay Jones" label="Rachel Bay Jones"/><category term="So Big / So Small" label="So Big / So Small"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ben_Platt/Words_Fail/</id><title>Ben Platt - Words Fail - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:47:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:47:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ben_Platt/Words_Fail/" title="Ben Platt - Words Fail - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I never meant to make it such a mess <br>I never thought that it would go this far <br>So I just stand here sorry <br>Searching for something to say <br>Something to say <br>Words fail, words fail <br>There's nothing I can say <br><br>I guess I thought I could be part of this <br>I never had this kind of thing before <br>I never had that perfect girl <br>Who somehow could see the good part of me <br><br>I never had the dad who stuck it out <br>No corny jokes or baseball gloves <br>No mom who just was there <br>'Cause mom was all that she had to be <br><br>That's not a worthy explanation <br>I know there is none <br>Nothing can make sense of all these things I've done <br><br>Words fail, words fail <br>There's nothing I can say <br>Except sometimes, you see everything you wanted <br>And sometimes, you see everything you wish you had <br>And it's right there, right there, right there <br>In front of you <br>And you want to believe it's true <br>So you... make it true <br>And you think maybe everybody wants it <br>And needs it... a little bit... too <br><br>This was just a sad invention <br>It wasn't real, I know <br>But we were happy <br>I guess I couldn't let that go <br>I guess I couldn't give that up <br>I guess I wanted to believe <br>'Cause if I just believe <br>Then I don't have to see what's really there <br><br>No, I'd rather pretend I'm something better than <br>These broken parts <br>Pretend I'm something other than <br>This mess that I am <br>'Cause then I don't have to look at it <br>And no one gets to look at it <br>No, no one can really see <br><br>'Cause I've learned to slam on the brake <br>Before I even turn the key <br>Before I make the mistake <br>Before I lead with the worst of me <br>I never let them see the worst of me <br><br>'Cause what if everyone saw? <br>What if everyone knew? <br>Would they like what they saw? <br>Or would they hate it too? <br>Will I just keep on running away from what's true? <br><br>All I ever do is run <br>So how do I step in <br>Step into the sun? <br>Step into the sun]]></content><category term="Ben Platt" label="Ben Platt"/><category term="Words Fail" label="Words Fail"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rachel_Bay_Jones/Good_For_You/</id><title>Rachel Bay Jones - Good For You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:47:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:47:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rachel_Bay_Jones/Good_For_You/" title="Rachel Bay Jones - Good For You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So you found a place where the grass is greener <br>And you jumped the fence to the other side <br>Is it good? <br>Are they giving you a world I could never provide? <br><br>Well I hope you're proud of your big decision <br>Yeah, I hope it's all that you want and more <br>Now you're free from the agonizing life you were living before <br><br>And you say what you need to say <br>So that you get to walk away <br>It would kill you to have to stay trapped <br>When you've got something new <br>Well I'm sorry you had it rough <br>And I'm sorry I'm not enough <br>Thank God they rescued you <br><br>So you got what you always wanted <br>So you got your dream come true <br>Good for you <br>Good for you, you , you <br>Got a taste of a life so perfect <br>So you did what you had to do <br>Good for you <br>Good for you <br><br>Why did Connor kill himself? <br><br>Wait what? <br><br>He was doing better <br>That's what he told you in every single email <br>and then a month later he kills himself? <br>How does that make sense? <br><br>Why are you so obsessed with this? <br>You didn't even know him <br><br>Because it's important! <br><br>Because he was your lab partner? <br>Or because, I don't know <br>Maybe because you want to add another extracurricular for your college application <br><br>Because I know what it's like to feel invisible, just like Connor! <br>To feel invisible and alone and like nobody would even notice if you vanished into thin air <br>I bet you used to know what that felt like, too! <br><br>We need more emails <br>Emails showing that he was getting worse <br>This isn't funny! <br><br>Oh I think it's hilarious! <br>I think everyone would probably think it's hilarious <br><br>What is that supposed to mean? <br><br>It means you should remember who your friends are <br><br>I thought the only reason you even talk to me is because of your car insurance? <br><br>So? <br><br>So? Maybe the only reason you talk to me, <br>Jared, is because you don't have any other friends! <br><br>I could tell everyone everything! <br><br>Great! Go ahead, do it! <br>Tell everyone how you helped write emails pretending to be a kid who killed himself. <br><br>Fuck you, Evan! Asshole <br><br>Does it cross your mind to be slightly sorry? <br>Do you even care that you might be wrong? <br>Was it fun? <br>Well I hope you had a blast while you dragged me along <br><br>And you say what you need to say <br>And you play who you need to play <br>And if somebody's in your way <br>Crush them and leave them behind <br><br>Well, I guess if I'm not of use <br>Go ahead you can cut me loose <br>Go ahead now <br>I won't mind <br><br>I'll shut my mouth and I'll let you go <br>Is that good for you? <br>Would that be good for you you you? <br><br>I'll just sit back while you run the show <br>Is that good for you? <br>Would that be good for you you you? <br><br>I'll shut my mouth and I'll let you go <br>Is that good for you? <br>Would that be good for you you you? <br>I'll just sit back while you run the show <br>Is that good for you? <br>Good for you <br><br>All I need is some time to think <br>But the boat is about to sink <br>Can't erase what I wrote and link <br>Tell me how could you change the story? <br>All the words that I can't take back <br>Like a train coming off the track <br>Cause the rails and my bones all crack <br>I've got to find a way to <br>Stop it, stop it! Just let me off! <br><br>So you got what you always wanted <br>So you got your dream come true <br>Good for you <br>Good for you, you , you <br>Got a taste of a life so perfect <br>Now you say that you're someone new <br>Good for you <br>Good for you <br>Good for you <br>Good for you <br><br>So you got what you always wanted]]></content><category term="Rachel Bay Jones" label="Rachel Bay Jones"/><category term="Good For You" label="Good For You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Dreyfuss/Only_Us/</id><title>Laura Dreyfuss - Only Us - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:47:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:47:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Dreyfuss/Only_Us/" title="Laura Dreyfuss - Only Us - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't need you to sell me on reasons to want you <br>I don't need you to search for the proof that I should <br>You don't have to convince me <br>You don't have to be scared you're not enough <br>'Cause what we've got going is good <br><br>I don't need more reminders of all that's been broken <br>I don't need you to fix what I'd rather forget <br>Clear the slate and start over <br>Try to quiet the noises in your head <br>We can't compete with all that <br><br>So what if it's us <br>What if it's us <br>And only us <br>And what came before won't count anymore or matter <br>Can we try that? <br><br>What if it's you <br>And what if it's me <br>And what if that's all that we need it to be <br>And the rest of the world falls away <br>What do you say? <br><br>I never thought there'd be someone like you who would want me <br><br>Well... <br><br>So I give you ten thousand reasons to not let me go <br>But if you really see me <br>If you like me for me and nothing else <br>Well, that's all that I've wanted for longer that you could possibly know <br><br>So it can be us <br>It can be us <br>And only us <br>And what came before won't count anymore or matter <br>We can try that <br><br>It's not so impossible <br><br>Nobody else but the two of us here <br><br>'Cause you're saying it's possible <br><br>We can just watch the whole world disappear <br><br>'Til you're the only one I still know how to see <br><br>It's just you and me <br><br>It'll be us <br>It'll be us <br>And only us <br>And what came before won't count anymore <br><br>We can try that <br>You and me <br>That's all that we need it to be <br>And the rest of the world falls away <br>And the rest of the world falls away <br><br>The world falls away <br>The world falls away <br>And it's only us]]></content><category term="Laura Dreyfuss" label="Laura Dreyfuss"/><category term="Only Us" label="Only Us"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Park/To_Break_In_A_Glove/</id><title>Michael Park - To Break In A Glove - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:47:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:47:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Park/To_Break_In_A_Glove/" title="Michael Park - To Break In A Glove - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This glove's really cool, wow. <br><br>Oh, why don't you take it <br><br>Oh. No, no, I couldn't. <br><br>Why not <br><br>Are you sure <br><br>I bought this glove a thousand years ago <br>For some birthday or some Christmas that has come and gone <br>I thought we might play catch or... I don't know <br>But he left it in the bag, with the tag still on <br><br>You'll have to break it in though, first. <br>You can't catch anything with it that stiff. <br><br>How do you break it in <br><br>Well, it's all a process that is really quite precise <br>A sort of secret method known to very few <br>So, if you're in the market for professional advice <br>Well today could be a lucky day for you <br><br>Shaving cream. <br><br>Shaving cream <br><br>Oh yeah. You rub that in for about five minutes, <br>tie it all up with rubber bands, <br>put it under your mattress, and sleep on it. <br>And you do that for at least a week, every day, consistent. <br><br>And though this method isn't easy <br>Every second that you spend is gonna pay off <br>It'll pay off in the end <br><br>It just takes a little patience <br>It takes a little time <br>A little perseverance <br>And a little uphill climb <br><br>You might not think it's worth it <br>You might begin to doubt <br>But you can't take any shortcuts <br>You gotta stick it out <br><br>And it's the hard way <br>But it's the right way <br>The right way... to break in a glove <br><br>With something like this, <br>you gotta be ready to put in the work, <br>make the commitment. So what do you think <br><br>I mean, definitely. <br><br>Some people say just use a microwave <br>Or try that "run it through hot water" technique <br>Well, they can gloat about the time they saved <br>'Til they gotta buy another glove next week <br><br>It just takes a little patience <br><br>It takes a little patience <br><br>Takes a little time <br><br>A little perseverance <br><br>And a little uphill climb <br><br>And it's the hard way <br>But it's the right way <br>The right way... <br><br>'Cause there's a right way in everything you do <br><br>Keep that grit <br>Follow through <br><br>Even when everyone around you thinks you're crazy <br>Even when everyone around you lets things go <br>And whether you're prepping for some test <br>Or you're miles from some goal <br>Or you're just trying to do what's best <br>For a kid who's lost control <br><br>You do the hard thing <br>'Cause that's the right thing <br>Yeah, that's the right thing <br><br>Connor was really lucky to have a dad that... uh, <br>a dad who cared so much about... taking care of stuff. <br><br>Shaving cream, rubber bands, mattress, repeat. <br>Got it <br><br>Got it. <br><br>It's the hard way <br><br>But it's the right way <br><br>The right way <br>To break in a glove <br><br>You're good to go.]]></content><category term="Michael Park" label="Michael Park"/><category term="To Break In A Glove" label="To Break In A Glove"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ben_Platt/You_Will_Be_Found/</id><title>Ben Platt - You Will Be Found - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:47:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:47:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ben_Platt/You_Will_Be_Found/" title="Ben Platt - You Will Be Found - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever felt like nobody was there <br>Have you felt forgotten in the middle of nowhere <br>Have you ever felt like you could disappear <br>Like you could fall and no one would hear <br><br>Well, let that lonely feeling wash away <br>Maybe there's a reason to believe you'll be okay <br>Cause when you don't feel strong enough to stand <br>You can reach, reach out your hand <br><br>And oh, someone will come running <br>And I know they'll take you home <br><br>Even when the dark comes crashing through <br>When you need a friend to carry you <br>And when you're broken on the ground <br>You will be found <br><br>So let the sun come streaming in <br>Cause you'll reach up and you'll rise again <br>Lift your head and look around <br>You will be found <br>You will be found <br>You will be found <br>You will be found <br>You will be found <br><br>Have you seen this? <br>Someone put a video of your speech online. <br><br>My speech? <br><br>People started sharing it I guess <br>And now, I mean Connor is everywhere. <br><br>Your speech is everywhere <br>This morning, The Connor Project page it only had fifty-six people following it. <br><br>Well, how many does it have now? <br><br>Four thousand five hundred eighty two <br>Sixteen thousand two hundred and thirty nine <br><br>I don't understand? <br>What happened? <br><br>You did! <br><br>There's a place where we don't have to feel unknown <br>And every time that you call out <br>You're a little less alone <br><br>If you only say the word <br>From across the silence <br>Your voice is heard <br><br>Even when the dark comes crashing through <br>When you need a friend to carry you <br>When you're broken on the ground <br>You will be found <br><br>So let the sun come streaming in <br>Cause you'll reach up and you'll rise again <br>If you only look around <br>You will be found <br>You will be found <br>You will be found <br>You will be found <br>You will be found <br><br>Out of the shadows <br>The morning is breaking <br>And all is new <br>All is new <br><br>It's feeling awfully empty <br>And suddenly I see <br>That all is new <br>All is new <br><br>You are not alone <br>You are not alone <br>You are not alone <br>You are not alone <br><br>You are not alone <br>You are not alone <br>You are not <br>You are not alone <br><br>Even when the dark comes crashing through <br>When you need someone to carry you <br>When you're broken on the ground <br><br>You will be found <br>So let the sun come streaming in <br>Cause you'll reach up and you'll rise again <br>If you only look around <br>You will be found <br><br>Even when the dark comes crashing through <br>You will be found <br>When you need someone to carry you <br>You will be found <br>You will be found <br>You will be found]]></content><category term="Ben Platt" label="Ben Platt"/><category term="You Will Be Found" label="You Will Be Found"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mike_Faist/Disappear/</id><title>Mike Faist - Disappear - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:47:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:47:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mike_Faist/Disappear/" title="Mike Faist - Disappear - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Guys like you and me <br>We're just the losers <br>And we keep waiting to be seen, right? <br>And no one seems to care <br>Or stops to notice that we're there <br>So we get lost in the in between <br><br>But if you can somehow keep them thinking of me <br>And make me more than an abandoned memory <br>That means we matter too <br>It means someone will see that you are there <br><br>No one deserves to be forgotten <br>No one deserves to fade away <br>No one should come and go <br>And have no one know he was ever even here <br>No one deserves to disappear <br>To disappear <br>Disappear <br><br>It's true <br>But even if you've always been that <br>Barely in the background kind of guy <br><br>You still matter <br><br>And even if you're somebody who can't escape the feeling <br>that the world's past you by <br><br>You still matter <br><br>If you never get around to doing some remarkable thing <br>That doesn't mean that you're not worth remembering <br>But the people who need to know <br><br>They need to know <br><br>You need to know <br><br>I'll show them <br><br>That no one deserves to be forgotten <br><br>No one deserves to be forgotten <br>No one deserves to fade away, to fade away <br><br>No one should flicker out <br>Or have any doubt that it matters that they are here <br><br>No one deserves <br><br>No one deserves <br><br>To disappear, to disappear, to disappear <br><br>When you're falling in a forest and there's nobody around <br>All you want is somebody to find you <br>When you're falling in a forest <br>And when you hit the ground <br>All you need is somebody to find you <br><br>No one deserves to be forgotten <br><br>No one deserves to fade away <br><br>No one deserves to be forgotten <br><br>No one deserves to be forgotten <br>No one should flicker out or have any doubt <br>That it matters that they are here <br><br>No one deserves to disappear <br>To disappear <br>To Disappear <br>No one deserves, no one deserves, no one deserves to be forgotten <br>No one deserves to disappear <br>Disappear]]></content><category term="Mike Faist" label="Mike Faist"/><category term="Disappear" label="Disappear"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ben_Platt/If_I_Could_Tell_Her/</id><title>Ben Platt - If I Could Tell Her - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:47:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:47:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ben_Platt/If_I_Could_Tell_Her/" title="Ben Platt - If I Could Tell Her - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[He said <br>There's nothing like your smile <br>Sort of subtle and perfect and real <br>He said <br>You never knew how wonderful <br>That smile could make someone feel <br><br>And he knew <br>Whenever you get bored <br>You scribble stars on the cuffs of your jeans <br>And he noticed <br>That you still fill out the quizzes <br>that they put in those teen magazines <br><br>But he kept it all inside his head <br>What he saw he left unsaid <br>And though he wanted to <br>He couldn't talk to you <br>He couldn't find the way <br>But he would always say <br><br>If I could tell her <br>Tell her everything I see <br>If I could tell her <br>How she's everything to me <br>But we're a million worlds apart <br>And I don't know how I would even start <br>If I could tell her <br>If I could tell her <br><br>Did he say anything else? <br><br>About you? <br><br>Never mind, I don't really care <br><br>No, no, no, he said so many things, <br>I'm just trying to remember the best ones. <br><br>He thought <br>You looked really pretty, er- <br>It looked pretty cool when you put indigo streaks in your hair <br><br>He did?! <br><br>And he wondered how you learned to dance <br>Like all the rest of the world isn't there <br><br>But he kept it all inside his head <br>What he saw he left unsaid <br><br>If I could tell her <br>Tell her everything I see <br>If I could tell her <br>How she's everything to me <br><br>But we're a million worlds apart <br><br>And I don't know how I would even start if I could tell her <br><br>If I could tell her <br>But what do you do <br>When there's this great divide <br><br>He just seemed so far away <br><br>And what do you do <br>When the distance is too wide <br><br>I think I don't know anything <br><br>And how do you say I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you <br><br>But we're a million worlds apart <br>And I don't know how I would even start <br>If I could tell her <br>If I could]]></content><category term="Ben Platt" label="Ben Platt"/><category term="If I Could Tell Her" label="If I Could Tell Her"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Dreyfuss/Requiem/</id><title>Laura Dreyfuss - Requiem - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:47:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:47:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Dreyfuss/Requiem/" title="Laura Dreyfuss - Requiem - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Why should I play this game of pretend? <br>Remembering through a secondhand sorrow? <br>Such a great son and wonderful friend <br>Oh don't the tears just pour <br><br>I can curl up and hide in my room <br>There in my bed still sobbing tomorrow <br>I could give in to all of the gloom <br>But tell me, tell me what for <br><br>Why should I have a heavy heart? <br>Why should I start to break in pieces? <br>Why should I go and fall apart for you? <br><br>Why should I play the grieving girl and <br>Lie saying that I miss you <br>And that my world has gone dark without your light <br>I will sing no requiem tonight <br><br>I'm going to bed <br><br>Come sit with me <br><br>Cynthia <br><br>For five minutes? <br><br>I'm exhausted <br><br>You know Larry, at some point you're going to have to start- <br><br>Not tonight. Please. I'll leave the light on for you. <br><br>I gave you the world, you threw it away, <br>Leaving these broken pieces behind you <br>Everything wasted, nothing to say <br>So I can sing no requiem <br><br>I hear your voice, feel you near <br>Within these words I finally find you <br>And now that I know that you are still here <br>I will sing no requiem tonight <br><br>Why should I have a heavy heart? <br><br>Why should I say I'll keep you with me? <br>Why should I go and fall apart for you? <br>Why should I play the grieving girl and lie saying that I miss you <br>And that my world has gone dark without your light <br>I will sing no requiem <br>Tonight <br>'Cuz when the villains fall, the kingdoms never weep <br>No one lights a candle to remember <br>No, no one mourns at all <br>They lay them down to sleep <br>So don't tell me that I didn't have it right <br>Don't tell me that it wasn't black and white <br>After all you've put me through, don't say it wasn't true <br>That you were not the monster that I knew, <br>'Cuz I cannot play the grieving girl and lie <br>Saying that I miss you and that my world has gone dark <br><br>I will sing no requiem <br><br>I will sing no requiem <br><br>I will sing no requiem tonight]]></content><category term="Laura Dreyfuss" label="Laura Dreyfuss"/><category term="Requiem" label="Requiem"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mike_Faist/Sincerely_Me/</id><title>Mike Faist - Sincerely, Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:47:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:47:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mike_Faist/Sincerely_Me/" title="Mike Faist - Sincerely, Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Evan Hansen, <br>We've been way too out of touch <br>Things have been crazy and it sucks that we don't talk that much <br>I should tell you that I think of you each night <br>I rub my nipples and start moaning with delight <br><br>Why would you write that? <br><br>I'm just trying to tell the truth <br><br>You know what? If you aren't going to take this seriously... <br><br>Okay you need to calm yourself! <br><br>This has to be perfect, okay? <br>The emails have to prove that we were actually friends. <br>They've got to be completely realistic <br><br>There is nothing unrealistic about the love that one man feels for another. <br><br>Let's go back. <br><br>In fact, it's something quite beautiful. <br><br>Let's go back Jared! <br><br>I've gotta tell you life without you has been hard <br><br>Hard? <br><br>Has been bad <br><br>Bad? <br><br>Has been rough <br><br>Kinky! <br><br>And I miss talking about life and other stuff <br><br>Very specific <br><br>Shut up <br><br>I like my parents <br><br>Who says that? <br><br>I love my parents <br>But each day's another fight <br>If I stop smoking drugs then everything might be alright <br><br>Smoking drugs <br><br>Just fix it! <br><br>This isn't realistic at all! It doesn't even sound like Connor! <br><br>Well I want to show that I was a good friend, <br>Y'know? That I was trying to help him <br><br>You are just cute as a freaking button <br><br>If I stop smoking crack <br><br>Crack?! <br><br>If I stop smoking pot then everything might be alright <br>I'll take your advice <br>I'll try to be more nice <br>I'll turn it around <br>Wait and see <br><br>It’s all that it takes <br>Is a little reinvention <br>It’s easy to change if you give it your attention <br>All you gotta do is just believe you can be who you want <br>to be sincerely, me <br><br>Are we done yet? <br><br>Well I mean I can't just show them one email <br><br>Okay, please stop hyperventilating <br><br>I'm not hyperventilating <br><br>You're having considerable trouble breathing <br><br>I'm having no trouble breathing <br><br>Do you need a paper bag to breath into? <br><br>I'm not hyperventilating! <br><br>Dear Connor Murphy, <br>Yes I've also missed our talks <br>Stop doing drugs <br>Just try to take deep breaths and go on walks <br><br>I'm sending pictures of the most amazing trees <br><br>No! <br><br>You'll be obsessed with all my forest expertise <br><br>Ridiculous! <br><br>Dude I'm proud of you <br>Just keep pushing through <br>You're turning around <br>I can see <br><br>Just wait and see <br><br>It’s all that it takes <br>Is a little reinvention <br>It’s easy to change if you give it your attention <br>All you gotta do is just believe you can be who you want to be sincerely, me <br><br>My sister's hot <br><br>What the hell? <br><br>My bad <br><br>Dear Evan Hansen, thanks for every note you send <br><br>Dear Connor Murphy, I'm just glad to be your friend <br><br>Our friendship goes beyond your average kind of bond <br><br>But not because we're Gay <br>No not because we're gay <br>We're close, but not that way <br>The only man that I love is my dad <br><br>Well anyway <br><br>You're getting better everyday <br><br>I'm getting better everyday <br><br>We're getting better everyday <br><br>Hey hey hey hey! <br><br>It’s all that it takes <br>Is a little reinvention <br>It’s easy to change if you give it your attention <br>All you gotta do is just believe you can be who you want to be sincerely, <br><br>Miss you dearly <br><br>Sincerely Me <br>Sincerely Me <br>Sincerely Me <br>Sincerely Me]]></content><category term="Mike Faist" label="Mike Faist"/><category term="Sincerely, Me" label="Sincerely, Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ben_Platt/For_Forever/</id><title>Ben Platt - For Forever - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:47:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:47:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ben_Platt/For_Forever/" title="Ben Platt - For Forever - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[End of May or Early June <br>This picture perfect afternoon we shared <br>Drive the winding country road <br>Grab a scoop at A La Mode <br>And then we're there <br><br>An open field that's framed with trees <br>We pick a spot and shoot the breeze <br>Like buddies do <br><br>Quoting songs by our favorite bands <br>Telling jokes no one understands <br>Except us two <br>And we talk and take in the view <br><br>All we see is sky for forever <br>Let the world pass by for forever <br>Feels like we could go on for forever this way <br>Two friends on a perfect day <br><br>We walk a while and we talk about <br>The things we'll do when we get out of school <br>Bike the Appalachian trail or <br>Write a book <br>Or learn to sail <br>Wouldn't that be cool <br><br>There's nothing that we can't discuss <br>Like girls we wish would notice us but never do <br>He looks around and says to me <br>"There's nowhere else I'd rather be" <br>I say "me too" <br><br>And we talk and take in the view <br>We just talk and take in the view <br><br>All we see is sky for forever <br>We let the world pass by for forever <br>Feels like we could go on for forever this way <br>This way <br><br>All we see is light for forever <br>'Cause the sun shines bright for forever <br>Life will be alright for forever this way <br>Two friends on a perfect day <br><br>And there he goes <br>Racing toward the tallest tree <br>From far across the yellow field I hear him calling "follow me" <br>And there we go <br>Wondering how the world might look from up so high <br><br>One foot after the other <br>One branch then to another <br>I climb higher and higher <br>I climb until the entire <br>Sun shines on my face <br><br>And I suddenly feel the branch give way <br>I'm on the ground <br>My arm goes numb <br>I look around <br>And I see him come to get me <br>He's come to get me <br>And everything's okay <br><br>All we see is sky for forever <br>We let the world pass by for forever <br>Buddy, you and I for forever this way <br>This way <br><br>All we see is light <br>'Cause the sun burns bright <br>We could be alright for forever this way <br>Two friends <br>True friends <br>On a perfect day]]></content><category term="Ben Platt" label="Ben Platt"/><category term="For Forever" label="For Forever"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ben_Platt/Waving_Through_A_Window/</id><title>Ben Platt - Waving Through A Window - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:47:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:47:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ben_Platt/Waving_Through_A_Window/" title="Ben Platt - Waving Through A Window - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've learned to slam on the brake <br>Before I even turn the key <br>Before I make the mistake <br>Before I lead with the worst of me <br>Give them no reason to stare <br>No slipping up if you slip away <br>So I've got nothing to share <br>No, I got nothing to say <br><br>Step out, step out of the sun <br>If you keep getting burned <br>Step out, step out of the sun <br>Because you've learned, because you've learned <br><br>On the outside always looking in <br>Will I ever be more than I've always been? <br>'cause I'm tap, tap, tapping on the glass <br>I'm waving through a window <br>I try to speak, but nobody can hear <br>So I wait around for an answer to appear <br><br>While I'm watch, watch, watching people pass <br>I'm waving through a window <br>Oh, can anybody see, is anybody waving <br>Back at me? <br><br>We start with stars in our eyes <br>We start believing that we belong <br>But every sun doesn't rise <br>And no one tells you where you went wrong <br><br>Step out, step out of the sun <br>If you keep getting burned <br>Step out, step out of the sun <br>Because you've learned, because you've learned <br><br>On the outside always looking in <br>Will I ever be more than I've always been? <br>'cause I'm tap, tap, tapping on the glass <br>Waving through a window <br>I try to speak, but nobody can hear <br>So I wait around for an answer to appear <br>While I'm watch, watch, watching people pass <br>Waving through a window <br>Oh, can anybody see, is anybody waving? <br><br>When you're falling in a forest and there's nobody around <br>Do you ever really crash, or even make a sound <br>When you're falling in a forest and there's nobody around <br>Do you ever really crash, or even make a sound <br>When you're falling in a forest and there's nobody around <br>Do you ever really crash, or even make a sound <br>When you're falling in a forest and there's nobody around <br>Do you ever really crash, or even make a sound <br>Did I even make a sound <br>Did I even make a sound <br>It's like I never made a sound <br>Will I ever make a sound? <br><br>On the outside always looking in <br>Will I ever be more than I've always been <br>'cause I'm tap, tap, tapping on the glass <br>Waving through a window <br>I try to speak <br>But nobody can hear <br>So I wait around for an answer to appear <br>While I'm watch, watch, watching people pass <br>Waving through a window <br>Can anybody see, is anybody waving back at me? <br>Oooh, is anybody waving <br>Waving, waving, whoa-oh, whoa-oh-oh-oh]]></content><category term="Ben Platt" label="Ben Platt"/><category term="Waving Through A Window" label="Waving Through A Window"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rachel_Bay_Jones/Anybody_Have_A_Map_/</id><title>Rachel Bay Jones - Anybody Have A Map? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:47:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:47:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rachel_Bay_Jones/Anybody_Have_A_Map_/" title="Rachel Bay Jones - Anybody Have A Map? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Have you been writing those letters to yourself <br>"Dear Evan Hansen <br>This is gonna be a good day and here's why" <br><br>I started one <br><br>Those letters are important, honey <br>They're gonna help you build your confidence! <br><br>I guess <br><br>Can we try to have an optimistic outlook, huh <br>Can we buck up just enough to see the world won't fall apart <br>Maybe this year we decide we're not giving up before we've tried <br>This year we make a new start <br><br>Hey, I know <br>You can go around and ask the other kids to sign your cast <br>How 'bout that <br><br>Perfect <br><br>I'm proud of you already <br><br>Oh... good <br><br>Another stellar conversation for the scrapbook <br>Another stumble as I'm reaching for the right thing to say <br>I'm kinda coming up empty <br>I can't find my way to you <br><br>Does anybody have a map <br>Anybody maybe happen to know how the hell to do this <br>I don't know if you can tell <br>But this is me just pretending to know <br>So where's the map <br>I need a clue <br>'Cause the scary truth is <br>I'm flyin' blind <br>I'm making this up as I go <br><br>It's your senior year, Connor <br>You are not missing the first day <br><br>I already said I'd go tomorrow <br><br>He doesn't listen <br>Look at him <br>He's probably high <br><br>He's definitely high <br><br>I don't want you going to school high, Connor <br><br>Perfect <br>So then I won't go <br>Thanks, mom! <br><br>Another masterful attempt ends with disaster <br><br>Interstate's already jammed <br><br>Pour another cup of coffee <br>And watch it all crash and burn <br><br>Connor finished the milk! <br><br>It's a puzzle <br>It's a maze <br>I've tried to steer through it a million ways <br>But each day is another wrong turn <br><br>I better head out <br><br>If Connor's not ready, I'm leaving without him <br><br>Does anybody have a map Anybody have a map <br>Anybody maybe happen to know how the hell to do this <br>I don't know if you can tell <br>But this is me just pretending to know <br><br>So where's the map <br><br>I need a clue <br><br>'Cause the scary truth is <br><br>I'm flyin' blind <br><br>I'm flyin' blind <br><br>I'm flyin' blind <br><br>I'm flyin' <br><br>I'm flyin' blind <br>And I'm making this up as I go <br>As I go]]></content><category term="Rachel Bay Jones" label="Rachel Bay Jones"/><category term="Anybody Have A Map?" label="Anybody Have A Map?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/매니악/BLACK_TEAR_Feat_이미쉘/</id><title>매니악 - BLACK TEAR (Feat. 이미쉘) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:48:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:48:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%A4%EB%8B%88%EC%95%85/BLACK_TEAR_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%EB%AF%B8%EC%89%98/" title="매니악 - BLACK TEAR (Feat. 이미쉘) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너와 다른 나는 <br>목소리가 달라 달라 달라 <br>그루브가 달라 달라 달라 <br>이제 볼륨을 키워 <br>내가 네 안에 들어가 <br>먼곳에서 왔지 <br>많은 변함을 봤지 <br>남과 다르다는걸 <br>애초부터 눈치깠지 <br>엄마는 아니라고 <br>ma daddy from Chicago <br>he was borm in Mississippi <br>mommy는 목포 전라도 <br>Thats a hell of a combo <br>머릿결도 곱슬에 <br>놀림도 받고 <br>난 안된단 소리가 싫어서 <br>싸워 합의도 못받고 <br>maniac도 부족해 <br>정신상탠 나가 <br>they call me a psyco <br>난 꼭 이겨내 <br>자랑스러운 nigga가 돼 <br>for the fam tho <br>I'm tryna stay strong <br>Through all the fake homiez <br>that hatin on me <br>다 기쁜척 하지만 배 아프지 <br>cuz I'm gettin this money <br>this ones for my daughter <br>so Imma grind harder <br>nobody can't stop me <br>너 피부도 papa처럼 짙어 <br>gurl so u cang live life sloppy <br>내가 잊으려 해도 떠올라 <br>내 심장에 박혀진 가시 <br>희망없이 살았지만 <br>널보고 힘내 <br>while moving with caution <br>I use my brain to help me <br>maintain tell me reach fame <br>I dun seen too many reach <br>this spot to turn <br>Kurt Cobain nigga <br>지금 네 귓가에 <br>들려오는 음악소리 <br>파고드는 내목소리 <br>너의 안에서 <br>마음속에 남게될거야 <br>오래 기억될거야 <br>날카로워진 나의 성격이 <br>안보이는 차별 <br>대학도 졸업했지만 <br>I can't teach a class <br>cuz I'm ain't a white boy <br>포기할수 없지 <br>그렇지만 I dun brought <br>out my temper <br>1 shot maniac <br>bruce banner trifecta <br>확실한 rap skill을 들고있어 <br>언젠가는 보겠지 <br>그 picture <br>작년만해도 it's too bad <br>I dissed ya <br>2016년 it's too bad <br>I dissed ya <br>raisin hell non stop <br>raise a toast to wonshot <br>남과 다르다는 한 이유로 <br>열정과 힘을 담어 <br>when I spit my flow now come on <br>들어와 나의 음악속으로 <br>깊이빠져봐 리듬속으로 <br>마치 다른 세계로 떠나듯 <br>마치 바닷속을 헤엄치듯 <br>빠져봐 나의 플로우속으로 <br>느껴봐 나의 노랫소리를 <br>마치 다른 나랄 여행하듯 <br>마치 하늘위를 날아가듯 <br>follow me <br>follow me <br>마치 여행을 하듯이 <br>I'm here you set you free <br>하늘을 위로 fly <br>바다를 헤엄치듯이 <br>follow me <br>follow me <br>마치 여행을 하듯이 <br>I'm here you set you free <br>하늘을 위로 fly <br>바다를 헤엄치듯이 <br>]]></content><category term="매니악" label="매니악"/><category term="BLACK TEAR (Feat. 이미쉘)" label="BLACK TEAR (Feat. 이미쉘)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Easton_Corbin/A_Girl_Like_You/</id><title>Easton Corbin - A Girl Like You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:49:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:49:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Easton_Corbin/A_Girl_Like_You/" title="Easton Corbin - A Girl Like You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Got lots of bars around this town <br>They got cold beer, yeah, and they got Crown <br>Got neon light in the windowpane <br>Got lots of guys thinkin' they got game <br>Got loud guitars a little out of tune <br>But they ain't got a girl like you <br>Naw, they don't <br><br>They play lots of songs on the radio <br>'Bout them good ole' country girls that we all know <br>Long tan legs and cutoff jeans <br>Yeah, just shakin' that sugar every country boy's dream <br>I've heard them all at least a time or two <br>Ain't none 'bout a girl like you, that's true <br><br>You've got that beautiful born with it kind of thing <br>It comes so natural, no baby don't ever change <br>And I wonder when I see the smile on your face <br>Baby, what did I do to ever get a girl like you <br>A girl like you <br><br>You can dress it on up or you can just hang out <br>Kick it on Broadway or kick back on the couch <br>You can dance on a bar, you can dance in the rain <br>Shotgun a beer, just sip champagne <br>Yeah, there's only one, ain't room for two <br>There ain't another girl like you, another girl like you <br><br>You've got that beautiful born with it kind of thing <br>It comes so natural, no baby don't ever change <br>And I wonder when I see the smile on your face <br>Baby, what did I do to ever get a girl like you <br>A girl like you <br><br>Baby, what did I do to get a girl like you <br><br>A girl like you don't come along but once in a lifetime, better hang on <br>I can't find one thing wrong, I could just go on and on and on <br><br>You've got that beautiful born with it kind of thing <br>It comes so natural, no baby don't ever change <br>And I wonder when I see the smile on your face <br>Baby, what did I do to ever get a girl like you <br>A girl like you <br><br>I could sail the ocean blue, and never find, never find a girl like you]]></content><category term="Easton Corbin" label="Easton Corbin"/><category term="A Girl Like You" label="A Girl Like You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Henry_Gallagher/24K_Magic/</id><title>Henry Gallagher - 24K Magic - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:49:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:49:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Henry_Gallagher/24K_Magic/" title="Henry Gallagher - 24K Magic - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tonight <br>I just want to take you higher <br>Throw your hands up in the sky <br>Let's set this party off right <br><br>Players, put yo' pinky rings up to the moon <br>Girls, what y'all trying to do <br>24 karat magic in the air <br>Head to toe so player <br>Uh, look out <br><br>Pop pop, it's show time Show time <br>Show time Show time <br>Guess who's back again <br>Oh they don't know Go on tell 'em <br>Oh they don't know Go on tell 'em <br>I bet they know soon as we walk in Showin' up <br>Wearing Cuban links ya <br>Designer minks ya <br>Inglewood's finest shoes Whoop, whoop <br>Don't look too hard <br>Might hurt ya'self <br>Known to give the color red the blues <br><br>Ooh shit, I'm a dangerous man with some money in my pocket <br>Keep up <br>So many pretty girls around me and they waking up the rocket <br>Keep up <br>Why you mad Fix ya face <br>Ain't my fault y'all be jocking <br>Keep up <br><br>Players only, come on <br>Put your pinky rings up to the moon <br>Girls, what y'all trying to do <br>24 karat magic in the air <br>Head to toe so player <br>Uh, look out <br><br>Second verse for the hustlas hustlas <br>Gangstas gangstas <br>Bad bitches and ya ugly ass friends Haha <br>Can I preach Uh oh Can I preach Uh oh <br>I gotta show 'em how a pimp get it in <br>First, take your sip sip, do your dip dip <br>Spend your money like money ain't shit Whoop, whoop <br>We too fresh <br>Got to blame it on Jesus <br>Hashtag blessed <br>They ain't ready for me <br><br>I'm a dangerous man with some money in my pocket <br>Keep up <br>So many pretty girls around me and they waking up the rocket <br>Keep up <br>Why you mad Fix ya face <br>Ain't my fault y'all be jocking <br>Keep up <br><br>Players only, come on <br>Put your pinky rings up to the moon <br>Hey girls <br>What y'all trying to do <br>24 karat magic in the air <br>Head to toe so player <br>Uh, look out <br><br>Wooh <br>Everywhere I go they be like <br>Ooh, so player ooh <br>Everywhere I go they be like <br>Ooh, so player ooh <br>Everywhere I go they be like <br>Ooh, so player ooh <br>Now, now, now <br>Watch me break it down like Uh <br>24 karat, 24 karat magic <br>What's that sound <br>24 karat, 24 karat magic <br>Come on now <br>24 karat, 24 karat magic <br>Don't fight the feeling <br>Invite the feeling <br><br>Just put your pinky rings up to the moon <br>Girls, what y'all trying to do <br>24 karat magic in the air <br>Head to toe so player <br>Put your pinky rings up to the moon <br>Girls, what y'all trying to do Do <br>24 karat magic in the air <br>Head to toe so player <br>24 karat <br>Uh, look out <br><br>24 karat magic, magic, magic]]></content><category term="Henry Gallagher" label="Henry Gallagher"/><category term="24K Magic" label="24K Magic"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피아_PIA/MY_BED_SLEEP_SLOW/</id><title>피아 (PIA) - MY BED (SLEEP SLOW) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:51:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:51:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EC%95%84_PIA/MY_BED_SLEEP_SLOW/" title="피아 (PIA) - MY BED (SLEEP SLOW) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[막다른 길에 멈춰 울며 떨었던 <br>어둡고 혼자임을 느낀 그때 <br>어디에도 따스함은 없었어 <br>겁에 질려 모든 게 두려웠고 <br>모든 게 떠나버릴 것 같아 <br>난 차마 난 손을 내밀 수도 없었어 <br>난 누굴까 나 어디로 갈까 <br>어디서 멈춰 서 있나 <br>나의 바다여 다시 꿈을 꾸는 <br>나에게 불 같은 축복을 <br>돌이킬 수도 없는 길을 택했던 <br>조금도 망설임 없던 무모했던 때 <br>내 곁엔 그 누구도 <br>그 누구도 없었어 <br>소리쳐도 지독한 <br>비웃음만 울릴 뿐 <br>나 내게 물어 왜일까 난 어딜까 <br>초라한 뒷모습만 남아 <br>난 누굴까 나 어디로 갈까 <br>어디서 멈춰 서 있나 <br>나의 바다여 다시 꿈을 꾸는 <br>나에게 불 같은 축복을 <br>다시 부딪혀 버려진다 해도 <br>나에게 못다한 다짐을 <br>나 어디로 갈까 <br>나 어디로 갈까 <br>나 어디로 갈까 <br>돌이킬 수도 없는 길을 택했던 <br>조금도 망설임 없던 무모했던 때 <br>내 곁에 그 누구도 <br>그 누구도 없었어 <br>나의 바다여 다시 꿈을 꾸는 <br>나에게 불 같은 축복을 <br>다시 부딪혀 버려진다 해도 <br>나에게 못다한 다짐을 <br>못다한 다짐을 <br>못다한 다짐을 <br>못다한 다짐을 <br>못다한 다짐을 <br>]]></content><category term="피아 (PIA)" label="피아 (PIA)"/><category term="MY BED (SLEEP SLOW)" label="MY BED (SLEEP SLOW)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피아_PIA/원숭이_RED_APE/</id><title>피아 (PIA) - 원숭이 (RED APE) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:51:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:51:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EC%95%84_PIA/%EC%9B%90%EC%88%AD%EC%9D%B4_RED_APE/" title="피아 (PIA) - 원숭이 (RED APE) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나만 기억해 난 기어서라도 널 <br>물고 늘어져 <br>치욕적인 그날 터질 것 같던 <br>그날같이 잊지 않고 돌려주겠어 <br>네 기억에 새겨주겠어 기억해 <br>봐 이렇게 힘없는 나 <br>또 날 삼키려는 파리떼 <br>나 마음껏 웃어줬지 <br>나 그렇게 비웃었지 <br>그는 또다시 내게로 와 <br>그냥 그렇게 이해해라 <br>사는 건 그런 거다 하지만 <br>뭘 내게 원했던지 <br>그게 뭘 하라는 건지 <br>결코 타협할 수 없어 <br>비참해진 날 봐 <br>우릴 봐 그리고 웃어봐 <br>이런 원숭이를 봐 이런 날 봐 <br>글쎄 난 모르겠어 <br>나 기어코 돌아섰지 <br>나 그렇게 비웃었지 <br>그는 또다시 내게로 와 <br>그냥 그렇게 이해해라 <br>사는 건 그런 거다 하지만 <br>뭘 내게 원했던지 <br>그게 뭘 하라는 건지 <br>결코 타협할 수 없어 <br>비참해진 날 봐 <br>기억해 난 널 네가 원한 전부 <br>기억해 나 이렇게 여전히 <br>우릴 봐 그리고 웃어봐 <br>이런 원숭이를 봐 이런 날 봐 <br>하나만 기억해 난 기어서라도 널 <br>물고 늘어져 <br>치욕적인 그날 터질 것 같던 <br>그날같이 잊지 않고 돌려주겠어 <br>네 기억에 새겨주겠어 기억해 <br>기억해 난 널 네가 원한 전부 <br>기억해 나 이렇게 여전히 <br>기억해 난 널 네가 원한 전부 <br>기억해 나 이렇게 <br>]]></content><category term="피아 (PIA)" label="피아 (PIA)"/><category term="원숭이 (RED APE)" label="원숭이 (RED APE)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피아_PIA/KICK_FLIP_With_NUCKSAL_DEEPFLOW/</id><title>피아 (PIA) - KICK FLIP (With NUCKSAL, DEEPFLOW) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:51:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:51:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EC%95%84_PIA/KICK_FLIP_With_NUCKSAL_DEEPFLOW/" title="피아 (PIA) - KICK FLIP (With NUCKSAL, DEEPFLOW) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Insane <br>you wrong it`s not a game <br>You better check yourself <br>that`s wrong way <br>My vane <br>let`s fly again turn to bay <br>Kick flip 360 <br>Kick flip 360 <br>NUCKSAL <br>머리가 바람에 날려 난 자유로워 <br>내 긴 머리 마치 상징 여호와 <br>모두를 용서할 정도로 기분 좋아 <br>거리의 예술가들 <br>춤을 추며 알로하 <br>판을 뒤집어버려 <br>kick flip 발돋움 <br>하늘에 닿을 듯이 모두 손들어 <br>피아 형들 나오니까 정신 붙들어 <br>마이크는 봉화 올림픽 난 불 들어 <br>거리로 뛰쳐나가 <br>덩치 큰 차들보다 <br>넌 자유롭네 이 거대한 틀 속에 난 <br>높이 더 날아올라 <br>회색 빛 빌딩 숲과 <br>나의 이 날개 난 커다란 불새 <br>Insane <br>you wrong it`s not a game <br>You better check yourself <br>that`s wrong way <br>My vane <br>let`s fly again turn to bay <br>Kick flip 360 <br>Insane <br>you wrong it`s not a game <br>You better check yourself <br>that`s wrong way <br>My vane <br>let`s fly again turn to bay <br>Kick flip <br>DEEPFLOW <br>모든 출처는 거리 <br>HIP HOP 내 놀이 <br>빈털터리에서 이젠 짭짤한 벌이 <br>Attain to glory <br>공들여 쌓은 탑 <br>난 여기 우두머리 and you 들러리 <br>우리 방식을 훔쳐가진 못해 <br>Be ordinal 난 내 꺼야 always <br>Kick push 이 아스팔트 위 <br>Kick flip 끝없이 달리지 <br>거리로 뛰쳐나가 <br>덩치 큰 차들보다 <br>넌 자유롭네 이 거대한 틀 속에 난 <br>높이 더 날아올라 <br>회색 빛 빌딩 숲과 <br>나의 이 날개 난 커다란 불새 <br>Insane <br>you wrong it`s not a game <br>You better check yourself <br>that`s wrong way <br>My vane <br>let`s fly again turn to bay <br>Kick flip 360 <br>Insane <br>you wrong it`s not a game <br>You better check yourself <br>that`s wrong way <br>My vane <br>let`s fly again turn to bay <br>Kick flip 360 <br>하얗게 날아올라 <br>단 한번도 내게 한계는 없어 <br>Insane <br>you wrong it`s not a game <br>You better check yourself <br>that`s wrong way <br>My vane <br>let`s fly again turn to bay <br>Kick flip 360 <br>Insane <br>you wrong it`s not a game <br>You better check yourself <br>that`s wrong way <br>My vane <br>let`s fly again turn to bay <br>Kick flip 360 <br>]]></content><category term="피아 (PIA)" label="피아 (PIA)"/><category term="KICK FLIP (With NUCKSAL, DEEPFLOW)" label="KICK FLIP (With NUCKSAL, DEEPFLOW)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피아_PIA/GLOOMY_SUNDAY_With_LEE_WON_SUK_Of_Daybreak/</id><title>피아 (PIA) - GLOOMY SUNDAY (With LEE WON SUK Of Daybreak) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:51:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:51:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EC%95%84_PIA/GLOOMY_SUNDAY_With_LEE_WON_SUK_Of_Daybreak/" title="피아 (PIA) - GLOOMY SUNDAY (With LEE WON SUK Of Daybreak) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그날 또 저무는 햇살에 <br>떠오른 숨 쉬는 네 미소 <br>날 흔들고 지치게 한 건 <br>네 생각과 상념과 혼돈 <br>다시 외로운 거리에 홀로된 <br>버려진 사람들 속에서 <br>너 혼자 남아 슬퍼 울지마 <br>나 같이 떠나 그곳으로 <br>그곳으로 <br>그땐 이미 아름다운 거리의 <br>밤이 사라진 후였어 <br>그건 여리고 흐트러진 <br>내 상처와 아픔과도 같아 <br>이젠 의미 없는 웃음에 <br>물든 도시와 사람을 떠나 <br>슬픔을 접을 때 기억해줘 <br>저 하늘 그곳에서 <br>제발 이제 그날을 <br>슬퍼 말아줘 <br>이제 다시 함께 해 <br>제발 이제 그날을 <br>슬퍼 말아줘 <br>이제 다시 함께 해 <br>우리 영원히 <br>나 약속해 <br>깊은 슬픔 그 안의 내겐 <br>끝나지 않을 이야기 <br>깊은 슬픔 그날의 초대 <br>이제 우리 영원히 <br>깊은 슬픔 그 안의 내겐 <br>끝나지 않을 이야기 <br>깊은 슬픔 그날의 초대 <br>이제 내 손을 잡아 <br>제발 이제 그날을 <br>슬퍼 말아줘 <br>이제 다시 함께 해 <br>우리 영원히 <br>나 약속해 <br>우리 영원히 영원히 <br>제발 이제 <br>제발 이제 <br>제발 이제 <br>]]></content><category term="피아 (PIA)" label="피아 (PIA)"/><category term="GLOOMY SUNDAY (With LEE WON SUK Of Daybreak)" label="GLOOMY SUNDAY (With LEE WON SUK Of Daybreak)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피아_PIA/MIDNIGHT_RUN_MIDNITE_Mix/</id><title>피아 (PIA) - MIDNIGHT RUN (MIDNITE Mix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:51:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:51:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EC%95%84_PIA/MIDNIGHT_RUN_MIDNITE_Mix/" title="피아 (PIA) - MIDNIGHT RUN (MIDNITE Mix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[달빛이 어둠을 달리고 <br>돌아온 자들이 덤비는 <br>소름 돋는 밤이 왔지 <br>이 잔인한 <br>붉은 밤 별이 타오르고 <br>또 다른 새벽이 쏟아지는데 <br>그건 아무런 소용없어 <br>너의 눈을 통해본 <br>이 세상은 <br>내겐 온통 유령들일 뿐 <br>단 한 번만이라도 <br>이 세상 안에 <br>살아있게 단 한 번이라도 <br>Let`s go <br>어쩌면 네가 내게로 온 <br>운명을 걸 수밖에 없는 <br>단 하나의 희망이라고 해 <br>Bring it on <br>붉은 밤 별이 타오르고 <br>또 다른 새벽이 쏟아지는데 <br>내겐 소용없어 <br>너의 눈을 통해본 <br>이 세상은 <br>내겐 온통 유령들일 뿐 <br>단 한 번만이라도 <br>이 세상 안에 <br>살아있게 단 한 번이라도 <br>Let`s go <br>Listen you silly boy <br>I’ll make a brave man <br>천만 번을 다시 산다 해도 <br>이렇게는 아닐지 몰라 <br>단 한 번 이 순간의 나 <br>어쩌면 제일 갈지 몰라 <br>단 한 번이라도 <br>Let`s go <br>Break it down <br>너의 눈을 통해본 <br>이 세상은 <br>내겐 온통 유령들일 뿐 <br>단 한 번만이라도 <br>이 세상 안에 <br>살아있게 단 한 번이라도 <br>]]></content><category term="피아 (PIA)" label="피아 (PIA)"/><category term="MIDNIGHT RUN (MIDNITE Mix)" label="MIDNIGHT RUN (MIDNITE Mix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피아_PIA/SHINE/</id><title>피아 (PIA) - SHINE - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:51:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:51:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EC%95%84_PIA/SHINE/" title="피아 (PIA) - SHINE - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람 거슬러 오른 이곳은 <br>잿빛 찬란한 타인들의 고향 <br>머물지 않을 뿐인 절망은 <br>네 어깨 위를 <br>차오르는 sunshine <br>바람 거슬러 오른 이곳은 <br>잿빛 찬란한 타인들의 고향 <br>머물지 않을 뿐인 절망은 <br>네 어깨 위를 <br>차오르는 <br>Let the sunshine in <br>Let the sunshine in <br>버림받은 자의 땅으로부터 <br>첨탑을 쌓아 높이 높이 더 <br>타오르는 태양을 맞이하며 <br>녹아버린다 해도 <br>붉은 거리의 행렬 속 <br>서로를 뜯어대며 <br>흩뿌려진 이름 모를 <br>조각들 사이를 <br>이빨을 숨긴 자들의 <br>검은 눈이 <br>숨 죽인 채 타오르네 <br>어리석은 내게 <br>주어진 건 여기까지 <br>바람 거슬러 오른 이곳은 <br>잿빛 찬란한 타인들의 고향 <br>머물지 않을 뿐인 절망은 <br>네 어깨 위를 <br>차오르는 <br>Let the sunshine in <br>Let the sunshine in <br>몰락하는 땅에 <br>피어나는 고통 속 <br>쓰라린 기억만 쌓여라 <br>처음부터 틀린 답이라 <br>넌 아니라고 했잖아 <br>넌 아니라 했잖아 <br>붉은 거리의 행렬 속 <br>서로를 뜯어대며 <br>흩뿌려진 이름 모를 <br>조각들 사이를 <br>이빨을 드러낸 <br>야수들의 미소가 <br>Cause we know <br>the time has come <br>바람 거슬러 오른 이곳은 <br>잿빛 찬란한 타인들의 고향 <br>머물지 않을 뿐인 절망은 <br>네 어깨 위를 <br>차오르는 <br>Let the sunshine in <br>Let the sunshine in <br>Let the sunshine in <br>]]></content><category term="피아 (PIA)" label="피아 (PIA)"/><category term="SHINE" label="SHINE"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피아_PIA/자오선/</id><title>피아 (PIA) - 자오선 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:51:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:51:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EC%95%84_PIA/%EC%9E%90%EC%98%A4%EC%84%A0/" title="피아 (PIA) - 자오선 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오렌지 빛 짙게 밴 오후 <br>뜨거운 계절의 <br>살을 에이는 듯 <br>스며드는 저 너머의 물결 <br>한참을 되짚었지 <br>어디서부터 인가 넘쳐버린 <br>한없이 어리던 내 변명들과 <br>채울수록 더 허전했던 <br>너덜대는 이 한 몸 <br>고이 펼쳐놓고 <br>덧없이 흔적을 지우는데 <br>I fade away <br>마치 어둠을 훔치는 <br>저 빛을 따라 <br>I fade away <br>숨이 차오르는 순간부터 <br>단숨에 피어 오른 <br>불꽃을 가둔 후 <br>뜨거운 숯을 몸에 두르고 <br>끝으로 달리는 듯 <br>두려움 없던 무명의 밤 <br>너덜대는 이 한 몸 <br>고이 펼쳐놓고 <br>덧없이 흔적을 지우는데 <br>I fade away <br>마치 어둠을 훔치는 <br>저 빛을 따라 <br>I fade away <br>숨이 차오르는 순간부터 <br>단숨에 피어 오른 불꽃 <br>뜨거운 빛을 몸에 <br>단숨에 피어 오른 불꽃 <br>뜨거운 빛을 몸에 <br>단숨에 피어 오른 불꽃 <br>뜨거운 빛을 몸에 <br>적시고 <br>숨이 차오르는 그 순간 <br>숨이 차오르는 그 순간 <br>숨이 차오르는 그 순간 <br>숨이 차오르는 <br>Blow it away <br>Blow away <br>Blow away <br>Blow away <br>Blow it away <br>Blow away <br>Blow it away <br>I fade away <br>마치 어둠을 훔치는 <br>저 빛을 따라 <br>I fade away <br>숨이 차오르는 순간부터 <br>I fade away <br>마치 어둠을 훔치는 <br>저 빛을 따라 <br>I fade away <br>숨이 차오르는 그 순간부터 <br>숨이 차오르는 그 순간부터 <br>숨이 차오르는 그 순간부터 <br>숨이 차오르는 그 순간부터 <br>]]></content><category term="피아 (PIA)" label="피아 (PIA)"/><category term="자오선" label="자오선"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피아_PIA/STORM_IS_COMING_1Piece_Mix/</id><title>피아 (PIA) - STORM IS COMING (1Piece Mix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:51:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:51:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EC%95%84_PIA/STORM_IS_COMING_1Piece_Mix/" title="피아 (PIA) - STORM IS COMING (1Piece Mix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마치 아름다운 꿈을 꾸는듯해 <br>이 도시의 불빛은 <br>아직은 알 수 없을 걸 <br>이제 곧 그가 오네 <br>he's coming <br>영원할 줄 알았겠지 아마 <br>널 위해 후회하지는 않아 <br>네게 돌이킬 수 없는 <br>그날이 오네 <br>그날이 오네 <br>그날이 오네 <br>그날이 오네 <br>그날이 오네 <br>그날이 오네 <br>그날이 오네 <br>도시의 <br>마치 아름다운 꿈을 <br>꾸는 꾸는 꾸는 <br>그날이 오네 <br>도시의 불빛은 <br>마치 아름다운 꿈을 꾸는 <br>그날이 오네 <br>마치 아름다운 꿈을 꾸는듯해 <br>이 도시의 불빛은 <br>아직은 알 수 없을 걸 <br>이제 곧 그가 오네 <br>he's coming <br>영원할 줄 알았겠지 아마 <br>널 위해 후회하지는 않아 <br>네게 돌이킬 수 없는 <br>그날이 오네 <br>그날이 오네 <br>그날이 오네 <br>그날이 오네 <br>그날이 오네 <br>그날이 오네 <br>도시의 <br>마치 아름다운 꿈을 <br>꾸는 꾸는 꾸는 <br>그날이 오네 <br>도시의 불빛은 <br>마치 아름다운 꿈을 꾸는 <br>그날이 오네 <br>]]></content><category term="피아 (PIA)" label="피아 (PIA)"/><category term="STORM IS COMING (1Piece Mix)" label="STORM IS COMING (1Piece Mix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피아_PIA/넌_나의/</id><title>피아 (PIA) - 넌 나의 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:51:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:51:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EC%95%84_PIA/%EB%84%8C_%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98/" title="피아 (PIA) - 넌 나의 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이젠 두려움에 떨지 않기를 <br>커진 그림자들로 <br>이 차가운 입김 견디기를 <br>타오른 태양 속으로 <br>잿빛 스민 노을 속을 <br>내달리다 <br>까마득히 밀려온 이곳은 <br>시들지 않는 <br>흑백의 소음 가득히 <br>어디에도 없는 그들 <br>넌 나의 Insomnia <br>Don't you drag me down <br>넌 나의 Insomnia <br>Don`t you drag me to hell <br>결코 드러나지 않을 줄 알아 <br>그들의 세상 뒤로 <br>이미 부러져 조각 나버린 <br>버림받은 자들의 땅 <br>잿빛 스민 노을 속을 <br>내달리다 <br>까마득히 밀려온 이곳 <br>시들지 않는 <br>흑백의 소음 가득히 <br>어디에도 없는 그들 <br>넌 나의 Insomnia <br>Don't you drag me down <br>넌 나의 Insomnia <br>Don`t you drag me to hell <br>Don't you drag me down <br>넌 어느새 내 곁에 섰네 <br>섬뜩함조차 익숙해 <br>여전히 두려워 떠네 <br>넌 나의 Insomnia <br>넌 나의 Insomnia <br>]]></content><category term="피아 (PIA)" label="피아 (PIA)"/><category term="넌 나의" label="넌 나의"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피아_PIA/백색의_샤_With_TABLO_LEE_JAE_KYUNG_Of_Nell/</id><title>피아 (PIA) - 백색의 샤 (With TABLO, LEE JAE KYUNG Of Nell) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:51:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:51:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EC%95%84_PIA/%EB%B0%B1%EC%83%89%EC%9D%98_%EC%83%A4_With_TABLO_LEE_JAE_KYUNG_Of_Nell/" title="피아 (PIA) - 백색의 샤 (With TABLO, LEE JAE KYUNG Of Nell) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We're unwilling kings <br>born against the grain <br>Forget the novocaine <br>If you're tryin' to <br>get this crown off us <br>bring the pain <br>We don't frown or fuss <br>though everybody's takin' shots <br>like this rounds on <br>Us versus them <br>what a game to play <br>Ride with me <br>up against the waves <br>till the world wipes out <br>Bring the guitars <br>drums and the mics out <br>이 아름다운 곳을 머물며 <br>누린 자유와 우리 사랑은 <br>We're still young <br>but God forgive us <br>We don't need your <br>babysitters to lock us indoors <br>The ocean is callin' <br>We're steppin out <br>into the waves <br>We're fallin' deeper than <br>philosophies <br>divin' through the shallow truth <br>Swimming free into the sunset <br>No more lies to anchor you <br>Till the world wipes out <br>Bring the guitars <br>drums and the mics out <br>Uh Uh <br>Bring the guitars <br>drums and the mics out <br>이 아름다운 곳을 머물며 <br>누린 자유와 우리 사랑은 <br>언젠가는 너와 내가 <br>되돌려줘야 할 <br>결국 잠시 길을 내준 <br>위대한 여행의 <br>선물임을 기억해 <br>이 아름다운 곳을 머물며 <br>누린 자유와 우리 사랑은 <br>이 아름다운 곳을 머물며 <br>누린 자유와 우리 사랑은 <br>]]></content><category term="피아 (PIA)" label="피아 (PIA)"/><category term="백색의 샤 (With TABLO, LEE JAE KYUNG Of Nell)" label="백색의 샤 (With TABLO, LEE JAE KYUNG Of Nell)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피아_PIA/소용돌이_The_SPIRAL_2016/</id><title>피아 (PIA) - 소용돌이 (The SPIRAL 2016) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:51:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:51:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EC%95%84_PIA/%EC%86%8C%EC%9A%A9%EB%8F%8C%EC%9D%B4_The_SPIRAL_2016/" title="피아 (PIA) - 소용돌이 (The SPIRAL 2016) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[헤어나지 못해 <br>갇혀있던 거칠었던 <br>내 기억에 상처 받아 <br>아파하던 <br>그런 널 바라볼 수 밖에 없어 <br>또 다시 나 갇혀 <br>그렇게 또 지쳐있던 넌 <br>순수한 그리움에 날 대신해 <br>아래로 아래로 아래로 <br>느낄 수 있어 네 자신을 봐 <br>여기 거대한 너 널 믿어봐 <br>크게 외쳐봐 네 자신을 봐 <br>멈추지 않는 너 난 널 원해 <br>내 기억에 혼돈스럽고 <br>또 지나쳤던 건 <br>이제 모두 떨치고 싶어 <br>깊은 늪 소용돌이 속 <br>던져버려 지우고 싶었어 <br>거침없고 거대했던 너 <br>두려움에 맞선 너 <br>멈추지 마 보여봐 <br>그대로 그대로 <br>멈출 순 없어 <br>그대로 멈출 순 없어 <br>느낄 수 있어 네 자신을 봐 <br>여기 거대한 너 널 믿어봐 <br>크게 외쳐봐 네 자신을 봐 <br>멈추지 않는 너 난 널 원해 <br>마침내 어두운 밑바닥 <br>도시 저편 <br>거기 웅크린 날 보며 <br>알았어 난 느꼈어 <br>나 이젠 멈출 수 없어 <br>날 여기 재울 수 없어 <br>느낄 수 있어 네 자신을 봐 <br>여기 거대한 너 널 믿어봐 <br>크게 외쳐봐 네 자신을 봐 <br>멈추지 않는 너 난 널 원해 <br>크게 외쳐봐 네 자신을 봐 <br>멈추지 않는 너 난 널 원해 <br>크게 외쳐봐 네 자신을 봐 <br>멈추지 않는 너 난 널 원해 <br>]]></content><category term="피아 (PIA)" label="피아 (PIA)"/><category term="소용돌이 (The SPIRAL 2016)" label="소용돌이 (The SPIRAL 2016)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Under_Cover_Names/</id><title>Peter Hammill - Under Cover Names - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:52:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:52:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Under_Cover_Names/" title="Peter Hammill - Under Cover Names - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No thanks for the memory, no thanks at all <br>No way we can wipe the slate or contrive escape <br>From the names we're called <br>No thanks for the memory, here it comes again <br>This life running on the spot, though we hide a lot <br>With our cover names <br><br>We can no more change the past than shed our skins <br><br>But we keep on thinking that we might go someplace <br>Where not a soul knows what has gone before <br>With such headfuls of self accusation <br>That we don't even know our own names anymore <br><br>No thanks for the memory <br>No thanks <br><br>Call them by a different name and turn about <br>We can no more change our spots than wash them out <br><br>No thanks for the memory, locked in the frame <br>No way we can change the pattern of things that happened <br>Under cover names <br><br>And we keep on skirting round the true confession <br>With fresh identities and best laid plans <br>And we keep on working to outreach the shadow <br>But the shadow will outrun the man <br>With such headfuls of self accusation <br>That no pseudonyms can hide our shame <br>Lost in a jungle of our own creation <br>Lost in a labyrinth of cover names <br>We can no more change the past than live again <br>We can no more shed our skins than know our real names <br><br>Nobody knows our real name <br>Nobody knows their real name <br>We hide under cover names <br>No thanks for the memory]]></content><category term="Peter Hammill" label="Peter Hammill"/><category term="Under Cover Names" label="Under Cover Names"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/The_Plays_The_Thing/</id><title>Peter Hammill - The Play`s The Thing - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:52:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:52:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/The_Plays_The_Thing/" title="Peter Hammill - The Play`s The Thing - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How could he know so much <br>How could he bear such knowledge <br>How could he dare to write it in the plays <br>What is it Shakespeare'd say <br>If he came back today <br>Surely he'd recognize these mortal coils <br><br>How do we carry on <br>No one knows where they fit in <br>No one knows who they are or where they've been <br>What does the writer mean <br>How do we play this scene <br>What didn't Shakespeare know that we do now <br><br>Stiffen the sinews <br>Wear hard favour'd rage <br>All history's drama <br>The world is a stage <br><br>There is a history in all men's lives <br>Figuring the nature of the times deceas'd <br>The which observ'd, a man may prophesy <br>With a near aim, of the main chance of things <br>As yet not come to life, which in their seeds <br>And weak beginnings lie intreasured <br>Such things become the hatch and brood of time <br><br>Oh, but the show goes on <br>On through the seven ages <br>That of the world must mirror man's, in fact <br>Here comes the seventh act <br>See how the mirror's cracked <br>Here comes sans everything for humankind <br><br>To capture the conscience <br>Of nations and kings <br>All history's drama <br>The play's the thing <br>The play's the thing <br>The play's the thing <br><br>How could he know so much]]></content><category term="Peter Hammill" label="Peter Hammill"/><category term="The Play`s The Thing" label="The Play`s The Thing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Sun_City_Nightlife/</id><title>Peter Hammill - Sun City Nightlife - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:52:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:52:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Sun_City_Nightlife/" title="Peter Hammill - Sun City Nightlife - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[To the city beat on a treacherous curve <br>Up upon the high wire you're observed <br>You live as you live, you'll get what you deserve <br>High life, dig those highlights <br>Sun City nightlife <br>You'll be like a moth consumed by a flame <br><br>It's a rich man's world, kick those beggars and fools <br>Conspicuous consumption the only rule <br>But the law of retribution will be terribly cruel <br><br>Oh, but you mustn't stop to think about your place upon the planet <br>If you did, you might steal yourself away <br>And it doesn't really matter if the show goes up tomorrow <br>After all, this petty place is day to day <br>Highlights of the highlife <br>Dancing at midnight <br>Dancing all moral existence away <br><br>Nightlife, highlights, highlife, twilight <br>Oh, you mustn't ever think about your place upon the planet <br>Don't look further than the bottom of a drink <br>Don't ever think about the way you'll feel tomorrow <br>Don't stop dancing or the boat will sink <br>All in all it's gone before you blink <br><br>Highlights of the high life <br>Sun City nightlife <br>You'll be like a moth consumed by flame <br>Twilight of the high life <br>Chimes at midnight <br>You're still dancing all moral existence away <br><br>A motor bike in Afrika <br>He's riding the white line <br>Oblivious of snakes stretched out across the way like trip wire <br>He's dancing <br>Biko, Biko Biko, Biko]]></content><category term="Peter Hammill" label="Peter Hammill"/><category term="Sun City Nightlife" label="Sun City Nightlife"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Vote_Brand_X/</id><title>Peter Hammill - Vote Brand X - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:52:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:52:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Vote_Brand_X/" title="Peter Hammill - Vote Brand X - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here's the modern political man, for sure he's nobody's fool <br>Believes in media coverage as a promotional tool <br>Trust in him because he's got the right face <br>Just in case you harbour doubt <br>Here is a slogan to tout <br><br>He's such a principled man, all heart, ruled by his brain <br>You've seen the TV commercials, you've seen the poster campaign <br>You've seen the ads in the papers, there's nothing else to explain <br>Just some words to maximise the market <br>Just a message that will reach the target <br>Promises that turn to dust <br>He is a man you can trust <br>This is a man of the people in politics now <br><br>Politics now, it's just like selling soap powder <br>No money down you lucky punters <br>Full guarantee <br>Five year's trial free <br><br>He is a man you can trust <br>By dint of market research he knows which truths he should tell <br>He's got the mark of conviction, it serves the agency well <br>Yes, he's on course for election in politics now <br>Trust the propagandists' manifesto <br>Trust the politician with the promo <br>Trust the ads to buy your vote <br><br>Vote for brand x, it's just like selling soap powder <br>Whatever next You lucky punters <br>Full guarantee <br>Whatever next <br>Show trials by decree <br><br>The show trials are free <br>The show trials come free <br>Vote for brand x]]></content><category term="Peter Hammill" label="Peter Hammill"/><category term="Vote Brand X" label="Vote Brand X"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Auto/</id><title>Peter Hammill - Auto - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:52:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:52:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Auto/" title="Peter Hammill - Auto - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a sensation I wouldn't trade <br>Pinpoint in the onrush <br>Dancing to the rhythm of the wiper blades <br>Up ahead on the autobahn <br>Headlights like a lava stream <br>Up ahead in the distance is where we're going <br>Where we will have been <br><br>Back in the motor, keep going overnight <br>We've got no certain destination <br>But for all we know we might <br>So get back in the motor, let's drive it anyplace <br>Better to travel hopefully <br>Than to arrive, in any case <br><br>While you check out the map book <br>Just like a novel that's all out of joint <br>Our passport into anonymity <br>Stick a pin into the vanishing point <br>I could drive for hours <br>Don't even need to know the way to go <br>I could drive forever <br>With some classical music on the radio <br><br>Back in the motor, back into overdrive <br>And if we travel hopefully then we'll know we're alive <br>Get back in das Auto, let's drive it anyplace <br>Better to travel hopefully than to arrive in any case <br><br>We could drive forever <br>We could drive forever <br>I caught you thinking, I bet you were <br>That we could drive forever <br>In the never never land of the metaphor <br><br>Back in the motor, keep going overnight <br>We've got no key to the highway <br>But for all we know we might as well <br>Get back in the motor, let's drive it anyplace <br>Better to travel hopefully than to arrive in any case <br>So get back in the motor, let's get on with the drive <br>And if we travel hopefully then we know we're alive <br><br>Get back in the motor <br>Let's get back in the motor <br>Get in tune with the motor <br>Get back]]></content><category term="Peter Hammill" label="Peter Hammill"/><category term="Auto" label="Auto"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Time_To_Burn/</id><title>Peter Hammill - Time To Burn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:52:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:52:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Time_To_Burn/" title="Peter Hammill - Time To Burn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Time to burn, we could talk all the problems through <br>Are the promises still unbroken <br>Do the spoken words still ring true <br>Oh, and where are you <br><br>Time to burn, wakes and weddings, celestial choirs <br>And while one hand shakes on the bargain <br>See the other stoke the suttee pyre <br>So we're all on fire <br>Burning for tomorrow <br><br>So much time wish and hoping <br>Soon the future will come <br>With a bridal wreath for the wedding <br>In the hands of the prodigal son <br>So much left undone <br>Here we are with time to burn <br><br>So much time wishful thinking <br>All the whitest of lies <br>With the prodigal caught at the border <br>And the order of service awry <br>No time for goodbyes <br>Will we ever start to learn <br><br>Time to burn, wakes and weddings become confused <br>All the faces over familiar <br>In the whirlwind of deja vu <br>Oh, but where are you <br><br>Time to burn, all our lifelines are gathered round <br>With a speech from the back of a postcard <br>All the memories free in one bound <br>Free, and gone to ground <br>Free, and gone forever <br>Free, and gone to ground <br>So I will remember <br>So much lost and found <br>Here we are with time to burn]]></content><category term="Peter Hammill" label="Peter Hammill"/><category term="Time To Burn" label="Time To Burn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/This_Book/</id><title>Peter Hammill - This Book - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:52:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:52:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/This_Book/" title="Peter Hammill - This Book - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Away from the past, this chance is the last <br>We are changing completely <br>We are moving the feast, we are motion <br>I've seen you become the bride of the sun <br>You surrender so sweetly <br>Sacrificing yourself to devotion <br><br>This book is ended and I put it down <br>This book is ended and I put it down <br>I'm saved, I'm saving for the future <br>This book is ended and I put it down <br>Find I'm befriended in a foreign town <br>I'm saved, I'm sailing for the future <br><br>But only yesterday night <br>I stood in the pouring rain, shouting at the thunder <br>I said Lord, I'm starting to understand the hidden mystery <br>Lord, the compass falls in my hand <br>I can sail to the far horizon <br><br>Could you conceive a mirror <br>Where you could never see yourself <br><br>Away from the past, the iconoclasts <br>We are changing completely <br>We are breaking the mould, we are rapture <br>I've seen you astride the wind and the tide <br>My dark angel, you greet me with a samurai sword <br>Close the chapter <br><br>This book is ended and I put it down <br>Find I'm befriended in a foreign town <br>I'm here, but I'm nearer to the future <br><br>But only yesterday night <br>I stood in the pouring rain, shouting at the thunder <br>I said Lord, I'm starting to understand the hidden mystery <br>Lord, the compass falls in my hand <br>I can sail to the far horizon <br><br>This book is ended and I put down <br>Find I'm befriended in a foreign town <br>This book is ended and I put it down]]></content><category term="Peter Hammill" label="Peter Hammill"/><category term="This Book" label="This Book"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Sci-Finance_Revisited/</id><title>Peter Hammill - Sci-Finance (Revisited) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:52:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:52:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Sci-Finance_Revisited/" title="Peter Hammill - Sci-Finance (Revisited) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You got some shares, it's a capital venture <br>You hedge your bets with a gilt edged bond <br>You're stretched out tight by the terms of debenture <br>The game is on <br><br>You got a fortune on paper <br>How it shines on the VDU <br>The simple truth is that sooner or later <br>The market plays you <br><br>There goes the daylight <br>Night comes on the city so soon <br>In the dance of the typical capitalists <br>What piper plays the tune <br><br>Money's ideal, money's power <br>Money's the drive that's more than skin deep <br>Hard at work through the twenty four hours <br>Oh, but money's never cheap <br><br>You made some pretty deals, I hear you say <br>Judas and Faust are squeaky clean <br>When the last of the deals have been cleared away <br>What comes up on the screen <br>There goes the daylight <br>Night comes on the city so soon <br>In the dance of the typical capitalists <br>What piper plays the tune <br>Only the money <br><br>But the deal includes us <br>We put ourselves into the stocks <br>When we built up the temple of the money god <br>We opened up Pandora's box <br>There goes the daylight <br>Now there is silence on the floor <br>Only money computers chatter privately <br>No people any more <br><br>No people any more <br>Only the money, only the money <br>Is that what you want <br>Is that it <br>There goes the daylight]]></content><category term="Peter Hammill" label="Peter Hammill"/><category term="Sci-Finance (Revisited)" label="Sci-Finance (Revisited)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Invisible_Ink/</id><title>Peter Hammill - Invisible Ink - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:52:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:52:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Invisible_Ink/" title="Peter Hammill - Invisible Ink - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Follow the instructions <br>The envelope is sealed <br>We're waiting on an update <br>Something like the reinvention of the wheel <br>Who made the world so complicated <br>Who made the watchword wait and see <br>I wake myself up, shake myself up <br>Take myself apart but still can't see <br>The esoteric is lost on me <br><br>Follow the instructions <br>They speak in many tongues <br>In unlimited edition <br>And the last step on the ladder is the bottom rung <br>The diagram is so confusing <br>Anagrammatical the mystery <br>I wake myself up, shake myself up <br>Break myself apart and find in me <br>The esoteric machinery <br>The esoteric invisibly <br><br>Follow the instructions <br>Tell us what you think <br>They lose something in translation <br>They might as well be printed in invisible ink <br><br>Esoteric machinery <br>The esoteric invisibly <br>The esoteric is lost on me <br>The esoteric invisibility <br><br>Who made the world so complicated <br>Who put the alpha in the ABC <br>I wake myself up, shake myself up <br>Break myself apart but finally <br>The esoteric is lost on me <br>The esoteric, no time to think <br>The esoteric, written in invisible ink <br><br>In invisible ink <br>Indivisible link <br>In invisible ink]]></content><category term="Peter Hammill" label="Peter Hammill"/><category term="Invisible Ink" label="Invisible Ink"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Hemlock/</id><title>Peter Hammill - Hemlock - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:52:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:52:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peter_Hammill/Hemlock/" title="Peter Hammill - Hemlock - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here it comes up on the screen <br>The propaganda of the military industrial machine <br>By now we find there's little choice <br>When our masters tell us smile we rejoice <br>With the nuclear shield safely in place <br>We're assured of the survival of the human race <br><br>The earth is flat and pigs can fly <br>Swallow hard and believe the lies <br>In these alleys all are blind <br>Skittles fall for the dreams of humankind <br><br>And nuclear power is safe as hell <br>Swallow hard, young William Tell <br>The earth is flat and pigs can fly <br>If you swallow hard you believe the lies <br><br>In the banks the deals are made <br>Of course there's no profit in lending the Third World aid <br>If the larder shelves are bare let the people eat cake <br>And thank the governments for the air <br>Meanwhile, in the cells, secret police <br>Champion freedom, offer justice, keep the peace <br><br>The Pope talks to God, the Ayatollah too <br>Swallow hard and believe it true <br>The earth is flat and pigs can fly <br>If you swallow hard you'll believe the lies <br>It's a hemlock world <br><br>It's a hemlock world that we must drink <br>Swallow hard and don't try to think <br>It's a hemlock world that we all face <br>Swallow hard on the bitter taste <br>Swallow hard on the bitter taste <br>Swallow hard on the aftertaste <br><br>It's a hemlock, it's a hemlock world]]></content><category term="Peter Hammill" label="Peter Hammill"/><category term="Hemlock" label="Hemlock"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kasmir/Huonoo_Seuraa/</id><title>Kasmir - Huonoo Seuraa - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:54:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:54:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kasmir/Huonoo_Seuraa/" title="Kasmir - Huonoo Seuraa - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Puhut mulle niinku veljelle <br>Saastat katseesi toisille <br>Sa juot lonkeroo <br><br>Naa ei treffit oo <br>Enka mitaan kai voi sille <br><br>Sa kerrot viimeoisesta <br>jostain tyypista lamesta <br>ja ma hymyilen <br>vaikka rukoilen <br>oo et se ois ollu ma <br><br>Sanon hetki vaan <br>joudun poistumaan <br>Loydan nyrkkini peilista <br><br>Loytyy multakin punasii kenkii <br>ja onhan mul moukkamaisia frendeja <br>Voisin vaihtaa autonkin douchempaan <br>jos se sua kiinnostaa <br><br>Hei beibi anna mun olla sun huonoo seuraa <br>Anna mun olla sun huonoo seuraa <br>Anna mun olla sun huonoo seuraa <br>jos se sua kiihottaa <br><br>Sa naurat mun vitseille <br>Tyhmimmillekkin jutuille <br>Ma jotain spedeilin <br>Otin kuvankin <br>Kun sa kiipesit mun olalle <br><br>Saatoin sut kotiovelle <br>kaupungin toiselle laidalle <br>Ma en haluisi et taa loppuisi <br>Annat pusun mun poskelle <br><br>Kun vedin oven kii <br>ma sanoin niinpa nii <br>sa paadyt jollekkin toiselle <br><br>Loytyy multakin punasii kenkii <br>ja onhan mul moukkamaisia frendeja <br>Voisin vaihtaa autonkin douchempaan <br>jos se sua kiinnostaa <br><br>Hei beibi anna mun olla sun huonoo seuraa <br>Anna mun olla sun huonoo seuraa <br>Anna mun olla sun huonoo seuraa <br><br>Niinku noi jotka lupaa olla uskollisii <br>ennenku jaa kiinni <br>Porukalla rankkaa sua ykkosesta kymppiin <br>Varmaa pukeutuuki niinku meklarit Lontoossa <br>mut jos se sua kiinnostaa <br><br>Hei beibi anna mun olla sun huonoo seuraa <br>Anna mun olla sun huonoo seuraa <br>Anna mun olla sun huonoo seuraa <br>jos se sua kiinnostaa <br><br>Hei beibi anna mun olla sun huonoo seuraa <br>Anna mun olla sun huonoo seuraa <br>Anna mun olla sun huonoo seuraa <br>jos se sua kiihottaa]]></content><category term="Kasmir" label="Kasmir"/><category term="Huonoo Seuraa" label="Huonoo Seuraa"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sofia_Carson/Back_To_Beautiful_Alan_Walker_Remix/</id><title>Sofia Carson - Back To Beautiful (Alan Walker Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:55:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:55:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sofia_Carson/Back_To_Beautiful_Alan_Walker_Remix/" title="Sofia Carson - Back To Beautiful (Alan Walker Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They say <br>You're not good enough, you're not brave enough <br>You should cover up your body <br>Tell me, watch my weight <br>Gotta paint my face <br>Or else no one's gonna want me <br><br>Why do we say this to ourselves? <br>And even worse to each other? <br>Why do we say this to ourselves? Ooh <br><br>We gotta, get back to beautiful <br>Gotta, get back to beautiful <br>All these wars, starting wars <br>Over who can hurt who more <br>Gotta, get back to beautiful <br><br>(Get back, beautiful) <br><br>(Get back, beautiful) <br><br>Judging who we love, judging where we're from <br>(Where we're from) <br>When did this become so normal? <br>Celebrating hate is now a commonplace <br>(Commonplace) <br>When did this become so normal? <br><br>Why do we say this to ourselves? <br>And even worse to each other? <br>Why do we say this to ourselves? Ooh <br>Why do we say this to ourselves? (Why) <br>And even worse to each other? (Ooh) <br>Why do we say this to ourselves? Ooh <br><br>We gotta, get back to beautiful <br>Gotta, get back to beautiful (Come back, oh) <br>All these wars, starting wars <br>Over who can hurt who more <br>Gotta, get back to beautiful <br><br>(Get back, beautiful) <br><br>(Get back, beautiful) <br><br>We gotta, get back to beautiful <br>Gotta, get back to beautiful (Come back, oh) <br>All these wars, starting wars <br>All these wars, starting wars <br>Over who can hurt who more <br>Gotta, get back to beautiful <br><br>(Get back, beautiful) <br><br>(Get back, beautiful)]]></content><category term="Sofia Carson" label="Sofia Carson"/><category term="Back To Beautiful (Alan Walker Remix)" label="Back To Beautiful (Alan Walker Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Rain/I_Grandi_Non_Piangono_Mai/</id><title>Mr. Rain - I Grandi Non Piangono Mai - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:56:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:56:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Rain/I_Grandi_Non_Piangono_Mai/" title="Mr. Rain - I Grandi Non Piangono Mai - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I grandi non piangono mai <br>Devi essere piu forte quante volte me l'hai detto <br>Il numero di lacrime che io ricevo non e mai proporzionale al numero di lacrime che verso <br><br>C'eri quando ero giu <br>Prometto non lo faro piu <br>Ho fatto un mucchio di stronzate per fortuna c'eri tu <br>Tra i miei problemi con la droga, crescere tre figli piccoli <br>Senza chiedere aiuto e farlo da sola <br>Ma, tu mi hai insegnato cos'e il rispetto <br>Ho incontrato mille bastardi ma quello non l'ho mai perso <br>Tu sei stata la prima a dirmi di farlo <br>La prima a credere in me <br>E prima ancora di me stesso <br>Dimmi che devo fare, mi hai detto ce la puoi fare <br>Una stella che vive di luce propria continua a brillare <br>Io non dimentico il passato <br>Come farei a negare il cuore alla persona che me l'ha dato <br><br>Imparerei a crescere <br>Dormirai con la paura del buio <br>Saremo io e te <br>Tutto andra bene se starai con me <br>Non importa in che parte del mondo sarai <br>Io ci saro sempre lo sai <br>Nessuno meritera le tue lacrime <br><br>I grandi no, non piangono mai <br><br>Pensi davvero che io no non ti riconosca <br>Per tutti i ruoli che hai interpretato meriti un Oscar <br>Ed io che mi chiedevo quante maschere avessi <br>Eri tu la mia miglior nemica la mia peggior rivale <br>Eri la mia insegnante, Babbo Natale, il portiere che ti apre se dimentichi la chiave <br>La stessa che mi ha insegnato a sbagliare ha interpretato tutti i ruoli del mondo <br>Prima di essere una madre <br>Le ore diventano i giorni, i giorni diventano anni e gia sei grande <br>Non puoi comprare il tempo, nessuno lo riavra <br>Scrivo canzoni da quando non ho piu memoria <br>Ho capito che preservare i miei ricordi e la mia priorita <br>Ora che giro per il mondo analizzo il mio sogno <br>Ricordatevi che anch'io sotto ai tatuaggi ho un cuore <br><br>A mio figlio diro che i grandi non piangono mai <br><br>Ma almeno se non dopo questa canzone <br><br>Imparerei a crescere <br>Dormirai con la paura del buio <br>Saremo io e te <br>Tutto andra bene se starai con me <br>Non importa in che parte del mondo sarai <br>Io ci saro sempre lo sai <br>Nessuno meritera le tue lacrime <br>I grandi no, non piangono mai]]></content><category term="Mr. Rain" label="Mr. Rain"/><category term="I Grandi Non Piangono Mai" label="I Grandi Non Piangono Mai"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nave_Monjo/Stole_Yo_Bitch/</id><title>Nave Monjo - Stole Yo Bitch - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:56:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:56:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nave_Monjo/Stole_Yo_Bitch/" title="Nave Monjo - Stole Yo Bitch - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I stole yo bitch, I stole yo bitch <br>I stole yo bitch <br>I stole yo, I stole her <br>I stole her, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>I stole her, I stole her <br>I stole her, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>I stole her, I stole her <br>I stole her, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>I stole her, I stole her <br>It's on, Monjo <br><br>I stole your bitch <br>I took her shopping just because and we got lit <br>Got shopping bags on shopping bags and now we dip <br>Spent so much I prolly could've paid her rent <br>She wanna burn one so I had to cop a zip <br>Hit my plug up, like I need a copy quick <br>Hey, now we hidin' and she's ridin' on my dick <br>We're too faded and we only took a sip <br>That J so strong and she gone <br><br>I stole yo bitch, I stole yo bitch <br>I stole yo bitch, I stole yo bitch <br>I stole yo bitch, I stole yo bitch <br>I stole yo bitch, I stole yo bitch <br><br>I stole her, I stole her <br>I stole her, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>I stole her, I stole her <br>I stole her, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>I stole her, I stole her <br>I stole her, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>I stole her, I stole her <br>I stole her, I stole her <br><br>I stole yo bitch, than gave her back <br>She callin' back, cause I'm the shit <br>She wanted more, I gave her more <br>And than I quit <br>I gotta go and check the time upon my wrist <br>Can't spent too much time with your ho, I gotta dip <br>I got another shawty on the line <br>Talkin' 'bout she want my time <br>I'ma gon' pull up on her <br>All she wanna do is take a ride <br> on the low <br>But we couldn't keep it on the low <br>Girl you're mine for the night <br>They know how it go <br><br>I stole yo bitch, I stole yo bitch <br>I stole yo bitch, I stole yo bitch <br>I stole yo bitch, I stole yo bitch <br>I stole yo bitch, I stole yo bitch <br><br>I stole her, I stole her <br>I stole her, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>I stole her, I stole her <br>I stole her, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>I stole her, I stole her <br>I stole her, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>I stole her, I stole her <br>I stole her, I stole yo bitch <br><br>I stole yo bitch, ha ha ha ha <br>I stole yo bitch, hehe <br>I stole yo bitch, ha ha ha ha ha ha ha <br>I stole yo bitch, ha ha ha <br>Stole yo bitch <br>I stole her, I stole her <br>Mind yo ho]]></content><category term="Nave Monjo" label="Nave Monjo"/><category term="Stole Yo Bitch" label="Stole Yo Bitch"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molly_Kate_Kestner/Prom_Queen/</id><title>Molly Kate Kestner - Prom Queen - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:56:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:56:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molly_Kate_Kestner/Prom_Queen/" title="Molly Kate Kestner - Prom Queen - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[God save the prom queen <br>Teenage daydream <br>Just another dressed up heartbreak <br>God save the prom queen <br>Only eighteen <br>Turned her tears to diamonds in her crown <br><br>She's the first in line at the party <br>She's the first in line at the club <br>And she's got that body, always gotta flaunt it <br>Everybody's looking up <br>When she walks by you want to be her <br>And your boyfriend pretends not to see her <br>'Cause she's got that fire, doesn't even try <br>Her booty has its own zip code <br>All the peasants bow down <br><br>God save the prom queen <br>Teenage daydream <br>Just another dressed up heartbreak <br>God save the prom queen <br>Only eighteen <br>Turned her tears to diamonds in her crown <br>Oh Oh Oh, Oh, Oh Oh Oh, Oh, Oh Oh Oh, Oh Ohhhhh <br><br>Take a look at the future <br>Who knows what's ahead? <br>There's a house on a hill with an indoor pool <br>And a millionaire in her bed <br>And the years go by and she still dreams <br>She's the hottest girl in town <br>And the makeup's stronger, gotta wear it longer <br>Just to keep a man around <br><br>God save the prom queen <br>Teenage daydream <br>Just another dressed up heartbreak <br>God save the prom queen <br>Only eighteen <br>Turned her tears to diamonds in her crown <br>Diamonds in her crown <br>Oh Oh Oh, Oh, Oh Oh Oh, Oh, Oh Oh Oh, Oh Ohhhhh <br>Diamonds in her crown <br>Oh Oh Oh, Oh, Oh Oh Oh, Oh, Oh Oh Oh, Oh Ohhhhh <br><br>And she lives her dreams through the magazines <br>And her daddy's gone and she needs someone <br>And she's got the looks and the boys on hooks <br>But she'll trade it all for a heart that's whole <br>God save the prom queen <br>Ohhhhhhhh (Oh Oh Oh, Oh, Oh Oh Oh, Oh, Oh Oh Oh, Oh Ohhhhh) <br>God save the prom queen! <br>Ohhhhhhhh (Oh Oh Oh, Oh, Oh Oh Oh, Oh, Oh Oh Oh, Oh Ohhhhh) <br><br>God save the prom queen <br>Teenage day dream <br>God save the prom queen (she turned her tears) <br>She turned her tears to diamonds in her crown]]></content><category term="Molly Kate Kestner" label="Molly Kate Kestner"/><category term="Prom Queen" label="Prom Queen"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Reino_Nordin/Momentumii/</id><title>Reino Nordin - Momentumii - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:58:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:58:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Reino_Nordin/Momentumii/" title="Reino Nordin - Momentumii - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Kun muut nousi sangyst ma olin menos nukkumaan <br>oisin ihmettelin maailmaa, unelmien nayteikkunaa <br>Oon nahny kaikenlaisii paivii, myrskysii ja sateisii <br>Ku tuuli on tarttunu sateenvarjoo oon heittany sen helvettiin <br>Taa on ollu pitka matka <br>ku mul on nait unelmii <br>Mut en oo luovuttanu koskaan <br>nyt jos koskaan pidan kii <br>Kun on momentumii <br>Kun on momentumii <br>Momentumii <br>Momentumii <br>Ja kun mun aika koittaa ma en aio nukkua <br>Tata hetkee ei voi haaskaa, aamuoihin harhailla <br>Oon tehny kaikenlaisii retkii, lyhyita ja pidempii <br>Oon ettiny mun reittii, taivaaseen tai helvettiin <br>Taa on ollu pitka matka, ku mul on nait unelmii <br>Mut en oo luovuttanu koskaan, nyt jos koskaan pidan kii <br>Kun on momentumii <br>Kun on momentumii <br>Momentumii <br>Momentumii <br>Kun on momentumii <br>momentumii <br>Taa on ollu pitka matka, ku mul on nait unelmii <br>Mut en oo luovuttanu koskaan, nyt jos koskaan pidan kii <br>nyt jos koskaan pidan kii <br>Kun on momentumii <br>kun on momentumii <br>Kun on momentumii <br>Momentumii <br>Momentumii <br>Kun on momentumii]]></content><category term="Reino Nordin" label="Reino Nordin"/><category term="Momentumii" label="Momentumii"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Livin_Aint_Easy/</id><title>The Menzingers - Livin` Ain`t Easy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:58:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:58:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Livin_Aint_Easy/" title="The Menzingers - Livin` Ain`t Easy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In vibrant hues and subtle brush strokes of memory <br>The life I've painted I've sold for a quick twenty <br>It's on display now for the privileged and the wealthy <br>God, I despise their reassuring, lying eyes <br>Our home stands tall behind that foreclosure sign <br>Everything in boxes from another lifetime <br>Continental breakfast in the lobby <br>But they're always out of coffee <br><br>Only a fool would think living could be easy <br>Only a fool would think living could be easy <br><br>This little motel room on I 80 west of nowhere <br>Why count the stars You'll never know where you are <br>Somewhere light years from the world you used to know <br>Like a lock that doesn't turn, like a plant that doesn't grow <br>Long for the words with hearts and wings <br>From five states over, I'm running from everything <br>Continental breakfast in the lobby <br>But they're always out of coffee <br><br>Only a fool would think living could be easy <br>Only a fool would think living could be easy <br><br>Oh you know it breaks my heart <br>Watching your whole life fall apart <br>A bastard stands up with the night <br>As we try to break free with all our might <br><br>Only a fool would think living could be easy <br>Only a fool would think living could be easy <br>Only a fool would think living could be easy <br>Only a fool would think living could be easy <br><br>In vibrant hues and subtle brush strokes of memory <br>The life I've painted I've sold for a quick twenty]]></content><category term="The Menzingers" label="The Menzingers"/><category term="Livin` Ain`t Easy" label="Livin` Ain`t Easy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/After_The_Party/</id><title>The Menzingers - After The Party - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:58:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:58:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/After_The_Party/" title="The Menzingers - After The Party - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's the little things my mind commits <br>To etch behind my eyelids <br>Like getting stoned when we wake up <br>Coffee grounds and coffee cups <br>Your silhouette in high top sneakers <br>And hardcore from laptop speakers <br>The classics to the more obscure <br>From Minor Threat to your old roommate's band <br><br>Like a kaleidoscope admiring years <br>I navigate around your tattoos <br>Said you got that one on a whim <br>When you were breaking up with him <br>And that Matryoshka Russian doll <br>The largest shell from big to small <br>What a way to start anew <br>To shed your skin and find the old you <br><br>Everybody wants to get famous <br>But you just want to dance in a basement <br>You don't care if anyone is watching <br>Just as long as you stay in motion <br>We put miles on these old jean jackets <br>Got caught up in the drunk conversations <br>But after the party, it's me and you <br>After the party, it's me and you <br><br>The new old look on everything we see <br>From high upon this rooftop over South Philly <br>To the nights we lose our self control <br>From the sex, from the drugs, from the rock and roll <br><br>Everybody wants to get famous <br>But you just want to dance in a basement <br>You don't care if anyone is watching <br>Just as long as you stay in motion <br>We put miles on these old jean jackets <br>Got caught up in the drunk conversations <br>But after the party, it's me and you <br>After the party, it's me and you <br>After the party, it's me and you <br>After the party, it's me and you]]></content><category term="The Menzingers" label="The Menzingers"/><category term="After The Party" label="After The Party"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/The_Bars/</id><title>The Menzingers - The Bars - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:58:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:58:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/The_Bars/" title="The Menzingers - The Bars - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sunken eyes and strangers' faces <br>I fall asleep in the strangest places <br>What the hell am I doing Where have my friends gone <br>Can't stand these people no more <br>But you cannot leave when you can't find the shore <br>Smashed my phone, asked my wife who's this new friend of mine <br><br>Why do some people make you nervous <br>And others drive you to drink <br>When the bars are closing <br><br>Mixed up memorial to past libation <br>A sudden fear of <br>Too hung over to sleep, too tired to stay alive <br><br>There's so much missing time to kill <br>I shake like an airplane on its way down <br><br>Why do some people make you nervous <br>And others drive you to drink <br>When the bars are closing <br>When the bars are closing <br><br>Know I'm gonna come stumbling home with the sun <br>Know I'm gonna come stumbling home with the sun <br>I used to care <br>Now I stare into the <br><br>Sunken eyes and strangers' faces <br>I fall asleep in the strangest places <br>What the hell am I doing Where have my friends gone <br><br>Why do some people make you nervous <br>And others drive you to drink <br>When the bars are closing <br>When the bars are closing]]></content><category term="The Menzingers" label="The Menzingers"/><category term="The Bars" label="The Bars"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Your_Wild_Years/</id><title>The Menzingers - Your Wild Years - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:58:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:58:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Your_Wild_Years/" title="The Menzingers - Your Wild Years - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Long for the words with hearts and wings <br>Something familiar when you miss everything <br>You rest your head against the window pane <br>Feet on the dash through the steady rain <br>I drove you home while you slept in the front seat <br>After a show at the Stone Pony <br>Watch you awake so god damn sweetly <br>Over the Walt Whitman Bridge back to Philly <br><br>I toss and turn at four in the morning <br>Petrified of where our future's going <br>'Cause you're the kind of girl that deserves the world <br>I'm just the kind of guy that promises the world <br>So I fix a drink nice and strong in the kitchen <br>Something quick that'll cure my conscience <br>Creep back to bed and I kiss your forehead <br>Maybe everything is fine and it's all in my head <br><br>A little Irish in your blood <br>A little Polish in your name <br>A little Boston in your attitude <br>Just the way you were raised <br>A little Irish in your blood <br>A little Polish in your name <br>A little Boston in your attitude <br>Just the way you were raised <br>Just the way you were raised <br>Just the way you were raised <br>Just the way you were raised <br>Just the way you were raised <br><br>We drove up to Massachusetts together <br>Your old house was just like you remember <br>We stayed in your adolescent room <br>Rummaged through the boxes labeled former you <br>The souvenirs of happiness in the moment <br>Your wild years that you often mention <br>The sands of time in an hourglass <br>That you're always begging for back <br><br>I got drunk in the afternoon <br>With your father in the living room <br>As the television broke the silence <br>You smiled, know that I was trying <br>The best that I can do <br><br>A little Irish in your blood <br>A little Polish in your name <br>A little Boston in your attitude <br>Just the way you were raised <br>A little Irish in your blood <br>A little Polish in your name <br>A little Boston in your attitude <br>Just the way you were raised <br>Just the way you were raised <br>Just the way you were raised <br>Just the way you were raised <br>Just the way you were raised]]></content><category term="The Menzingers" label="The Menzingers"/><category term="Your Wild Years" label="Your Wild Years"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Bad_Catholics/</id><title>The Menzingers - Bad Catholics - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:58:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:58:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Bad_Catholics/" title="The Menzingers - Bad Catholics - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We should have never thought that we could get stoned <br>And drive around with just a half a pack of smokes <br>A bottle of clear eyes, an appetite, we were <br>Pillaging the Turkey Hill on Main Ave in West Side <br><br>Wouldn't you guess the only thing we had to fear would be <br>Flashing their lights in our rear view mirror <br>This time they got us it's all over now <br>You were praying Hail Mary's for an escape route <br><br>But thank God for your father's last name <br>And all the connections that he's made <br>To everyone you're such a sweet church girl <br>But I know your secret <br><br>Bad Catholics weren't we darling <br>Always dipping out before communion started <br>Bad Catholics weren't we darling <br>Always dipping out before communion started <br><br>Another summer and another church picnic <br>I watch a mother run around in a panic <br>Chasing her kid with his orange soda mustache <br>While his fathers by the gambling wheel <br><br>There I saw you in the beer tent hanging <br>With your new husband and your baby on the way <br>Oh it's kinda strange how it made me miss something <br>Long lost in the both of us now <br><br>You thanked God that I found my way <br>And introduced me to what's his name <br>To everyone you're such a sweet church girl <br>But I know your secret, yeah I know your secret <br><br>Bad Catholics weren't we darling <br>Always dipping out before communion started <br>Bad Catholics weren't we darling <br>Always dipping out before communion started <br>Bad Catholics weren't we darling <br>Always dipping out before communion started <br>Bad Catholics weren't we darling <br>Always dipping out before communion started]]></content><category term="The Menzingers" label="The Menzingers"/><category term="Bad Catholics" label="Bad Catholics"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Boy_Blue/</id><title>The Menzingers - Boy Blue - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:58:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:58:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Boy_Blue/" title="The Menzingers - Boy Blue - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Took our father's name and our mother's heart <br>Felt the sister's pain then it fell apart <br>We were told one thing and they showed us another <br>Is it finally true we're not getting any younger <br><br>The boy blue with the silver spoon <br>They found him dying in the living room <br>Say goodbye to the bride and groom <br>See them off for their honeymoon <br><br>Dreadful sound echoed through the trees <br>Dirty headlights put us all on our knees <br>Route 502 we were waiting for you <br>But you couldn't see it was New Year's Eve <br><br>The boy blue with the silver spoon <br>They found him dying in the living room <br>Say goodbye to the bride and groom <br>See them off for their honeymoon <br><br>I've been told <br>There's no going home <br>No room for you and me <br>No empty seats in eternity <br>I've been told <br>No going home <br>No song left to sing <br>No second act to mortality <br><br>The boy blue with the silver spoon <br>They found him dying in the living room <br>Say goodbye to the bride and groom <br>See them off for their honeymoon <br><br>The boy blue with the silver spoon <br>They found him dying in the living room <br>Say goodbye to the bride and groom <br>See them off for their honeymoon]]></content><category term="The Menzingers" label="The Menzingers"/><category term="Boy Blue" label="Boy Blue"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Black_Mass/</id><title>The Menzingers - Black Mass - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:58:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:58:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Black_Mass/" title="The Menzingers - Black Mass - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was staring through the stained glass <br>Into the procession of a black mass <br>Saw how subject at the altar wants their life back <br>The view from here, there's a in flowers <br>It's born beyond repair for an altar <br>It's stranger laying with the lamb to the slaughter <br><br>But hey, do you really want to throw it away <br>Do you really want to throw it away <br>I'd do anything to make you stay <br><br>We used to want to take the back roads <br>But now we found a distance shorter <br>You used to call me darling <br>Now you prefer more formal <br>We used to get high and stare at the moon <br>And wonder how long it would take to walk to <br>But now that's like the distance between me and you <br><br>But hey, do you really want to throw it away <br>Do you really want to throw it away <br>I'd do anything to make you stay <br><br>For just a little, just a little bit longer <br>For just a little, just a little bit longer <br>For just a little, just a little bit longer <br>For just a little, just a little bit longer]]></content><category term="The Menzingers" label="The Menzingers"/><category term="Black Mass" label="Black Mass"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/House_On_Fire/</id><title>The Menzingers - House On Fire - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:59:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:59:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/House_On_Fire/" title="The Menzingers - House On Fire - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Waiting for your life to start then you die <br>Was your heart beating in the first place <br>Waiting for your life to start then you die <br>Was your heart beating in the first place <br><br>Lost myself in the kitchen <br>There's an old friend falling down the stairs <br>He said there's cops in the alley way <br>It's too late for similar sin <br>It burns up <br><br>Waiting for your life to start then you die <br>Was your heart beating in the first place <br>Waiting for your life to start then you die <br>Was your heart beating in the first place <br><br>Found myself in the basement <br>There's smoke, there's ash over everything <br>This girl I know, yeah, she's trying to get high <br>She's telling me, she's telling me, Let it burn up <br><br>Yeah, does it make you nervous <br>Have you fulfilled your purpose <br>Yeah, does it make you nervous <br>How she's on fire <br>Yeah, does it make you nervous <br>Have you fulfilled your purpose <br>Yeah, does it make you nervous <br>How she's on fire <br><br>Waiting for your life to start then you die <br>Was your heart beating in the first place <br>Waiting for your life to start then you die <br>Was your heart beating in the first place <br><br>We set the house on fire <br>And we ain't going nowhere <br>We set the house on fire <br>And we ain't going nowhere <br>We set the house on fire <br>And we ain't going nowhere <br>We set the house on fire <br>And we ain't going nowhere]]></content><category term="The Menzingers" label="The Menzingers"/><category term="House On Fire" label="House On Fire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Charlies_Army/</id><title>The Menzingers - Charlie`s Army - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:59:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:59:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Charlies_Army/" title="The Menzingers - Charlie`s Army - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I guess I should tell her I'm sorry <br>I never showed up to the party <br>Yeah, I got into a misunderstanding <br>With her old boyfriend named Charlie <br><br>Yeah, I love, I love my Juliette <br>But her ex boyfriend wants me dead <br><br>But tell your man I ain't afraid to die <br><br>When I first met her I fell in love <br>And she smiled because she knew <br>We were day drinking in Brooklyn <br>It was death in the afternoon, yeah <br><br>I love, I love my Juliette <br>But her ex boyfriend wants me dead <br><br>Charlie's army's coming for me <br>Charlie's army's coming for me <br>He says, Boy, you're gonna be sorry <br>Charlie's army's coming for me <br><br>Tell your man I ain't afraid to die <br>If loving Julie is a capitol crime <br>Tell your man I ain't afraid to die <br>If loving Julie is a capitol crime <br><br>I'm not gonna tell him I'm sorry <br>'Cause it's me and her after the party <br>No need for a misunderstanding <br>'Cause nothing's gonna change my mind, yeah <br><br>I love, I love my Juliette <br>But her ex boyfriend wants me dead <br><br>Charlie's army's coming for me <br>Charlie's army's coming for me <br>He says, Boy, you're gonna be sorry <br>Charlie's army's coming for me <br><br>Tell your man I ain't afraid to die <br>If loving Julie is a capitol crime <br>Tell your man I ain't afraid to die <br>If loving Julie is a capitol crime]]></content><category term="The Menzingers" label="The Menzingers"/><category term="Charlie`s Army" label="Charlie`s Army"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Midwestern_States/</id><title>The Menzingers - Midwestern States - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:59:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:59:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Midwestern_States/" title="The Menzingers - Midwestern States - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I hope this isn't a burden <br>Thanks for having us over <br>We could sleep on the couch <br>We could sleep on the floor <br>We would leave before you even noticed we were here <br>Even notice us at all <br><br>Been having problems with our landlord <br>He said he's taking us both to court <br>She got her hours slashed <br>And my unemployment's drying up fast <br>We both got worthless diplomas <br>From worthless universities <br>Two bachelors in worthless studies <br>But at least it made our parents happy <br>And cost a whole lot of money <br><br>You said LA's only two days <br>If we drive straight, damned if we get tired <br>Said you didn't mind stopping just as long as we got out of the Midwest states <br>The Midwestern states <br>The Midwestern states <br>The Midwestern states <br>The Midwestern states <br><br>But I know somewhere in Chicago <br>Where we can stay for a little <br>I hope this isn't a burden <br>Thanks for having us over <br>Most nights we always fall asleep with <br>Something dumb on Netflix <br>Some nights trash reality <br>Or kids cartoons or shitty documentaries <br>Not perfect but we're good together <br>Yeah, me, you, and our bad tattoos <br>Yeah, all our stick and pokes, all our inside jokes <br>We'll regret them when we're dead and sober <br>But we're still breathing and the party ain't over <br><br>You said LA's only two days <br>If we drive straight, damned if we get tired <br>Said you didn't mind stopping just as long as we got out of the Midwest states <br>You said LA's only two days <br>If we drive straight, damned if we get tired <br>Said you didn't mind stopping just as long as we got out of the Midwest states <br>The Midwestern states <br>The Midwestern states <br>The Midwestern states <br>The Midwestern states]]></content><category term="The Menzingers" label="The Menzingers"/><category term="Midwestern States" label="Midwestern States"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Lookers/</id><title>The Menzingers - Lookers - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:59:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:59:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Lookers/" title="The Menzingers - Lookers - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lost in a picture frame <br>The way our bodies used to behave <br>The way we smiled in the moment <br>Before they permanently froze <br>But that was the old me and you <br>When we were both lookers <br><br>Lost in a picture frame <br>The way my body used to behave <br>The way I smiled in the moment <br>Before it permanently froze <br>But that was the old me <br>I was such a looker in the old days <br><br>You little Kerouac <br>Always running like Dean and Sal <br>Always waiting on a freight train <br>Always looking for a story to tell <br>But that was the old you <br>You were such a looker in the old days <br><br>Sha la la la Jersey girls <br>Are always total heartbreakers <br>Julie from the Wonder Bar <br>I still wonder where you are <br>Cause I know the old you <br>And you know the old me <br><br>I was certain that I'd find her <br>In the back of the diner <br>In a cloud full of nicotine <br>In a teenage memory <br>That I hold till eternity <br>Cause the future ain't coming for it <br><br>Sha la la la Jersey girls <br>Are always total heartbreakers <br>Julie from the Wonder Bar <br>I still wonder where you are <br>Oh, sha la la la Jersey girls <br>Are always total heartbreakers <br>Julie from the Wonder Bar <br>I still wonder where you are <br>Cause I know the old you <br>And you know the old me <br>When we were both lookers <br><br>In a 5 by 8 black and white <br>On the night stand of my mind <br>From a time I hardly recognize <br><br>Sha la la la Jersey girls <br>Are always total heartbreakers <br>Julie from the Wonder Bar <br>I still wonder where you are <br>Oh, sha la la la Jersey girls <br>Are always total heartbreakers <br>Julie from the Wonder Bar <br>I still wonder where you are <br>Cause I know the old you <br>And you know the old me <br>When we were both lookers]]></content><category term="The Menzingers" label="The Menzingers"/><category term="Lookers" label="Lookers"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Thick_As_Thieves/</id><title>The Menzingers - Thick As Thieves - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:59:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:59:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Thick_As_Thieves/" title="The Menzingers - Thick As Thieves - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I held up a liquor store <br>Demanding topshelf metaphors <br>Silly smile and open arms <br>Drop a line to charm the silent alarm <br><br>Mutual angels calling the cops <br>They'll be choosing sides when the fighting stops <br>Police summon the cavalry <br>While we six kings made our getaway <br><br>Thick as thieves on our knees <br>With an ocean in between <br>Thick as thieves on our knees <br>With an ocean in between <br>With an ocean in between <br><br>Laughter in the darkness <br>Whispers in the shadows <br>I was there when the wall fell down <br>I'll be there when the ocean rises <br><br>Building castles of cans and bottles <br>Drinking like they do in novels <br>Know they'll catch me by and by <br>But tonight you are my alibi <br><br>Same old song that we all come from <br>Faded stars in the air that we breathe <br>In the earth, in the sea <br><br>Thick as thieves on our knees <br>With an ocean in between <br>Thick as thieves on our knees <br>With an ocean in between <br>Thick as thieves on our knees <br>With an ocean in between <br>Thick as thieves on our knees <br>With an ocean in between <br>With an ocean in between]]></content><category term="The Menzingers" label="The Menzingers"/><category term="Thick As Thieves" label="Thick As Thieves"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Tellin_Lies/</id><title>The Menzingers - Tellin` Lies - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T17:59:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T17:59:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Menzingers/Tellin_Lies/" title="The Menzingers - Tellin` Lies - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh yeah, oh yeah, everything is terrible <br>Buying marijuana makes you feel like a criminal <br>When your new friends take a joke too literal <br>Making you feel like the bad guy <br><br>Oh where are we gonna go <br>Oh now that our twenties are over <br><br>Oh yeah, oh yeah, all hope abandoned <br>I'm not young enough to be a companion <br>Not old enough to be a guide <br>With a cliche time to try <br><br>Oh where are we gonna go <br>Oh now that our twenties are over <br><br>Where are we gonna go now that our twenties are over <br>Where are we gonna go now that our twenties are over <br>Where are we gonna go now that our twenties are over <br>Everyone's asking me over and over <br>The decade taken hostage <br>By my own guilty conscience <br>When you gonna quit this nonsense <br>Everyone's asking me over and over <br>But I don't mind telling lies, lies <br><br>So oh yeah, oh yeah, let's go to Vegas <br>Put it all on black and get married by Elvis <br>If we wake up broke, we'll be fine <br>We'll get rich in another lifetime <br><br>Oh where are we gonna go <br>Oh now that our twenties are over <br><br>Where are we gonna go now that our twenties are over <br>Where are we gonna go now that our twenties are over <br>Where are we gonna go now that our twenties are over <br>Everyone's asking me over and over <br>The decade taken hostage <br>By my own guilty conscience <br>When you gonna quit this nonsense <br>Everyone's asking me over and over <br>But I don't mind telling lies, lies <br><br>That tension you can cut with a knife <br>Like a wedding ring that never fit right <br>Like a car alarm that won't stop howling <br>A decade lost in the motions <br>To romance and cheap whiskey <br>The subtle sound of a fleeting feeling <br>Like four chords that don't love you no more <br>In a motel room, a sleeping bag on the floor <br>'Cause they're all the same <br>Things can't change 'cause they're all the same <br>Telling lies <br>Things can't change 'cause they're all the same <br>Telling lies <br>Things can't change 'cause they're all the same <br>Telling lies <br>Things can't change 'cause they're all the same <br>Telling lies <br>Things can't change 'cause they're all the same <br>Telling lies <br>Things can't change 'cause they're all the same <br>Telling lies <br>Things can't change 'cause they're all the same <br>Telling lies <br>Things can't change]]></content><category term="The Menzingers" label="The Menzingers"/><category term="Tellin` Lies" label="Tellin` Lies"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/옥숭아/너_빼고_다_있어_Feat_이진_정민호/</id><title>옥숭아 - 너 빼고 다 있어 (Feat. 이진, 정민호) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:01:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:01:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A5%EC%88%AD%EC%95%84/%EB%84%88_%EB%B9%BC%EA%B3%A0_%EB%8B%A4_%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%84_%EC%A0%95%EB%AF%BC%ED%98%B8/" title="옥숭아 - 너 빼고 다 있어 (Feat. 이진, 정민호) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[신경 쓰이나 봐 Um <br>아무렇지 않은 줄 알았는데 <br>니 앞에만 서면 니 생각만 하면 <br>일이 손에 잡히질 않아 <br>혼자 멍하니 나 생각해 봤어 <br>너와 함께 있는 내 모습 <br>내가 생각해도 웃음이 나 <br>La Lal La <br>집에서 닭다리만 뜯던 내가 <br>웬일로 순살만 찾고 있어 <br>밥그릇 싹싹 비우던 내가 <br>어느 샌가 쌀을 새고만 있네 <br>이젠 노래 하나 하나도 <br>내 노래 같아 <br>볼빨간 사춘기 언니들도 <br>우주를 준대 <br>난 너에게 행복만 줄게 <br>널 보면 느껴지는 어색함이 <br>어떻게 해야 할지 모르겠어 <br>나랑 밥 먹기가 불편할까 <br>오늘따라 니 표정이 어둡네 <br>그냥 그대로가 예뻐 <br>예뻐 보이려고 애쓰진 마 <br>언제부터 이렇게 예뻤을까 <br>그냥 니가 좋은가 봐 <br>지금 커피 한 잔 어때요 <br>어 <br>나랑 맛있는 거 먹으러 갈래요 <br>어떤 거요 <br>아니 오늘 영화 볼래 <br>그러지 말고 우리 집에서 <br>치킨 먹고 갈래요 <br>라면도 있어 <br>너 빼고 다 있어 <br>]]></content><category term="옥숭아" label="옥숭아"/><category term="너 빼고 다 있어 (Feat. 이진, 정민호)" label="너 빼고 다 있어 (Feat. 이진, 정민호)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/옥숭아/당신에게/</id><title>옥숭아 - 당신에게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:01:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:01:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A5%EC%88%AD%EC%95%84/%EB%8B%B9%EC%8B%A0%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C/" title="옥숭아 - 당신에게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하얗고 차가운 겨울날 <br>두 손을 꽉 쥐고 세상 밖으로 <br>나왔을 때 아마도 소리 내어 운 건 <br>나를 마중 나왔던 당신이 <br>너무 아름다워서가 아니었을까 <br>아름다운 나의 엄마 <br>그 누구보다 사랑합니다 <br>당신께 받은 사랑 <br>평생을 다해도 갚지 못할 테지만 <br>저와 두 손 꼭 잡고 <br>오래 머물러줘요 <br>오래 머물러줘요 <br>난 두 자리 수의 나이가 되고 <br>친구와 만나는 게 행복했을 때 <br>당신도 친구가 <br>필요하지 않았나요 <br>지금에서야 바라 본 당신 <br>여전히 그 자릴 비워뒀네요 <br>아름다운 나의 엄마 <br>그 누구보다 사랑합니다 <br>당신께 받은 사랑 <br>평생을 다해도 갚지 못할 테지만 <br>저와 두 손 꼭 잡고 <br>오래 머물러줘요 <br>오래 머물러줘요 <br>그때도 지금도 여전히 <br>누구보다 빛날 당신이 <br>나의 엄마라 정말 행복합니다 <br>아름다운 나의 엄마 <br>평생을 다해도 갚지 못할 테지만 <br>오래 오래 우리 두 손 잡고 <br>행복해요 <br>]]></content><category term="옥숭아" label="옥숭아"/><category term="당신에게" label="당신에게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/세비야/Dont_Say_Goodbye/</id><title>세비야 - Don`t Say Goodbye - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:01:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:01:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%B8%EB%B9%84%EC%95%BC/Dont_Say_Goodbye/" title="세비야 - Don`t Say Goodbye - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[믿어지지가 않는 <br>얘기를 듣고 있는데 난 왜 <br>니가 더 좋아 <br>전혀 니가 밉지 않아 <br>점점 더해가는 내 마음만 <br>아무리 니가 날 뿌리 쳐도 <br>l can't leave <br>Baby I can't live <br>without you <br>너도 힘든걸 알아 그러니까 <br>Don't say good bye <br>여린 니가 먼저 말하기 <br>얼마나 아프고 힘들었을지 <br>더 잘 아니까 애쓰지마 <br>일부러 그런 니 맘 다치는 <br>모진 말 더 하지마 <br>지금 이대로 가다가 보면 <br>우리 어떻게든 되어 있을 테니 <br>니 맘 다치게 하지는 마 <br>아무리 니가 날 뿌리 쳐도 <br>l can't leave <br>Baby I can't live <br>without you <br>너도 힘든걸 알아 그러니까 <br>Don't say good bye <br>]]></content><category term="세비야" label="세비야"/><category term="Don`t Say Goodbye" label="Don`t Say Goodbye"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성소년/겨울속의_봄_Vocal_빌리_Piano_Ver/</id><title>감성소년 - 겨울속의 봄 (Vocal 빌리) (Piano Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:01:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:01:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84/%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8%EC%86%8D%EC%9D%98_%EB%B4%84_Vocal_%EB%B9%8C%EB%A6%AC_Piano_Ver/" title="감성소년 - 겨울속의 봄 (Vocal 빌리) (Piano Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[누구에게나 있겠죠 <br>지워질 리 없는 기억이 <br>하루를 보내기도 힘들만큼 <br>아픈 기억이 <br>그 누구도 알 수 없겠죠 <br>아무도 나일 수 없음에 <br>나만큼 나의 맘을 알아주길 <br>바라는 건 욕심일 뿐인걸 <br>겨울이 있어서 <br>봄이 반가운 것처럼 <br>따스함을 느끼도록 <br>추운 거겠죠 <br>눈물들을 다 비워서 <br>더 많이 웃으라고 <br>또 이렇게 <br>힘든 건가 봐요 <br>많지 않던 잠이 <br>늘어가고 <br>나쁜 생각들이 <br>나를 감싸고 <br>여느 때처럼 <br>지나갈 거라고 <br>난 그렇게 믿고 싶어 <br>겨울이 있어서 <br>봄이 반가운 것처럼 <br>따스함을 느끼도록 <br>추운 거겠죠 <br>눈물들을 다 비워서 <br>더 많이 웃으라고 <br>또 이렇게 <br>힘든 건가 봐요 <br>아픔이란 얼룩에 움츠려져 <br>웅크리고 있던 나에게 <br>많은 위로들이 <br>아픔을 덜어주고 <br>그저 나를 기다려주고 <br>믿어줬던 사람들 <br>그 빛이 눈을 뜨게 했어 <br>겨울에 피는 꽃처럼 <br>다시 일어날 거예요 <br>소중함을 느끼도록 <br>추운 거였죠 <br>이제야 난 알았어요 <br>그 많은 마음들이 <br>겨울 속에 봄이었다는 걸 <br>]]></content><category term="감성소년" label="감성소년"/><category term="겨울속의 봄 (Vocal 빌리) (Piano Ver.)" label="겨울속의 봄 (Vocal 빌리) (Piano Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성소년/겨울속의_봄_Vocal_빌리/</id><title>감성소년 - 겨울속의 봄 (Vocal 빌리) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:01:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:01:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84/%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8%EC%86%8D%EC%9D%98_%EB%B4%84_Vocal_%EB%B9%8C%EB%A6%AC/" title="감성소년 - 겨울속의 봄 (Vocal 빌리) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[누구에게나 있겠죠 <br>지워질 리 없는 기억이 <br>하루를 보내기도 힘들만큼 <br>아픈 기억이 <br>그 누구도 알 수 없겠죠 <br>아무도 나일 수 없음에 <br>나만큼 나의 맘을 알아주길 <br>바라는 건 욕심일 뿐인걸 <br>겨울이 있어서 <br>봄이 반가운 것처럼 <br>따스함을 느끼도록 <br>추운 거겠죠 <br>눈물들을 다 비워서 <br>더 많이 웃으라고 <br>또 이렇게 <br>힘든 건가 봐요 <br>많지 않던 잠이 <br>늘어가고 <br>나쁜 생각들이 <br>나를 감싸고 <br>여느 때처럼 <br>지나갈 거라고 <br>난 그렇게 믿고 싶어 <br>겨울이 있어서 <br>봄이 반가운 것처럼 <br>따스함을 느끼도록 <br>추운 거겠죠 <br>눈물들을 다 비워서 <br>더 많이 웃으라고 <br>또 이렇게 <br>힘든 건가 봐요 <br>아픔이란 얼룩에 움츠려져 <br>웅크리고 있던 나에게 <br>많은 위로들이 <br>아픔을 덜어주고 <br>그저 나를 기다려주고 <br>믿어줬던 사람들 <br>그 빛이 눈을 뜨게 했어 <br>겨울에 피는 꽃처럼 <br>다시 일어날 거예요 <br>소중함을 느끼도록 <br>추운 거였죠 <br>이제야 난 알았어요 <br>그 많은 마음들이 <br>겨울 속에 봄이었다는 걸 <br>]]></content><category term="감성소년" label="감성소년"/><category term="겨울속의 봄 (Vocal 빌리)" label="겨울속의 봄 (Vocal 빌리)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/희원/어떤_이별/</id><title>희원 - 어떤 이별 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:01:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:01:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9D%AC%EC%9B%90/%EC%96%B4%EB%96%A4_%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84/" title="희원 - 어떤 이별 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 원망하지 <br>않는다는 말 <br>나보다 더 좋은 사람 <br>만나라는 말 <br>혹시 다음에 <br>길에서 보게 되면 <br>웃으면서 보자고 <br>인사 정도는 하자고 <br>너의 행복을 <br>빌어주겠다며 <br>난 괜찮다는 <br>이 말도 안 되는 <br>말들을 <br>내뱉으면서 <br>난 또 행복한 <br>이별을 했다고 <br>난 괜찮은 <br>이별을 했다고 <br>널 보자마자 <br>도망갈 나면서 <br>터질듯한 심장을 <br>탓할 나면서 <br>네가 없는 <br>방에 들어가 <br>널 원망하는 <br>눈물을 쏟아 <br>붙잡지도 않았으면서 <br>붙잡을 용기도 <br>없었으면서 <br>널 보자마자 <br>도망갈 나면서 <br>터질듯한 심장을 <br>탓할 나면서 <br>네가 없는 방에 들어가 <br>널 원망하는 눈물을 쏟아 <br>붙잡지도 않았으면서 <br>붙잡을 용기도 <br>없었으면서 <br>]]></content><category term="희원" label="희원"/><category term="어떤 이별" label="어떤 이별"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/K_Special/Jdeviens_Ouf_Feat_Djaz/</id><title>K Special - J`deviens Ouf (Feat. Djaz) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:02:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:02:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/K_Special/Jdeviens_Ouf_Feat_Djaz/" title="K Special - J`deviens Ouf (Feat. Djaz) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[J'deviens ouf <br>Je perds mon controle mon sang chaud m'etouffe <br>Essouffle par la lassitude de ces coups de feu <br>Quand j'en entends parler a croire qu'ils prennent ca pour un jeu <br>Ta vie n'est pas un film mieux vaut rester sage <br><br>Y'a trop d'embrouille, je crois que la race humaine part en couille <br>Le respect se perd, la paix n'existe plus mais j'espere <br>Que Pere tout puissant arrivera a faire taire tous ces conflits <br>Ces trucs de fou qui se passe sur terre <br>Mon pater me dit que ce n'est pas termine <br>Car c'est le cine qui donne des idees <br>A ces jeunes des cites decides a tirer <br>Quand y'a pepin sache que ce n'est pas le pire <br>J'en raconte pas plus sinon on ne va plus s'en sortir <br>En tirant des phrases attirant l'attention des tyrans <br>Peut etre qu'ils reflechiront tout en s'inspirant <br>De mes textes bases de faits reels <br>Je dis ce que je vis, vis a vis d'une perte fraternelle <br>Pourquoi les gars se tapent quand ils ne se captent pas <br>ca se peut qu'ils se voient comme chien et chat <br>Et si c'est ca on n'y peut rien <br>On vit avec, j'aimerai que sur ce point la on fasse un break <br>Au lieu de se braquer entre nous <br>ca me donne le trac mais <br>Quand t'as pas le choix mieux vaut jouer le detraque <br>Et quand j'en viens a ce point la ca me fait craquer <br><br>J'deviens ouf <br>Je perds mon controle mon sang chaud m'etouffe <br>Essouffle par la lassitude de ces coups de feu <br>Quand j'en entends parler a croire qu'ils prennent ca pour un jeu <br>Ta vie n'est pas un film mieux vaut rester sage <br>J'deviens ouf <br>Je perds mon controle mon sang chaud m'etouffe <br>Essouffle par la lassitude de ces coups de feu <br>Quand j'en entends parler a croire qu'ils prennent ca pour un jeu <br>Ta vie n'est pas un film mieux vaut rester sage <br><br>Tuer un re fre, a dire vrai <br>C'est une pensee qui m'effraie <br>Vivre avec une mort sur la conscience putain dire que je l'ai fait <br>Je pourrai plus me mater dans une glace le matin <br>Sans y apercevoir le regard sombre de l'assassin <br>Perdu dans un coin de ma cellule je me dis <br>Que je rate l'ultime llet bi <br>Mon paradis s'eloigne je suis maudit <br>Maudit soit ce 10 janvier j'en veux <br>A tous ces on dit qui m'ont fait flancher en chien <br>C'est a Fresnes que je traine onze ans c'est la peine que je tire <br>Oui je peux dire que ca laisse du temps pour reflechir <br>Je revois ma famille, ma femme et les petits yeux de ma fille <br>Repense a ma victime vois la salete de mon crime fretille <br>D'angoisse, degueulasse comme ce schlass dans sa chair <br>Recouverte par le sang est la plaie de sa chere mere <br>Qui pleure fils qui meurt, erreur gravee <br>Meme le sommeil je peux plus trouver <br><br>J'deviens ouf <br>Je perds mon controle mon sang chaud m'etouffe <br>Essouffle par la lassitude de ces coups de feu <br>Quand j'en entends parler a croire qu'ils prennent ca pour un jeu <br>Ta vie n'est pas un film mieux vaut rester sage <br>J'deviens ouf <br>Je perds mon controle mon sang chaud m'etouffe <br>Essouffle par la lassitude de ces coups de feu <br>Quand j'en entends parler a croire qu'ils prennent ca pour un jeu <br>Ta vie n'est pas un film mieux vaut rester sage <br><br>Il a tire sur untel <br>Et l'autre a telephone sa clique c'est le bordel <br>A base de coups de feu ou de cocktails des descentes sans sentiments <br>Sans que tu le saches ca sent le guet apens <br>Guette un peu y'a un qui baigne dans son sang <br>C'est en passant par la que j'ai su qu'il fallait s'en sortir <br>Et si tu penses a demain ca peut etre encore pire <br>Les jeunes sont presses de ne plus se laisser marcher dessus <br>Si tu leur manques de respect plus tard ils peuvent te chier dessus <br>Telle est la loi de tout les mecs des cites excites <br>Mais si t'es fort ce n'est pas la peine de la cite <br>Si cette situation suscite un zoom <br>C'est que trop de fois dans une cite on entend boom <br>Le resultat est le meme <br>ca me fait mal men quand je m'amene <br>A manier le mic avec des histoires que tout le monde ramene <br><br>J'deviens ouf <br>Je perds mon controle mon sang chaud m'etouffe <br>Essouffle par la lassitude de ces coups de feu <br>Quand j'en entends parler a croire qu'ils prennent ca pour un jeu <br>Ta vie n'est pas un film mieux vaut rester sage <br>J'deviens ouf <br>Je perds mon controle mon sang chaud m'etouffe <br>Essouffle par la lassitude de ces coups de feu <br>Quand j'en entends parler a croire qu'ils prennent ca pour un jeu <br>Ta vie n'est pas un film mieux vaut rester sage]]></content><category term="K Special" label="K Special"/><category term="J`deviens Ouf (Feat. Djaz)" label="J`deviens Ouf (Feat. Djaz)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/K_Special/Les_Porcs_Feat_Sniper/</id><title>K Special - Les Porcs (Feat. Sniper) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:02:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:02:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/K_Special/Les_Porcs_Feat_Sniper/" title="K Special - Les Porcs (Feat. Sniper) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, celle ci est pour ceux qu'ont disparu sous la torture <br>a tous ceux qui s'battent, qui luttent <br>Qui tournent face a ce systeme d'ordure <br>Systeme d'enflure, a cause de bavure policiere <br>Comme dit Salif, voila a quoi la justice sert <br>Y'a plus d'mystere, on est comme des animaux pourchasses par l'homme <br>Bonhomme faut qu'on galope pour ne pas qu'il nous degomme <br>On s'cache dans les halls pour pas subir la sentence <br>Meme si le reve de tous c'est d'niquer un keuf a distance <br><br>Agents de police judiciaire employes par l'etat <br>L'flingue a bout d'bras, dans l'quartier en train braquer mes freres <br>J'ai flaire l'danger, leurs actes racistes et leur injustice <br>Le FN represente le premier syndicat d'police <br>Qui regroupe 25% d'la profession, un sur quatre <br>Quatre agents par vehicules donc un fasciste dans chaque section <br>Policiers, douaniers, matons, perte de bracelets, batons <br>Flingues automatiques, et bombes anti agression <br>Dans les tess ca scrute, la menace est imminente <br>Pendant qu'ils reprimandent, chez ces fils de putes ca recrute <br><br>Qui a le droit de rendre justice <br>Seraient ce ces porcs Dis moi si j'ai tort <br>Dis moi si comme moi ils te font prejudice <br>J'les hais me demande pas pourquoi <br>Moi j'connais pas d'keuf gentil ou courtois <br>Qui a le droit de rendre justice <br>Seraient ce ces porcs Dis moi si j'ai tort <br>Dis moi si comme moi ils te font prejudice <br>Maintenant que dire des Arabes et des Noirs places dans leurs services <br><br>Le sujet traite de flics donc j'me dois d'etre severe <br>J'peux pas commencer mon couplet sans la speciale nique sa <br>Mere <br>Dedie a tous ces fils de putes qui militent pour c'pays <br>De la BAC jusqu'aux hommes en treillis <br>Tous petes a la vinasse, une haleine qui sent fort <br>Un kepi, une traque ma, un flingue, ca les rend fort <br>Quand la tension te mon, Raymond appelle du renfort <br>ca joue l'homme fier et fort <br>Sous l'uniforme ca sent l'porc <br>J'ai dix mesures pour m'exprimer, mon couplet j'le resume <br>Nique sa mere la police que leur drapeau se consume <br><br>J'ai depuis longtemps opte pour le raisonnement bete et mechant simple <br>Comme bonjour, pour moi y a pa d'keuf ti gen maint' <br>Et maintes fois malmene pour delit d'facies <br>Lyrics sentis fils de tain p' que j'postillone dans leur face <br>Yes yes yo <br>CRS galbes comme des bestiaux <br>Belek les mecs c'est soir ce, ca ti par en test yo <br>Rap a demi mesure ou de politesse yo <br>Lansso ne rale pas on est pas la <br>Dans l'but de wesh des pipots la <br>T'affole pas on s'en bat la <br>Race a un bon oint j de popo dans l'bec <br>Histoire de narguer la BAC mec <br><br>Qui a le droit de rendre justice <br>Seraient ce ces porcs Dis moi si j'ai tort <br>Dis moi si comme moi ils te font prejudice <br>Le jour ou je subirais la sentence <br>Je niquerais les keufs a distance <br>Qui a le droit de rendre justice <br>Seraient ce ces porcs Dis moi si j'ai tort <br>Dis moi si comme moi ils te font prejudice <br>Quand on vit dans une tess c'est comme ca qu'c'est <br><br>Si t'es mal vu par ces gens la, fait pas l'dur <br>En cas d'controle, reste cool <br>J'dis pas qu'faut faire l'bouffon, faut eviter les bavures <br>Ce s'rait bete de s'manger une balle parce que tu fais l'brave <br>Car une gaffe peut t'arriver en un seul geste <br>Fait son taff, ouais <br>ca d'vient plus frequent de nos jours <br>Des personnes qu'on tabasse a mort <br>En garde a vue prenez garde a vous <br>Parce qu'il y a plus de corrompus alors <br>Sauve toi d'la quand ca pue l'porc <br>Une famille qui pleure est egale a un commissariat qui rigole tout l'temps <br>Disant ce bougnoule n'a pas eu d'bol putain <br>Jamais d'inculpation <br>Esclave devient une occupation <br>Mettre en sang un black avant incarceration <br>Garcon, j'te comprends si t'as la haine <br>Apres toutes ces patrouilles qui vadrouillent soit disant <br>C'est meme pas la peine <br>a croire qu'on est tous vus comme des hyenes <br>Comme des betes sauvages qu'on elimine dans un travail a la chaine <br>Pourquoi faut il qu'ils aient les nerfs apres nous les jeunes de banlieues <br>Est ce leur salaire qui fait que <br>Nous on s'en sort comme on peut <br>Meme s'il nous arrive de pas se faire de la maille honnete <br>C'est pas pour autant qu'il faut nous traiter comme des marionnettes <br><br>Qui a le droit de rendre justice <br>Seraient ce ces porcs Dis moi si j'ai tort <br>Dis moi si comme moi ils te font prejudice <br>J'les hais me demande pas pourquoi <br>Moi j'connais pas d'keuf gentil ou courtois <br>Qui a le droit de rendre justice <br>Seraient ce ces porcs Dis moi si j'ai tort <br>Dis moi si comme moi ils te font prejudice <br>Maintenant que dire des Arabes et des Noirs places dans <br>Leurs services <br><br>Qui a le droit de rendre justice <br>Seraient ce ces porcs Dis moi si j'ai tort <br>Dis moi si comme moi ils te font prejudice <br>Le jour ou je subirais la sentence <br>Je niquerais les keufs a distance <br>Qui a le droit de rendre justice <br>Seraient ce ces porcs Dis moi si j'ai tort <br>Dis moi si comme moi ils te font prejudice <br>Quand on vit dans une tess c'est comme ca qu'c'est]]></content><category term="K Special" label="K Special"/><category term="Les Porcs (Feat. Sniper)" label="Les Porcs (Feat. Sniper)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유재환/첫_이별/</id><title>유재환 - 첫 이별 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:02:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:02:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EC%9E%AC%ED%99%98/%EC%B2%AB_%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84/" title="유재환 - 첫 이별 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[추우니까 들어가 나 괜찮아 <br>신경 쓰지 말고 들어가 <br>사실은 너 없는 하루가 처음이라 <br>무서워져 점점 <br>옆에 있느라 고생했어 <br>힘들었지 너 그동안 <br>모자란 나 너의 맘에 <br>들었을지 모르겠어 잘 <br>너와 함께한 많은 날들이 <br>내게는 가장 귀한 순간들이 <br>눈을 감아도 수채화처럼 번져 <br>웃어주는 너 <br>너와 함께 처음 하는 이별이 <br>처음이라 방법을 잘 모르겠어 <br>내 앞에서 늘 웃음 짓던 너처럼 <br>웃어주는 나 <br>눈을 떴을 때 있던 네가 <br>이젠 눈을 감아야지 <br>보이는 게 마음 아파도 <br>보고 싶어 눈 감았어 <br>내게 미안해하던 표정도 <br>조금씩 멀어지는 뒷모습도 <br>오래 담으려 해도 눈물에 가려 <br>사라지는 너 <br>너와 함께 만들어간 세상도 <br>마지막 인사와 함께 무너져가 <br>함께 꾸던 그 언젠가의 꿈처럼 <br>사라지는 나 <br>]]></content><category term="유재환" label="유재환"/><category term="첫 이별" label="첫 이별"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유재환/The_Alchemist/</id><title>유재환 - The Alchemist - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:02:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:02:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EC%9E%AC%ED%99%98/The_Alchemist/" title="유재환 - The Alchemist - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[거울 속 내 모습 보다가 <br>문득 내가 다른 사람 같아 <br>나도 모르는 모습을 만들어 <br>그 안에 난 누구일까 <br>나 아닌 것에 맞추려다 <br>서서히 잃어가는 것 같아 <br>뭐가 진짜 나인지 모르겠어 <br>무서워 내가 사라질까봐 <br>No one's an alchemist <br>There is no alchemist <br>그 모든 게 나니까 <br>우린 돌아오니까 <br>우린 돌아오니까 <br>밤하늘 별들을 보다가 <br>이름 모를 공허함에 잠겨 <br>살아가는 건 무언 갈 얻으려 <br>잃어가는 과정일까 <br>너무 많은 걸 바꾸려다 <br>부질없는 일임을 또 느껴 <br>정해진 건 움직이지 않는걸 <br>알면서 잡아도 괜찮을까 <br>No one's an alchemist <br>There is no alchemist <br>그 모든 게 나니까 <br>우린 돌아오니까 <br>우린 돌아오니까 <br>지난 겨울 진 꽃이 <br>오늘은 피겠지 <br>어젯밤에 진달이 <br>오늘도 뜨겠지 <br>그 모든 게 나니까 <br>우린 돌아올 거야 <br>No one's an alchemist <br>There is no alchemist <br>]]></content><category term="유재환" label="유재환"/><category term="The Alchemist" label="The Alchemist"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유재환/Universe_With_양요섭/</id><title>유재환 - Universe (With 양요섭) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:02:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:02:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EC%9E%AC%ED%99%98/Universe_With_%EC%96%91%EC%9A%94%EC%84%AD/" title="유재환 - Universe (With 양요섭) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Universe 오늘 너의 그 느낌 <br>처음 느껴본 이 느낌 <br>널 안으려고 한발 다가가도 <br>너는 점점 멀어지지 <br>흔히 볼 수 없는 <br>너의 모습이 <br>떠다니네 나의 주윌 <br>너를 벗어나려 <br>하지도 못하게 <br>더 꽉 잡아두고서 <br>round we go <br>이 흐름 속에 잠기네 <br>Babe I'd fall to you <br>언제라도 어디라도 <br>널 찾을 수 있어 <br>I'd fall to you 나의 눈에 <br>보이지 않더라도 <br>너에게로 빨려들어 <br>블랙홀처럼 빠져 <br>only you <br>밤하늘 사라지는 <br>유성일지라도 <br>I fall in love <br>영원히 널 안고선 <br>Fly the universe to you <br>너에게 날아가 <br>hey you're the universe <br>the universe <br>You're my the universe <br>Hey you <br>You're the universe <br>universe universe <br>넌 우주이고 <br>나의 그 모든 것 <br>I'm the universe <br>the universe universe universe <br>흔히 볼 수 없는 <br>네 우아함에 <br>멎어버려 내 숨이 <br>널 품에 안고 <br>입을 맞춘 순간 <br>이 순간도 숨이 멎지 <br>Babe I'd fall to you <br>언제라도 어디라도 <br>네게 갈 수 있어 <br>I'd fall to you 나의 손에 <br>잡히지 않더라도 <br>너에게로 빨려들어 <br>블랙홀처럼 빠져 <br>only you <br>밤하늘 사라지는 <br>유성일지라도 <br>I fall in love <br>영원히 널 안고선 <br>Fly the universe to you <br>너에게 날아가 <br>Hey you're the universe <br>the universe <br>You're my the universe <br>Hey you <br>You're the universe <br>universe universe <br>넌 우주이고 <br>나의 그 모든 것 <br>I'm the universe <br>the universe universe universe <br>블랙홀처럼 빠져 <br>only you <br>별처럼 한순간의 <br>사랑일지라도 <br>I fall in love <br>영원히 널 안고선 <br>Fly the universe to you <br>너에게 달려가 <br>블랙홀처럼 빠져 <br>only you <br>밤하늘 사라지는 <br>유성일지라도 <br>I fall in love <br>영원히 널 안고선 <br>Fly the universe to you <br>너에게 날아가 <br>Hey you're the universe <br>the universe <br>You're my the universe <br>Hey you <br>You're the universe <br>universe universe <br>넌 우주이고 <br>나의 그 모든 것 <br>I'm the universe <br>the universe universe universe <br>]]></content><category term="유재환" label="유재환"/><category term="Universe (With 양요섭)" label="Universe (With 양요섭)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/혜미/그때_그날_우리_Inst/</id><title>혜미 - 그때 그날 우리 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:03:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:03:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%98%9C%EB%AF%B8/%EA%B7%B8%EB%95%8C_%EA%B7%B8%EB%82%A0_%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_Inst/" title="혜미 - 그때 그날 우리 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[처음 본 그 순간 난 잊을 수가 없죠 <br>아무 말 없이 웃기만 했던 <br>그때 그날 우리 <br>저 햇살이 또 내려주네요 <br>들려주네요 그대 고운 눈길 <br>내게 닿는 어디든 이렇게 <br>다 빛이 되네요 그대 그대라면 <br>알아요 알아요 이게 사랑이란 걸 <br>그토록 나 기다려왔던 그댄 거죠 <br>한걸음 한걸음 <br>조금씩 다가갈게요 <br>더 이상 멀어지지 마요 <br>내 곁에서 <br>손에 닿을 듯한 가까운 그대인데 <br>맘을 붙잡고 입을 막았던 <br>그때 그날 우리 <br>저 바람이 또 흩날리네요 <br>차오르네요 그대 여린 미소 <br>기다리면 시간이 흐르면 <br>그대가 올까요 내게 꿈에라도 <br>알아요 알아요 이게 사랑이란 걸 <br>그토록 나 기다려왔던 그댄 거죠 <br>한걸음 한걸음 <br>조금씩 다가갈게요 <br>더 이상 멀어지지 마요 <br>내 맘을 들어줘요 <br>다시 그댈 보게 될까요 <br>난 눈을 감아요 <br>꿈에서라도 그대가 올까 봐 <br>사랑해 사랑해 맘으로만 불렀던 <br>내 맘을 이젠 그대에게 말할래요 <br>영원히 그대만 <br>그대만 사랑할래요 <br>이렇게 그대만 부르는 내 맘을 <br>들어줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="혜미" label="혜미"/><category term="그때 그날 우리 (Inst.)" label="그때 그날 우리 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/혜미/그때_그날_우리/</id><title>혜미 - 그때 그날 우리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:03:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:03:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%98%9C%EB%AF%B8/%EA%B7%B8%EB%95%8C_%EA%B7%B8%EB%82%A0_%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC/" title="혜미 - 그때 그날 우리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[처음 본 그 순간 난 잊을 수가 없죠 <br>아무 말 없이 웃기만 했던 <br>그때 그날 우리 <br>저 햇살이 또 내려주네요 <br>들려주네요 그대 고운 눈길 <br>내게 닿는 어디든 이렇게 <br>다 빛이 되네요 그대 그대라면 <br>알아요 알아요 이게 사랑이란 걸 <br>그토록 나 기다려왔던 그댄 거죠 <br>한걸음 한걸음 <br>조금씩 다가갈게요 <br>더 이상 멀어지지 마요 <br>내 곁에서 <br>손에 닿을 듯한 가까운 그대인데 <br>맘을 붙잡고 입을 막았던 <br>그때 그날 우리 <br>저 바람이 또 흩날리네요 <br>차오르네요 그대 여린 미소 <br>기다리면 시간이 흐르면 <br>그대가 올까요 내게 꿈에라도 <br>알아요 알아요 이게 사랑이란 걸 <br>그토록 나 기다려왔던 그댄 거죠 <br>한걸음 한걸음 <br>조금씩 다가갈게요 <br>더 이상 멀어지지 마요 <br>내 맘을 들어줘요 <br>다시 그댈 보게 될까요 <br>난 눈을 감아요 <br>꿈에서라도 그대가 올까 봐 <br>사랑해 사랑해 맘으로만 불렀던 <br>내 맘을 이젠 그대에게 말할래요 <br>영원히 그대만 <br>그대만 사랑할래요 <br>이렇게 그대만 부르는 내 맘을 <br>들어줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="혜미" label="혜미"/><category term="그때 그날 우리" label="그때 그날 우리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한효택/Feel_Me_Feat_윤인영/</id><title>한효택 - Feel Me (Feat. 윤인영) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:03:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:03:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%ED%9A%A8%ED%83%9D/Feel_Me_Feat_%EC%9C%A4%EC%9D%B8%EC%98%81/" title="한효택 - Feel Me (Feat. 윤인영) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[feel me I will be your light <br>feel me I will be your hope <br>I know it's dark and you <br>feel alone <br>when the light goes down <br>I know it's hard that you <br>lose yourself <br>when the light shines bright <br>You never know <br>what tomorrow <br>will be like <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Don't be afraid to be <br>the one you dream of <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Feel me <br>Wherever you go <br>I'll be your light <br>Feel me <br>Wherever you walk <br>I'll be your hope <br>Feel me <br>Sometimes it looks dark <br>but you know <br>Feel me <br>I'm with you forever <br>Oh Oh Oh <br>I know you can't see <br>who you are <br>the treasure that you are <br>I know you can be <br>more than this <br>More than what they say <br>So hold my hand and let's <br>take on this youth now <br>youth now <br>you youth now <br>No second chance it's time <br>to be who you are <br>Wa Wa Wa Wa Wa <br>Wa Wa Wa Wa Wa <br>Feel me <br>wherever you go <br>I'll be your light <br>Feel me <br>Wherever you walk <br>I'll be your hope <br>Feel me <br>sometimes it looks dark <br>but you know <br>Feel me <br>I'm with you forever <br>Feel me <br>Sometimes it looks dark <br>but you know <br>Feel me <br>I'm with you forever <br>Oh Oh Oh <br>]]></content><category term="한효택" label="한효택"/><category term="Feel Me (Feat. 윤인영)" label="Feel Me (Feat. 윤인영)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Syd/Body/</id><title>Syd - Body - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:03:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:03:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Syd/Body/" title="Syd - Body - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Drink in your glass <br>You drinking it fast <br>I'm watching you dance <br>You’re watching my hands <br>Throw it back babe <br>Give it to me don't hold back babe <br>If your friends could see you <br>right now <br>No lying girl I bet <br>they'd wanna be you right now <br>Your body's takin over you <br>Your body's takin over you <br>Baby we can take it slow <br>say my name <br>Don't let go <br>I can hear your body when I <br>Pull your hair <br>what’s my name <br>Girl I swear <br>I can hear your body babe <br>The bed is your stage <br>Take it away <br>Put on a show <br>Put on a play <br>Don't ask babe <br>You know I'm your <br>number one fan babe <br>So <br>Get those cameras <br>rollin right now <br>I’m directing <br>and I really wanna see you act out <br>Let your body take over you <br>Your body's takin over you <br>Now baby we can take it slow <br>say my name <br>Don't let go <br>I can hear your body when I <br>Pull your hair <br>what’s my name <br>Girl I swear <br>I can hear your body babe <br>Now baby we can take it slow <br>say my name <br>Don't let go <br>I can hear your body when I <br>Pull your hair <br>what’s my name <br>Girl I swear <br>I can hear your body babe <br>Ladies say <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Yeah hey hey hey hey hey hey <br>yeah hey hey hey hey hey hey <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>My ladies say <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Yeah hey hey hey hey hey hey <br>yeah hey hey hey hey hey hey <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>Now baby we can take it slow <br>say my name <br>Don't let go <br>I can hear your body when I <br>Pull your hair <br>what’s my name <br>Girl I swear <br>I can hear your body babe <br>Now baby we can take it slow <br>say my name <br>Don't let go <br>I can hear your body when I <br>Pull your hair <br>what’s my name <br>Girl I swear <br>I can hear your body babe <br>Take it slow <br>]]></content><category term="Syd" label="Syd"/><category term="Body" label="Body"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/진재/연화/</id><title>진재 - 연화 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:04:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:04:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%84%EC%9E%AC/%EC%97%B0%ED%99%94/" title="진재 - 연화 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[시간이 흘러 <br>이젠 지쳐버린 내가 <br>본적 없는 진흙 속에 <br>그 꽃처럼 <br>넘어지고 다쳐도 <br>뒤돌아 봤을 때 <br>후회는 없다 생각했는데 <br>다가온 세상에 숨겨둔 <br>날 얼마나 지울까 <br>떠나간 내가 조금만 <br>덜 아프다면 <br>모른 채 향기롭게 <br>꽃을 피울 텐데 <br>맘속에 담아만 <br>두기엔 힘겨워서 <br>흩날려버린 추억 <br>얼마나 아름다운지 <br>아름다운지 <br>아름다운지 <br>아무 말없이 걷던 <br>아픈 거릴 보며 <br>조금 더 가면 작은 <br>소리라도 낼까 <br>넘어지고 다쳐도 <br>뒤돌아 봤을 때 <br>후회는 없다 생각했는데 <br>다가온 세상에 숨겨둔 <br>날 얼마나 지울까 <br>떠나간 내가 조금만 <br>덜 아프다면 <br>모른 채 향기롭게 <br>꽃을 피울 텐데 <br>맘속에 담아만 <br>두기엔 힘겨워서 <br>흩날려버린 추억 <br>얼마나 아름다운지 <br>아름다운지 <br>아름다운지 <br>시간이 흘러 <br>이젠 지쳐버린 내가 <br>본적 없는 진흙 속에 <br>그 꽃처럼 <br>]]></content><category term="진재" label="진재"/><category term="연화" label="연화"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김홍석/과거가_없는_남자/</id><title>김홍석 - 과거가 없는 남자 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:04:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:04:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%99%8D%EC%84%9D/%EA%B3%BC%EA%B1%B0%EA%B0%80_%EC%97%86%EB%8A%94_%EB%82%A8%EC%9E%90/" title="김홍석 - 과거가 없는 남자 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 과거가 없어 잃어버렸지 <br>흔들리던 술잔에 빠뜨려버렸어 <br>넋을 놓고 있다 도둑 맞았나 <br>하지만 난 지금 행복한 것 같아 <br>피하지 말아줘 <br>너에게 똑바로 걸어 갈 거야 <br>이제는 해피투게더 <br>오 그렇게 <br>그래요 해피투게더 <br>눈물 없는 미래만 있을 뿐 <br>난 미래가 있어 그렇게라도 <br>믿고 싶은 건 내 작은 행복 <br>아무것도 몰라 내 이름도 몰라 <br>하지만 난 지금 행복한 것 같아 <br>피하지 말아줘 <br>너에게 똑바로 걸어 갈 거야 <br>이제는 해피투게더 <br>오 그렇게 <br>그래요 해피투게더 <br>눈물 없는 미래만 있을 뿐 <br>이제는 해피투게더 <br>오 그렇게 <br>그래요 해피투게더 <br>눈물 없는 미래만이 <br>오 내겐 미래만이 <br>눈물 없는 미래만 있을 뿐 <br>]]></content><category term="김홍석" label="김홍석"/><category term="과거가 없는 남자" label="과거가 없는 남자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김홍석/그녀같은_그녀/</id><title>김홍석 - 그녀같은 그녀 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:04:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:04:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%99%8D%EC%84%9D/%EA%B7%B8%EB%85%80%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EA%B7%B8%EB%85%80/" title="김홍석 - 그녀같은 그녀 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그녀 같은 그녀를 만났다 <br>이제 원래 그녀 같은 그녀는 없다 <br>매일 서로 감싸 안고 <br>서로 보듬던 날들 <br>눈물로 시를 쓰던 날들 <br>내 앞에 있는 그녀를 보며 <br>그때로 돌아가고 싶진 <br>않다고 말했다 <br>어이없이 웃고만 있었지 <br>말로 모든 것을 말하던 <br>그때가 생각이 나서 피식 웃었다 <br>눈물로 시를 쓰던 날들 <br>내 앞에 있는 그녀를 보며 <br>그때로 돌아가고 싶진 <br>않다고 말했다 <br>눈물로 시를 쓰던 날들 <br>내 앞에 있는 그녀를 보며 <br>그때로 돌아가고 싶진 <br>않다고 말했다 <br>라라라라 <br>라라라라 <br>라라라라 <br>라라라라 <br>라라라라라 <br>라라라라 <br>라라 <br>라라 <br>]]></content><category term="김홍석" label="김홍석"/><category term="그녀같은 그녀" label="그녀같은 그녀"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/만수/연습벌레/</id><title>만수 - 연습벌레 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:04:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:04:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%8C%EC%88%98/%EC%97%B0%EC%8A%B5%EB%B2%8C%EB%A0%88/" title="만수 - 연습벌레 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나도 내가 싫어 내버려둬 <br>거울 보는 것도 더러워 <br>랩 한다고 암만 나대도 <br>걍 백수 촌놈 황인종 두개골 <br>알고 있어 나는 무가치해 <br>게으름과 매일 친한 티 내 <br>지난 니넨 EP와 믹테 <br>싱글을 냈지만 뭔가 keep해 <br>둘게 없어 그래 난 한심해 <br>허슬하자 말해도 치매 <br>작심삼일 아냐 낼 아침에 <br>똥을 싸지 씨와이 위에 <br>할말 없어 존재가 이래 <br>뢈이라고 막 쓰고 삐대 <br>누가 날 좀 잡아다 패줘 <br>양심에 털이 났어 like 청문회 <br>야 이 친구야 <br>뭘 그렇게 너의 치부를 <br>좋다고 떠들어대 <br>남들 다 하듯이 <br>스웨거를 해 <br>여기 애들은 <br>죄다 겉멋 들었대 <br>편의점 폐기로 EP를 냈던 <br>그 패기 내뿜어 자연스럽게 <br>김동희 피디가 만들어줬잖아 <br>자 다시 보여줘 연습벌레 <br>니나노 니나노 <br>그냥 놀고 먹고 자자 <br>인생 뭐 별거 있나 <br>복권이나 하나 사자 <br>허슬 따윈 너나 해라 <br>여긴 티끌 모아 티끌 <br>한 우물 암만 파라 <br>빽 없으면 너도 B급 <br>니나노 니나노 <br>그냥 놀고 먹고 자자 <br>인생 뭐 별거 있나 <br>복권이나 하나 사자 <br>허슬 따윈 너나 해라 <br>여긴 티끌 모아 티끌 <br>한 우물 암만 파라 <br>빽 없으면 너도 B급 <br>그래 한심하지 랩 하러 와서 <br>너프만 되고 석양만 졌어 <br>형들은 내게 비트에 <br>몸을 맡기라 했지 <br>근데 난 죽었어 <br>역시 난 음악을 한다고 <br>말 하기 부끄러 <br>하늘에 정의가 빗발침 <br>뢈 치는 꼬라지가 걸릴 건 <br>심의 유통사에 <br>못을 박으려 해 <br>망치 나가심 <br>아나 이런 나의 <br>팬들땜에 안되겠어 <br>강해져 걍 돌격할래 <br>이젠 안 죽어 영웅이여 <br>일어나셈 라임 폭탄 받아라 <br>마디 포착할 때 <br>그래 꼼짝마 움직이지마 <br>플로 모두 발사 <br>여기 내 자리야 <br>그런 기념으로 <br>왕의 길 하고 작업할게 <br>아 피곤해 힘들어 자고 담에 <br>야 이 친구야 <br>뭘 그렇게 너의 치부를 <br>좋다고 떠들어대 <br>남들 다 하듯이 <br>스웨거를 해 <br>여기 애들은 <br>죄다 겉멋 들었대 <br>편의점 폐기로 <br>EP를 냈던 그 패기 <br>내뿜어 자연스럽게 <br>김동희 피디가 만들어줬잖아 <br>자 다시 보여줘 연습벌레 <br>니나노 니나노 <br>그냥 놀고 먹고 자자 <br>인생 뭐 별거 있나 <br>복권이나 하나 사자 <br>허슬 따윈 너나 해라 <br>여긴 티끌 모아 티끌 <br>한 우물 암만 파라 <br>빽 없으면 너도 B급 <br>니나노 니나노 <br>그냥 놀고 먹고 자자 <br>인생 뭐 별거 있나 <br>복권이나 하나 사자 <br>허슬 따윈 너나 해라 <br>여긴 티끌 모아 티끌 <br>한 우물 암만 파라 <br>빽 없으면 너도 B급 <br>친구들은 날 떠나갔어 <br>형아들은 날 떠나갔어 <br>여자들은 날 떠나갔어 <br>전 여친은 날 떠나갔어 <br>친구들은 이미 날 떠나갔어 <br>형아들은 이미 날 떠나갔어 <br>여자들은 이미 날 떠나갔어 <br>전 여친은 이미 날 떠나갔어 <br>내게 남은 거라고는 <br>회사의 바람 <br>근데 녹음 하는 법도 <br>잊어버렸지 난 빠가 <br>어느 샌가 멀어진 <br>힙합의 대한 정의 <br>나름 느끼려 해도 <br>맘처럼 되지 않아 <br>음악은 아마 내게 <br>어울리지 않는 가봐 <br>지금 당장이라도 <br>집으로 갈까 <br>알바고 나발이고 <br>시급보다 시급한 건 <br>이미 정해져 버린 <br>월급이 아닐까 <br>근데 나 가기 싫어 <br>이제 열심히 할래 <br>아빠처럼 되긴 싫어 <br>무시할래 내 한계 <br>이전 것들은 버려 <br>올해 정규 명반에 <br>우리 고모의 손엔 <br>한 보따리 샤넬 <br>해녀는 끝야 이제 <br>잠수 안 타 내 꿈을 넓힐래 <br>이건 장수왕 뢈 <br>가짜 급식들 <br>만수로 국정화 해 <br>검정 래퍼는 밝은 <br>내 미래 앞에 kiiling <br>니나노 니나노 <br>그냥 놀고 먹고 자라 <br>인생 뭐 별거 있나 <br>복권이나 하나 사라 <br>허슬 따윈 내가 한다 <br>너흰 티끌 모아 티끌 <br>한 우물 내가 판다 <br>벗어날게 여기 B급 <br>니나노 니나노 <br>그냥 놀고 먹고 자라 <br>인생 뭐 별거 있나 <br>복권이나 하나 사라 <br>허슬 따윈 내가 한다 <br>너흰 티끌 모아 티끌 <br>한 우물 내가 판다 <br>벗어날게 여기 B급 <br>]]></content><category term="만수" label="만수"/><category term="연습벌레" label="연습벌레"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NA_엔에이/후회_그리고_다짐/</id><title>N.A (엔.에이) - 후회, 그리고 다짐 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:04:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:04:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NA_%EC%97%94%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4/%ED%9B%84%ED%9A%8C_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EA%B3%A0_%EB%8B%A4%EC%A7%90/" title="N.A (엔.에이) - 후회, 그리고 다짐 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[후회하기엔 커버렸지 <br>돌이킬 수도 없겠지 <br>아무리 노력을 해봐도 <br>돌아보면 남아있던 건 <br>나뿐이었네 <br>해봤자 안될거라는 말 <br>어차피 안될거라는 말 <br>누군가 내게 속삭이고 <br>내려놓겠다고 다짐했던 <br>맘 어딘가 아려오는 밤에 <br>조용히 눈을 감다 <br>후회하기엔 커버렸지 <br>돌이킬 수도 없겠지 <br>아무리 노력을 해봐도 <br>돌아보면 남아있던 건 <br>나뿐이었네 <br>해봤자 안될거라는 말 <br>어차피 안될거라는 말 <br>누군가 내게 속삭이고 <br>내려놓겠다고 다짐했던 <br>맘 어딘가 아려오는 밤에 <br>조용히 눈을 감다 <br>다가가면 물러서는 <br>나의 모습을 <br>어떡하면 살릴 수 있을까 <br>넘어지고 힘들어도 <br>이것 모두다 <br>나를 위한거라고 <br>아파서 포기하고 싶지만 <br>내가하는 것이 아니라고 <br>누군가 내맘 토닥이며 <br>이 약속 지키겠노라고 <br>다짐하던 나의 기도앞에 <br>조용히 눈을 감다 <br>아파서 포기하고 싶지만 <br>내가하는 것이 아니라고 <br>누군가 내맘 토닥이며 <br>이 약속 지키겠노라고 <br>다짐하던 나의 기도앞에 <br>조용히 눈을 감다 <br>Kannst Du Mir Helfen <br>Ich Weiss Nicht <br>Was Ich Tun Soll <br>Kannst Du Mir Helfen <br>Ich Weiss Nicht <br>Was Ich Tun Soll <br>]]></content><category term="N.A (엔.에이)" label="N.A (엔.에이)"/><category term="후회, 그리고 다짐" label="후회, 그리고 다짐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정나현/사랑하니까/</id><title>정나현 - 사랑하니까 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:04:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:04:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EB%82%98%ED%98%84/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%98%EB%8B%88%EA%B9%8C/" title="정나현 - 사랑하니까 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아니라는거 알죠 <br>안된다고 말하죠 <br>서로가 달라서 <br>그래서 더 아픈가봐요 <br>다가온 내 사랑이 <br>그대라서 너무 아프죠 <br>나 어떡하나요 <br>혼자 그댈 떠올려 본다 <br>사랑하는데 <br>널 가질 수도 없죠 <br>밀어내려고 노력 <br>해봐도 안돼 <br>조용히 혼자 남아 <br>가슴아픈 마음들로 <br>소리쳐 그댈 불러본다 <br>사랑하면 할수록 <br>깊어지는 내맘을 <br>어쩔수가 없죠 <br>그래서 더 힘든가봐요 <br>찾으려던 사람이 <br>그대라서 내가 아프죠 <br>나 어떡할까요 <br>점점 되돌릴수가 없죠 <br>사랑하는데 <br>널 가질수도 없죠 <br>밀어내려고 노력 <br>해봐도 안돼 <br>조용히 혼자 남아 <br>가슴아픈 마음들로 <br>소리쳐 그댈 불러본다 <br>자꾸만 눈물이 흘러 <br>하염없이 바보처럼 <br>그댈 바라본다 <br>사랑하니까 사랑하니까 <br>이렇게 우리 <br>헤어지면은 안돼 <br>한없이 밀려오는 <br>아픈 추억들만 남아 <br>가슴속 너를 새겨본다 <br>이렇게 너를 그려본다 <br>]]></content><category term="정나현" label="정나현"/><category term="사랑하니까" label="사랑하니까"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/고은성/Incanto/</id><title>고은성 - Incanto - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:04:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:04:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%A0%EC%9D%80%EC%84%B1/Incanto/" title="고은성 - Incanto - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sanctus sanctus <br>Dominus deus <br>Offerete domino <br>Gloria et honorem <br>Sanctus sanctus <br>Dominus deus <br>Offerete domino <br>Gloria et honorem <br>L’amore che io canto <br>E' pagina d’eterno <br>Airone che mai <br>Nessuno potra <br>Imprigionare in noi <br>Bandiera di una fede <br>Piu bianca della neve <br>Battito che <br>Dovunque sarai <br>Non ti abbondondera <br>Amor che hai visto i secoli <br>andar via <br>Sopravvivendo alla follia <br>Che acceca gli uomini e gli dei <br>Amore senza fine e senz’addio <br>Come Giulietta amo <br>Romeo E Romeo la ricambio <br>Incanto d’amor <br>Fenice che risorge <br>Dal buio e dalla morte <br>Tormente e poesia <br>Dorata alchimia <br>Che dentro di noi <br>Non morira mai <br>Amor che hai visto <br>i secoli andar via <br>Castelli e regni in polvere <br>Nell’infinito correre <br>Amore senza fine e senz’addio <br>Di Giulietta e di Romeo <br>Che anche l’odio trasformo <br>Incanto d’amor <br>Sanctus sanctus <br>Dominus deus <br>Offerete domino <br>Gloria et honorem <br>Sanctus sanctus <br>Dominus deus <br>Offerete domino <br>Gloria et honorem <br>Sanctus sanctus <br>Dominus deus <br>Offerete domino <br>Gloria et honorem <br>Sanctus sanctus <br>Dominus deus <br>Offerete domino <br>Gloria et honorem <br>Amor che hai visto <br>i secoli andar via <br>Sopravvivendo alla follia <br>Che acceca gli uomini e gli dei <br>Amore senza fine e senz’addio <br>Come Giulietta amo <br>Romeo E Romeo la ricambio <br>Incanto d’amor <br>Incanto d’amor <br>]]></content><category term="고은성" label="고은성"/><category term="Incanto" label="Incanto"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백인태/El_Triste/</id><title>백인태 - El Triste - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:04:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:04:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%EC%9D%B8%ED%83%9C/El_Triste/" title="백인태 - El Triste - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Que triste fue decirnos adios <br>Cuando nos adorabamos mas <br>Hasta la golondrina emigro <br>Presagiando el final <br>Que triste luce todo sin ti <br>Los mares de las playas se van <br>Se tinen los colores de gris <br>Hoy todo es soledad <br>No se si vuelva a verte despues <br>No se que de mi vida sera <br>Sin el lucero azul de tu ser <br>Que no me alumbra ya <br>Hoy quiero saborear mi dolor <br>No pido compasion ni piedad <br>La historia de este amor se <br>escribio <br>Para la eternidad <br>Que triste todos dicen que soy <br>Que siempre estoy hablando de ti <br>No saben que pensando en tu <br>amor En tu amor <br>He podido ayudarme a vivir <br>He podido ayudarme a vivir <br>Hoy quiero saborear mi dolor <br>No pido compasion ni piedad <br>La historia de este amor se <br>escribio <br>Para la eternidad <br>Que triste todos dicen que soy <br>Que siempre estoy hablando de ti <br>No saben que pensando en tu <br>amor En tu amor <br>He podido ayudarme a vivir <br>He podido ayudarme a vivir <br>]]></content><category term="백인태" label="백인태"/><category term="El Triste" label="El Triste"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/고훈정/Adagio/</id><title>고훈정 - Adagio - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:04:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:04:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%A0%ED%9B%88%EC%A0%95/Adagio/" title="고훈정 - Adagio - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Non so dove trovarti <br>non so come cercarti <br>Ma sento una voce che <br>nel vento parla di te <br>Quest'anima senza cuore <br>aspetta te adagio <br>Le notti senza pelle <br>i sogni senza stelle <br>Immagini del tuo viso <br>che passano all'improvviso <br>Mi fanno sperare ancora <br>che ti trovero <br>adagio <br>Chiudo gli occhi e vedo te <br>trovo il cammino che <br>mi porta via dall'agonia <br>Sento battere in me <br>questa musica che <br>ho inventato per te <br>Se sai come trovarmi <br>se sai dove cercarmi <br>abbracciami con la mente <br>il sole mi sembra spento <br>accendi il tuo nome in cielo <br>Dimmi che ci sei <br>Quello che vorrei <br>Vivere in te <br>Il sole mi sembra spento <br>abbracciami con la mente <br>smarrita senza di te <br>Dimmi che ci sei <br>e ci credero <br>musica sei <br>Non so dove trovarti <br>non so come cercarti <br>Adagio <br>]]></content><category term="고훈정" label="고훈정"/><category term="Adagio" label="Adagio"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/고은성/Il_Tempo_Vola/</id><title>고은성 - Il Tempo Vola - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:05:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:05:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%A0%EC%9D%80%EC%84%B1/Il_Tempo_Vola/" title="고은성 - Il Tempo Vola - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Vieni qui da me <br>presto qui da me <br>qui fa giorno e io lo farei con te <br>qui fa notte e io la farei con te <br>qui ci sono io che penso a te <br>Se mi affaccio c'e anche <br>un cielo per <br>me anche il sole c'e o le nuvole <br>o millenni di stelle brillano <br>finche io le spengo all'alba <br>Il tempo vola <br>questa frase se n'esce da sola <br>io non volevo <br>ne pensarla <br>ne dirla ma e andata <br>E' l'amore un po' infantile <br>e una cosa un po' infantile <br>non e un gioco ma <br>come un gioco si vince e si perde <br>la felicita Oh <br>E per questo che noi ci giochiamo <br>questo amore a ogni amore <br>che per gioco noi facciamo <br>E' per questo che con il tempo <br>ci sfugge che cosa l'amore sia <br>Vieni qui da me <br>presto vieni da me <br>tutto il tempo troppo senza te <br>ogni spazio e vuoto intorno a me <br>e sto al centro muto e penso <br>Il tempo vola <br>vola il tempo che avra le sue frette <br>Il tempo vola <br>ogni giorno diventa la notte <br>E' l'amore un po' infantile <br>e una cosa un po' infantile <br>non e un gioco ma <br>come un gioco si vince e si perde <br>la felicita Oh <br>E per questo che noi ci giochiamo <br>questo amore a ogni amore <br>che per gioco noi facciamo <br>Sara per questo che <br>con il tempo ci sfugge che cosa <br>Il tempo vola <br>Il tempo vola <br>Il tempo vola <br>ogni giorno diventa la notte <br>Qui ci sono i miei occhi che io <br>vivo tu fingi di essere qui con me <br>le palpebre ti stringono <br>ti stringono <br>Poi i miei occhi si aprono <br>come porte sbattute tu te ne vai <br>ma non mi dici addio <br>E' l'amore un po' infantile <br>]]></content><category term="고은성" label="고은성"/><category term="Il Tempo Vola" label="Il Tempo Vola"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백인태/La_Sete_Di_Vivere/</id><title>백인태 - La Sete Di Vivere - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:05:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:05:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%EC%9D%B8%ED%83%9C/La_Sete_Di_Vivere/" title="백인태 - La Sete Di Vivere - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Luna sopra di noi <br>Di quale amore ci innamorerai <br>Stella caduta ieri <br>Difendi ancora i miei desideri <br>Il tempo ci porta via <br>E passa attraverso me <br>Un brivido che <br>Diventa gia poesia <br>Vorrei soltanto che <br>Tu fossi qui con me <br>Bere dalle tue mani <br>Perdermi nel mare` <br>Sogno ancora di dividere <br>Questa sete che ho di vivere <br>Con te sempre con te <br>Solo con te <br>Vita che cosa c'e <br>Dall'altra parte delle nuvole <br>Libera i miei pensieri <br>E che il domani non sia piu ieri <br>Gli amori non hanno eta <br>Vivono dentro noi <br>Poi volano via <br>Il vento gli raccontera <br>Vorrei soltanto che <br>Tu fossi qui con me <br>Bere dalle tue mani <br>Perdermi nel mare <br>Sogno ancora di divider <br>Questa sete che ho di vivere <br>Con te sempre con te <br>solo con te <br>Vorrei fermare qui <br>il tempo che verra <br>Lasciare l'anima libera di andare <br>Vite intere per ricominciare <br>Mondi immensi tutti da rifare <br>Con te sempre con te <br>solo con te <br>Sogno ancora di dividere <br>Questa sete che ho di vivere <br>con te sempre con te <br>Vorrei fermare qui <br>il tempo che verra <br>Lasciare l'anima libera di andare <br>Sogno ancora di dividere <br>Questa sete che ho di <br>vivere con te <br>Questa sete che ho di <br>vivere con te <br>]]></content><category term="백인태" label="백인태"/><category term="La Sete Di Vivere" label="La Sete Di Vivere"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/고훈정/베틀노래/</id><title>고훈정 - 베틀노래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:05:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:05:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%A0%ED%9B%88%EC%A0%95/%EB%B2%A0%ED%8B%80%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="고훈정 - 베틀노래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 땀의 한 방울도 <br>날줄에 스며 <br>그대 영혼 감싸기에 <br>따뜻하거라 <br>고즈너기 풀어 감은 <br>고통의 실꾸리 <br>한 평생 오가는 <br>만남의 잉아 <br>우리님 생각과 <br>실실이 짜여 <br>새벽바람 막아줄 <br>실비단이거라 <br>기다리마 <br>기다리마 <br>기다리마 <br>하루에도 열두 번 <br>끊기는 실이여 <br>하루에도 열두 번 <br>끊기는 <br>무작정 풀리기엔 <br>무서운 맘이거든 <br>단번에 끝내기엔 <br>아쉬운 밤이거든 <br>허천들린 사랑가 <br>평생 동안 흘린 눈물 <br>모조리 스며 <br>그대 아픔 덮어주는 <br>비단길 이거라 <br>비단길 이거라 <br>비단길 이거라 <br>]]></content><category term="고훈정" label="고훈정"/><category term="베틀노래" label="베틀노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Gangsta_From_Suicide_Squad_The_Album/</id><title>Kehlani - Gangsta (From Suicide Squad The Album) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:05:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:05:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Gangsta_From_Suicide_Squad_The_Album/" title="Kehlani - Gangsta (From Suicide Squad The Album) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I need a gangsta <br>To love me better <br>Than all the others do <br>To always forgive me <br>Ride or die with me <br>That's just what gangsters do <br><br>I'm fucked up, I'm black and blue <br>I'm built for all the abuse <br>I got secrets that nobody, nobody, nobody knows <br>I'm good on that pussy shit <br>I don't want what I can get <br>I want someone with secrets that nobody, nobody, nobody knows <br><br>I need a gangsta <br>To love me better <br>Than all the others do <br>To always forgive me <br>Ride or die with me <br>That's just what gangsters do <br><br>My freakness is on the loose <br>And running all over you <br>Please, take me to places that nobody, nobody knows <br>You got me hooked up on the feeling <br>You got me hanging from the ceiling <br>Got me up so high I'm barely breathing <br>So don't let me, don't let me, don't let me, don't let me go <br><br>I need a gangsta gangsta gangsta <br>To love me better love me, love me better better, baby <br>Than all the others do they do, they do, they do, oh, oh, oh <br>To always forgive me always forgive me <br>Ride or die with me ride or die with me <br>That's just what gangsters do do, oh]]></content><category term="Kehlani" label="Kehlani"/><category term="Gangsta (From Suicide Squad The Album)" label="Gangsta (From Suicide Squad The Album)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/I_Wanna_Be/</id><title>Kehlani - I Wanna Be - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:05:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:05:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/I_Wanna_Be/" title="Kehlani - I Wanna Be - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tell me what I gotta do to make you fall in love <br>Tell me what I gotta do to make you want this love <br>Tell me what I gotta do to keep you coming my way <br>Tell me what I gotta do, I'll come and pick you up <br><br>Oh I would like <br>Oh I would like <br>To get to know <br>To get to know <br>If this could be <br>If this could be <br>Be what we want <br>Be what we want <br>Oh I would like <br>Oh I would like <br>To get to know <br>To get to know <br>If I could have <br>If I could have <br>You for my own now <br><br>I wanna be I wanna be the only girl that you ever need <br>I wanna be I wanna be the only place that you wanna be <br>I wanna be I want this to be for forever <br>I know that you're with it but you can do better <br>I want a lifetime love, I want a guarantee baby <br><br>Tell me what I gotta do to keep laying down my lane <br>Tell me how you like it, I'm a put them hoes to shame <br>I'll do what I gotta do to keep you coming my way <br>I know what I gotta do to make you call my name <br><br>Oh I would like <br>Oh I would like <br>To get to know <br>To get to know <br>If this could be <br>If this could be <br>Be what we want <br>Be what we want <br>Oh I would like <br>Oh I would like <br>To get to know <br>To get to know <br>If I could have <br>If I could have <br>You for my own now <br><br>I wanna be I wanna be yeah, I wanna be the only girl that you ever need <br>I wanna be I wanna be the only place that you wanna be <br>I wanna be I want this to be for forever <br>I know that you're with it but you can do better <br>I want a lifetime love, I want a guarantee baby <br><br>I wanna be, I wanna be, I wanna be <br>Who you pull up and slide in for, yeah <br>I wanna be, I wanna be, I wanna be <br>Be the one that you riding for <br>Needing love, I'll be the one who you providing for <br>Know I'm the one, what they trying for Yeah <br>What you want, what you hiding for <br>Pull up, let me get you in the zone <br>And I wanna be <br><br>I wanna be the only girl that you ever need <br>I wanna be the only girl that you ever need <br>I wanna be I wanna be the only place that you wanna be <br>I wanna be the only place that you wanna be <br>I wanna be I want this to be for forever <br>I know that you're with it but you can do better <br>I want a lifetime love, I want a guarantee baby <br><br>Oh, oh <br>Yeah, yeah <br>Uh, huh]]></content><category term="Kehlani" label="Kehlani"/><category term="I Wanna Be" label="I Wanna Be"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Thank_You/</id><title>Kehlani - Thank You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:05:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:05:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Thank_You/" title="Kehlani - Thank You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I never said that I had it all figured it out <br>I never said, I never said that I live my days without doubt <br>I swear all I've ever done is be honest and stay modest <br><br>So this is a, sincere, unscripted <br>Unwritten for all that you've given <br>Forgiving, I'm driven <br>I wanna be better than I was better than I am <br>So I say <br><br>All I'm trying to say is I thank you <br>I thank you <br>All I'm trying to say is I thank you <br>I thank you <br>All I'm trying to say is I thank you <br><br>I never said that I was done with my growth <br>I never said, I never said that I was done doing the most <br>And I swear all I've ever done was stay honest and keep my promise <br><br>So here goes my real life, unscripted <br>Unwritten for all that you've given <br>Forgiving, I'm driven <br>I wanna be better than I was, greater than I am <br>So I say <br><br>All I gotta say is I thank you <br>Thank you <br>All I gotta say is I thank you <br>Thank you <br><br>Hey Thank you for watching me walk across the stage <br>For walking me through my heartbreaks <br>Thanks for the love every step of the way <br>With no support this wouldn't be as great <br>Thank you for making me stronger than most <br>For taking it beyond my coast <br>Thank you for raising a glass when I toast <br><br>All I gotta say is I thank you <br>Thank you <br>All I gotta say is I thank you <br>Thank you <br>All I gotta say is I thank you <br>All I gotta say <br>All I gotta say <br>Thank you <br>All I gotta say is I thank you]]></content><category term="Kehlani" label="Kehlani"/><category term="Thank You" label="Thank You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Hold_Me_By_The_Heart/</id><title>Kehlani - Hold Me By The Heart - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:05:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:05:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Hold_Me_By_The_Heart/" title="Kehlani - Hold Me By The Heart - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wasn't sure I'd be alright <br>Wasn't sure I'd be okay again <br>Didn't know how to take flight <br>Wings broken couldn't seem to bend <br><br>Somehow you came and like the wind, you picked me up for good <br>And now I know what I have missed, I've been thinking that you should <br><br>Pick up the pieces <br>Help me learn to stand <br>Lift me from the ground and use your hands <br>To hold me by the heart <br>Tell me I'll be whole again <br>Hold me by the heart <br>Tell me it will never end <br>'Cause I've begun to think that <br>I was nothing short of broken <br>So baby, hold me by the heart hold me by the heart <br>Help me fly again <br><br>Always read all the fairytales <br>Always knew that it would come <br>Through the pain I convinced myself <br>It's only magical for some <br><br>Somehow you came and like a prince and picked me up for good <br>And now I know what I have missed, I'm thinking that you should <br><br>Just pick up the pieces <br>Help me learn to stand <br>Lift me from the ground and use your hands <br>To hold me by the heart <br>Tell me I'll be whole again <br>And hold me by the heart <br>Tell me it will never end <br>'Cause I've begun to think that <br>I was nothing short of broken <br>So baby, hold me by the heart hold me by the heart <br>Help me fly again <br><br>Pick up the pieces <br>Help me learn to stand Help me learn to stand <br>Lift me from the ground and <br>Use your hands Use your hands <br>Pick up the pieces Hey <br>Help me learn to stand Help me learn to stand <br>Lift me from the ground and <br>Use your hands Use your hands <br>Use your hands <br>Hold me by the heart <br>Hold me by the heart Hold me by the heart <br>Tell me it would never end <br>'Cause I've begun to think that <br>I was nothing short of broken <br>So hold me by the heart <br>Help me fly again]]></content><category term="Kehlani" label="Kehlani"/><category term="Hold Me By The Heart" label="Hold Me By The Heart"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/In_My_Feelings/</id><title>Kehlani - In My Feelings - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:05:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:05:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/In_My_Feelings/" title="Kehlani - In My Feelings - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Are you putting her on your thing <br>Oh my God, I'm gonna, it's gonna be like TMZ Kehlani TMZ laughs <br>And then he's gonna be suing me for slander laughs <br><br>If this isn't love <br>Why do I feel this way <br><br>Why you got me so obsessed with you <br>Why you got me wasting time laying next to you <br>Why do you tell me, come over, to watch you just stare at your phone Don't know why I expected you <br>To give me attention, affection and love <br>You're like a drug, never enough <br>Can't take you high, need a new plug <br>You got me been, got me way too messed up <br><br>And I don't know why I'm even still here <br>Can't shake it off, I've been here for years on top of years <br>And I, I'm ready to, I'm ready to, be off of you <br>'Cause I admit, that baby I, I just may be stuck on you <br><br>If this isn't love <br>Why do I pick up my phone every time that you call <br>Why do I feel this way <br>Why do I I feel this feel this way <br>I'm in my feelings If this isn't love <br>Why do I let you give me half then give you my all <br>Why do I feel this way <br>Why do I do this feel this way <br>I'm in my feelings <br><br>No Uh uh whoa Uh uh yeah Uh uh whoa <br>In my feelings <br>No Uh uh whoa Uh uh yeah Uh uh whoa <br>In my feelings <br><br>Why you be doing me scandalous <br>You just assume that I'm strong and can handle it <br>Why do you make me feel like I'm less than my worth <br>And it won't be for long, I ain't having it <br>You don't do the shit that you said would be done <br>You find it fun, to feel shit and run <br>Love like a gun, it leaves me stunned <br>Out on the floor and I just can't get up <br><br>And I don't know why I'm even still here <br>Can't shake it off, I've been here for years on top of years <br>And I, I'm ready to, I'm ready to, be off of you <br>'Cause I admit, that baby I, I just may be stuck on you <br><br>If this isn't love <br>Why do I pick up my phone every time that you call <br>Why do I feel this way <br>Why do I I feel this feel this way <br>I'm in my feelings If this isn't love <br>Why do I let you give me half then give you my all <br>Why do I feel this way <br>Why do I do this feel this way <br>I'm in my feelings <br><br>No Uh uh whoa Uh uh yeah Uh uh whoa <br>In my feelings <br>No Uh uh whoa Uh uh yeah Uh uh whoa <br>In my feelings <br><br>Oh, why, why do I, why do I feel this way <br>Why am I still this way <br>Why after all these times, you still play all these games <br>Why after all these nights, I still give you all my days <br><br>And I don't know why I'm even still here <br>Can't shake it off, I've been here for years on top of years <br>And I, I'm ready to, I'm ready to, be off of you <br>'Cause I admit, that baby I, I just may be stuck on you <br>I just may be stuck on you <br><br>If this isn't love <br>Why do I pick up my phone every time that you call <br>Every time that you call, whoa <br>Why do I I feel this feel this <br>I'm in my feelings feel this <br>Why do I let you give me half then give you my all <br>Give you my all, oh oh <br>Why do I do this feel this way <br>I'm in my feelings <br><br>No Uh uh whoa Uh uh yeah Uh uh whoa <br>In my feelings <br>No Uh uh whoa Uh uh yeah Uh uh whoa <br>In my feelings]]></content><category term="Kehlani" label="Kehlani"/><category term="In My Feelings" label="In My Feelings"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Get_Like/</id><title>Kehlani - Get Like - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:05:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:05:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Get_Like/" title="Kehlani - Get Like - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The only person in the whole world <br>Ever <br>Ever <br><br>I don't like when I catch them out the corner of their, of their eyes <br>Look all hypnotized <br>I don't mind when I catch you stare me all the way down in my thighs <br>Makes me realize <br><br>That I'm shy and just a little awkward <br>But you bring it out of me, out of me <br>'Cause <br><br>You're the only one that I get like <br>You're the only one that I get like <br>Get like this for <br>You're the only one that I get like <br>You're the only one that I get like <br>Get like this for <br>Ain't nobody else make me feel like <br>You're the only one that I feel like <br>Feel like this for <br>You're the only one that I get like <br>You're the only one that I get like <br>Get like this for <br><br>I confess, after we get down we always leave a mess <br>Don't wanna get dressed <br>We get loud, don't think anyone can make me make a sound <br>Know that make you proud <br><br>'Cause I'm shy and just a little awkward <br>But you bring it out of me, out of me <br>'Cause <br><br>You're the only one that I get like <br>You're the only one that I get like <br>Get like this for <br>You're the only one that I get like <br>You're the only one that I get like <br>Get like this for <br>Ain't nobody else make me feel like <br>You're the only one that I feel like <br>Feel like this for <br>You're the only one that I get like <br>You're the only one that I get like <br>Get like this for <br><br>All you, all yours, it's yours, it's yours It's yours <br>All you, all yours, I'm sure, it's yours It's yours <br>All you, all yours, it's yours, it's yours It's yours <br>All you, all yours, I'm sure, it's yours It's yours <br><br>You're the only one that I get like <br>You're the only one that I get like <br>Get like this for <br>You're the only one that I get like <br>You're the only one that I get like <br>Get like this for <br>Ain't nobody else make me feel like <br>You're the only one that I feel like <br>Feel like this for <br>You're the only one that I get like <br>You're the only one that I get like <br>Get like this for]]></content><category term="Kehlani" label="Kehlani"/><category term="Get Like" label="Get Like"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Too_Much/</id><title>Kehlani - Too Much - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:05:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:05:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Too_Much/" title="Kehlani - Too Much - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Shoulda told that nigga in the beginning <br>If he thought he was bout to play me, nigga don't play yourself, nigga <br>He fucking with the baddest, the rawest, the realest nigga <br><br>I know I'm not what you need <br>Baby why you trying <br>Come over and come fuck me <br>Ain't no sense in lying <br>Do you deserve it honestly <br>We could just part ways <br>Find out our own destiny <br>Baby, baby, baby <br><br>You know I'm more than just a girl that you can meet walking down the street <br>I think you know that I'm the one that you want in your company <br><br>I'm too much of a woman <br>Too much of a woman <br>Too much of a bad ass bitch <br>Too much of a boss <br>Baby it's your loss <br>Now you gotta live with it <br><br>Too much, three much, four much, five much, too much for you <br>Too much, three much, four much, five much, too much for you <br><br>Too much, too much, too much for you <br>Yeah <br><br>There ain't really nothing left <br>Baby that's a promise <br>You were fucking with the best <br>Something I will say <br>That I might just miss your sex <br>That don't mean I want you <br>You can go and stay my ex <br>Baby, baby, baby <br><br>You know I'm more than just a girl that you can meet walking down the street <br>I think you know that I'm the one that you want in your company <br><br>I'm too much of a woman <br>Too much of a woman <br>Too much of a bad ass bitch <br>Too much of a boss <br>Baby it's your loss <br>Now you gotta live with it <br><br>Too much, three much, four much, five much, too much for you <br>Too much, three much, four much, five much, too much for you <br><br>You told me you love me, I told you I wanna see it <br>You told me it's mine and I could have it when I pleases <br>Every night we sexing, you wearing your Jesus pieces <br>Like Jesus Christ himself gon save a nigga from misleading <br>I want you to know I meant that <br>Gotta know that I sent that <br>Text in the middle of the night to tell your ass how to fuck that flight <br>Cause I can't sit at home, on your couch, listening to word of mouth <br>Bout how you been out and about, fucking hoes <br><br>Cause I'm too much of a woman <br>Too much of a woman too much <br>Too much of a bad ass bitch <br>Too much of a boss <br>Baby it's your loss <br>Now you gotta live with it <br><br>Too much, three much, four much, five much, too much for you <br>Too much, three much, four much, five much, too much for you <br><br>Too much, too much for you, baby, yeah <br>Too much, too much, no <br>Too much, too much for you]]></content><category term="Kehlani" label="Kehlani"/><category term="Too Much" label="Too Much"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Escape/</id><title>Kehlani - Escape - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:05:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:05:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Escape/" title="Kehlani - Escape - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Never did I think I'd want you <br>Always seen you 'round my way <br>Never had the strength to tell you <br>I kinda, sorta think you're great <br>Strange for me to wanna love someone who's better by themselves <br>Hate to know that I made you crazy for myself <br><br>'Cause I don't want you thinking that my love's in vain <br>'Cause baby I've been falling for you but falling back up out your way <br><br>'Cause I can't make you lose yourself <br>L looking for me <br>And I can't let you make me your, your everything <br>I just wanna be an escape <br>I just wanna be an escape <br>Baby can we escape escape, escape <br><br>Admiring you from a distance <br>Scared to go and make a move <br>Didn't wanna be distracting <br>You be all up in your groove <br>It's strange for me to wanna love someone who's raw by themselves <br>I'd hate for you to search for someone else <br><br>'Cause I don't want you thinking that my love's in vain <br>'Cause baby I've been falling for you but falling back up on out your way <br><br>'Cause I can't make you lose yourself looking for me <br>And I can't let you make me your, your everything <br>I just wanna be an escape <br>I just wanna be an escape <br>Baby can we escape escape, escape <br><br>Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, aye, aye <br>'Cause I've been staying low, holding back <br>Fighting the feelings that you've been giving <br>And I've been trying to put it all into words <br>But I can't so I'm singing <br><br>'Cause I don't want you thinking that my love's in vain <br>'Cause baby I've been falling for you but falling back up on out your way <br><br>'Cause I can't make you lose yourself looking for me <br>And I can't let you make me your, your everything <br>I just wanna be an escape <br>I just wanna be an escape <br>Baby can we escape escape, escape]]></content><category term="Kehlani" label="Kehlani"/><category term="Escape" label="Escape"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Everything_Is_Yours/</id><title>Kehlani - Everything Is Yours - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:05:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:05:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Everything_Is_Yours/" title="Kehlani - Everything Is Yours - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Probably because there are so many things that he didn't, I tried to forget, you know I try to forgive, I forgive her, but you, you know when, you go back and you think about the things he did, nobody, I don't know nobody like him <br><br>Up at a time when I shouldn't be <br>Thinking 'bout things that I shouldn't be <br>Sad about shit I'm sad about for the past year <br>I've been low, I've been down and out it <br>And it cost a few with love and the <br>I've been here and you know the times that I'm talking bout <br><br>Oh, oh <br>I would give it all to make it all work <br>Oh, oh <br>I wish I could say that you knew my worth <br>Oh, oh <br>End of the day, you was my first <br>At the end of the day, you'll know you're worse <br><br>I love you shawty, shawty <br>You know you my shawty, shawty <br>I need you to make me happy <br>There will never be nobody <br><br>My ring is yours save it, for me <br>Everything is yours save it all for me <br>My ring is yours save it, for me <br>Everything is yours <br><br>Thinkin' bout your bed when I shouldn't be <br>Missing all that when I shouldn't be <br>You was on the road, I was on the road <br>We'd be back to back, back and forth <br>They know how it goes, know you got your pride <br>Just admit you hate being alone <br>Know you allowed to know <br>I'm sitting right beside your throne <br><br>Oh, oh <br>I ignored my friends, they ain't gon' make it all work <br>Oh, oh <br>But I just can't say that you know my worth <br>Oh, oh <br>End of the day, you're still my first <br>At the end of the day, I know you're worse <br><br>I love you shawty, shawty you know it <br>You know you my shawty, shawty <br>You know you my shawty <br>I need you to make me happy <br>There will never be nobody <br><br>My ring is yours save it, for me <br>Everything is yours save it all for me <br>My ring is yours save it, for me <br>Everything is yours yours <br>My ring is yours save it, for me <br>Everything is yours save it all for me <br>My ring is yours save it, for me <br>Everything is yours]]></content><category term="Kehlani" label="Kehlani"/><category term="Everything Is Yours" label="Everything Is Yours"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Not_Used_To_It/</id><title>Kehlani - Not Used To It - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:06:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:06:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Not_Used_To_It/" title="Kehlani - Not Used To It - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Typical story of an Oakland girl <br>Typical story heard around the world <br>Mama on her way, daddy up above <br>Out of 14, I guess it made me tough <br>Used to roll up on a block on the east side <br>I crack enough 40's by the sea side <br>Lose a nigga every week to a drive by <br>Whole bookshelf of stories behind these eyes I <br><br>I don't mean, I don't mean for it to sound so damn common <br>I don't mean, I don't mean for it to sound like I'm jawsin' <br>But when I say it's hard to open up to you <br>It's hard to get close to you <br>I want it with everything in me to one day just say I'm in love with you <br><br>But I'm not used to it, I'm not use to it, I am not <br>I'm not used to it, I'm not used to it, hey <br>I'm not used to it, I'm not used to it, I am not <br>I'm not used to it, I'm not used to it <br>I'm not used to it <br><br>One day, one day, one day <br>One day, one day, one day <br><br>All single mothers in my family <br>Don't know if you're really understanding me <br>Never seen a nigga be a real man <br>I never seen a nigga with a real plan <br>And I still never been to a wedding <br>And I just see my family stressing <br>Over son's who grew up with no daddies and every generation <br>Was all just raised by my granny <br>But nah <br><br>I don't mean, I don't mean for it to sound so damn common <br>I don't mean, I don't mean for it to sound like I'm jawsin' <br>But when I say it's hard to just side with you <br>It's hard to confide in you <br>I want it with everything in me to one day just say that I ride with you <br><br>But I'm not used to it, I'm not use to it, I am not <br>I'm not used to it, I'm not used to it, hey <br>I'm not used to it, I'm not used to it, I am not <br>I'm not used to it, I'm not used to it <br>I'm not used to it <br><br>One day, one day, one day <br>One day, one day, one day <br><br>Sometimes I pop off cause it's all that I'm used to <br>Sometimes I pop one cause I have to <br>Sometimes I run from all my problems <br>Sometimes I make sure that I solve em <br>I don't mean, I don't mean for it to sound so damn common <br>I don't mean, I don't mean for it to sound so damn common, but I'm not used to it <br><br>But I'm not used to it, I'm not use to it, I am not baby, yeah <br>I'm not used to it, I'm not used to it, hey I'm not used to it <br>I'm not used to it, I'm not used to it, I am not baby I'm sorry <br>I'm not used to it, I'm not used to it I'm not, I'm not <br><br>Yeah, yeah <br>One day, one day, one day, one day <br>Yeah, yeah, hey yeah <br>Cause I'm not used to it]]></content><category term="Kehlani" label="Kehlani"/><category term="Not Used To It" label="Not Used To It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Personal/</id><title>Kehlani - Personal - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:06:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:06:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Personal/" title="Kehlani - Personal - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They sleeping, they sleeping, they sleeping, they sleeping on me <br>But I don't waste my time tryna prove that I'm something to see, oh I <br>The real ones they know and the ones that do not I don't need <br>'Cause mostly the vision and I give reasons to believe <br><br>That I'm honest, I'm honest, I'm telling no lies <br>When I say I'm up next I'm not just for the ride <br>Never a point when I questioned my mind <br>Know what I'm doing, I pay for this time <br>Come up regardless, I'm comin regardless <br>I'm hungry, I'm starving, remaining a topic <br>Never an option, got your undivided whenever I'm plotting <br><br>Don't take it personal, personal, personal <br>Don't take it personal, personal, personal <br>I know it hurts to know, hurts to know, hurts to know <br>I don't want it na, na, na, don't need it yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Don't take it personal, personal, personal <br>Don't take it personal, personal, personal <br>I know it hurts to know, hurts to know, hurts to know <br>I don't want it na, na, na, don't need it yeah, yeah, yeah <br><br>I know that you hear this and you gon' just know that I'm speaking to you <br>Shouldn't have got so ahead of yourself now you're losing your cool <br>I know that you know that I'm right, you admit it that I am the truth <br>But look you at you now, look at your face, looking sad in the booth <br><br>Signed off a tape, chewed off a tape, did it alone, and I ain't touched a plate <br>You was my nigga, we could have been great <br>You so far gone, got you thinking you're safe <br>All said and done you lost my respect <br>All said and done you're the one I regret <br>Now you gon' watch from the crowd <br>Lookin' up like the rest <br><br>Don't take it personal, personal, personal Look <br>Don't take it personal, personal, personal I need you to promise me one thing <br>I know it hurts to know, hurts to know, hurts to know That you not gon' take it like that <br>I don't want it, don't need it <br>Don't take it personal, personal, personal Promise me that you won't take it <br>Don't take it personal, personal, personal Swear to me that you won't take it <br>I know it hurts to know, hurts to know, hurts to know <br>I don't want it, don't need it <br><br>No I could never judge anyone I loved <br>Even if you lose sight of all the things I've done <br>I'm not who I once was <br>These days I'm all grown up <br>I fuck with me heavy <br>I'm all chose up <br><br>And I only did right by you <br>When you fucked her I survived by you <br>Prayin for the girls that believe your news <br>Prayin for myself cause I be all truth <br>I got good heart, good soul, good sex, no stress <br>Next for me is best <br>Don't you run your mouth <br>Cause in this song I say it best <br><br>Don't take it personal, personal, personal <br>Don't take it personal, personal, personal <br>I know it hurts to know, hurts to know, hurts to know <br>I don't want it, don't need it <br>Don't take it personal, personal, personal <br>Don't take it personal, personal, personal <br>I know it hurts to know, hurts to know, hurts to know <br>I don't want it, don't need it]]></content><category term="Kehlani" label="Kehlani"/><category term="Personal" label="Personal"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/CRZY/</id><title>Kehlani - CRZY - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T18:06:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T18:06:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/CRZY/" title="Kehlani - CRZY - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Crazy I go I go I go I go <br>Everything I do <br>I do it with a passion <br>If I gotta be a bitch <br>I'ma be a bad one <br>I'm A.I. with the designs <br>du-ragging <br>Bounce back game good <br>why we talkin' practice <br>Yeah yeah yeah <br>pull up score when I want to <br>Best thing next to Heaven <br>They be tryna count me <br>out though <br>I'm just countin' <br>countin' blessins <br>A real woman 'bout her paper <br>Niggas don't know <br>where I came from <br>Why I really really came up <br>You never could say <br>I'm backing <br>All this shit I've been through <br>And it made me <br>more of an assassin <br>I kill 'em I kill 'em <br>I kill 'em with compassion <br>And baby if they askin' <br>Tell 'em tell 'em <br>tell 'em tell 'em <br>I go I go I go I go <br>crazy crazy <br>I go I go I go I go <br>crazy crazy <br>Live for the challenge <br>only make me stronger <br>One more reason <br>to turn up on 'em <br>I go I go I go I go <br>crazy crazy <br>Lit lit lit lit <br>only L I take is to the face <br>You showed up to see me <br>lose but I overcome <br>so you overcame <br>Basic basic <br>ain't nothin' bout me basic <br>I'm crazy I'm crazy <br>better watch <br>what you say to me <br>'Cause Young Sway <br>got the answers <br>Give 'em hell <br>give 'em pressure <br>VIP couch no manners <br>dirty-dirty-dirty dancin' <br>Take a look at what I did <br>go for circle with the wrist <br>Whippin'-whippin' up the grits <br>get a handful of this nicely <br>I got it I got it <br>I got it and you gon' respect it <br>Ain't nothin' <br>ain't nothin' <br>Gon' stop me from <br>makin' it happen <br>So baby if they askin' <br>Tell 'em tell 'em <br>tell 'em tell 'em <br>I go I go I go I go <br>crazy crazy <br>I go I go I go I go <br>crazy crazy <br>Live for the challenge <br>only make me stronger <br>One more reason <br>to turn up on 'em <br>I go I go I go I go <br>crazy crazy <br>I go I go I go I go <br>crazy <br>I go I go I go I go <br>crazy crazy <br>]]></content><category term="Kehlani" label="Kehlani"/><category term="CRZY" label="CRZY"/></entry></feed>