<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:35:21+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_뉴_크리에이션_워십/Arise_Studio_Ver/</id><title>New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - Arise (Studio Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:35:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:35:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_%EB%89%B4_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%85%98_%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD/Arise_Studio_Ver/" title="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - Arise (Studio Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Arise <br>영광의 빛으로 <br>Arise <br>세상에 그 빛 비추어라 <br>열방은 네게로 <br>그 영광의 빛으로 <br>눈을 들어보라 <br>모두 나아오네 <br>Arise <br>영광의 빛으로 <br>Arise <br>세상에 그 빛 비추어라 <br>열방은 네게로 <br>그 영광의 빛으로 <br>눈을 들어보라 <br>모두 나아오네 <br>Light up your world <br>너의 빛으로 <br>Light up your world <br>주의 영으로 <br>열방은 네게로 <br>그 영광의 빛으로 <br>눈을 들어보라 <br>모두 나아오네 <br>Light up your world <br>너의 빛으로 <br>Light up your world <br>주의 영으로 <br>Light up your world <br>너의 빛으로 <br>Light up your world <br>주의 영으로 <br>너는 주 안에서 빛 <br>너는 온 세상의 빛 <br>우린 주 안에서 빛 <br>우린 온 세상의 빛 <br>We are light in the Lord <br>We are light of the world <br>We are light in the Lord <br>We are light of the world <br>Light up your world <br>너의 빛으로 <br>Light up your world <br>주의 영으로 <br>Light up your world <br>너의 빛으로 <br>Light up your world <br>주의 영으로 <br>]]></content><category term="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)" label="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)"/><category term="Arise (Studio Ver.)" label="Arise (Studio Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_뉴_크리에이션_워십/주_예수_이름_높이어_Studio_Ver/</id><title>New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 주 예수 이름 높이어 (Studio Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:35:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:35:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_%EB%89%B4_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%85%98_%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD/%EC%A3%BC_%EC%98%88%EC%88%98_%EC%9D%B4%EB%A6%84_%EB%86%92%EC%9D%B4%EC%96%B4_Studio_Ver/" title="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 주 예수 이름 높이어 (Studio Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주 예수 이름 높이어 <br>다 찬양하여라 <br>금 면류관을 드려서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>금 면류관을 드려서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>주 믿는 성도 다함께 <br>주 앞에 엎드려 <br>무궁한 노래 불러서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>무궁한 노래 불러서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>이 지구 위에 거하는 <br>온 지파 족속들 <br>그 크신 위엄 높여서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>그 크신 위엄 높여서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>모든 왕의 왕 또 주의 주 <br>온 땅과 만물을 주관하시네 <br>처음과 나중되신 우리 왕 <br>영원히 다스리네 <br>모든 왕의 왕 또 주의 주 <br>온 땅과 만물을 주관하시네 <br>처음과 나중되신 우리 왕 <br>영원히 다스리네 <br>모든 왕의 왕 또 주의 주 <br>온 땅과 만물을 주관하시네 <br>처음과 나중되신 우리 왕 <br>영원히 다스리네 <br>모든 왕의 왕 또 주의 주 <br>온 땅과 만물을 주관하시네 <br>처음과 나중되신 우리 왕 <br>영원히 다스리네 <br>주 믿는 성도 다함께 <br>주 앞에 엎드려 <br>무궁한 노래 불러서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>무궁한 노래 불러서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>]]></content><category term="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)" label="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)"/><category term="주 예수 이름 높이어 (Studio Ver.)" label="주 예수 이름 높이어 (Studio Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_뉴_크리에이션_워십/내_구주_예수님/</id><title>New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 내 구주 예수님 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:35:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:35:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_%EB%89%B4_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%85%98_%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD/%EB%82%B4_%EA%B5%AC%EC%A3%BC_%EC%98%88%EC%88%98%EB%8B%98/" title="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 내 구주 예수님 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 구주 예수님 주 같은 분 없네 <br>내 평생에 찬양하리 <br>놀라운 주의 사랑을 <br>위로자 되시며 피난처 되신 주님 <br>나의 영혼 온 맘 다해 <br>주를 경배합니다 <br>온 땅이여 주님께 외쳐라 <br>능력과 위엄의 왕 되신 주 <br>산과 바다 소리쳐 <br>주의 이름을 높이리 <br>주 행한 일 기뻐 노래하며 <br>영원히 주님을 사랑하리라 <br>신실하신 주의 약속 나 받았네 <br>내 구주 예수님 주 같은 분 없네 <br>내 평생에 찬양하리 <br>놀라운 주의 사랑을 <br>위로자 되시며 피난처 되신 주님 <br>나의 영혼 온 맘 다해 <br>주를 경배합니다 <br>온 땅이여 주님께 외쳐라 <br>능력과 위엄의 왕 되신 주 <br>산과 바다 소리쳐 <br>주의 이름을 높이리 <br>주 행한 일 기뻐 노래하며 <br>영원히 주님을 사랑하리라 <br>신실하신 주의 약속 <br>온 땅이여 주님께 외쳐라 <br>능력과 위엄의 왕 되신 주 <br>산과 바다 소리쳐 <br>주의 이름을 높이리 <br>주 행한 일 기뻐 노래하며 <br>영원히 주님을 사랑하리라 <br>신실하신 주의 약속 <br>온 땅이여 주님께 외쳐라 <br>능력과 위엄의 왕 되신 주 <br>산과 바다 소리쳐 <br>주의 이름을 높이리 <br>주 행한 일 기뻐 노래하며 <br>영원히 주님을 사랑하리라 <br>신실하신 주의 약속 <br>온 땅이여 주님께 외쳐라 <br>능력과 위엄의 왕 되신 주 <br>산과 바다 소리쳐 <br>주의 이름을 높이리 <br>주 행한 일 기뻐 노래하며 <br>영원히 주님을 사랑하리라 <br>신실하신 주의 약속 나 받았네 <br>]]></content><category term="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)" label="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)"/><category term="내 구주 예수님" label="내 구주 예수님"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_뉴_크리에이션_워십/평강의_왕/</id><title>New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 평강의 왕 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:35:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:35:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_%EB%89%B4_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%85%98_%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD/%ED%8F%89%EA%B0%95%EC%9D%98_%EC%99%95/" title="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 평강의 왕 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[평강의 왕 우리 주님 <br>이 땅에 곧 오시리 <br>모든 나라 모든 민족 <br>주 오실 길 예비하네 <br>다시 오실 우리 주님을 <br>땅 끝에서 뵈오리 <br>하늘 향해 깃발을 들고 <br>모든 민족 외치네 <br>호산나 호산나 왕이 오시네 <br>호산나 호산나 어린 양 예수 <br>평강의 왕 우리 주님 <br>이 땅에 곧 오시리 <br>모든 나라 모든 민족 <br>주 오실 길 예비하네 <br>다시 오실 우리 주님을 <br>땅 끝에서 뵈오리 <br>하늘 향해 깃발을 들고 <br>모든 민족 외치네 <br>호산나 호산나 왕이 오시네 <br>호산나 호산나 어린 양 예수 <br>영광의 왕 우리 주님을 <br>모든 민족 경배해 <br>만왕의 왕 우리 주님께 <br>모든 열방 찬양해 <br>영광의 왕 우리 주님을 <br>모든 민족 경배해 <br>만왕의 왕 우리 주님께 <br>모든 열방 찬양해 <br>호산나 호산나 왕이 오시네 <br>호산나 호산나 어린 양 예수 <br>호산나 호산나 왕이 오시네 <br>호산나 호산나 어린 양 예수 <br>어린 양 예수 왕이 오시네 <br>호산나 호산나 왕이 오시네 <br>호산나 호산나 어린 양 예수 <br>호산나 호산나 왕이 오시네 <br>호산나 호산나 어린 양 예수 <br>호산나 호산나 왕이 오시네 <br>호산나 호산나 어린 양 예수 <br>호산나 호산나 왕이 오시네 <br>호산나 호산나 어린 양 예수 <br>호산나 호산나 왕이 오시네 <br>호산나 호산나 어린 양 예수 <br>호산나 호산나 왕이 오시네 <br>호산나 호산나 어린 양 예수 <br>]]></content><category term="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)" label="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)"/><category term="평강의 왕" label="평강의 왕"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_뉴_크리에이션_워십/Arise/</id><title>New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - Arise - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:35:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:35:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_%EB%89%B4_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%85%98_%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD/Arise/" title="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - Arise - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Arise 영광의 빛으로 <br>Arise 세상에 그 빛 비추어라 <br>열방은 네게로 그 영광의 빛으로 <br>눈을 들어보라 모두 나아오네 <br>Arise 영광의 빛으로 <br>Arise 세상에 그 빛 비추어라 <br>열방은 네게로 그 영광의 빛으로 <br>눈을 들어보라 모두 나아오네 <br>Light up your world 너의 빛으로 <br>Light up your world 주의 영으로 <br>Light up your world 너의 빛으로 <br>Light up your world 주의 영으로 <br>열방은 네게로 그 영광의 빛으로 <br>눈을 들어보라 모두 나아오네 <br>Light up your world 너의 빛으로 <br>Light up your world 주의 영으로 <br>Light up your world 너의 빛으로 <br>Light up your world 주의 영으로 <br>너는 주 안에서 빛 <br>너는 온 세상의 빛 <br>너는 주 안에서 빛 <br>너는 온 세상의 빛 <br>We are light in the Lord <br>We are light of the world <br>We are light in the Lord <br>We are light of the world <br>Light up your world 너의 빛으로 <br>Light up your world 주의 영으로 <br>Light up your world 너의 빛으로 <br>Light up your world 주의 영으로 <br>You are light in the Lord <br>You are light of the world <br>You are light in the Lord <br>You are light of the world <br>We are light in the Lord <br>We are light of the world <br>We are light in the Lord <br>We are light of the world <br>We are light in the Lord <br>We are light of the world <br>We are light in the Lord <br>We are light of the world <br>Light up your world 너의 빛으로 <br>Light up your world 주의 영으로 <br>Light up your world 너의 빛으로 <br>Light up your world 주의 영으로 <br>]]></content><category term="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)" label="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)"/><category term="Arise" label="Arise"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_뉴_크리에이션_워십/온_세상_창조주/</id><title>New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 온 세상 창조주 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:35:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:35:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_%EB%89%B4_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%85%98_%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD/%EC%98%A8_%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81_%EC%B0%BD%EC%A1%B0%EC%A3%BC/" title="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 온 세상 창조주 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[온 세상 창조주 온 세상 구원자 <br>모든 것 이기신 능력의 하나님 <br>하나님 열방을 우리게 주셨네 <br>그 명령 따라서 열방을 취하리 <br>모든 만물 주를 찬양해 <br>모든 민족 주께 경배해 <br>온 세상 창조주 온 세상 구원자 <br>모든 것 이기신 능력의 하나님 <br>하나님 열방을 우리게 주셨네 <br>그 명령 따라서 열방을 취하리 <br>모든 만물 주를 찬양해 <br>모든 민족 주께 경배해 <br>모든 만물 주를 찬양해 <br>모든 민족 주께 경배해 <br>모두 승리하리 열방 얻게 되리 <br>하나님께서 통치하시네 <br>모두 승리하리 열방 얻게 되리 <br>위대하신 왕 여호와 <br>찬양 할렐루야 찬양 할렐루야 <br>하나님께서 통치하시네 <br>찬양 할렐루야 찬양 할렐루야 <br>위대하신 왕 여호와 <br>모두 승리하리 열방 얻게 되리 <br>하나님께서 통치하시네 <br>모두 승리하리 열방 얻게 되리 <br>위대하신 왕 여호와 <br>]]></content><category term="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)" label="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)"/><category term="온 세상 창조주" label="온 세상 창조주"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_뉴_크리에이션_워십/경배하리_내_온_맘_다해/</id><title>New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 경배하리 내 온 맘 다해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:35:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:35:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_%EB%89%B4_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%85%98_%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD/%EA%B2%BD%EB%B0%B0%ED%95%98%EB%A6%AC_%EB%82%B4_%EC%98%A8_%EB%A7%98_%EB%8B%A4%ED%95%B4/" title="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 경배하리 내 온 맘 다해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[경배하리 내 온 맘 다해 <br>찬양하리 내 온 힘 다해 <br>주 찾으리 나 사는 동안 <br>주님의 길을 나 따라가리 <br>I will give You all my worship <br>I will give You all my praise <br>You alone I long to worship <br>You alone are worthy of my <br>주님만을 경배하리 <br>주님만을 찬양하리 <br>찬양 받기 합당하신 <br>존귀하신 주만 높이리 <br>무릎 꿇고 주 맞이하리 <br>내 모든 것 다 드리리 <br>주를 향해 내 눈을 들고 <br>주 의지하리 주만 의지하리 <br>주님만을 경배하리 <br>주님만을 찬양하리 <br>찬양 받기 합당하신 <br>존귀하신 주만 높이리 <br>주님만을 경배하리 <br>주님만을 찬양하리 <br>찬양 받기 합당하신 <br>존귀하신 주만 높이리 <br>I will give You all my worship <br>I will give You all my praise <br>You alone I long to worship <br>You alone are worthy of my praise <br>I will give You all my worship <br>I will give You all my praise <br>You alone I long to worship <br>You alone are worthy of my praise <br>주님만을 경배하리 <br>주님만을 찬양하리 <br>찬양 받기 합당하신 <br>존귀하신 주만 높이리 <br>]]></content><category term="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)" label="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)"/><category term="경배하리 내 온 맘 다해" label="경배하리 내 온 맘 다해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_뉴_크리에이션_워십/예수_하나님의_공의/</id><title>New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 예수 하나님의 공의 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:35:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:35:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_%EB%89%B4_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%85%98_%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD/%EC%98%88%EC%88%98_%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%98_%EA%B3%B5%EC%9D%98/" title="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 예수 하나님의 공의 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[예수 하나님의 사랑 <br>주 은혜와 <br>말씀으로 나타났네 <br>예수 거룩한 하나님 <br>영광 중에 <br>영광 중에 <br>그의 나라 임하시네 <br>주의 나라 영원하며 <br>그의 영광 무궁하리 <br>왕의 위엄과 능력이 <br>이제 임하였으니 <br>주의 주권과 주의 통치와 <br>주의 나라 힘과 권세 임하네 <br>예수 하나님의 공의 <br>예수 하나님의 공의 <br>주 독생자 <br>그의 나라 임하시네 <br>예수 제물이 되신 주 <br>영광 중에 <br>그의 나라 임하시네 <br>주의 나라 영원하며 <br>그의 영광 무궁하리 <br>왕의 위엄과 능력이 <br>이제 임하였으니 <br>주의 주권과 주의 통치와 <br>주의 나라 힘과 권세 임하네 <br>예수 하나님의 공의 <br>주의 나라 영원하며 <br>그의 영광 무궁하리 <br>왕의 위엄과 능력이 <br>이제 임하였으니 <br>주의 주권과 주의 통치와 <br>주의 나라 힘과 권세 임하네 <br>예수 하나님의 공의 <br>주의 나라 영원하며 <br>그의 영광 무궁하리 <br>왕의 위엄과 능력이 <br>이제 임하였으니 <br>주의 주권과 주의 통치와 <br>주의 나라 힘과 권세 임하네 <br>예수 하나님의 공의 <br>주의 나라 영원하며 <br>그의 영광 무궁하리 <br>왕의 위엄과 능력이 <br>이제 임하였으니 <br>주의 주권과 주의 통치와 <br>주의 나라 힘과 권세 임하네 <br>예수 하나님의 공의 <br>]]></content><category term="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)" label="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)"/><category term="예수 하나님의 공의" label="예수 하나님의 공의"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_뉴_크리에이션_워십/주_예수_이름_높이어/</id><title>New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 주 예수 이름 높이어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:35:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:35:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_%EB%89%B4_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%85%98_%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD/%EC%A3%BC_%EC%98%88%EC%88%98_%EC%9D%B4%EB%A6%84_%EB%86%92%EC%9D%B4%EC%96%B4/" title="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 주 예수 이름 높이어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주 예수 이름 높이어 <br>다 찬양하여라 <br>금 면류관을 드려서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>금 면류관을 드려서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>주 믿는 성도 다함께 <br>주 앞에 엎드려 <br>무궁한 노래 불러서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>무궁한 노래 불러서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>이 지구 위에 거하는 <br>온 지파 족속들 <br>그 크신 위엄 높여서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>그 크신 위엄 높여서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>모든 왕의 왕 <br>또 주의 주 <br>온 땅과 만물을 <br>주관하시네 <br>처음과 나중되신 우리 왕 <br>영원히 다스리네 <br>모든 왕의 왕 <br>또 주의 주 <br>온 땅과 만물을 <br>주관하시네 <br>처음과 나중되신 우리 왕 <br>영원히 다스리네 <br>모든 왕의 왕 <br>또 주의 주 <br>온 땅과 만물을 <br>주관하시네 <br>처음과 나중되신 우리 왕 <br>영원히 다스리네 <br>모든 왕의 왕 <br>또 주의 주 <br>온 땅과 만물을 <br>주관하시네 <br>처음과 나중되신 우리 왕 <br>영원히 다스리네 <br>주 믿는 성도 다함께 <br>주 앞에 엎드려 <br>무궁한 노래 불러서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>무궁한 노래 불러서 <br>만유의 주 찬양 <br>모든 왕 <br>또 주의 주 <br>온 땅과 만물 <br>주관하시네 <br>처음과 나 우리 왕 <br>영원히 다스리네 <br>모든 왕의 왕 <br>또 주의 주 <br>온 땅과 만물을 <br>주관하시네 <br>처음과 나중되신 우리 왕 <br>영원히 다스리네 <br>모든 왕의 왕 <br>또 주의 주 <br>온 땅과 만물을 <br>주관하시네 <br>처음과 나 우리 왕 <br>영원히 다스리네 <br>]]></content><category term="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)" label="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)"/><category term="주 예수 이름 높이어" label="주 예수 이름 높이어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_뉴_크리에이션_워십/면류관_가지고/</id><title>New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 면류관 가지고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:35:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:35:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_%EB%89%B4_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%85%98_%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD/%EB%A9%B4%EB%A5%98%EA%B4%80_%EA%B0%80%EC%A7%80%EA%B3%A0/" title="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 면류관 가지고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[면류관 가지고 <br>주 앞에 드리세 <br>저 천사 기쁜 노래가 <br>온 땅에 퍼지네 <br>내 혼아 깨어서 <br>주 찬송하여라 <br>온 백성 죄를 속하신 <br>만왕의 왕일세 <br>면류관 가지고 <br>주 앞에 드리세 <br>그 손과 몸의 상처가 <br>영광 중 빛나네 <br>하늘의 천사도 <br>그 영광 보고서 <br>고난의 신비 알고자 <br>늘 흠모하도다 <br>면류관 가지고 <br>주 앞에 드리세 <br>온 세상 전쟁 그치고 <br>참 평화 오겠네 <br>그 보좌 앞에서 <br>온 백성 엎드려 <br>그 한량없는 영광을 <br>늘 찬송하겠네 <br>내 혼아 깨어서 <br>주 찬송하여라 <br>온 백성 죄를 속하신 <br>만왕의 왕일세 <br>하늘의 천사도 <br>그 영광 보고서 <br>고난의 신비 알고자 <br>늘 흠모하도다 <br>그 보좌 앞에서 <br>온 백성 엎드려 <br>그 한량없는 영광을 <br>늘 찬송하겠네 <br>]]></content><category term="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)" label="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)"/><category term="면류관 가지고" label="면류관 가지고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_뉴_크리에이션_워십/주의_임재_앞에_잠잠해/</id><title>New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 주의 임재 앞에 잠잠해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:35:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:35:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_%EB%89%B4_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%85%98_%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD/%EC%A3%BC%EC%9D%98_%EC%9E%84%EC%9E%AC_%EC%95%9E%EC%97%90_%EC%9E%A0%EC%9E%A0%ED%95%B4/" title="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십) - 주의 임재 앞에 잠잠해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주의 임재 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주 여기 계시네 <br>와서 모두 굽혀 경배해 <br>신령과 진리로 <br>순결하신 주님 <br>거룩한 존전에 <br>주의 임재 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주 여기 계시네 <br>주의 영광 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주의 빛 비치네 <br>거룩한 불 태우시며 <br>영광의 관 쓰네 <br>주 영광 찬란해 <br>빛 되신 우리 왕 <br>주의 영광 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주의 빛 비치네 <br>주 영광 찬란해 <br>빛 되신 우리 왕 <br>주의 영광 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주의 빛 비치네 <br>주 영광 찬란해 <br>빛 되신 우리 왕 <br>주의 영광 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주의 빛 비치네 <br>주의 능력 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주 역사하시네 <br>죄 사하고 치유하시는 <br>놀라운 주 은혜 <br>주 믿는 자에게 <br>능치 못함 없네 <br>주의 능력 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주 역사하시네 <br>주 믿는 자에게 <br>능치 못함 없네 <br>주의 능력 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주 역사하시네 <br>주 믿는 자에게 <br>능치 못함 없네 <br>주의 능력 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주 역사하시네 <br>주 영광 찬란해 <br>빛 되신 우리 왕 <br>주의 영광 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주의 빛 비치네 <br>순결하신 주님 <br>거룩한 존전에 <br>주의 임재 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주 여기 계시네 <br>순결하신 주님 <br>거룩한 존전에 <br>주의 임재 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주 여기 계시네 <br>]]></content><category term="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)" label="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)"/><category term="주의 임재 앞에 잠잠해" label="주의 임재 앞에 잠잠해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이비아/믿어지지_않지만_Feat_윤지수/</id><title>이비아 - 믿어지지 않지만 (Feat. 윤지수) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:35:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:35:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B9%84%EC%95%84/%EB%AF%BF%EC%96%B4%EC%A7%80%EC%A7%80_%EC%95%8A%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%8C_Feat_%EC%9C%A4%EC%A7%80%EC%88%98/" title="이비아 - 믿어지지 않지만 (Feat. 윤지수) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[믿어지지 않지만 <br>받아들일 거야 <br>어느 늦은 오후 <br>환하게 온 세상이 <br>밝아져 보였어 <br>흩어져 간 시간들 <br>틈 속에서 <br>보듬어 주리라고 <br>생각지도 않아 <br>이젠 아냐 <br>소용없단 걸 <br>알잖아 <br>흐트러진 내 모습 <br>소리 내어 웃어도 <br>바스락 부서진 낙엽처럼 <br>믿어지지 않지만 <br>받아들일 거야 <br>내 맘도 모르게 <br>소리 없이 달리던 <br>회전목마처럼 <br>말없는 시계는 <br>멈춰 있네 <br>아무것도 들리지 않아 <br>]]></content><category term="이비아" label="이비아"/><category term="믿어지지 않지만 (Feat. 윤지수)" label="믿어지지 않지만 (Feat. 윤지수)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Cool_Kids/Connect_4/</id><title>The Cool Kids - Connect 4 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:38:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:38:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Cool_Kids/Connect_4/" title="The Cool Kids - Connect 4 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I ain't got no issues with it <br>30 foot yacht with the kitchen in it <br>Ooh, I got a thing for the yachts too <br>You still got the dealer phone number <br>Yea I gotchu <br>Spot you real quick like a weight lift <br>Magician with a nigga, I could shape shift <br>Dog called said he need about 8 minutes <br>Man, that was quick <br>Homie don't waste not a second <br>You disrespect, he gon' get you chased out of Texas <br>So watch your tone and don't ask a lot of questions <br>Or lose this plug like a wifi connection <br>Aye, I'mma cop an acre out in Cancun <br>With big Jeep wagons in the sand dunes <br>Yea, I'mma start my selection <br>If you was smart, you'd guard your connections <br><br>Mmm, connect 4 <br>I'mma line 'em up in a row <br>You need the connect though <br>I'mma get him on the phone <br>Connect 4 <br>Line 'em up in a row <br>You need the connect though <br>I'mma get him on the phone <br>Connect 4, connect 4, connect 4 <br>I'mma get him on the phone <br><br>So how you waiting in line but you connected <br>Aye boy your story just ain't adding up <br>Sure bro, I'll let you have her when I've had enough <br>I found a mouth on this bitch, I can't pass it up <br>If she ain't got no back like a flip flop <br>Sandal chocolate, she can ride with Banco Poppa <br>Aye aye, and if you get a new connect <br>And you don't share it with your dog <br>Then that's really not you partner <br>I'm importing white gold from the jungle <br>This Banco to Captain Crunch dog Colombo <br>First edition Mariani music with the Feragami <br>Same color lobster, bitch hold on lock connect <br><br>Mmm, connect 4 <br>I'mma line 'em up in a row <br>You need the connect though <br>I'mma get him on the phone <br>Connect 4 <br>Line 'em up in a row <br>You need the connect though <br>I'mma get him on the phone <br>Connect 4, connect 4, connect 4 <br>I'mma get him on the phone <br><br>Fresh off the stoop in them New Balance <br>Crazy new colors got a few palettes <br>Sounds like funk records found a new talent <br>We the naughty champ nigga, peep the new Jacky <br>Shoutout to Joe my connect on the low <br>Puttin' two and two together and we have that connect four <br>Me and Mikey alright, we just booked a world tour <br>Doing knowledge, 125 percent, I'm getting more <br>Just like Zeke and Joe D <br>It's the essence and the message with Nas and AZ <br>Aye I said that on a remix with Drake <br>The plug just called, you can scoop it today nigga <br><br>Mmm, connect 4 <br>I'mma line 'em up in a row <br>You need the connect though <br>I'mma get him on the phone <br>Connect 4 <br>Line 'em up in a row <br>You need the connect though <br>I'mma get him on the phone <br>Connect 4, connect 4, connect 4 <br>I'mma get him on the phone]]></content><category term="The Cool Kids" label="The Cool Kids"/><category term="Connect 4" label="Connect 4"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jim_Bergsted/Mental_Lover/</id><title>Jim Bergsted - Mental Lover - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:38:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:38:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jim_Bergsted/Mental_Lover/" title="Jim Bergsted - Mental Lover - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Being hurt isn't all that bad <br>All this pain makes me feel alive <br>I got defeated but I am glad that it ended just like that <br><br>You can cry on my shoulder <br>Will you let me cry on yours <br>I'll be holding your hand tonight <br>despite the trouble it will cause <br><br>I wanna be your <br>I wanna be be <br>I wanna be your <br>I wanna be be <br>I wanna be your <br>I wanna be be <br>I want it want it, want it <br>I wanna be be <br>I <br>I want to be your mental lover <br>And I <br>I don't want this to be over <br><br>I had a dream <br>it felt so real <br>I will keep the memories the memories <br>You can cry on my shoulder <br>Will you let me cry on yours <br>I'll be touching your skin tonight <br>despite the trouble it will cause <br><br>Cause I <br>I want to be your mental lover <br>And I <br>I don't want this to be over <br>I wouldn't change a single thing <br>I would do it all again <br>Cause I <br>I want to be your mental lover <br><br>Don't you leave me now <br>Don't you leave my mind <br>Don't you leave my soul <br><br>Don't you leave me now <br>Don't you leave my mind <br>Don't you dare to go <br><br>Don't you leave me now <br>Don't you leave my mind <br>Don't you leave my soul <br><br>Don't you leave me now <br>Don't you leave my mind <br>Don't you dare to go <br>Don't you dare to go <br><br>No <br>Don't you dare to go <br>Don't you dare to go <br>Don't you dare to go <br><br>I want to be your <br>I <br>I want to be your mental lover <br>And I <br>I don't want this to be over <br>I wouldn't change a single thing <br>I would do it all again <br>Cause I <br>I want to be your mental lover <br>I <br>Mental lover <br>I <br>Mental lover <br>I wanna be your]]></content><category term="Jim Bergsted" label="Jim Bergsted"/><category term="Mental Lover" label="Mental Lover"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jorja_Smith/Imperfect_Circle/</id><title>Jorja Smith - Imperfect Circle - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:39:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:39:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jorja_Smith/Imperfect_Circle/" title="Jorja Smith - Imperfect Circle - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Round and round and round and round <br>And round and round we go <br>Round and round and round and round <br>And round and round we go <br>Round and round and round and round <br>And round and round we go <br>Round and round and round and round <br>And round and round we go <br>Round and round and round and round <br>And round and round we go <br>Round and round in circles <br>Like we got no place to go <br><br>I've seen <br>A couple issues in the news that need discussing <br>But is there any point if they just keep repeating <br>Will this ever end Questioning ourselves again <br>Who say <br>You can't sit here, you can't come here <br>Wait that was back then <br>Eenie meenie minie moe <br>So who is left then <br>Knocking us down one by one <br>Look, this game is not fitting <br>Why is this happening again <br><br>Round and round and round and round <br>And round and round we go <br>Round and round and round and round <br>And round and round we go <br>Round and round and round and round <br>And round and round we go <br>Round and round in circles <br>Like we got no place to go <br><br>I've seen <br>Too much news about abusing color <br>We're all a canvas would you paint me red if I was darker <br>Too much blood spilt, it's like you can't escape the history <br>What was once is now now, just more eyes can see <br>We're all becoming too acquainted to these tainted lies <br>Like it's normal to be stop searched and then end your life <br>If I saw Martin would he tell me that he's had a dream <br>But if he's dreaming I would rather let him stay asleep <br>'Cause it's <br><br>Round and round and round and round <br>And round and round we go <br>Round and round and round and round <br>And round and round we go <br>Round and round and round and round <br>And round and round we go <br>Round and round in circles <br>Like we got no place to go <br><br>Round and round and <br>Round and round and <br>Round and round and <br>Round and round and <br>Round and round and <br>Round and round and <br>Round and round and <br>Round <br>Round and round and <br>Round and round and <br>Round and round and <br>Round and round and <br>Round and round and <br>Round and round and <br>Round and round and <br>Round and round and]]></content><category term="Jorja Smith" label="Jorja Smith"/><category term="Imperfect Circle" label="Imperfect Circle"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jorja_Smith/Carry_Me_Home/</id><title>Jorja Smith - Carry Me Home - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:39:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:39:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jorja_Smith/Carry_Me_Home/" title="Jorja Smith - Carry Me Home - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight strikes, where is my prince <br>Lost my comfort, more time to think <br>Broken and bruised, tell me what I am <br>Feel so unused, help me find your hand <br><br>I guess the sun still waits here <br>Had to hold it up for him <br><br>Carry me home <br>Bear my weight on your shoulders <br>Carry me home <br>Nothing else matters <br>Carry me home <br>Bear my weight on your shoulders <br>Carry me home <br>And don't let go <br><br>Say, said I don't ever say things so you can hear <br>Yet I waited, oh for your seas to fill <br>And now this barter seems to hide the place down and leave <br>The hurt <br>And now I feel like I've become your pain <br>Your daughter won't be safe with me <br><br>I guess the sun still waits here, here <br>Had to hold it up for him <br><br>Carry me home <br>Bear my weight on your shoulders no, oh I <br>Carry me home <br>Nothing else matters <br>Carry me home <br>Bear my weight on your shoulders <br>Carry me home <br>And don't let go <br><br>Guess I'm still here waiting <br>Darling I'm sorry, I tried <br>I gotta hold it up for him]]></content><category term="Jorja Smith" label="Jorja Smith"/><category term="Carry Me Home" label="Carry Me Home"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jorja_Smith/Carry_Me_Home_Interlude/</id><title>Jorja Smith - Carry Me Home (Interlude) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:39:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:39:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jorja_Smith/Carry_Me_Home_Interlude/" title="Jorja Smith - Carry Me Home (Interlude) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know you're weary and I've worn you out <br>but you can rest your mind here and take your trainers off and <br>I apologize <br>I should have approached this differently <br>We said we'd be honest with each other so I guess <br>You make me feel like the unrequited lover <br>I don't wanna follow you around until you find the truth <br>But I'd rather not kiss every stranger until I find you <br>Can't you just appear in my hands and I'll carry you instead <br>There's planets in my palms, if you get bored of my skin <br>I'm in change with the moon Habitual rituals <br>Your smiling and light is my only residual <br>The first time we met <br>did you go home and think of me too <br>Our silence said it's strange <br>we know and self consciousness is heavy <br>I know People overthink things <br>Women wreak havoc Men implode <br>But don't trouble yourself with my opinions <br>Just remember me in the morning and carry me home]]></content><category term="Jorja Smith" label="Jorja Smith"/><category term="Carry Me Home (Interlude)" label="Carry Me Home (Interlude)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jorja_Smith/So_Lonely/</id><title>Jorja Smith - So Lonely - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:39:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:39:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jorja_Smith/So_Lonely/" title="Jorja Smith - So Lonely - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Feelin' out of touch <br>Lost my way <br>No one ever asked me why <br>Tried to move along <br>Never looking back <br>You're gonna come around in time <br>Alone <br>Alone <br>Alone now my friend <br>Alone <br>Alone <br>Alone now my friend <br>Talkin' to the wolves <br>But my shadow's gone <br>Too much time to pretend <br>there's nothin' wrong <br>So lonely <br>So lonely <br>So lonely now my friend <br>Oh so lonely <br>So lonely <br>So lonely now my friend <br>I don't want to feel this way <br>Although it is true <br>when they say no <br>It's good for you to be alone no <br>But you can't learn it <br>all on your own no <br>Lonely <br>So lonely <br>So lonely now <br>my friend <br>Lone lonely <br>So lonely <br>So lonely has become my friend <br>]]></content><category term="Jorja Smith" label="Jorja Smith"/><category term="So Lonely" label="So Lonely"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jorja_Smith/Something_In_The_Way/</id><title>Jorja Smith - Something In The Way - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:39:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:39:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jorja_Smith/Something_In_The_Way/" title="Jorja Smith - Something In The Way - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I left I thought I would be stronger <br>But in fact, it took away my energy <br>Hard to tell you that I could not really see <br>Beyond the gates of this purgatory <br>I am so tainted now, I cannot wash you off <br>The memories still don't seem to fade <br>When I left, did you even wash your tears <br>'Cause mine have been dryin' for days <br><br>Something in the way <br>Why am I crying for you, babe <br>Can't stand the rain <br>Time to move on anyway <br><br>Don't ask me why <br>It's done <br>So long, goodbye <br>I'm gone <br><br>'Cause only sun in the summer lasts <br>No holdin' on and no lookin' back <br>Even the sun doesn't seem to last <br>It don't hold on, it's not comin' back <br><br>If I kept a hold a little longer <br>I would never think I'd ever get away <br>Don't want to say I tried to keep ya <br>Say love is blind, I couldn't see you change, no <br>Don't wanna find myself back in that place <br>I have wasted all my tears on fools <br>There was no help for me, no saving grace <br>I had been tryin' for days <br><br>There was something in the way <br>Why am I crying for you, babe <br>No I can't stand the rain <br>Time to move on anyway <br><br>Don't ask me why <br>It's done <br>So long, goodbye <br>I'm gone <br><br>'Cause only sun in the summer lasts <br>No holdin' on and no lookin' back <br>Even the sun doesn't seem to last <br>It don't hold on, it's not comin' back <br><br>Well there was something in the way <br>Why am I crying for you, babe <br>I can't stand the rain <br>Time to move on anyway <br><br>'Cause only sun in the summer lasts <br>No holdin' on and no lookin' back <br>Even the sun doesn't seem to last <br>It don't hold on, it's not comin' back <br>Even the sun in the summer doesn't seem to last <br>No holdin' on and no lookin' back <br>Even the sun doesn't seem to last <br>It don't hold on, it's not comin' back]]></content><category term="Jorja Smith" label="Jorja Smith"/><category term="Something In The Way" label="Something In The Way"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Claudia_Leitte/Taquita/</id><title>Claudia Leitte - Taquita - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:41:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:41:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Claudia_Leitte/Taquita/" title="Claudia Leitte - Taquita - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh o oh o oh lalalalala lalala <br>Oh o oh o oh lalalalala lalala <br><br>Eu to pronta pra descer do salto <br>Cabelo ja ta baguncado <br>O meu rebolado merece aplausos ai ai ai ai <br>E eu imaginando a gente <br>No transe de um beijo quente <br>Corre esse risco, foge comigo pra outro lugar <br><br>Olha como eu amo dancar <br>O meu corpo nao quer mais parar <br>Rebola, rebola, rebola aah <br>Alucino no seu reggaeton <br>Vou descendo com o dedo na boca <br>To louca, to louca <br><br>eta taquita <br>Xalalalala ooh xalalalala <br>Arrasando, causando <br>Pulando, dancando, te olhando <br>Pra te provocar <br><br>Taquita <br>Xalalalala xalalalala <br>To querendo amor <br>To querendo amar <br><br>eta taquita <br>Xalalalala ooh xalalalala <br>Arrasando, causando <br>Pulando, dancando, te olhando <br>Pra te provocar <br><br>Taquita <br>Xalalalala xalalalala <br>To querendo amor <br>To querendo amar <br><br>Eu to pronta pra descer do salto <br>Cabelo ja ta baguncado <br>O meu rebolado merece aplauso ai ai ai ai <br>E eu imaginando a gente <br>No transe de um beijo quente <br>Corre esse risco, foge comigo pra outro lugar <br><br>Olha como eu amo dancar <br>O meu corpo nao quer mais parar <br>Rebola, rebola, rebola aah <br>Alucino no seu reggaeton <br>Vou descendo com o dedo na boca <br>To louca, to louca <br><br>eta taquita <br>Xalalalala ooh xalalalala <br>Arrasando, causando <br>Pulando, dancando, te olhando <br>Pra te provocar <br><br>Taquita <br>Xalalalala xalalalala <br>To querendo amor <br>To querendo amar <br><br>eta taquita <br>Xalalalala ooh xalalalala <br>Arrasando, causando <br>Pulando, dancando, te olhando <br>Pra te provocar <br><br>Taquita <br>Xalalalala xalalalala <br>To querendo amor <br>To querendo amar <br><br>eta taquita <br>Xalalalala ooh xalalalala <br>Arrasando, causando <br>Pulando, dancando, te olhando <br>Pra te provocar <br><br>Taquita <br>Xalalalala xalalalala <br>To querendo amor <br>To querendo amar <br><br>eta taquita <br>Xalalalala]]></content><category term="Claudia Leitte" label="Claudia Leitte"/><category term="Taquita" label="Taquita"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/문규리/불타는_밤/</id><title>문규리 - 불타는 밤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:41:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:41:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B8%EA%B7%9C%EB%A6%AC/%EB%B6%88%ED%83%80%EB%8A%94_%EB%B0%A4/" title="문규리 - 불타는 밤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[노을이 불타는 <br>작은 섬 바닷가에서 <br>우연히 만난 <br>멋쟁이 그 남자 <br>바다가 보이는 <br>찻집에 마주 앉아서 <br>커피를 마시며 <br>사랑이 시작 됐네 <br>음악에 취해 <br>사랑에 취해 <br>부서지는 이 마음 <br>젊음이 불타는 <br>아름다운 밤이여 <br>달빛아래 두 그림자 <br>별빛아래 두 그림자 <br>마주잡은 두 손 <br>정들어 가는데 <br>해변의 벤취에서 <br>사랑을 속삭이는 <br>깊어가는 불타는 밤이여 <br>노을이 불타는 <br>작은 섬 바닷가에서 <br>우연히 만난 <br>멋쟁이 그 남자 <br>바다가 보이는 <br>찻집에 마주 앉아서 <br>커피를 마시며 <br>사랑이 시작 됐네 <br>음악에 취해 <br>사랑에 취해 <br>부서지는 이 마음 <br>젊음이 불타는 <br>아름다운 밤이여 <br>달빛아래 두 그림자 <br>별빛아래 두 그림자 <br>마주잡은 두 손 <br>정들어 가는데 <br>해변의 벤취에서 <br>사랑을 속삭이는 <br>깊어가는 불타는 밤이여 <br>깊어가는 불타는 밤이여 <br>]]></content><category term="문규리" label="문규리"/><category term="불타는 밤" label="불타는 밤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Living/A_Light/</id><title>Living - A Light - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:41:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:41:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Living/A_Light/" title="Living - A Light - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[early morning in the woods in autumn <br>and the leaves have started to glow <br>every lifeform in this meadow's noticed how the lights have started to breathe <br>I raise my arms and let the waves over me I will not stop until the very last note is over <br><br>share a secret with me and let go <br>lead me to the lips from which from which the song of life and love unfolds <br>let me sing the harmony's soul]]></content><category term="Living" label="Living"/><category term="A Light" label="A Light"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Living/Intuition/</id><title>Living - Intuition - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:41:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:41:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Living/Intuition/" title="Living - Intuition - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[one half's alone, the other is home <br>you know I try so hard to hold on <br><br>you know how true it is in your own core <br>uphold the law with which you rule, don't fall <br>give in to your light <br>let go of your sight]]></content><category term="Living" label="Living"/><category term="Intuition" label="Intuition"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Living/Apples__Oranges/</id><title>Living - Apples &amp; Oranges - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:41:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:41:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Living/Apples__Oranges/" title="Living - Apples &amp; Oranges - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[not so reckless, often mindless <br>keeping secrets, hiding treasures <br>in the shadows, from the darkness <br>now you see me, now you don't <br><br>if you can't do it for the memories we share, do it for our love <br>when you find someone to be glad together, don't play games with fate]]></content><category term="Living" label="Living"/><category term="Apples &amp; Oranges" label="Apples &amp; Oranges"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Living/Cerulean/</id><title>Living - Cerulean - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:41:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:41:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Living/Cerulean/" title="Living - Cerulean - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[is it by the shadow we measure the light <br>is it by the weakness we measure the strength <br>is it by how low you are we measure how high you can get <br>i want to fill every empty space with the colors you chose to rule my world <br>is it just a moment that goes by when we love <br><br>would you please let the clouds go, i want to ride another storm <br>would you wish on a star for a night's sleep to come alone <br><br>is it by the shadow we measure the light <br>isn't it by how low you are we measure how should i know <br>i want to fill every empty space with the colors you chose to rule my world <br>is it just a moment that goes by when we love <br>i know you know i know you know i know <br>it must be love <br><br>would you please let the clouds go, i want to ride another storm <br>would you wish on a star for a night's sleep to come alone]]></content><category term="Living" label="Living"/><category term="Cerulean" label="Cerulean"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Living/Risen/</id><title>Living - Risen - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:41:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:41:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Living/Risen/" title="Living - Risen - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[would you say you're willing to know me <br>from the way that I sing this song <br>would you say I'm so hard to please <br>I could never just let my dreams become a chore <br>not today, not today, not today, I won't say <br>i just don't know <br><br>once you know which part of me you cannot break or borrow <br>take the words you stole from the people you don't even know <br>throw them to the wind before you hurt the one you love <br><br>i will be living life as it were mine <br>you will find restful sleep when you wake up]]></content><category term="Living" label="Living"/><category term="Risen" label="Risen"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더_넛츠_The_NuTs/언젠가는_Inst/</id><title>더 넛츠 (The NuTs) - 언젠가는 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:41:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:41:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94_%EB%84%9B%EC%B8%A0_The_NuTs/%EC%96%B8%EC%A0%A0%EA%B0%80%EB%8A%94_Inst/" title="더 넛츠 (The NuTs) - 언젠가는 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[젊은 날엔 젊음을 모르고 <br>사랑할 땐 사랑이 보이지 않았네 <br>하지만 이제 뒤돌아보니 <br>우린 젊고 서로 사랑을 했구나 <br>눈물 같은 시간의 강 위에 <br>떠내려가는 건 한 다발의 추억 <br>그렇게 이제 뒤돌아보니 <br>젊음도 사랑도 아주 소중했구나 <br>언젠가는 우리 다시 만나리 <br>어디로 가는지 아무도 모르지만 <br>언젠가는 우리 다시 만나리 <br>헤어진 모습 이대로 <br>젊은 날엔 젊음을 잊었고 <br>사랑할 땐 사랑이 흔해만 보였네 <br>하지만 이제 생각해 보니 <br>우린 젊고 서로 사랑을 했구나 <br>언젠가는 우리 다시 만나리 <br>어디로 가는지 아무도 모르지만 <br>언젠가는 우리 다시 만나리 <br>헤어진 모습 이대로 <br>언젠가는 우리 다시 만나리 <br>어디로 가는지 아무도 모르지만 <br>언젠가는 우리 다시 만나리 <br>헤어진 모습 이대로 <br>]]></content><category term="더 넛츠 (The NuTs)" label="더 넛츠 (The NuTs)"/><category term="언젠가는 (Inst.)" label="언젠가는 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더_넛츠_The_NuTs/언젠가는/</id><title>더 넛츠 (The NuTs) - 언젠가는 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:41:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:41:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94_%EB%84%9B%EC%B8%A0_The_NuTs/%EC%96%B8%EC%A0%A0%EA%B0%80%EB%8A%94/" title="더 넛츠 (The NuTs) - 언젠가는 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[젊은 날엔 젊음을 모르고 <br>사랑할 땐 사랑이 보이지 않았네 <br>하지만 이제 뒤돌아보니 <br>우린 젊고 서로 사랑을 했구나 <br>눈물 같은 시간의 강 위에 <br>떠내려가는 건 한 다발의 추억 <br>그렇게 이제 뒤돌아보니 <br>젊음도 사랑도 아주 소중했구나 <br>언젠가는 우리 다시 만나리 <br>어디로 가는지 아무도 모르지만 <br>언젠가는 우리 다시 만나리 <br>헤어진 모습 이대로 <br>젊은 날엔 젊음을 잊었고 <br>사랑할 땐 사랑이 흔해만 보였네 <br>하지만 이제 생각해 보니 <br>우린 젊고 서로 사랑을 했구나 <br>언젠가는 우리 다시 만나리 <br>어디로 가는지 아무도 모르지만 <br>언젠가는 우리 다시 만나리 <br>헤어진 모습 이대로 <br>언젠가는 우리 다시 만나리 <br>어디로 가는지 아무도 모르지만 <br>언젠가는 우리 다시 만나리 <br>헤어진 모습 이대로 <br>]]></content><category term="더 넛츠 (The NuTs)" label="더 넛츠 (The NuTs)"/><category term="언젠가는" label="언젠가는"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Sounds/Thrill/</id><title>The Sounds - Thrill - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:42:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:42:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Sounds/Thrill/" title="The Sounds - Thrill - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I could see it slipping through my fingers <br>But I didn't feel a thing <br>I thought it was best to keep moving forward <br>But I am the one standing still <br><br>I'm out the outside <br>I'm told to keep my distance <br>Cause you're on the inside <br>And it's hard to keep resisting <br>Cause when I look at you it's such a thrill <br>Everytime I look at you it's such a thrill <br><br>They say that life is ever changing <br>But old habits are hard to kill <br>They say that my life's just an illusion <br>Reflections in the ocean lighting still <br><br>I'm out the outside <br>I'm told to keep my distance <br>Cause you're on the inside <br>And it's hard to keep resisting <br>Cause when I look at you it's such a thrill <br>Everytime I look at you <br>I know I love you still <br><br>Oh I'm on the outside <br>I'm told to keep my distance <br>You're on the inside <br>And it's hard to keep resisting <br>Yeah it's hard to keep resisting <br>Yeah it's hard to keep resisting <br>Cause when I look at you it's a hard thing to do <br>Everytime I look at you <br>I know I love you still <br><br>Oh I'm on the outside <br>You're on the inside <br>Cause when I look at you it's such a thrill <br>Everytime I look at you <br>I know I love you still]]></content><category term="The Sounds" label="The Sounds"/><category term="Thrill" label="Thrill"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Flame/</id><title>Sundara Karma - Flame - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:42:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:42:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Flame/" title="Sundara Karma - Flame - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Whoa wow, whoa wow, whoa wow, whoa wow <br><br>Cold fire feeling, is the cold fire feeling in my bones <br>Skylines breathing as the sun lies beating down the door <br><br>I'm tired of watching the shadows on the wall <br>My eyes are foreseeing <br>The shackles open, we're finally free to bolt <br>If you're done with believing <br><br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside <br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside out <br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside <br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside out <br><br>Found true meaning, now my head starts spinning out the cave <br>You won't come with me cause you're just too comfortable in chains <br><br>I'm tired of watching the shadows on the wall <br>My eyes are foreseeing <br>The shackles open, we're finally free to bolt <br>If you're done with believing <br><br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside <br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside out <br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside <br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside out <br><br>Oh oh oh, oh oh oh, oh oh oh, oh oh oh, oh oh oh]]></content><category term="Sundara Karma" label="Sundara Karma"/><category term="Flame" label="Flame"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/Jazzies_Groove/</id><title>Soul II Soul - Jazzie`s Groove - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:44:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:44:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/Jazzies_Groove/" title="Soul II Soul - Jazzie`s Groove - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What is Soul II Soul <br>Eh, well we're a sound system <br>An amalgamation of good dance music <br>There is, um, three of us from the north side <br>And two from the east <br>And through our style, you know <br>People just came to recognize us <br>As the funky dreads <br><br>Well, you know, trust has always meant a lot to all of us <br>For us to stay together <br>Where one would make a decision <br>And the rest would follow <br>I don't know, you know <br>That's the way we thought <br>The way things should be <br>I guess the way things should go <br>Soul II Soul <br><br>I don't know, it took us a real long time <br>To get things together, you know <br>But hopefully we're on our way <br><br>Yeah, we started in clubs and so on <br>A little bit of pressure here and there <br>You know we had our ups and downs <br>For everybody who can remember Africa Center <br>The center of the world <br>That gave us the, um, idea to now make our own music <br>Creating our own styles here in London <br><br>The future Ha, ha the future for Soul II Soul <br>A happy face, a thumping bass for a loving race Peace]]></content><category term="Soul II Soul" label="Soul II Soul"/><category term="Jazzie`s Groove" label="Jazzie`s Groove"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/Back_To_Life/</id><title>Soul II Soul - Back To Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:44:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:44:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/Back_To_Life/" title="Soul II Soul - Back To Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Back to life, back to reality <br>Back to life, back to reality <br>Back to life, back to reality <br>Back to the here and now, yeah <br>Show me how <br>Decide what you want from me <br>Tell me maybe I could be there for you <br><br>How ever do you want me, how <br>How ever do you need me <br>How ever do you want me <br>How ever do you need me, how <br>How ever do you want me <br>How ever do you need me <br><br>Back to life <br>Back to the present time <br>Back from a fantasy <br>Tell me now, take the initiative <br>I'll leave it in your hands <br>Until you're ready <br><br>How ever do you want me, how <br>How ever do you need me <br>How ever do you want me <br>How ever do you need me, how <br>How ever do you want me <br>How ever do you need me <br><br>I live at the top of the block <br>No more room for trouble and fuss <br>Need a change, a positive change <br>Look it's me writing on the wall <br><br>How ever do you want me, how <br>How ever do you need me <br>How ever do you want me <br>How ever do you need me, how <br>How ever do you want me <br>How ever do you need me <br><br>Back to life back to the day we have <br>Let's end this foolish game <br>Hear me out, don't let it waste away <br>Make up your mind so I know where I stand <br><br>How ever do you want me, how <br>How ever do you need me <br>How ever do you want me <br>How ever do you need me, how <br>How ever do you want me <br>How ever do you need me]]></content><category term="Soul II Soul" label="Soul II Soul"/><category term="Back To Life" label="Back To Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/Get_A_Life/</id><title>Soul II Soul - Get A Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:44:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:44:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/Get_A_Life/" title="Soul II Soul - Get A Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[this thing called life <br>know whats the meaning of the line <br>tell me <br>well its like dreaming of your goals <br>ambitions feeling free <br>achieve what <br>whats in your minds eye <br>this is what you should gain <br>satisfaction becomes a shinnning example <br>a test of a sample of a new race <br>that has ample supply of positivity <br>you mean flow <br>well like electricity <br>so you see a clear way with no ambiguity <br>dont you know <br>whats the meaning <br>whats the meaning of life <br>whats the meaning <br>whats the meaning of life <br>elevate your mind <br>free your soul <br>well come on come on <br>feel the feeling let your body take control <br>well dont be afraid to experiment you know umm <br>go ahead you know and implement your ideas <br>your notions put them in motion <br>like the words the funki dreds have spoken to you <br>so listen up loud and clear <br>this is a word you must be aware of <br>what ya gonna do put it in your life tool <br>and thats the meaning of life <br>whats the meaning <br>whats the meaning of life <br>whats the meaning <br>whats the meaning of life <br>whats the meaning <br>whats the meaning of life <br>whats the meaning <br>whats the meaning of life <br>and it goes on <br>elevate your mind <br>free your soul <br>well come on come on <br>feel the feeling let your body take control <br>so there it is work it out for yourself <br>yeah , be selective be ojective <br>be an asset to the collective <br>as you know you have to get a life <br>whats the meaning <br>whats the meaning of life <br>whats the meaning <br>whats the meaning of life <br>whats the meaning <br>whats the meaning of life <br>whats the meaning <br>whats the meaning of life <br>elevate your mind <br>free your soul <br>well come on come on <br>feel the feeling let your body take control <br>ah yeah]]></content><category term="Soul II Soul" label="Soul II Soul"/><category term="Get A Life" label="Get A Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/Love_Enough/</id><title>Soul II Soul - Love Enough - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:44:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:44:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/Love_Enough/" title="Soul II Soul - Love Enough - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All the best is yours and more <br>The world is knocking at your door <br>First class <br><br>Breaking through in all you do <br>The leader of the fresh and new <br>You're a genius <br><br>From the bottom to the top <br>You made yourself <br>You never stop <br>You're an a plus <br><br>You look too young to be alone <br>You seem so sad <br>And your smile is gone <br>So i have to ask <br><br>Hey, do you love enough baby <br>Oh, do you love enough baby <br>Hey, do you love enough baby <br>Oh, do you love enough baby <br><br>On your way to reach your dreams <br>You had it rough you had it lean <br>So tough, too tough <br><br>You had faith you made your move <br>You found your way into the groove <br>To trust enough <br><br>Did you ever ask yourself <br>Is so much work good for your health <br>What do you deserve <br><br>You choose your road you're on your own <br>Without a lover to call your own <br>What's it really worth <br><br>Hey, do you love enough baby <br>Oh, do you love enough baby <br>Hey, do you love enough baby <br>Oh, do you love enough baby <br><br>Have you asked yourself lately <br>Do i get enough lovin' in my life <br>Could you be makin' a mistake here <br>Maybe you better think twice <br>Do you really wanna be lonely <br>Could you use a little company <br>Have you ever asked yourself lately <br>Do i get enough love for me <br><br>Hey, do you love enough baby <br>Oh, do you love enough baby <br>Hey, do you love enough baby <br>Oh, do you love enough baby]]></content><category term="Soul II Soul" label="Soul II Soul"/><category term="Love Enough" label="Love Enough"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/Universal_Love/</id><title>Soul II Soul - Universal Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:44:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:44:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/Universal_Love/" title="Soul II Soul - Universal Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I dream of the day of universal love <br><br>life too precious to throw away like a flame it can easily blow away <br><br>into the future we're destined to go <br>time will show you we <br>already know the way <br>cultures closely connected all respected none neglected <br>the dream of love which is universal must happen then we will be one <br>bring down the walls <br><br>everybody listen make a change negative attitudes rearrange <br>join together forget the hate, the time is now we shouldn't leave it too late <br>colours never deceive me one family people believe me <br>brothers and sisters related <br>ancestrally who needs a barrier]]></content><category term="Soul II Soul" label="Soul II Soul"/><category term="Universal Love" label="Universal Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/Missing_You/</id><title>Soul II Soul - Missing You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:44:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:44:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/Missing_You/" title="Soul II Soul - Missing You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ooh, yeah <br>You're the sweetest <br>Yeah, baby <br>Oh, yes, you are <br>You're the sweetest <br>Yes, baby, ooh <br><br>Dreaming of you alone <br>Feelings in my mind and thoughts of you grow <br>On and on through the journey <br>In time that day I know will come <br><br>Drop of rain from the sky <br>A prayer, a miss on his lips, yeah <br>A glance, a smile and suddenly life comes alive <br><br>That's the way I'm missing you, boy <br>Your love is so sweet <br>That's the day our love will unfold, oh <br>Missing you <br>That's the way I'm missing you, boy <br>Your love is so sweet <br>That's the day our dreams will unfold, oh, yeah, yeah <br><br>I wait for you until the time is right <br>I hope and pray each and every night <br>To make you happy, sometimes blue <br>I need to feel, feel for you <br><br>Drop of rain from the sky <br>A prayer, a miss on his lips, yeah <br>A glance, a smile and suddenly life is alive <br><br>That's the way I'm missing you, boy, mmm <br>Your love is so sweet <br>That's the day our dreams will unfold, oh <br>Missing you <br>That's the way I'm missing you boy <br>Your love is so sweet <br>That's the day our dreams will unfold, oh <br><br>Ooh, baby, ooh <br>The sweetest, yeah, yeah <br><br>As the morning comes, I'll open my eyes <br>And think once again, am I dreaming <br>Is this true, I know our love will come through <br>Because, baby, you're the sweetest <br><br>That's the way I'm missing you, boy <br>Your love is so sweet <br>And that's the day our love will unfold, oh <br>Missing you <br>That's the way I'm missing you, boy <br>Your love is so sweet <br>That's the day our dreams will unfold, oh, yeah <br>Your love is so sweet <br><br>And you know that I know I'm missing you <br>Wanting you, loving you, my love is true <br>And you know that I know my love is true <br>Missing you, wanting you, my loving you <br>And you know I know my love is true <br>Missing you, wanting you, and I'm loving you <br>And you know that I know I'm loving you <br>Missing you, wanting you, my love is true]]></content><category term="Soul II Soul" label="Soul II Soul"/><category term="Missing You" label="Missing You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/I_Care/</id><title>Soul II Soul - I Care - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:44:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:44:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/I_Care/" title="Soul II Soul - I Care - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I would not want to live in a world <br>Say that i would not want to live in a world without you <br>Sout to soul I love you <br>Say that i love a higher love, so high a love it lets my spirit see <br><br>I would not want to live in a world <br>Say that i would not want to live in a world without you <br>Soul to soul i love you <br>Say that i would not want to live in a world without you <br><br>Soul to soul i love you <br>Soul to soul i care <br>I would not want to live in a world if you're not there <br><br>Say that i love a richer love so rich a love it cannot be <br>Continued <br>Say that i love a stronger love <br>So strong nothing else remains <br><br>I would not want to live in a world, say that i would not want to <br>Live in a world without you <br>Soul to soul i love you say that i would not want to live in a <br>World without you <br><br>Soul to soul i love you <br>Soul to soul i care <br>I would not want to live in a world if you're not there]]></content><category term="Soul II Soul" label="Soul II Soul"/><category term="I Care" label="I Care"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/Keep_On_Moving/</id><title>Soul II Soul - Keep On Moving - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:44:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:44:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_II_Soul/Keep_On_Moving/" title="Soul II Soul - Keep On Moving - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Keep on moving <br>Don't stop like the hands of time <br>Click clock, find your own way to stay <br>The time will come one day <br>Why do people choose to live their lives this way <br><br>Keep on moving, don't stop, no <br>Keep on moving <br>Keep on moving <br>Keep on moving don't stop, no <br>Keep on moving <br><br>It's our time, time today <br>The right time is here to stay <br>Stay in my life, my life always <br>Yellow is the color of sunrays <br>I hide myself from no one <br>I know the time will surely come when <br>You'll be in my life, my life always <br>Yellow is the color of sunrays <br><br>Keep on moving <br>Keep on moving <br>Don't stop <br>Keep on moving, don't stop no <br>Like the hands of time <br>Keep on moving <br>Click clock <br>Find your own way to stay <br>Keep on moving <br>The time will come one day <br><br>Keep on moving, don't stop, no <br>Keep on moving <br>Keep on moving <br>Keep on moving, don't stop, no <br>Keep on moving <br><br>I know the time, time today <br>Walking alone in my own way <br>Extremely cold and rainy day <br>Friends and I have fun along the way <br>Yes we do <br>I hide myself from no one <br>I know the time will really come when <br>You'll be in my life, my life always <br>Yellow is the color of sunrays <br><br>Keep on moving <br>Keep on moving <br>Don't stop <br>Keep on moving, don't stop no <br>Like the hands of time <br>Keep on moving <br>Click clock <br><br>Keep on moving <br>Find your own way to stay <br>The time will come one day <br>Yes <br>Keep on moving <br>Keep on moving, don't stop, no <br>Keep on moving]]></content><category term="Soul II Soul" label="Soul II Soul"/><category term="Keep On Moving" label="Keep On Moving"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sophia_소피아/Life_Is_Feat_DooKID/</id><title>Sophia (소피아) - Life Is (Feat. DooKID) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:44:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:44:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sophia_%EC%86%8C%ED%94%BC%EC%95%84/Life_Is_Feat_DooKID/" title="Sophia (소피아) - Life Is (Feat. DooKID) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Life is <br>Life is <br>Life is always lonely <br>Life is always lonely <br>Life is always lonely <br>Life is always lonely <br>아무도 없는 방 <br>나를 맞이하는 차가운 공기 <br>Tic Toc 정적 속 <br>유난히 둔탁한 소리 <br>생각보다 외로운 <br>표정을 짓고 있잖아 <br>꺼진 모니터가 비추는 <br>내 모습이 <br>하염없이 걷다 보니 <br>난 혼자서 걷고 있어 <br>주변은 적들 뿐 인데도 <br>착각 어린 시선을 <br>보내는 사람들 <br>물론 악의는 없을 터 <br>날 가둬 논 곳에는 <br>이미 만들어진 질서 <br>누가 날 갖다 놨어 <br>이 도시 한복판에 <br>무언의 압박 속 <br>잠시 물러나 항복하네 <br>도움도 돈도 안 되니까 <br>나가 넌 도태 됐어 <br>그래도 피 땀 어린 손으로 <br>Microphone Checka <br>가식을 두르고 <br>나에게 친한 척을 하면서도 <br>선을 그어 <br>그래 다 뿌리치고 터벅터벅 걸어 <br>변한 건 없어 단지 <br>심장박동이 급격해졌을 뿐 <br>Life is <br>Life is always lonely <br>Life is always lonely <br>Life is always lonely <br>Life is always lonely <br>Life is <br>Life is always lonely <br>어쩌면 이건 Paranoid <br>어쩌면 이건 Paranoid <br>누군가 나를 반겨도 <br>한 번 더 의심하고 보네 <br>필요치 않음 내치는 일 <br>아니 언제부턴가 <br>그걸 내가 하고있어 <br>그토록 혐오했던 짓거리를 <br>자기개발 안 할 거면 <br>친한 척 말아 <br>넌 도태 됐어 <br>네가 없어도 외로이 <br>Microphone Checka <br>이리 된 거 홀로 삶을 노래하네 <br>감흥이 없을 듯해도 <br>Cash Rules Everything Around Me <br>오늘도 터벅터벅 걸어 <br>변한 건 없어 단지 <br>심장박동이 차분해졌을 뿐 <br>life is <br>Life is always lonely <br>Life is always lonely <br>Life is <br>Life is <br>Life is always lonely <br>]]></content><category term="Sophia (소피아)" label="Sophia (소피아)"/><category term="Life Is (Feat. DooKID)" label="Life Is (Feat. DooKID)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김진솔/민요메들리/</id><title>김진솔 - 민요메들리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:46:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:46:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%84%EC%86%94/%EB%AF%BC%EC%9A%94%EB%A9%94%EB%93%A4%EB%A6%AC/" title="김진솔 - 민요메들리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아리 아리 쓰리 쓰리 아라리요 <br>아리 아리 고개로 넘어간다 <br>아주까리 정자는 구경자리 <br>살구나무 정자로만 만나보세 hey <br>아리 아리 쓰리 쓰리 아라리요 <br>아리 아리 고개로 넘어간다 <br>열라는 콩팥은 왜 아니 열고 <br>아주까리 동백은 왜 여는가 <br>바람이 분다 바람이 분다 <br>연평 바다에 어얼사 돈바람 분다 <br>얼사 좋네 하 좋네 군밤이요 <br>에헤라 생율 밤이로구나 <br>달도 밝다 달도 밝다 <br>우주 강산에 어얼사 저 달이 밝아 <br>얼사 좋네 하 좋네 군밤이요 <br>에헤라 생율 밤이로구나 <br>눈이 온다 눈이 온다 <br>이 산 저 산에 어얼사 흰눈이 온다 <br>얼사 좋네 하 좋네 군밤이요 <br>에헤라 생율 밤이로구나 <br>날좀보소 날좀보소 날좀보소 <br>동지 섣달 꽃 본듯이 날좀보소 <br>아리아리랑 스리스리랑 <br>아라리가 났네 <br>아리랑 고개로 날 넘겨주소 <br>아리아리랑 스리스리랑 <br>아라리가 났네 <br>아리랑 고개로 날 넘겨주소 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아라리요 <br>아리랑 고개로 넘어간다 <br>나를 버리고 가시는 임은 <br>십리도 못가서 발병난다 <br>1 2 3 4 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아라리요 <br>아리랑 고개로 넘어간다 <br>나를 버리고 가시는 임은 <br>십리도 못가서 발병난다 <br>십리도 못가서 발병난다 <br>십리도 못가서 발병난다 <br>십리도 못가서 발병난다 <br>]]></content><category term="김진솔" label="김진솔"/><category term="민요메들리" label="민요메들리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sayyi/Luh_That_Sound_Feat_Jeremih/</id><title>Sayyi - Luh That Sound (Feat. Jeremih) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:46:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:46:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sayyi/Luh_That_Sound_Feat_Jeremih/" title="Sayyi - Luh That Sound (Feat. Jeremih) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ride a little time on top <br>Girl, won't you do the thing your way <br>You know I got a brand new watch <br>Rollie, no time ticker <br>Baby cause it's our time <br>Ain't nothing wrong with it <br>When they say you have them funds <br>All I need is a bad lil bitch <br>Know what to do with a bag <br>Told you long time, I been that nigga <br>Now you gotta pay me in cash <br><br>Love that sound baby, love that sound baby <br>Love that sound baby, love that sound baby <br>Love that sound baby, love that sound baby <br>Love that sound baby, love that sound baby <br><br>I love that sound on the money counter <br>Stacks on stacks, counting on the counter <br>Counter on the counter, money on the hour <br>Lot of dirty money, gotta take a shower <br>Getting fresher than a dope boy, no powder <br>Got the tommy in the Ghost and I ain't on Power <br>On the paper every 24, Jack Bower <br>I don't fuck with no fakers, I don't know cowards <br>Yeah, I love that sound on the rubber bands <br>Bad bitch baguette on the way to France <br>No IOU, need it in advance <br>Get a snowball in hell, got a better chance <br>No way a nigga gon' be broke <br>Got bread on bread, that's doe see doe <br>My bank account kidnap 6 zero's <br>That new money, singing C notes and I <br><br>Love that sound baby, love that sound baby <br>Love that sound baby, love that sound baby <br>Love that sound baby, love that sound baby <br>Love that sound baby, love that sound baby <br><br>Ride a little time on top <br>Girl, won't you do the thing your way <br>You know I got a brand new watch <br>Rollie, no time ticker <br>Baby cause it's our time <br>Ain't nothing wrong with it <br>When they say you have them funds <br>All I need is a bad lil bitch <br>Know what to do with a bag <br>Told you long time, I been that nigga <br>Now you gotta pay me in cash <br><br>Love that sound baby, love that sound baby <br>Love that sound baby, love that sound baby <br>Love that sound baby, love that sound baby <br>Love that sound baby, love that sound baby]]></content><category term="Sayyi" label="Sayyi"/><category term="Luh That Sound (Feat. Jeremih)" label="Luh That Sound (Feat. Jeremih)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Two_Tone_Rebel/</id><title>E-Dubble - Two Tone Rebel - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:46:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:46:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Two_Tone_Rebel/" title="E-Dubble - Two Tone Rebel - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hop to it with the fluids <br>Study like a student who be fucking with them truants <br>I never left <br>No pack but I still smell sewage <br>Catch me blowing on that loud like a motherfucking tuba <br>Like it's motherfucking Zumba <br>Robot drop top cut throat mula <br>Hopped out that uber <br>Brand new shoes no newer <br>Don't fuck with me I got that two tone rebel shit stuck to me <br>And it's a luxury fucking with these beats got me living comfortably <br>And what I provide is the soundtrack that proves we went through this life <br>Never divide, always survive <br>Okay folks, we have arrived <br><br>Jazzers on deck when I come through <br>No Five O on my gum shoe <br>We got more kicks than a kung fu <br>Flick fuckboy might get it when he come to <br>But he don't seem like he'll be waking up <br>Most slept on him, fuck it cousin show me love <br>Two one fifth in my veins don't get it fucked <br>Run up on me wrong I won't even fuck a knuckle up <br><br>Roughly about the size of Shaq, I fire back <br>I fire first, the damage hurts <br>The chorus hits, the drums are sick <br>Got kids out in Dubai banging my old shit <br>The dude is home <br>The wheels are clean <br>The flow is mean <br>I been E dubble since the days of between <br>And god damn, I'm about the Shoulder Lean <br>Like Young Dro and TI <br>lock and loaded <br>Drama they like me <br>Fools size dont psych me <br>Pull up on eighteens and yeah they just like me <br>V8 all in mine, my wheels and my rims shine <br>RT go hard G no question with rim job <br>Front for that sponsor, front for that front doe' <br>If they can't each time my horse would be front row <br>Fuck what they came for, I know what they came for <br>My name is E dubble and I am not paid <br>Fuck plan B, I got a plan for it <br>I put my head down and I just ran for it <br>Couldn't see the pitfalls that I ran towards <br>Moving so fast I was coming out my airforce <br>Keep your shoes on, get your move on <br>Stop slippin' you been trippin' way too long <br>Both shoes on, new true song <br>Rings a bell Well, it must be two tones <br><br>Jazzers on deck when I come through <br>No Five O on my gum shoe <br>Beat got more kicks than a kung fu <br>Flick fuckboy might get it when he come to <br>But he don't seem like he'll be waking up <br>Most slept on, fuck it cousin show me love <br>Two one fifth in my veins don't get it fucked <br>Run up on me wrong I won't even fuck a knuckle up lock and loaded <br><br>Jazzers on deck when I come through <br>No Five O on my gum shoe <br>Beat got more kicks than a kung fu <br>Flick fuckboy might get it when he come to <br>But he don't seem like he'll be waking up <br>Most slept on, fuck it cousin show me love <br>Two one fifth in my veins don't get it fucked <br>Run up on me wrong I won't even fuck a knuckle up <br><br>Jazzers on deck when I come through <br>No Five O on my gum shoe <br>Beat got more kicks than a kung fu <br>Flick fuckboy might get it when he come to <br>But he don't seem like he'll be waking up <br>Most slept on, fuck it cousin show me love <br>Two one fifth in my veins don't get it fucked <br>Run up on me wrong I won't even fuck a knuckle up]]></content><category term="E-Dubble" label="E-Dubble"/><category term="Two Tone Rebel" label="Two Tone Rebel"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Graceland/</id><title>E-Dubble - Graceland - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:46:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:46:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Graceland/" title="E-Dubble - Graceland - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been down, for so long <br>But so long to that me <br>I've been gone, I've been wrong <br>But I'm gonna succeed <br>I'm aware, now I care about my surroundings <br>There's bigger things happening <br>Now I'm not sleeping on my dreams <br>Ohhh <br>I'm not sleeping on my dreams <br>Oh ohhhh <br>I'm not sleeping on my dreams <br><br>'82, I was born, given life <br>'92, I was ten, living life <br>'93, shit done change I saw light <br>When that real rap played my brain get all hyped <br>So I'm two steppin', yeah <br>I'm up in the place and every crew repping <br>But they got love for the Pais, BP <br>And I ain't even stepping on stage <br>I don't mean to dissuade <br>I just came to get blazed <br>In any case, you know that I be bloggin' bloggin' <br>And I ain't even typed one word <br>Man, that shit don't rhyme <br>And that shit's absurd <br>Still got that head nod shit that will shake your nerves <br>And I go <br><br>I've been down, for so long <br>But so long to that me <br>I've been gone, I've been wrong <br>But I'm gonna succeed <br>I'm aware, now I care about my surroundings <br>There's bigger things happening <br>Now I'm not sleeping on my dreams <br>Ohhh <br>I'm not sleeping on my dreams <br>Oh ohhhh <br>I'm not sleeping on my dreams <br><br>I turned your water to wine <br>Turned your wine into water <br>It's impressive get the messes, that's some shit they ain't taught us <br>That's the shit they ain't teaching <br>How to argue with reason <br>How to live up to big dreams and never deceive 'em <br>I got my girl in the front, got my dog in the back <br>They stuntin' all over like they ain't part of the pack <br>We always keep calm, we like when its cool <br>I do, I take a different path when my ass outta school <br>I got that 1 2 3 4, arrogant tool <br>And when it goes off it blows off the ignorant fools <br>I ain't talking about the second amendment <br>We can bend it and stretch it, but either way I got my mind as a weapon <br>I can promise I don't threaten to beckon <br>Never asking for seconds unless we all ate, pray for digestion <br>Hope that we can leave an impression <br>Hope that we can dodge the dogmatic and take heed of the blessings <br>And I'm gone <br><br>I've been down, for so long <br>But so long to that me <br>I've been gone, I've been wrong <br>But I'm gonna succeed <br>I'm aware, now I care about my surroundings <br>There's bigger things happening <br>Now I'm not sleeping on my dreams <br>Ohhh <br>I'm not sleeping on my dreams <br>Oh ohhhh <br>I'm not sleeping on my dreams]]></content><category term="E-Dubble" label="E-Dubble"/><category term="Graceland" label="Graceland"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Getting_By_Im_Good/</id><title>E-Dubble - Getting By (I`m Good) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:46:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:46:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Getting_By_Im_Good/" title="E-Dubble - Getting By (I`m Good) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh shit <br><br>When the five roll up and they saw that J <br>But its not big deal 'cause away you stay <br>Say I'm good Motherfucker <br>Motherfucker I'm good tryna fuck her <br>When your girl act up in a public place, and you ain't got that much to say <br>Motherfucker I'm good, motherfucker what <br>Motherfucker I'm good, motherfucker what <br>Motherfucker go <br><br>Ay, let me take it from the top though <br>I'm the fire man catch me in the high post <br>I'm the fire man catch me getting high though <br>Never see me stuntin' even if I won the lotto <br>I ain't playin' no lotto, I got a sure thing all in my bravado <br>They got a tax on the willing <br>They've been smacked to the building <br>Then they wonder why we barely getting by though <br>I be getting by though, I be getting by though <br>Is Iraq Chiraq, Pablo <br>Everybody movin' something, everybody movin' nothing <br>Everybody wonder how they getting by though <br>How they getting by though How they getting by though <br>How they getting, How they ge , How they, How they, How they getting by though <br>They got a tax on the willing <br>They've been smacked to the building <br>Then they wonder why we barely getting by though <br><br>When the five roll up and they saw that J <br>But its not big deal 'cause away you stay <br>Say I'm good Motherfucker <br>Motherfucker I'm good tryna fuck her <br>When your girl act up in a public place, and you ain't got that much to say <br>Motherfucker I'm good, motherfucker what <br>Motherfucker I'm good, motherfucker what <br>Motherfucker go <br><br>I got the TV on with the sound turned off <br>No Danza, I'm the new boss <br>New stanzas, two hands up <br>Cold pen, like I'm the new frost <br>I'mma, hold up, find me in my habitat <br>Bloggin' like a motherfucker <br>Grabbing on that hourglass <br>My stopwatch like an hour fast <br>Living in the future but the future lives an hour past <br>So we chop it up, move it out some <br>We be working hard for the fam and the outcome <br>Black Paisley, the story's never outdone <br>All we do is truth tell, leaving when it's not fun <br>All we do is win even when I'm at a loss <br>Onomatopoeia, fuckin' up these boss <br>Onomatopoeia, when I'm drivin' cars <br>Vroom, vroom, go fast <br>We duckin' in the Charge <br><br>When the five roll up and they saw that J <br>But its not big deal 'cause away you stay <br>Say I'm good Motherfucker <br>Motherfucker I'm good tryna fuck her <br>When your girl act up in a public place, and you ain't got that much to say <br>Motherfucker I'm good, motherfucker what <br>Motherfucker I'm good, motherfucker what <br>Motherfucker go]]></content><category term="E-Dubble" label="E-Dubble"/><category term="Getting By (I`m Good)" label="Getting By (I`m Good)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Olly_Olly_Oxen_Free/</id><title>E-Dubble - Olly Olly (Oxen Free) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:47:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:47:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Olly_Olly_Oxen_Free/" title="E-Dubble - Olly Olly (Oxen Free) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Olly Olly Oxen Free <br>Two tone rebel never leave scraps on the table when there's food left <br>Olly Olly Oxen Free <br>I rely on myself in the work that I carry in my tool chest <br>Olly Olly Oxen Free <br>Who runs Who hides Who lives Who dies In this fool's quest <br>Olly Olly Oxen Free <br>And I'll be damned if I let myself trip from a lesser man's ledge <br><br>Early in the morning, barely got my eyes up <br>Take two steps forward pull the blinds up <br>Trying to see if this world made its mind up <br>Wise up, no chance, catch me with them blinders <br>Bring the bass back, like I run the base path <br>Pull me back up in the game I got an ace bandage <br>'88 choc milk with that egg sandwich <br>Can't play a player when it play with the mazes <br>They need a fall guy, no man, totem pole <br>Big girl tried to honeypot the yoga pose <br>Big deal I can wait out all the rope a dopes <br>Only deal with greens so you never catch me overdose <br>Uh huh <br>See they barking up the wrong tree <br>Off key singing like they think that they just bought me <br>Uh <br>But you can never buy me <br>Soundproof truth that my people are behind me <br><br>Olly Olly Oxen Free <br>Two tone rebel never leave scraps on the table when there's food left <br>Olly Olly Oxen Free <br>I rely on myself in the work that I carry in my tool chest <br>Olly Olly Oxen Free <br>Who runs Who hides Who lives Who dies In this fools quest <br>Olly Olly Oxen Free <br>And I'll be damned if I let myself trip from a lesser mans ledge <br><br>If they not their own man, I don't fuck with 'em <br>'Cause can't nobody hold me down, like puffing 'em <br>In this game, you know I got the toughest skin <br>I was told you can't break what doesn't bend <br>I'm in love with sin, I'll be wiling 'cause <br>Had a tree sprayed with raid because my style is above <br>Yeah my style is love, my style is get get it <br>I reside at the top, you will never visit <br>You can never kick it where the winners are <br>They talk tough, we roll up and they be bitching hard <br>We just laugh at 'em, it's simple mathematics <br>I keep a blade on me, go and take a stab at it <br>I'll be in a cut, I'm all about the bucks <br>Did he have a face Well then it wasn't us <br>On that bias shit <br>You can't deny this shit <br>E dub and Reef drugs, we supply the hit <br><br>Olly Olly Oxen Free <br>Two tone rebel never leave scraps on the table when there's food left <br>Olly Olly Oxen Free <br>I rely on myself in the work that I carry in my tool chest <br>Olly Olly Oxen Free <br>Who runs Who hides Who lives Who dies In this fools quest <br>Olly Olly Oxen Free <br>And I'll be damned if I let myself trip from a lesser mans ledge]]></content><category term="E-Dubble" label="E-Dubble"/><category term="Olly Olly (Oxen Free)" label="Olly Olly (Oxen Free)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Waves/</id><title>E-Dubble - Waves - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:47:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:47:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Waves/" title="E-Dubble - Waves - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My name is e dubble <br><br>Woah baby <br>It's them waves, oh <br>It's alright baby <br>Got them waves, yo <br>It's alright baby <br>It's them waves, yeah <br>It's alright baby <br>It's them waves, yeah <br><br>Yeah, fuck that, I'm a backseat blogger <br>Shotgun pretext looking like a logger <br>Oh, probably sipping on a lager <br>Beard so big you should probably call me father <br>Huh, and I mean like Hey Zeus <br>No Christ but the choir's singing Hey Jude <br>Yeah, cuz I'm a Beatle when I roll stones <br>And I'mma be there when you get home <br><br>I push that rap way back straight, gimme that beat break <br>8 bars, sing along, two tone <br>Haha, yo <br>I push that rap way back straight, gimme that beat break <br>8 bars, sing along, two tone renegade <br>Blueprints, never afraid, party like I'm hella paid <br>Like a '99 Eminem yellow fade <br>Uncle Jay getting cake, laughing at his little date <br>They be dashing with a passion 'cuz they been ashamed <br>Fuck with me and you know just what it means, if you think I mean beef come and see just what I eat <br>What I eat]]></content><category term="E-Dubble" label="E-Dubble"/><category term="Waves" label="Waves"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Heat_Five_Ohh/</id><title>E-Dubble - Heat (Five Ohh) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:47:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:47:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Heat_Five_Ohh/" title="E-Dubble - Heat (Five Ohh) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Riding through the city with my eyes low <br>I'm getting getting love out in Oslo <br>I'm rolling with a posse full of pyros <br>These people need the heat so we deliver like we Five O <br>Five O, there go the Five O <br>They talking shit they pulling guns just like they Five O <br>Five O, there go the Five O <br>And I ain't stressing no depressants, got the hydro <br><br>I eat well, I fuck great, I have no complaints <br>Them lames in the background can't eat off my plate <br>I'm e dub, I'm two tones, there is no debate <br>If you sleep on me wake up that bed 'bout to break <br>I got that two step, '82, black and blue Nike shoes <br>I can trek through anything mostly I know what it do <br>Back when I was smaller was mistaken for a baller <br>I grew up with a shoulder chip got big as I got taller <br>And I'm on it 'till I'm not, bullshit got me hot <br>Why the fuck so many brothers losing lives on shocken cops <br>A preacher I am not, politcian I am not <br>With that body camera stamina put baby in the spot <br>Bassline go hammer, my beats have no manners <br>They come to your table and eat up your sandwich <br>I have that advantage, I been had the leverage <br>That seven foot rank can still get quite protected <br>I'll expose who controls everything from beneath <br>They dispose of the soul, release with the bleach <br>Any thoughts of the matrix, controlled by police <br>And we made to believe they want peace <br><br>I cop a chainsaw and motherfucking vroom, vroom <br>I'll make you feel like you just ate up some shroom, shrooms <br>I brought my baseball bat, but I ain't come to play <br>The cops watch us hope they got us on a big display <br><br>Two tone rebel never settle for the subtle <br>I be double when it comes to getting digi with your hustle <br>I be on it 'cause they want it, if they didn't I would flush it <br>Got a hundred different ways to turn them bitches into nothing <br>If you looking at the numbers, if you really do the numbers <br>Population lost the politicians fucking with encumbrance <br>I ain't fucking with the politics, fuck it I'll be honest with you <br>Ever watching, I be over me just like Obama's picture <br>I will never run, I will only put it down <br>How I see it, how I spray it, this is all within the sound <br>I see them going hard, so I'm gonna make 'em proud <br>It's what we love to do for our people in the crowd <br><br>Riding through the city with my eyes low <br>I'm getting getting love out in Oslo <br>I'm rolling with a posse full of pyros <br>These people need the heat so we deliver like we Five O <br>Five O, there go the Five O <br>They talking shit they pulling guns just like they Five O <br>Five O, there go the Five O <br>And I ain't stressing no depressants, got the hydro]]></content><category term="E-Dubble" label="E-Dubble"/><category term="Heat (Five Ohh)" label="Heat (Five Ohh)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/War_Of_Attrition/</id><title>E-Dubble - War Of Attrition - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:47:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:47:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/War_Of_Attrition/" title="E-Dubble - War Of Attrition - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When the reaper come to join ya <br>Can you keep that chin up high <br>Did you do your best with all you had <br>Or did you live life through those lies <br><br>When the reaper come to join ya <br>Can you keep that chin up high <br>Did you do your best with all you had <br>Or did you live life through those lies <br><br>Did you do what they had told you <br>Or did you branch out through your soul <br>And if you lost that game, but won that war <br>Ohhhh <br><br>In the city with heathens, smoking that dope shit <br>Work for a purpose and pull you off of the sofa <br>Work for the people, eliminate evil <br>This pen and paper is enough to make it raise to the steeples <br>I got my people behind me, and they don't play clown <br>If the given's a given, then we ain't fuckin' around <br>If the given's a given, then we can come to your town <br>For the right price I can burn the stage to the ground <br>I got my Lewis the Dog, she don't play bitch she don't play bitch <br>Fuck with me, you fuck with her, like Lilo and Stitch <br>I am legend with the message, and I don't need to trip <br>I got a million different ways to make you forty and <br>I keep my tense in the present, I fuck up some verbs <br>Politicking but this is because the rest is absurd <br>I'm a pog slammer, slammin' everything that occurred <br>I'm a pog slammer, slammin' everything that occurred <br><br>When the reaper come to join ya <br>Can you keep that chin up high <br>Did you do your best with all you had <br>Or did you live life through those lies <br><br>Did you do what they had told you <br>Or did you branch out through your soul <br>And if you lost that game, but won that war <br>Ohhhh <br><br>My life on my clock turn up <br>Too fast for the regular pace <br>No salsa dance, I two step at brunch, and that's only when I feel like a motherfucking <br>Damn what I'm feeling <br>Damn what I'm feeling <br>Doing what I love, got they hand to the ceiling <br>I'm the man in the building, I stand like a building <br>Double trouble motherfucker brought bands for the children <br>God damn in the building, I stand like a man in the building <br>I stand like a man when I'm chilling <br>I stand like a man when I'm killing <br>I never been about those money motherfucker's standing on the beat <br>I got a hundred different ways to tell a motherfucker Bounce <br>I go Hey, tell a motherfucker Bounce <br>I go Hey, tell a motherfucker Bounce <br>I go Hey, tell a motherfucker Bounce <br><br>When the reaper come to join ya <br>Can you keep that chin up high <br>Did you do your best with all you had <br>Or did you live life through those lies <br><br>Did you do what they had told you <br>Or did you branch out through your soul <br>And if you lost that game, but won that war <br>Ohhhh <br><br>Hey, yo way to bounce that <br>Break your motherfucking neck <br>I be wiling on <br>What you looking at fag <br>Pretty little punk <br>Break your motherfucking neck <br>I be wiling on <br>What you looking at fag]]></content><category term="E-Dubble" label="E-Dubble"/><category term="War Of Attrition" label="War Of Attrition"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/One_Question/</id><title>E-Dubble - One Question - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:47:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:47:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/One_Question/" title="E-Dubble - One Question - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a Northeast spitter with a big sized cap and them lames ain't fucking with me <br>Got brains, got brawn, got a dog named Lewis so them named stayed, the named stayed <br><br>I'm a Northeast spitter with a big sized cap and them lames ain't fucking with me <br>Got brains, got brawn, got a dog named Lewis so them dames stay fucking with me <br>I can't complain I got a mug she can love for a very long time and I'm pretty damn good in the sheets <br>I got balls so big you ain't even gotta ask get your fine ass up in the seat <br><br>Now little lady may I ask you a question my shit gets to flexin' <br>In every direction there's sexual tension <br>Back to the question and with some discretion I have this erection that needs some attention <br>The spandex neglected to stay in its section now I cannot stand up until I'm ejected <br>I need some protection I don't do infections <br>It's not a suggestion let's contra those ceptives <br>I go, so hard I don't know better, dog <br>Beefin' with myself so I'll probably get a bodyguard <br>Hit 'em with the audio <br>We be at the Mardi Gras <br>Other side of town <br>We get down with the all of y'all <br>Bounce Hop to it if you really need a quick fix <br>Spit game quicker than an Eagle with a pick 6 <br> Write it on my list for next Christmas <br>Santa finally caught himself a motherfucking sneak diss <br><br>I'm a Northeast spitter with a big sized cap and them lames ain't fucking with me <br>Got brains, got brawn, got a dog named Lewis so them dames stay fucking with me <br>I can't complain I got a mug she can love for a very long time and I'm pretty damn good in the sheets <br>I got balls so big you ain't even gotta ask get your fine ass up in the seat <br><br>Now little mama <br>I'mma ask you just one question <br>Please don't tell me no lie <br>I've been around this block <br>More than once, more than twice <br>Now little mama <br>I'mma work you all something really special, if you want it <br>Got a hundred different ways that I can get your ass to coming <br>No fronting, I'm blunted, after work <br>We can cuddle, I'm the big spoon <br>You're the little spoon in the cupboard <br>I love it, you can dub it <br>And handle it how you want it <br>With the dubble, there's no trouble <br>Twerking is undiscovered <br>Hell yeah, out to bubble and double up on the subtle <br>Find the baby I don't bumble and settle up in the suburbs <br><br>I'm a Northeast spitter with a big sized cap and them lames ain't fucking with me <br>Got brains, got brawn, got a dog named Lewis so them dames stay fucking with me <br>I can't complain I got a mug she can love for a very long time and I'm pretty damn good in the sheets <br>I got balls so big you ain't even gotta ask get your fine ass up in the seat <br><br>Bring that old up right out <br>Tell your friends in the back to get up right now <br>We got that new soul Two Tone is up right now <br>And I'm a Philly Philly bull so you love that sound <br>And I'mma make sure you love it <br>Damn sure you love it <br>Goddamn, get you're best to me <br>No crabs in the bucket, we all cousins <br>And we stay making history <br>No lord I know <br><br>I'm a Northeast spitter with a big sized cap and them lames ain't fucking with me <br>Got brains, got brawn, got a dog named Lewis so them dames stay fucking with me <br>I can't complain I got a mug she can love for a very long time and I'm pretty damn good in the sheets <br>I got balls so big you ain't even gotta ask get your fine ass up in the seat <br>I'm a Northeast spitter with a big sized cap and them lames ain't fucking with me <br>Got brains, got brawn, got a dog named Lewis so them dames stay fucking with me <br>I can't complain I got a mug she can love for a very long time and I'm pretty damn good in the sheets <br>I got balls so big you ain't even gotta ask get your fine ass up in the seat]]></content><category term="E-Dubble" label="E-Dubble"/><category term="One Question" label="One Question"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Golden_Ones/</id><title>E-Dubble - Golden Ones - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:47:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:47:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Golden_Ones/" title="E-Dubble - Golden Ones - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[On my way to Fishtown headed back from Ambler <br> in the system I can see they hands up <br>This could be they anthem, this could be a go to <br>Boom bat rap with a knack for a boat shoe <br>Approach you, they goat you to poach you <br>And joke you, jerk you <br>Six ways to Sunday then Monday they merk you <br>Don't buy this you should stick to yourself <br>Even dreams get hustled so be good to your health <br>All you have when the chips are low <br>An it can show, I'm back stage but I'm fit to blow <br>Top shelf when I spit my flow, be it fast or slow <br>It's two tones but I bet you know <br>I get it in like a hole in one <br>And it's been fun, but my shit's like a stolen gun <br>Hot n' dirty, sippin' some vodka early <br>Fuck rules here's the Golden One <br><br>One Never live my life like a chump does <br>That's something that I just don't like <br>Two Never bring a knife to a gun fight <br>They got guns so they probably won't fight <br>Three Always take no for an answer <br>The yes' will come in due time <br>Four Always give a nice firm handshake <br>A dead fist simply can't be ignored <br><br>Paisley tattoo on her butt cheek <br>Cheeky little lady if you ask me <br>And if you ask me 'bout them ass cheeks <br>I can verify them jawns is real <br>And if you got a problem with the BP <br>You can always come and just see me <br>I got an attitude like C3 PO meets the G called OG <br><br>Up goes Fraiser, Two Tone Rebel, misspell 'til you make it <br>Like dying Mike never thought that he could dance right <br>Then I saw the power of the rhythm of a past life <br>Figured take a few thwacks at it, I always loved third base <br>I I I I never knew about collagen, but I could always save face <br>Hey, I sit in bed and pump the breaks before I start to feel drummin' <br>Different strokes, different folks, listen to the drummin' <br>85 back beat bumpin' in the stomach <br>Got that one, two, three, four, fuck it who's comin' <br>Got that East Coast slang that's plain to see <br>I'm the two one fist spitter I'm the D U B <br>But back back then man, go ATs, be BIG, Tu P A C <br>No O P P, I was K I D, no 40 40 tub, no H O V, no M O B, no crude up love <br>The hella big fella mellow 'til they all gun bug and then it's on <br> All the boppers want they numbers in my cellular phone <br>Who can blame 'em know we're shammin' it's a hell of a tone <br>And if they meet Lewis the dog then I throw 'em a bone <br>I'm talkin' <br><br>One Never live my life like a chump does <br>That's something that I just don't like <br>Two Never bring a knife to a gun fight <br>They got guns so they probably won't fight <br>Three Always take no for an answer <br>The yes' will come in due time <br>Four Always give a nice firm handshake <br>A dead fist simply can't be ignored <br><br>Paisley tattoo on her butt cheek <br>Cheeky little lady if you ask me <br>And if you ask me 'bout them ass cheeks <br>I can verify them jawns is real <br>And if you got a problem with the BP <br>You can always come and just see me <br>I got an attitude like C3 PO meets the G called OG]]></content><category term="E-Dubble" label="E-Dubble"/><category term="Golden Ones" label="Golden Ones"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Wait/</id><title>E-Dubble - Wait - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:47:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:47:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/E-Dubble/Wait/" title="E-Dubble - Wait - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Two tone, represent, can't do with a mic and a check <br>Looks like I might be back, I might be back, I might be back <br>No doubt with that <br>Came back fresh win a house from that <br>They paid racks for that, back to back, just another nut to crack <br>E dub, they call me that, cause my first name and my surname <br>Nom de plumes are like plumes that smoke <br>In that they linger longer than the big flame <br>I've been known to do, I've been known to do <br>I've been known to do big things <br>Age 12 had 'Ready to Die' on repeat, no big change <br>I go, I go hard as fuck, good God I'm charging up <br>I'm up on Amazon like, Fuck it all these targets suck <br>I'm optimum with prime until he turns to garbage trucks <br>And dumps out, like kung pow, no turn down, just turn up <br>I got a really really big heart, I got a really really big _ <br>And when it comes to growling I don't mess around <br>With my bites as bad as my bark <br>Motherfucker I've been dope from the start <br>I start dope from the bin <br>Got a team full of FPS shooters <br>So who you think is gon' win <br>Motherfucker I <br><br>Follow them breadcrumbs <br>We leave them to teach some <br>Each one will speak without preaching to be one <br>Keep your eyes open <br>Approach each new season <br>With hope that the ghosts from our past heed our reason <br><br>Monopolize, hypothesize, I got to ride, those people died <br>Peace inside, no mix supplies, no need to weep, we feed the fire <br>Beast alive, no need to lie, just heed the fire, lead the fire <br>Y'all need the heat, y'all choose to weep <br>And y'all keep the beast in, like a pizza piea <br>I mean preach the pious, reach survivors <br>Got a four fifths lined that'll eat papyrus <br>Gonna cop a chopper so big motherfuckers can't reach me with the Zika virus <br>And this ain't a game <br>Why be a God when you can be a king <br>At least a king's a real thing <br>Bout' to take some names and then fuck the whole game up <br><br>I venture to say that my soul isn't taxed still <br>Best to not say that our future's not fragile <br>I live in this place between lithium and natural <br>Don't like the taste though <br>I won't swallow that pill <br><br>I pop pills, pills I pop, pop two pills, on stilts I walk <br>Fuckboys outlining chalk, can't fuck with the Incredible Hulk <br>The incredible GOAT, no time left being indelible vote <br>Better make the choice and when you make the choice <br>You better leave us a credible hope <br>I got sixteens for like 4k, no divorces, no wonder age <br>Rippin' verses for a fickle purpose <br>Just get to work, do what the whores say <br>Top back, no horseplay, my forte, no poor taste <br>I stay in that one spot, keep cool in fourth place <br>Motherfucker]]></content><category term="E-Dubble" label="E-Dubble"/><category term="Wait" label="Wait"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/On_The_Road/</id><title>Diealright - On The Road - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:48:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:48:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/On_The_Road/" title="Diealright - On The Road - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>Find a head <br>Find a head <br>Find a head <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>Find a head <br>Find a head <br>Find a head <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>Find a head <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>Find a head <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>Find a head <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road if I had eyes <br>On the road if I had arms <br>On the road if I had legs <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>Bye bye my bloody hands <br>Bye bye my gloomy days <br>Bye bye my lovely cats <br>Bye bye my lonely man <br>Bye bye my bloody hands <br>Bye bye my gloomy days <br>Bye bye my lovely cats <br>Bye bye my lonely man <br>Bye bye my bloody hands <br>Bye bye my gloomy days <br>Bye bye my lovely cats <br>Bye bye my lonely man <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>Find a head <br>Find a head <br>Find a head <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the road <br>On the <br>]]></content><category term="Diealright" label="Diealright"/><category term="On The Road" label="On The Road"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/F-/</id><title>Diealright - F- - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:48:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:48:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/F-/" title="Diealright - F- - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves eating dogs <br>Night lips tears <br>A chair in abyss <br>The dawn doesn't watch it <br>Who need pain <br>A bluedays cheat <br>A streets memories <br>The sun's memories <br>Wolves eating dogs <br>Night lips tears <br>A chair in abyss <br>The dawn doesn't watch it <br>Who need pain <br>A bluedays cheat <br>A streets memories <br>The sun's memories <br>Every everywhere <br>I'm here <br>you're in there <br>Every everywhere <br>I'm here <br>We're in there <br>Every everywhere <br>I'm here <br>you're in there <br>Every everywhere <br>I'm here <br>Wolves eating dogs <br>Night lips tears <br>A chair in abyss <br>The dawn doesn't watch it <br>Who need pain <br>A bluedays cheat <br>A streets memories <br>The sun's memories <br>Every everywhere <br>I'm here <br>you're in there <br>Every everywhere <br>I'm here <br>We're in there <br>Every everywhere <br>I'm here <br>you're in there <br>Every everywhere <br>I'm here <br>you're in there <br>Every everywhere <br>I'm here <br>you're in there <br>Every everywhere <br>I'm here <br>you're in there <br>Every everywhere <br>I'm here <br>you're in there <br>Every everywhere <br>I'm here <br>you're in there <br>]]></content><category term="Diealright" label="Diealright"/><category term="F-" label="F-"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/When_We/</id><title>Diealright - When We - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:48:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:48:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/When_We/" title="Diealright - When We - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When we fall <br>more and more <br>yeah into the pit <br>Prepared Vortex <br>Please kill me <br>We couldn't find medicine <br>Could not help us <br>dear you and me <br>When caught the sun <br>in my eyes <br>Then you were gone <br>in my eyes <br>When caught the sun <br>in my eyes <br>When caught the sun <br>in my eyes <br>Then you were gone <br>in my eyes <br>When caught the sun <br>in my eyes <br>]]></content><category term="Diealright" label="Diealright"/><category term="When We" label="When We"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/Garden/</id><title>Diealright - Garden - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:48:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:48:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/Garden/" title="Diealright - Garden - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I absolve you from your sin <br>Wiggle wiggle under this place <br>You will be changed <br>by the Flowery words <br>I absolve you from your sin <br>Wiggle wiggle under this place <br>You will be changed <br>by the Flowery words <br>To be made of <br>lies and lies and <br>lies and lies and lies <br>Enjoy greed <br>Dink desire <br>Have a fun time <br>Where the fake flowers bloom <br>If that is your last paradise <br>Where the fake flowers bloom <br>If that is your last paradise <br>Then you <br>Soot me or shoot you <br>or shoot them <br>Do that <br>Soot me or shoot you <br>or shoot them <br>Do that <br>Where the fake flowers bloom <br>If that is your last paradise <br>Where the fake flowers bloom <br>If that is your last paradise <br>Then you <br>Soot me or shoot you <br>or shoot them <br>Do that <br>Soot me or shoot you <br>or shoot them <br>Do that <br>Soot me or shoot you <br>or shoot them <br>Do that <br>Soot me or shoot you <br>or shoot them <br>Do <br>]]></content><category term="Diealright" label="Diealright"/><category term="Garden" label="Garden"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/Hello/</id><title>Diealright - Hello - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:48:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:48:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/Hello/" title="Diealright - Hello - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[hello I’m no name girl <br>how are you hey guys <br>my fever and my fear <br>and my feeling is for you <br>you know my name what is my name <br>I don't know who is me <br>I don't know who is me <br>hello I’m no name girl <br>hello I’m no name <br>hello I’m no name girl <br>hello I’m no name girl <br>you know my name what is my name <br>I don't know who is me <br>I don't know who is me <br>good boy good girl good boy good girl <br>hello I’m no name girl <br>how are you hey guys <br>my fever and my fear <br>and my feeling is for you <br>you know my name what is my name <br>I don't know who is me <br>I don't know who is me <br>hello I’m no name girl <br>hello I’m no name <br>hello I’m no name girl <br>hello I’m no name girl <br>you know my name what is my name <br>I don't know who is me <br>I don't know who is me <br>]]></content><category term="Diealright" label="Diealright"/><category term="Hello" label="Hello"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/URA/</id><title>Diealright - U.R.A - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:48:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:48:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/URA/" title="Diealright - U.R.A - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No means No reasons No feelings <br>like a ch <br>So what Why you crying <br>Hey sweety Shut you down <br>You are a <br>You are a deepshit <br>You are a <br>No means No reasons No feelings <br>like a ch <br>So what Why you crying <br>Hey sweety Shut you down <br>You are a <br>You are a deepshit <br>You are a <br>You are a deepshit <br>You are a <br>You are a deepshit <br>You are a <br>Take your body <br>You are a <br>You are a deepshit <br>You are a <br>You are a deepshit <br>You are a <br>You are a deepshit <br>You are a <br>]]></content><category term="Diealright" label="Diealright"/><category term="U.R.A" label="U.R.A"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/Hunt/</id><title>Diealright - Hunt - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:48:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:48:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/Hunt/" title="Diealright - Hunt - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Take a six steps <br>And Make a stand <br>Look around there <br>I'll immerse your head <br>But Don't worry about that <br>It's my endearment <br>It Just like you <br>Hey huntsman <br>Take a six steps <br>And Make a stand <br>Look around there <br>I'll immerse your head <br>But Don't worry about that <br>It's my endearment <br>It Just like you <br>Hey huntsman <br>Desire another a New target <br>I'll get you I'll get you <br>Take a six steps <br>And Make a stand <br>Look around there <br>I'll immerse your head <br>]]></content><category term="Diealright" label="Diealright"/><category term="Hunt" label="Hunt"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/Satellite/</id><title>Diealright - Satellite - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:48:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:48:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/Satellite/" title="Diealright - Satellite - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[heart dry always thirst <br>who anyone anytime thirst <br>lonely rolling day and night <br>night night night night <br>heart dry always thirst <br>who anyone anytime thirst <br>lonely rolling day and night <br>night night night night <br>heart dry always thirst <br>who anyone anytime thirst <br>lonely rolling day and night <br>night night night night <br>round and round and <br>round and round and <br>round and round and <br>round and i'm always <br>round and round and <br>round and round and <br>round and round and <br>round and i'm always <br>heart dry always thirst <br>who anyone anytime thirst <br>lonely rolling day and night <br>night night night night <br>heart dry always thirst <br>who anyone anytime thirst <br>lonely rolling day and night <br>night night night night <br>round and round and <br>round and round and <br>round and round and <br>round and i'm always <br>round and round and <br>round and round and <br>round and round and <br>round and i'm always <br>round and round and <br>round and round and <br>round and round and <br>round and i'm always <br>round and round and <br>round and round and <br>round and round and <br>round and i'm always <br>]]></content><category term="Diealright" label="Diealright"/><category term="Satellite" label="Satellite"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/Johnny/</id><title>Diealright - Johnny - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:48:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:48:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/Johnny/" title="Diealright - Johnny - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Can you hear me <br>Can you see me <br>Hide and hide and dive <br>I'm a dark sea fish <br>Look at honey <br>look at honey <br>The messy emotions <br>and bomb <br>Be with you <br>Look at honey <br>look at honey <br>The messy emotions <br>and bomb <br>Be with you <br>Deep Sea fish <br>It's Johnny <br>Deep Sea fish <br>It's Johnny <br>Look at honey <br>look at honey <br>Look at honey <br>look at honey <br>Deep Sea fish <br>It's Johnny <br>Deep Sea fish <br>It's Johnny <br>]]></content><category term="Diealright" label="Diealright"/><category term="Johnny" label="Johnny"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/Heaven/</id><title>Diealright - Heaven - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:48:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:48:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diealright/Heaven/" title="Diealright - Heaven - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[give me an apple <br>what the pass next <br>give me a gold <br>show me your heart <br>fuck you liar get out <br>give me give me fuck <br>i don’t need all hey <br>screw that give me <br>some new baby <br>screw that show me <br>your heaven <br>screw that give me <br>some new baby <br>screw that show me <br>your heaven <br>give me an apple <br>what the pass next <br>give me a gold <br>show me your heart <br>fuck you liar get out <br>give me give me fuck <br>i don’t need all hey <br>screw that give me <br>some new baby <br>screw that show me <br>your heaven <br>screw that give me <br>some new baby <br>screw that show me <br>your heaven <br>i want spirit <br>i want spirit <br>i want spirit <br>i want spirit <br>Where what does it mean <br>no no no no nothing <br>Well What is your name <br>Where what does it mean <br>no no no no nothing <br>Well What is your name <br>give me an apple <br>what the pass next <br>give me a gold <br>show me your heart <br>fuck you liar get out <br>give me give me fuck <br>i don’t need all hey <br>i want spirit <br>i want spirit <br>i want spirit <br>i want spirit <br>Where what does it mean <br>no no no no nothing <br>Well What is your name <br>]]></content><category term="Diealright" label="Diealright"/><category term="Heaven" label="Heaven"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박현성/고고고_MR/</id><title>박현성 - 고고고 (MR) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:49:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:49:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%98%84%EC%84%B1/%EA%B3%A0%EA%B3%A0%EA%B3%A0_MR/" title="박현성 - 고고고 (MR) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한 발짝 한 발짝 뛰어 <br>뻘같은 저 세상속에 <br>되돌릴 수 없는 길이라고 해도 <br>봄 여름 가을 겨울 <br>거칠게 다가오는 <br>시련의 파도를 넘어넘어봐 <br>고고고고 달려봐 <br>저거친 바람속으로 <br>두려움도 다 떨쳐버리고 <br>고고고고 달려봐 <br>불타는 용광로처럼 <br>활화산 처럼 활활 타올라봐 <br>사랑하는 사람을 위해 <br>내 모든걸 아낌없이 바쳐봐 <br>힘이 들어서 휘청거려도 <br>울다 웃다 지칠지라도 <br>고고고고 달려봐 <br>저거친 바람속으로 <br>두려움도 다 떨쳐버리고 <br>고고고고 달려봐 <br>불타는 용광로처럼 <br>활화산 처럼 활활 타올라봐 <br>사랑하는 사람을 위해 <br>내 모든걸 아낌없이 바쳐봐 <br>힘이 들어서 휘청거려도 <br>울다 웃다 지칠지라도 <br>울다 웃다 지칠지라도 <br>]]></content><category term="박현성" label="박현성"/><category term="고고고 (MR)" label="고고고 (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박현성/찾아주세요_MR/</id><title>박현성 - 찾아주세요 (MR) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:49:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:49:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%98%84%EC%84%B1/%EC%B0%BE%EC%95%84%EC%A3%BC%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94_MR/" title="박현성 - 찾아주세요 (MR) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑이란 다 그런 거라 <br>남들은 말을 하지만 <br>그런사랑도 하지못한 나 <br>내가내가 너무너무 싫어요 <br>내 사랑을 찾아 주세요 <br>사랑 할 사람 없나요 <br>다시한번 두손모아 기도할께요 <br>내 사랑을 꼭 찾아주세요 <br>사랑이란 다 그런 거라 <br>남들은 말을 하지만 <br>그런사랑도 하지못한 나 <br>내가내가 너무너무 미워요 <br>내 사랑을 찾아 주세요 <br>사랑 할 사람 없나요 <br>다시한번 무릎꿇고 기도할께요 <br>내 사랑을 꼭 찾아주세요 <br>내 사랑을 찾아 주세요 <br>사랑 할 사람 없나요 <br>다시한번 두손모아 기도할께요 <br>내 사랑을 꼭 찾아주세요 <br>내 사랑을 꼭 찾아주세요 <br>]]></content><category term="박현성" label="박현성"/><category term="찾아주세요 (MR)" label="찾아주세요 (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박현성/남자의하루_MR/</id><title>박현성 - 남자의하루 (MR) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:49:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:49:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%98%84%EC%84%B1/%EB%82%A8%EC%9E%90%EC%9D%98%ED%95%98%EB%A3%A8_MR/" title="박현성 - 남자의하루 (MR) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[해 보다 먼저 일어나 하루를 열고 <br>별보다 이 몸 늦게 누이며 <br>청춘을 생각 했었지 <br>인생 뭐 별거 있냐고 <br>마음먹기 달렸지 <br>꿈은 이루라고 꾸는거야 <br>오늘도 나를 달래네 <br>하지만 꼭 한가지 <br>잊으면 안되는게 있어 <br>사랑은 미루지마 <br>추억도 가져가야지 <br>인생도 사랑도 바로 바로 내꺼야 <br>오늘도 긴 하룰 살았어 <br>멋진 내 인생의 페이지 <br>인생 뭐 별거 있냐고 <br>마음먹기 달렸지 <br>꿈은 이루라고 꾸는거야 <br>오늘도 나를 달래네 <br>하지만 꼭 한가지 <br>잊으면 안되는게 있어 <br>사랑은 미루지마 <br>추억도 가져가야지 <br>인생도 사랑도 바로 바로 내꺼야 <br>오늘도 긴 하룰 살았어 <br>멋진 내 인생의 페이지 <br>오늘도 긴 하룰 살았어 <br>멋진 남자의 하루를 <br>]]></content><category term="박현성" label="박현성"/><category term="남자의하루 (MR)" label="남자의하루 (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박현성/예쁜그대_MR/</id><title>박현성 - 예쁜그대 (MR) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:49:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:49:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%98%84%EC%84%B1/%EC%98%88%EC%81%9C%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80_MR/" title="박현성 - 예쁜그대 (MR) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[예쁜 그대 그대만 보면 <br>내 가슴 두근두근 <br>그 눈빛에 퐁당 빠져 <br>하루종일 일도 안돼 <br>귀여운 그대 그대만 보면 <br>내 눈은 빙글 빙글 <br>그 입술에 흠뻑젖어 <br>하루종일 그대 생각뿐 <br>내 마음 하늘을 날아가네 <br>새처럼 구름처럼 <br>세월이 흘러도 변치않을 <br>나는 당신의 남자 <br>영원히 사랑해요 <br>내 곁에만 있어줘요 <br>예쁜 그대 그대만 보면 <br>내 가슴 두근두근 <br>그 눈빛에 퐁당 빠져 <br>하루종일 일도 안돼 <br>귀여운 그대 그대만 보면 <br>내 눈은 빙글 빙글 <br>그 입술에 흠뻑젖어 <br>하루종일 그대 생각뿐 <br>내 마음 하늘을 날아가네 <br>꽃처럼 바람처럼 <br>세월이 흘러도 변치않을 <br>나는 당신의 남자 <br>영원히 사랑해요 <br>내 곁에만 있어줘요 <br>당신을 사랑해요 <br>내 곁에만 있어줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="박현성" label="박현성"/><category term="예쁜그대 (MR)" label="예쁜그대 (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박현성/노래한곡_MR/</id><title>박현성 - 노래한곡 (MR) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:49:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:49:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%98%84%EC%84%B1/%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98%ED%95%9C%EA%B3%A1_MR/" title="박현성 - 노래한곡 (MR) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[인생은 오르막 길 <br>덜커덕 완행 열차지 <br>남들은 쉽게쉽게 <br>달려 가는데 <br>내인생은 제자리 뱅뱅 <br>돈도 없고 빽도 없지만 <br>마음둘곳 하나 있지요 <br>한숨이 터져 나오고 <br>뜨거운 눈물 삼킬때 <br>불러봐요 목터지게 <br>쿵짝쿵짝짝 <br>흐느끼듯 불러봐요 <br>노래 한곡조 <br>마음을 달래 주는 <br>노래한곡 불러봅시다 <br>인생은 오르막 길 <br>덜커덕 완행 열차지 <br>남들은 쉽게쉽게 <br>달려 가는데 <br>내인생은 제자리 뱅뱅 <br>돈도 없고 빽도 없지만 <br>마음둘곳 하나 있지요 <br>한숨이 터져 나오고 <br>뜨거운 눈물 삼킬때 <br>불러봐요 목터지게 <br>쿵짝쿵짝짝 <br>흐느끼듯 불러봐요 <br>노래 한곡조 <br>마음을 달래 주는 <br>노래한곡 불러봅시다 <br>돈도 없고 빽도 없지만 <br>마음둘곳 하나 있지요 <br>한숨이 터져 나오고 <br>뜨거운 눈물 삼킬때 <br>불러봐요 목터지게 <br>쿵짝쿵짝짝 <br>흐느끼듯 불러봐요 <br>노래 한곡조 <br>마음을 달래 주는 <br>노래한곡 불러봅시다 <br>노래한곡 불러봅시다 <br>]]></content><category term="박현성" label="박현성"/><category term="노래한곡 (MR)" label="노래한곡 (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박현성/고고고/</id><title>박현성 - 고고고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:49:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:49:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%98%84%EC%84%B1/%EA%B3%A0%EA%B3%A0%EA%B3%A0/" title="박현성 - 고고고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한 발짝 한 발짝 뛰어 <br>뻘같은 저 세상속에 <br>되돌릴 수 없는 길이라고 해도 <br>봄 여름 가을 겨울 <br>거칠게 다가오는 <br>시련의 파도를 넘어넘어봐 <br>고고고고 달려봐 <br>저거친 바람속으로 <br>두려움도 다 떨쳐버리고 <br>고고고고 달려봐 <br>불타는 용광로처럼 <br>활화산 처럼 활활 타올라봐 <br>사랑하는 사람을 위해 <br>내 모든걸 아낌없이 바쳐봐 <br>힘이 들어서 휘청거려도 <br>울다 웃다 지칠지라도 <br>고고고고 달려봐 <br>저거친 바람속으로 <br>두려움도 다 떨쳐버리고 <br>고고고고 달려봐 <br>불타는 용광로처럼 <br>활화산 처럼 활활 타올라봐 <br>사랑하는 사람을 위해 <br>내 모든걸 아낌없이 바쳐봐 <br>힘이 들어서 휘청거려도 <br>울다 웃다 지칠지라도 <br>울다 웃다 지칠지라도 <br>]]></content><category term="박현성" label="박현성"/><category term="고고고" label="고고고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박현성/찾아주세요/</id><title>박현성 - 찾아주세요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:49:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:49:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%98%84%EC%84%B1/%EC%B0%BE%EC%95%84%EC%A3%BC%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94/" title="박현성 - 찾아주세요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑이란 다 그런 거라 <br>남들은 말을 하지만 <br>그런사랑도 하지못한 나 <br>내가내가 너무너무 싫어요 <br>내 사랑을 찾아 주세요 <br>사랑 할 사람 없나요 <br>다시한번 두손모아 기도할께요 <br>내 사랑을 꼭 찾아주세요 <br>사랑이란 다 그런 거라 <br>남들은 말을 하지만 <br>그런사랑도 하지못한 나 <br>내가내가 너무너무 미워요 <br>내 사랑을 찾아 주세요 <br>사랑 할 사람 없나요 <br>다시한번 무릎꿇고 기도할께요 <br>내 사랑을 꼭 찾아주세요 <br>내 사랑을 찾아 주세요 <br>사랑 할 사람 없나요 <br>다시한번 두손모아 기도할께요 <br>내 사랑을 꼭 찾아주세요 <br>내 사랑을 꼭 찾아주세요 <br>]]></content><category term="박현성" label="박현성"/><category term="찾아주세요" label="찾아주세요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박현성/남자의하루/</id><title>박현성 - 남자의하루 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:49:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:49:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%98%84%EC%84%B1/%EB%82%A8%EC%9E%90%EC%9D%98%ED%95%98%EB%A3%A8/" title="박현성 - 남자의하루 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[해 보다 먼저 일어나 하루를 열고 <br>별보다 이 몸 늦게 누이며 <br>청춘을 생각 했었지 <br>인생 뭐 별거 있냐고 <br>마음먹기 달렸지 <br>꿈은 이루라고 꾸는거야 <br>오늘도 나를 달래네 <br>하지만 꼭 한가지 <br>잊으면 안되는게 있어 <br>사랑은 미루지마 <br>추억도 가져가야지 <br>인생도 사랑도 바로 바로 내꺼야 <br>오늘도 긴 하룰 살았어 <br>멋진 내 인생의 페이지 <br>인생 뭐 별거 있냐고 <br>마음먹기 달렸지 <br>꿈은 이루라고 꾸는거야 <br>오늘도 나를 달래네 <br>하지만 꼭 한가지 <br>잊으면 안되는게 있어 <br>사랑은 미루지마 <br>추억도 가져가야지 <br>인생도 사랑도 바로 바로 내꺼야 <br>오늘도 긴 하룰 살았어 <br>멋진 내 인생의 페이지 <br>오늘도 긴 하룰 살았어 <br>멋진 남자의 하루를 <br>]]></content><category term="박현성" label="박현성"/><category term="남자의하루" label="남자의하루"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박현성/예쁜그대/</id><title>박현성 - 예쁜그대 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:49:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:49:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%98%84%EC%84%B1/%EC%98%88%EC%81%9C%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80/" title="박현성 - 예쁜그대 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[예쁜 그대 그대만 보면 <br>내 가슴 두근두근 <br>그 눈빛에 퐁당 빠져 <br>하루종일 일도 안돼 <br>귀여운 그대 그대만 보면 <br>내 눈은 빙글 빙글 <br>그 입술에 흠뻑젖어 <br>하루종일 그대 생각뿐 <br>내 마음 하늘을 날아가네 <br>새처럼 구름처럼 <br>세월이 흘러도 변치않을 <br>나는 당신의 남자 <br>영원히 사랑해요 <br>내 곁에만 있어줘요 <br>예쁜 그대 그대만 보면 <br>내 가슴 두근두근 <br>그 눈빛에 퐁당 빠져 <br>하루종일 일도 안돼 <br>귀여운 그대 그대만 보면 <br>내 눈은 빙글 빙글 <br>그 입술에 흠뻑젖어 <br>하루종일 그대 생각뿐 <br>내 마음 하늘을 날아가네 <br>꽃처럼 바람처럼 <br>세월이 흘러도 변치않을 <br>나는 당신의 남자 <br>영원히 사랑해요 <br>내 곁에만 있어줘요 <br>당신을 사랑해요 <br>내 곁에만 있어줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="박현성" label="박현성"/><category term="예쁜그대" label="예쁜그대"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박현성/노래한곡/</id><title>박현성 - 노래한곡 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:49:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:49:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%98%84%EC%84%B1/%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98%ED%95%9C%EA%B3%A1/" title="박현성 - 노래한곡 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[인생은 오르막 길 <br>덜커덕 완행 열차지 <br>남들은 쉽게쉽게 <br>달려 가는데 <br>내인생은 제자리 뱅뱅 <br>돈도 없고 빽도 없지만 <br>마음둘곳 하나 있지요 <br>한숨이 터져 나오고 <br>뜨거운 눈물 삼킬때 <br>불러봐요 목터지게 <br>쿵짝쿵짝짝 <br>흐느끼듯 불러봐요 <br>노래 한곡조 <br>마음을 달래 주는 <br>노래한곡 불러봅시다 <br>인생은 오르막 길 <br>덜커덕 완행 열차지 <br>남들은 쉽게쉽게 <br>달려 가는데 <br>내인생은 제자리 뱅뱅 <br>돈도 없고 빽도 없지만 <br>마음둘곳 하나 있지요 <br>한숨이 터져 나오고 <br>뜨거운 눈물 삼킬때 <br>불러봐요 목터지게 <br>쿵짝쿵짝짝 <br>흐느끼듯 불러봐요 <br>노래 한곡조 <br>마음을 달래 주는 <br>노래한곡 불러봅시다 <br>돈도 없고 빽도 없지만 <br>마음둘곳 하나 있지요 <br>한숨이 터져 나오고 <br>뜨거운 눈물 삼킬때 <br>불러봐요 목터지게 <br>쿵짝쿵짝짝 <br>흐느끼듯 불러봐요 <br>노래 한곡조 <br>마음을 달래 주는 <br>노래한곡 불러봅시다 <br>노래한곡 불러봅시다 <br>]]></content><category term="박현성" label="박현성"/><category term="노래한곡" label="노래한곡"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/인젝/고스트_Ghost/</id><title>인젝 - 고스트 (Ghost) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:49:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:49:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B8%EC%A0%9D/%EA%B3%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8_Ghost/" title="인젝 - 고스트 (Ghost) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Rap하라 했는데 간지부려 <br>내게 물어 Rap이나하지 <br>왜 간지부려 <br>나도 몰라 신이 있음 <br>아마 나를 갖고놀아 <br>이런 말장난 Hash tag 걸린 일상야 <br>야 점심때야 야 <br>정신차려야 야 할때야 아 <br>몸뚱인 하난데 영혼은 두개 Ghost <br>해는 내게 해가 돼 <br>Fucking 나는 골 때려 <br>원한다면 Call 때려 <br>내가 글로 찾아갈게 곧 봬요 <br>얼굴로 예술하네 <br>술에 손도 안댔는데 <br>그대 입술 취해 여기까지 Keep해요 <br>밤이 되면 내가 아냐 <br>내가 나올테니 조심 <br>날이 밝아 질때까지 Going <br>이밤에 Hip-Hop에 <br>미쳐버릴거야 너도 나도 <br>Inject의 Fucking rapping주입 aim <br>I'm a go go go go ghost <br>I'm a go go go go ghost <br>맞어 Don don don don don't stop <br>느낌대로 Track을 <br>찢을거야 마치 Monster <br>I'm a go go go go ghost <br>I'm a go go go go ghost <br>맞어 Don don don don don't stop <br>느낌대로 Track을 <br>찢을거야 마치 Monster <br>나를 알어 I'm a sc의 Ghost <br>안가려 장르 난 호러계의 Most <br>일도 양보 할수없어 일도양단 A <br>이도 저도 못함 넌 내게 쎄게 베임 <br>천원돌파해 빌딩에서 우주까지 <br>그러면 남녀노소까지 수긍하지 <br>R A P 나만의 색깔 찾아 삼만리 <br>다녀오니 Respect이 늘어났지 <br>inject 좀 쩔어 누가봐도 <br>Swag 좀 쩔어 <br>Hustle 하다보면 언젠가는 <br>돈 벌어 더 쩔어 <br>더 털어 Hip-Hop에 열정부어 <br>부릉 시동걸어 훗날 이건 Word up <br>그러면 다음 새 시대에 <br>내 이름 하나 새겨 <br>누구나 다 기억해 <br>나이를 먹어도 말이여 <br>호불호 갈리는 목소리 안변해 I'm sorry <br>대신에 쏴줄게 Bang <br>I'm a go go go go ghost <br>I'm a go go go go ghost <br>맞어 Don don don don don't stop <br>느낌대로 Track을 <br>찢을거야 마치 Monster <br>I'm a go go go go ghost <br>I'm a go go go go ghost <br>맞어 Don don don don don't stop <br>느낌대로 Track을 <br>찢을거야 마치 Monster <br>I'm a go go go go ghost <br>I'm a go go go go ghost <br>맞어 Don don don don don't stop <br>느낌대로 Track을 <br>찢을거야 마치 Monster <br>I'm a go go go go ghost <br>I'm a go go go go ghost <br>맞어 Don don don don don't stop <br>느낌대로 Track을 <br>찢을거야 마치 Monster <br>]]></content><category term="인젝" label="인젝"/><category term="고스트 (Ghost)" label="고스트 (Ghost)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/뉴에덴워십_Neweden_Worship/성령이여_우리게_오셔서_Inst/</id><title>뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship) - 성령이여 우리게 오셔서 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:52:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:52:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%89%B4%EC%97%90%EB%8D%B4%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD_Neweden_Worship/%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9%EC%9D%B4%EC%97%AC_%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EA%B2%8C_%EC%98%A4%EC%85%94%EC%84%9C_Inst/" title="뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship) - 성령이여 우리게 오셔서 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>말씀으로 회복케 하소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>하나 되는 기쁨을 주소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>말씀으로 회복케 하소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>하나 되는 기쁨을 주소서 <br>날마다 주시는 주님의 은혜 <br>날마다 주시는 하늘의 소망 <br>날마다 주시는 주안에 <br>기쁨 주님의 사랑 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>말씀으로 회복케 하소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>하나 되는 기쁨을 주소서 <br>날마다 주시는 주님의 은혜 <br>날마다 주시는 하늘의 소망 <br>날마다 주시는 주안에 <br>기쁨 주님의 사랑 <br>성령의 불로 나를 태워 주소서 <br>예수의 이름을 선포케 하소서 <br>성령의 불로 우릴 태워 주소서 <br>성령의 불로 나를 태워 주소서 <br>예수의 이름을 선포케 하소서 <br>성령의 불로 우릴 태워 주소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>말씀으로 회복케 하소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>하나 되는 기쁨을 주소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>말씀으로 회복케 하소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>하나 되는 기쁨을 주소서 <br>성령의 불로 나를 태워 주소서 <br>예수의 이름을 선포케 하소서 <br>성령의 불로 우릴 태워 주소서 <br>성령의 불로 나를 태워 주소서 <br>예수의 이름을 선포케 하소서 <br>성령의 불로 우릴 태워 주소서 <br>성령의 불로 나를 태워 주소서 <br>예수의 이름을 선포케 하소서 <br>성령의 불로 우릴 태워 주소서 <br>]]></content><category term="뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship)" label="뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship)"/><category term="성령이여 우리게 오셔서 (Inst.)" label="성령이여 우리게 오셔서 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/뉴에덴워십_Neweden_Worship/주님께_영광_Glory_To_Our_God_Inst/</id><title>뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship) - 주님께 영광 (Glory To Our God) (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:52:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:52:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%89%B4%EC%97%90%EB%8D%B4%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD_Neweden_Worship/%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98%EA%BB%98_%EC%98%81%EA%B4%91_Glory_To_Our_God_Inst/" title="뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship) - 주님께 영광 (Glory To Our God) (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One hundred and fifty three fish <br>주 향한 순종의 열매 <br>One hundred and fifty three fish <br>주님의 놀라운 기적 <br>사람을 낚는 어부 되리라 <br>그 말씀 내게 이뤄 주소서 <br>작은 순종을 기뻐 받으사 <br>한 영혼 주님 알게하소서 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>Glory to our God <br>One hundred and fifty three fish <br>주 향한 순종의 열매 <br>One hundred and fifty three fish <br>주님의 놀라운 기적 <br>사람을 낚는 어부 되리라 <br>그 말씀 내게 이뤄 주소서 <br>작은 순종을 기뻐 받으사 <br>한 영혼 주님 알게하소서 <br>사람을 낚는 어부 되리라 <br>그 말씀 내게 이뤄 주소서 <br>작은 순종을 기뻐 받으사 <br>한 영혼 주님 알게하소서 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>Glory to our God <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>Glory to our God <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>Glory to our God <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>Glory to our God <br>]]></content><category term="뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship)" label="뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship)"/><category term="주님께 영광 (Glory To Our God) (Inst.)" label="주님께 영광 (Glory To Our God) (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/뉴에덴워십_Neweden_Worship/성령이여_우리게_오셔서/</id><title>뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship) - 성령이여 우리게 오셔서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:52:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:52:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%89%B4%EC%97%90%EB%8D%B4%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD_Neweden_Worship/%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9%EC%9D%B4%EC%97%AC_%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EA%B2%8C_%EC%98%A4%EC%85%94%EC%84%9C/" title="뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship) - 성령이여 우리게 오셔서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>말씀으로 회복케 하소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>하나 되는 기쁨을 주소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>말씀으로 회복케 하소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>하나 되는 기쁨을 주소서 <br>날마다 주시는 주님의 은혜 <br>날마다 주시는 하늘의 소망 <br>날마다 주시는 주안에 <br>기쁨 주님의 사랑 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>말씀으로 회복케 하소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>하나 되는 기쁨을 주소서 <br>날마다 주시는 주님의 은혜 <br>날마다 주시는 하늘의 소망 <br>날마다 주시는 주안에 <br>기쁨 주님의 사랑 <br>성령의 불로 나를 태워 주소서 <br>예수의 이름을 선포케 하소서 <br>성령의 불로 우릴 태워 주소서 <br>성령의 불로 나를 태워 주소서 <br>예수의 이름을 선포케 하소서 <br>성령의 불로 우릴 태워 주소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>말씀으로 회복케 하소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>하나 되는 기쁨을 주소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>말씀으로 회복케 하소서 <br>성령이여 우리게 오셔서 <br>하나 되는 기쁨을 주소서 <br>성령의 불로 나를 태워 주소서 <br>예수의 이름을 선포케 하소서 <br>성령의 불로 우릴 태워 주소서 <br>성령의 불로 나를 태워 주소서 <br>예수의 이름을 선포케 하소서 <br>성령의 불로 우릴 태워 주소서 <br>성령의 불로 나를 태워 주소서 <br>예수의 이름을 선포케 하소서 <br>성령의 불로 우릴 태워 주소서 <br>]]></content><category term="뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship)" label="뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship)"/><category term="성령이여 우리게 오셔서" label="성령이여 우리게 오셔서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/뉴에덴워십_Neweden_Worship/주님께_영광_Glory_To_Our_God/</id><title>뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship) - 주님께 영광 (Glory To Our God) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:52:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:52:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%89%B4%EC%97%90%EB%8D%B4%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD_Neweden_Worship/%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98%EA%BB%98_%EC%98%81%EA%B4%91_Glory_To_Our_God/" title="뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship) - 주님께 영광 (Glory To Our God) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One hundred and fifty three fish <br>주 향한 순종의 열매 <br>One hundred and fifty three fish <br>주님의 놀라운 기적 <br>사람을 낚는 어부 되리라 <br>그 말씀 내게 이뤄 주소서 <br>작은 순종을 기뻐 받으사 <br>한 영혼 주님 알게하소서 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>Glory to our God <br>One hundred and fifty three fish <br>주 향한 순종의 열매 <br>One hundred and fifty three fish <br>주님의 놀라운 기적 <br>사람을 낚는 어부 되리라 <br>그 말씀 내게 이뤄 주소서 <br>작은 순종을 기뻐 받으사 <br>한 영혼 주님 알게하소서 <br>사람을 낚는 어부 되리라 <br>그 말씀 내게 이뤄 주소서 <br>작은 순종을 기뻐 받으사 <br>한 영혼 주님 알게하소서 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>Glory to our God <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>Glory to our God <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>Glory to our God <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>주님께 영광 <br>Glory to our God <br>]]></content><category term="뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship)" label="뉴에덴워십 (Neweden Worship)"/><category term="주님께 영광 (Glory To Our God)" label="주님께 영광 (Glory To Our God)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이끼/요즘_우리/</id><title>이끼 - 요즘 우리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:52:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:52:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%81%BC/%EC%9A%94%EC%A6%98_%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC/" title="이끼 - 요즘 우리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 우리 사이 예전 같지 않아 <br>지금의 내 마음이 <br>변했다는 건 아니야 <br>지난 우리 처음 설레임을 <br>느끼고 싶을뿐야 <br>길을 걷다 스친 우리의 두 손 <br>우리 가벼운 뽀뽀에도 <br>멎을 것만 같던 내 심장 <br>우연히 마주친 너의 눈빛 <br>웃는 얼굴도 그랬어 <br>서로가 서로에게 <br>익숙해졌다는 건 <br>그 만큼 편해졌단 것 <br>그게 나쁘단 건 아냐 <br>서로에게 중요한게 무엇인지 <br>잊지 말자 알겠지 <br>설레임을 안고 갔던 첫 여행 <br>떨리던 마음에 잠도 못 이뤘었지 <br>함께 잡고 있던 우리 두 손 <br>네 손길도 그랬어 <br>서로가 서로에게 <br>익숙해졌다는 건 <br>그 만큼 편해졌단 것 <br>그게 나쁘단 건 아냐 <br>서로에게 중요한게 무엇인지 <br>잊지 말자 <br>우리가 함께 했던 오랜 시간들 <br>내게는 너무 소중해 <br>힘든 일이 있더라도 <br>함께 이겨내며 우리 변치말자 <br>잊지 말자 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="이끼" label="이끼"/><category term="요즘 우리" label="요즘 우리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헌제식당/가을이_끝나갈_무렵/</id><title>헌제식당 - 가을이 끝나갈 무렵 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T22:54:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T22:54:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%8C%EC%A0%9C%EC%8B%9D%EB%8B%B9/%EA%B0%80%EC%9D%84%EC%9D%B4_%EB%81%9D%EB%82%98%EA%B0%88_%EB%AC%B4%EB%A0%B5/" title="헌제식당 - 가을이 끝나갈 무렵 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[온지도 얼마 안됐는데 <br>벌써 가는구나 <br>가슴속에 있는 모든 짐을 <br>내려놓듯이 <br>지는 가을 석양에 <br>슬퍼 우는 귀뚜라미 <br>가을햇살에 몸을 비비는 도토리 <br>감나무에 떨어진 아침이슬은 <br>감빛에 담겨서 빨강 물방울 <br>어찌하나요 가을이 가려 하네요 <br>사각사각 가을바람 소리에 <br>한없이 떨어져버린 낙엽들이 <br>내발을 멈추게 하네요 <br>가을아 가려거든 <br>내 가슴에 가을향기 <br>가득 채우고 가려무나 <br>휑한 벌판에 홀로 남은 허수아비 <br>겨울 맞을 준비 한창인 다람쥐 <br>은행나무 밑으로 흐르는 냇물 <br>은행잎이 담겨서 노랑 시냇물 <br>어찌하나요 가을이 가려 하네요 <br>사각사각 가을바람 소리에 <br>한없이 떨어져버린 낙엽들이 <br>내발을 멈추게 하네요 <br>가을아 가려거든 <br>내 가슴에 가을향기 <br>가득 채우고 가려무나 <br>어찌하나요 가을이 가려 하네요 <br>사각사각 가을바람 소리에 <br>한없이 떨어져버린 낙엽들이 <br>내발을 멈추게 하네요 <br>가을아 가려거든 <br>내 가슴에 가을향기 <br>가득 채우고 가려무나 <br>가득 채우고 가려무나 <br>가득 채우고 가려무나 <br>]]></content><category term="헌제식당" label="헌제식당"/><category term="가을이 끝나갈 무렵" label="가을이 끝나갈 무렵"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gulddreng/Nemt/</id><title>Gulddreng - Nemt - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:04:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:04:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gulddreng/Nemt/" title="Gulddreng - Nemt - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Noget som jeg ikk' forstar <br>Alle si'r det er sa hardt <br>Der' noget som jeg ikk' forstar <br>Fortael mig hvorfor det er hardt <br><br>Jeg laener mig tilbage <br>Spo'r hva' du ska' i dag <br>Jeg gi'r dig nyt toj uh ja <br>Sa du ka' ta' det gamle af <br>Jeg har Versace Versace <br>Du har HandM <br>Hva' med Versace <br>Taske fra Chanel <br><br>Troede ikk' det var sa nemt <br>Nemt at vaere kendt <br>Det er det <br>For hele verden elsker mig <br>Troede ikk' det var sa nemt <br>Nemt at vaere kendt <br>Baby, det er det <br>For hele verden elsker mig <br>Uh ja, uh ja, uh ja <br>Uh ja, uh ja, uh ja <br>For hele verden elsker mig <br><br>Gor mig ingenting at det er hardt <br>Det sagde hun faktisk ogs' i gar <br>Alle si'r det er sa slemt <br>For mig er alting fucking nemt <br><br>Jeg laener mig tilbage <br>Ka' hore de andre klage <br>Tag det nu rolex <br>Jeg ska' nok betale <br>Jeg har det luksus det luksus <br>Du har tommermaend <br>Jeg har en sod hund en sod hund <br>Vil du med mig hjem <br><br>Troede ikk' det var sa nemt <br>Nemt at vaere kendt <br>Det er det <br>For hele verden elsker mig <br>Troede ikk' det var sa nemt <br>Nemt at vaere kendt <br>Baby, det er det <br>For hele verden elsker mig <br>Uh ja, uh ja, uh ja <br>Uh ja, uh ja, uh ja <br>For hele verden elsker mig <br>Uh ja, uh ja, uh ja <br>Uh ja, uh ja, uh ja <br>For hele verden elsker mig <br><br>Det er sa nemt for mig <br>Hele verden elsker mig <br>Fordi jeg er sa rig <br>Hver gang gar Gulddreng platin <br>Og du er sa nem for mig <br>Og jeg ved du elsker mig <br>Og hva' de sa end si'r <br>Skinner Gulddreng bar' lidt mer' <br><br>Troede ikk' det var sa nemt ah <br>Nemt at vaere kendt <br>Det er det <br>For hele verden elsker mig uh ja <br>Troede ikk' det var sa nemt ah <br>Nemt at vaere kendt <br>Baby, det er det det er det <br>For hele verden elsker mig <br><br>Ja det' sa nemt <br>Nemt, nemt, nemt, nemt <br>Baby du' sa nem <br>Nem, nem, nem, nem, nem <br>Ja det' sa nemt <br>Nemt, nemt, nemt, nemt <br>Baby du' sa nem <br>Nem, nem, nem, nem, nem <br>Uh ja, uh ja, uh ja <br>Uh ja, uh ja, uh ja <br>For hele verden elsker mig]]></content><category term="Gulddreng" label="Gulddreng"/><category term="Nemt" label="Nemt"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Tap_Dancin_On_A_Tightrope_Bonus_Track/</id><title>Crobot - Tap Dancin` On A Tightrope (Bonus Track) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:04:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:04:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Tap_Dancin_On_A_Tightrope_Bonus_Track/" title="Crobot - Tap Dancin` On A Tightrope (Bonus Track) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tap Dancin' on a Tightrope <br><br>They all say, live your dreams, kid and they're the first to kick me out the door <br>If I don't bring home that paycheck, the world won't be my friend <br>Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no <br><br>Take your time to hurry up now <br>Pretty soon your life will be a death <br>Do your own thing <br>Fuck what they think <br>I'm just trying to get mine, too <br><br>I'm tap dancin' on <br>I'm tap dancin on a tightrope <br>I'm tap dancin on a tightrope <br><br>The world spins around a dollar sign and everyone's trying to buy the sun <br>Put a price tag on the people <br>Known by a number not a name <br>Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no <br><br>Take your time to hurry up now <br>Pretty soon your life will be a death <br>Do your own thing <br>Fuck what they think <br>I'm just trying to get mine, too <br>Get mine, too <br><br>I'm tap dancin' on <br>I'm tap dancin on a tightrope <br>I'm tap dancin on a tightrope <br><br>Livin' once and I'm doing it for me <br>I don't have time for misery <br>Livin' my life how I choose to be <br>Livin' once and I'm doing it for me <br>I don't have time for misery <br>Livin' my life how I choose to be <br><br>I'm tap dancin' on <br>I'm tap dancin on a tightrope <br>I'm tap dancin on a tightrope]]></content><category term="Crobot" label="Crobot"/><category term="Tap Dancin` On A Tightrope (Bonus Track)" label="Tap Dancin` On A Tightrope (Bonus Track)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Queen_Of_The_Light/</id><title>Crobot - Queen Of The Light - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:04:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:04:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Queen_Of_The_Light/" title="Crobot - Queen Of The Light - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Queen of the Light <br><br>She has the keys to under Earth <br>Her only wish, a holy rebirth <br>All dressed in the darkness <br>But she'll trade it all for a white dress <br><br>Been out of morality too long <br><br>She swears our love has been dying <br>But what do you expect from the king of the damned <br><br>Been out of mortality too long <br>Still singing the same old dead song <br><br>But if you need to go <br><br>And she walked out on the night <br>She lived the darkest life <br>But all she wants to be is the Queen of the Light <br><br>All these words from this brimstone bride <br>Claim the grass is always burning on the underside <br><br>Been down on this gravity too long <br>Still singing the same old falling song <br><br>But if you need to go <br><br>She walked out on the night <br>She lived the darkest life <br>But all she wants to be is the Queen <br>Yeah, all she wants to be <br><br>Is the Queen of the Light <br>Yeah, the Queen of the Light <br><br>But if you need to go <br><br>She walked out on the night <br>She lived the darkest life <br>But all she wants to be is the Queen <br>Yeah, all she wants to be <br><br>Is the Queen of the Light <br>Yeah, the Queen of the Light <br>Yeah, the Queen of the Light <br>Oh the Queen of the Light]]></content><category term="Crobot" label="Crobot"/><category term="Queen Of The Light" label="Queen Of The Light"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Wizards/</id><title>Crobot - Wizards - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:04:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:04:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Wizards/" title="Crobot - Wizards - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wizards <br><br>Wasteland <br>World of radiation <br>Human mutation runs rampant <br><br>Magic <br>Made with the wave of his staff <br>With the crystal attached <br>Carried 'crossed his back <br><br>Reptile hearts terrorize our lands <br>You gotta slay a few dragons before you get to the princess <br><br>The heavy handed wizards <br>You run away, run away, run away <br>The heavy handed wizards <br>You run away, run away, run away <br><br>Dream machines <br>Mechanical beings <br>Telepathically suppressing our freedom <br><br>Destruction <br>Droid execution <br>By the sword and the wand <br><br>Reptile hearts terrorize our lands <br>You gotta slay a few dragons before you get to the princess <br><br>The heavy handed wizards <br>You run away, run away, run away <br>The heavy handed wizards <br>You run away, run away, run away <br><br>Run <br><br>Reptile hearts terrorize our lands <br>You gotta slay a few dragons before you get to the princess <br><br>The heavy handed wizards <br>You run away, run away, run away <br>The heavy handed wizards <br>You run away, run away, run away <br>Run]]></content><category term="Crobot" label="Crobot"/><category term="Wizards" label="Wizards"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Chupacabra/</id><title>Crobot - Chupacabra - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:04:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:04:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Chupacabra/" title="Crobot - Chupacabra - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Chupacabra <br><br>Get up <br><br>300 dead sheep in Columbia <br>Victims of a creature as vicious as a god <br>Hairless and hungry, covered in mange <br>Carnivorous in all its attacking ways <br><br>Well I found that bloodsucker down by the river <br><br>Down by the river <br>El Chupacabra <br>Oh, down by the river <br>El Chupacabra, Chupacabra <br><br>Does such a thing exist, we may never know <br>All with glowing eyes of red, could steal your very soul <br>Movement in the distance, wait 'til the coast is clear <br>Monster of Mexico, I got your goat right here <br><br>Well I found that bloodsucker down by the river <br><br>Down by the river <br>El Chupacabra <br>Oh, down by the river <br>El Chupacabra, Chupacabra <br><br>Get up <br><br>Well I found that bloodsucker down by the river <br><br>Down by the river <br>El Chupacabra <br>Oh, down by the river <br>El Chupacabra, Chupacabra <br><br>Oh, down by the river <br>El Chupacabra, Chupacabra <br>Oh]]></content><category term="Crobot" label="Crobot"/><category term="Chupacabra" label="Chupacabra"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Night_Of_The_Sacrifice/</id><title>Crobot - Night Of The Sacrifice - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:04:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:04:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Night_Of_The_Sacrifice/" title="Crobot - Night Of The Sacrifice - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In the night of the sacrifice <br>Stones run red with the blood <br>For the mercy of the Gods <br>We pay our price <br><br>Conjuring the dust divine <br>Those who bear the sign <br>And you won't have to summon them twice <br><br>Now you're gonna die <br>Step right up <br>Don't be shy <br><br>You're senses will collide <br>Smoke and blood <br>No one gets out alive <br>No one gets out alive <br>No, no, no <br><br>In the night of the sacrifice <br>Crimson soaked swords <br>Arming spellbinding hoards of the dark light <br><br>With this wicker <br>She'll burn quicker that's for sure, baby <br>Give 'em whatcha got now <br>What's the use of a soul anyhow <br><br>Now you're gonna die <br>Step right up <br>Don't be shy <br><br>You're senses will collide <br>Smoke and blood <br>No one gets out alive <br>No one gets out alive <br>No, no, no <br><br>Now you're gonna die <br>Step right up <br>Don't be shy <br><br>You're senses will collide <br>Smoke and blood <br>No one gets out alive <br>No one gets out alive]]></content><category term="Crobot" label="Crobot"/><category term="Night Of The Sacrifice" label="Night Of The Sacrifice"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Fly_On_The_Wall/</id><title>Crobot - Fly On The Wall - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:04:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:04:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Fly_On_The_Wall/" title="Crobot - Fly On The Wall - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here I sit <br>Contemplating what shape to shift <br>I see so clear <br><br>When I'm closest to a sun's tear <br>These colors they come to me <br>Some, I'm sure, you've never seen <br><br>Well our eyes aren't the same <br>Yours are trained <br>Mine were freed <br>By something supernatural <br><br>And I'm just a fly on the wall <br><br>Understand <br>I am a twice born man <br>Second time's a charm <br>To feel the grip of space's endless arm <br><br>These colors they come to me <br>Some, I'm sure, you've never seen <br><br>Well our eyes aren't the same <br>Yours are trained <br>Mine were freed <br>By something supernatural <br><br>And I'm just a fly on the wall <br>It's something supernatural <br><br>You beg, you take, you steal from me <br>You love, you hate, you scream at me <br><br>These colors they come to me <br>Some, I'm sure, that you've never seen <br><br>Well our eyes aren't the same <br>Yours are trained <br>Mine were freed <br>By something supernatural <br><br>And I'm just a fly on the wall <br>It's something supernatural <br><br>And I'm just a fly on the wall <br>It's something supernatural]]></content><category term="Crobot" label="Crobot"/><category term="Fly On The Wall" label="Fly On The Wall"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Cloud_Spiller/</id><title>Crobot - Cloud Spiller - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:04:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:04:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Cloud_Spiller/" title="Crobot - Cloud Spiller - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, I went down to the water, just to wipe my brow <br>My head felt so heavy, like a broken down levee <br>And to my surprise I met that lake's lovely child <br>Well, oh yeah how she sheds her light <br>The one thing that keeps me alive <br><br>She fell down right from the sky <br>Eyes from the north got plenty of reasons why <br>Cloud spiller, she saved me <br>And now I'm free <br><br>After I shook the hooks of that succubus <br>The sun left its radiance and ran for the coast, oh <br>The cries of Skinwalkers cuts through the night <br><br>Oh yeah how she sheds her light <br>The one thing that keeps me alive <br><br>She fell down right from the sky <br>Eyes from the north got plenty of reasons why <br>Cloud spiller, she saved me <br>And now I'm free <br><br>Gravity's my only enemy <br>Why do you have to pull down on me <br>Gravity's my only enemy <br>Why do you have to pull down on me <br><br>Oh baby, keep me alive <br><br>She fell down right from the sky <br>Eyes from the north got plenty of reasons why <br>Cloud spiller, she saved me <br>And now I'm free <br>Yea, I'm free]]></content><category term="Crobot" label="Crobot"/><category term="Cloud Spiller" label="Cloud Spiller"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Skull_Of_Geronimo/</id><title>Crobot - Skull Of Geronimo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:04:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:04:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Skull_Of_Geronimo/" title="Crobot - Skull Of Geronimo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The Skull of Geronimo <br><br>I'm not built to lose <br>Bred from bloodlines of those who give the blues <br>Born to win <br>It's easy to be a player when you buy your way in <br><br>Oh boy, I can't wait to be one of the boys <br><br>The Skull of Geronimo <br>The key is a kiss once I I take hold <br>The Skull of Geronimo <br>The key is a kiss once I take hold <br><br>Bit and saddle horn <br>Stolen from those who protect the fort <br>Nine days from the day they dug up the relics of a warrior's grave <br><br>Oh Boy, I can't wait to be one of the boys <br><br>The Skulll of Geronimo <br>The key is a kiss once I take hold <br>The Skull of Geronimo <br>The key is a kiss once I take hold <br><br>Can't take, take, take what you'll never have <br>We'll keep our secrets in hell <br><br>The Skull of Geronimo <br>The key is a kiss once I take hold <br>The skull of Geronimo <br>The key is a kiss once I take hold <br><br>Can't take, take, take what you'll never have <br>We'll keep our secrets in hell <br>Can't take, take, take what you'll never have <br>We'll keep our secrets in hell]]></content><category term="Crobot" label="Crobot"/><category term="Skull Of Geronimo" label="Skull Of Geronimo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/La_Mano_De_Lucifer/</id><title>Crobot - La Mano De Lucifer - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:04:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:04:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/La_Mano_De_Lucifer/" title="Crobot - La Mano De Lucifer - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[La Mano de Lucifer <br><br>A failed rebellion against the one creator <br>Exiled to the fires in every clergy's fable <br>Nine circles to render the heart bloodless <br><br>But it's better to reign in hell <br>Than to serve God's will <br><br>As he takes his seat upon a dark winged unicorn <br>And he points his finger toward the red eyed children <br><br>La Mano de Lucifer <br>Persevere wayward angel <br><br>Swiftly swings the sword of eternal flames <br>Conjured up by the declaration of his name <br><br>La Mano de Lucifer <br>Persevere wayward angel <br>La Mano de Lucifer <br>Persevere wayward angel <br><br>Hold on to the fallen son, his breath will guide you along <br>Hold on to the fallen son, his breath will guide you along <br><br>A hunter's collection of tormented souls <br>He's known for the breaking of rules of the old <br><br>But it's better to reign in hell <br>Than to serve God's will <br><br>La Mano de Lucifer <br>Persevere wayward angel <br>La Mano de Lucifer <br>Persevere wayward angel]]></content><category term="Crobot" label="Crobot"/><category term="La Mano De Lucifer" label="La Mano De Lucifer"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/The_Necromancer/</id><title>Crobot - The Necromancer - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:04:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:04:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/The_Necromancer/" title="Crobot - The Necromancer - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The Necromancer <br><br>In the wake of the morning <br>The breaking of day <br>The land of the deadites lies just this way <br><br>Their souls have arisen <br>An army awake <br>The hand of the mage enslaves <br><br>All hail The Necromancer <br>All hail, the Necromancer <br><br>The killed get up and kill <br><br>In the light of the moon <br>The breath of the night <br>Bloody mist on the battlefield <br>This war ends tonight <br><br>Life of the lifeless we'll try and take <br>Pillage one and all, burn 'em at the stake <br><br>All hail The Necromancer <br>All hail, the Necromancer <br><br>The killed get up and kill <br>The killed get up and kill <br><br>What does it take to slay the slayed <br>How do you hunt the hunted <br><br>All hail The Necromancer <br>All hail, the Necromancer <br><br>The killed get up and kill <br>The killed get up and kill]]></content><category term="Crobot" label="Crobot"/><category term="The Necromancer" label="The Necromancer"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Nowhere_To_Hide/</id><title>Crobot - Nowhere To Hide - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:05:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:05:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Nowhere_To_Hide/" title="Crobot - Nowhere To Hide - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nowhere to Hide <br><br>The hangman's coming, bring him forth <br>Get your spirit ready to crossover <br>You won't hide for long behind the dungeon walls <br>There's no escaping after the hammer falls <br><br>Hands to the sky cause it's tumbling down <br>Cracking a smile as it hits the ground <br><br>Speechless and all choked up <br>Justice attached to a rope <br>There ain't nowhere to hide on the frontline <br><br>Speechless and all choked up <br>Justice attached to a rope <br>There ain't nowhere to hide on the frontline <br><br>The gallows' swingin' to a dead man's song <br>Sounds of flaming arrows, a rhythm so strong <br>Knights are saddled send the prison hounds <br>It's a war of the worlds until he's found <br><br>Hands to the sky cause it's tumbling down <br>Cracking a smile as it hits the ground <br><br>Speechless and all choked up <br>Justice attached to a rope <br>There ain't nowhere to hide on the frontline <br>Speechless and all choked up <br>Justice attached to a rope <br>There ain't nowhere to hide on the frontline <br><br>Hands to the sky cause it's tumbling down <br>Cracking a smile as it hits the ground <br><br>Speechless and all choked up <br>Justice attached to a rope <br>There ain't nowhere to hide on the frontline <br>Speechless and all choked up <br>Justice attached to a rope <br>There ain't nowhere to hide on the frontline]]></content><category term="Crobot" label="Crobot"/><category term="Nowhere To Hide" label="Nowhere To Hide"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Legend_Of_The_Spaceborne_Killer/</id><title>Crobot - Legend Of The Spaceborne Killer - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:05:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:05:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crobot/Legend_Of_The_Spaceborne_Killer/" title="Crobot - Legend Of The Spaceborne Killer - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Legend of the Spaceborne Killer <br><br>The Legend of the Spaceborne Killer <br>Made the front page today <br>Nobody knows where he came from <br>Why he's here <br>Or what he'll do to you <br><br>I just saw the flashing lights <br>They blinded me they shined so bright <br><br>Is it half bird, half bot, or half alien <br>Well, I don't know <br>But he's got something in his hand <br><br>The Legend of the Spaceborne Killer <br>I met face to face today <br>I couldn't tell just what he wanted <br>If I had to give I would've gave it away <br><br>I just saw his glowing eyes <br>They blinded me they shined so bright <br><br>Is it half bird, half bot, or half alien <br>I don't know <br>But he's got something in his hand <br><br>No more buildings to stand tall <br>He must've destroyed them all <br><br>Is it half bird, half bot, or half alien <br>I don't know <br>But he's got something in his hand]]></content><category term="Crobot" label="Crobot"/><category term="Legend Of The Spaceborne Killer" label="Legend Of The Spaceborne Killer"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cunnie_Williams/For_The_Children/</id><title>Cunnie Williams - For The Children - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:05:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:05:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cunnie_Williams/For_The_Children/" title="Cunnie Williams - For The Children - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This is for the future of every family <br>New generation got to find a way to be <br>One love, one people is the only way to live <br><br>Without wanting is the only way to give <br><br>This is for the future of everyone of us <br>I send this message <br>Please remember love <br>This is for the future of everyone of us <br>I send this message <br>Please remember love <br>This is for the world that <br>I may not live to see <br>A world where everyone <br>Lives in peace and harmony <br>No more worries about war around the world <br>A better life for every little boy and girl <br><br>This is for the future of everyone of us <br>I send this message <br>Please remember love <br>This is for the future of everyone of us <br>I send this message <br>Please remember love <br>This is for the future <br>Please hear me when I say <br>We've got to learn a lesson <br>From the problems of today <br>One man can't rule this world <br>Everyone can see <br>Free love, free life, free thinking <br>An equalitiy <br><br>This is for the future of everyone of us <br>I send this message <br>Please remember love <br>This is for the future of everyone of us <br>I send this message <br>Please remember love]]></content><category term="Cunnie Williams" label="Cunnie Williams"/><category term="For The Children" label="For The Children"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cunnie_Williams/War_Song/</id><title>Cunnie Williams - War Song - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:05:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:05:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cunnie_Williams/War_Song/" title="Cunnie Williams - War Song - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[War Song <br><br>Please won't someone hear my cry <br>Wipe this tear drops from my eyes <br>Tell me if life worth a prayer <br>Will I knee, will you be there <br><br>Don't wanna another war song x4 <br><br>Mother's tears are tears of pain <br>Broken future and the blood stains <br>Material gain can destroy your mind <br>Think of all the beauty that you left behind <br><br>Don't wanna another war song <br>Like the mountains and the seas <br>Don't wanna another war song <br>Like the flowers and the trees <br>Don't wanna another war song <br>No more joy for girls and boys <br>Don't wanna another war song <br>No more playing with the toys <br>Don't wanna another war song <br>Can you understand what's going on <br>Don't wanna another war song <br>Can you tell me what's too wrong <br>Don't wanna another war song <br>Can you see that it's wrong <br>Don't wanna another war song <br>Tell me will this pain go on <br>Don't wanna another war song <br>I don't wanna hear another song <br>Don't wanna another war song <br>It's been goin' on too long]]></content><category term="Cunnie Williams" label="Cunnie Williams"/><category term="War Song" label="War Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cunnie_Williams/Go_When_He_Calls_Me/</id><title>Cunnie Williams - Go When He Calls Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:05:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:05:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cunnie_Williams/Go_When_He_Calls_Me/" title="Cunnie Williams - Go When He Calls Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lord I'm a sinner <br>I confess all to you <br>You never let me down <br>Trouble you seen me through <br>Why did you do it <br>Save a poor wretch like me <br>Don't feel I'm worthy <br>But I'm so glad you did <br>Gave me a brand new song <br>Never knew love like this <br>Feeling is burning strong <br>Feeling I can't resist <br>Don't care what people say <br>I'm going all the way <br>Any time any place <br>You just call my name <br>And I'll go <br><br>Go when he calls me <br>Go when he calls me <br>Go when he calls me <br><br>Feel like I lost my light <br>Darkness covered my soul <br>Things were'nt going right <br>Lost all my self control <br>But you turned my life around <br>True love in him I found <br>Put me on solid ground <br>And I'm gonna stay down <br>Cause I don't care what people say <br>I'm going all the way <br>Any time any place <br>You just call my name <br>And I'll go <br><br>Go when he calls me <br>Go when he calls me <br>Go when he calls me]]></content><category term="Cunnie Williams" label="Cunnie Williams"/><category term="Go When He Calls Me" label="Go When He Calls Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cunnie_Williams/Come_Back_To_Me/</id><title>Cunnie Williams - Come Back To Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:05:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:05:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cunnie_Williams/Come_Back_To_Me/" title="Cunnie Williams - Come Back To Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I told some lies <br>And make you cry <br>Broke your heart <br>What a foolish guy <br>Played with your head <br>Cheated in bed <br>An'though you knew <br>Not a world to say <br><br>Now I'm begging you <br><br>Baby please come back to me Back to me <br>Here is where you ought to be Ought to be <br>My days and nights are so lonely <br>Baby come back to me <br>Baby please come back to me Back to me <br>Here is where you ought to be Ought to be <br>My days and nights are so lonely <br>Baby come back to me <br><br>Sit by the phone <br>Sit all alone <br>Waiting for you <br>To call and tell me <br>You want to come home <br>Mistakes I made <br>Threw love away <br>I know how it feels to loose everything <br>It hurts everyday <br><br>And I'm begging you <br><br>Baby please come back to me Back to me <br>Here is where you ought to be Ought to be <br>My days and nights are so lonely <br>Baby come back to me Baby please come back to me <br>Baby please come back to me Back to me <br>Here is where you ought to be Ought to be <br>My days and nights are so lonely <br>Baby come back to me <br><br>Baby please come back to me Babe, back to me <br>Here is where you ought to be Ought to be <br>My days and nights are so lonely <br>Baby come back to me Baby please come back to me <br>Baby please come back to me Back to me <br>Here is where you ought to be <br>My days and nights are so lonely <br>Baby come back to me <br><br>Baby please come back to me <br>Here is where you ought to be <br>My days and nights are so lonely <br>Baby come back to me <br>Baby please come back to me <br>Ought to be <br>Baby please come back to me]]></content><category term="Cunnie Williams" label="Cunnie Williams"/><category term="Come Back To Me" label="Come Back To Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cunnie_Williams/Suddendly_Its_Magic/</id><title>Cunnie Williams - Suddendly It`s Magic - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:06:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:06:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cunnie_Williams/Suddendly_Its_Magic/" title="Cunnie Williams - Suddendly It`s Magic - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I always thought I would be strong <br>If I made it through the pain <br>Well, I've been in and out of love <br>And it all hurts just the same, oh yeah <br>Love can really change your life <br>There's something magic in my world tonight <br><br>I feel so free <br>It's like a fantasy <br>Havin' you next to me <br>Suddenly it's magic <br><br>One look, one touch <br>Words just don't say enough <br>When you fall in love <br>Suddenly, suddenly it's magic <br><br>I'm not afraid of letting go <br>I've got to find what's right for me <br>I'm not afraid to stand alone <br>If that's the way it has to be <br>After all that I've been through <br>There's magic when I'm here with you <br><br>I feel so free <br>It's like a fantasy <br>Havin' you next to me <br>Suddenly it's magic <br><br>One look, one touch <br>Words just don't say enough <br>When you fall in love <br>Suddenly, suddenly it's magic <br><br>We can dream our dreams forever <br>When I'm here with you <br>Baby, heaven's a heartbeat away <br>Now that we're together <br>Love could last forever <br>There's magic in my life <br>With you, you,]]></content><category term="Cunnie Williams" label="Cunnie Williams"/><category term="Suddendly It`s Magic" label="Suddendly It`s Magic"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aranda/Starting_Over/</id><title>Aranda - Starting Over - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:06:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:06:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aranda/Starting_Over/" title="Aranda - Starting Over - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Am I breaking <br>I can't own up <br>Nothing's making sense <br><br>Taking everything <br>owing all to nothing <br>Is this where I begin <br><br>I'm waking up <br>I've had enough <br>it's time to let it go <br><br>I'm alive <br>I'm a wreck <br>Gunna live my life with no regrets <br>And I'm gunna find my way to <br>starting over <br>I'm starting over <br><br>No plans <br>too sober <br>Moving forward <br>new day in front of me <br><br>Oh, I'm waking up <br>I've had enough <br>it's time to let it go <br><br>I'm alive <br>I'm a wreck <br>Gunna live my life with no regrets <br>And I'm gunna find my way to <br>starting over <br>I'm starting over <br><br>And I <br>I'm a mess <br>Gotta live my life <br>not dead, not yet <br><br>And I <br>Gotta find my way to starting over <br>I'm starting over <br>Woah oh oh oh oh oh <br><br>We'll take this rising up <br>I feel it getting stronger and stronger <br>I'm not dead, not yet <br>I'm alive <br><br>I'm alive <br>I'm a wreck <br>I live my life with no regrets <br><br>And I <br>I found my way to starting over <br>I'm starting over <br><br>And I <br>I'm a wreck <br>Gotta live my life <br>not dead, not yet <br><br>And I <br>I found my way to starting over <br>I'm starting over <br><br>And I <br>know <br>not dead, not yet <br><br>And I <br>I found my way to starting over <br>I'm starting over <br><br>And I]]></content><category term="Aranda" label="Aranda"/><category term="Starting Over" label="Starting Over"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aranda/Are_You_Listening_/</id><title>Aranda - Are You Listening? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:06:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:06:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aranda/Are_You_Listening_/" title="Aranda - Are You Listening? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know where the edges got frayed when the little things started drivin' me crazy <br>Do you understand me <br>You're the one looking over my shoulder <br><br>I'm counting down till the tears are over <br>It's not the way we planned it <br>I'm reeling it in <br>Cause you can't seem to see that the truth set you free babe <br>I don't understand <br>Why I'm alone even when you were with me <br>And all I wanna say is <br>Love gets in the way <br>And somehow this became nothin more than pretending <br>And all I wanna do is leave you with the truth <br>It's you I'm talking too <br>But are you listening <br>I wanna leave but I need to stay <br>You're the one pushing me away <br>And time ain't on our side, no <br>And I don't want any more of this drama can't define where we'll be tomorrow <br>It has to change today <br>It's slipping away cause you're too about you and the damage you do babe <br>We're better as friends <br>I hope we can save what we got left <br>And all I wanna say is <br>Love gets in the way <br>And somehow this became nothin more than pretending <br>And all I wanna do is <br>Leave you with the truth <br>It's you I'm talking too <br>But are you listening <br>And I know that <br>I've been playing with fire trying not to burn out <br>And I know you're <br>Pulling me down <br>Let go girl <br>I'll try just to be there oh when you need me <br>Can you here me now <br>Now <br>All I wanna say is all I wanna say is <br>All I wanna say <br>is <br>All I wanna say is love gets in the way and somehow this became nothin more than pretending <br>And all I wanna do is <br>Leave you with the truth <br>As you are talking too <br>But are you listening But are you <br>But are you listening <br>Are you listening]]></content><category term="Aranda" label="Aranda"/><category term="Are You Listening?" label="Are You Listening?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aranda/Shadow_Of_The_Sun/</id><title>Aranda - Shadow Of The Sun - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:06:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:06:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aranda/Shadow_Of_The_Sun/" title="Aranda - Shadow Of The Sun - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Waited a thousand years now, I stand still in time <br>In a battle I'm not strong enough to fight <br>Give me faith that I once left behind <br><br>and now you're saving my life <br><br>How can I escape when there's nowhere to run <br>This won't let me wait until the morning comes <br>Fight through this storm I reach for you <br>Cause I never thought I find the one <br>In the shadow of the sun <br>The shadow of the sun <br><br>Even darkness won't let me hide won't let me hide <br>Moving so fast the stars fade to light <br>Should the sun ever refuse to shine <br>Still you're saving my life <br><br>How can I escape when there's nowhere to run <br>This won't let me wait until the morning comes <br>Fight through this storm I reach for you <br>Cause I never thought I find the one <br>In the shadow of the sun <br>The shadow of the sun <br><br>Wait, don't leave me down here without you <br>Wait, cause I can't remember the world I thought I knew <br><br>How can I escape when there's nowhere to run <br>This won't let me wait until the morning comes <br>Fight through this storm I reach for you <br>Cause I never thought I find the one <br>In the shadow of the sun <br>The shadow of the sun]]></content><category term="Aranda" label="Aranda"/><category term="Shadow Of The Sun" label="Shadow Of The Sun"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aranda/Comin_Back_For_More/</id><title>Aranda - Comin` Back For More - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:06:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:06:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aranda/Comin_Back_For_More/" title="Aranda - Comin` Back For More - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've got a lot things but you're taking it <br>I made a big mistake can I pay for it <br>You've got a lot of nerve <br><br>I already know so don't remind me <br>You know you took my heart now you're breaking it <br>You throw it in my face I'm not taking it <br>You've got a lot of nerve <br>I already know so don't remind me <br><br>When you think the worst is over <br>It drags you down a little lower <br>We are living in insanity <br>Too young to care what we've been told <br>Knocked down, but were getting up again <br>Whoa, coming back for more <br>We are living in insanity <br>Too young to know what we don't know <br>Face down oh were getting up again <br>Whoa, coming back for more <br><br>You know I had a plan now they're changing it <br>I made a big mistake would you pay for it <br>I got a lot of nerve <br>I already know so don't remind me <br>I had a lot of heart now they're breaking it <br>Is it all a joke are we faking it <br>We got a lot of nerve <br>I already know so don't remind me <br><br>When you think the worst is over over <br>It drags you down a little lower <br>We are living in insanity <br>Too young to care what we've been told <br>Knocked down, but were getting up again <br>Whoa, coming back for more <br>We are living in insanity <br>Too young to know what we don't know <br>Face down oh were getting up again <br>Whoa, coming back for more <br><br>Oh, we know they wanna put us in chains <br>we see you coming from a million miles away <br>We know they wanna put us in chains <br>You know we see you coming from a million miles away <br><br>We are living in insanity <br>Too young to care what we've been told <br>Knocked down, but were getting up again <br>Whoa, coming back for more <br>We are living in insanity <br>Too young to know what we don't know <br>Face down oh were getting up again <br>Whoa, coming back for more]]></content><category term="Aranda" label="Aranda"/><category term="Comin` Back For More" label="Comin` Back For More"/></entry></feed>