<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:18:04+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Light_As_The_Breeze_Live_At_Dublin_Show_2012/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - Light As The Breeze (Live At Dublin Show, 2012) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Light_As_The_Breeze_Live_At_Dublin_Show_2012/" title="Leonard Cohen - Light As The Breeze (Live At Dublin Show, 2012) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She stands before you naked <br>you can see it, you can taste it <br>and she comes to you light as the breeze. <br>Now you can drink it or you can nurse it <br>it don't matter how you worship <br>as long as you're <br>down on your knees. <br>So I knelt there at the delta <br>at the alpha and the omega <br>at the cradle of the river and the seas. <br>And like a blessing come from heaven <br>for something like a second <br>I was healed and my heart <br>was at ease. <br><br>O baby I waited <br>so long for your kiss <br>for something to happen <br>oh something like this. <br><br>And you're weak and you're harmless <br>and you're sleeping in your harness <br>and the wind going wild <br>in the trees <br>and it ain't exactly prison <br>but you'll never be forgiven <br>for whatever you've done <br>with the keys. <br><br>O baby I waited ... <br><br>It's dark now and it's snowing <br>O my love I must be going <br>The river has started to freeze. <br>And I'm sick of pretending <br>I'm broken from bending <br>I've lived too long on my knees. <br><br>Then she dances so graceful <br>and your heart's hard and hateful <br>and she's naked <br>but that's just a tease. <br>And you turn in disgust <br>from your hatred and from your love <br>and comes to you <br>light as the breeze. <br><br>O baby I waited ... <br><br>There's blood on every bracelet <br>you can see it, you can taste it <br>and it's Please baby <br>please baby please. <br>And she says, Drink deeply, pilgrim <br>but don't forget there's still a woman <br>beneath this <br>resplendent chemise. <br><br>So I knelt there at the delta <br>at the alpha and the omega <br>I knelt there like one who believes. <br>And the blessings come from heaven <br>and for something like a second <br>I'm cured and my heart <br>is at ease]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="Light As The Breeze (Live At Dublin Show, 2012)" label="Light As The Breeze (Live At Dublin Show, 2012)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/I_Cant_Forget_Live_At_Copenhagen_Show_2012/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - I Can`t Forget (Live At Copenhagen Show, 2012) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/I_Cant_Forget_Live_At_Copenhagen_Show_2012/" title="Leonard Cohen - I Can`t Forget (Live At Copenhagen Show, 2012) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I stumbled out of bed <br>I got ready for the struggle <br>I smoked a cigarette <br>And I tightened up my gut <br>I said this can't be me <br>Must be my double <br>And I can't forget, I can't forget <br>I can't forget but I don't remember what <br>I'm burning up the road <br>I'm heading down to Phoenix <br>I got this old address <br>Of someone that I knew <br>It was high and fine and free <br>Ah, you should have seen us <br>And I can't forget, I can't forget <br>I can't forget but I don't remember who <br><br>I'll be there today <br>With a big bouquet of cactus <br>I got this rig that runs on memories <br>And I promise, cross my heart <br>They'll never catch us <br>But if they do, just tell them it was me <br><br>Yeah I loved you all my life <br>And that's how I want to end it <br>The summer's almost gone <br>The winter's tuning up <br>Yeah, the summer's gone <br>But a lot goes on forever <br>And I can't forget, I can't forget <br>I can't forget but I don't remember what]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="I Can`t Forget (Live At Copenhagen Show, 2012)" label="I Can`t Forget (Live At Copenhagen Show, 2012)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Field_Commander_Cohen_Live_At_Denver_Soundcheck_2012/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - Field Commander Cohen (Live At Denver Soundcheck, 2012) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Field_Commander_Cohen_Live_At_Denver_Soundcheck_2012/" title="Leonard Cohen - Field Commander Cohen (Live At Denver Soundcheck, 2012) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Field Commander Cohen, he was our most important spy. <br>Wounded in the line of duty <br>parachuting acid into diplomatic cocktail parties <br>urging Fidel Castro to abandon fields and castles. <br>Leave it all and like a man <br>come back to nothing special <br>such as waiting rooms and ticket lines <br>silver bullet suicides <br>and messianic ocean tides <br>and racial roller-coaster rides <br>and other forms of boredom advertised as poetry. <br>I know you need your sleep now <br>I know your life's been hard. <br>But many men are falling <br>where you promised to stand guard. <br><br>I never asked but I heard you cast your lot along with the poor. <br>But then I overheard your prayer <br>that you be this and nothing more <br>than just some grateful faithful woman's favourite singing millionaire <br>the patron Saint of envy and the grocer of despair <br>working for the Yankee Dollar. <br><br>I know you need your sleep now ... <br><br>Ah, lover come and lie with me, if my lover is who you are <br>and be your sweetest self awhile until I ask for more, my child. <br>Then let the other selves be wrong, yeah, let them manifest and come <br>till every taste is on the tongue <br>till love is pierced and love is hung <br>and every kind of freedom done, then oh <br>oh my love, oh my love, oh my love <br>oh my love, oh my love, oh my love.]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="Field Commander Cohen (Live At Denver Soundcheck, 2012)" label="Field Commander Cohen (Live At Denver Soundcheck, 2012)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Seems_So_Long_Ago_Nancy_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - Seems So Long Ago, Nancy (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Seems_So_Long_Ago_Nancy_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/" title="Leonard Cohen - Seems So Long Ago, Nancy (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It seems so long ago <br>Nancy was alone <br>looking ate the Late Late show <br>through a semi-precious stone. <br>In the House of Honesty <br>her father was on trial <br>in the House of Mystery <br>there was no one at all <br>there was no one at all. <br>It seems so long ago <br>none of us were strong; <br>Nancy wore green stockings <br>and she slept with everyone. <br>She never said she'd wait for us <br>although she was alone <br>I think she fell in love for us <br>in nineteen sixty one <br>in nineteen sixty one. <br><br>It seems so long ago <br>Nancy was alone <br>a forty five beside her head <br>an open telephone. <br>We told her she was beautiful <br>we told her she was free <br>but none of us would meet her in <br>the House of Mystery <br>the House of Mystery. <br><br>And now you look around you <br>see her everywhere <br>many use her body <br>many comb her hair. <br>In the hollow of the night <br>when you are cold and numb <br>you hear her talking freely then <br>she's happy that you've come <br>she's happy that you've come.]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="Seems So Long Ago, Nancy (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)" label="Seems So Long Ago, Nancy (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Famous_Blue_Raincoat_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - Famous Blue Raincoat (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Famous_Blue_Raincoat_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/" title="Leonard Cohen - Famous Blue Raincoat (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's four in the morning, the end of December <br>I'm writing you now just to see if you're better <br>New York is cold, but I like where I'm living <br>There's music on Clinton Street all through the evening. <br>I hear that you're building your little house deep in the desert <br>You're living for nothing now, I hope you're keeping some kind of record. <br><br>Yes, and Jane came by with a lock of your hair <br>She said that you gave it to her <br>That night that you planned to go clear <br>Did you ever go clear? <br><br>Ah, the last time we saw you you looked so much older <br>Your famous blue raincoat was torn at the shoulder <br>You'd been to the station to meet every train <br>And you came home without Lili Marlene <br><br>And you treated my woman to a flake of your life <br>And when she came back she was nobody's wife. <br><br>Well I see you there with the rose in your teeth <br>One more thin gypsy thief <br>Well I see Jane's awake -- <br><br>She sends her regards. <br><br>And what can I tell you my brother, my killer <br>What can I possibly say? <br>I guess that I miss you, I guess I forgive you <br>I'm glad you stood in my way. <br><br>If you ever come by here, for Jane or for me <br>Your enemy is sleeping, and his woman is free. <br><br>Yes, and thanks, for the trouble you took from her eyes <br>I thought it was there for good so I never tried. <br><br>And Jane came by with a lock of your hair <br>She said that you gave it to her <br>That night that you planned to go clear -- <br><br>Sincerely, L. Cohen]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="Famous Blue Raincoat (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)" label="Famous Blue Raincoat (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/The_Partisan_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - The Partisan (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/The_Partisan_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/" title="Leonard Cohen - The Partisan (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When they poured across the border <br>I was cautioned to surrender <br>this I could not do; <br>I took my gun and vanished. <br>I have changed my name so often <br>I've lost my wife and children <br>but I have many friends <br>and some of them are with me. <br><br>An old woman gave us shelter <br>kept us hidden in the garret <br>then the soldiers came; <br>she died without a whisper. <br><br>There were three of us this morning <br>I'm the only one this evening <br>but I must go on; <br>the frontiers are my prison. <br><br>Oh, the wind, the wind is blowing <br>through the graves the wind is blowing <br>freedom soon will come; <br>then we'll come from the shadows. <br><br>Les Allemands etaient chez moi (The Germans were at my home) <br>ils m'ont dit "Resigne-toi" (They said, "Surrender,") <br>mais je n'ai pas pu (this I could not do) <br>j'ai repris mon arme (I took my weapon again) <br><br>J'ai change cent fois de nom (I have changed names a hundred times) <br>j'ai perdu femme et enfants (I have lost wife and children) <br>mais j'ai tant d'amis (But I have so many friends) <br>j'ai la France entiere (I have all of France) <br><br>Un vieil homme dans un grenier (An old man, in an attic) <br>pour la nuit nous a caches (Hid us for the night) <br>les Allemands l'ont pris (The Germans captured him) <br>il est mort sans surprise (He died without surprise) <br><br>Oh, the wind, the wind is blowing <br>through the graves the wind is blowing <br>freedom soon will come; <br>then we'll come from the shadows.]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="The Partisan (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)" label="The Partisan (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Sing_Another_Song_Boys_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - Sing Another Song, Boys (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Sing_Another_Song_Boys_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/" title="Leonard Cohen - Sing Another Song, Boys (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(Let's sing another song, boys, this one has grown old and bitter.) <br>Ah his fingernails, I see they're broken <br>his ships they're all on fire. <br>The moneylender's lovely little daughter <br>ah, she's eaten, she's eaten with desire. <br>She spies him through the glasses <br>from the pawnshops of her wicked father. <br>She hails him with a microphone <br>that some poor singer, just like me, had to leave her. <br>She tempts him with a clarinet <br>she waves a Nazi dagger. <br>She finds him lying in a heap; <br>she wants to be his woman. <br>He says, "Yes, I might go to sleep <br>but kindly leave, leave the future <br>leave it open." <br><br>He stands where it is steep <br>oh I guess he thinks that he's the very first one <br>his hand upon his leather belt now <br>like it was the wheel of some big ocean liner. <br>And she will learn to touch herself so well <br>as all the sails burn down like paper. <br>And he has lit the chain <br>of his famous cigarillo. <br>Ah, they'll never, they'll never ever reach the moon <br>at least not the one that we're after; <br>it's floating broken on the open sea, look out there, my friends <br>and it carries no survivors. <br>But lets leave these lovers wondering <br>why they cannot have each other <br>and let's sing another song, boys <br>this one has grown old and bitter.]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="Sing Another Song, Boys (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)" label="Sing Another Song, Boys (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Suzanne_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - Suzanne (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Suzanne_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/" title="Leonard Cohen - Suzanne (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Suzanne takes you down to her place near the river <br>You can hear the boats go by <br>You can spend the night beside her <br>And you know that she's half crazy <br>But that's why you want to be there <br>And she feeds you tea and oranges <br>That come all the way from China <br>And just when you mean to tell her <br>That you have no love to give her <br>Then she gets you on her wavelength <br>And she lets the river answer <br>That you've always been her lover <br>And you want to travel with her <br>And you want to travel blind <br>And you know that she will trust you <br>For you've touched her perfect body with your mind. <br>And Jesus was a sailor <br>When he walked upon the water <br>And he spent a long time watching <br>From his lonely wooden tower <br>And when he knew for certain <br>Only drowning men could see him <br>He said "All men will be sailors then <br>Until the sea shall free them" <br>But he himself was broken <br>Long before the sky would open <br>Forsaken, almost human <br>He sank beneath your wisdom like a stone <br>And you want to travel with him <br>And you want to travel blind <br>And you think maybe you'll trust him <br>For he's touched your perfect body with his mind. <br><br>Now Suzanne takes your hand <br>And she leads you to the river <br>She is wearing rags and feathers <br>From Salvation Army counters <br>And the sun pours down like honey <br>On our lady of the harbour <br>And she shows you where to look <br>Among the garbage and the flowers <br>There are heroes in the seaweed <br>There are children in the morning <br>They are leaning out for love <br>And they will lean that way forever <br>While Suzanne holds the mirror <br>And you want to travel with her <br>And you want to travel blind <br>And you know that you can trust her <br>For she's touched your perfect body with her mind.]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="Suzanne (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)" label="Suzanne (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Diamonds_In_The_Mine_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - Diamonds In The Mine (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Diamonds_In_The_Mine_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/" title="Leonard Cohen - Diamonds In The Mine (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The woman in blue, she's asking for revenge <br>the man in white -- that's you -- says he has no friends. <br>The river is swollen up with rusty cans <br>and the trees are burning in your promised land. <br>And there are no letters in the mailbox <br>and there are no grapes upon the vine <br>and there are no chocolates in the boxes anymore <br>and there are no diamonds in the mine. <br><br>Well, you tell me that your lover has a broken limb <br>you say you're kind of restless now and it's on account of him. <br>Well, I saw the man in question, it was just the other night <br>he was eating up a lady where the lions and Christians fight. <br><br>And there are no letters in the mailbox <br>and there are no grapes upon the vine <br>and there are no chocolates in the boxes anymore <br>and there are no diamonds in the mine. <br><br>(You tell them now) <br><br>Ah, there is no comfort in the covens of the witch <br>some very clever doctor went and sterilized the bitch <br>and the only man of energy, yes the revolution's pride <br>he trained a hundred women just to kill an unborn child. <br><br>And there are no letters in the mailbox <br>oh no, there are no, no grapes upon your vine <br>and there are, there are no chocolates in your boxes anymore <br>and there are no diamonds in your mine. <br>And there are no letters in the mailbox <br>and there are no grapes upon the vine <br>and there are no chocolates in your boxes anymore <br>and there are no diamonds in your mine.]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="Diamonds In The Mine (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)" label="Diamonds In The Mine (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Hey_Thats_No_Way_To_Say_Goodbye_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - Hey, That`s No Way To Say Goodbye (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Hey_Thats_No_Way_To_Say_Goodbye_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/" title="Leonard Cohen - Hey, That`s No Way To Say Goodbye (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I loved you in the morning, our kisses deep and warm <br>your hair upon the pillow like a sleepy golden storm <br>yes, many loved before us, I know that we are not new <br>in city and in forest they smiled like me and you <br>but now it's come to distances and both of us must try <br>your eyes are soft with sorrow <br>Hey, that's no way to say goodbye. <br>I'm not looking for another as I wander in my time <br>walk me to the corner, our steps will always rhyme <br>you know my love goes with you as your love stays with me <br>it's just the way it changes, like the shoreline and the sea <br>but let's not talk of love or chains and things we can't untie <br>your eyes are soft with sorrow <br>Hey, that's no way to say goodbye. <br><br>I loved you in the morning, our kisses deep and warm <br>your hair upon the pillow like a sleepy golden storm <br>yes many loved before us, I know that we are not new <br>in city and in forest they smiled like me and you <br>but let's not talk of love or chains and things we can't untie <br>your eyes are soft with sorrow <br>Hey, that's no way to say goodbye.]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="Hey, That`s No Way To Say Goodbye (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)" label="Hey, That`s No Way To Say Goodbye (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Tonight_Will_Be_Fine_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - Tonight Will Be Fine (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Tonight_Will_Be_Fine_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/" title="Leonard Cohen - Tonight Will Be Fine (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes I find I get to thinking of the past. <br>We swore to each other then that our love would surely last. <br>You kept right on loving, I went on a fast <br>now I am too thin and your love is too vast. <br>But I know from your eyes <br>and I know from your smile <br>that tonight will be fine <br>will be fine, will be fine, will be fine <br>for a while. <br><br>I choose the rooms that I live in with care <br>the windows are small and the walls almost bare <br>there's only one bed and there's only one prayer; <br>I listen all night for your step on the stair. <br><br>But I know from your eyes <br>and I know from your smile <br>that tonight will be fine <br>will be fine, will be fine, will be fine <br>for a while. <br><br>Oh sometimes I see her undressing for me <br>she's the soft naked lady love meant her to be <br>and she's moving her body so brave and so free. <br>If I've got to remember that's a fine memory. <br><br>And I know from her eyes <br>and I know from her smile <br>that tonight will be fine <br>will be fine, will be fine, will be fine <br>for a while.]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="Tonight Will Be Fine (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)" label="Tonight Will Be Fine (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/The_Stranger_Song_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - The Stranger Song (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/The_Stranger_Song_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/" title="Leonard Cohen - The Stranger Song (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's true that all the men you knew were dealers <br>who said they were through with dealing <br>Every time you gave them shelter <br>I know that kind of man <br>It's hard to hold the hand of anyone <br>who is reaching for the sky just to surrender <br>who is reaching for the sky just to surrender. <br>And then sweeping up the jokers that he left behind <br>you find he did not leave you very much <br>not even laughter <br>Like any dealer he was watching for the card <br>that is so high and wild <br>he'll never need to deal another <br>He was just some Joseph looking for a manger <br>He was just some Joseph looking for a manger <br><br>And then leaning on your window sill <br>he'll say one day you caused his will <br>to weaken with your love and warmth and shelter <br>And then taking from his wallet <br>an old schedule of trains, he'll say <br>I told you when I came I was a stranger <br>I told you when I came I was a stranger. <br><br>But now another stranger seems <br>to want you to ignore his dreams <br>as though they were the burden of some other <br>O you've seen that man before <br>his golden arm dispatching cards <br>but now it's rusted from the elbows to the finger <br>And he wants to trade the game he plays for shelter <br>Yes he wants to trade the game he knows for shelter. <br><br>Ah you hate to see another tired man <br>lay down his hand <br>like he was giving up the holy game of poker <br>And while he talks his dreams to sleep <br>you notice there's a highway <br>that is curling up like smoke above his shoulder. <br>It is curling just like smoke above his shoulder. <br><br>You tell him to come in sit down <br>but something makes you turn around <br>The door is open you can't close your shelter <br>You try the handle of the road <br>It opens do not be afraid <br>It's you my love, you who are the stranger <br>It's you my love, you who are the stranger. <br><br>Well, I've been waiting, I was sure <br>we'd meet between the trains we're waiting for <br>I think it's time to board another <br>Please understand, I never had a secret chart <br>to get me to the heart of this <br>or any other matter <br>When he talks like this <br>you don't know what he's after <br>When he speaks like this <br>you don't know what he's after. <br><br>Let's meet tomorrow if you choose <br>upon the shore, beneath the bridge <br>that they are building on some endless river <br>Then he leaves the platform <br>for the sleeping car that's warm <br>You realize, he's only advertising one more shelter <br>And it comes to you, he never was a stranger <br>And you say ok the bridge or someplace later. <br><br>And then sweeping up the jokers that he left behind ... <br><br>And leaning on your window sill ... <br><br>I told you when I came I was a stranger.]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="The Stranger Song (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)" label="The Stranger Song (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/One_Of_Us_Cannot_Be_Wrong_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - One Of Us Cannot Be Wrong (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/One_Of_Us_Cannot_Be_Wrong_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/" title="Leonard Cohen - One Of Us Cannot Be Wrong (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I lit a thin green candle, to make you jealous of me. <br>But the room just filled up with mosquitos <br>they heard that my body was free. <br>Then I took the dust of a long sleepless night <br>and I put it in your little shoe. <br>And then I confess that I tortured the dress <br>that you wore for the world to look through. <br>I showed my heart to the doctor: he said I just have to quit. <br>Then he wrote himself a prescription <br>and your name was mentioned in it! <br>Then he locked himself in a library shelf <br>with the details of our honeymoon <br>and I hear from the nurse that he's gotten much worse <br>and his practice is all in a ruin. <br><br>I heard of a saint who had loved you <br>so I studied all night in his school. <br>He taught that the duty of lovers <br>is to tarnish the golden rule. <br>And just when I was sure that his teachings were pure <br>he drowned himself in the pool. <br>His body is gone but back here on the lawn <br>his spirit continues to drool. <br><br>An Eskimo showed me a movie <br>he'd recently taken of you: <br>the poor man could hardly stop shivering <br>his lips and his fingers were blue. <br>I suppose that he froze when the wind took your clothes <br>and I guess he just never got warm. <br>But you stand there so nice, in your blizzard of ice <br>oh please let me come into the storm.]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="One Of Us Cannot Be Wrong (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)" label="One Of Us Cannot Be Wrong (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Lady_Midnight_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - Lady Midnight (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Lady_Midnight_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/" title="Leonard Cohen - Lady Midnight (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I came by myself to a very crowded place; <br>I was looking for someone who had lines in her face. <br>I found her there but she was past all concern; <br>I asked her to hold me, I said, "Lady, unfold me," <br>but she scorned me and she told me <br>I was dead and I could never return. <br>Well, I argued all night like so many have before <br>saying, "Whatever you give me, I seem to need so much more." <br>Then she pointed at me where I kneeled on her floor <br>she said, "Don't try to use me or slyly refuse me <br>just win me or lose me <br>it is this that the darkness is for." <br><br>I cried, "Oh, Lady Midnight, I fear that you grow old <br>the stars eat your body and the wind makes you cold." <br>"If we cry now," she said, "it will just be ignored." <br>So I walked through the morning, sweet early morning <br>I could hear my lady calling <br>"You've won me, you've won me, my lord <br>you've won me, you've won me, my lord <br>yes, you've won me, you've won me, my lord <br>ah, you've won me, you've won me, my lord <br>ah, you've won me, you've won me, my lord."]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="Lady Midnight (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)" label="Lady Midnight (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/You_Know_Who_I_Am_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - You Know Who I Am (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/You_Know_Who_I_Am_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/" title="Leonard Cohen - You Know Who I Am (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I cannot follow you, my love <br>you cannot follow me. <br>I am the distance you put between <br>all of the moments that we will be. <br>You know who I am <br>you've stared at the sun <br>well I am the one who loves <br>changing from nothing to one. <br><br>Sometimes I need you naked <br>sometimes I need you wild <br>I need you to carry my children in <br>and I need you to kill a child. <br><br>You know who I am... <br><br>If you should ever track me down <br>I will surrender there <br>and I will leave with you one broken man <br>whom I will teach you to repair. <br><br>You know who I am... <br><br>I cannot follow you, my love <br>you cannot follow me. <br>I am the distance you put between <br>all of the moments that we will be. <br><br>You know who I am...]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="You Know Who I Am (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)" label="You Know Who I Am (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/So_Long_Marianne_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - So Long, Marianne (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/So_Long_Marianne_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/" title="Leonard Cohen - So Long, Marianne (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come over to the window, my little darling <br>I'd like to try to read your palm. <br>I used to think I was some kind of Gypsy boy <br>before I let you take me home. <br>Now so long, Marianne, it's time that we began <br>to laugh and cry and cry and laugh about it all again. <br><br>Well you know that I love to live with you <br>but you make me forget so very much. <br>I forget to pray for the angels <br>and then the angels forget to pray for us. <br><br>Now so long, Marianne, it's time that we began ... <br><br>We met when we were almost young <br>deep in the green lilac park. <br>You held on to me like I was a crucifix <br>as we went kneeling through the dark. <br><br>Oh so long, Marianne, it's time that we began ... <br><br>Your letters they all say that you're beside me now. <br>Then why do I feel alone? <br>I'm standing on a ledge and your fine spider web <br>is fastening my ankle to a stone. <br><br>Now so long, Marianne, it's time that we began ... <br><br>For now I need your hidden love. <br>I'm cold as a new razor blade. <br>You left when I told you I was curious <br>I never said that I was brave. <br><br>Oh so long, Marianne, it's time that we began ... <br><br>Oh, you are really such a pretty one. <br>I see you've gone and changed your name again. <br>And just when I climbed this whole mountainside <br>to wash my eyelids in the rain! <br><br>Oh so long, Marianne, it's time that we began ...]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="So Long, Marianne (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)" label="So Long, Marianne (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Intro_To_So_Long_Marianne_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - Intro To So Long, Marianne (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Intro_To_So_Long_Marianne_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/" title="Leonard Cohen - Intro To So Long, Marianne (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come over to the window, my little darling <br>I'd like to try to read your palm <br>I used to think I was some kind of Gypsy boy <br>Before I let you take me home <br>Now so long, Marianne, it's time that we began <br>To laugh and cry and cry and laugh about it all again <br>Well you know that I love to live with you <br>But you make me forget so very much <br>I forget to pray for the angels <br>And then the angels forget to pray for us <br>Now so long, Marianne, it's time that we began ... <br>We met when we were almost young <br>Deep in the green lilac park <br>You held on to me like I was a crucifix <br>As we went kneeling through the dark <br>Oh so long, Marianne, it's time that we began ... <br>Your letters they all say that you're beside me now <br>Then why do I feel alone? <br>I'm standing on a ledge and your fine spider web <br>Is fastening my ankle to a stone <br>Now so long, Marianne, it's time that we began ... <br>For now I need your hidden love <br>I'm cold as a new razor blade <br>You left when I told you I was curious <br>I never said that I was brave <br>Oh so long, Marianne, it's time that we began ... <br>Oh, you are really such a pretty one <br>I see you've gone and changed your name again <br>And just when I climbed this whole mountainside <br>To wash my eyelids in the rain! <br>Oh so long, Marianne, it's time that we began]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="Intro To So Long, Marianne (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)" label="Intro To So Long, Marianne (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Bird_On_A_Wire_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/</id><title>Leonard Cohen - Bird On A Wire (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:03:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:03:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leonard_Cohen/Bird_On_A_Wire_Live_At_Isle_Of_Wight_Festival_UK/" title="Leonard Cohen - Bird On A Wire (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Like a bird on the wire <br>like a drunk in a midnight choir <br>I have tried in my way to be free. <br>Like a worm on a hook <br>like a knight from some old fashioned book <br>I have saved all my ribbons for thee. <br>If I, if I have been unkind <br>I hope that you can just let it go by. <br>If I, if I have been untrue <br>I hope you know it was never to you. <br>Like a baby, stillborn <br>like a beast with his horn <br>I have torn everyone who reached out for me. <br>But I swear by this song <br>and by all that I have done wrong <br>I will make it all up to thee. <br>I saw a beggar leaning on his wooden crutch <br>he said to me, "You must not ask for so much." <br>And a pretty woman leaning in her darkened door <br>she cried to me, "Hey, why not ask for more?" <br><br>Oh like a bird on the wire <br>like a drunk in a midnight choir <br>I have tried in my way to be free.]]></content><category term="Leonard Cohen" label="Leonard Cohen"/><category term="Bird On A Wire (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)" label="Bird On A Wire (Live At Isle Of Wight Festival, UK)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김영근/집으로_오는_길/</id><title>김영근 - 집으로 오는 길 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%98%81%EA%B7%BC/%EC%A7%91%EC%9C%BC%EB%A1%9C_%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%94_%EA%B8%B8/" title="김영근 - 집으로 오는 길 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[해가지는 그곳으로 <br>외길을 따라 <br>무거워진 발길을 재촉해 <br>어지러운 세상과 <br>그리고 사람들 <br>가끔씩은 두렵기도 했지 <br>저 반짝이는 불빛을 따라 <br>떠났던 길 <br>혹시 너무 멀리 <br>가버린건 아닌지 <br>무엇이 되려했나 <br>이험한 세상에서 난 또 <br>어떤걸 갖고싶었나 <br>집으로 오는 길 <br>저 반짝이는 불빛을 따라 <br>걸었던 길 <br>혹시 너무 멀리 <br>가버린건 아닌지 <br>무엇이 되려했나 <br>이험한 세상에서 난 또 <br>어떤걸 갖고싶었나 <br>집으로 오는 길 <br>무엇을 찾고싶었나 <br>이 넓은 세상에서 <br>어떤걸 갖고싶었나 <br>집으로 오는 길 <br>해가지는 그곳으로 <br>외길을 따라 <br>무거워진 발길을 재촉해 <br>]]></content><category term="김영근" label="김영근"/><category term="집으로 오는 길" label="집으로 오는 길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/True_Love_Deluxe_Edition/</id><title>Bastian Baker - True Love (Deluxe Edition) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/True_Love_Deluxe_Edition/" title="Bastian Baker - True Love (Deluxe Edition) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I hold your hair when you vomit <br>I shave my beard while you shit <br>I shout at you when you’re driving <br>If you don’t know true love, well this is it <br><br>True love <br>True love <br>If you don’t know true love, well this is it <br><br>True love <br>True love <br>If you don’t know true love, well this is it <br><br>You tell our sex life to your girlfriends <br>You pop my blackheads and my zits <br>When I cry at the movies, you swear to silence with a spit <br><br>True love <br>True love <br>If you don’t know true love, well this is it <br><br>True love <br>True love <br>If you don’t know true love, well this is it <br><br>I know your farts aren’t made of sugar <br>I know when your mother’s on the rag <br>You know my brother wants to fuck you <br>That doesn’t even make me mad <br><br>True love <br>True love <br>If you don’t know true love, well this is it <br><br>True love <br>True love <br>If you don’t know true love, well this is it <br><br>When the fridge is empty, that’s your fault <br>When the toilets seat is up, well that’s my fault <br>I like the color of your hair <br>You wear my t-shirt to bed <br>I think it’s time we had a kid <br><br>True love <br>True love <br>If you don’t know true love, well this is it. <br><br>True love <br>True love <br>If you don’t know true love, well this is it <br><br>This is it <br>This is it <br>If you don’t know true love, well this is it <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="True Love (Deluxe Edition)" label="True Love (Deluxe Edition)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Come_Home_Deluxe_Edition/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Come Home (Deluxe Edition) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Come_Home_Deluxe_Edition/" title="Bastian Baker - Come Home (Deluxe Edition) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Another sad love story <br>I know you think you know what’s coming <br>This time it’s not ‘bout me <br>It’s how a friend’s heart got broken <br><br>And so I guess this song’s for you <br>It’s my only way to help you <br>Don’t need to tell you to be strong <br>Don’t need to qualify what’s wrong <br><br>Still the only thing <br>That I should try to say how it would be <br>Baby definitely come home <br>Come home <br>Come home <br>Come home <br><br>Right now the phone is ringing and <br>On the other end you’re drowning in tears <br>I don’t know who must be that boy <br>Speaking with an unkown voice <br><br>In the past couple weeks devolved to love <br>This ends relationship <br>On a fast burning way <br><br>Still the only thing <br>That I should try to say how it would be <br>Baby definitely come home <br>Come home <br><br>Come home <br>Come home <br>Come home <br>Come home <br>Come home <br>Come home <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Come Home (Deluxe Edition)" label="Come Home (Deluxe Edition)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/I_Wont_Cry_Deluxe_Edition/</id><title>Bastian Baker - I Won`t Cry (Deluxe Edition) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/I_Wont_Cry_Deluxe_Edition/" title="Bastian Baker - I Won`t Cry (Deluxe Edition) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Left at home all alone <br>My inners bleed <br>The shell was blown <br>A slamming door won’t be undone <br>The damage done <br>Down to the bone <br>While I wait here all my hope declines <br>Though when you left I said I’d be fine <br>Now I realize this was the last time <br>So I pray <br>Everyday <br><br>But I won’t cry <br>When we say goodbye <br>No, I won’t cry <br>When we say goodbye <br><br>The flowers faded its colour blood <br>It takes my will to look ahead <br>My beard is grown, my hair turn grey <br>But my love is stable, never sways <br>As life’s candle slowly waste away <br>Look in the mirror, no longer see my face <br>I deserve all that hate words you felt <br>You parting words that left me to melt <br><br>But I won’t cry <br>When we say goodbye <br>No, I won’t cry <br>When we say goodbye <br><br>No, I won’t cry <br>I won’t cry <br>No, I won’t cry <br>I won’t cry <br><br>But I won’t cry <br>When we say goodbye <br>No, I won’t cry <br>When we say goodbye <br><br>No, I won’t cry <br>I won’t cry <br>No, I won’t cry <br>I won’t cry <br>？]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="I Won`t Cry (Deluxe Edition)" label="I Won`t Cry (Deluxe Edition)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/One_Last_Time_Live_Acoustic_Ver_Deluxe_Edition/</id><title>Bastian Baker - One Last Time (Live Acoustic Ver.) (Deluxe Edition) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/One_Last_Time_Live_Acoustic_Ver_Deluxe_Edition/" title="Bastian Baker - One Last Time (Live Acoustic Ver.) (Deluxe Edition) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Half-opened door <br>And I’m about to leave <br>I go in and out <br>To blow you one last kiss <br>Grab my old jacket, I’m filled with grief. <br>When all is done, what will I miss? <br><br>I’ll miss your smile coz i love your laugh <br>I’ll miss the present as it blurs into past <br><br>Before I start this mountain climb. <br><br>Let me touch you one last time. <br>Let me slip into this bed <br>Let me try out one more rhyme, <br>So you’ll leave with my song in your head. <br><br>I’m running down <br>These old wooden stairs <br>Is there a final word when nothing’s left to say? <br>I’ll let you sleep, I won’t disturb <br>Let our dreams drive our path <br><br>I’ll miss your smile coz i love your laugh <br>I’ll miss the present as it blurs into past <br>Before I start this mountain climb. <br><br>Let me touch you one last time. <br>Let me slip into this bed <br>Let me try out one more rhyme, <br>So you’ll leave with my song in your head. <br><br>Now if I could, I would stay <br>And that’s something I don’t often say <br>And I just couldn’t bear to wake you up… <br><br>Let me touch you one last time. <br>Let me slip into this bed <br>Let me try out one more rhyme, <br>So you’ll leave with my song in your head. <br><br>And I just couldn’t bear to wake you up… <br><br>Half-opened door <br>And I’m about to leave <br>I go in and out <br>To blow you one last kiss <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="One Last Time (Live Acoustic Ver.) (Deluxe Edition)" label="One Last Time (Live Acoustic Ver.) (Deluxe Edition)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Give_Me_Your_Heart/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Give Me Your Heart - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Give_Me_Your_Heart/" title="Bastian Baker - Give Me Your Heart - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Heaven can wait, I am fine down here. <br>With all the heartache and hurt we endure <br>Baby you’re getting so hard to resist <br>How I suffer this injustice <br><br>These words yet again in a written form <br>Don’t wanna make it worse than it is <br>So I swallow falling tears, they’re my last and best memories <br>Gotta keep them near my soul, with all the embers of burning coal <br><br>So give me your heart, <br>Don’t wanna fall in love with you <br>You give me your heart <br>Don’t wanna fall in love with you <br>You give me your heart <br>Don’t wanna fall in love with you <br><br>I shall rip your heart from its cavity, <br>If that’s what it takes, <br>It’s no use to resist it, <br>Coz it belongs to me <br><br>I’ll lock it in a little case <br>Oh I’m sure it will be safe <br>A hidden key somewhere far away <br>You’ll never want to find it anyway <br><br>I am your only love now for eternity <br><br>So give me your heart, <br>Don’t wanna fall in love with you <br>You give me your heart <br>Don’t wanna fall in love with you <br>You give me your heart <br>Don’t wanna fall in love with you <br><br>I’ll keep the key, somewhere far away <br>You’ll never want to find it anyway <br>So give me your heart, <br>Give me your heart <br><br>You give me your heart <br>Don’t wanna fall in love with you <br><br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Give Me Your Heart" label="Give Me Your Heart"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Song_For_EV/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Song For E.V. - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Song_For_EV/" title="Bastian Baker - Song For E.V. - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stare, at lips while they’re bouncing in sync <br>Same words yet again but I’m knocked <br>Away it’s happening <br><br>Saved, we know that we just can’t wait <br>We’ll burn into the lights <br>Before we wake up slowly. <br><br>But you said you were mine. <br>You said you were mine. <br>You said you were mine. <br>You said you were mine. <br><br>But wait, there’s so much out there we can’t lose. <br>Between empty spaces I drew the lines, dividing all we have. <br>Coz I’m not who you thought you would be with today <br>While I power through life, you’re sick and you’re pale, we’ll always be at odds to see. <br><br>Cause you said you were mine. <br>You said you were mine. <br>You said you were mine. <br>You said you were mine. <br><br>Now I’m breaking the spell, feel us aging on ice <br>Can we melt down again, instead of losing this fight? <br>Now let’s see who’ll be the last to die <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Song For E.V." label="Song For E.V."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Earrings_On_A_Table/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Earrings On A Table - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Earrings_On_A_Table/" title="Bastian Baker - Earrings On A Table - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Earrings on a table <br>That’s all I got left from you <br>And feelings I’m not able <br>To show you when I’m with you. <br><br>I don’t want to say too much <br>Let’s just keep in touch <br>And hope we’ll meet again. <br><br>I’ve been fighting so long <br>Against feelings so strong <br>I didn’t want to love you in vain <br><br>Cause after all this time <br>Of sharing thoughts of mine <br>It burns your soul inside <br>It melts my world, my pride <br><br>Earrings on a table <br>And a lock of your hair <br>Like a link to remind us of all of the things we shared. <br><br>In Bastille speria, <br>A 3 star hotel made of firey passion <br>First floor under sex attack <br>Room a hundred four. That’s where we are stuck. <br><br>Cause after all this time <br>Of sharing thoughts of mine <br>It burns your soul inside <br>It melts my world, my pride <br><br>Earrings on a table <br>Is that all I will keep of you? <br>Lying on a floor of marble <br>Exhausted I’m wrapped in you <br><br>I remember that night <br>I first started writing about you <br>Earrings on a table <br>I lost you <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Earrings On A Table" label="Earrings On A Table"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Prime/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Prime - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Prime/" title="Bastian Baker - Prime - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Collect my thoughts, and while I wait <br>I’m in between depression ‘n dream <br>Don’t lose control keep up the fight <br>this is all I think about. <br>Never thought I’d end up here. <br>Now I know. <br><br>To live the things you want to Live <br>It’s no surprise to pay the price <br>I wanted music they gave me fame. <br>I shook my ass 6 Saturdays. <br>They gave me one more reason to be on stage. <br><br>But I come from a little town <br>Respect and love are all around <br>I found a world where nothing’s real. <br>They rule it but they’ll disappear <br>Disposable I’m nothing new, another one next year <br><br>Starting to forgive the bad <br>The atmosphere that drove me mad <br>On to love and off of hate <br>So come on home I just can’t wait <br>We’ll pour the wine and sing along all night long <br><br><br>Could be good, could be bad. <br>Could not have happened <br>Don’t be sad <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Prime" label="Prime"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Never_In_Your_Town/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Never In Your Town - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Never_In_Your_Town/" title="Bastian Baker - Never In Your Town - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[New years day never was much fun for me <br>Too much fantasy. <br>I try not to judge if it’s bad or good <br>Black or white <br><br>You ask me, would you like a drink <br>Is that all you think about? <br>Yeah you tell me my Life Is great <br>Everything is in its place <br><br>I was never in your town <br>I grew up on my ship <br><br>2009 I felt detached, didn’t catch the disease <br>2010 at the ringing of twelve I burst into tears. <br><br>You ask me, would you like a drink <br>Is that all you think about? <br>Yeah you tell me my Life Is great <br>Everything is in its place <br><br>I was never in your town <br>I grew up on a ship <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Never In Your Town" label="Never In Your Town"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Kids_Off_The_Streets/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Kids Off The Streets - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Kids_Off_The_Streets/" title="Bastian Baker - Kids Off The Streets - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Feel the love they wanna share <br>See them escape from their nightmare <br>All around them there are angels who care <br>About their future. <br><br>Kids off the streets. <br><br>You think there’s a light, <br>Shining on the little things you’ve reached <br>Living in the dark, all the work you still have to achieve. <br><br>Kids off the streets. <br><br>The largest smile on earth <br>Her skin and bones are hiding hurt <br>She tries to explain that her father, well is simply missing her. <br><br>You think there’s a light, <br>Shining on the little things you’ve reached <br>Living in the dark, all the work you still have to achieve. <br><br>Kids off the streets <br><br>Remains a mystery to me <br>One which I cannot believe <br>See the kids they’re starving in the streets. <br>Humanity is still so far <br>Humanity is still so far <br><br>There’s a lot to do, <br>A lot to say, <br>To make it better than yesterday <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Kids Off The Streets" label="Kids Off The Streets"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Dirty_Thirty/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Dirty Thirty - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Dirty_Thirty/" title="Bastian Baker - Dirty Thirty - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I’d been waiting for hours？ <br>When finally you came back home, and you kissed me.？ <br>I told you mother is in the room and she’s afraid. <br>And when you found her, I heard the screams？ <br>But in the end I fell asleep, <br>And from my bedroom heard the stinging verb “to cheat” <br><br>The morning after I woke up in time to see <br>She’d been crying you were not meant to be, anymore.？？ <br><br>So take your suitcase and get out, get out <br>Take your suitcase and get out, get out.？？ <br><br>With her head in her hands she tries to hide <br>Her make up flowing down on tears？ <br>Am I too young to understand such hate? <br>Daddy can you explain to my little brain？ <br>What’s wrong with you? <br>Feel my pain!？ <br>Oh what a shame coz you said <br>We were the best family in the world <br><br>So take your suitcase and get out, get out？ <br>Take your suitcase and get out, get out.？ <br><br>But I don’t know where you are, maybe gone <br>In my head your nothing more than flesh and bones <br>I had a father who like many said goodbye <br>The age of 30 took away my lullabies <br><br>Now I’m looking back to the time <br>When everything seemed bright and full of fun <br>Your warm embrace is what I think I miss the most <br>Mother’s doing great and in her way appreciates the work she does. <br>Without you it feels like we’re a bit lost <br><br>So take your suitcase and get out, get out？ <br>Take your suitcase and get out, get out <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Dirty Thirty" label="Dirty Thirty"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/One_Last_Time/</id><title>Bastian Baker - One Last Time - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/One_Last_Time/" title="Bastian Baker - One Last Time - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Half-opened door <br>And I’m about to leave <br>I go in and out <br>To blow you one last kiss <br>Grab my old jacket, I’m filled with grief. <br>When all is done, what will I miss? <br><br>I’ll miss your smile coz i love your laugh <br>I’ll miss the present as it blurs into past <br><br>Before I start this mountain climb. <br><br>Let me touch you one last time. <br>Let me slip into this bed <br>Let me try out one more rhyme, <br>So you’ll leave with my song in your head. <br><br>I’m running down <br>These old wooden stairs <br>Is there a final word when nothing’s left to say? <br>I’ll let you sleep, I won’t disturb <br>Let our dreams drive our path <br><br>I’ll miss your smile coz i love your laugh <br>I’ll miss the present as it blurs into past <br>Before I start this mountain climb. <br><br>Let me touch you one last time. <br>Let me slip into this bed <br>Let me try out one more rhyme, <br>So you’ll leave with my song in your head. <br><br>Now if I could, I would stay <br>And that’s something I don’t often say <br>And I just couldn’t bear to wake you up… <br><br>Let me touch you one last time. <br>Let me slip into this bed <br>Let me try out one more rhyme, <br>So you’ll leave with my song in your head. <br><br>And I just couldn’t bear to wake you up… <br><br>Half-opened door <br>And I’m about to leave <br>I go in and out <br>To blow you one last kiss <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="One Last Time" label="One Last Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Bewitched_Feat_Rootwords/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Bewitched (Feat. Rootwords) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Bewitched_Feat_Rootwords/" title="Bastian Baker - Bewitched (Feat. Rootwords) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When she leaves me I’m alone <br>And if she’s with me I feel wrong <br><br>There’s something special about this girl that I belong to <br><br>Coz when I’m joyful she feels bad <br>To show that I care I say I’m sad <br><br>Sometimes I hate myself for all that love I got <br><br>She’s taking me up <br>Breaking me down <br>Making me feel so sad but then again I’m fine <br><br>There is nothing in between <br>Sometimes adult sometimes teen <br>and when in doubt, I’m a red horned angel, <br><br>I’d spend a lifetime thinking of her <br>But I’m certain that it’s worse <br>Than my curse <br>I try to runaway <br><br>She’s taking me up <br>Breaking me down <br>Making me feel so sad but then again I’m fine <br><br>Listen girl <br>I ain’t knocking the chase <br>But you got me stuck between a rock and a hard place <br>I love your beauty and grace <br>Your love I duly embrace <br>You’re truly the pace <br>The reason why I’m running this race <br>But every time I get closer <br>You close to me <br>Makes me wonder if you getting the most of me <br>Makes me wonder about the way it’s supposed to be <br>Cold summers in winter you are roasting me <br>But still I forgive <br>For you I live <br>Everything I got to give it up to ya <br>You know I’m stuck to ya <br>I’m glued on clued on to ya way of thinking <br>I sway towards you in a wink baby <br>A blink and <br>You’re the only chick I wanna run with <br>Bonnie and Clyde <br>True Romance <br>Believe me <br>You are one in a mil <br>A diamond in the ruff <br>Hard to find <br>In you I confide <br>Don’t leave me <br>I know it’s not easy <br>But… <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Bewitched (Feat. Rootwords)" label="Bewitched (Feat. Rootwords)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Follow_The_Wind/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Follow The Wind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Follow_The_Wind/" title="Bastian Baker - Follow The Wind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve closed my bedroom door <br>Turned off the lights <br>Downstairs they’re spreading some rumors <br>I don’t like <br><br>The message I’ve been waiting for two days <br>Has made it’s way, crossed oceans, it’s not too late. <br>Does the distance start to make you feel afraid? <br><br>Can you love me as I am? <br>but only see me from Time to Time? <br>Trust me just as if I were here <br>Or maybe teach me how to fly <br><br>I feel a chill running through my body <br>Every time I see your morning smile <br>Will we risk it all? <br>If it were up to me then I would take the chance. <br><br>Even if I’ve heard a thousand tales <br>Ruined by a sea, where no ship sails <br>Does the distance start to make you feel afraid? <br><br>Can you love me as I am? <br>but only see me from Time to Time? <br>Trust me just as if I were here <br>Or maybe teach me how to fly <br><br>Does the distance start to make you feel afraid? <br>Can you love me as I am? <br>but only see me from Time to Time? <br>Trust me just as if I were here <br>Or maybe teach me how to fly <br><br>Or would you throw me to the ground <br>pretending all the fault is mine <br>Don’t let the fire burning in you <br>Turn into ashes the wind once blew <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Follow The Wind" label="Follow The Wind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Youre_The_One/</id><title>Bastian Baker - You`re The One - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Youre_The_One/" title="Bastian Baker - You`re The One - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I just forget who I was <br>And now the hurting’s too strong <br>I will swear on one thing <br>That you’ll never suffer anymore <br><br>All my recent mistakes <br>Made just at the wrong time <br>It’s a sort of weakness <br><br>I don’t know why I keep acting like that <br><br>You’re the one <br><br>There is something deep inside telling me you’re the one for me <br>And with that thought in my mind, I still wish you were here <br>So hear this call through the radio <br>To set your minds free, and start to be the one who’s gonna make me learn to breathe <br><br>Because <br>You’re the one for me <br>The only one for me <br><br>Just to know that you’re gone <br>Reminds me where I went wrong <br>I’m crying at the lakefront <br>I know you’re brave and I apologize again <br><br>What I feel is always <br>The same you know it won’t change <br>You’re strong and I’ll be sorry <br>Until the day you’re coming back to me my love <br><br>You’re the one <br><br>There is something deep inside telling me you’re the one for me <br>And with that thought in my mind, I still wish you were here <br>So hear this call through the radio <br>To set your minds free, and start to be the one Who’s gonna make me learn to breathe <br><br>Because <br>You’re the one for me <br>The only one for me <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="You`re The One" label="You`re The One"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Leaving_Tomorrow/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Leaving Tomorrow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Leaving_Tomorrow/" title="Bastian Baker - Leaving Tomorrow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Blame it on our sorrow <br>Smiles have disappeared <br>Who could be our hero <br>Anyone here <br>I’m sorry for the love you lost <br>Yeah I'm sorry for the love you lost <br>We’re leaving tomorrow <br>and everyone knows <br>That the memories <br>we have are as precious as gold <br>One bag no shoes and little hope <br>Bombs broke down our home <br>I leave it all <br>The days are hot and the nights cold <br>Sickness of all sort I leave it all <br>I’m sorry for the love you lost <br>Yeah I'm sorry for the love you lost <br>We’re leaving tomorrow <br>and everyone knows <br>That the memories <br>we have are as precious as gold <br>I’m saying goodbye <br>Saving my tears <br>coz I ain’t gonna cry <br>In front of you <br>So I'm saying goodbye <br>I’ll think of you once <br>I've started to fly <br>I’m sorry for the love you lost <br>Yeah I’m sorry for the love you lost <br>We’re leaving tomorrow <br>and everyone knows <br>That the memories <br>we have are as precious as gold <br>We’re leaving tomorrow <br>and everyone knows <br>Blame it on our sorrow <br>Smiles have disappeared <br>Who could be our hero <br>Anyone here <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Leaving Tomorrow" label="Leaving Tomorrow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/79_Clinton_Street/</id><title>Bastian Baker - 79 Clinton Street - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:04:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:04:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/79_Clinton_Street/" title="Bastian Baker - 79 Clinton Street - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If you take my hand I’ll be the king of the world <br>And if you take my hand you’d be my lovely girl <br>If you take my hand I’ll be the king of the world <br>And if you take my hand… <br><br>Lower east side, the midnight lights. <br>A man is hangin’, the law’s not on his side <br>Tonight I won’t buy his pills. <br>I guess I spent too much on my Big Apple bill <br><br>A friend and I went out for dinner. <br>I had Italian food; he went with a burger. <br>With spicy sauce on a precipice of lips, <br>He’s raring to go to the club I already miss. <br><br>If you take my hand I’ll be the king of the world <br>And if you take my hand you’d be my lovely girl. <br>If you take my hand I’ll be the king of the world <br>And if you take my hand, <br>Well, you take my hand. <br><br>We’re walking fast, Meatpacking is waiting. <br>In a yellow cab we start flirting. <br>She’s sweet and sexy, my friend can’t take her charm, <br>Let’s see who’ll be the first snuggled in her arms. <br><br>Eleven dollars, I can afford this, <br>I gave a good tip, like I’d promised. <br>Elevator elevates us to the highest floor, <br>In as second we’ll be knocking on the club’s front door. <br>I think back to my life and I beg. <br>Give me more! <br><br>If you take my hand I’ll be the king of the world <br>And if you take my hand you’d be my lovely girl. <br>If you take my hand I’ll be the king of the world <br>If you take my hand, <br>Well, you take my hand <br>Blame it on our sorrow <br>Smiles have disappeared <br>Who could be our hero? <br>Anyone here? <br><br>I’m sorry for the love you lost <br>Yeah I m sorry for the love you lost <br><br>We’re leaving tomorrow and everyone knows <br>That the memories we have are as precious as gold <br><br>One bag, no shoes and little hope <br>Bombs broke down our home <br>I leave it all <br><br>The days are hot and the nights cold <br>Sickness of all sort <br>I leave it all <br><br>I’m sorry for the love you lost <br>Yeah I m sorry for the love you lost <br><br>We’re leaving tomorrow and everyone knows <br>That the memories we have are as precious as gold <br><br>I’m saying goodbye <br>Saving my tears coz I ain’t gonna cry <br>In front of you. <br>So I m saying goodbye. I’ll think of you once I ve started to fly. <br><br>I’m sorry for the love you lost <br>Yeah I’m sorry for the love you lost <br><br>We’re leaving tomorrow and everyone knows <br>That the memories we have are as precious as gold <br><br>Blame it on our sorrow <br>Smiles have disappeared <br>Who could be our hero? <br>Anyone here? <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="79 Clinton Street" label="79 Clinton Street"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Hallelujah_Platinum_Edition/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Hallelujah (Platinum Edition) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Hallelujah_Platinum_Edition/" title="Bastian Baker - Hallelujah (Platinum Edition) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve heard there was a secret chord <br>that David played and it pleased the Lord <br>but you don’t really care for music, do you? <br>it goes like this the fourth, the fifth <br>the minor fall and the major lift <br>the baffled king composing Hallelujah <br><br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br><br>Your faith was strong but you needed proof <br>you saw her bathing on the roof <br>her beauty in the moonlight overthrew you <br>she tied you to the kitchen chair <br>she broke your throne, and she cuts your hair <br>and from your lips she drew the Hallelujah <br><br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br><br>Maybe there is a God above <br>but all I’ve ever learned from love was <br>how to shoot somebody who outdrew you <br>but it’s not to cry that you hear at night <br>as not somebody who see the light, <br>it’s a colder and it’s broken Hallelujah <br><br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Hallelujah (Platinum Edition)" label="Hallelujah (Platinum Edition)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Well_Follow_You_Platinum_Edition/</id><title>Bastian Baker - We`ll Follow You (Platinum Edition) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Well_Follow_You_Platinum_Edition/" title="Bastian Baker - We`ll Follow You (Platinum Edition) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We are here today, to support our favorite team？ <br>So stand up and get ready for the final scream？ <br>If you’re in the place or just behind you’re TV screen？ <br>It’s all the same (united as one) we sing？？ <br><br>It will be hard and we’ll sweat a lot for sure？ <br>They have to know that our passion is pure <br>So stand up and shout and our heart is beaten fast <br>I wanna hear the crowd and see everybody sing ？？ <br><br>We fight, we win, we follow you <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="We`ll Follow You (Platinum Edition)" label="We`ll Follow You (Platinum Edition)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/The_Road_Feat_Aliose_Platinum_Edition/</id><title>Bastian Baker - The Road (Feat. Aliose) (Platinum Edition) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/The_Road_Feat_Aliose_Platinum_Edition/" title="Bastian Baker - The Road (Feat. Aliose) (Platinum Edition) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[At first we were only sailing <br>Through the blowing wind and the blue seas. <br>Horizons without clouds <br><br>With the magic in our eyes <br>And the whole world would say <br>Look at these kids: “they’re shining bright”. <br><br>As the days were passing by, <br>The falling rain would touch the fools, <br>They didn’t think it could happen <br>They’d built their castle of stone <br>And when the rain became a storm, <br>Then she began to cry, <br>In her teared blurry eyes her nightmare starts <br><br>This is finally where the road ends <br>I have to thank you for the trip <br>It’s been a beautiful one <br>Though I have to admit <br><br>This is finally where the road ends <br>And I let you go away <br>I let you be the one <br>That you have become <br><br>Love’s a fight and each one knows how to play, <br>A little storm will never blow their love away. <br>A smaller sun has just arrived and they look in each other’s eyes, <br>Thinking “yes we made it through, it’s not time to say goodbye” <br><br>Flying for a little moment lost in heaven, <br>In peace and harmony, as if nothing had happened. <br>Till’ there’s a wound in shorty’s heart and she starts losing blood, <br>He tries to help her all he can, but their stone’s made of sand <br><br>This is finally where the road ends <br>I have to thank you for the trip <br>It’s been a beautiful one <br>Though I have to admit <br><br>This is finally where the road ends <br>And I let you go away <br>I let you be the one <br>That you have become <br><br>This is finally where the road ends <br>I have to thank you for the trip <br>It’s been a beautiful one <br>Though I have to admit <br><br>Something solid as we were <br>Yeah is such a special thing <br>There are many others out there <br>I hope you’ll find someone to sing <br>I hope you’ll find someone to sing for you <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="The Road (Feat. Aliose) (Platinum Edition)" label="The Road (Feat. Aliose) (Platinum Edition)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Tomorrow_May_Not_Be_Better_Live_Acoustic_Ver_Platinum_Edition/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Tomorrow May Not Be Better (Live Acoustic Ver.) (Platinum Edition) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Tomorrow_May_Not_Be_Better_Live_Acoustic_Ver_Platinum_Edition/" title="Bastian Baker - Tomorrow May Not Be Better (Live Acoustic Ver.) (Platinum Edition) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It is hard to describe how I feel inside <br>It’s even worse to see nobody by my side <br>It is four in the morning I just shot the TV <br>I’m going to bed leaving my dreams on MTV <br><br>I got no reason to wake up, tomorrow I could sleep, <br>All day or start something, somehow coz sunrise and sunset will come forever <br>My illness leaves me weak-kneed and fevered. <br>It is not only a headache: I also feel afraid <br>I worry all the time when the panic attacks I’m scared <br>I feel like my soul is empty, my life’s deprived of sense. <br>I always want to scream out as loudly as I can <br><br>It is hard to describe how I feel inside <br>It’s even worse to see nobody by my side <br>It is four in the morning I just shot the TV <br>I’m going to bed leaving my dreams of MTV <br><br>I’m afraid of the future and I regret the past. <br>And when I see those old pictures it’s all gone by so fast <br>Only a quarter of my life up but all hope is dead <br>I’ll be confined to an office; it’s not what I had planned. <br><br>In this abyss of what’s to come I don’t know where I stand. <br>Someone should stretch out a rope now, stretch out a rope! <br>I put myself in a big mess, I’m not sure I understand what people talk about <br>What they talk about!! <br><br>It is hard to describe how I feel inside <br>It’s even worse to see nobody by my side <br>It is four in the morning I just shot the TV <br>I’m going to bed leaving my dreams of MTV <br><br>Money, Fame and Fashion what is it all worth? <br>If when you go out, you’re not happy with your birth. <br>It’s now five in the morning, I think this song’s over <br>I wonder if I’ll wake up tomorrow may not be better <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Tomorrow May Not Be Better (Live Acoustic Ver.) (Platinum Edition)" label="Tomorrow May Not Be Better (Live Acoustic Ver.) (Platinum Edition)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Song_About_A_Priest/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Song About A Priest - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Song_About_A_Priest/" title="Bastian Baker - Song About A Priest - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I never knew a girl could be <br>The brand new thing that I’d always needed <br>It feels so strange to be alone, <br>And on my own, once again. <br><br>You’ve been gone for so long that if I saw you <br>I would deny the pain you made me go through <br><br>You’ve been gone for so long that if I saw you <br>I would deny the tears I shed out for you <br><br>I know that I love her <br>I know she loves me too <br>But I am just a servant <br>We’re not allowed to be two. <br><br>She arrives. <br><br>Standing here, <br>Right in front of the lake <br>And I feel like <br>You were just here. <br><br>You’ve been gone for so long that if I saw you <br>I would deny the pain you made me go through <br><br>You’ve been gone for so long that if I saw you <br>I would deny the tears I shed out for you <br><br>I know that I love her <br>I know she loves me too <br>But I am just a servant <br>We’re not allowed to be two <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Song About A Priest" label="Song About A Priest"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Love_Machine/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Love Machine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Love_Machine/" title="Bastian Baker - Love Machine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She came to this town, no money, not a pound. <br>Illegal traveler she is a criminal lover. <br>She’s lost never found, took to the underground <br>When I saw her the first time, she made me lose my mind. <br><br>And I don’t really want to fall in love again <br>Coz with that type of girl you’ve got to understand <br>She’ll never be your friend; she’ll leave you in the end; lost in pain. <br><br>Because she’s here to make the money, <br>She knows that she’s pretty <br>She’s a heartbreaker, a criminal lover <br><br>And she’s here to make the money, <br>She knows that she’s pretty <br>She’s a heartbreaker, a criminal lover <br><br>She’s a love, a love, a love <br>She’s a love, a love, a love machine <br>Oh she’s a love, a love, a love <br>A love, a love, a love machine. <br><br>She works by the night yet she’s at peace with her heart <br>She has to fight to survive, police can always arrive. <br>But she don’t lose her cool when they’re passing by, <br>She’s not a fool she’ll use the money to get high. <br><br>And I don’t really want to fall in love again <br>Coz with that type of girl you’ve got to understand <br>She’ll never be your friend; she’ll leave you in the end; lost in pain. <br><br>Because she’s here to make the money, <br>She knows that she’s pretty <br>She’s a heartbreaker, a criminal lover <br><br>And she’s here to make the money, <br>She knows that she’s pretty <br>She’s a heartbreaker, a criminal lover <br><br>She’s a love, a love, a love <br>She’s a love, a love, a love machine <br>Oh she’s a love, a love, a love <br>A love, a love, a love machine. <br><br>Situation’s not that clear I think <br>That she may disappear <br>So I’m searching the town to save her body from crime <br>Yeah she’s a dangerous one <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Love Machine" label="Love Machine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Planet_Earth/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Planet Earth - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Planet_Earth/" title="Bastian Baker - Planet Earth - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hello you I’m back again, it’s time to talk with you again <br>I’ve travelled the world and now the journey’s over, is over. <br><br>I’ve got to tell you what I’ve heard <br>I’ve got to tell you what I’ve smelled <br>I’ve got to tell you what I’ve seen <br>What I’ve seen <br><br>I’ve seen the world and it’s no longer the same <br>Deathbed of pollution and the world is dying <br><br>And I hear the world shouting <br>And I hear the world’s shout <br><br>Everywhere and all the time, <br>Man destroying everything, <br>Looking only for his money, <br>For his money <br><br>For every tree chopped to the ground <br>Another house is shooting up <br>Now we’ll never hear the sound <br>Of the songbird’s joyous ballad <br><br>I’ve seen the world and it’s no longer the same <br>Deathbed of pollution and the world is dying <br><br>And I hear the world shouting <br>And I hear the world’s shout <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Planet Earth" label="Planet Earth"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/With_You_Gone/</id><title>Bastian Baker - With You Gone - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/With_You_Gone/" title="Bastian Baker - With You Gone - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was counting the days we’d been together <br><br>When I heard the car starting to drive <br>And the screaming wheels were announcing <br>That maybe this time it’s definite that you will be free <br><br>But you, were the one <br>You, will remain <br>You… <br><br>I took a look outside and I saw you had gone and in the empty hall <br>There were none of your shoes left <br>I am right she won’t come back <br>So I’m starting to run, <br>Hoping that I can get to… <br><br>You were the one <br>You will remain <br>You… <br><br>Standing on the edge of the lonely, windy street <br>Thinking of it all, yeah of what you just did to me… <br><br>Carry me in your heart, <br>You know you’re never gonna leave mine. <br>I’m a desperado walking, into the night… <br><br>The bar tender is my new best friend <br>And the jukebox my enemy coz it always plays the songs of our past <br>My bed will not be too small anymore, <br>Do you realize, you had given a meaning to life? <br><br>You were the one <br>You will remain <br>You… <br><br>Standing on the edge of the lonely, windy street <br>Thinking of it all, yeah of what you just did to me… <br><br>Carry me in your heart, <br>You know you’re never gonna leave mine. <br>I’m a desperado walking, into the night… <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="With You Gone" label="With You Gone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Smile/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Smile - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Smile/" title="Bastian Baker - Smile - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It’s crazy, I don’t know what is happening to me <br>I feel as if a tragedy has befallen my life <br>And now I’m crying <br><br>Smile, baby just a smile, smile… <br>Smile, baby just a smile, smile… <br><br>I feel alone but I’d love to be more and more on my own, <br>Go out and walk for a while and cry; listen to some of your songs. <br><br>Smile, babe just smile, smile… <br>Smile, baby just a smile, smile… <br><br>I won’t get married, or at least I’ll think of you everyday <br>Coz I won’t love someone else that’s for sure ？ what did you say? <br><br>Smile, babe just a smile, smile… <br>Smile, baby just a smile, smile… <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Smile" label="Smile"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Having_Fun/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Having Fun - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Having_Fun/" title="Bastian Baker - Having Fun - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Today is going to be the day <br>You will forget all your trouble. <br>I’ll give you a chance <br>For one day and one night. <br>I know that you got your reasons, <br>It’s not my problem, <br>The only thing I want, <br>Is to forgive it all right now. <br>So take your problems and just, <br>Put them away, put them away, put them away, <br>Take your problems and just, <br>Put them away, put them away, put them away. <br><br>And it’s, one day, one night, <br>Fantasy turns real life for you. <br>You’ll do everything you want, <br>It’s a special day until the break of dawn <br>You’re just, havin’ fun, havin’ fun, havin’ fun. <br><br>The world today is only wrapped in war <br>I give you the chance to forget it, forget it. <br>Come to the place I told you, <br>Come and take pleasure that’s what I want for you. <br>Then it’s one day and you’ll be back to your shame <br>One night and you’ll be back to your blaming games <br>Be together, no tomorrow, turn seconds into hours, baby, let’s go <br><br>And it’s, one day, one night, <br>Fantasy turns real life for you. <br>You’ll do everything you want, <br>A special day until the break of dawn <br>You’re just, havin’ fun, havin’ fun, havin’ fun. <br><br>One day, one night, you wanna day wanna night. <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Having Fun" label="Having Fun"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/I_Still_Dont_Realize/</id><title>Bastian Baker - I Still Don`t Realize - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/I_Still_Dont_Realize/" title="Bastian Baker - I Still Don`t Realize - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Try to sleep in my car <br>Dad’s gone, he left me in parts. <br>I don’t know if he’s going to return. <br>No one more than myself <br>Collect my thoughts and forgive it <br>Guess I’m not a good one <br>2 a.m. and I’m still awake. <br>Since the moment he left me with no key, <br>Thoughts have flooded vacant minds. <br><br>I still don’t realize <br>I need to take a new start <br>So diverged from the dreams I had in my head <br>I don’t recognize myself, <br>I think like a man whose future is passed him <br><br>My mind is sick and empty I know, <br>I seek the way I’d better go. <br>Lies they bring nothing at all, <br>So kill your fears and your ghosts <br>Time to free your soul <br>I’ve got some problems and I want to cry <br>I know too well we’re short on time <br>Why do we have to live and try to work until night <br>When we know that we all die? <br><br>I still don’t realize <br>I need to take a new start <br>So diverged from the dreams I had in my head <br>I don’t recognize myself, <br>I think like a man whose future is passed him <br><br>Now I think I realize, <br>I need to take a new start. <br>I’m not that far from the dreams I had in my head. <br>I will recognize myself, <br>I won’t think like a man whose future is passed him <br>It’ll all be good. <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="I Still Don`t Realize" label="I Still Don`t Realize"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Tomorrow_May_Not_Be_Better/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Tomorrow May Not Be Better - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Tomorrow_May_Not_Be_Better/" title="Bastian Baker - Tomorrow May Not Be Better - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It is hard to describe <br>how I feel inside <br>It’s even worse to see <br>nobody by my side <br>It is four in the morning <br>I just shot the TV <br>I’m going to bed <br>leaving my dreams on MTV <br>I got no reason to wake up <br>tomorrow I could sleep <br>All day or start something <br>somehow coz sunrise <br>and sunset will come forever <br>My illness leaves me <br>weak-kneed and fevered <br>It is not only a headache <br>I also feel afraid <br>I worry all the time <br>when the panic attacks <br>I’m scared <br>I feel like my soul is empty <br>my life’s deprived of sense <br>I always want to scream out <br>as loudly as I can <br>It is hard to describe <br>how I feel inside <br>It’s even worse to see <br>nobody by my side <br>It is four in the morning <br>I just shot the TV <br>I’m going to bed <br>leaving my dreams of MTV <br>I’m afraid of the future <br>and I regret the past <br>And when I see those old pictures <br>it’s all gone by so fast <br>Only a quarter of my life up <br>but all hope is dead <br>I’ll be confined to an office <br>it’s not what I had planned <br>In this abyss of what’s to come <br>I don’t know where I stand <br>Someone should stretch <br>out a rope now <br>stretch out a rope <br>I put myself in a big mess <br>I’m not sure I understand <br>what people talk about <br>What they talk about <br>It is hard to describe <br>how I feel inside <br>It’s even worse to see <br>nobody by my side <br>It is four in the morning <br>I just shot the TV <br>I’m going to bed <br>leaving my dreams of MTV <br>Money Fame and Fashion <br>what is it all worth <br>If when you go out <br>you’re not happy <br>with your birth <br>It’s now five in the morning <br>I think this song’s over <br>I wonder <br>if I’ll wake up tomorrow <br>may not be better <br>It’s now five in the morning <br>I think this song’s over <br>I wonder <br>if I’ll wake up tomorrow <br>may not be better <br>It’s now five in the morning <br>I think this song’s over <br>I wonder <br>if I’ll wake up tomorrow <br>may not be better <br>It is hard to describe <br>how I feel inside <br>It’s even worse to see <br>nobody by my side <br>It is four in the morning <br>I just shot the TV <br>I’m going to bed <br>leaving my dreams on MTV <br>It is hard to describe <br>how I feel inside <br>It’s even worse to see <br>nobody by my side <br>It is four in the morning <br>I just shot the TV <br>I’m going to bed <br>leaving my dreams on MTV <br>It is hard to describe <br>how I feel inside <br>It’s even worse to see <br>nobody by my side <br>It is four in the morning <br>I just shot the TV <br>I’m going to bed <br>leaving my dreams on MTV <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Tomorrow May Not Be Better" label="Tomorrow May Not Be Better"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Nobody_Should_Die_Alone/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Nobody Should Die Alone - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Nobody_Should_Die_Alone/" title="Bastian Baker - Nobody Should Die Alone - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If you think that your end is near <br>When your headache is worse than any passed year <br>When the only feeling left is fear <br>All drive to escape disappeared <br><br>Nobody should die alone, make a wish before you’re gone <br>And ask your old friends to share the past before the end <br><br>Had a great life, but stayed unknown, unknown. <br>Everyday spent waiting for the ringing of a phone <br>Or some visit to flavour your blending days, bland day. <br>Seems like the sky has turned grey <br><br>Nobody should die alone, make a wish before you’re gone <br>And ask you’re old friends to share the past before the end <br><br>Take the step, push the door, <br>And if you fall don’t lie on the floor <br>Memories in pictures they’re hanging on the wall <br>Don’t wait for the others to come <br>Coz they can’t see what you’ve become <br>You’re speaking slowly, slowly rotting <br>Did I just see an angel pass above you’re head? <br><br>Nobody should die alone, make a wish before you’re gone <br>And ask your old friends to share the past before the end <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Nobody Should Die Alone" label="Nobody Should Die Alone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Lucky/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Lucky - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Lucky/" title="Bastian Baker - Lucky - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You say you are, never gonna leave me. <br>Like a child, you will always help me <br>Through the storms, I like the way <br>You stand by me. <br>I know I’m lucky <br><br>Wonder when, wonder when you saw me <br>Crying tears, certainly it’s been a <br>Couple years, the brighter side of life has shone <br>That I’m not wrong <br><br>That everything I thought I <br>Would have to do to do right <br>Is never gonna be what it was planned to be, coz I’m lucky <br>The days are shining happy <br>The pain forever missing <br>From when I wake, throughout the day <br>A lasting smile upon my face <br><br>Lucky I’m lucky and I hope I’ll always be <br>Lucky all my life so nobody <br>Will ever need to worry about me <br>I’m living free <br><br>Lucky star, I know it’s shining somewhere <br>In the sky high above in thin air <br>Watching down, to ensure that I’m all right <br>I feel at peace <br><br>That everything I thought I <br>Would have to do to do right <br>Is never gonna be what it was planned to be, coz I’m lucky <br>The days are shining happy <br>The pain forever missing <br>From when I wake, throughout the day <br>A lasting smile upon my face <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Lucky" label="Lucky"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Id_Sing_For_You/</id><title>Bastian Baker - I`d Sing For You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Id_Sing_For_You/" title="Bastian Baker - I`d Sing For You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Follow me, follow me you know, that I could be the one for you <br>I could save you from your hurt, <br>You could leave this crazy Earth <br>When society’s too dirty for your dreams <br>And you’re unhappy with your day-to-day life, <br>You could be my other half <br><br>I’d sing for you <br>You’d sing for me <br>And the distance is not true <br>When we know it’s me and you <br>I’d sing for you <br>You’d sing for me <br>We’d be sharing all and more <br>We would love without discord <br><br>Leave a town, leave a town of fear <br>Your enemies are hiding near <br>Mountains are our empty spaces, there will be no one who’ll say <br>“I got to work I’m growing old <br>And all I’m looking for is gold” <br>There you’ll hear the silence sing <br>I swear it’s a perfect thing <br><br>I’d sing for you <br>You’d sing for me <br>And the distance is not true <br>When we know it’s me and you <br>I’d sing for you <br>You’d sing for me <br>We’d be sharing all and more <br>We would love without discord <br><br>Just the two of us lost somewhere in the US <br>Would be a dream come true… <br>I’ll ride the train, the bus, take a plane I’ll never stop <br>Just to be with you… <br><br>I’d sing for you <br>You’d sing for me <br>We’d be sharing all and more <br>We would love without discord <br>I’d sing for you <br>You’d sing for me <br>And the distance is not true, when we know it’s me and you <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="I`d Sing For You" label="I`d Sing For You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Colorful_Hospital/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Colorful Hospital - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Colorful_Hospital/" title="Bastian Baker - Colorful Hospital - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t be sad it’s just a normal goodbye <br>I’ll be better where I will be <br>You won’t have to take care of me <br><br>Coz I have tried to live, <br>I have tried to escape reality <br>But it’s too hard, <br>You won’t have to take care of me <br><br>The only thing I’m seeing clearly now <br>Is that I’ll probably end in a colorful hospital <br><br>It’s not that I don’t love you <br>It’s not that I don’t trust you <br>I just want to go somewhere else <br>You won’t have to take care of me <br><br>Coz ever since I was born <br>I have tried every therapy <br>Every remedy <br>So you won’t have to take care of me <br><br>The only thing I’m seeing clearly now <br>Is that I’ll probably end in a colorful hospital <br><br>My future is behind me <br>And I don’t see yet what could make me feel happy here <br>You won’t have to take care of me <br><br>A hospital is waiting, <br>I just have to walk up the stairs <br>And wait, see and stare <br>You won’t have to take care of me. <br><br>The only thing I’m seeing clearly now <br>Is that I’ll probably end in a colorful hospital <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Colorful Hospital" label="Colorful Hospital"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Two_Thousand_Years_Feat_BJ_Scott/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Two Thousand Years (Feat. BJ Scott) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Two_Thousand_Years_Feat_BJ_Scott/" title="Bastian Baker - Two Thousand Years (Feat. BJ Scott) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Walking through seasons <br>Stumbling on reasons <br>Learning those lessons <br>One step at the time <br>Consider the past <br>How the future’s cast <br>Making decisions between water and wine <br><br>And when you die will anybody care? <br>A few are gonna cry <br>‘Coz they are scared <br><br>‘Coz there's two thousand motherfucking years behind us <br>So whatever you tell me, it's never gonna hurt me ‘coz I know, I know that you don't know <br><br>Sun fades away <br>Lose the light of the day <br>So on it goes <br>And I wonder how long <br><br>How long, how long, until our bodies turn to clay? <br>No gods left to obey <br>No prayers left to pray <br><br>‘Coz there's two thousand motherfucking years behind us <br>So whatever you tell me, it's never gonna hurt me 'coz I know, I know that you don't know <br><br>And when you're gonna die <br>You know I’m gonna care <br>I know I’m gonna cry <br>‘Coz I’m so scared <br><br>‘Coz there's two thousand motherfucking years behind us <br>So whatever you tell me, it's never gonna hurt me ‘coz I know, I know that you don't know <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Two Thousand Years (Feat. BJ Scott)" label="Two Thousand Years (Feat. BJ Scott)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Tell_The_Night/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Tell The Night - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Tell_The_Night/" title="Bastian Baker - Tell The Night - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I won't lie <br>If you're asking me <br>Do I trust my own memories <br>Are they lies if they come from me? <br>Or are they blurred by what I want to see? <br><br>Go on tell the night <br>That it's meant to be the day <br>How the moonlight was our guide <br>When the sun refused to stay <br>It's getting hard to trust my mind <br>As the past will always fade <br>So go on tell the night <br>That it's meant to be the day <br><br>Thinking back <br>Only makes it worse <br>Focusing makes all your thoughts disperse <br>It's when I’m tested that I realize <br>What will hurt me <br>Will reduce in size <br><br>Go on tell the night <br>That it's meant to be the day <br>How the moonlight was our guide <br>When the sun refused to stay <br>It's getting hard to trust my mind <br>As the past will always fade <br>So go on tell the night <br>That it's meant to be the day <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Tell The Night" label="Tell The Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Rainbow/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Rainbow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Rainbow/" title="Bastian Baker - Rainbow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It’s over now, the curtain call on your so-called love affair <br>You love me you say, and I don’t feel the same way, and this is what’s hard about this case <br><br>How am I supposed to hold you tight? <br><br>You’re like a rainbow, you’re like a rainbow <br>And our love casts a shadow on our needs <br>Rainbow, we’re like a rainbow <br>Where the hues separate, and never fuse <br><br>It’s over now, the tears have fallen down, on what you called our love <br>You hate me you say, and I don’t feel the same way, but this is no surprise in such a case <br><br>How am I supposed to hold you tight? <br><br>You’re like a rainbow, you’re like a rainbow <br>And our love casts a shadow on our needs <br>Rainbow, we’re like a rainbow <br>Where the hues separate, and never fuse <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Rainbow" label="Rainbow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Charlie_From_Sydney/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Charlie From Sydney - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Charlie_From_Sydney/" title="Bastian Baker - Charlie From Sydney - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You walked into a coffee shop where it all came undone <br>On a normal Sunday you got shot, and now you’re gone <br>You didn’t ask anyone for anything <br>At the wrong place at the wrong time, I didn’t know you, but still I cry <br><br>I get lost in the small things of life <br>My troubles they pale to your strife <br>I’m angry, I’m sad, but I’m fine <br>I’m fine, and I’m safe, but I cry <br><br>The empty eyes of your killer are staring down at me <br>My tears are all for you, my dear Charlie <br>Who didn’t ask anyone for anything <br>At the wrong place at the wrong time, I didn’t know you, but still I cry <br><br>I get lost in the small things of life <br>My troubles they pale to your strife <br>I’m angry, I’m sad, but I’m fine <br>I’m fine, and I’m safe, but I cry <br><br>You didn’t ask anyone for anything <br>At the wrong place at the wrong time, I didn’t know you, but still I cry <br><br>I get lost in the small things of life <br>My troubles they pale to your strife <br>I’m angry, I’m sad, but I’m fine <br>I’m fine, and I’m safe, but I cry <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Charlie From Sydney" label="Charlie From Sydney"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Aint_No_Love/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Ain`t No Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Aint_No_Love/" title="Bastian Baker - Ain`t No Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There ain't no sunshine if you hide behind a mountain <br>There ain't no air if you're stuck under the sea <br>There ain’t no grass if you never want to leave the buildings and the city <br>And there ain't no love if you don't seek <br><br>There ain't no love <br><br>There ain't no religion if you believe in people <br>There ain't no crisis if at least you’re trying to share <br>There ain't no drama if you’re living in the present <br>And there ain't no love if you don't seek <br><br>There ain't no love <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Ain`t No Love" label="Ain`t No Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/We_Are_The_Ones_FF/</id><title>Bastian Baker - We Are The Ones (#FF) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/We_Are_The_Ones_FF/" title="Bastian Baker - We Are The Ones (#FF) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I’m going back to the place I hate <br>This time you’ll be standing next to me <br>With all the judging from their little thrones <br>This time I won’t accept the meatless bone <br>I’m going back to the arrogance <br>They only care to make the people dance <br>With broken promises and gossips spun <br>This time I’m not trusting anyone <br><br>They’re talking louder than we are <br>They’re more important than we are <br>They’re better looking than we are <br>But we are the ones who can see through the dark <br><br>I’m going back to the place I hate <br>Despite their treatment like I’m royalty <br>If you’ve been wondering just where I’ve been <br>Turn on the TV, and look carefully <br>It’s pessimism pours from everywhere <br>No one can ever stand the atmosphere <br>Beyond your lazy ways and sad complaints <br>You’ve got nobody but yourself to blame <br><br>They’re talking louder than we are <br>They’re more important than we are <br>They’re better looking than we are <br>But we are the ones who can see through the dark <br><br>Talking, talking, talking… <br>all the glamorous people they know, <br>people they know <br>Talking, talking, talking… <br>about the people they saw, people they saw <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="We Are The Ones (#FF)" label="We Are The Ones (#FF)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Planned_It_All/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Planned It All - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:05:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:05:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Planned_It_All/" title="Bastian Baker - Planned It All - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s lose faith, and keep it all <br>Count our blessings, less is more <br>I just wanna say I'm sorry <br><br>We planned it all <br>Built unbreakable walls <br>Then I ruined it on my own <br>You took the fall <br>We had it all <br>Let me ruin it all alone <br>Now you are safe, when I'm so lost <br><br>In for Life, but out for more <br>Behind the bars of our sorrow <br>I just wanna say I'm sorry <br>Couldn’t hear your words <br>Oh telling me it hurts <br>I just wanna hear you say you' re sorry <br><br>We planned it all <br>Built unbreakable walls <br>Then I ruined it on my own <br>You took the fall <br>We had it all <br>Let me wounded it all alone <br>Now you are safe, when I'm so lost <br><br>I’m sick of driving where's the end <br>I’m sick of trying can't pretend <br><br>We planned it all <br>Built unbreakable walls <br>Then I ruined it on my own <br>You took the fall <br>We had it all <br>Let me wounded it all alone <br>Now you are safe, when I'm so lost <br><br>Let’s lose faith, and keep it all <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Planned It All" label="Planned It All"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/I_Want_You/</id><title>Bastian Baker - I Want You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:06:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:06:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/I_Want_You/" title="Bastian Baker - I Want You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Her hair, and make up almost done <br>I sit, and wait I’m playing dumb <br>It ain't no shame, just sacrifice <br>And anyway, I knew the price <br><br>On and on keep the tension strong <br>Sexual where you belong <br>On and on your hips are begging me on <br>Side to side, you’re right <br><br>I want you <br>I need you <br>I’m wishing you <br>Would think it too <br><br>Can't touch you like a bruise <br>Although I’m right here I’m unused <br>I don't know what I should do <br>While you try on your high heel shoes <br>You’re working hard, I’m hardly working <br>Just a jester, a waiter waiting <br>Trying to seek adrenaline <br>But all I’ve got are mixed up feelings <br><br>On and on keep the tension strong <br>Sexual where you belong <br>On and on your hips are begging me on <br>Side to side, you’re right <br><br>I want you <br>I need you <br>I’m wishing you <br>Would think it too <br><br>Keep going, keep going, keep going, don't stop it now <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="I Want You" label="I Want You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Everything_We_Do/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Everything We Do - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:06:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:06:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Everything_We_Do/" title="Bastian Baker - Everything We Do - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A playground with no kids on it <br>In the middle of Berlin <br>After another drunken night I sit <br>On a bench, and I begin <br>To wonder why I’m half asleep <br>Why my head hurts so bad <br>I wonder if I I’m just a creep <br>Trying not to be mad <br><br>It’s like with everything I do <br>The beginning’s so exciting <br>In the middle part I doubt <br>And in the end I’m disappointed <br>With you <br><br>I wanna clear, and clean my thoughts <br>‘coz it's turned into obsession <br>And baby what I hate the most <br>Is that your my first addiction <br>It's like every time I blink <br>I’m shocked, and amazed <br>But when I start to drink <br>It's only dreams that I chase <br><br>It’s like with everything I do <br>The beginning’s so exciting <br>In the middle part I doubt <br>And in the end I’m disappointed <br><br>I’d share it all, I’d share it all, I’d share it all <br>With you <br><br>It’s like with everything I do <br>The beginning’s so exciting <br>In the middle part I doubt <br>And in the end I’m disappointed <br><br>It’s like with everything we do <br>The beginning’s so exciting <br>In the middle part we doubt <br>And in the end we’re disappointed <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Everything We Do" label="Everything We Do"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Tattoo_On_My_Brain/</id><title>Bastian Baker - Tattoo On My Brain - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:06:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:06:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/Tattoo_On_My_Brain/" title="Bastian Baker - Tattoo On My Brain - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come back to me, and I’ll run to you, no matter when or where <br>Want to lose it all just to win with you, now that I know the meaning of being two <br>The world’s filled with places so beautiful, if only we could share them <br>Make the puzzle whole <br>I swear <br><br>At first I had to ask twice for your name <br>And now it’s like a tattoo on my brain <br><br>For you I’d kill my thoughts that I’ve honed for years <br>Never felt dependent, it’s my greatest fear <br>Fell into the trap that I’ve always mocked, you’re calling into question what I’m living for but <br>I swear <br><br>At first I had to ask twice for your name <br>And now it’s like a tattoo on my brain <br><br>I was drunk and drugged in my last night’s dream <br>I woke up sweating and wondering <br>Can all this disappear so suddenly? <br>How it feels weird to have it done to me <br>I swear <br><br>At first I had to ask twice for your name <br>And now it’s like a tattoo on my brain <br>I swear <br><br>You etched on my brain <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="Tattoo On My Brain" label="Tattoo On My Brain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/White_Room/</id><title>Bastian Baker - White Room - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:06:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:06:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastian_Baker/White_Room/" title="Bastian Baker - White Room - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I dreamt you were here <br>you opened the door <br>You started crying in my arms <br>and I carried you around <br>You said you were feeling so down <br>the whole time you weren't mine <br>How I crave that smile on your face <br>As Michael Stipe <br>he said before me <br>this fantasy was just a dream <br>For I've woken up <br>all by myself in Berlin <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>I dreamt you were here <br>to everyone surprised <br>Because as usual you'd never hint <br>when you'll arrive <br>I thought what a crazy thing to do <br>these feelings are so new <br>Would we just wanna be me and you <br>As Michael Stipe <br>he said before me <br>this fantasy was just a dream <br>For I've woken up <br>all by myself in Berlin <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>For I've woken up <br>all by myself in Berlin <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>I had a dream <br>]]></content><category term="Bastian Baker" label="Bastian Baker"/><category term="White Room" label="White Room"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코다파이/1초마다_점점_Vocal_By_추은경/</id><title>코다파이 - 1초마다 점점 (Vocal By 추은경) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:08:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:08:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%8B%A4%ED%8C%8C%EC%9D%B4/1%EC%B4%88%EB%A7%88%EB%8B%A4_%EC%A0%90%EC%A0%90_Vocal_By_%EC%B6%94%EC%9D%80%EA%B2%BD/" title="코다파이 - 1초마다 점점 (Vocal By 추은경) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나를 보는 그 눈빛이 좋아서 <br>나를 아는 그 표정이 좋아서 <br>그댈 좋아하게 된 것 같아 <br>나도 모르게 내 맘에 들어와 <br>따뜻한 햇살도 밤하늘 별도 <br>그댈 따라 가버린 것 같아서 <br>눈부시게 빛나 <br>be be your love <br>눈을 감아도 난 그대가 보여 <br>내 맘에 들어와 <br>나를 설레게 해 <br>1초마다 점점 니가 좋아져 <br>자꾸 쳐다보게 돼 <br>너에게 난 그저 <br>수많은 사람중에 하나 <br>아무말 못하고 <br>바라만 보는데 <br>또 하루 지나면 <br>내게 와줄까 <br>내가 널 많이 좋아해 <br>나도 모르게 <br>내 맘에 들어와 <br>어딜가도 하루종일 따라와 <br>매일 내 머릿속을 돌아다녀 <br>꿈이 아니라면 좋을텐데 <br>가까워진 듯하면 또 멀어져 <br>내 맘에 들어와 <br>나를 설레게 해 <br>1초마다 점점 <br>니가 좋아져 <br>자꾸 쳐다보게 돼 <br>너에게 난 그저 <br>수많은 사람중에 하나 <br>아무말 못하고 <br>바라만 보는데 <br>또 하루 지나면 <br>내게 와줄까 <br>내가 널 많이 좋아해 <br>나도 모르게 <br>내 맘에 들어와 <br>자고나면 모두 <br>깨져버릴 꿈 <br>이 순간이 <br>사라질까 두려워 <br>내 맘에 들어와 <br>나를 설레게 해 <br>1초마다 점점 <br>니가 좋아져 <br>자꾸 쳐다보게 돼 <br>너에게 난 그저 <br>수많은 사람중에 하나 <br>아무말 못하고 <br>바라만 보는데 <br>또 하루 지나면 <br>내게 와줄까 <br>내가 널 많이 좋아해 <br>나도 모르게 <br>내 맘에 들어와 <br>]]></content><category term="코다파이" label="코다파이"/><category term="1초마다 점점 (Vocal By 추은경)" label="1초마다 점점 (Vocal By 추은경)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Childish_Gambino/Me_And_Your_Mama/</id><title>Childish Gambino - Me And Your Mama - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:08:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:08:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Childish_Gambino/Me_And_Your_Mama/" title="Childish Gambino - Me And Your Mama - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm in love when we are smokin' that la-la-la-la-la <br>I'm in love when we are smokin' that la-la-la-la-la <br>I'm in love when we are smokin' that la-la-la-la-la <br>I'm in love when we are smokin' that la-la-la-la-la <br>I'm in love when we are smokin' that la-la-la-la-la <br>I'm in love when we are smokin' that la-la-la-la-la <br>I'm in love when we are smokin' that la-la-la-la-la <br>I'm in love when we are smokin' that la-la-la-la-la <br><br>Do what you want! <br>I'm telling you <br>Let me into your heart! <br><br>Can't stand it, backhanded! <br>They wanna see us fallin' apart! <br>You know that I love you! <br>So let me into your heart! <br><br>Let me into your heart <br>Do you really love me? <br>I'm gon' get you, girl, ahhhh! <br><br>This is the end of us! <br>Sleeping with the moon and the stars! <br>I know where you've been, you can see the sun! <br><br>Let me into your heart! <br>Oh, this ain't no bullshit! <br>I really love you, girl! <br><br>Girl you really got a hold on me <br>So this isn't just puppy love <br>Girl you really got a hold on me <br>So this isn't just puppy love <br><br>I'm in love when we are smokin' that <br>Oh my God, I <br>Let me into <br>Girl you really got a hold, woo!]]></content><category term="Childish Gambino" label="Childish Gambino"/><category term="Me And Your Mama" label="Me And Your Mama"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정엽/설레/</id><title>정엽 - 설레 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:09:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:09:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%97%BD/%EC%84%A4%EB%A0%88/" title="정엽 - 설레 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 <br>설레 너의 웃음에 <br>너의 눈빛에 설레 <br>설레 스치는 나의 <br>코끝에 너의 향기 <br>날 보고 지어준 미소에 <br>자꾸 녹아내려 <br>날 보며 불러준 이름이 <br>귓가에서 또 울려 <br>운명이 이런거야 <br>내 앞에 있는 너야 <br>사랑한다 말할거야 <br>아무도 모를거야 <br>숨겨온 내 맘속에 <br>지켜온 내 마음에 <br>너만을 채울 거야 <br>내 꿈속엔 언제나 너와 나 둘이 <br>오래 너의 기억에 <br>너의 마음에 살래 <br>몰래 니 옆에서만 <br>니 품에서만 살래 <br>조금씩 닮아갈 표정에 <br>들떠있는 내 맘 <br>언젠가 눈뜨면 내 옆에 <br>잠든 너를 생각해 <br>운명이 이런거야 <br>내 앞에 있는 너야 <br>사랑한다 말할거야 <br>아무도 모를거야 <br>숨겨온 내 맘속에 <br>지켜온 내 마음에 <br>너만을 채울 거야 <br>내 꿈속엔 언제나 너와 나 <br>내 맘속엔 언제나 너와 나 둘이 <br>우리 <br>]]></content><category term="정엽" label="정엽"/><category term="설레" label="설레"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Studio_EIM/Promise_Of_Heaven_Feat_와타아메/</id><title>Studio EIM - Promise Of Heaven (Feat. 와타아메) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:09:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:09:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Studio_EIM/Promise_Of_Heaven_Feat_%EC%99%80%ED%83%80%EC%95%84%EB%A9%94/" title="Studio EIM - Promise Of Heaven (Feat. 와타아메) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한참 지나쳐버린 걸까 <br>잡은 두 손에 약속했던 <br>그 날의 우리의 속삭임들 <br>이젠 눈을 감아도 보여 <br>함께 거닐었던 그곳과 <br>아득히 따스했던 하늘빛 <br>내 곁에 머무를 때면 <br>이 햇살처럼 <br>한참을 하얗게 웃었던 걸요 <br>내 품에 가득한 그 미소와 <br>그대의 숨소리 <br>바람이 전해줄 거예요 <br>이제 나 아는 걸 <br>우리 함께 한 약속을 <br>언젠가 우리 <br>다시 만나게 되는 날 <br>그땐 <br>알려줄 거라는 걸 <br>아직 남은 이야기 <br>들려주고 싶은 걸 <br>돌아오는 그 날을 꿈꿔요 <br>]]></content><category term="Studio EIM" label="Studio EIM"/><category term="Promise Of Heaven (Feat. 와타아메)" label="Promise Of Heaven (Feat. 와타아메)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hailee_Steinfeld/Starving_Acoustic/</id><title>Hailee Steinfeld - Starving (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:10:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:10:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hailee_Steinfeld/Starving_Acoustic/" title="Hailee Steinfeld - Starving (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You know just what to say <br>Things that scare me <br>I should just walk away <br>But I can't move my feet <br>The more that I know you <br>the more I want to <br>Something inside me's changed <br>I was so much younger <br>yesterday oh <br>I didn't know that I was starving <br>'til I tasted you <br>Don't need no butterflies <br>when you give me <br>the whole damn zoo <br>By the way right away you <br>do things to my body <br>I didn't know that I was starving <br>'til I tasted you <br>I didn't I didn't I did I did <br>I tasted you <br>Don't need no don't need no <br>Don't need Don't need <br>a whole damn zoo <br>By the way by the way <br>you do things to my body <br>I didn't know that I was starving <br>'til I tasted you <br>You know just how <br>to make my heart beat faster <br>Emotional earthquake <br>bring on disaster <br>You hit me head on <br>got me weak in my knees <br>Yeah something <br>inside me's changed <br>I was so much younger yesterday <br>Yeah yeah <br>So much younger yesterday <br>Oohhh yeah <br>I didn't know that I was starving <br>'til I tasted you <br>Don't need no butterflies <br>when you give me <br>the whole damn zoo <br>By the way by the way <br>you do things to my body <br>I didn't know that I was starving <br>'til I tasted you <br>I didn't I didn't I did I did <br>I tasted you <br>Don't need no don't need no <br>Don't need Don't need <br>a whole damn zoo <br>By the way by the way <br>you do things to my body <br>I didn't know that I was starving <br>'til I tasted you <br>You yeah 'til I tasted you <br>By the way by the way <br>you do things to my body <br>I didn't know that I was starving <br>'til I tasted you <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>La la la la la da la da da dum <br>Da da da da <br>The more that I know you <br>the more I want to <br>Something inside me's changed <br>I was so much younger yesterday <br>]]></content><category term="Hailee Steinfeld" label="Hailee Steinfeld"/><category term="Starving (Acoustic)" label="Starving (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/금빛예림/사랑의_N타워/</id><title>금빛예림 - 사랑의 N타워 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:10:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:10:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%88%EB%B9%9B%EC%98%88%EB%A6%BC/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%98_N%ED%83%80%EC%9B%8C/" title="금빛예림 - 사랑의 N타워 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[N N N 앤이 되주세요 <br>앤이 되주세요 <br>N N N 앤이 되주세요 <br>앤이 되주세요 <br>나만의 하늘이 되어 주세요 <br>사랑의 열쇠로 <br>서로를 꼭꼭 묶어주세요 <br>윙크 살짝 미소도 살짝 <br>내 마음 뺏겨 버렸네 <br>당신은 내 삶의 중심 <br>흔들리지 말아주세요 <br>비바람에 계절이 가도 <br>나 거기 서있을께요 <br>당신은 나의 N N N <br>사랑을 약속해줘요 <br>이 세상 다할 때까지 <br>우리사랑 영원할거야 <br>내 사랑은 N 타워니까 <br>N N N <br>N N N 앤이 되주세요 <br>앤이 되주세요 <br>N N N 앤이 되주세요 <br>앤이 되주세요 <br>나만의 사랑이 되어 주세요 <br>사랑의 열쇠로 <br>서로를 꼭꼭 묶어주세요 <br>하트 살짝 키스도 살짝 <br>내 마음 뺏겨 버렸네 <br>당신은 내 삶의 중심 <br>흔들리지 말아주세요 <br>비바람에 계절이 가도 <br>나 거기 서있을께요 <br>당신은 나의 N N N <br>사랑을 약속해줘요 <br>이 세상 다할 때까지 <br>우리 사랑 영원할거야 <br>내 사랑은 N 타워니까 <br>N N N <br>]]></content><category term="금빛예림" label="금빛예림"/><category term="사랑의 N타워" label="사랑의 N타워"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/She_Dont_Honky_Tonk_No_More/</id><title>Ronnie Dunn - She Don`t Honky Tonk No More - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:15:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:15:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/She_Dont_Honky_Tonk_No_More/" title="Ronnie Dunn - She Don`t Honky Tonk No More - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Neon lights once turned her on, whiskey made her crazy <br>She'd flirt and tease me all night long, like a fiddle, she'd play me <br>I've seen her drink tequila straight, flat out lose her mind <br>And party till the break of day, was all fun and good times <br><br>Strait took it home, he almost quit, climbed down off his horse <br>Jones walked it through those pearly gates, big gold swingin' doors <br>Right now I could use a shot of somethin' hardcore, that's for sure <br>She, don't honky tonk no more <br><br>Man they'd play that neon moon, back and forth we'd sway <br>We'd live, we'd breathe those cowboy tunes, I still do today <br>I ain't givin' up at all, I can't turn her loose <br>Gotta get her back to two step songs, three chords and the truth <br><br>Strait took it home, he almost quit, climbed down off his horse <br>Jones walked it through those pearly gates, big gold swingin' doors <br>Right now I could use a shot of somethin' hardcore, that's for sure <br>She, don't honky tonk no more <br><br>Strait took it home, he almost quit, climbed down off his horse <br>Jones walked it through those pearly gates, big gold swingin' doors <br>Right now I could use a shot of somethin' hardcore, that's for sure <br>She, don't honky tonk no more <br><br>Oh, she, don't honky tonk no more]]></content><category term="Ronnie Dunn" label="Ronnie Dunn"/><category term="She Don`t Honky Tonk No More" label="She Don`t Honky Tonk No More"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/Only_Broken_Heart_In_San_Antone/</id><title>Ronnie Dunn - Only Broken Heart In San Antone - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:15:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:15:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/Only_Broken_Heart_In_San_Antone/" title="Ronnie Dunn - Only Broken Heart In San Antone - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I had to get out of Galveston <br>I had to take it on the run <br>Too many sad reminders of <br>Losin' a once in a lifetime love <br>I headed west to San Antone <br>Oh, what a foolish choice <br><br>I'm the only broken heart <br>In San Antone tonight <br>Guess this ain't no place to start <br>This gettin' on with my life <br>Everybody's hand in hand <br>Moonlight walkin', makin' plans <br>It sure is lonely, when you're the only <br>Broken heart, in San Antone <br><br>I look into the clear blue sky <br>I see the color of her eyes <br>I watch the river flowin' free <br>The way her love washed over me <br>I try to run but I can't hide <br>'Cause her memory's deep inside <br><br>I'm the only broken heart <br>In San Antone tonight <br>This ain't no place to start <br>This gettin' on with my life <br>Everybody's hand in hand <br>Moonlight walkin', makin' plans <br>It sure is lonely, when you're the only <br>Broken heart, in San Antone <br><br>Everybody's hand in hand <br>Moonlight walkin', makin' plans <br>It sure gets lonely <br>When you're the only broken heart <br>In San Antone tonight <br>No, this ain't no place to start <br>This gettin' on with my life <br><br>I'm the only broken heart <br>In San Antone tonight]]></content><category term="Ronnie Dunn" label="Ronnie Dunn"/><category term="Only Broken Heart In San Antone" label="Only Broken Heart In San Antone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/Tattooed_Heart/</id><title>Ronnie Dunn - Tattooed Heart - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:15:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:15:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/Tattooed_Heart/" title="Ronnie Dunn - Tattooed Heart - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You don't need a lot of money <br>Honey, you don't have to play no games <br>All I need is all your loving <br>To get the blood rushing through my veins, oh <br>I wanna say we're going steady <br>Like it's 1954 <br>No, it doesn't have to be forever <br>Just as long as I'm the name on your tattooed heart <br><br>Tattooed heart, tattooed heart <br>Tattooed heart, tattooed heart <br>Tattooed heart, tattooed heart <br>Tattooed heart, tattooed heart <br><br>You don't need to worry about making me crazy <br>Cause I'm way past that, yeah <br>And so just call me, if you want me cause you got me <br>And I'll show you how much I want to be <br>On your tattooed heart <br><br>Tattooed heart, tattooed heart <br>Tattooed heart, tattooed heart <br>Tattooed heart, tattooed heart <br>Tattooed heart, tattooed heart <br>Just as long as I'm the name on your tattooed heart <br><br>Wrap me in your jacket, my baby <br>And lay me in your bed <br>And kiss me underneath the moonlight <br>Darling, let me trace the lines on your tattooed heart <br><br>Tattooed heart, tattooed heart <br>Tattooed heart, tattooed heart <br>Tattooed heart, tattooed heart <br>Tattooed heart, tattooed heart <br>Just as long as I'm the name on your tattooed heart]]></content><category term="Ronnie Dunn" label="Ronnie Dunn"/><category term="Tattooed Heart" label="Tattooed Heart"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/I_Put_That_There/</id><title>Ronnie Dunn - I Put That There - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:15:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:15:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/I_Put_That_There/" title="Ronnie Dunn - I Put That There - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[That Johnny Cash poster, hangin' on the wall <br>That black and white one, where he's flippin' you off <br>And that fist sized hole it's hidin' <br>in between the studs behind it, I put that there <br><br>That black mark in the driveway, on the way out to the road <br>That dashboard Jesus, bobbin' as she goes <br>That desperate in the prayer, she's prayin' <br>that heart full of lonely kinda feelin', I put that there <br><br>That hundred miles of highway, between her and me <br>That whole lot of empty, where she used to be <br>That whiskey bottle smashed, in pieces on the floor <br>Like so many reasons she don't love me no more <br>That goodbye, hangin' like smoke in the air, I put that there <br><br>That pawn shop tag on a quarter carat ring <br>That cover up tattoo, over her name <br>That fist full of golden rings <br>that hole where my heart used to be, I put that there <br><br>Oh, that hundred miles of highway, between her and me <br>That whole lot of empty, where she used to be <br>That whiskey bottle smashed, in pieces on the floor <br>Like so many reasons she don't love me no more <br>That goodbye, hangin' like smoke in the air, yeah, I put that there <br><br>Yeah, that hundred miles of highway, between her and me <br>That whole lot of empty, where she used to be <br>That whiskey bottle smashed, in pieces on the floor <br>Like so many reasons she don't love me no more <br>That goodbye, hangin' like smoke in the air, yeah, I put that there <br><br>Oh, I put that there]]></content><category term="Ronnie Dunn" label="Ronnie Dunn"/><category term="I Put That There" label="I Put That There"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/Thats_Why_They_Make_Jack_Daniels/</id><title>Ronnie Dunn - That`s Why They Make Jack Daniels - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:15:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:15:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/Thats_Why_They_Make_Jack_Daniels/" title="Ronnie Dunn - That`s Why They Make Jack Daniels - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Some memories never fade <br>Some broken hearts just stay that way <br>Some dreams just aren't meant to be <br>But you keep, holdin' on, long after she's gone <br><br>That's why they make Jack Daniels <br>Two fingers in a glass <br>It ain't gonna make it any better <br>But, it won't hurt as bad <br><br>Some scars time won't heal <br>Some goodbyes that you're still gonna feel <br>Some ghosts just keep comin' back, from the past <br>And it won't, ever let you move on <br><br>That's why they make Jack Daniels <br>Two fingers in a glass <br>It ain't gonna make it any better <br>But, it won't hurt as bad <br><br>Some nights just never end <br>Sometimes I need to forgive you again <br><br>That's why they make Jack Daniels <br>Two fingers in a glass <br>It ain't gonna make it any better <br>But, it won't hurt as bad <br><br>It ain't gonna make it any better <br>But, it won't hurt as bad]]></content><category term="Ronnie Dunn" label="Ronnie Dunn"/><category term="That`s Why They Make Jack Daniels" label="That`s Why They Make Jack Daniels"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/I_Worship_The_Woman_You_Walked_On/</id><title>Ronnie Dunn - I Worship The Woman You Walked On - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:15:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:15:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/I_Worship_The_Woman_You_Walked_On/" title="Ronnie Dunn - I Worship The Woman You Walked On - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You don't wrong a heart, of a woman that loves you <br>You don't turn your back on her tears <br>The arms you leave lonely, won't wait forever You know what <br>That's why I'm here <br><br>'Cause I worship the woman you walked on <br>I hold her at night, 'til she's satisfied <br>Oh, I try to right all you did wrong <br>I worship the woman you walked on <br><br>I've met the wrongs haunt you, the should haves, the want tos <br>Are ghosts now in your empty bed <br>You gave up her soft touch, turned your back on her sweet love <br>You must have, been out of your head <br><br>Oh, I worship the woman you walked on <br>I hold her at night, 'til she's satisfied <br>Oh, I try to right all you did wrong <br>I worship the woman you walked on <br><br>Oh, I worship the woman you walked on <br>I hold her at night, 'til she's satisfied <br>I try to right all you did wrong <br>I worship the woman you walked on <br><br>Oh, I worship <br>Oh, the woman <br>You walked on <br><br>You don't wrong a heart, of a woman that loves you <br>You don't turn your back on her tears]]></content><category term="Ronnie Dunn" label="Ronnie Dunn"/><category term="I Worship The Woman You Walked On" label="I Worship The Woman You Walked On"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/Damn_Drunk_Feat_Kix_Brooks/</id><title>Ronnie Dunn - Damn Drunk (Feat. Kix Brooks) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:15:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:15:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/Damn_Drunk_Feat_Kix_Brooks/" title="Ronnie Dunn - Damn Drunk (Feat. Kix Brooks) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Whoa I, I just wanna ease your mind <br>Put your doubts to bed tonight <br>Lay down and let me tell you <br>You're, you're the kind of once in our lives <br>That lock it down don't come around twice <br>I guess what I'm sayin' <br>This heart of mine ain't playin' <br><br>If you were this guitar, I'd turn it to eleven <br>If you were an angel, I'd pray to go to heaven <br>If they wouldn't let me in, I'd break the gates down <br>I'd break 'em all down <br>If you were on the other side of the world <br>I'd spin that thing right back around just to get to you girl <br>I love the way you always go and mess me up <br>If you were a whiskey, girl, I'd be a damn drunk <br><br>Oh hey, go on and roll those pretty blue eyes <br>Laugh and say boy you lie <br>Girl I wouldn't dare <br>Dare to make you love me more <br>I can take that on for sure <br>Cause what we got is crazy crazy good <br><br>If you were this guitar, I'd turn it to eleven <br>If you were an angel, I'd pray to go to heaven <br>If they wouldn't let me in, I'd break the gates down <br>I'd break 'em all down <br>If you were on the other side of the world <br>I'd spin that thing right back around just to get to you girl <br>I love the way you always go and mess me up <br>If you were a whiskey, girl, I'd be a damn drunk <br><br>If you were this guitar, I'd turn it to eleven <br>If you were an angel, I'd pray to go to heaven <br>If they wouldn't let me in, I'd break the gates down <br>I'd break 'em all down <br>If you were on the other side of the world <br>I'd spin that thing right back around just to get to you girl <br>Cause I love the way you always go and mess me up <br>If you were a whiskey, girl, I'd be a damn drunk <br>If you were a whiskey, girl, I'd be a damn drunk]]></content><category term="Ronnie Dunn" label="Ronnie Dunn"/><category term="Damn Drunk (Feat. Kix Brooks)" label="Damn Drunk (Feat. Kix Brooks)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/Aint_No_Trucks_In_Texas/</id><title>Ronnie Dunn - Ain`t No Trucks In Texas - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:15:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:15:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ronnie_Dunn/Aint_No_Trucks_In_Texas/" title="Ronnie Dunn - Ain`t No Trucks In Texas - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There ain't no bar on the edge of town <br>Ain't no guitar with a lonely sound <br>There ain't no band playing that song <br>About some girl that's been gone too long <br><br>There ain't no trucks in Texas <br>Ain't no football in the south <br>Ain't no bourbon in Kentucky, I ain't drinkin' me some now <br>Ain't no stars in California, Memphis never had the blues <br>Oh, there ain't no trucks in Texas, and I ain't missing you <br><br>There ain't no phone sitting by my drink <br>I don't hope it's you every time it rings <br>I don't care where you are <br>I don't wish you'd turn around that car <br>I don't call your friends, I don't want to know <br>I don't regret letting you go <br><br>And there ain't no trucks in Texas <br>Ain't no football in the south <br>Ain't no bourbon in Kentucky, and I ain't drinkin' me some now <br>Ain't no stars in California, Memphis never had the blues <br>Oh, there ain't no trucks in Texas, and I ain't missing you <br><br>They don't get high in Colorado or party down in New Orleans <br>Ain't no losers out in Vegas <br>Ain't no Jack in Tennessee <br>I ain't had me one too many, and if you believe that's true <br>Oh, there ain't no trucks in Texas, and I ain't missing you <br><br>I ain't missing you <br>I ain't missing you]]></content><category term="Ronnie Dunn" label="Ronnie Dunn"/><category term="Ain`t No Trucks In Texas" label="Ain`t No Trucks In Texas"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/테이/사랑은_왜_Inst/</id><title>테이 - 사랑은 왜 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:15:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:15:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%80_%EC%99%9C_Inst/" title="테이 - 사랑은 왜 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑이란 가슴보다 <br>한 뼘 짙은 설레임 <br>그 끝이 무엇인 줄 모르고 <br>사랑 할 땐 네게서 <br>미움 찾지 못했던 나 <br>아팠어도 마냥 바보 같던 사랑 <br>영원 할 것 같았던 우리의 시작은 <br>처음과 멀어질수록 자꾸 <br>지난 시간 속에 <br>각자의 길을 걷잖아 <br>사랑은 왜 내게서 <br>머물지를 못하고 <br>지친 내 가슴 안에 빈자리 <br>그 틈을 삼킨 채 그렇게 나를 떠나 <br>대체 왜 너 하나 지켜내지 못하고 <br>흩어진 가슴 여미는데 <br>또 난 왜 여기 서있나 <br>영원 할 것 같았던 우리의 시작은 <br>처음과 멀어질수록 자꾸 <br>지난 시간 속에 <br>각자의 길을 걷잖아 <br>사랑은 왜 내게서 <br>머물지를 못하고 <br>지친 내 가슴 안에 빈자리 <br>그 틈을 삼킨 채 그렇게 나를 떠나 <br>대체 왜 너 하나 지켜내지 못하고 <br>흩어진 가슴 여미는데 <br>또 난 왜 여기 서있나 그대 <br>그대는 내 마음을 원했고 <br>나 역시 그대를 원했지 <br>그 칼날 같던 사랑 <br>그 사랑 땜에 베인데도 나 <br>나 이렇게 서 있을게 <br>사랑은 왜 내 곁에 <br>머물지도 못하고 <br>멍든 내 가슴 안에 <br>외로운 상처만 남긴 채 <br>그렇게 나를 괴롭히지 <br>왜 너 하나 지키지도 못했던 <br>비겁한 나를 꾸짖는데 <br>또 난 왜 여기서 있나 <br>]]></content><category term="테이" label="테이"/><category term="사랑은 왜 (Inst.)" label="사랑은 왜 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/테이/그리운_날에는/</id><title>테이 - 그리운 날에는 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:15:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:15:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9A%B4_%EB%82%A0%EC%97%90%EB%8A%94/" title="테이 - 그리운 날에는 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가슴속에 스며드는 <br>외로움이 나는 힘들어 <br>끝도 없이 밀려오는 <br>허전함이 나를 깨울 땐 <br>후회한단 말 못하고 <br>그 이별을 끌어 않았던 <br>미련스런 그 날들이 <br>오늘처럼 느껴집니다 <br>사랑 모래 위에 쌓은 성처럼 <br>때론 힘없이 무너져도 <br>믿고 싶었던 <br>함께하는 것만으로도 <br>따뜻했던 날을 기억합니다 <br>시간 따라 흩어지는 <br>마음속에 조각들마저 <br>하나하나 맞춰가며 <br>그 날들을 추억합니다 <br>그리움 불러 보는 것만으로도 <br>가슴 벅차 행복했었던 <br>마냥 좋았던 철없었던 <br>우리 모습들이 <br>눈물 나도록 또 그리워 <br>머물 수 없는 그래서 더욱 <br>소중했던 많은 날이 <br>깨진 유리파편 되어 <br>내 가슴을 베어 옵니다 <br>다시 써가는 널 향한 그리움 <br>거센 파도를 마주하는 <br>바위처럼 닳아 간데도 <br>품고 싶었던 수 많았던 <br>우리만의 비밀 <br>눈물 나도록 또 그립습니다 <br>]]></content><category term="테이" label="테이"/><category term="그리운 날에는" label="그리운 날에는"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/테이/다시_사랑할_수_있을까/</id><title>테이 - 다시 사랑할 수 있을까 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:15:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:15:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4/%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%A0_%EC%88%98_%EC%9E%88%EC%9D%84%EA%B9%8C/" title="테이 - 다시 사랑할 수 있을까 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언젠간 만날꺼라고 너를 <br>마음으로 기도했어 <br>너와의 이별후 시간이 지나도 <br>내맘속에는 항상 너였으니까 <br>너 아닌 다른 사람과 가끔 <br>이 길을 걸어 보아도 <br>내 마음속에는 우리 보냈던 <br>소중한 시간들만 남아있는데 <br>내가 너를 다시 사랑할 수 있을까 <br>가슴이 자꾸 널 보며 말을하는데 <br>내앞의 너를 기다렸다고 <br>다시 나를 보라고 <br>한마디 말도 못해 가슴이 아파 <br>어쩌다 마주치게 된 너를 <br>멍하니 바라 보았어 <br>나 눈물이 흘러 아픔이 흘러 <br>하려던 말삼키고 너를보는데 <br>내가 너를 다시 사랑할 수 있을까 <br>가슴이 자꾸 널보며 말을 하는데 <br>내 앞의 너를 기다렸다고 <br>다시 나를 보라고 <br>한마디 말도 못해 가슴이 아파 <br>우리 마음이 지금 우리가 <br>다른 곳을 보고 서로 걸어온 <br>시간에 멀어져서 <br>서로가 또 상처 일텐데 <br>왜 너와는 항상 아프기만 한 걸까 <br>아직도 우리 상처가 <br>아물지 않아서 <br>너와 다시 또 멀어진대도 <br>너를 볼 수 없대도 <br>아마도 너를 잊기 힘들 것 같아 <br>다시 사랑할 수 있을까 <br>]]></content><category term="테이" label="테이"/><category term="다시 사랑할 수 있을까" label="다시 사랑할 수 있을까"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/테이/따뜻했던_그대만/</id><title>테이 - 따뜻했던, 그대만 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:15:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:15:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4/%EB%94%B0%EB%9C%BB%ED%96%88%EB%8D%98_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%A7%8C/" title="테이 - 따뜻했던, 그대만 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새벽 공기 <br>문득 닿을때까지 <br>널 생각했어 <br>우주를 메우고 <br>별이 빛나던 사랑 안녕 <br>두렵고 공허한 <br>하루의 결들이 달랐어 <br>너 때문에 <br>멈춰진 시간에 <br>그대만 그대만 그대만 <br>코끝 저리도록 차올라 <br>따뜻했던 그대만 <br>우린 왜 이렇게 <br>되버린걸까 <br>왜 끝난 걸까 <br>헤어진 이유를 <br>찾지 못했어 <br>생각 안나 <br>빛나던 순간과 <br>숨결의 온도만 남았어 <br>난 아직도 <br>멈춰진 시간에 <br>그대만 그대만 그대만 <br>코끝 저리도록 차올라 <br>따뜻했던 그대만 <br>사랑해 그말부터 <br>태어난 나는 <br>세상이 어떻든 <br>너라는 존재로 <br>걷고 노래하고 살아가다 <br>세상에 끝에선 <br>어떻게 살아가 <br>나는 모르겠어 <br>아직도 따뜻했던 그대만 <br>새벽공기 문득 닿을때까지 <br>사랑 안녕 <br>]]></content><category term="테이" label="테이"/><category term="따뜻했던, 그대만" label="따뜻했던, 그대만"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/테이/그냥가/</id><title>테이 - 그냥가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:15:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:15:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4/%EA%B7%B8%EB%83%A5%EA%B0%80/" title="테이 - 그냥가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[처음 보는 표정과 <br>터져나온 그 말들 <br>전혀 예상하지 못한 <br>너의 숱한 상처들 <br>고갤 들 수 없었지 <br>어느 한부분 조차 <br>틀린 것 없어 <br>미안한 내 맘 <br>하나 둘 꺼낸 마음은 <br>하나 둘 쌓여만 가고 <br>시간은 점점 <br>두렵도록 차가워지고 <br>조용해진 공간에 <br>작게 뱉은 그 말은 <br>너무 아픈 진심이라 <br>붙잡을 수 없어 <br>그대를 사랑한 <br>내 맘이 죄라면 <br>차갑게 떠나가 <br>나를 찾지마 차라리 <br>그게 더 아플테니까 <br>우리의 엇갈린 <br>시간이 그토록 <br>힘들게 했다면 <br>고갤 끄덕여줄게 <br>그냥 가 <br>하나도 틀린게 없어 <br>하나도 답할게 없어 <br>마지막인걸 알면서 <br>널 볼수가 없어 <br>조용해진 공간에 <br>작게 뱉은 그 말은 <br>너무 아픈 진심이라 <br>붙잡을 수 없어 <br>그대를 사랑한 <br>내 맘이 죄라면 <br>차갑게 떠나가 <br>나를 찾지마 차라리 <br>그게 더 아플테니까 <br>우리의 엇갈린 <br>시간이 그토록 <br>힘들게 했다면 <br>고갤 끄덕여줄게 <br>그냥 가 <br>바람에 이별이 흩날리길 <br>흩날릴 상처로 마주하길 <br>이렇게 이기적인 나야 <br>미안해 <br>그대를 사랑한 <br>내 맘이 죄라면 <br>차갑게 떠나가 <br>나를 찾지마 차라리 <br>그게 더 아플테니까 <br>우리의 엇갈린 <br>시간이 그토록 <br>힘들게 했다면 <br>고갤 끄덕여줄게 <br>그냥 가 <br>미안하고 미안해서 <br>]]></content><category term="테이" label="테이"/><category term="그냥가" label="그냥가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/테이/사랑은_왜/</id><title>테이 - 사랑은 왜 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:15:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:15:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%80_%EC%99%9C/" title="테이 - 사랑은 왜 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑이란 가슴보다 <br>한 뼘 짙은 설레임 <br>그 끝이 무엇인 줄 모르고 <br>사랑 할 땐 네게서 <br>미움 찾지 못했던 나 <br>아팠어도 마냥 바보 같던 사랑 <br>영원 할 것 같았던 우리의 시작은 <br>처음과 멀어질수록 자꾸 <br>지난 시간 속에 <br>각자의 길을 걷잖아 <br>사랑은 왜 내게서 <br>머물지를 못하고 <br>지친 내 가슴 안에 빈자리 <br>그 틈을 삼킨 채 그렇게 나를 떠나 <br>대체 왜 너 하나 지켜내지 못하고 <br>흩어진 가슴 여미는데 <br>또 난 왜 여기 서있나 <br>영원 할 것 같았던 우리의 시작은 <br>처음과 멀어질수록 자꾸 <br>지난 시간 속에 <br>각자의 길을 걷잖아 <br>사랑은 왜 내게서 <br>머물지를 못하고 <br>지친 내 가슴 안에 빈자리 <br>그 틈을 삼킨 채 그렇게 나를 떠나 <br>대체 왜 너 하나 지켜내지 못하고 <br>흩어진 가슴 여미는데 <br>또 난 왜 여기 서있나 그대 <br>그대는 내 마음을 원했고 <br>나 역시 그대를 원했지 <br>그 칼날 같던 사랑 <br>그 사랑 땜에 베인데도 나 <br>나 이렇게 서 있을게 <br>사랑은 왜 내 곁에 <br>머물지도 못하고 <br>멍든 내 가슴 안에 <br>외로움 상처만 남긴 채 <br>그렇게 나를 괴롭히지 <br>왜 너 하나 지키지도 못했던 <br>비겁한 나를 꾸짖는데 <br>또 난 왜 여기서 있나 <br>]]></content><category term="테이" label="테이"/><category term="사랑은 왜" label="사랑은 왜"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/테이/그리움도_사랑이다/</id><title>테이 - 그리움도 사랑이다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:15:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:15:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9B%80%EB%8F%84_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%A4/" title="테이 - 그리움도 사랑이다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[미쳤나봐 널 그냥 보냈어 <br>바보처럼 망설이다가 <br>잡지 못했어 <br>그저 낯설기만한 뒷모습에 <br>덩그러니 남겨졌어 <br>눈을뜨면 넌 나를 찾아와 <br>차가워진 이별로 <br>나를 깨워서일까 <br>아파온다 죽을것처럼 무너진다 <br>눈물은 너를 놓기전엔 <br>멈추지 않아 <br>떠나간다 난 너에게 추억이 된다 <br>니가있던 그 시간들은 두고가라 <br>난 끝내 못난 사람이라 <br>나에겐 그리움도 사랑이다 <br>끝이란 건 끝나지 않더라 <br>너에게서 멀어지는 법 <br>알 수가 없어 <br>아파온다 지각한 마음 미련이라 <br>이별은 그날 그때부터 <br>멈추지 않아 <br>떠나간다 난 너에게 추억이 된다 <br>니가있던 그 시간들은 두고가라 <br>난 끝내 못난 사람이라 <br>나에겐 그리움도 사랑이다 <br>무너져 내린다 <br>마음 가누지 못한 채 <br>결이 달라진 시간과 <br>잘려버린 세상 끝에 혼자 남아 <br>뒤돌아본다 숨 내쉬듯 <br>널 되뇌인다 <br>꿈결같던 그 기억들과 눈물나게 <br>고마운마음 모두 사랑이라 <br>내맘이 멈추질 않아 <br>그리움도 사랑이라 <br>]]></content><category term="테이" label="테이"/><category term="그리움도 사랑이다" label="그리움도 사랑이다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/를LEL/푸른_안개_Vocal_By_LEL/</id><title>를(LEL) - 푸른 안개 (Vocal By LEL) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:16:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:16:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%BCLEL/%ED%91%B8%EB%A5%B8_%EC%95%88%EA%B0%9C_Vocal_By_LEL/" title="를(LEL) - 푸른 안개 (Vocal By LEL) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세상에는 여러 가지 <br>푸른색이 있지 <br>우리가 알지 못하는 곳에도 <br>어쩔 때는 짙은 안개로 <br>뒤덮여있어 <br>잡힐 듯 말듯 답답할 때도 있지 <br>아름다운 푸른색이 있다면 <br>멍과 같은 푸른색도 있고 <br>어두운 푸른색이 있었다면 <br>밝은 푸른색도 있어왔지 <br>푸른 안개 속을 헤쳐 나갈 때 <br>작은 빛도 찾을 수가 없을 때 <br>소중한 인연들이 나의 손을 잡고 <br>짙은 색깔에 빛 속으로 날 이끄네 <br>아름다운 푸른색이 있다면 <br>멍과 같은 푸른색도 있고 <br>어두운 푸른색이 있었다면 <br>밝은 푸른색도 있어왔지 <br>푸른 안개 속을 헤쳐 나갈 때 <br>작은 빛도 찾을 수가 없을 때 <br>소중한 인연들이 나의 손을 잡고 <br>짙은 색깔에 빛 속으로 <br>작은 희망이라도 <br>푸른 안개 속을 헤쳐 나갈 때 <br>작은 빛도 찾을 수가 없을 때 <br>소중한 인연들이 나의 손을 잡고 <br>짙은 색깔에 빛 속으로 날 이끄네 <br>]]></content><category term="를(LEL)" label="를(LEL)"/><category term="푸른 안개 (Vocal By LEL)" label="푸른 안개 (Vocal By LEL)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/를LEL/아른거린다_Vocal_By_백지웅/</id><title>를(LEL) - 아른거린다 (Vocal By 백지웅) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:16:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:16:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%BCLEL/%EC%95%84%EB%A5%B8%EA%B1%B0%EB%A6%B0%EB%8B%A4_Vocal_By_%EB%B0%B1%EC%A7%80%EC%9B%85/" title="를(LEL) - 아른거린다 (Vocal By 백지웅) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아른거린다 네 웃는 모습이 <br>참 행복해하던 그 모습이 <br>하루 종일 날 설레게 했던 <br>너에 웃는 얼굴 참 그립다 <br>아른거린다 네 슬픈 표정도 <br>참 미안해하던 그 모습도 <br>너무나 아팠었던 마지막 <br>그 순간까지도 참 그립다 <br>아른거린다 많이 좋아하고 <br>많이 사랑했던 그 모습도 <br>햇살 가득 했었던 봄날과 <br>추웠던 겨울도 너로 빛났었어 <br>돌아갈 수도 지울 수도 없는 <br>그때가 너무나 그리워서 <br>네 사진을 한참 바라보다 <br>한숨을 쉬다가 또 바라봐 <br>아른거린다 많이 좋아하고 <br>많이 사랑했던 그 모든 기억들 <br>햇살 가득했었던 봄날과 <br>추웠던 겨울도 너로 빛났었어 <br>너무 보고 싶다 네 모든 것들이 <br>돌아갈 수 없는 지울 수도 없는 <br>햇살 가득했었던 봄날과 <br>추웠던 겨울도 너 하나 만으로 <br>빛났었어 <br>빛이 나던 그날들 <br>아른거린다 많이 좋아하고 <br>많이 사랑했던 그 모든 기억들 <br>햇살 가득했었던 봄날과 <br>추웠던 겨울도 너로 빛났었어 <br>]]></content><category term="를(LEL)" label="를(LEL)"/><category term="아른거린다 (Vocal By 백지웅)" label="아른거린다 (Vocal By 백지웅)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/를LEL/어쩌면_Vocal_By_Anna/</id><title>를(LEL) - 어쩌면 (Vocal By Anna) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:16:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:16:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%BCLEL/%EC%96%B4%EC%A9%8C%EB%A9%B4_Vocal_By_Anna/" title="를(LEL) - 어쩌면 (Vocal By Anna) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[따뜻한 커피향도 어느 순간엔 <br>차갑게 식어버리듯이 <br>따뜻한 네 마음도 내가 모르게 <br>천천히 식어갔나 봐 <br>변해가는 널 외면해봐도 <br>네 눈빛에 다 드러나서 <br>어쩔 줄 몰라 널 밀어내고 <br>다시 그리워하고 있어 <br>어쩜 우린 조금 더 사랑했다면 <br>다음 계절을 함께했을까 <br>어쩜 우린 조금 더 참았었다면 <br>여전히 함께였을까 <br>변해가는 널 외면해봐도 <br>네 눈빛에 다 드러나서 <br>어쩔 줄 몰라 널 밀어내고 <br>다시 그리워하고 있어 <br>어쩜 우린 조금 더 사랑했다면 <br>다음 계절을 함께했을까 <br>어쩜 우린 조금 더 참았었다면 <br>여전히 함께였을까 <br>내가 바라던 네 모습과 <br>네가 바라던 내 모습이 <br>뒤엉켜버려서 <br>이렇게 아픈 거니 <br>어쩜 우린 조금 더 사랑했다면 <br>평생 함께하지 않았을까 <br>어쩜 우린 조금 더 이해했다면 <br>영원히 함께였을까 <br>어쩜 우린 조금 더 사랑했다면 <br>모든 계절을 함께했을까 <br>어쩜 우린 조금 더 이해했다면 <br>영원히 함께였을까 <br>나는 아직도 너야 <br>나는 아직도 너야 <br>덩그러니 나 혼자 남아 <br>너를 못 잊어 바보같이 <br>널 그리워해 <br>]]></content><category term="를(LEL)" label="를(LEL)"/><category term="어쩌면 (Vocal By Anna)" label="어쩌면 (Vocal By Anna)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/를LEL/나의_손등이_너의_손등에_Vocal_By_LEL/</id><title>를(LEL) - 나의 손등이 너의 손등에 (Vocal By LEL) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:16:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:16:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%BCLEL/%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%86%90%EB%93%B1%EC%9D%B4_%EB%84%88%EC%9D%98_%EC%86%90%EB%93%B1%EC%97%90_Vocal_By_LEL/" title="를(LEL) - 나의 손등이 너의 손등에 (Vocal By LEL) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[작은 교실에 혼자 앉아서 <br>외롭고 쓸쓸하단 <br>생각이 들 때에 <br>네가 내 앞에 <br>나타나 주길 바랬던 <br>그때가 가끔씩 생각이 나 <br>시간이 흘러 <br>나의 이름이 어느새 <br>세상에 알려졌을 때에도 <br>네가 생각나서 <br>널 찾으려 해도 <br>시간에 흐려져 <br>결국 찾지 못했지 <br>나의 손등이 <br>너의 손등에 처음 스쳤었던 <br>그땔 기억하니 <br>나의 어깨가 <br>너의 어깨에 처음 닿았었던 <br>그땔 기억하니 <br>지금 다시 널 보게 된다면 <br>또다시 담담하게 <br>널 대하겠지만 <br>못했던 말들 숨겼던 표정 <br>조금씩 열어서 <br>네게 다가갈 텐데 <br>나의 입술이 <br>너의 입술에 <br>결국 닿지 못한 채 <br>멀어졌지만 <br>나의 마음엔 <br>너의 마음이 <br>아직도 잔잔하게 남아 있어 <br>지금 다시 널 보게 된다면 <br>또다시 담담하게 <br>널 대하겠지만 <br>못했던 말들 숨겼던 표정 <br>조금씩 열어서 <br>네게 다가갈 텐데 <br>너에게로 다가갈 텐데 <br>]]></content><category term="를(LEL)" label="를(LEL)"/><category term="나의 손등이 너의 손등에 (Vocal By LEL)" label="나의 손등이 너의 손등에 (Vocal By LEL)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/를LEL/흰_눈_위의_햇살_Vocal_By_Lish/</id><title>를(LEL) - 흰 눈 위의 햇살 (Vocal By Lish) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:16:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:16:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%BCLEL/%ED%9D%B0_%EB%88%88_%EC%9C%84%EC%9D%98_%ED%96%87%EC%82%B4_Vocal_By_Lish/" title="를(LEL) - 흰 눈 위의 햇살 (Vocal By Lish) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Merry Christmas <br>Happy New Year <br>흔한 인사 속에서 <br>흔한 일상 속에서 <br>특별한 일도 없이 <br>설레는 일도 없이 <br>그렇게 보내는 게 <br>쓸쓸할 때 <br>어느새 너 <br>내 맘에 들어와 <br>얼어붙은 마음을 <br>조용히 두드리네 <br>살갑게 다가와서 <br>오래된 친구처럼 <br>편안한 미소로 <br>날 감싸주네 <br>흰 눈 위에 햇살보다 <br>따스하게 날 <br>녹이는 그대여 <br>추위 속에 <br>떨리는 내 몸도 <br>그대 온기에 <br>봄이 된 것 같아 <br>모두 가진 것 같아 <br>꿈결같이 웃음 짓는 너 <br>추운 겨울 속에서 <br>큰 희망이 돼주네 <br>아침을 맞이할 때 <br>힘이 나게 만드는 <br>너에게 유일한 <br>태양이고 싶어 <br>흰 눈 위에 햇살보다 <br>따스하게 날 <br>녹이는 그대여 <br>추위 속에 <br>떨리는 내 몸도 <br>그대 온기에 <br>봄이 된 것 같아 <br>모두 가진 것 같아 <br>그댈 꼭 안고서 <br>영원히 있고 싶어 <br>사랑하는 한 사람 <br>그게 너야 <br>추위 속에 <br>떨리는 내 몸도 <br>그대 온기에 <br>봄이 된 것 같아 <br>모두 가진 것 같아 <br>봄이 된 것 같아 <br>모두 가진 것 같아 <br>]]></content><category term="를(LEL)" label="를(LEL)"/><category term="흰 눈 위의 햇살 (Vocal By Lish)" label="흰 눈 위의 햇살 (Vocal By Lish)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/를LEL/추억과도_이별하려_해_Vocal_By_백지웅_마수혜/</id><title>를(LEL) - 추억과도 이별하려 해 (Vocal By 백지웅, 마수혜) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:17:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:17:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%BCLEL/%EC%B6%94%EC%96%B5%EA%B3%BC%EB%8F%84_%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84%ED%95%98%EB%A0%A4_%ED%95%B4_Vocal_By_%EB%B0%B1%EC%A7%80%EC%9B%85_%EB%A7%88%EC%88%98%ED%98%9C/" title="를(LEL) - 추억과도 이별하려 해 (Vocal By 백지웅, 마수혜) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[농담 했던 기억도 <br>일상 적인 대화도 <br>사소한 기억들 조차도 <br>깊게 그려져 있네 <br>그때 우리가 정말 <br>참 많이 그립지만 <br>벅찰 만큼 너무나 좋았지만 <br>말 그대로 그땐 <br>그때일 뿐이니까 그러니까 <br>추억과도 이별하려 해 <br>미련과도 이별하려 해 <br>우리가 다시 만나게 되면 <br>똑같은 이유 때문에 <br>또 헤어질 걸 알기에 <br>솔직히 너무 보고 싶다 <br>우리 항상 하던 대로 <br>하루를 보내고 싶어 <br>하지만 두 번 아프기 싫어서 <br>추억과도 이별하려 해 <br>그때 우리가 정말 <br>참 많이 그립지만 <br>벅찰 만큼 너무나 좋았지만 <br>말 그대로 그땐 <br>그때일 뿐이니까 그러니까 <br>추억과도 이별하려 해 <br>미련과도 이별하려 해 <br>우리가 다시 만나게 되면 <br>똑같은 이유 때문에 <br>또 헤어질 걸 알기에 <br>솔직히 너무 보고 싶다 <br>우리 항상 하던 대로 <br>하루를 보내고 싶어 <br>하지만 두 번 아프기 싫어서 <br>추억과도 이별하려 해 <br>모든 걸 함께 했던 <br>우리들 아파도 <br>함께 했던 우리들 <br>한 순간 선명해진다 해도 <br>다시 흐릿해 질 꺼야 <br>꼭 그렇게 될 꺼야 <br>솔직히 너무 보고 싶다 <br>우리 항상 하던 대로 <br>하루를 보내고 싶어 <br>하지만 두 번 아프기 싫어서 <br>추억과도 이별하려 해 <br>]]></content><category term="를(LEL)" label="를(LEL)"/><category term="추억과도 이별하려 해 (Vocal By 백지웅, 마수혜)" label="추억과도 이별하려 해 (Vocal By 백지웅, 마수혜)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/를LEL/있는_그대로_Vocal_By_LEL_JUN_K/</id><title>를(LEL) - 있는 그대로 (Vocal By LEL, JUN. K) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:17:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:17:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%BCLEL/%EC%9E%88%EB%8A%94_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%A1%9C_Vocal_By_LEL_JUN_K/" title="를(LEL) - 있는 그대로 (Vocal By LEL, JUN. K) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뾰족해 지는 세상 <br>때로는 상처 속에 <br>아프지만 <br>산들바람이 되어 <br>무지개 빛 행복을 <br>주고 싶어 <br>완벽하진 못해도 <br>항상 솔직함으로 <br>모든걸 내 가슴에 <br>안을 거야 <br>꾸미지 않은 채로 <br>진심 가득한 채로 <br>마음을 열고서 <br>있는 그대로의 너와나 <br>있는 그대로가 빛이나 <br>손의 손을 잡고 날아올라 <br>은하수를 함께 걸어 <br>눈빛이 통하는 이순간 <br>마음이 하나된 이순간 <br>어린 아이처럼 해맑은 <br>미소에 별들도 춤을 춰 <br>뜨거운 도시 속에 <br>이 여름을 봄으로 바꿔주고 <br>낮에도 달빛 되어 <br>시원함을 주고 싶어 <br>있는 그대로의 너와나 <br>있는 그대로가 빛이나 <br>손의 손을 잡고 날아올라 <br>은하수를 함께 걸어 <br>눈빛이 통하는 이순간 <br>마음이 하나된 이순간 <br>어린 아이처럼 해맑은 <br>미소에 별들도 춤을 춰 <br>있는 그대로 있는 그대로 <br>있는 그대로 <br>손의 손을 잡고 날아 올라 <br>은하수를 함께 걸어 <br>눈빛이 통하는 이순간 <br>마음이 하나된 이순간 <br>어린 아이처럼 해맑은 <br>미소에 별들도 춤을 춰 <br>모든걸 안고서 <br>모두 안고서 <br>별들과 춤을 춰 <br>끝없이 펼쳐진 <br>은하수에 몸을 맡긴 채 <br>자유롭게 <br>자유롭게 <br>자유롭게 <br>]]></content><category term="를(LEL)" label="를(LEL)"/><category term="있는 그대로 (Vocal By LEL, JUN. K)" label="있는 그대로 (Vocal By LEL, JUN. K)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/를LEL/희미한_흔적_Vocal_By_LEL/</id><title>를(LEL) - 희미한 흔적 (Vocal By LEL) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:17:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:17:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%BCLEL/%ED%9D%AC%EB%AF%B8%ED%95%9C_%ED%9D%94%EC%A0%81_Vocal_By_LEL/" title="를(LEL) - 희미한 흔적 (Vocal By LEL) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잊혀지기 싫었는지 <br>흔적이라도 남기려 <br>무언가 가득 찬 <br>맘에 들어가도 <br>너의 주위에 빛나는 <br>한없이 밝게 빛나는 <br>그 모든 것들로 <br>금세 사라져가 <br>어떻게든 기억되고 싶었던 <br>희미한 흔적은 수없이 <br>그려졌다 사라져 <br>이뤄지지 못한 바램들은 <br>나의 꿈속에서 <br>희미한 흔적의 흔적만 <br>또다시 금세 잊혀져 <br>자꾸만 금세 잊혀져 <br>너의 주위에 밝게 <br>빛나는 것들로 <br>어떻게든 기억되고 싶었던 <br>희미한 흔적은 수없이 <br>그려졌다 사라져 <br>이뤄지지 못한 바람들은 <br>나의 꿈속에서 <br>희미한 흔적의 흔적만 <br>이뤄지지 못한 바람들은 <br>나의 꿈속에서 <br>희미한 흔적의 흔적만 <br>또다시 금세 잊혀져 <br>자꾸만 금세 잊혀져 <br>너의 주위에 밝게 <br>빛나는 것들로 <br>]]></content><category term="를(LEL)" label="를(LEL)"/><category term="희미한 흔적 (Vocal By LEL)" label="희미한 흔적 (Vocal By LEL)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/를LEL/마음의_종이_Vocal_By_정민/</id><title>를(LEL) - 마음의 종이 (Vocal By 정민) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:17:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:17:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%BCLEL/%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C%EC%9D%98_%EC%A2%85%EC%9D%B4_Vocal_By_%EC%A0%95%EB%AF%BC/" title="를(LEL) - 마음의 종이 (Vocal By 정민) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 생각하면서 널 그려보다가 <br>마음속에서 부러진 연필 <br>어쩔 줄 몰라 꼭 쥐고만 있어 <br>널 다시 그리려 널 떠올리다가 <br>마음의 종이 눈물에 젖어 <br>그리지 못해 멍하니 서있어 <br>해맑게 웃던 모습이 <br>소중했던 너의 미소가 <br>나의 마음의 종이보다 <br>더 하얗기 때문에 <br>떠올리지 못하나 봐 <br>널 보고싶어서 널 다시 그리려 <br>부러진 연필 다시 붙이려 <br>노력 해봐도 그게 잘 안돼 <br>해맑게 웃던 모습이 <br>소중했던 너의 미소가 <br>나의 마음의 종이보다 <br>더 하얗기 때문에 떠올리지 못해 <br>해맑게 웃던 모습이 <br>소중했던 너의 미소가 <br>나의 마음의 종이보다 <br>더 하얗기 때문에 떠올리지 못해 <br>해맑게 웃던 모습이 <br>소중했던 너의 미소가 <br>나의 마음의 종이보다 <br>더 하얗기 때문에 <br>떠올리지 못하나 봐 <br>하얗기 때문에 <br>떠올리지 못하나 봐 <br>]]></content><category term="를(LEL)" label="를(LEL)"/><category term="마음의 종이 (Vocal By 정민)" label="마음의 종이 (Vocal By 정민)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/를LEL/나만_궁금한_거니_Vocal_By_Super_Kiro_Rap_Wizil/</id><title>를(LEL) - 나만 궁금한 거니 (Vocal By Super Kiro, Rap Wizil) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:17:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:17:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%BCLEL/%EB%82%98%EB%A7%8C_%EA%B6%81%EA%B8%88%ED%95%9C_%EA%B1%B0%EB%8B%88_Vocal_By_Super_Kiro_Rap_Wizil/" title="를(LEL) - 나만 궁금한 거니 (Vocal By Super Kiro, Rap Wizil) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루 종일 너만 생각해 oh baby <br>하루 종일 가슴이 설레 oh no <br>Every time Everyday <br>눈을 뜨고 세수를 하고 밥 먹고 <br>집을 나설 때도 <br>네 얼굴 떠오르다가 <br>왠지 모르게 답답해져 <br>닿을 듯 말 듯해서 <br>알 것 같다가 알 수 없어 <br>잡힐 듯 말 듯해서 <br>너에게 빠진 내 행동이 멋대로 또 <br>앞서가는 건 아닌지 잘 모르겠어 <br>나만 궁금한 거니 <br>너도 궁금한 거니 <br>혹시나 혼자서 또 <br>들떠있는 건 아닌지 <br>섣불리 다가갔다가 <br>네가 사라져 버릴까 봐 <br>걱정하면서 또 언제나 그랬듯이 <br>다시 네 생각에 매일매일 자꾸만 <br>빠져들고 있어 <br>인스타에 네 사진 보면 ho <br>나도 모르게 미소가 <br>네 스타일에 또 감탄해 <br>감각적인 너를 또 <br>습관적으로 보게 돼 <br>이렇게 예쁜 네가 나를 <br>얼만큼 생각하는지 <br>아직도 난 잘 모르겠어 <br>나만 궁금한 거니 <br>너도 궁금한 거니 <br>혹시나 혼자서 또 <br>들떠있는 건 아닌지 <br>섣불리 다가갔다가 <br>네가 사라져 버릴까 봐 <br>걱정하면서 또 언제나 그랬듯이 <br>다시 네 생각에 매일매일 자꾸만 <br>빠져들고 있어 <br>작은 틈이라도 내어주면 <br>난 문을 열고 네 맘에 <br>확 들어 가고 싶어 girl <br>그래 나는 조급해 애매한 건 싫어 <br>어린애처럼 더는 <br>감정을 숨길 수 없어 <br>고백할래 남자답게 <br>이제 말할 time인 것 같은데 <br>용기 내서 뱉은 말에 <br>I want you to say 이 말을 <br>너무나 기다려왔다고 <br>그래 너를 좋아해 <br>네 모든 걸 좋아해 <br>이제는 그만 우리 <br>솔직해지면 어떨까 <br>재는 건 이제 그만 <br>할 때도 된 것 같아 <br>지금 바로 너에게 달려가 <br>얘기하고 말 거야 <br>그대로의 모습을 그냥 널 좋아해 <br>그냥 널 좋아해 웃는 모습이 좋아 <br>너의 말투가 좋아 <br>함께 있는 게 좋아 <br>모든 걸 좋아해 같이 걷는 게 좋아 <br>너의 향기가 좋아 진짜 널 좋아해 <br>]]></content><category term="를(LEL)" label="를(LEL)"/><category term="나만 궁금한 거니 (Vocal By Super Kiro, Rap Wizil)" label="나만 궁금한 거니 (Vocal By Super Kiro, Rap Wizil)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/를LEL/가슴이_그렇게_하래_Vocal_By_황수영/</id><title>를(LEL) - 가슴이 그렇게 하래 (Vocal By 황수영) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:17:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:17:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%BCLEL/%EA%B0%80%EC%8A%B4%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A0%87%EA%B2%8C_%ED%95%98%EB%9E%98_Vocal_By_%ED%99%A9%EC%88%98%EC%98%81/" title="를(LEL) - 가슴이 그렇게 하래 (Vocal By 황수영) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[평소처럼 밥을 먹고서 <br>평소처럼 신발을 신고 나와 <br>항상 다니던 길에 골목을 돌아 <br>더 씩씩한 척 하룰 시작해 <br>아무일 없었단 듯이 <br>평소처럼 웃고 떠들고 <br>매일매일 바쁜 하룬데 <br>말로 표현하기 힘든 기분이 있어 <br>틈틈이 떠오르는 네 생각 <br>더 이상 하기 싫은데 <br>잔잔한 맘에 네 모습이 <br>차오르는 이유 <br>가슴이 그렇게 하래 <br>너를 또 그리워 하래 <br>정말로 네가 미웠었는데 <br>정말로 잊고 싶은데 <br>내 맘이 뜻대로 안돼 <br>더욱 더 아파져도 다시 또 너를 <br>사랑하게 만드는 이유 <br>가슴이 그렇게 하래 <br>추억들은 전부 다 <br>새하얗게 흐려져 <br>잔향만 남았지만 <br>어쩔 때는 가끔씩 <br>어쩔 때는 정말 아주 많이 <br>네가 생각이 나는 건 <br>가슴이 그렇게 하래 <br>너를 또 그리워 하래 <br>정말로 네가 미웠었는데 <br>정말로 잊고 싶은데 <br>내 맘이 뜻대로 안돼 <br>더욱 더 아파져도 다시 또 너를 <br>사랑하게 만드는 이유 <br>가슴이 그렇게 하래 <br>빛났었던 우리 철없이 순수하고 <br>어렸지만 그래서 <br>더 아름답던 날들 <br>덩그러니 내 마음 한 켠에 <br>아직도 남아서 이렇게 <br>또 널 부르고 있어 <br>그래 널 아직 사랑해 <br>가슴이 너 하나만 바라보라고 <br>시키는데 어쩌니 정말 <br>너 돌아오면 안되니 정말 <br>잔잔한 가슴에 <br>더 파도 치게 만드는 <br>너의 기억들로 오늘을 또 보낸다 <br>너의 기억들로 오늘을 또 보낸다 <br>]]></content><category term="를(LEL)" label="를(LEL)"/><category term="가슴이 그렇게 하래 (Vocal By 황수영)" label="가슴이 그렇게 하래 (Vocal By 황수영)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/를LEL/반딧불을_따라서_Vocal_By_장우영/</id><title>를(LEL) - 반딧불을 따라서 (Vocal By 장우영) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:17:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:17:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%BCLEL/%EB%B0%98%EB%94%A7%EB%B6%88%EC%9D%84_%EB%94%B0%EB%9D%BC%EC%84%9C_Vocal_By_%EC%9E%A5%EC%9A%B0%EC%98%81/" title="를(LEL) - 반딧불을 따라서 (Vocal By 장우영) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[초라해진 나의 바다와 <br>모래 위에 쓰러진 행복 <br>어쩔 때는 내가 나 자신에게 <br>미안해지는 걸 <br>조개 껍질 맨발로 된 마음을 <br>자꾸 찌르게 되고 <br>하늘 위에 화려한 유성들이 <br>자꾸 지나가지만 <br>희미한 반딧불을 따라서 <br>한번 더 그림자를 일으켜본다 <br>신발끈을 다시 꼭 매고서 <br>달리는 내 모습이 때론 <br>너무 안쓰럽기도 하지만 <br>아름다워질 그림자를 안고 <br>다시 뛰어본다 <br>가벼워진 나의 물병은 이제 <br>물 한 방울도 없지만 <br>마른 입술 살짝 깨물어보며 <br>다시 달리고 있어 <br>희미한 반딧불을 따라서 <br>한번 더 그림자를 일으켜본다 <br>신발끈을 다시 꼭 매고서 <br>달리는 내 모습이 안쓰러워도 <br>희미한 반딧불을 따라서 <br>한번 더 그림자를 일으켜본다 <br>신발끈을 다시 꼭 매고서 <br>달리는 내 모습이 때론 <br>너무 안쓰럽기도 하지만 <br>아름다워질 그림자를 안고 <br>다시 뛰어본다 <br>]]></content><category term="를(LEL)" label="를(LEL)"/><category term="반딧불을 따라서 (Vocal By 장우영)" label="반딧불을 따라서 (Vocal By 장우영)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/를LEL/잘_지내니__Vocal_By_LEL/</id><title>를(LEL) - 잘 지내니? (Vocal By LEL) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:17:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:17:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%BCLEL/%EC%9E%98_%EC%A7%80%EB%82%B4%EB%8B%88__Vocal_By_LEL/" title="를(LEL) - 잘 지내니? (Vocal By LEL) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잘 지내니 이렇게 <br>묻는 것도 이젠 어색한걸 <br>지난날이 아련하고 <br>또 아련해서 연락해봤어 <br>그리웠니 아니면 <br>다 잊었니 궁금해진 맘에 <br>물어보고 싶었지만 <br>내입이 떨어지지 않더라 <br>그때로 돌아가는 건 <br>너에게는 힘들겠단 생각에 <br>또다시 잘 지내란 <br>말만 또 계속 되풀이 할 뿐 <br>이렇게도 아쉬운 <br>우리의 사랑이 끝이라는 걸 <br>인정하기 싫지만 <br>이젠 모두 내려 놓으려 해 <br>눈물이나 가끔은 <br>붙잡고 싶은 맘도 생기지만 <br>알고 있어 말 그대로 <br>추억은 추억뿐이라는걸 <br>잘 지내 <br>그때로 돌아가는 건 <br>너에게는 힘들겠단 생각에 <br>또다시 잘 지내란 <br>말만 또 계속 되풀이 할 뿐 <br>이렇게도 아쉬운 <br>우리의 사랑이 끝이라는 걸 <br>인정하기 싫지만 <br>이젠 모두 내려 놓으려 해 <br>눈물이나 가끔은 <br>붙잡고 싶은 맘도 생기지만 <br>알고 있어 말 그대로 <br>추억은 추억뿐이라는걸 <br>잘 지내 <br>아니 못 참겠어 <br>솔직히 나 점점 더 힘들어 <br>하지만 우리 소중한 추억 <br>망치고 싶지 않아 <br>이렇게 말하는 거야 <br>모르겠니 아직도 <br>난 너를 사랑하고 있다는 걸 <br>겉으로만 괜찮은 척 <br>하는 것도 이젠 못하겠어 <br>돌아가자 그때로 <br>한없이 사랑했던 시간으로 <br>아름답게 빛나는 눈빛으로 <br>나를 바라보던 그 모습으로 <br>]]></content><category term="를(LEL)" label="를(LEL)"/><category term="잘 지내니? (Vocal By LEL)" label="잘 지내니? (Vocal By LEL)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/구름/더_나은_사람/</id><title>구름 - 더 나은 사람 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:17:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:17:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B5%AC%EB%A6%84/%EB%8D%94_%EB%82%98%EC%9D%80_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C/" title="구름 - 더 나은 사람 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[익숙하지 않은 말의 <br>네가 골라준 책이 <br>너를 아껴주는 방법을 <br>알려주는 것 같아 <br>아무것도 보지 않고 <br>무엇을 걱정한 걸까 <br>이젠 네가 하는 말들이 <br>몸짓으로 보이네 <br>넌 이렇게나 멈춰있는 <br>내게 글을 쓰게 해 <br>모래뿐인 내 하루에 <br>꽃이 되어주네 <br>넌 이렇게나 좋은 <br>사람으로 내게 와 <br>날 좀 더 나은 <br>사람이 되게 해 <br>아직은 내가 모르고 <br>있을 너의 모습들이 <br>매일 널 만나는 날마다 <br>날 행복하게 만드네 <br>언제쯤 네 허리에 <br>감는 손이 익숙해질까 <br>몸에 닿는 나의 손끝이 <br>아직도 어색해 <br>넌 이렇게나 멈춰있는 <br>내게 춤을 추게 해 <br>먼지뿐인 내 하루에 <br>빛이 되어주네 <br>넌 이렇게나 멋진 <br>사람으로 내게 와 <br>날 좀 더 나은 <br>사람이 되게 해 <br>난 이렇게나 항상 <br>너를 향해 노래하려 해 <br>네가 아플 때마다 <br>길이 되어주게 <br>넌 이렇게나 좋은 <br>사람으로 내게 와 <br>날 좀 더 나은 <br>사람이 되게 해 <br>]]></content><category term="구름" label="구름"/><category term="더 나은 사람" label="더 나은 사람"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Griswolds/I_Want_It_All/</id><title>The Griswolds - I Want It All - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:18:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:18:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Griswolds/I_Want_It_All/" title="The Griswolds - I Want It All - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I, I'll never forgive you <br>I just want to take you home <br>And I never miss you <br>Just don't want to be alone <br>I want it all <br>And all, I'm done <br><br>I, I'll never forgive you <br>And I'm waiting by the phone <br>And I never miss you <br>Cos my heart's in cruise control <br>I want it all <br>And all, I'm done <br>I want it all <br>And all, I'm done <br><br>I, I'll never forgive you <br>I just want to take you home <br>And I never miss you <br>Just don't want to be alone <br>I want it all <br>And all, I'm done <br><br>I, I'll never forgive you <br>And I'm waiting by the phone <br>And I never miss you <br>Cos my heart's in cruise control <br>I want it all <br>And all, I'm done <br><br>We made a huge mistake <br>And I took all that I could take <br>We made a huge mistake <br>Are we better off this way <br>And we found truth in all the confusion <br>Throwing it all away throwing it all away <br>And we made a huge mistake <br>And we're better off this way <br><br>I, I want to forgive you <br>Why you pulling at my soul <br>Try not to miss you <br>Make believe I'm in control <br>I want it all <br>And all, I'm done <br><br>I, I want to forgive you <br>And I want to take you home <br>Try not to miss you <br>Just don't want to be alone <br>I want it all <br>And all, I'm done <br><br>We made a huge mistake <br>And I took all that I could take <br>We made a huge mistake <br>Are we better off this way <br>And we found truth in all the confusion <br>Throwing it all away throwing it all away <br>And we made a huge mistake <br>And we're better off this way <br><br>And I could never be the one you hold <br>I could never be the one you hold <br>I hate that I don't hate you, though <br>I'll make this home without you <br>And I could never be the one hold <br>No, I could never be the one you hold <br>I love that I still love you, though <br>I'll make this home without you <br><br>We're better off <br><br>We found truth in all the confusion <br>We're throwing it all away <br>And we found truth in all the confusion <br>We're throwing it all away throwing it all away <br>We made a huge mistake <br>And we're better off this way <br>And we made a huge mistake <br>And we're better off this way]]></content><category term="The Griswolds" label="The Griswolds"/><category term="I Want It All" label="I Want It All"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Griswolds/High_Times_For_Low_Lives/</id><title>The Griswolds - High Times For Low Lives - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T16:18:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T16:18:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Griswolds/High_Times_For_Low_Lives/" title="The Griswolds - High Times For Low Lives - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're a trouble maker man <br>Nothing in your life means anything <br>You're a problematic child <br>You're problematic <br><br>Oh this is high times for low lives <br>You bet we can see <br>Oh this is high times for low lives <br><br>It must be hard to just be yourself <br>Coz, life's writing cheques <br>That you just can't digest and <br>Welcome to my living hell <br>Yeah, welcome to my living hell <br><br>You're a trouble maker man <br>Nothing in your life means anything <br>You're a problematic child <br>You're problematic <br><br>Oh this is high times for low lives <br>You bet we can see <br>Oh this is high times for low lives <br><br>I bet it must be hard to make friends <br>Coz, life's breaking legs and <br>You can't make amends and <br>Welcome to my living hell <br>Yeah, welcome to my living hell <br><br>I'm at war with the ceiling <br>At war with myself and <br>I guess this must be bad for my health <br>Yeah I guess this must be bad for my health and <br>Welcome to my living hell <br><br>You're a trouble maker man <br>Nothing in your life means anything <br>You're a problematic child <br>You're problematic <br><br>Oh this is high times for low lives <br>You bet we can see <br>Oh this is high times for low lives <br>Oh this is high times for low lives <br><br>Yeah this is high times for low lives <br>It's hard times for low lives <br>High times for low lives]]></content><category term="The Griswolds" label="The Griswolds"/><category term="High Times For Low Lives" label="High Times For Low Lives"/></entry></feed>