<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:48:03+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마리슈/잘까요/</id><title>마리슈 - 잘까요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:02:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:02:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%88/%EC%9E%98%EA%B9%8C%EC%9A%94/" title="마리슈 - 잘까요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[매일 밤 귓가에 <br>마주 앉은 그대여 <br>오늘도 새벽을 <br>채우고 있네요 <br>나 그대가 곁에 <br>있는 것도 같은데 <br>우리 잘까요 <br>아침 해가 밝아와요 <br>달빛도 별빛도 <br>잠자고 있는 밤 <br>자욱한 그대 목소리 <br>귓가에 맺혀 <br>나 그대가 곁에 <br>있는 것도 같은데 <br>왠지 우리는 <br>꿈을 꾸는 것도 같은데 <br>우리 잘까요 잘까요 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>자장 자장 자장 <br>]]></content><category term="마리슈" label="마리슈"/><category term="잘까요" label="잘까요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마리슈/오늘밤_왈츠/</id><title>마리슈 - 오늘밤 왈츠 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:02:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:02:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%88/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98%EB%B0%A4_%EC%99%88%EC%B8%A0/" title="마리슈 - 오늘밤 왈츠 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비 그리고 깊은 밤 <br>우릴 반기던 가로수 <br>기억하나요 <br>수줍게 빛나던 별빛 <br>물끄러미 바라본 <br>우리 거닐던 모습이 <br>마치 뒤뚱거리듯 <br>춤을 추는 것 같아 <br>우린 밤하늘을 우산 삼아 <br>젖은 달빛을 조명 삼아 <br>걷다 걷다 걷다가 걷다 보면 <br>우린 어느새 춤을 추네 <br>애써 태연히 걸어도 <br>애써 딴청을 피워도 <br>숨길 수 없어요 <br>살며시 맞닿은 손등 <br>이 축제의 시간이 <br>곧 끝이 나겠지만 <br>이 길이 메마르는 <br>아침이 오겠지만 <br>우린 밤하늘을 우산 삼아 <br>젖은 달빛을 조명 삼아 <br>걷다 걷다 걷다가 걷다 보면 <br>우린 어느새 춤을 추네 <br>우린 밤하늘을 우산 삼아 <br>젖은 달빛에 우릴 담아 <br>걷다 걷다 걷다가 걷다 보면 <br>우린 어느새 춤을 추네 <br>깊어가는 오늘 밤이 <br>마치 꿈을 꾸는 것만 같아 <br>워 워어어 워 <br>라라 라라라라 라랄랄라 <br>라라라라 라랄랄라 <br>라라라라 라랄라 라랄리라 <br>라라 라라라 라랄리라 <br>라라 라라라라 라랄라라 <br>라라라라 라랄랄라 <br>라라라라 라랄라 라랄리라 <br>우린 어느새 춤을 추네 <br>우린 어느새 춤을 추네 <br>]]></content><category term="마리슈" label="마리슈"/><category term="오늘밤 왈츠" label="오늘밤 왈츠"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마리슈/그대_랩소디/</id><title>마리슈 - 그대 랩소디 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:02:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:02:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%88/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80_%EB%9E%A9%EC%86%8C%EB%94%94/" title="마리슈 - 그대 랩소디 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대에게 주는 그대만을 위한 <br>그대만의 이야기 <br>그대만을 위한 나의 목소리 <br>그대 바라보고 그대 손을 잡고 <br>그대 이름 부르고 <br>그대 말해주오 나의 그대여 <br>그대에게 주는 그대만을 위한 <br>그대만의 이야기 <br>그대만을 위한 나의 목소리 <br>그대 바라보고 그대 손을 잡고 <br>그대 이름 부르고 <br>나를 말해주오 나의 그대여 <br>난 그대만을 위한 사랑의 노래 <br>그대만을 위한 하늘 아래 <br>그대 하나만을 비추는 멜로디 우 <br>우 우 우 우 <br>그대만이 가득한 <br>그대만을 위한 밤 <br>그대만을 위한 작은 위로 <br>난 그대만을 위한 사랑의 노래 <br>그대만을 위한 하늘 아래 <br>그대 하나만을 비추는 멜로디 오 <br>그대만을 위한 사랑의 노래 <br>사랑의 노래를 해 <br>그대만을 위한 사랑의 노래 <br>그대를 위한 노래 <br>그대만을 위한 사랑의 노래 <br>그대만 위한 노래 <br>그대에게 주는 맘 <br>그대만의 이야기 <br>그대만을 위한 나의 목소리 <br>]]></content><category term="마리슈" label="마리슈"/><category term="그대 랩소디" label="그대 랩소디"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마리슈/어서_만나요/</id><title>마리슈 - 어서 만나요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:02:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:02:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%88/%EC%96%B4%EC%84%9C_%EB%A7%8C%EB%82%98%EC%9A%94/" title="마리슈 - 어서 만나요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이런 맘이었을까 <br>종일 떠올려도 마르지 않는 <br>그대 그대 그대 그대 그대 그대 <br>그댄 햇살이 되어 <br>길었던 외로움은 꽃을 피웠네 <br>그대 그대 그대 그대 그대 그대 <br>보고 싶은 맘에 잠을 설치고 <br>이런 내 모습이 낯설어 또 웃고 <br>더딘 기다림의 밤이 걷히면 <br>어서 만나요 <br>얼었던 마음들이 녹아 내리고 <br>어서 만나요 <br>어제 꾸었던 꿈은 오늘이 되어 <br>숱한 계절을 잘 견뎌냈으니 <br>어서 만나요 <br>내 모든 순간들에 그대가 있고 <br>어서 만나요 <br>그댈 그리는 맘은 오늘이 되어 <br>그대 마음 한 켠에 기다리고 있어 <br>어서 만나요 <br>언제부터였을까 <br>내 두 눈에 맺힌 사랑의 노래 <br>그대 그대 그대 그대 그대 그대 <br>그댄 바람이 되어 <br>분홍빛으로 날 데려가 주오 <br>그대 그대 그대 그대 그대 그대 <br>오 이 꿈들이 깨지지 않도록 <br>어서 만나요 <br>얼었던 마음들이 녹아 내리고 <br>어서 만나요 <br>어제 꾸었던 꿈은 오늘이 되어 <br>숱한 계절을 잘 견뎌냈으니 <br>어서 만나요 <br>내 모든 순간들에 그대가 있고 <br>어서 만나요 <br>그댈 그리는 맘은 오늘이 되어 <br>그대 마음 한 켠에 기다리고 있어 <br>어서 만나요 <br>그대 그대 그대 <br>그대 그대 그대 <br>]]></content><category term="마리슈" label="마리슈"/><category term="어서 만나요" label="어서 만나요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Metallica/Atlas_Rise/</id><title>Metallica - Atlas, Rise! - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:04:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:04:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Metallica/Atlas_Rise/" title="Metallica - Atlas, Rise! - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bitterness and burden <br>Curses rest on thee <br>Solitaire and sorrow <br>All eternity <br>Save the Earth and <br>claim perfection <br>Deem the mass and <br>blame rejection <br>Hold the pose <br>fein perception <br>Grudges break your back <br>All you bear <br>All you carry <br>All you bear <br>Place it right on <br>Right on me <br>Die as you suffer in vain <br>Own all the grief and the pain <br>Die as you hold up the skies <br>Atlas rise <br>How does it feel on your own <br>Bound by the world all alone <br>Crushed under heavy skies <br>Atlas rise <br>Crucify and witness <br>Circling the sun <br>Bastardized in ruin <br>What have you become <br>Blame the world and <br>blame your maker <br>Wish 'em to the undertaker <br>Crown yourself the other savior <br>So you carry on <br>All you bear <br>All you carry <br>All you bear <br>Place it right on <br>Right on me <br>Die as you suffer in vain <br>Own all the grief and the pain <br>Die as you hold up the skies <br>Atlas rise <br>How does it feel on your own <br>Bound by the world all alone <br>Crushed under heavy skies <br>Crushed under heavy skies <br>Atlas rise <br>Masquerade as maker <br>Heavy is the crown <br>Beaten down and broken <br>Drama wears you down <br>Overload <br>the martyr stumbles <br>Hit the ground and <br>Heaven crumbles <br>All alone the fear shall humble <br>Swallow all your pride <br>All you bear <br>All you carry <br>All you bear <br>Place it right on <br>Right on me <br>Die as you suffer in vain <br>Own all the grief and the pain <br>Die as you hold up the skies <br>Atlas rise <br>How does it feel on your own <br>Bound by the world all alone <br>Crushed under heavy skies <br>Crushed under heavy skies <br>Atlas rise <br>]]></content><category term="Metallica" label="Metallica"/><category term="Atlas, Rise!" label="Atlas, Rise!"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Drake/Two_Birds_One_Stone/</id><title>Drake - Two Birds, One Stone - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:04:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:04:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Drake/Two_Birds_One_Stone/" title="Drake - Two Birds, One Stone - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro] <br>Yeah, more, yeah <br><br>[Verse] <br>More time with family and friends, more life <br>More time to get it right <br>It's only me, but I'm seeing four shadows in the light <br>My demons visit me every night <br>To the most high, I'm forever indebted <br>I know I gotta pay somethin', I know that day's comin' <br>I put it all in the music <br>Because if I don't say it here, then I won't say nothin' <br>Could feel my hand getting tired from holding the grudges <br>Two birds, one stone, my aim is amazin' <br>I need to start losing my shit on you niggas that's hatin' <br>Too reserved, like I called ahead for me and my lady <br>Free C5, how the fuck we got the boss waiting? <br>Ever since the blue basement, I found God and I lost patience <br>Between rocks and hard places of all places <br>Spotted everywhere, like Dalmation <br>Cops snoop around now, 'cause all of my dogs famous <br>Please welcome the October fall baby <br>Vaughan Road Academy, star player―my mind's not all there <br>Used to carry a lot of dead weight like a pallbearer <br>People too scared to tell the truth, so it's all dares <br>Count it, it's all there, and we all square <br>Quick money, I'm in and out <br>My dad used to use a soap bar 'til it's thinnin' out <br>But, shit, look at Dennis now <br>All Stacy Adams and linnen'd out <br>More blessings for Sandy and him, more life <br>My parents never got it right <br>But God bless 'em both, I think we all alike <br>We all wide awake late at night, thinking on what to change <br>If we do get to do it twice in another life <br>Scared to go to sleep now <br>'Cause being awake is what all my dreams were like <br>Back when the bar that I had set for myself was out of sight <br>Tell me how I went and did chin-ups <br>On this shit when I can't see it <br>Pin-ups of Meagan Good and Pam Grier <br>Soul sisters inspired my old scriptures <br>Now that feeling's gone like them old pictures <br>Mixin' liquor got us both twisted, words get so vicious <br>You just stare at me while you roll Swishers <br>Girl, I love you, but I don't miss ya <br>And no matter what year it is, I'm a 06er <br>Go figure, cold nigga, stay in school, man <br>Fuck the rap game, it's all lies and it's all filthy <br>Two percent of us rich and the rest of these niggas all milk it <br>Got two of my niggas off with a "not guilty" <br>Gave back to the city and never said it if I didn't live it <br>But still they try and tell you I'm not the realest <br>Like I'm some privileged kid <br>That never sat through a prison visit <br>Or like it was just handed to me tied with a ribbon <br>I never worked to get it <br>But really it's you with all the drug dealer stories <br>That's gotta stop, though <br>You made a couple chops and now you think you Chapo <br>If you ask me though, you ain't lining the trunk with kilos <br>You bagging weed watching Pacino with all your niggas <br>Like, "This what we need to be on," but you never went live <br>You middle-man in this shit, boy, you was never them guys <br>I can tell, 'cause I look most of you dead in your eyes <br>And you'll be tryna sell that story for the rest of your lives <br>Can't show us where the cash is <br>Me, I don't judge, I'm just going off what the math is <br>Numbers inflated <br>They all look at me, like, "What have you done for me lately?" <br>"I like your older shit but wasn't in love with the latest." <br>Aw, baby, stop debatin', I'm just a creative <br>My numbers out of this world <br>No wonder they got me feeling so alienated <br>You were the man on the moon <br>Now you just go through your phases <br>Life of the angry and famous <br>Rap like I know I'm the greatest <br>Then give you tropical flavours <br>Still never been on hiatus <br>You stay xann'd and perk'd up <br>So when reality set in, you don't gotta face it <br>I'm down 200 in Vegas but winning life on a daily basis <br>It seems like nobody wants to stay in my good graces <br>I'm like a real estate agent, putting you all in your places <br>Look what happens soon as you talk to me crazy <br>Is you crazy?]]></content><category term="Drake" label="Drake"/><category term="Two Birds, One Stone" label="Two Birds, One Stone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/컬YP/십만원/</id><title>컬YP - 십만원 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:04:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:04:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BB%ACYP/%EC%8B%AD%EB%A7%8C%EC%9B%90/" title="컬YP - 십만원 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[10만원이 필요하면 <br>언제든지 필요하다 말해 <br>100만원은 힘들지만 <br>10만원은 언제든 가능해 <br>우리가 함께한 시간에 <br>함께 나눈 추억에 <br>그 정도는 언제 든지 <br>든지 든지 든지 가능해 <br>술 한잔이 생각나면 <br>언제든지 사달라고 말해 <br>양주라면 힘들지만 <br>소주라면 언제든 가능해 <br>세상이 아무리 차갑고 <br>아무리 모질어도 <br>그 정도는 언제 든지 <br>든지 든지 든지 가능해 <br>Give me a call Oh Call me <br>Don't worry <br>내가 곁에 있잖아 <br>Give me a call Oh Call me <br>Don't worry <br>내가 곁에 있잖아 <br>친 친 친 친구 있어 <br>좋다는 게 뭐야 <br>힘 힘 힘 힘들 때 <br>기댈 수 있는 거야 <br>혼자라고 느껴지는 순간에 <br>떠오르는 사람 얼굴 이야 <br>그게 바로 바로 바로 <br>바로 바로 바로 친구야 <br>혼자서 밥 먹으려다 <br>슬퍼지려 하면 나를 불러 <br>매일 오면 그렇지만 <br>가끔이면 언제든지 들려 <br>우리가 함께한 시간에 <br>함께 나눈 추억에 <br>그 정도는 언제 든지 <br>든지 든지 든지 가능해 <br>아무 말 하긴 싫은데 <br>혼자 있기 싫은 날은 말해 <br>아무것도 묻지 않고 <br>니 옆에 가만히 있어 줄게 <br>세상이 아무리 차갑고 <br>아무리 모질어도 <br>그 정도는 언제 든지 <br>든지 든지 든지 가능해 <br>Give me a call Oh Call me <br>Don't worry <br>내가 곁에 있잖아 <br>Give me a call Oh Call me <br>Don't worry <br>내가 곁에 있잖아 <br>친 친 친 친구 있어 <br>좋다는 게 뭐야 <br>힘 힘 힘 힘들 때 <br>기댈 수 있는 거야 <br>혼자라고 느껴지는 순간에 <br>떠오르는 사람 얼굴 이야 <br>그게 바로 바로 바로 <br>바로 바로 바로 친구야 <br>친 친 친 친구 있어 <br>좋다는 게 뭐야 <br>힘 힘 힘 힘들 때 <br>기댈 수 있는 거야 <br>혼자라고 느껴지는 순간에 <br>떠오르는 사람 얼굴 이야 <br>그게 바로 바로 바로 <br>바로 바로 바로 친구야 <br>그게 바로 바로 바로 <br>바로 바로 바로 친구야 <br>]]></content><category term="컬YP" label="컬YP"/><category term="십만원" label="십만원"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지근식/그대에게_Feat_최승호/</id><title>지근식 - 그대에게 (Feat. 최승호) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:08:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:08:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EA%B7%BC%EC%8B%9D/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_Feat_%EC%B5%9C%EC%8A%B9%ED%98%B8/" title="지근식 - 그대에게 (Feat. 최승호) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아침햇살에 눈이 부셔요 새들은 하늘높이 올라요 <br><br>멀리보이는 푸른 강물은 온몸으로 출렁거려요 <br><br><br><br>가로수들이 웃음머금고 사람들 물결속에 쌓이면 <br><br>온갖꽃들도 웃음머금고 바람따라 일렁거려요 <br><br>아 이렇게 좋은 날엔 그대에게 전화를 걸어 <br><br><br><br>안녕하고 웃으며 얘기하고파 나의 마음을 나의 사랑을 <br><br>그대에게 전해주고파]]></content><category term="지근식" label="지근식"/><category term="그대에게 (Feat. 최승호)" label="그대에게 (Feat. 최승호)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지근식/저_하늘을_날아서_Feat_신수연/</id><title>지근식 - 저 하늘을 날아서 (Feat. 신수연) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:08:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:08:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EA%B7%BC%EC%8B%9D/%EC%A0%80_%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98%EC%9D%84_%EB%82%A0%EC%95%84%EC%84%9C_Feat_%EC%8B%A0%EC%88%98%EC%97%B0/" title="지근식 - 저 하늘을 날아서 (Feat. 신수연) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다시 돌아올수 없는 기억들을 <br>이제는 깨끗이 지워봐요 <br>그리고 저녁 노을이 붉게 물드는 <br>들길 끝까지 걸어가요 <br>별빛이 내려와 눈물 되기전에 <br>어둡던 지난날 지워봐요 <br>언제나 넘실 거리는 환상을 안고 <br>삶의 끝까지 달려가요 <br><br>깨어진 꿈들의 아픈 조각들은 <br>저부는 바람결에 사라지고 <br>이제는 내 뜻대로 힘든 이세상 <br>웃음 지으며 살아 가고싶어 <br><br>새처럼 저 하늘을 날아서 <br>넒은 세상 보고싶어 <br>새처럼 저 하늘을 날아서 <br>넒은 세상 보고싶어]]></content><category term="지근식" label="지근식"/><category term="저 하늘을 날아서 (Feat. 신수연)" label="저 하늘을 날아서 (Feat. 신수연)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지근식/네게_줄_수_있는_건_오직_사랑뿐_Feat_한동준/</id><title>지근식 - 네게 줄 수 있는 건 오직 사랑뿐 (Feat. 한동준) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:08:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:08:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EA%B7%BC%EC%8B%9D/%EB%84%A4%EA%B2%8C_%EC%A4%84_%EC%88%98_%EC%9E%88%EB%8A%94_%EA%B1%B4_%EC%98%A4%EC%A7%81_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EB%BF%90_Feat_%ED%95%9C%EB%8F%99%EC%A4%80/" title="지근식 - 네게 줄 수 있는 건 오직 사랑뿐 (Feat. 한동준) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[표정없는 세월을 보며 <br>흔들리는 너에게 <br>아무것도 줄 수 없는 <br>내가 미웠어 내가 미웠어 <br>불빛없는 거릴 걸으며 <br>헤매이는 너에게 <br>꽃 한송이 주고 싶어 <br>들녁 해바라기를 <br>* 새들은 왜 날아가나 <br>바람은 왜 불어오나 <br>내가슴 모두 태워 줄수 있는건 <br>오직 사랑뿐 오직 사랑뿐]]></content><category term="지근식" label="지근식"/><category term="네게 줄 수 있는 건 오직 사랑뿐 (Feat. 한동준)" label="네게 줄 수 있는 건 오직 사랑뿐 (Feat. 한동준)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헬로비너스/Runway/</id><title>헬로비너스 - Runway - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:09:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:09:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%AC%EB%A1%9C%EB%B9%84%EB%84%88%EC%8A%A4/Runway/" title="헬로비너스 - Runway - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You and I <br>넌 눈을 뜨고서 꾸는 꿈 <br>Yes I do <br>이건 끝이 없는 신기루 <br>내 모든 걸 다 흔들어놔 <br>너의 눈 너의 코 <br>너의 입 특히 눈빛 <br>on on and on on on and on <br>그래 널 기다렸어 boy <br>on on and on on on and on <br>오래전 그날부터 ah <br>널 떠올리다 널 헤매이다 <br>길을 잃은 느낌 oh yeah <br>이 세상이 난 이렇게도 <br>예쁜 적은 처음이야 <br>궁금해 너란 아이 <br>널 여행하고파 <br>긴 활주로를 열어줘 <br>지금 내게만 baby <br>tell me tell me 불러줘 <br>tell me tell me 말해줘 <br>네 두 눈 속의 sign <br>널 기다리는 나 <br>긴 활주로를 열어줘 <br>내가 갈 수 있게 <br>You and I <br>핑크빛의 기류와 이 순간 <br>네가 너무 좋은 나 <br>날 숨기지는 않을 거야 <br>알잖아 이런 나 <br>이런 맘 이런 느낌 <br>on on and on on on and on <br>햇살이 눈이 부셔 boy <br>on on and on on on and on <br>생각만 해도 떨려 oh <br>이 도시가 난 이렇게도 <br>예쁜 적은 처음이야 <br>궁금해 너란 아이 <br>널 여행하고파 <br>긴 활주로를 열어줘 <br>지금 내게만 baby <br>tell me tell me 불러줘 <br>tell me tell me 말해줘 <br>네 두 눈 속의 sign <br>널 기다리는 나 <br>긴 활주로를 열어줘 <br>내가 갈 수 있게 <br>난 발자국을 남길래 <br>네 머릿속에 가득히 <br>나 밖에 모르게 널 <br>그리고 또 영원히 yeah <br>tell me tell me tell me ah <br>tell me tell me tell me <br>더 가까워진 사이 <br>tell me tell me tell me <br>널 바라보는 나 <br>tell me tell me tell me <br>궁금해 너란 아이 <br>널 여행하고파 <br>긴 활주로를 열어줘 <br>지금 내게만 baby <br>tell me tell me 불러줘 <br>tell me tell me 말해줘 <br>네 두 눈 속의 sign <br>널 기다리는 나 <br>긴 활주로를 열어줘 <br>내가 갈 수 있게 <br>]]></content><category term="헬로비너스" label="헬로비너스"/><category term="Runway" label="Runway"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kingons/Bye_Bye_My_Girl/</id><title>Kingons - Bye Bye My Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:09:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:09:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kingons/Bye_Bye_My_Girl/" title="Kingons - Bye Bye My Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Why you're laughing <br>even though I was betrayed again <br>Look a like know the future though <br>Why you'er angry? <br>I would have raised the best gift <br>It looks like has been found to <br>like the future. <br><br>Why you're laughing <br>even though I was betrayed again <br>Look a like know the future though <br>Why you'er angry? <br>I would have raised the best gift <br>It looks like has been found to <br>like the future. <br><br>(Bey bey my girl) <br>Just go home place <br>I might no longer meet? <br>(Bey bey my girl) <br>Just go to bed place? <br>I might not be able <br>anymore to speak!! <br>(Bey bey my girl) <br>I'm glad I like you <br>(Bey bey my girl) <br>Wait'll meet you in the afterlife! <br><br>And it looks like you ready to <br>go on another trip <br>is surging memories <br>Today know what day! <br>And recall <br>Only a little more <br>Only a little more <br>I'm sure <br>(Bey bey my girl) <br>Just go home place <br>I might no longer meet? <br>(Bey bey my girl) <br>Just go to bed place? <br>I might not be able <br>anymore to speak!! <br>(Bey bey my girl) <br>I'm glad I like you <br>(Bey bey my girl) <br>Wait'll meet you in the afterlife!]]></content><category term="Kingons" label="Kingons"/><category term="Bye Bye My Girl" label="Bye Bye My Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kingons/P_O_P/</id><title>Kingons - P. O. P - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:10:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:10:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kingons/P_O_P/" title="Kingons - P. O. P - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know <br>"sha la la la la" <br>I hear music in the morning. <br>I fell that music forwards it so. <br>I think "shing-a-ling-a-ling" <br>do not sing in my room. <br>I look at stone of the garden. <br>Only a curtain soaks into sunlight. <br>I want to stand in the line <br>of the big child, <br>and small adult. <br>I want to cry. <br>I want to cry. <br>"Wow!" <br>I don't know <br>"sha la la la la" <br>I hear music in the morning. <br>I fell that music forwards it so. <br>I think "shing-a-ling-a-ling" <br>do not sing in my room. <br>I look at stone of the garden. <br>Only a curtain soaks into sunlight. <br>I want to stand in the line <br>of the big child, <br>and small adult. <br>I want to cry. <br>I want to cry. <br>"Wow!" <br><br>Wake up. wake up. <br>Sunday in the morning. <br>I found beautiful stone to you. <br>I saw the stone. I saw the stone. <br>It began to shine and dance suddenly. <br>Wake up. Wake up. <br>Sunday in the morning <br>I found beautiful stone to you. <br>I wanna send it to you <br>before magic is over. <br>Wake up. Wake up. <br>Wake up. Wake up. <br><br>Only a curtain soaks into sunlight. <br>I want to stand in the line <br>of the big child, <br>and small adult. <br>I want to cry. <br>I want to cry. <br>"Wow!" <br><br>Wake up. wake up. <br>Sunday in the morning. <br>I found beautiful stone to you. <br>I saw the stone. I saw the stone. <br>It began to shine and dance suddenly. <br>Wake up. Wake up. <br>Sunday in the morning <br>I found beautiful stone to you. <br>I wanna send it to you <br>before magic is over.]]></content><category term="Kingons" label="Kingons"/><category term="P. O. P" label="P. O. P"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BLACKPINK/휘파람_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>BLACKPINK - 휘파람 (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:15:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:15:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BLACKPINK/%ED%9C%98%ED%8C%8C%EB%9E%8C_Acoustic_Ver/" title="BLACKPINK - 휘파람 (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[hey boy <br>Make’ em whistle like a missile bomb bomb <br>Every time I show up blow up uh <br>Make’ em whistle like a missile bomb bomb <br>Every time I show up blow up uh <br>넌 너무 아름다워 <br>널 잊을 수가 없어 <br>그 눈빛이 아직 나를 <br>이렇게 설레게 해 boom boom <br>24 365 <br>오직 너와 같이 하고파 <br>낮에도 이 밤에도 <br>이렇게 너를 원해 ooh ooh <br>모든 남자들이 날 매일 check out <br>대부분이 날 가질 수 있다 착각 <br>절대 많은 걸 원치 않아 맘을 원해 난 <br>넌 심장을 도려내 보여봐 <br>아주 씩씩하게 때론 chic chic 하게 <br>So hot so hot 내가 어쩔 줄 모르게 해 <br>나지막이 불러줘 <br>내 귓가에 도는 휘파람처럼 <br>이대로 지나치지 마요 <br>너도 나처럼 날 잊을 수가 없다면 WHOA <br>널 향한 이 마음은 Fire <br>내 심장이 빠르게 뛰잖아 <br>점점 가까이 들리잖아 <br>휘파람 <br>UH 휘 파람 파람 파람 <br>can you hear that <br>휘 파라파라 파라 밤 <br>휘파람 <br>UH 휘 파람 파람 파람 <br>can you hear that <br>휘 파라파라 파라 밤 <br>Hold up <br>아무 말 하지 마 <br>Just whistle to my heart <br>그 소리가 지금 나를 <br>이렇게 설레게 해 boom boom <br>생각은 지루해 <br>느낌이 shhh <br>Every day all day <br>내 곁에만 있어줘 zoom zoom <br>Uh 언제나 난 stylin’ <br>도도하지만 네 앞에선 darlin’ <br>뜨거워지잖아 like a desert island <br>너 알아갈수록 울려대는 마음속 <br>그만 내빼 넘어와라 내게 boy <br>이젠 checkmate <br>게임은 내가 win uh-huh <br>난 널 택해 안아줘 더 세게 누가 널 가로 <br>채 가기 전에 내가 uh <br>이대로 지나치지 마요 <br>너도 나처럼 날 잊을 수가 없다면 WHOA <br>널 향한 이 마음은 Fire <br>내 심장이 빠르게 뛰잖아 <br>점점 가까이 들리잖아 <br>휘파람 <br>UH 휘 파람 파람 파람 <br>can you hear that <br>휘 파라파라 파라 밤 <br>휘파람 <br>UH 휘 파람 파람 파람 <br>can you hear that <br>휘 파라파라 파라 밤 <br>This beat got me feelin’ like <br>바람처럼 스쳐가는 <br>흔한 인연이 아니길 <br>많은 말은 필요 없어 <br>지금 너의 곁에 <br>나를 데려가 줘 ohh <br>Make’ em whistle like a missile bomb bomb <br>Every time I show up blow up uh <br>Make’ em whistle like a missile bomb bomb <br>Every time I show up blow up uh <br>]]></content><category term="BLACKPINK" label="BLACKPINK"/><category term="휘파람 (Acoustic Ver.)" label="휘파람 (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BLACKPINK/STAY/</id><title>BLACKPINK - STAY - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:15:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:15:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BLACKPINK/STAY/" title="BLACKPINK - STAY - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[툭하면 거친 말들로 <br>내 맘에 상처를 내놓고 <br>미안하단 말 한마디 없이 <br>또 나 혼자 위로하고 <br>오늘 하루도 혹시 날 떠날까 <br>늘 불안해 해 <br>I just want you to stay <br>점점 무뎌져 가는 너의 그 무표정 속에 <br>천천히 내려놓자며 거울에 속삭이곤 해 <br>날 당연하게 생각하는 너지만 <br>그게 너다워 <br>그래도 stay stay stay with me <br>널 닮은 듯한 슬픈 멜로디 <br>이렇게 날 울리는데 eh eh <br>네 향기는 달콤한 felony <br>너무 밉지만 사랑해 <br>어두운 밤이 날 가두기 전에 <br>내 곁을 떠나지마 <br>아직 날 사랑하니 <br>내 맘과 같다면 오늘은 떠나지마 <br>굳이 너여야만 하는 이유는 묻지마 <br>그저 내 곁에 stay with me <br>It goes a little something like <br>지금 당장 많은 걸 바라는 게 아냐 <br>그저 내 곁에 stay with me <br>사실은 난 더 바라는 게 없어 이제 <br>심장은 뛰긴 하는 건지 무감각해 그래 <br>사람들과의 억지스런 한마디보단 <br>너와의 어색한 침묵이 차라리 좋아 <br>So stay 그게 어디가 됐건 말이야 <br>가끔 어둠이 올 때면 I’ll be your fire <br>거짓 같은 세상 속 유일한 truth it’s you <br>This a letter from me to you <br>널 닮은 듯한 슬픈 멜로디 <br>이렇게 날 울리는데 eh eh <br>네 향기는 달콤한 felony <br>너무 밉지만 사랑해 <br>어두운 밤이 날 가두기 전에 <br>내 곁을 떠나지마 <br>아직 날 사랑하니 <br>내 맘과 같다면 오늘은 떠나지마 <br>굳이 너여야만 하는 이유는 묻지마 <br>그저 내 곁에 stay with me <br>It goes a little something like <br>지금 당장 많은걸 바라는 게 아냐 <br>그저 내 곁에 stay with me <br>It goes a little something like <br>지금 당장 많은걸 바라는 게 아냐 <br>그저 내 곁에 stay with me <br>]]></content><category term="BLACKPINK" label="BLACKPINK"/><category term="STAY" label="STAY"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BLACKPINK/불장난/</id><title>BLACKPINK - 불장난 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:15:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:15:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BLACKPINK/%EB%B6%88%EC%9E%A5%EB%82%9C/" title="BLACKPINK - 불장난 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 엄만 매일 내게 말했어 <br>언제나 남자 조심하라고 <br>사랑은 마치 불장난 같아서 다치니까 Eh <br>엄마 말이 꼭 맞을지도 몰라 <br>널 보면 내 맘이 뜨겁게 달아올라 <br>두려움보단 널 향한 끌림이 더 크니까 Eh <br>멈출 수 없는 이 떨림은 <br>On and on and on <br>내 전부를 너란 세상에 <br>다 던지고 싶어 <br>Look at me look at me now <br>이렇게 넌 날 애태우고 있잖아 <br>끌 수 없어 <br>우리 사랑은 불장난 <br>My love is on fire <br>Now burn baby burn <br>불장난 <br>My love is on fire <br>So don’t play with me boy <br>불장난 <br>Oh no 난 이미 멀리 와버렸는걸 <br>어느새 이 모든 게 장난이 아닌 걸 <br>사랑이란 빨간 불씨 <br>불어라 바람 더 커져가는 불길 <br>이게 약인지 독인지 우리 엄마도 몰라 <br>내 맘 도둑인데 왜 경찰도 몰라 <br>불 붙은 내 심장에 더 부어라 너란 기름 <br>kiss him will I diss him I <br>don’t know but I miss him <br>중독을 넘어선 이 사랑은 crack <br>내 심장의 색깔은 black <br>멈출 수 없는 이 떨림은 <br>On and on and on <br>내 전부를 너란 불길 속으로 <br>던지고 싶어 <br>Look at me look at me now <br>이렇게 넌 날 애태우고 있잖아 <br>끌 수 없어 <br>우리 사랑은 불장난 <br>My love is on fire <br>Now burn baby burn <br>불장난 <br>My love is on fire <br>So don’t play with me boy <br>불장난 <br>걷잡을 수가 없는 걸 <br>너무나 빨리 퍼져 가는 이 불길 <br>이런 날 멈추지 마 <br>이 사랑이 오늘 밤을 태워버리게 <br>whooo <br>]]></content><category term="BLACKPINK" label="BLACKPINK"/><category term="불장난" label="불장난"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍개/편지/</id><title>홍개 - 편지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:15:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:15:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EA%B0%9C/%ED%8E%B8%EC%A7%80/" title="홍개 - 편지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[텅 빈 편지지에는 <br>그대의 이야기만을 <br>담아내려 해요 <br>생각이 헤픈 건지 <br>하루하루 의미 없이 <br>끄적이고 있죠 <br>어느덧 길어지던 인사와 <br>수많은 비유 속에 <br>감춰진 진심을 <br>이렇게나마 전하려고 해 <br>나에게 떠난단 말도 <br>하지 않았죠 <br>아플 거란 거 알고 있었죠 <br>모른 척했었던 거죠 <br>이제는 알아요 <br>슬플 땐 울어야 해요 <br>내 감정에 솔직해져야겠어 <br>봄이 돌아와서 <br>문득 그대가 그리울 때 <br>바보처럼 미소를 지을 거야 <br>비밀이 되어버린 사랑을 <br>소중했던 기억들을 <br>지워버려서 <br>다시는 그댈 볼 수 없지만 <br>인연은 운명이 <br>될 거라던 그 말에 <br>언젠간 그 손 잡을 수 있게 <br>미련을 남겨요 <br>이제는 알아요 <br>슬플 땐 울어야 해요 <br>내 감정에 솔직해져야겠어 <br>봄이 돌아와서 <br>문득 그대가 그리울 때 <br>바보처럼 미소를 지을 거야 <br>네가 돌아오지 않는다 해도 <br>나는 괜찮아 <br>너의 곁에서 맴돌 순 있으니까 <br>네가 사랑하지 않는다 해도 <br>나는 괜찮아 <br>너의 곁에서 난 행복했으니까 <br>텅 빈 편지지에는 <br>우리의 이야기들을 <br>담아내려 해요 <br>생각이 예쁜 거죠 <br>하루하루 꿈꾸듯이 <br>그려가고 있죠 <br>]]></content><category term="홍개" label="홍개"/><category term="편지" label="편지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/셀프어쿠스틱/11월_11일/</id><title>셀프어쿠스틱 - 11월 11일 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:15:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:15:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%85%80%ED%94%84%EC%96%B4%EC%BF%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B1/11%EC%9B%94_11%EC%9D%BC/" title="셀프어쿠스틱 - 11월 11일 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[11월11일 <br>대체 무슨 날이길래 <br>너도 나도 할 것 없이 <br>들고 있는 저건 뭘까 <br>마트를 가도 편의점을 가도 <br>지하철역 앞을 가도 <br>초코 막대 과자가 <br>이렇게 많은걸 보면 분명 <br>알아 나도 <br>오늘이 무슨 날인지 <br>1년에 한 번뿐인 <br>오늘은 바로 <br>숫자 1처럼 <br>힘차게 일어서자는 <br>지체장애인의 날 <br>자랑스러운 대한민국 <br>해군이 만들어진 <br>해군 창설 기념일 <br>소중한 우리 농산물 <br>우리 것이 최고여 <br>농업인의 날 <br>오늘은 11월 11일 <br>]]></content><category term="셀프어쿠스틱" label="셀프어쿠스틱"/><category term="11월 11일" label="11월 11일"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Who/I_Cant_Explain_Mono_Ver/</id><title>The Who - I Can`t Explain (Mono Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:18:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:18:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Who/I_Cant_Explain_Mono_Ver/" title="The Who - I Can`t Explain (Mono Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Got a feeling inside Can't explain <br>It's a certain kind Can't explain <br>I feel hot and cold Can't explain <br>Yeah, down in my soul, yeah Can't explain <br><br>I said Can't explain <br>I'm feeling good now, yeah, but Can't explain <br><br>Dizzy in the head and I'm feeling blue <br>The things you've said, well, maybe they're true <br>I'm gettin' funny dreams again and again <br>I know what it means, but <br><br>Can't explain <br>I think it's love <br>Try to say it to you <br>When I feel blue <br><br>But I can't explain Can't explain <br>Yeah, hear what I'm saying, girl Can't explain <br><br>Dizzy in the head and I'm feeling bad <br>The things you've said have got me real mad <br>I'm gettin' funny dreams again and again <br>I know what it means but <br><br>Can't explain <br>I think it's love <br>Try to say it to you <br>When I feel blue <br><br>But I can't explain Can't explain <br>Forgive me one more time, now Can't explain <br><br>I said I can't explain, yeah <br>You drive me out of my mind <br>Yeah, I'm the worrying kind, babe <br>I said I can't explain]]></content><category term="The Who" label="The Who"/><category term="I Can`t Explain (Mono Ver.)" label="I Can`t Explain (Mono Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Devil/</id><title>Tyler Glenn - Devil - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:19:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:19:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Devil/" title="Tyler Glenn - Devil - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday mornings make me nervous <br>They don't feel like they used to feel <br>My religion feels wrong, but I can't tell my mom <br>I'm afraid that my words would kill <br><br>I think I still believe in Jesus <br>He's a friend when I choose to pray <br>But my demons get me high <br>'Til I'm burning all the time <br>Yeah, they never wash my sins away <br><br>Singing I I I <br>I'm singing hymns at the top of my lungs <br>I I I <br>I'm singing hymns at the top of my lungs <br><br>I think the devil made me do it, do it, baby <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br><br>I think the devil made me do it, now I'm crazy <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br><br>Don't pray for me <br>Don't pray for me <br>Don't, no no no no <br>Don't pray for me <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br><br>As Sunday service got me anxious <br>It's the reason that I was depressed <br>I could see it on their face <br>I did not deserve His grace <br>So I skipped the holy sacrament <br><br>I swear I still believe in something <br>But I couldn't pray the gay away <br>So if I'm the wicked one <br>I'm still my mama's son <br>And you'll never take that love away <br><br>Singing I I I <br>I'm singing hymns at the top of my lungs <br>I I I <br>I'm singing hymns at the top of my lungs <br><br>Oh, I think the devil made me do it, do it, baby <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br><br>I think the devil made me do it, now I'm crazy <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br><br>Don't pray for me <br>Don't pray for me <br>Don't, no no no no <br>Don't pray for me <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br><br>I'm letting go, it's not your fault <br>You'll always be a work of art <br>I told you I'm leaving this morning <br>No, wait wait, don't pick up the phone <br><br>Just let it go to message, maybe you could keep it <br>Yeah, tell her I'm coming home <br>Tell mama I'm coming home <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br><br>I think the devil made me do it, do it, baby <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br><br>I think the devil made me do it, now I'm crazy <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br><br>Don't pray for me <br>Don't pray for me <br>Don't, no no no no <br>Don't pray for me <br>I found myself when I lost my faith <br><br>I'm letting go, it's not your fault <br>You'll always be a work of art <br>I told you I'm leaving this morning <br>No, wait wait, don't pick up the phone <br><br>You'll let it go to message <br>Maybe you could heep it <br>Just tell her I'm coming home <br>Tell mama I'm coming home <br>I found myself when I lost my faith]]></content><category term="Tyler Glenn" label="Tyler Glenn"/><category term="Devil" label="Devil"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/John_Give_Em_Hell/</id><title>Tyler Glenn - John, Give `Em Hell - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:19:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:19:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/John_Give_Em_Hell/" title="Tyler Glenn - John, Give `Em Hell - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I heard your voice inside my darkness <br>You gave me something to hold onto <br>And did you ever start to notice <br>All these voices change the world <br><br>And John, they got you all wrong <br>So I wrote you this song <br>And John, keep on keeping on <br>There's work to be done <br><br>And in the meantime give 'em hell <br>In the meantime give 'em hell <br>Truth is all that they want <br>But the truth's a one two punch <br><br>Give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell <br><br>Give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell <br><br>Our lives are different, different commitments <br>Sins and religion, what do they mean <br>Some say you're evil, but I think you're real <br>I just want what's real from this whole thing <br><br>And John, they got you all wrong <br>So I wrote you this song <br>And John, keep on keeping on <br>Don't let them think they've won <br><br>And in the meantime give 'em hell <br>In the meantime give 'em hell <br>Truth is all that they want <br>But the truth's a one two punch <br><br>Give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell <br><br>And give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell <br><br>And give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell <br><br>Give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell <br><br>Give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell <br><br>Go give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell <br>Give 'em hell]]></content><category term="Tyler Glenn" label="Tyler Glenn"/><category term="John, Give `Em Hell" label="John, Give `Em Hell"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Black_Light/</id><title>Tyler Glenn - Black Light - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:19:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:19:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Black_Light/" title="Tyler Glenn - Black Light - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Change is good when I touch him <br>But I wish we would, we could start now <br>Is it crazy that you're on my couch <br>Everything you're saying's what I'm saying <br>Loving life and excommunication <br><br>I'll go and turn the lights <br>I like them low at night <br>I could tell you what I'm thinking <br>I gotta tell you what I'm thinking <br><br>Oh, say that you're feeling what I'm feeling too <br>Pray I don't play the way I used to <br>Oh, something's taking over me <br>You got me under the black light, baby <br><br>Stay, come and be my daily ritual <br>Play, we'll break the rules like back in school <br>I want you under, under, under me <br>I want you under the black light, baby <br><br>Lose my mind <br>Trouble seems to be a friend of mine <br>Could we keep the faith <br>I really want to but I can't see straight <br>Everything you say is what I'm saying <br>Love and life and miscommunication <br><br>I'm ready for the real <br>Man, life is so surreal <br>I can tell you what I'm thinking <br>I'm gonna tell you what I'm thinking <br><br>Oh, say that you're feeling what I'm feeling too <br>Pray I don't play the way I used to <br>Oh, something's taking over me <br>You got me under the black light, baby <br><br>Oh stay, come and be my daily ritual <br>Play, we'll break the rules like back in school <br>I want you under, under, under me <br>I want you under the black light, baby <br><br>Fortune favors the brave <br>Thing are getting weird but I like it <br>Please, please say I'm not insane <br>Thing are getting weird but I like it <br>Under the black light <br><br>Say that you're feeling what I'm feeling too <br>Pray I don't play the way I used to <br>Oh, something's taking over me <br>You got me under the black light, baby <br><br>Stay, come and be my daily ritual <br>Play, we'll break the rules like back in school <br>I want you under, under, under me <br>I want you under the black light, baby <br><br>I want you, I want you x8]]></content><category term="Tyler Glenn" label="Tyler Glenn"/><category term="Black Light" label="Black Light"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/One_More/</id><title>Tyler Glenn - One More - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:19:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:19:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/One_More/" title="Tyler Glenn - One More - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's always me and you against the world, I swear <br>I could be like anybody else, I don't fight fair <br>But you don't care <br><br>It's always me and you against the world, my god <br>Spend an afternoon inside your room watching Sci Fi <br>You get me high <br><br>And if you give me just one more night <br>I could prove that there's a God <br>And if you give me just one more try <br>I was liking you a lot <br><br>I know it's crazy and insane <br>I think it's weird when you're away <br>It's you I adore <br>So give me one more, one more <br><br>It's always me and you against the world, by far <br>We could be like anybody else in a parked car <br>But I've got your heart <br><br>It's always me and you against the world, my god <br>Spend a decade letting go of shame and then we'll talk <br>I'm gonna walk, I gotta walk <br><br>But if you give me just one more night <br>I could prove that there's a God <br>And if you give me just one more try <br>I was liking you a lot <br><br>I know it's crazy and insane <br>I think it's weird when you're away <br>It's you I adore <br>So give me one more, one more, one more <br><br>I know, I know it's never too late <br>Never too late, never too late <br>I know, I know it's never too late <br>Never too late, never too late <br><br>And if you give me just one more night <br>I could prove that there's a God <br>And if you give me just one more try <br>I was liking you a lot <br><br>I know it's crazy and insane <br>I think it's weird when you're away <br>It's you I adore <br>So give me one more, one more, one more <br><br>It's never too late <br>Never too late <br>Never too late <br>One more, one more]]></content><category term="Tyler Glenn" label="Tyler Glenn"/><category term="One More" label="One More"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Midnight/</id><title>Tyler Glenn - Midnight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:19:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:19:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Midnight/" title="Tyler Glenn - Midnight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[God, God <br>God, God <br>God <br><br>Faith, please have a little in me, hey <br>I know you hate it when I stray <br>But I tried everything, I drank the wine and stained the sheets <br>I'm clumsy when I speak <br><br>Call, you never call me anymore <br>We're past the point of self control <br>I'm getting back to you, things I thought were true <br>I know it's really nothing new <br><br>God, where the hell are you hiding <br>My hands are in the air and I'm excited <br>I've been on the run, so I'm not coming Sunday <br>It's alright, I'll probably talk to you at midnight <br><br>God, I could never be like you <br>I can't change, I can't change and I don't want to <br>I've been on the run, so I'm not coming Sunday <br>It's alright, I'll probably talk to you at midnight <br><br>Fear, that's what it was just to be clear <br>You went and made everything weird <br>But that's another song, another night, a shattered rung <br>I guess what's done is done <br><br>Bright, I fall and stumble towards the light <br>I'll miss the days and nights <br>We wrestled in my bedroom, my knees will give out soon <br>I know it's really nothing new <br><br>God, where the hell are you hiding <br>My hands are in the air and it's so exciting <br>I've been on the run, so I'm not coming Sunday <br>It's alright, I'll probably talk to you at midnight <br><br>God, I could never be like you <br>I can't change, I can't change and I don't want to <br>I've been on the run, so I'm not coming Sunday <br>It's alright, I'll probably talk to you at midnight <br><br>I'll probably talk to you at midnight <br><br>God, I could never be like you <br>I can't change, I can't change and I don't want to <br>I've been on the run, so I'm not coming Sunday <br>It's alright, I'll probably talk to you at midnight]]></content><category term="Tyler Glenn" label="Tyler Glenn"/><category term="Midnight" label="Midnight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/First_Vision/</id><title>Tyler Glenn - First Vision - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:19:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:19:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/First_Vision/" title="Tyler Glenn - First Vision - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I see it <br>I see it <br>I see it <br>I see it in front of me <br>I see it <br>I see it <br>I see it <br>This is my first vision <br><br>I just tried to pay for a round of drinks on my hotel key <br>I've been depressed lately but I say that I'm happy <br>I swear to God I think that death is following me <br>On my third glass of Malbec <br>He hasn't texted me back <br><br>I fell in love with him but he's a married man <br>Still got these feelings I don't think he'll understand <br>I feel the blush in my brain when I touch his hand <br>We could talk for hours <br>Yeah, we'd talk for hours <br><br>I see it <br>I see it <br>I see it <br>I see it in front of me <br>I see it <br>I see it <br>I see it <br>This is my first vision <br><br>My brother started saying things behind my back <br>Nobody wants to talk about the elephant <br>We'll just ignore the problems 'til we all forget <br>Something's in the distance <br>Something <br>Something <br><br>My further light and knowledge gave me second sight <br>I think I lost the spirit maybe it's a sign <br>Let's say I gave up God and Jesus <br>What do I believe in and what do I believe <br><br>I see it <br>I see it <br>I see it <br>I see it in front of me <br>I see it <br>I see it <br>I see it <br>This is my first vision <br><br>I used feel it and now I don't feel it at all <br>I'm painting over all the paintings on my wall <br>My tears are dry and finally I feel ten feet tall <br>Darkness, get behind me <br>Darkness <br>Darkness <br><br>I see it <br>I see it <br>I see it <br>I see it in front of me <br>I see it <br>I see it <br>I see it <br>This is my first vision <br><br>This is my first vision]]></content><category term="Tyler Glenn" label="Tyler Glenn"/><category term="First Vision" label="First Vision"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Waiting_Around/</id><title>Tyler Glenn - Waiting Around - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:19:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:19:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Waiting_Around/" title="Tyler Glenn - Waiting Around - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're an old pro <br>Drama rama like a talk show <br>Makes me wanna quit my day job <br>Lose my inhibition <br>Inhibition <br><br>Going solo <br>Man, I post too many photos <br>Jack and cherry Coca cola <br>On my white t shirt <br>Gone, lost religion <br>What religion <br><br>Oh, you got me waiting around for your call <br>My faith is patient but it's hitting a wall <br>Swear on the book you're gonna miss me <br>Kiss me if we're not gonna talk <br><br>I'm always waiting around for your call <br>Show me a sign and I'll send you my love <br>You got me giving up on Jesus <br>Lost in places I don't wanna go <br>Waiting and waiting around for you <br><br>Vice and virtue <br>I got words that are gonna hurt you <br>I'm a go and get the hell out of town <br>Go south, get caught for stealing <br>I need you near me <br><br>I need a new clue <br>Spill my guts out on my new shoes <br>I want you, but he will do what he do <br>When we're through he's up and leaving <br>Why did you leave me <br><br>Oh, you got me waiting around for your call <br>My faith is patient but it's hitting a wall <br>Swear on the book you're gonna miss me <br>Kiss me if we're not gonna talk <br><br>I'm always waiting around for your call <br>Show me a sign, show me anything at all <br>You got me giving up on Jesus <br>Lost in places I don't wanna go <br>Waiting and waiting around for you <br><br>I'm a fool but I'm tired of being foolish <br>Reading up on history can mess with your head <br>Up at night, you and I went and died <br>Stone cold like the sheets in my bed <br><br>You got me waiting around for your call <br>My faith is patient but its hitting a wall <br>Swear on the book you're gonna miss me <br>Kiss me if we're not gonna talk <br><br>I'm always waiting around for your call <br>Show me a sign, give me anything at all <br>You got me giving up on Jesus <br>Lost in places I don't wanna go <br>Waiting and waiting around for you <br><br>Always waiting around]]></content><category term="Tyler Glenn" label="Tyler Glenn"/><category term="Waiting Around" label="Waiting Around"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Shameless/</id><title>Tyler Glenn - Shameless - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:19:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:19:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Shameless/" title="Tyler Glenn - Shameless - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, your talk is cheap, you like mystery <br>I been awake since 2AM <br>I can barely stand another low <br>But the highs I wanna do 'em again <br>Maybe meet you with a couple friends <br>This ain't love, but maybe we pretend <br>Rent some pornographic movie <br>And we both know how it ends <br>I won't say it again <br><br>It's the darkest time of the night <br>God and vodka might save my life <br>You judge, but I don't give a damn <br>I live a life so shameless <br><br>I live a life so shameless <br>Oh no, I don't give a damn <br>I live a life so shameless <br><br>Go ahead, lock me up <br>And throw away the key <br>My heart's beatin' like a feelin' <br>I got more tricks up my sleeve <br>You'll never get it, but you regret it <br>You won't forget this when we're done <br>Hell and heaven, quit pretendin' <br>Now I'm havin' too much fun <br>Do you want some <br><br>Why not take me now as I am <br>Why not take me now like a man <br>You hate what you don't understand <br>I live a life so shameless <br><br>I live a life so shameless <br>I live a life so shameless <br>Oh no, I don't give a damn <br>I live a life so shameless <br><br>I've been fighting off <br>A hurricane inside of me <br>Here comes waves waves waves <br>In my brain brain brain <br>I just wanna feel your body <br>On my bo bo dy <br>A public enemy <br><br>It's the darkest time of the night <br>God and vodka just saved my life my life, my life, my life <br>You judge, but I don't give no <br>No I don't give a damn <br>Why not take me not as I am <br>Why not take me not like a man <br>You hate what you don't understand <br>I live a life so shameless <br><br>Oh no, I don't give a damn <br>I live a life so shameless <br>You hate what you don't understand <br>I live a life so shameless <br>No no no no no no no no <br>I live a life so shameless <br>You hate what you don't understand, I don't give a damn <br>I live a life so shameless]]></content><category term="Tyler Glenn" label="Tyler Glenn"/><category term="Shameless" label="Shameless"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Gates/</id><title>Tyler Glenn - Gates - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:19:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:19:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Gates/" title="Tyler Glenn - Gates - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Too many lights on me <br>There's way too, too many lights on me <br>And give me everything you got <br>I think I'm going to go get lost <br>Cause there's way too, too many lights <br><br>Imma kiss my love like I want to <br>Dancing in the dark like I used to <br>Does anybody wanna smoke in the back room <br>I used to be somebody cool that your friends knew <br><br>Imma kiss my love like I want to <br>Gotta love him while I can like the great's do <br>We can make it through the night <br>It'll be cool, it'll be cool <br><br>I'll see you at the gates, I'll see you at the gates <br>Baby, we're just gonna live forever, baby, heaven's gonna stay <br>If it's true and I lost my way, if it's true and I lost my way then <br>I'll see you at the gates, Imma see you at the gates <br><br>I will see you at the gates see you at <br>I will see you at the gates see you at <br>I will see you at the gates see you at <br>I will see you at the gates see you at <br><br>There's too many lights on me, yeah <br>I never wanted so many eyes on me <br>We can meet up in a dream <br>I say we stop pretending, please <br>Cause there's way too, too many lights <br><br>Imma live my life like I want to <br>Hanging in the park like I used to <br>Does anybody have a song we can sway to <br>We used to be somebody cool that our friends knew <br><br>Imma tell the truth like I can't choose <br>Gotta tell them while I can like the great's do <br>We can make it through the night if we keep our cool <br>If we keep our cool <br><br>I'll see you at the gates, I'll see you at the gates <br>Baby, we're just gonna live forever, baby, heaven's gonna stay <br>If it's true and I lost my way, if it's true and I lost my way then <br>I'll see you at the gates, Imma see you at the gates <br><br>I will see you at the gates see you at <br>I will see you at the gates yeah <br>I will see you at the gates see you at <br>I will see you at the gates <br><br>Take me to the coast, my makeup's on and I think I feel pretty <br>Keep me far away from Salt Lake City <br>It's you I love the most, so let's have a toast <br>A tango with the Father, Son, and Holy Ghost <br><br>I'll see you at the gates, I'll see you at the gates <br>Baby, we're just gonna live forever, baby, heaven's gonna stay <br>If it's true and I lost my way, if it's true and I lost my way then <br>I'll see you at the gates, Imma see you at the gates <br><br>I will see you at the gates see you at <br>I will see you at the gates see you at <br>I will see you at the gates see you at <br>I will see you at the gates see you at <br><br>I will see you at the gates see you at <br>I will see you at the gates see you at <br>I will see you at the gates see you at <br>I will see you at the gates]]></content><category term="Tyler Glenn" label="Tyler Glenn"/><category term="Gates" label="Gates"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Gods__Monsters/</id><title>Tyler Glenn - Gods + Monsters - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:19:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:19:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Gods__Monsters/" title="Tyler Glenn - Gods + Monsters - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I believed in gods and monsters too <br>Then I found out they're all impostors just like you <br>Somebody take me higher, higher, higher <br>Until I'm up in the clouds <br>I'm a king with no crown <br>And I ain't ever gonna come back down <br><br>I just walked around your city <br>It felt like a lifetime ago <br>We were naked in your bed <br>I remember what I said <br><br>It was like I made you kiss him on the mouth <br>I was looking at your phone <br>You were in the shower <br>That was then and this is now <br><br>Yeah <br>Players only love you when they're playing <br>Players only love you when they're playing <br>Playing, playing, oh <br><br>I believed in gods and monsters too <br>Then I found out they're all impostors just like you <br>Somebody take me higher, higher, higher <br>Until I'm up in the clouds <br>I'm a king with no crown <br>And I ain't ever gonna come back down <br><br>November 6th was a hell of a ride <br>Do you remember when I called you and we both cried <br>You were with your friends at the fault line <br>Then you fed me some lie about your old mind <br>I lost the Lord then I lost you <br>Then I mixed my dignity with your new fruit juice <br>I keep on leaning on the window seat <br>And angels on the buildings <br>Your a song that we sung to <br><br>Players only love you when they're playing, yeah <br>Players only love you when they're playing, playing <br>Oh <br><br>I believed in gods and monsters too <br>Then I found out they're all impostors just like you <br>Somebody take me higher, higher, higher <br>Until I'm up in the clouds <br>I'm a king with no crown <br>And I ain't ever gonna come back down <br><br>I took a peepee on the curtain and I <br>I took a peepee on the curtain and I freak <br>I need more sleep, less of the dream <br>Maybe more weed <br>Yes please, yes please, yes please <br><br>I believed in gods and monsters too <br>Then I found out they're all impostors just like you <br>Somebody take me higher, higher, higher <br>Until I'm up in the clouds <br>I'm a king with no crown <br>And I ain't ever gonna come back down <br><br>Well I ain't ever gonna come back down <br>No I ain't ever gonna come back down <br>I ain't ever gonna go]]></content><category term="Tyler Glenn" label="Tyler Glenn"/><category term="Gods + Monsters" label="Gods + Monsters"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Trash/</id><title>Tyler Glenn - Trash - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:19:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:19:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Trash/" title="Tyler Glenn - Trash - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I think I lost myself in your new religion <br>You say a prayer for me like a superstition <br>We were always made for love <br>We could always speak in tongues <br>On my knees and I'm seeing visions <br>Yeah, you remind me that seven sins are deadly <br>You used to baptize me when I wasn't ready <br>Water never turns to wine <br>I've been drinking all the time <br>I think of you whenever I see fire in the sky <br><br>Your friends think I'm a freak <br>What was in my drink <br>I can't even think, but we got history <br>In all of this, I lost myself <br>Maybe I'll see you in hell <br>Okay, whatever <br>One man's trash is another man's treasure <br><br>I said my flesh is weak but the spirit's willing <br>And you would sell my soul just to make the killing <br>If you wanted me to stay <br>I'd repent my days away <br>I think of you when I see fire in the sky <br><br>Your friends think I'm a freak <br>What was in my drink <br>I can't even think, but we got history <br>In all of this, I lost myself <br>Maybe I'll see you in hell <br>Okay, whatever <br>One man's trash is another man's treasure <br><br>You keep throwing me out like <br>You keep throwing me out like <br>You keep throwing me out like <br>One man's trash is another man's treasure <br>One man's trash is another man's treasure <br><br>Your friends think I'm a freak <br>What was in my drink <br>I can't even think, but we got history <br>In all of this, I lost myself <br>Maybe I'll see you in hell <br>Okay, whatever <br>One man's trash is another man's treasure <br>One man's trash is another man's treasure]]></content><category term="Tyler Glenn" label="Tyler Glenn"/><category term="Trash" label="Trash"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/GDMML_GRLS/</id><title>Tyler Glenn - G.D.M.M.L. GRLS - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:19:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:19:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/GDMML_GRLS/" title="Tyler Glenn - G.D.M.M.L. GRLS - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey I've been freaking out <br>Cause I can't keep it up and I'm scared <br>I wanna tell you but it's just like a cross to bear <br>Just like a cross to bear <br><br>I ride the lightning like I'm nineteen <br>And I'm barely aware <br>It's like a cross to bear <br>Just like a cross to bear <br><br>They wanna talk about my sin <br>They wanna say I've lost my shit <br>I'm losing my religion <br>And I just can't get over it, over it <br><br>I keep on hearing evil voices, voices <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>They keep on messing with my choices, choices <br>I keep on telling them <br><br>Hey, God didn't give me alternatives, no <br>When she put me on the earth <br>God didn't make me like girls <br>God didn't make me like <br><br>You see me freaking out <br>I'm thinking I might do something dumb <br>I wanna tell you and I'm not the only one <br>I'm not the only one <br><br>Go on, give up on me <br>I think my father still loves his son <br>I tried to kill myself and I'm not the only one <br>I'm not the only one <br><br>You wanna talk about my sin <br>You wanna say I'm losing it, losing it <br><br>I keep on hearing evil voices, voices <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>They keep on messing with my choices, choices <br>I keep on telling them <br><br>Hey, God didn't give me alternatives, no <br>When she put me on the earth <br>God didn't make me like girls <br>God didn't make me like you <br><br>Gay's not a challenge that I'll overcome <br>Not a thing to be tolerated <br>If I kiss a boy, I'm gonna kiss, that cool <br>Am I fucking up your day Now that's just rude <br>I can tell it was an issue <br>God God God God <br>You unfriended me from Facebook <br>Well we never really talked <br>Not even angry anymore <br>Not even angry anymore <br><br>Hey I've been freaking out <br>Cause I can't keep it up and I'm scared <br>I wanna tell you but it's just like a cross to bear <br>Just like a cross to bear <br><br>I keep on hearing evil voices, voices <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>They keep on messing with my choices, choices <br>I keep on telling them <br><br>Oh, God didn't give me alternatives, no <br>When she put me on the earth <br>God didn't make me like girls <br>God didn't make me like you]]></content><category term="Tyler Glenn" label="Tyler Glenn"/><category term="G.D.M.M.L. GRLS" label="G.D.M.M.L. GRLS"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Sudden_Death_OMG/</id><title>Tyler Glenn - Sudden Death (OMG) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:19:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:19:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tyler_Glenn/Sudden_Death_OMG/" title="Tyler Glenn - Sudden Death (OMG) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[God <br>I never asked to fall from grace <br>You saw it all over my face <br>I left for California <br>I'm searching for my soul <br>But I hate the traffic in LA <br><br>Everybody's saying <br>Baby, you got a little crazy <br>My mind's a little hazy <br>Better not say a word, but <br><br>Oh my god <br>Catch me I'm starting to fall <br>I don't know what all this is for <br>Keep coming at me with your disrespect <br>You went and started a war <br>Now I don't care anymore <br>I keep on living like it's sudden death <br>Sudden death <br><br>I keep on living <br>Keep on living <br>Keep on living <br>Sudden death <br>I keep on living <br>Keep on living <br>Keep on living <br><br>I wish that you would just see me <br>Carried away in revelry <br>It's been a car crash winter <br>They're calling me a sinner <br>Things aren't the way they used to be <br><br>Everybody's saying <br>Baby, you got a little crazy <br>My mind's a little hazy <br>Better not say a word, but <br><br>Oh my god <br>Catch me I'm starting to fall <br>I don't know what all this is for <br>Keep coming at me with your disrespect <br>You went and started a war <br>Now I don't care anymore <br>I keep on living like it's sudden death <br>Sudden death <br><br>I keep on living <br>Keep on living <br>Keep on living <br>Sudden death <br>I keep on living <br>Keep on living <br>Keep on living <br><br>We could go an fake through everything <br>And they could hear us louder if we scream <br>Maybe life is more than just a dream <br>Just a dream <br><br>Oh my god <br>Catch me I'm starting to fall <br>I don't know what all this is for <br>Keep coming at me with your disrespect <br>You went and started a war <br>Now I don't care anymore <br>I keep on living like it's sudden death <br>Sudden death <br><br>I keep on living <br>Keep on living <br>Keep on living <br>Sudden death <br>I keep on living <br>Keep on living <br>Keep on living <br><br>I keep on living <br>Keep on living <br>Keep on living <br>Sudden death <br>I keep on living <br>Keep on living <br>Keep on living <br><br>Oh my god]]></content><category term="Tyler Glenn" label="Tyler Glenn"/><category term="Sudden Death (OMG)" label="Sudden Death (OMG)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sonic_Youth/The_Diamond_Sea_Album_Version___Alternate_Ending/</id><title>Sonic Youth - The Diamond Sea (Album Version / Alternate Ending) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:22:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:22:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sonic_Youth/The_Diamond_Sea_Album_Version___Alternate_Ending/" title="Sonic Youth - The Diamond Sea (Album Version / Alternate Ending) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Time takes its crazy toll <br>And how does your mirror grow <br>You better watch yourself when you jump into it <br>Cause the mirror's gonna steal your soul <br><br>I wonder how it came to be my friend <br>That someone just like you has come again <br>You'll never, never know how close you came <br>Until you fall in love with the diamond rain <br><br>Throw all his trash away <br>Look out he's here to stay <br>Your mirror's gonna crack when he breaks into it <br>And you'll never never be the same <br><br>Look into his eyes and you can see <br>Why all the little kids are dressed in dreams <br>I wonder how he's gonna make it back <br>When he sees that you just know it's make belief <br><br>Blood crystallized as sand <br>And now I hope you'll understand <br>You reflected into his looking glass soul <br>Now the mirror is your only friend <br><br>Look into his eyes and you will see <br>That men are not alone on the diamond sea <br>Sail into the heart of the lonely storm <br>And tell her that you'll love her eternally <br><br>Time takes its crazy toll <br>Mirror fallin' off the wall <br>You better look out for the looking glass girl <br>Cause she's gonna take you for a fall <br><br>Look into his eyes and you shall see <br>Why everything is quiet and nothing's free <br>I wonder how he's gonna make her smile <br>When love is running wild on the diamond sea]]></content><category term="Sonic Youth" label="Sonic Youth"/><category term="The Diamond Sea (Album Version / Alternate Ending)" label="The Diamond Sea (Album Version / Alternate Ending)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sonic_Youth/My_Arena/</id><title>Sonic Youth - My Arena - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:22:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:22:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sonic_Youth/My_Arena/" title="Sonic Youth - My Arena - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1996, little trouble girl, geffen <br><br>Pass me a joint <br>It's time to anoint <br>The fortune is sun <br>As cosmic exploits <br>Spark that shit up <br><br>Oh yah <br><br>Get me a beer <br>I feel kind of queer <br>I want to get fuck up <br>Poor me a fuckin' tall one <br><br>Oh yah <br><br>Take off your clothes <br>But leave on your shoes <br>You smell like a rosary <br>And you look like a jew <br>You drunk all my wine girl <br><br>An empty bottle is nothing but trouble <br>Another bottle and make it a double <br>We're getting thirsty <br><br>Nowhere to go <br>Nothing to do <br>Nowhere to go <br>With someone like you <br>Nothing to do <br>There's nothing that's new <br>But no one is home <br>There's no one like you <br>No one to see <br>Nothing to say <br>No one to go <br>No one to stay <br>No one is home <br>No one is home <br>There's no one like you <br>Never alone <br>Nowhere to go <br>Nothing to do <br>Nothing to say <br>There's no one like you <br>Nowhere to go <br>Nowhere to go <br>With nothing to do <br>There's no place like home <br><br>Pass me a qual <br>Let's do it and done it <br>I think I like you <br>I think I drank you <br>Pass me the vacuum]]></content><category term="Sonic Youth" label="Sonic Youth"/><category term="My Arena" label="My Arena"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sonic_Youth/The_Diamond_Sea_Radio_Edit/</id><title>Sonic Youth - The Diamond Sea (Radio Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:22:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:22:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sonic_Youth/The_Diamond_Sea_Radio_Edit/" title="Sonic Youth - The Diamond Sea (Radio Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Time takes its crazy toll <br>And how does your mirror grow <br>You better watch yourself when you jump into it <br>Cause the mirror's gonna steal your soul <br><br>I wonder how it came to be my friend <br>That someone just like you has come again <br>You'll never, never know how close you came <br>Until you fall in love with the diamond rain <br><br>Throw all his trash away <br>Look out he's here to stay <br>Your mirror's gonna crack when he breaks into it <br>And you'll never never be the same <br><br>Look into his eyes and you can see <br>Why all the little kids are dressed in dreams <br>I wonder how he's gonna make it back <br>When he sees that you just know it's make belief <br><br>Blood crystallized as sand <br>And now I hope you'll understand <br>You reflected into his looking glass soul <br>Now the mirror is your only friend <br><br>Look into his eyes and you will see <br>That men are not alone on the diamond sea <br>Sail into the heart of the lonely storm <br>And tell her that you'll love her eternally <br><br>Time takes its crazy toll <br>Mirror fallin' off the wall <br>You better look out for the looking glass girl <br>Cause she's gonna take you for a fall <br><br>Look into his eyes and you shall see <br>Why everything is quiet and nothing's free <br>I wonder how he's gonna make her smile <br>When love is running wild on the diamond sea]]></content><category term="Sonic Youth" label="Sonic Youth"/><category term="The Diamond Sea (Radio Edit)" label="The Diamond Sea (Radio Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정주연/미운_오리새끼_Feat_김진/</id><title>정주연 - 미운 오리새끼 (Feat. 김진) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:22:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:22:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%A3%BC%EC%97%B0/%EB%AF%B8%EC%9A%B4_%EC%98%A4%EB%A6%AC%EC%83%88%EB%81%BC_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%84/" title="정주연 - 미운 오리새끼 (Feat. 김진) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왕따로 소외됐던 어린시절 <br>복도 철문 뒤에서 <br>홀로 밥 먹던 난 <br>아무도 돌보지 않던 아이 <br>그런 나에게 <br>다가온 단 한 분 <br>왕따로 소외됐던 어린시절 <br>복도 철문 뒤에서 <br>홀로 밥 먹던 난 <br>아무도 돌보지 않던 아이 <br>그런 나에게 <br>다가온 단 한 분 <br>주님을 만났네 <br>사랑의 시선에 덮였네 <br>더이상 두렵지 않았네 <br>사람들의 시선이 yeah <br>남들은 잘만 사는 것 같은 인생 <br>나에겐 왜이리도 복잡한지 <br>무엇하나 포기할 수 없는데 <br>느껴지는 거라곤 <br>초조와 막막함 <br>주님이 말하네 <br>괜찮아 괜찮아 괜찮아 <br>더이상 두렵지 않았네 <br>불확실한 미래가 yeah <br>괜찮아 괜찮아 <br>괜찮아 괜찮아 <br>괜찮아 <br>내 시선으로 보는 것보다 <br>하늘의 시선으로 보는 것 <br>주님 안에 참된 <br>나를 찾는 길 <br>]]></content><category term="정주연" label="정주연"/><category term="미운 오리새끼 (Feat. 김진)" label="미운 오리새끼 (Feat. 김진)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비_개인_오후/Loving_You/</id><title>비 개인 오후 - Loving You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:23:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:23:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84_%EA%B0%9C%EC%9D%B8_%EC%98%A4%ED%9B%84/Loving_You/" title="비 개인 오후 - Loving You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밥은 잘 챙기고 다니는지 <br>아님 또 굶었니 <br>내 생각 만으로 채우지 말고 <br>잘 좀 먹고 다녀 <br>내 생각 만으로도 <br>매일 배가 부르다는 넌 <br>오늘도 너무 예뻐 <br>그건 나도 마찬가지 <br>너만 생각하면 나도 <br>아무것도 다 필요 없어 <br>Loving you 너만을 위한 <br>내 Love for you <br>말로는 다 못해 <br>꺼내 보여주고 싶은 내 맘 <br>너도 알잖아 나에게 넌 <br>너 하나만 Only you <br>점점 더 점점 커져만 가는 <br>내 맘에 널 가두고 <br>내가 보고 싶을 때 <br>꺼내 보고 또 보고 <br>나만 갖고 싶은 너 <br>내 생각 만으로도 <br>매일 배가 부르다는 넌 <br>오늘도 너무 예뻐 <br>그건 나도 마찬가지 <br>너만 생각하면 나도 <br>아무것도 다 필요 없어 <br>Loving you 너만을 위한 <br>내 Love for you <br>말로는 다 못해 <br>꺼내 보여주고 싶은 내 맘 <br>너도 알잖아 나에게 넌 너 하나만 <br>Loving you 너만을 위한 <br>내 Love for you <br>말로는 다 못해 <br>꺼내 보여주고 싶은 내 맘 <br>너도 알잖아 나에게 넌 Only you <br>]]></content><category term="비 개인 오후" label="비 개인 오후"/><category term="Loving You" label="Loving You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/효린/One_Step_Feat_박재범/</id><title>효린 - One Step (Feat. 박재범) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:24:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:24:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9A%A8%EB%A6%B0/One_Step_Feat_%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/" title="효린 - One Step (Feat. 박재범) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[둘만 있을 땐 <br>참 어색해 우리 사이 <br>손이 스칠 때면 <br>한걸음 멀어져 <br>예전과 다르게 <br>어쩐지 묘한 느낌 <br>편하기만 했던 <br>니가 좋아졌어 <br>그냥 난 다 좋아 <br>니 목소릴 듣는 게 좋아 <br>재미없는 농담도 또 난 <br>너를 떠올리면 <br>내 맘이 말을 안 들어 왜 <br>조금만 더 와주면 되는데 <br>왜 이렇게 자꾸 <br>머뭇거려 넌 왜 <br>한걸음 다가오면 되는데 <br>One step one step one step <br>숨겨봤자 다 보였어 <br>니 맘 다 아는데 <br>모른 척 나를 밀어내 <br>한걸음 다가오면 되는데 <br>One step one step one step <br>기다리게 해서 미안해 <br>Girl I'm sorry <br>네가 내 옆에 있으면 <br>괜히 긴장돼 <br>알아줬으면 해 <br>내가 널 얼마나 아끼는지 <br>그래서 girl 더 조심스러워져 <br>But I'm comin’ <br>for your love tonight <br>그냥 난 다 좋아 <br>니 목소릴 듣는 게 좋아 <br>재미없는 농담도 또 난 <br>너를 떠올리면 <br>내 맘이 말을 안 들어 왜 <br>조금만 더 와주면 되는데 <br>왜 이렇게 자꾸 <br>머뭇거려 넌 왜 <br>한걸음 다가오면 되는데 <br>One step one step one step <br>숨겨봤자 다 보였어 <br>니 맘 다 아는데 <br>모른 척 나를 밀어내 <br>한걸음 다가오면 되는데 <br>One step one step one step <br>I think I'm ready for you <br>Come on over <br>더 이상 망설이지 않을게 <br>I’ll show ya <br>조금 더 달콤하게 <br>보내 봐 오늘 밤 <br>점점 더 가까워져 <br>우리 몸과 마음이 <br>어느새 우린 <br>서로 사랑하는 사이 <br>이제부터는 떨어질 <br>일은 절대 없어 <br>조금만 더 와주면 되는데 <br>왜 이렇게 자꾸 <br>머뭇거려 넌 왜 <br>한걸음 다가오면 되는데 <br>One step one step one step <br>숨겨봤자 다 보였어 <br>니 맘 다 아는데 <br>모른 척 나를 밀어내 <br>한걸음 다가오면 되는데 <br>One step one step one step <br>]]></content><category term="효린" label="효린"/><category term="One Step (Feat. 박재범)" label="One Step (Feat. 박재범)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왁스/너를_너를_너를_Inst/</id><title>왁스 - 너를 너를 너를 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:24:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:24:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%81%EC%8A%A4/%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC_%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC_%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC_Inst/" title="왁스 - 너를 너를 너를 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너 없는 하루를 몇 번 보낸 지 <br>나 오늘도 힘겹게 <br>너를 기다리는데 <br>며칠 자고 나면 정말 괜찮을지 <br>언제쯤이면 이 눈물이 마를지 <br>추억을 태워 너를 지우고 <br>또 너를 너를 너를 너를 <br>너를 잊어보려 애를 쓰지만 <br>아직도 그대 오 <br>나를 나를 나를 나를 <br>기억한다면 내게 돌아와 줘 <br>혹시 나를 잊어가나요 <br>내가 그렇게도 나빴었나요 <br>왜 나만 이렇게 또 너를 이렇게 <br>눈물로 지새우는지 <br>그래 너를 너를 너를 너를 못 잊어 <br>날 스쳐 갔던 너의 흔적들이 <br>너를 못 잊나 봐 <br>너 없이 이 밤을 몇 번 지샌 지 <br>언제쯤이면 이 눈물이 마를지 <br>추억을 태워 너를 지우고 <br>또 너를 너를 너를 너를 <br>너를 잊어보려 애를 쓰지만 <br>아직도 그대 오 <br>나를 나를 나를 나를 <br>기억한다면 내게 돌아와 줘 <br>혹시 나를 잊어가나요 <br>내가 그렇게도 나빴었나요 <br>왜 나만 이렇게 또 너를 이렇게 <br>눈물로 지새우는지 <br>그래 너를 너를 너를 너를 못 잊어 <br>날 스쳐 갔던 너의 흔적들이 <br>너를 못 잊나 봐 <br>미련 없이 보내줄 <br>용기가 나지 않아 <br>어제도 오늘도 <br>하염없이 눈물만 흘러 <br>아나요 아나요 혹시 그대 아나요 <br>아직도 난 기다리고 있다는 걸 <br>정말 나를 잊은 건가요 <br>내가 그렇게 뭘 잘못했나요 <br>왜 나를 이렇게 또 나를 이렇게 <br>눈물짓게 하는 건지 <br>그래 너를 너를 너를 너를 못 잊어 <br>날 스쳐 갔던 너의 흔적들이 <br>너를 기다리나 봐 <br>]]></content><category term="왁스" label="왁스"/><category term="너를 너를 너를 (Inst.)" label="너를 너를 너를 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왁스/너를_너를_너를/</id><title>왁스 - 너를 너를 너를 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:24:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:24:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%81%EC%8A%A4/%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC_%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC_%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC/" title="왁스 - 너를 너를 너를 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너 없는 하루를 몇 번 보낸 지 <br>나 오늘도 힘겹게 <br>너를 기다리는데 <br>며칠 자고 나면 정말 괜찮을지 <br>언제쯤이면 이 눈물이 마를지 <br>추억을 태워 너를 지우고 <br>또 너를 너를 너를 너를 <br>너를 잊어보려 애를 쓰지만 <br>아직도 그대 오 <br>나를 나를 나를 나를 <br>기억한다면 내게 돌아와 줘 <br>혹시 나를 잊어가나요 <br>내가 그렇게도 나빴었나요 <br>왜 나만 이렇게 또 너를 이렇게 <br>눈물로 지새우는지 <br>그래 너를 너를 너를 너를 못 잊어 <br>날 스쳐 갔던 너의 흔적들이 <br>너를 못 잊나 봐 <br>너 없이 이 밤을 몇 번 지샌 지 <br>언제쯤이면 이 눈물이 마를지 <br>추억을 태워 너를 지우고 <br>또 너를 너를 너를 너를 <br>너를 잊어보려 애를 쓰지만 <br>아직도 그대 오 <br>나를 나를 나를 나를 <br>기억한다면 내게 돌아와 줘 <br>혹시 나를 잊어가나요 <br>내가 그렇게도 나빴었나요 <br>왜 나만 이렇게 또 너를 이렇게 <br>눈물로 지새우는지 <br>그래 너를 너를 너를 너를 못 잊어 <br>날 스쳐 갔던 너의 흔적들이 <br>너를 못 잊나 봐 <br>미련 없이 보내줄 <br>용기가 나지 않아 <br>어제도 오늘도 <br>하염없이 눈물만 흘러 <br>아나요 아나요 혹시 그대 아나요 <br>아직도 난 기다리고 있다는 걸 <br>정말 나를 잊은 건가요 <br>내가 그렇게 뭘 잘못했나요 <br>왜 나를 이렇게 또 나를 이렇게 <br>눈물짓게 하는 건지 <br>그래 너를 너를 너를 너를 못 잊어 <br>날 스쳐 갔던 너의 흔적들이 <br>너를 기다리나 봐 <br>]]></content><category term="왁스" label="왁스"/><category term="너를 너를 너를" label="너를 너를 너를"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/웅산/Beautiful_Arirang/</id><title>웅산 - Beautiful Arirang - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:25:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:25:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9B%85%EC%82%B0/Beautiful_Arirang/" title="웅산 - Beautiful Arirang - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어둠이 지나간 <br>파란아침의 노래 <br>그 깊은 바다의 <br>힘찬 파도 소리 <br>저 넓은 세상에 <br>하얗게 뿌려놓은 햇살 <br>낯선 시인들의 <br>낮은 함성소리 <br>거친 바람이 <br>내 영혼을 깨운다 <br>나비처럼 날아올라 <br>춤추리라 <br>먼동이 터오는 <br>찬란한 아침의 노래 <br>가슴 속 피어난 <br>꽃 피우리라 <br>Arirang Arirang <br>Arirang Arirang <br>거친 바람이 <br>내 영혼을 깨운다 <br>나비처럼 날아올라 <br>춤추리라 <br>먼동이 터오는 <br>찬란한 아침의 노래 <br>가슴 속 피어난 <br>꽃 피우리라 <br>Arirang Arirang <br>Arirang Arirang <br>Arirang Arirang <br>Arirang Arirang <br>]]></content><category term="웅산" label="웅산"/><category term="Beautiful Arirang" label="Beautiful Arirang"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/웅산/I_Cant_Help_Myself/</id><title>웅산 - I Can`t Help Myself - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:25:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:25:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9B%85%EC%82%B0/I_Cant_Help_Myself/" title="웅산 - I Can`t Help Myself - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Johnny baby where are u <br>Can't you see that I love you <br>I have sinned time to time <br>Baby I've cried for us <br>But when I walk up <br>to the stage <br>woo woo woo <br>I can't help myself <br>Johnny baby come to me <br>I ain't perfect no no no <br>I've been reckless on and off <br>Baby won't you forgive me <br>Cause when I step <br>onto the stage woo <br>I can't help myself <br>Johnny baby where you'd go <br>You and I we're so fine <br>I have sinned time to time <br>But baby our love is like no other <br>But when I walk up <br>to the stage woo <br>I can't help myself <br>Johnny baby where you'd go <br>You and I we're so fine <br>I have sinned time to time <br>But baby our love is like no other <br>But when I walk up <br>to the stage woo <br>I can't help myself <br>Johnny baby come on back <br>Don't you know <br>Don't you know that I love you <br>I've been reckless on and off <br>I Promise I'll never betray you <br>Cause when I step <br>on to the stage woo <br>I can't help myself <br>Johnny come to me come to me <br>I can't help myself <br>come to me I can't help myself <br>]]></content><category term="웅산" label="웅산"/><category term="I Can`t Help Myself" label="I Can`t Help Myself"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/웅산/Jazz_Is_My_Life/</id><title>웅산 - Jazz Is My Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:25:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:25:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9B%85%EC%82%B0/Jazz_Is_My_Life/" title="웅산 - Jazz Is My Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[찰리 채플린 영화처럼 <br>smile smile smile <br>우리 함께 노래해요 <br>sing sing sing <br>탭슈즈 리듬맞춰 <br>뚜비두와 두비둡 <br>Sing sing 노래해요 <br>이 순간을 영원히 <br>뜨거운 탱고처럼 사랑해요 <br>에스프레소처럼 <br>기억해요 진하게 <br>퍼퓸 향기처럼 그대 몸을 감싸고 <br>빙빙 춤을 춰요 <br>그대여 나와 dance with me <br>달콤한 사랑이 오듯 <br>sweet sweet sweet <br>그대와 뜨거웠던 <br>그 kiss kiss kiss <br>Tic toc tac tic toe <br>시간을 함께 걸어요 <br>Swing swing 리듬 맞춰 <br>이 순간을 영원히 <br>영화 속 주인공처럼 사랑해요 <br>춤추는 저 나비처럼 fly fly fly <br>그댄 나의 노래 <br>끝없는 사랑이어라 <br>슈밥 슈비 두와 <br>그대여 나와 swing with me <br>영화 속 주인공처럼 사랑해요 <br>춤추는 저 나비처럼 fly fly fly <br>그댄 나의 노래 <br>끝없는 사랑이어라 <br>슈밥 슈비 두와 <br>그대여 나와 swing with me <br>Jazz is my life there's no other <br>Jazz is my life that's the high life <br>Jazz is my life there's no other <br>Jazz is my life that's the high life <br>Jazz is my life Jazz is my life <br>Jazz is my life Jazz is my life <br>Jazz is my life Jazz is my life <br>]]></content><category term="웅산" label="웅산"/><category term="Jazz Is My Life" label="Jazz Is My Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/웅산/Crazy_Love/</id><title>웅산 - Crazy Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:25:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:25:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9B%85%EC%82%B0/Crazy_Love/" title="웅산 - Crazy Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[코끝을 찌르는 그대의 향기 <br>It's love my crazy love <br>귓가에 멤도는 그대의 속삭임 <br>it's love my crazy love <br>아무리 애를 써도 또 내 맘은 <br>I'm under your spell <br>헤어나고 싶다고 너에게 <br>또 주문을 외도 넌 내 곁에 <br>어느새 너의 특별한 그 마법에 <br>Addicted to you <br>어색한 충고로 넌 내게 말했지 <br>You never know what love is <br>아무리 애를 써도 또 내 맘은 <br>I'm under your spell <br>헤어나고 싶다고 너에게 <br>또 주문을 외도 넌 내 곁에 <br>어느새 너의 특별한 그 마법에 <br>Addicted to you <br>어색한 충고로 넌 내게 말했지 <br>You never know what love is <br>아무리 애를 써도 또 내 맘은 <br>I'm under your spell <br>헤어나고 싶다고 너에게 <br>또 주문을 외도 넌 내 곁에 <br>널 벗어나기엔 <br>you are my temptation <br>널 거부하기엔 <br>I fall into your trap <br>You are my everything <br>You're my ecstasy <br>또 주문을 외도 넌 내 곁에 <br>]]></content><category term="웅산" label="웅산"/><category term="Crazy Love" label="Crazy Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/웅산/Hey_Boy/</id><title>웅산 - Hey Boy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:25:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:25:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9B%85%EC%82%B0/Hey_Boy/" title="웅산 - Hey Boy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey boy it's a Saturday night <br>and don't say <br>your love has faded away from me <br>I'm still thinking of you <br>Hey boy can't you see I'm crying <br>I'm right here where we left off <br>I'm still thinking of you <br>Don't say one word and <br>hold me tight <br>I'll put a spell on you <br>Oh please don't say goodbye <br>I can't let you leave my sight no no <br>Hold me tight and Say you love me <br>My love I really do love you so <br>You'll never know <br>how much I love you <br>I need you and I want you <br>Her lips might be sweeter <br>but don't tear my heart up <br>Cause you care for me <br>I'm still thinking of you <br>Her touch <br>might be tempting <br>but don't fall for it <br>You know you adore me <br>I'm still thinking of you <br>Don't say one word and <br>hold me tight <br>I'll put a spell on you <br>Oh after you've gone astray <br>I know that <br>I couldn't live through it <br>I feel blue and I feel down <br>My love please don't make me cry <br>Don't you ever leave my side I beg <br>Hold me tight every night and day <br>I can't get you out of my head <br>I can't get used to losing you <br>Sugar party that's what I want <br>As long as you love me <br>Oh after you've gone astray <br>I know that I couldn't live through it <br>I feel blue and I feel down <br>My love please don't make me cry <br>Don't you ever leave my side I beg <br>Hold me tight every night and day <br>]]></content><category term="웅산" label="웅산"/><category term="Hey Boy" label="Hey Boy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/곡식/쉿하고_그냥_뛰어/</id><title>곡식 - 쉿하고 그냥 뛰어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:25:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:25:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%A1%EC%8B%9D/%EC%89%BF%ED%95%98%EA%B3%A0_%EA%B7%B8%EB%83%A5_%EB%9B%B0%EC%96%B4/" title="곡식 - 쉿하고 그냥 뛰어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[G O E K Chic <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>오늘 밤은 뜨거워 <br>내일 아침이 두려워 <br>생각 말고 몸을 맡겨 <br>그저 비트를 타며 <br>Turn up <br>내가 함께 있잖아 <br>너 지금 딴 생각하면 <br>수많은 밤을 <br>또 오늘을 기억하며 <br>후회할 걸 알아 <br>대체 뭐가 부족해서 <br>즐기는 걸 피하려고만 해 <br>많이 바빠 시간 탓하지 마 <br>Tight 하게 놀면 되지 <br>그깟 전이 중요해 <br>뭐니 뭐니 해도 <br>Money가 제일 <br>이 죽이는 groove를 <br>느끼며 노는 우리가 <br>진짜 죽이는 group <br>You know are you ready <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>말만 많아 든 거 없는 <br>애들이 정말 참 많아 <br>오지라퍼들이 놀 줄 <br>모르는 졸음증 만드는 <br>바 바이러스 <br>못 노는 고문을 견딜 바엔 <br>난 다 잃어도 못 먹어도 Go <br>지루한 삶이 너를 지울 때 <br>흐리무레 해진 널 <br>내가 다시금 깨울게 <br>I love that <br>너흰 그저 가끔 한 번 뛰면 돼 <br>Stress 쌓일 때 <br>한번 와서 날 외치면 돼 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>say 곡식 곡식 곡식 곡식 <br>매일 같은 하루 같은 삶을 <br>사는 것에 지쳐가고 <br>질려가고 때론 정말 <br>미칠 때도 있겠지만 <br>고민한다 해도 변할 건 없으니 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 뛰어 <br>쉿 하고 그냥 뛰어 <br>쉿 <br>]]></content><category term="곡식" label="곡식"/><category term="쉿하고 그냥 뛰어" label="쉿하고 그냥 뛰어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/람다/그땐_몰랐었어/</id><title>람다 - 그땐 몰랐었어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:28:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:28:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9E%8C%EB%8B%A4/%EA%B7%B8%EB%95%90_%EB%AA%B0%EB%9E%90%EC%97%88%EC%96%B4/" title="람다 - 그땐 몰랐었어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그땐 내가 몰랐었어 너의 마음을 <br>그동안 참 바보였어 <br>그래서 이렇게 홀로 남아 <br>뒤돌아보니 남은 게 없어 <br>너도 없고 사랑도 없어 <br>어디쯤 갔니 물어볼 수도 없어 <br>항상 웃는 얼굴로 날 반겨주던 <br>너의 미소도 볼 수가 없어 <br>그땐 미처 몰랐었어 <br>햇살은 왜 야속하게 그대로 맑고 <br>시간은 또 속 모르게 그대로 흘러 <br>넌 어디니 <br>혼자 이렇게 되뇌이는 나 <br>난 몰랐었어 난 몰랐었어 <br>너의 사랑을 <br>난 몰랐었어 난 몰랐었어 <br>너의 사랑을 <br>]]></content><category term="람다" label="람다"/><category term="그땐 몰랐었어" label="그땐 몰랐었어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/람다/별이_빛나는_밤에/</id><title>람다 - 별이 빛나는 밤에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:28:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:28:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9E%8C%EB%8B%A4/%EB%B3%84%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B9%9B%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%B0%A4%EC%97%90/" title="람다 - 별이 빛나는 밤에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[별이 빛나는 밤에 <br>그대와 밤하늘 보며 <br>수많은 별을 세던 <br>그날 떠올린다 <br>달빛 찬란한 공간 <br>그대의 손을 꼭 잡고 <br>멈춰버리길 바라던 <br>그때 그 소중한 시간들아 <br>밝게 빛나던 사랑이 <br>추억 별 되어 내려와 <br>밤하늘의 별빛들은 <br>그때와 같이 그대론데 <br>떨어지는 별똥별에 <br>간절한 맘 빌어본다 <br>달빛처럼 식어 버린 <br>그대 마음을 되돌려달라고 <br>별이 빛나는 밤에 <br>그대의 눈 마주 보며 <br>수많은 약속했던 <br>그날 떠올린다 <br>두 눈 너란 별 담아 <br>영원히 간직하자고 <br>새끼손가락 걸었던 <br>그때 그 소중한 시간들아 <br>밝게 빛나던 사랑이 <br>추억 별 되어 내려와 <br>밤하늘의 별빛들은 <br>그때와 같이 그대론데 <br>떨어지는 별똥별에 <br>간절한 맘 빌어본다 <br>달빛처럼 식어버린 <br>그대 마음을 되돌려달라고 <br>별이 빛나는 밤에 <br>밝게 빛나던 사랑이 <br>추억 별 되어 내려와 <br>밤하늘의 별빛들은 <br>그때와 같이 그대론데 <br>떨어지는 별똥별에 <br>간절한 맘 빌어본다 <br>달빛처럼 식어버린 <br>그대 마음을 되돌려달라고 <br>]]></content><category term="람다" label="람다"/><category term="별이 빛나는 밤에" label="별이 빛나는 밤에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/람다/혹시_그런_거라면/</id><title>람다 - 혹시 그런 거라면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:28:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:28:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9E%8C%EB%8B%A4/%ED%98%B9%EC%8B%9C_%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%B0_%EA%B1%B0%EB%9D%BC%EB%A9%B4/" title="람다 - 혹시 그런 거라면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 오늘 뭐 할까 <br>저번 네가 말했던 <br>그곳에 가볼까 <br>가서 뭘 먹을까 <br>너 먹고 싶어 했던 것 <br>사줄게 같이 갈래 <br>왜 대답이 없어 <br>오늘 무슨 일 있어 <br>아까부터 <br>불편한 표정인 너 <br>내가 잘못했어 <br>그냥 다 잘못했어 <br>그러니까 아무 말 말고 <br>같이 가자 <br>혹시 헤어지자는 말하려고 <br>시간 끄는 건 아닐 거야 그치 <br>혹시 그랬던 거라면 <br>우리 사랑했던 <br>지난날 떠올려봐 부디 <br>기억의 조각 속에서 <br>웃는 모습 찾을 수 있다면 <br>제발 오 <br>우리 한번만 한번 더 <br>생각해보자 <br>내가 잘못했어 <br>그냥 다 잘못했어 <br>그러니까 아무 말 말고 <br>같이 가자 <br>혹시 그만하자는 말 <br>하려고 오늘 만난 건 <br>아닐 거야 그치 <br>혹시 이게 꿈이라면 <br>다시 사랑할 수 있다면 <br>더 잘할게 부디 <br>사랑한 시간 속에서 <br>웃는 모습 잊을 수 없다면 <br>제발 오 <br>우리 한번만 한번 더 <br>생각해보자 <br>]]></content><category term="람다" label="람다"/><category term="혹시 그런 거라면" label="혹시 그런 거라면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/람다/구름/</id><title>람다 - 구름 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:28:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:28:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9E%8C%EB%8B%A4/%EA%B5%AC%EB%A6%84/" title="람다 - 구름 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[두둥실 너는 구름이야 <br>항상 내 맘에 떠있어 <br>살며시 잡으려 해도 <br>잡힐 듯 말 듯 흩어져 <br>내 안에 수 놓여진 그대가 <br>가득 떠있네 머리 위에 <br>먹구름이라도 난 좋아 <br>내 맘에 비를 내린 대도 <br>그대 없인 난 뜬구름 <br>구름다리를 내어준다면 <br>나 살포시 건너가 <br>당신의 물방울이 될 거예요 <br>그대라는 큰 흰 구름 <br>포근하게 날 안아준다면 <br>나 살포시 기대어 <br>달콤한 솜사탕이 될 거예요 <br>내 안에 숨어있는 <br>그대가 가득 차있네 마음속에 <br>비구름이라도 난 좋아 <br>내 눈에 비를 내린 대도 <br>그대 없인 난 뜬구름 <br>구름다리를 내어준다면 <br>나 살포시 건너가 <br>당신의 물방울이 될 거예요 <br>그대라는 큰 흰 구름 <br>포근하게 날 안아준다면 <br>나 살포시 기대어 <br>달콤한 솜사탕이 될 거예요 <br>]]></content><category term="람다" label="람다"/><category term="구름" label="구름"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/람다/봄춘빛날희/</id><title>람다 - 봄춘빛날희 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:28:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:28:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9E%8C%EB%8B%A4/%EB%B4%84%EC%B6%98%EB%B9%9B%EB%82%A0%ED%9D%AC/" title="람다 - 봄춘빛날희 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[빛나는 봄에 돋아나 <br>가을을 앞두고 당신은 간다 <br>겨울 추위 함박눈 아래 <br>추억을 묻은 채 겨울잠 자면 <br>얼어붙은 눈물 녹으며 <br>다시 봄 온대도 당신은 없다 <br>사계절은 소생한대도 <br>당신이란 봄 만날 수 없네 <br>여전히 봄은 오고 또 가 <br>나에겐 사라져 버린 계절 <br>맘속에 고이 두고서 <br>다시 꽃피워보려 해봐도 <br>여전히 봄은 오고 또 가 <br>잡으려해도 잡히지 않는 <br>나 당신의 봄 속에서 <br>영원토록 잠들고 싶은 마음 <br>빛나는 봄에 돋아나 <br>가을을 앞두고 당신은 갔다 <br>사계절은 소생한대도 <br>당신이란 봄 만날 수 없네 <br>여전히 봄은 오고 또 가 <br>나에겐 사라져 버린 계절 <br>맘속에 고이 두고서 <br>다시 꽃피워보려 해봐도 <br>여전히 봄은 오고 또 가 <br>잡으려해도 잡히지 않는 <br>나 당신의 봄 속에서 <br>영원토록 잠들고 싶은 마음 <br>빛나는 봄에 돋아나 <br>가을을 앞두고 당신은 갔다 <br>사계절은 소생한대도 <br>당신이란 봄 만날 수 없네 <br>당신이란 봄 만날 수 없네 <br>]]></content><category term="람다" label="람다"/><category term="봄춘빛날희" label="봄춘빛날희"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/은경재/바람아_불어라/</id><title>은경재 - 바람아 불어라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:28:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:28:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%80%EA%B2%BD%EC%9E%AC/%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C%EC%95%84_%EB%B6%88%EC%96%B4%EB%9D%BC/" title="은경재 - 바람아 불어라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[누구나 찐하게 사랑하고 <br>이별도 하겠지만 <br>상처받은 인생이 <br>어디 나 하나 라더냐 <br>매일 밤 눈물도 흘려 보고 <br>독한 술에 빠졌지만 <br>한번 사는 내 인생을 <br>누가 대신 살아 주더냐 <br>바람아 저 구름아 <br>나를 데려 가 다오 <br>불타는 내 가슴이 <br>너를 향해 달려간다 <br>하늘아 내 사랑아 <br>세월이 날 잡아도 <br>마지막 사랑 찾아 <br>바람 부는 남자 <br>때로는 원망도 해봤지만 <br>소용없는 좌절 따윈 됐고 <br>남은 인생 내 식대로 <br>바람 불면 부는 대로 가 <br>바람아 저 구름아 <br>나를 데려 가 다오 <br>불타는 내 가슴이 <br>너를 향해 달려간다 <br>요즘 세상 쉬운 <br>일은 하나 없고 <br>주저앉아 고민하면 <br>달라지나 <br>어디 한번 내 식대로 <br>살아 보자 <br>바람 따라 살아가련다 <br>바람아 저 구름아 <br>나를 데려 가 다오 <br>불타는 내 가슴이 <br>너를 향해 달려간다 <br>하늘아 내 사랑아 <br>세월이 날 잡아도 <br>마지막 사랑 찾아 <br>바람 부는 남자 <br>]]></content><category term="은경재" label="은경재"/><category term="바람아 불어라" label="바람아 불어라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jessarae/Monday_Girl/</id><title>Jessarae - Monday Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:32:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:32:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jessarae/Monday_Girl/" title="Jessarae - Monday Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I feel alive when I'm looking for you <br>And then you're gone <br>Tell me, what can I do <br>I gotta find me some kind of help <br>Maybe a drink, maybe something else <br><br>Why can't I tell if you're no good for me <br>Nobody likes you in my family <br>Under the hook, communications gone <br>Well, there's a plane <br>Guess I'm getting on <br><br>My Monday girl <br>In a Saturday world <br>My Monday girl <br>I lost her in the weekend <br><br>I'm rearranged in so many ways <br>And I don't care if you're getting laid <br>I know exactly what I've got to give <br>Go ahead, shoot me if you want <br><br>Cause I don't know where I am in this place <br>Another city, another town, another face <br>If I can't be with the one that I love <br>I'll find someone who's just as lost <br><br>My Monday girl <br>In a Saturday world <br>My Monday girl <br>I lost her in the weekend <br><br>My Monday girl <br>In a Saturday world <br>My Monday girl <br>I lost her in the weekend <br>I lost her in the weekend <br>I lost her in the weekend <br><br>My Monday girl <br>In a Saturday world <br>My Monday girl <br>I lost her in the weekend <br>Sorry I can't keep up with you <br>Blue jeans, honey]]></content><category term="Jessarae" label="Jessarae"/><category term="Monday Girl" label="Monday Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jessarae/Stand_In_The_Rain_Live/</id><title>Jessarae - Stand In The Rain (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:32:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:32:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jessarae/Stand_In_The_Rain_Live/" title="Jessarae - Stand In The Rain (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to start a riot <br>If you want to start a war <br>Better shout the top of your voice <br>It's your choice to be the knock upon the door <br><br>If you want to make some trouble <br>Better squeeze between the bars <br>And pray the fight is still inside us <br>Despite us forgetting who we really are <br><br>You know we've heard this all before <br>Let's turn this hum into a roar <br>If they ask us what we're fighting for <br>We'll tell 'em we're the lords of lockdown <br>Yeah, we'll tell 'em we're the lords of lockdown <br><br>If you wanna win the battle <br>You gotta deal with all the pain <br>And if you wanna feel the sunshine <br>You gotta stand in the rain <br>It may be hard to cross the ocean <br>But, baby, there's no other way <br>Cause if you wanna feel the sunshine <br>You gotta stand in the rain <br><br>Nobody will be waiting <br>So let's just cut to the chase <br>And debating, hanging <br> keep a smile on your face <br><br>You know the people like to talk <br>Same as they've always done before <br>If they ask us what we're fighting for <br>We'll tell 'em we're the lords of lockdown <br>Yeah, we'll tell 'em we're the lords of lockdown <br><br>If you wanna win the battle <br>You gotta deal with all the pain <br>And if you wanna feel the sunshine <br>You gotta stand in the rain <br>It may be hard to cross the ocean <br>But, baby, there's no other way <br>Cause if you wanna feel the sunshine <br>You gotta stand in the rain <br><br>Cause if you wanna win the battle <br>You gotta deal with all the pain <br>And if you wanna feel the sunshine <br>You gotta stand in the rain <br>It may be hard to cross the ocean <br>But, baby, there's no other way <br>Cause if you wanna feel the sunshine <br>You gotta stand in the rain]]></content><category term="Jessarae" label="Jessarae"/><category term="Stand In The Rain (Live)" label="Stand In The Rain (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jessarae/Carving_Out_My_Heart_Live/</id><title>Jessarae - Carving Out My Heart (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:32:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:32:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jessarae/Carving_Out_My_Heart_Live/" title="Jessarae - Carving Out My Heart (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sugar coated empathy <br>All the shit you're expecting from me <br>Your little California dream <br>Is distracted and rarely seen <br><br>I'm beaten up by hours <br>Dialogue's gotten sour <br>Yesterday's promises are running free <br><br>This love we're feeding's got so hungry <br>I can't pay the bills with nothing <br>I'm carving out my heart <br>You believe it's so dead simple <br>I can't figure out the riddle <br>It's carving out my heart <br><br>I don't wanna mess you up <br>It's a shame you'd love me <br>No matter what <br>This love, it used to be so clean <br>Now we're swimming in a pool of caffeine <br><br>My words are tasting so bitter <br>And I can't deliver <br>Yesterdays promises are all running free <br><br>This love we're feeding's got so hungry <br>I can't pay the bills with nothing <br>I'm carving out my heart <br>You believe it's so dead simple <br>I can't figure out the riddle <br>It's carving out my heart <br>I'm carving out my heart <br><br>My words are tasting so bitter <br>And I can't deliver <br>Yesterdays promises are all running free <br><br>This love we're feeding's got so hungry <br>I can't pay the bills with nothing <br>I'm carving out my heart <br>You believe it's so dead simple <br>I can't figure out the riddle <br>It's carving out my heart <br><br>This love we're feeding's got so hungry <br>I can't pay the bills with nothing <br>I'm carving out my heart <br>I'm carving out my heart <br>I'm carving out my heart]]></content><category term="Jessarae" label="Jessarae"/><category term="Carving Out My Heart (Live)" label="Carving Out My Heart (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jessarae/Nobodys_Human/</id><title>Jessarae - Nobody`s Human - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:32:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:32:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jessarae/Nobodys_Human/" title="Jessarae - Nobody`s Human - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a train wreck dressed in regular clothes <br>You like to starve yourself and your ribs are on show <br>But hey, it's alright <br>Nobody's human <br><br>You're lipstick's smudged like a pure work of art <br>You can't stop smiling when you're falling apart <br>But hey, it's alright <br>Nobody's human <br><br>And all your friend have plenty to say <br>They saw the real you and now they're running away <br>But hey, it's alright <br>There's no computing <br><br>But it's okay if we stay screwed up <br>Let's just live life till we're used up <br>I know I can't cure your sorrow <br>Let's just face the pain tomorrow <br><br>We partied too hard and it's taking its toll <br>They're driving little miss lovely to the hospital <br>But hey, it's alright <br>We'll get through it <br><br>I ask myself why do we push too far <br>Hanging around the culture made of burnt out stars <br>But hey, it's alright <br>Nobody's human <br><br>But it's okay if we stay screwed up <br>Let's just live life till we're used up <br>I know I can't cure your sorrow <br>Let's just face the pain tomorrow <br><br>But it's okay if we stay screwed up <br>Let's just live life till we're used up <br>I know I can't cure your sorrow <br>Let's just face the pain tomorrow <br>So let's just face the pain tomorrow <br>Let's just face the pain tomorrow]]></content><category term="Jessarae" label="Jessarae"/><category term="Nobody`s Human" label="Nobody`s Human"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/River_Live/</id><title>Vanessa Carlton - River (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:33:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:33:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/River_Live/" title="Vanessa Carlton - River (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sailors on the sea, are we heading clear for the edge of the ocean <br>There's no city that keeps you king for a gypsy <br>And are we guided by some vision <br>All our moves adding up to an ancient arc <br>We are free of the canyon cliff of my heart <br><br>The river flows, it takes ahold and it's running through <br>And we ain't changing on our own, oh, we change for you <br>The river flows, it always flows <br><br>And he walks home in another city <br>Your mind's stuck in an ancient war <br>And all you need is the space for the beauty to take you <br>And she will take you <br><br>The river flows, it takes ahold and it's running through <br>And we ain't changing on our own, oh, we change for you <br>The river flows, it always flows <br>Flows through you, flows through you <br><br>The river flows, it takes ahold and it's coming through <br>And we ain't changing on our own, oh we change for you <br>The river flows, it always flows <br><br>And we're just sailors on the sea <br>Yeah, we're just sailors on the sea <br>Yeah, we're just sailors on the sea]]></content><category term="Vanessa Carlton" label="Vanessa Carlton"/><category term="River (Live)" label="River (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/Matter_Of_Time_Live/</id><title>Vanessa Carlton - Matter Of Time (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:33:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:33:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/Matter_Of_Time_Live/" title="Vanessa Carlton - Matter Of Time (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Give her all your darkness <br>Give her all your light <br>Love is like a carriage <br>It's no spirit in the night <br><br>Like a wishing well <br>Where your pennies fell <br><br>He said it's only a matter of time <br>Before your heart is mine <br>Have you been searching <br>You've been looking the world over <br><br>When is it time to let go <br>And is it then that you know <br>All the peace that we've been bringing out of each other <br>Out of each other <br><br>Flowing like a circuit <br>Through a curse of neon signs <br>Writing her a letter <br>What's the curve of your desire <br>When the cycle starts its run <br>And we become what we become <br><br>He said it's only a matter of time <br>Before your heart is mine <br>Have you been searching <br>You've been looking the world over <br><br>When is it time to let go <br>And is it then that you know <br>All the peace that we've been bringing out of each other <br>Out of each other <br><br>When is it time to let go <br>And is it then that you know <br>All the peace that we've been bringing out of each other <br>Out of each other <br><br>Give her all your darkness <br>Give her all your light <br>Love is like a carriage <br>It's no spirit in the night]]></content><category term="Vanessa Carlton" label="Vanessa Carlton"/><category term="Matter Of Time (Live)" label="Matter Of Time (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/Willows_Live/</id><title>Vanessa Carlton - Willows (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:33:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:33:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/Willows_Live/" title="Vanessa Carlton - Willows (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Find a love <br>Go build a cabin <br>Find land and a tree <br>Carve in a wish <br>On your knees, planting seeds <br>The dirt, makin rows, where the devil don't see <br><br>My love, I agree, so lucky to find ya <br>But memories, they don't stay behind us <br>Our minds are strong, could it be enough <br>To bring strength to the bones <br><br>Our weeping willow is hangin above me <br>On my back in the sun, would it fall upon me <br>I won't let you down and man you will keep safe my love <br><br>Sow the earth <br>A blanket of bounty <br>In the distance a hearse <br>The devil drives empty <br>In a babies eyes <br>The ritual purifies every design <br><br>Our weeping willow is hangin above me <br>On my back in the sun, would it fall upon me <br>I won't let you down cause man you have kept safe my love <br>Man you will keep safe my love <br><br>Our weeping willow is hangin above me <br>On my back in the sun, would it fall upon me <br>i won't let you down and man you will keep safe <br>I won't let you down, man you will keep safe <br>I won't let you down and man you will keep safe my love]]></content><category term="Vanessa Carlton" label="Vanessa Carlton"/><category term="Willows (Live)" label="Willows (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/Operator_Live/</id><title>Vanessa Carlton - Operator (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:33:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:33:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/Operator_Live/" title="Vanessa Carlton - Operator (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I could be your operator <br>I could bring you joy <br>Something like a freedom fighter <br>Guns ain't just for boys <br><br>I heard what you said <br>You should say it again, cause it's bold <br>It's getting late <br>Darling get a move on it, we should go <br><br>You should never tell your mother <br>You should give it time <br>Pour a drink, here, have another <br>Cause this is gonna blow your mind <br><br>Heard what you said <br>And I say what I mean <br>We should go, go <br>Pack up your things <br>I don't care what you bring <br>Leave your house for a home <br><br>You should call your little brother <br>Tell him to be good <br>Tell him that you really love him <br>You don't but you should <br><br>I heard what you said, so don't say it again <br>Cause it's cold, cold <br>It's getting late, we should get a move on it <br>We should go <br>Go <br><br>I could be your moneymaker <br>You could be my song <br>Worry bout the others later <br>We should get a move on <br>We should go, go <br>Pack up your things I don't care what you bring <br>Leave your house for a home]]></content><category term="Vanessa Carlton" label="Vanessa Carlton"/><category term="Operator (Live)" label="Operator (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/House_Of_Seven_Swords_Live/</id><title>Vanessa Carlton - House Of Seven Swords (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:33:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:33:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/House_Of_Seven_Swords_Live/" title="Vanessa Carlton - House Of Seven Swords (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Strength and devotion come without warning <br>You know when you know what to do <br>No simple scheming, you should be sleeping <br>Sometimes you just can't think it through <br><br>And that's the way it is, love <br>Go whichever way you need to go <br>Nobody can tell you how to build <br>Your house of seven swords <br><br>That's the way it is, love <br>Together and yet still we're on our own <br>Nobody can tell us how to build <br>Our house of seven swords <br><br>Shamen won't tell you <br>The preacher will try to <br>You could take your time <br>Take a trip <br><br>Let your eyes see hidden things <br>Your heart beat like a drum <br>Your eyes see hidden things <br>Your heart beat like a drum <br><br>'Cause that's the way it is, love <br>Go whichever way you need to go <br>Nobody can tell you how to build <br>Our house of seven swords <br><br>That's the way it is, love <br>Together and yet still we're on our own <br>Nobody can tell us how to build <br>Our house of seven swords <br><br>Oo, oo, oo ah <br><br>That's the way it is, love <br>That's the way it is, love <br>Your house of seven swords <br><br>That's the way it is, love <br>Together and yet still we're on our own <br>Nobody can tell us how to build <br>Our house of seven swords]]></content><category term="Vanessa Carlton" label="Vanessa Carlton"/><category term="House Of Seven Swords (Live)" label="House Of Seven Swords (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/Nothing_Where_Something_Used_To_Be_Live/</id><title>Vanessa Carlton - Nothing Where Something Used To Be (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:33:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:33:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/Nothing_Where_Something_Used_To_Be_Live/" title="Vanessa Carlton - Nothing Where Something Used To Be (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I will admit that you're the closest I have come <br>There's just something about you that I trust <br>I didn't say but I was sad to see you go <br>You went back to the ghost, I went back to what I know <br><br>Seems like every night, meet my friends at some bar <br>I tell myself I'm thinking but I'm just drinking til I feel far away <br>Saw your buddy, said he talked to you last week <br>Said you seemed pretty bummed, you've been wanting to call me <br>do it do it, do it do it <br>you should do it do it <br>do it do it <br><br>Cause now there's nothing where something used to be <br>Cause now there's nothing where something used to be <br><br>It's confusing cause I'm the one that left, it was pre emptive <br>I don't know who I am <br>Are we all searching for something we don't understand <br>Someone else to see through our battle plans <br>You should do it do it <br>do it do it <br>You should do it do it <br>do it do it <br><br>Cause now there's nothing where something used to be <br>Cause now there's nothing where something used to be <br><br>I try to remember there's no future there's no past <br>I try to remember if it can last then it will last <br>Try to remember it <br><br>Cause now there's nothing where something used to be <br>Cause now there's nothing where something used to be <br><br>Do it do it, do it do it <br>Do it do it, do it do it <br>Cause now there's nothing where something used to be <br><br>Do it do it, do it do it <br>Do it do it, do it do it]]></content><category term="Vanessa Carlton" label="Vanessa Carlton"/><category term="Nothing Where Something Used To Be (Live)" label="Nothing Where Something Used To Be (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/Blue_Pool_Live/</id><title>Vanessa Carlton - Blue Pool (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:33:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:33:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/Blue_Pool_Live/" title="Vanessa Carlton - Blue Pool (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Man, it's so nice to see you again <br>You're the great blue pool in LA <br>And I close my book, move my bag, make some space <br>Cause it's time to give that song a break <br>So tell me now how these few years have been <br>When it's living to honour the best <br>And I have been well, I've saved you a smile <br>These feelings they come and go fast <br>Light your cigarette, see the fame in your eyes <br>Sing me that new song you sing <br>The time for you and I was never quite right <br>It matters and means everything <br><br>Cause the garden walls grew quick <br>Before you know, you're outside of it <br>And the ivy's coming in <br>It's so beautiful if you can find it <br><br>And time, she's always kept you on her good side <br>Some people they still fight their fate <br>I understood clear what you said with your eyes <br>We all speak in different ways <br><br>Cause the garden walls grew quick <br>Before you know, you're outside of it <br>And the ivy's coming in <br>It's so beautiful if you can find it <br>The garden walls grow quick <br>Before you know, you're outside of it <br>And the ivy's coming in <br>It's so beautiful if you can find it]]></content><category term="Vanessa Carlton" label="Vanessa Carlton"/><category term="Blue Pool (Live)" label="Blue Pool (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/Take_It_Easy_Live/</id><title>Vanessa Carlton - Take It Easy (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:33:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:33:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanessa_Carlton/Take_It_Easy_Live/" title="Vanessa Carlton - Take It Easy (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm old enough to know, too young to let it go <br>Connected to one billion stars and lights <br>I know you have to go <br>Do we follow what we know <br>I'll be here for you in the night <br><br>Say it once, say it twice, to yourself, to the night <br>A shaman's prayer <br>It's natural <br>When it's quiet, get slow <br><br>As your castle crumbles down and it will, take it easy take it easy <br>When heaven wraps around you and she will, take it easy <br>Take it in easy <br><br>Are you waiting all the time for some unending delight <br>Have you ever broken your own heart <br><br>Say it once, say it twice, to yourself, to the night <br>A shaman's prayer <br>It's natural <br>When it's quiet get slow <br><br>As your castle crumbles down and it will, take it easy take it easy <br>When heaven wraps around you and she will, take it easy <br>Take it in easy <br><br>Take it in <br>Take it <br><br>Say it once, say it twice, to yourself, to the night <br>A shaman's prayer <br>It's natural <br>When it's quiet get slow <br><br>As your castle crumbles down and it will, take it easy take it easy <br>When heaven wraps around you and she will, take it easy <br>Take it easy <br>Take it easy <br>Take it easy <br>Take it in easy]]></content><category term="Vanessa Carlton" label="Vanessa Carlton"/><category term="Take It Easy (Live)" label="Take It Easy (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/약기운/철밥통/</id><title>약기운 - 철밥통 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:36:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:36:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%BD%EA%B8%B0%EC%9A%B4/%EC%B2%A0%EB%B0%A5%ED%86%B5/" title="약기운 - 철밥통 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아름다운 나라라는데 <br>사람들은 왜 이렇게 죽는지 <br>자살률이 1위요 <br>부정부패가 일이네 <br>국민이 죽던 말던 월급이 나오네 <br>빚더미에서 연금이 나오네 <br>국민을 위한 공무인가 <br>니 밥그릇을 바치는 국민인가 <br>아름다워서 놔두는게 아니야 <br>그냥 참는 거야 <br>힘없고 백 없으니 <br>살려면 눈 깔아야지 <br>사람들이 죽어 가는데 <br>국민들이 죽어 가는데 <br>밥그릇만 챙기는 너는 철밥통 <br>빚더미의 나라에서 <br>죽어가는 국민을 배경으로 <br>기념사진이나 찍고 <br>월급이나 받아가라 <br>국민이 죽던 말던 <br>정년은 보장되니 <br>어영부영 하다가 <br>연금이나 받아가라 <br>국민을 위한 공무인가 <br>니 밥그릇을 바치는 국민인가 <br>국민을 위한 공무인가 <br>니 밥그릇을 바치는 국민인가 <br>아름다워서 놔두는 게 아니야 <br>그냥 참는 거야 <br>힘없고 백 없으니 <br>살려면 눈 깔아야지 <br>사람들이 죽어 가는데 <br>국민들이 죽어 가는데 <br>밥그릇만 챙기는 너는 철밥통 <br>너는 철밥통 너는 철밥통 <br>]]></content><category term="약기운" label="약기운"/><category term="철밥통" label="철밥통"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/약기운/주정뱅이/</id><title>약기운 - 주정뱅이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:36:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:36:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%BD%EA%B8%B0%EC%9A%B4/%EC%A3%BC%EC%A0%95%EB%B1%85%EC%9D%B4/" title="약기운 - 주정뱅이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[불 지르고 죽이고 <br>폭발하는 것보다 <br>술 먹고 자빠지는 게 <br>차라리 낫잖아 <br>술 처먹고 개가 된다고 <br>왈왈왈 짖어 대는게 <br>독사처럼 독을 품고 <br>살아가는 것 보단 낫잖아 <br>내게 손가락질 하지마라 <br>내가 너보단 훨씬 낫잖아 <br>빙빙 돈다 하늘이 돈다 <br>지구의 자전이 <br>온몸으로 느껴지네 <br>맨 정신에 돌아버린 너보단 <br>술에 취한 내가 낫잖아 <br>맑은 정신으론 버틸 수 없는 <br>그런 세상에 살고 있으니 <br>이보게 친구 못난 얼굴 <br>찌푸리지 말고 <br>여기 와서 한잔 하게나 <br>빙빙 돈다 하늘이 돈다 <br>못생긴 줄 알았던 <br>니가 예뻐 보이네 <br>나는 너의 적이 아니야 <br>그냥 주정뱅이일 뿐이야 <br>아니꼽게 쳐다보지 마라 <br>내가 먹은 소주 값의 <br>절반은 세금이다 <br>빙빙 돈다 하늘이 돈다 <br>전화가 하고 싶다 <br>빙빙 돈다 하늘이 돈다 <br>눈물이 흐른다 <br>]]></content><category term="약기운" label="약기운"/><category term="주정뱅이" label="주정뱅이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/약기운/잘살긴_글렀어/</id><title>약기운 - 잘살긴 글렀어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:36:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:36:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%BD%EA%B8%B0%EC%9A%B4/%EC%9E%98%EC%82%B4%EA%B8%B4_%EA%B8%80%EB%A0%80%EC%96%B4/" title="약기운 - 잘살긴 글렀어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잘살긴 글렀어 <br>내가 가진 패를 보니 <br>이팔의 망통 <br>삼팔의 따라지 <br>살아봤자 니 호구요 <br>빚지고 뻥카 치면 <br>패가망신이네 <br>잘살긴 글렀어 <br>내가 사는 이 세상은 <br>공무원이 장땡 <br>정규직은 구삥 <br>계약직은 일곱끝이니 <br>죽기엔 아깝지만 <br>살기에는 살 떨리네 <br>사고가 나도 내 탓이요 <br>망해도 내 탓 죽어도 내 탓 <br>세상이 엿같이 흘러가는 건 <br>다 내 탓이네 다 내 탓이네 <br>일하다 죽어도 내 탓 <br>공무원은 장례라도 <br>잘 치러주지만 <br>공사장에서 깔려 죽으면 <br>뉴스에 한줄 이네 <br>죽은 사람 탓이라네 <br>예 오예 오예 <br>잘살긴 글렀어 <br>내가 사는 이 세상은 <br>병원이 빨아먹어 <br>마트가 빨아먹어 <br>살려다 보니 <br>말할 수 없네 <br>은행원에 갑 질에 <br>눈물만 흘릴 뿐이네 <br>잘살긴 글렀어 <br>내가 사는 이세상은 <br>공무원이 빨아먹어 <br>이웃이 등쳐먹어 <br>살려다 보니 <br>말할 수 없네 <br>대출을 갚다가 갚다가 <br>늙어 버리네 <br>잘살긴 글렀어 <br>잘살긴 글렀어 <br>잘살긴 글렀어 <br>잘살긴 글렀어 <br>뭐같이 생겨서 <br>잘살긴 글렀어 <br>잘살긴 글렀어 <br>잘살긴 글렀어 <br>잘살긴 글렀어 <br>다 내 탓이라네 <br>예 오예 오예 <br>다 내 탓이라네 <br>]]></content><category term="약기운" label="약기운"/><category term="잘살긴 글렀어" label="잘살긴 글렀어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/약기운/잊어줘_나를/</id><title>약기운 - 잊어줘 나를 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:36:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:36:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%BD%EA%B8%B0%EC%9A%B4/%EC%9E%8A%EC%96%B4%EC%A4%98_%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC/" title="약기운 - 잊어줘 나를 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그런 행복한 표정으로 <br>나를 바라보지 말아줘 <br>이 비참한 삶 <br>그 안의 현실을 <br>조금 기다리라 말하고 <br>손을 흔들고 웃지만 <br>널 위한 날 이런 날 잊어줘 <br>책상위에 놓아둔 <br>나의 사진을 찢어 버려줘 <br>아니 태워줘 <br>개뿔도 없는 허세들도 <br>뜬 구름 잡던 개소리들도 <br>모두 기억 속에서 지워줘 <br>언제나 아름다운 너 <br>사랑할 수밖에 없는 너 <br>그 사랑을 지키고 싶었었는데 <br>난 아무것도 할 수 없는 걸 <br>그런 행복한 표정으로 <br>나를 바라보지 마 <br>너의 사랑은 나를 <br>비참하게 만들뿐이야 <br>니가 원하는 것 중에 <br>반에 반도 줄 수 없는 <br>이런 날 잊어줘 <br>나를 잊어줘 <br>나를 잊어줘 <br>]]></content><category term="약기운" label="약기운"/><category term="잊어줘 나를" label="잊어줘 나를"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kings_Town/Kings_Town/</id><title>King`s Town - King`s Town - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:36:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:36:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kings_Town/Kings_Town/" title="King`s Town - King`s Town - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날씨는 점점 뜨거운데 <br>내 맘은 점점 차가워져 <br>오늘도 한숨 가득 <br>외로운 하루 <br>길거릴 걸으며 나 홀로 <br>외로움과 함께 나 홀로 <br>언제나 한참 동안 가슴앓이 <br>Don't stop the dance night <br>외로움을 날려줄꺼야 <br>Don't stop the dance night <br>음악 위에 몸을 맡겨 <br>Don't stop the dance night <br>외로움을 날려줄꺼야 <br>Don't stop the dance night <br>이 한잔에 몸을 맡겨 <br>K K I I N N G G Town <br>K K I I N N G G Town <br>K K I I N N G G Town <br>가벼운 스텝을 밟으며 <br>떠나지 않는 음악소리 <br>이젠 멈출 수 없는 심장소리 <br>Don't stop the dance night <br>외로움을 날려줄꺼야 <br>Don't stop the dance night <br>음악 위에 몸을 맡겨 <br>Don't stop the dance night <br>외로움을 날려줄꺼야 <br>Don't stop the dance night <br>이 한잔에 몸을 맡겨 <br>K K I I N N G G Town <br>K K I I N N G G Town <br>My happiness important in my life <br>never mind we all dance <br>K K I I N N G G Town <br>K K I I N N G G Town <br>K K I I N N G G Town <br>K K I I N N G G Town <br>]]></content><category term="King`s Town" label="King`s Town"/><category term="King`s Town" label="King`s Town"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Musicen/빌려줄게_MR_여자키_b1/</id><title>Musicen - 빌려줄게 (MR 여자키 b1) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:36:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:36:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Musicen/%EB%B9%8C%EB%A0%A4%EC%A4%84%EA%B2%8C_MR_%EC%97%AC%EC%9E%90%ED%82%A4_b1/" title="Musicen - 빌려줄게 (MR 여자키 b1) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[혼자 있기 힘들 때 <br>나를 빌려줄게 <br>힘이 들면 언제나 <br>내게 기대면 돼 <br>흘러내린 눈물을 <br>멈출 수 없다면 <br>내 어깰 빌려줄게 <br>내게 적시면 돼 <br>불을 다 켜봐도 <br>맘이 어둡다 느끼고 <br>몸을 뉘어봐도 <br>맘을 놓을 수 없다면 <br>잠시 날 빌려줄게 <br>기대도 돼 <br>주저 말고 내게 와 <br>길었던 그 하루가 <br>힘겨웠을 테니까 그대 <br>아무 말 안해도 돼 <br>it’s alright it’s alright <br>왜 나만 안되지 <br>생각은 무거워지고 <br>내일이 두려워 <br>잠이 들 수가 없다면 <br>잠시 날 빌려줄게 <br>기대도 돼 <br>주저 말고 내게 와 <br>길었던 그 하루가 <br>힘겨웠을 테니까 그대 <br>아무 말 안해도 돼 <br>it’s alright oh <br>아무도 그 하루에 <br>관심이 없대도 <br>더는 외롭지 않게 <br>내가 들어줄게 <br>소리내 울어도 돼 <br>그래도 돼 <br>원한다면 언제나 <br>혼자여도 괜찮아 <br>무너져도 괜찮아 <br>이제 내가 널 안아줄게 <br>it’s alright it’s alright]]></content><category term="Musicen" label="Musicen"/><category term="빌려줄게 (MR 여자키 b1)" label="빌려줄게 (MR 여자키 b1)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김오키/사랑_시___김수영_노래___박지하/</id><title>김오키 - 사랑 (시 : 김수영, 노래 : 박지하) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:37:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:37:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%98%A4%ED%82%A4/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_%EC%8B%9C___%EA%B9%80%EC%88%98%EC%98%81_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98___%EB%B0%95%EC%A7%80%ED%95%98/" title="김오키 - 사랑 (시 : 김수영, 노래 : 박지하) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어둠 속에 불빛 속에 <br>변치 않는 사랑을 <br>배웠다 너로 해서 <br>배웠다 너로 해서 <br>그러나 너의 얼굴은 <br>어둠에서 불빛으로 넘어가는 <br>그 찰나에 꺼졌다 살아났다 <br>너의 얼굴은 그만큼 불안하다 <br>그 찰나에 꺼졌다 살아났다 <br>너의 얼굴은 그만큼 불안하다 <br>번개처럼 번개처럼 <br>금이 간 너의 얼굴은 <br>어둠 속에 불빛 속에 <br>변치 않는 사랑을 <br>배웠다 너로 해서 <br>배웠다 너로 해서 <br>배웠다 너로 해서 <br>배웠다 너로 해서 <br>]]></content><category term="김오키" label="김오키"/><category term="사랑 (시 : 김수영, 노래 : 박지하)" label="사랑 (시 : 김수영, 노래 : 박지하)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/블리티/두근두근/</id><title>블리티 - 두근두근 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:39:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:39:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%94%EB%A6%AC%ED%8B%B0/%EB%91%90%EA%B7%BC%EB%91%90%EA%B7%BC/" title="블리티 - 두근두근 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너를 본 순간 <br>fall in love <br>빛이나 너무 멋진 걸 <br>어쩌지 니가 <br>너무 좋아져서 <br>내 맘 좀 볼래 <br>너와 요즘 난 <br>make it love <br>너무 행복할 뿐인 걸 <br>부러워하는 시선들이 <br>느껴져 내가 볼땐 <br>자꾸 니 생각에 <br>미소가 지어져 난 <br>네게 빠져 버린걸 <br>어째 베이베 <br>너와 함께하는 <br>요즘 이 시간들이 <br>나는 너무 <br>행복한걸요 <br>니가 날 바라보면 <br>베이비 오 마이 럽 <br>두근두근 니 맘 <br>더 알고 싶어 <br>러뷰 러뷰 베이베 <br>두근대 날 바라볼 때 <br>내 심장이 떨릴 때 <br>사랑해 지금 이대로만 <br>너와 영원했으면 <br>니가 날 안아주면 <br>베이비 오 마이 럽 <br>두근두근 니 맘 <br>다 갖고싶어 <br>러뷰 러뷰 베이베 <br>두근대 속삭여줄땐 <br>내 마음이 떨릴때 <br>사랑해 언제까지나 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>my love <br>너무 사랑해 <br>oh my love <br>헤어 나올 수 없는 걸 <br>어쩌지 꿈만 같아 <br>너만 보면 <br>내 맘 좀 볼래 <br>이래도 될까 싶은 love <br>너무 행복할 뿐일 걸 <br>날 사랑하는 너의 맘이 <br>느껴져 내가 볼 땐 <br>자꾸 니 생각에 <br>미소가 지어져 난 <br>너무 사랑스러워 <br>어째 베이베 <br>너와 함께 만들어갈 <br>이 기억들이 <br>나는 너무 <br>소중한걸요 <br>니가 날 바라보면 <br>베이비 오 마이 럽 <br>두근두근 니 맘 <br>더 알고싶어 <br>러뷰 러뷰 베이베 <br>두근대 날 바라볼 때 <br>내 심장이 떨릴때 <br>사랑해 지금 이대로만 <br>너와 영원했으면 <br>니가 날 안아주면 <br>베이비 오 마이 럽 <br>두근두근 니 맘 <br>다 갖고 싶어 <br>러뷰러뷰 베이베 <br>두근대 속삭여줄땐 <br>내 마음이 떨릴때 <br>사랑해 언제까지나 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>my love <br>사랑해 너와 입맞출때엔 <br>나를 사랑하는 <br>너의 맘이 전해져 <br>너도 지금 <br>내 맘이 전해지니 <br>너와 함께라는게 난 기뻐 <br>니가 날 바라보면 <br>베이비 오 마이 럽 <br>두근두근 니 맘 <br>더 알고싶어 <br>러뷰 러뷰 베이베 <br>두근대 날 바라볼때 <br>내 심장이 떨릴때 <br>사랑해 지금 이대로만 <br>너와 영원했으면 <br>니가 날 안아주면 <br>베이비 오 마이 럽 <br>두근두근 니 맘 <br>다 갖고싶어 <br>러뷰 러뷰 베이베 <br>두근대 속삭여줄땐 <br>내 마음이 떨릴때 <br>사랑해 언제까지나 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>my love <br>]]></content><category term="블리티" label="블리티"/><category term="두근두근" label="두근두근"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/다원/파란눈물_Non_Rap_Ver/</id><title>다원 - 파란눈물 (Non Rap Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:39:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:39:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EC%9B%90/%ED%8C%8C%EB%9E%80%EB%88%88%EB%AC%BC_Non_Rap_Ver/" title="다원 - 파란눈물 (Non Rap Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잊으려 한 니 웃음 <br>파랗게 된 니 입술 <br>나를 위해 흘린다는 <br>그 눈물을 <br>삯히고 삼키고 <br>오늘 하루도 널 지운다 <br>시간이 날 비웃고 <br>사랑이 날 비웃고 <br>잃어버린 가슴과 <br>날 채워버린 <br>두 사람 두 사랑 <br>나를 가둬버린 두 사랑 <br>웃다 울다 그리고 <br>웃다 울다 또 그리고 <br>희미해진 너의 그 얼굴 <br>나를 안아주던 그 입술이 <br>기다릴 걸 그랬어 <br>어떻게 널 지워가야 해 <br>왜 이제야 돌아와 <br>널 사랑하라 하니 <br>다른 사람 사랑하는 날 <br>니 곁에 있으라 있으라 <br>두 사람을 사랑하면 돼 <br>웃다 울다 그리고 <br>웃다 울다 또 그리고 <br>희미해진 너의 그 얼굴 <br>나를 안아주던 그 입술이 <br>기다릴걸 그랬어 <br>어떻게 널 지워가야 해 <br>오지 말지 그랬어 <br>죽었다고 생각하게 <br>원래 우린 없었던 거야 <br>사랑하다 헤어지고 그래 <br>기다리지 그랬어 <br>어떻게 날 지웠냐고 <br>남들처럼 흘린 눈물에 <br>오늘 하루도 넌 묻는다 <br>웃다 울다 그리고 <br>웃다 울다 또 그리고 <br>희미해진 너의 그 얼굴 <br>나를 안아주던 그 입술이 <br>기다릴 걸 그랬어 <br>어떻게 널 지워가야 해 <br>오지 말지 그랬어 <br>죽었다고 생각하게 <br>원래 우린 없었던 거야 <br>사랑하다 헤어지고 그래 <br>기다리지 그랬어 <br>어떻게 날 지웠냐고 <br>남들처럼 흘린 눈물에 <br>오늘 하루도 넌 묻는다 <br>]]></content><category term="다원" label="다원"/><category term="파란눈물 (Non Rap Ver.)" label="파란눈물 (Non Rap Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/다원/파란눈물_Feat_UG/</id><title>다원 - 파란눈물 (Feat. UG) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:39:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:39:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EC%9B%90/%ED%8C%8C%EB%9E%80%EB%88%88%EB%AC%BC_Feat_UG/" title="다원 - 파란눈물 (Feat. UG) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잊으려 한 니 웃음 <br>파랗게 된 니 입술 <br>나를 위해 흘린다는 <br>그 눈물을 <br>삯히고 삼키고 <br>오늘 하루도 널 지운다 <br>시간이 날 비웃고 <br>사랑이 날 비웃고 <br>잃어버린 가슴과 <br>날 채워버린 <br>두 사람 두 사랑 <br>나를 가둬버린 두 사랑 <br>웃다 울다 그리고 <br>웃다 울다 또 그리고 <br>희미해진 너의 그 얼굴 <br>나를 안아주던 그 입술이 <br>기다릴 걸 그랬어 <br>어떻게 널 지워가야 해 <br>왜 이제야 돌아와 <br>널 사랑하라 하니 <br>다른 사람 사랑하는 날 <br>니 곁에 있으라 있으라 <br>두 사람을 사랑하면 돼 <br>웃다 울다 그리고 <br>웃다 울다 또 그리고 <br>희미해진 너의 그 얼굴 <br>나를 안아주던 그 입술이 <br>기다릴걸 그랬어 <br>어떻게 널 지워가야 해 <br>오지 말지 그랬어 <br>죽었다고 생각하게 <br>원래 우린 없었던 거야 <br>사랑하다 헤어지고 그래 <br>기다리지 그랬어 <br>어떻게 날 지웠냐고 <br>남들처럼 흘린 눈물에 <br>오늘 하루도 넌 묻는다 <br>너 하나만을 <br>바라봤던 내 두 눈이 <br>이젠 다른 사람 <br>향해있는 이 기분이 <br>나 가끔 적응 안돼 <br>언제나 함께이길 <br>약속했었는데 <br>그렇게 사랑을 했던 <br>누구보다 영원할거라 <br>믿었는데 <br>니 자린 비워둘게 <br>말하던 너의 눈동자에 <br>비치던 눈물이 <br>흘러내리기도 전 <br>돌아서 버렸던 <br>그 매정했던 내 모습 <br>이제는 잊었어 <br>웃다 울다 그리고 <br>웃다 울다 또 그리고 <br>희미해진 너의 그 얼굴 <br>나를 안아주던 그 입술이 <br>기다릴 걸 그랬어 <br>어떻게 널 지워가야 해 <br>오지 말지 그랬어 <br>죽었다고 생각하게 <br>원래 우린 없었던 거야 <br>사랑하다 헤어지고 그래 <br>기다리지 그랬어 <br>어떻게 날 지웠냐고 <br>남들처럼 흘린 눈물에 <br>오늘 하루도 넌 묻는다 <br>]]></content><category term="다원" label="다원"/><category term="파란눈물 (Feat. UG)" label="파란눈물 (Feat. UG)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김현림/From_정현_Feat_박수진_Bonus_Track/</id><title>김현림 - From 정현 (Feat. 박수진) (Bonus Track) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:40:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:40:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%98%84%EB%A6%BC/From_%EC%A0%95%ED%98%84_Feat_%EB%B0%95%EC%88%98%EC%A7%84_Bonus_Track/" title="김현림 - From 정현 (Feat. 박수진) (Bonus Track) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑한다 꼭 너에게 <br>전하고 싶은 말 <br>누구보다 우릴 사랑하는 맘 <br>항상 곁에 있어 준 <br>하나님의 사랑을 <br>너희도 꼭 기억하기를 <br>1987년 09월 29일 <br>사내아이가 바로 태어났네 <br>그건 내 기억에는 전혀 없네 <br>세상 빛을 처음 본 <br>my birthday <br>태어나 지금까지 <br>everyday <br>쉬운 것 조차 하나 없네 <br>어리석은 수많은 실수와 <br>내 눈엔 부질없는 눈물만 <br>아무 생각 없이 교회에 <br>앉았다 문을 박차고 <br>교회를 나간 나 <br>PC방 만화방 어둔밤까지 <br>그렇게 시간을 보낸 나 <br>시간이 지나 성적에 <br>맞춰 대학으로 진학 <br>허무하게 20대를 지나 <br>30대에 접어든 나 <br>사랑한다 꼭 너에게 <br>전하고 싶은 말 <br>누구보다 우릴 사랑하는 맘 <br>항상 곁에 있어 준 <br>하나님의 사랑을 <br>너희도 꼭 기억하기를 <br>울고 웃던 지난날의 <br>흔적 30년이라는 <br>시간은 훌쩍 지났네 <br>기억 속에 하나님의 <br>사랑이 흘렀네 <br>뒤늦게 깨달았네 <br>나의 모든 상황속에서 <br>하나님의 사랑이 흘렀네 <br>지금까지도 내게 흐르네 <br>이 시간을 빌어 <br>너희 맘속에 항상 <br>기억하기를 <br>나처럼 후회 말라고 <br>하나님 사랑 알라고 <br>어른이 되어 살다 보면 <br>좌절과 어려움에 눈물이 나면 <br>다시 기억해 나에게 <br>큰 힘이 되는 하나님을 <br>사랑한다 꼭 너에게 <br>전하고 싶은 말 <br>누구보다 우릴 사랑하는 맘 <br>항상 곁에 있어 준 <br>하나님의 사랑을 <br>너희도 꼭 기억하기를 <br>]]></content><category term="김현림" label="김현림"/><category term="From 정현 (Feat. 박수진) (Bonus Track)" label="From 정현 (Feat. 박수진) (Bonus Track)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김현림/이유/</id><title>김현림 - 이유 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:40:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:40:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%98%84%EB%A6%BC/%EC%9D%B4%EC%9C%A0/" title="김현림 - 이유 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나를 위해서 십자가 지시고 <br>아무 이유 없이 고난받았네 <br>사랑한단 말 나를 사랑한단 말 <br>내 가슴에서 지워지지 않는 말 <br>저 갈보리 언덕 험한 십자가 <br>주는 그 모든 것 감당하셨네 <br>그 한 없는 사랑 <br>나의 구원되신 주님께 <br>감사드리네 <br>이 세상을 사랑하사 <br>하늘 보좌 모두 버리고 <br>이 땅 가운데 찾아오신 주님 <br>아무 흠도 없으신 주 <br>우릴 위해 십자가 고통 <br>참으셨네 <br>우릴 위해 죽으셨네 <br>감사할 때도 원망할 때도 <br>나의 모습 그대로를 <br>사랑하시네 <br>신실한 사랑 구원되신 주 예수 <br>찬양받기 합당하신 그 이름 <br>저 갈보리 언덕 험한 십자가 <br>주는 그 모든 것 감당하셨네 <br>그 한 없는 사랑 <br>나의 구원되신 주님께 <br>감사드리네 <br>이 세상을 사랑하사 <br>하늘 보좌 모두 버리고 <br>이 땅 가운데 찾아오신 주님 <br>아무 흠도 없으신 주 <br>우릴 위해 십자가 고통 <br>참으셨네 <br>우릴 위해 죽으셨네 <br>무엇도 끊을 수 없는 <br>신실하고 영원한 그 사랑 <br>이 세상을 사랑하사 <br>하늘 보좌 모두 버리고 <br>이 땅 가운데 찾아오신 주님 <br>아무 흠도 없으신 주 <br>우릴 위해 십자가 고통 <br>참으셨네 <br>우릴 위해 죽으셨네 <br>우릴 정말 사랑해서 <br>]]></content><category term="김현림" label="김현림"/><category term="이유" label="이유"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/두왑_사운즈_Doo-Wop_Sounds/You_Are/</id><title>두왑 사운즈 (Doo-Wop Sounds) - You Are... - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:41:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:41:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%91%90%EC%99%91_%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B4%EC%A6%88_Doo-Wop_Sounds/You_Are/" title="두왑 사운즈 (Doo-Wop Sounds) - You Are... - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무것도 모르던 <br>겁도 없었던 <br>하지 말라고 얘기해도 <br>듣지 않았던 그때 <br>내게 다가온 그대 <br>내 맘은 그저 그랬던 그때 <br>꿈만 같아 그랬던 난데 <br>You are You are <br>You are <br>You're my life 그대여 <br>You are You are <br>You are <br>You're my dream <br>내게 다가온 그대 <br>어느새 내 옆에 <br>이 모든 것이 꿈만 같아 <br>가끔은 실수해도 <br>또 짜증을 내도 <br>힘든 일도 많지만 <br>이 모든 것이 나에게 <br>You are You are <br>You are <br>You're my life 그대여 <br>You are You are <br>You are <br>You're my dream <br>이 모든 것이 나에게 <br>You are You are <br>You are <br>You're my life 그대여 <br>You are You are <br>You are <br>You're my dream <br>]]></content><category term="두왑 사운즈 (Doo-Wop Sounds)" label="두왑 사운즈 (Doo-Wop Sounds)"/><category term="You Are..." label="You Are..."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신아라/금이요_옥이요/</id><title>신아라 - 금이요 옥이요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:41:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:41:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%95%84%EB%9D%BC/%EA%B8%88%EC%9D%B4%EC%9A%94_%EC%98%A5%EC%9D%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="신아라 - 금이요 옥이요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[금이요 옥이요 <br>보석이로구나 <br>내 사랑 그대가 <br>금옥이로구나 <br>내가 찾던 바로 그 사람 <br>한 평생 그대와 <br>사랑해요 사랑해요 <br>큰소리로 외쳐봅니다 <br>내사랑 그대가 <br>금이요 옥이요 <br>보석이로구나 <br>금이로구나 옥이로구나 <br>황금같은 보석이요 <br>내사랑 그대가 <br>진주같은 보석입니다 <br>금이요 옥이요 <br>보석이로구나 <br>내 사랑 그대가 <br>금옥이로구나 <br>내가 찾던 바로 그 사람 <br>한 평생 그대와 <br>사랑해요 사랑해요 <br>큰소리로 외쳐봅니다 <br>내사랑 그대가 <br>금이요 옥이요 <br>보석이로구나 <br>금이로구나 옥이로구나 <br>황금같은 보석이요 <br>내사랑 그대가 <br>진주같은 보석입니다 <br>금이로구나 옥이로구나 <br>황금같은 보석이요 <br>내사랑 그대가 <br>진주같은 보석입니다 <br>진주같은 보석입니다 <br>]]></content><category term="신아라" label="신아라"/><category term="금이요 옥이요" label="금이요 옥이요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Paraguay_Live/</id><title>Iggy Pop - Paraguay (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:41:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:41:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Paraguay_Live/" title="Iggy Pop - Paraguay (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wild animals they do <br>Never wonder why <br>Just do what they goddamn do <br>Yeah <br><br>Wild animals they do <br>Never wonder why <br>Just do what they goddamn do <br><br>I'm goin' where sore losers go <br>To hide my face and spend my dough <br>Though it's a dream, it's not a lie <br>And I won't stop to say goodbye <br><br>Paraguay <br>Paraguay <br><br>See I just couldn't take no more <br>Of whippin' fools and keepin' score <br>I just thought well, fuck it man <br>I'm gonna pack my soul and scram <br><br>Paraguay <br>Paraguay <br><br>Out of the way I'll get away <br>Won't have to hear the things they say <br>Tamales and a bank account <br>Are all I need, so count me out <br><br>Paraguay <br>Paraguay <br><br>I'll have no fear <br>I'll know no fear <br>So far from here <br>I'll have no fear <br>Tra la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la <br>Tra la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la <br>Tra la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la <br>Tra la la la <br>Tra la la la <br>Tra la la la <br>Tra la la la <br><br>Wild animals they do <br>Never wonder why <br>Just do what they goddamn do <br><br>There's nothing awesome here <br>Not a damn thing <br>There's nothing new <br>Just a bunch of people scared <br>Everybody's fucking scared <br>Fear eats all the souls at once <br>I'm tired of it <br>And I dream about getting away <br>To a new life <br>Where there's not so much fucking knowledge <br>I don't want any of this information <br>I don't want YOU <br>No <br>Not anymore <br>I've had enough of you <br>Yeah, I'm talking to you <br>I'm gonna go to Paraguay <br>To live in a compound under the trees <br>With servants and bodyguards who love me <br>Free of criticism <br>Free of manners and mores <br>I wanna be your basic clod <br>Who made good <br>And went away while he could <br>To somewhere where people are still human beings <br>Where they have spirit <br>You take your motherfucking laptop <br>And just shove it into your goddamn foul mouth <br>And down your shit heel gizzard <br>You fucking phony two faced three timing piece of turd <br>And I hope you shit it out <br>With all the words in it <br>And I hope the security services read those words <br>And pick you up and flay you <br>For all your evil and poisonous intentions <br>Because I'm sick <br>And it's your fault <br>And I'm gonna go heal myself now <br>Yeah]]></content><category term="Iggy Pop" label="Iggy Pop"/><category term="Paraguay (Live)" label="Paraguay (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Break_Into_Your_Heart_Live/</id><title>Iggy Pop - Break Into Your Heart (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:41:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:41:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Break_Into_Your_Heart_Live/" title="Iggy Pop - Break Into Your Heart (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm gonna break into your heart <br>I'm gonna crawl under your skin <br>I'm gonna break into your heart <br>And follow till I see where you begin <br><br>Times so tight,it's closing in <br>Forty more hours to go <br>When the tumblers spin <br>I'm getting in <br>Gonna be time to grow <br><br>I'm gonna break into your heart <br>I'm gonna crawl under your skin <br>I'm gonna break into your heart <br>And follow till I see where you begin <br><br>Hooks go deep, but it's make believe <br>But you're never gonna grow <br>Your heart is buried underneath <br>Mountains capped with snow <br><br>I'm gonna break into your heart <br>I'm gonna crawl under your skin <br>I'm gonna break into your heart <br>And follow till I see where you begin <br><br>Break them all <br>Take them all <br>Fake them all <br>Steal them all <br>Fail them all <br>Touch them all <br>Break them all <br>Break them all <br><br>I'm gonna break into your heart <br>I'm gonna break into your heart <br>I'm gonna break into your heart <br>I'm gonna break into your heart <br>Till it all comes crashing down <br><br>I'm gonna break into your heart <br>I'm gonna crawl under your skin <br>I'm gonna break into your heart <br>And follow till I get under your skin <br>And the wall comes tumbling down <br>And you finally let me in <br>I'll break into your]]></content><category term="Iggy Pop" label="Iggy Pop"/><category term="Break Into Your Heart (Live)" label="Break Into Your Heart (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/China_Girl_Live/</id><title>Iggy Pop - China Girl (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:41:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:41:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/China_Girl_Live/" title="Iggy Pop - China Girl (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I couldn't escape this feeling <br>With my China Girl <br>I'm just a wreck without <br>My little China Girl <br>I'd hear hearts beating <br>Loud as thunder <br>See the stars crashing <br><br>I'm a mess without <br>My China Girl <br>Wake up mornings, there's <br>No China Girl <br>I'd hear hearts beating <br>Loud as thunder <br>I'd see stars crashing down <br><br>I'd feel tragic <br>Like I was Marlon Brando <br>When I'd look at my China Girl <br>I could pretend that nothing <br>Really meant too much <br>When I'd look at my China Girl <br><br>I'd stumble into town <br>Just like a sacred cow <br>Visions of swastikas in my head <br>And plans for everyone <br>It's in the white of my eyes <br><br>My little China Girl <br>You shouldn't mess with me <br>I'll ruin everything you are <br>I'll give you television <br>I'll give you eyes of blue <br>I'll give you men who want to rule the world <br><br>And when I get excited <br>My little China Girl says <br>Oh Jimmy, just shut your mouth <br>She says, Shhhh]]></content><category term="Iggy Pop" label="Iggy Pop"/><category term="China Girl (Live)" label="China Girl (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/The_Passenger_Live/</id><title>Iggy Pop - The Passenger (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:41:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:41:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/The_Passenger_Live/" title="Iggy Pop - The Passenger (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I am the passenger and I ride and I ride <br>I ride through the city's backsides <br>I see the stars come out of the sky <br>Yeah, the bright and hollow sky <br>You know it looks so good tonight <br><br>I am the passenger <br>I stay under glass <br>I look through my window so bright <br>I see the stars come out tonight <br>I see the bright and hollow sky <br>Over the city's ripped backsides <br>And everything looks good tonight <br>Singing la la la la la lala la la, la la la la lala la la etc <br><br>Get into the car <br>We'll be the passenger <br>We'll ride through the city tonight <br>We'll see the city's ripped backsides <br>We'll see the bright and hollow sky <br>We'll see the stars that shine so bright <br>Stars made for us tonight <br><br>Oh, the passenger <br>How, how he rides <br>Oh, the passenger <br>He rides and he rides <br>He looks through his window <br>What does he see <br>He sees the sign and hollow sky <br>He sees the stars come out tonight <br>He sees the city's ripped backsides <br>He sees the winding ocean drive <br>And everything was made for you and me <br>All of it was made for you and me <br>'Cause it just belongs to you and me <br>So let's take a ride and see what's mine <br>Singing la la la la lala la la x3 <br><br>Oh the passenger <br>He rides and he rides <br>He sees things from under glass <br>He looks through his window side <br>He sees the things that he knows are his <br>He sees the bright and hollow sky <br>He sees the city sleep at night <br>He sees the stars are out tonight <br>And all of it is yours and mine <br>And all of it is yours and mine <br>So let's ride and ride and ride and ride <br>Oh, oh, Singing la la la la lalalala]]></content><category term="Iggy Pop" label="Iggy Pop"/><category term="The Passenger (Live)" label="The Passenger (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Gardenia_Live/</id><title>Iggy Pop - Gardenia (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:41:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:41:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Gardenia_Live/" title="Iggy Pop - Gardenia (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Gardenia <br>Where are you <br>Black goddess in a shabby raincoat <br>Where are you tonight <br>Cheap purple baby doll dress <br>A gardenia in your hair <br>Much taller and stronger than me <br>A forbidden dream, a dream, a dream <br><br>All I wanna do is tell Gardenia <br>What to do tonight <br>All I wanna do is tell Gardenia <br>What to do tonight <br><br>Gardenia <br>Where are you tonight <br>The streets were your home <br>Now where do you roam <br>Your hourglass ass <br>And your powerful back <br>Your slant devil eyes <br>And the ditch down your spine <br>Deep as Deep as <br><br>All I wanna do is tell Gardenia <br>What to do tonight <br>All I wanna do is tell Gardenia <br>What to do tonight <br><br>We lay in the darkness <br>Then she turned the lights on <br>I saw a dangerous habit <br>When she turned the lights on <br>There's always a catch <br>In the darkness when you <br>When you turn the lights on <br>There's always a catch <br>Oh well, oh well, oh well, oh well <br><br>All I wanna do is tell Gardenia <br>What to do tonight <br>All I wanna do is tell Gardenia <br>What to do tonight <br><br>Alone in the cheapo motel <br>By the highway to hell <br>America's greatest living poet <br>Was ogling you all night <br>You should be wearing the finest gown <br>But here you are now <br>Gas, food, lodging, poverty, misery and gardenia <br>You could be burned at the stake <br>For all your mistakes, mistakes, mistakes <br><br>All I wanna do is tell Gardenia <br>What to do tonight <br>All I wanna do is tell Gardenia <br>What to do tonight]]></content><category term="Iggy Pop" label="Iggy Pop"/><category term="Gardenia (Live)" label="Gardenia (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Sunday_Live/</id><title>Iggy Pop - Sunday (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:41:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:41:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Sunday_Live/" title="Iggy Pop - Sunday (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This house, is as slick as a senator's statement <br>This job is a masquerade of recreation <br>Like a wreck, I'm sinking fast <br><br>The key to everything <br>I crawl for Sunday <br>When I don't have to move <br>Caught up in dreams untangled one day <br>Where I don't have to prove <br>The days roll on and finally Sunday <br>A Sunday afternoon <br>I've got it all <br>But what's it for <br>But getting some more <br><br>Always ready, always steady and <br>Always ready, always steady and <br><br>The street is as cold as a corporate law suit <br>A pride, I can't jive is telling me to wipe my boots <br>I'm a wreck <br>What did you expect <br><br>The key to everything <br>I crawl for Sunday <br>When I don't have to move <br>Caught up in dreams untangled one day <br>Where I don't have to prove <br>The days roll on and finally Sunday <br>A Sunday afternoon <br>I've got it all <br>And so what now <br><br>Do what they say and then do what they say, go back <br>Do what they say and then do what they say, go back <br>Do what they say and then do what they say, go back <br>Do what they say and do what they say till Sunday <br>Do what they say <br>Until I'm black and blue <br>Oh what can I do <br><br>Always ready, always steady and <br>Always ready, always steady and <br><br>Got all I need and it is killing me <br>And you <br>x6]]></content><category term="Iggy Pop" label="Iggy Pop"/><category term="Sunday (Live)" label="Sunday (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Tonight_Live/</id><title>Iggy Pop - Tonight (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:41:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:41:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Tonight_Live/" title="Iggy Pop - Tonight (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I saw my baby <br>She was turning blue <br>Oh, I knew that soon, her <br>Young life was through <br><br>And so I got down on my knees <br>Down by her bed <br>And these are the words <br>To her I said <br><br>Everything will be all right, Tonight x2 <br><br>No one moves <br>No one talks <br>No one thinks <br>No one walks, Tonight <br><br>Everyone will be all right, Tonight x2 <br><br>No one moves <br>No one talks <br>No one thinks <br>No one walks, Tonight, Tonight <br><br>I am gonna love her to the end x2 <br>I will love her 'til I die <br>I will see her in the skyTonight x5]]></content><category term="Iggy Pop" label="Iggy Pop"/><category term="Tonight (Live)" label="Tonight (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Funtime_Live/</id><title>Iggy Pop - Funtime (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:41:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:41:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Funtime_Live/" title="Iggy Pop - Funtime (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fun <br>hey baby we like your lips <br>Fun <br>hey baby we like your pants <br>all aboard for funtime <br>Fun <br>Hey, I feel lucky tonight <br>Fun <br>I'm gonna get stoned and run around <br>All aboard for funtime <br>Fun <br>Last night I was down in the lab <br>Fun <br>Talkin' to Dracula and his crew <br>All aboard for funtime <br>Fun <br>I don't need no heavy trips <br>Fun <br>I just do what I want to do <br>All aboard for funtime <br>Fun <br>Baby baby we like your lips <br>Fun <br>Baby baby we like your pants <br>All aboard for funtime <br>Fun <br>Everybody we want in <br>Fun <br>We want some we want some <br>All aboard for funtime <br>Fun <br>Baby baby we like your lips <br>Fun <br>Baby baby we like your pants <br>All aboard for funtime]]></content><category term="Iggy Pop" label="Iggy Pop"/><category term="Funtime (Live)" label="Funtime (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Sixteen_Live/</id><title>Iggy Pop - Sixteen (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:41:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:41:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Sixteen_Live/" title="Iggy Pop - Sixteen (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sweet Sixteen in leather boots <br>Body and soul I go crazy <br>Baby, baby I'm hungry Sweet Sixteen <br><br>Funky bar all full of faces <br>Pretty faces, beautiful faces <br>Body and soul, body and soul, I give to you <br><br>I am an easy mark <br>With my broken heart Sweet Sixteen <br><br>Show you my explosion Sweet Sixteen <br><br>Go out to the funky bar <br>I get hurt crying inside <br>'Cause everybody's so fine and <br>And they don't need me <br><br>Tell me, what can I do, Sweet Sixteen <br><br>I give you my body and soul Sweet Sixteen <br><br>I must be hungry <br>'Cause I go crazy <br>Over your leather boots <br><br>Now baby, I know <br>That's not normal <br>Well, I love you, I love you, I love you&lt;, Sweet Sixteen <br><br>Everywhere I go, I'm lonely]]></content><category term="Iggy Pop" label="Iggy Pop"/><category term="Sixteen (Live)" label="Sixteen (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/American_Valhalla_Live/</id><title>Iggy Pop - American Valhalla (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:41:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:41:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/American_Valhalla_Live/" title="Iggy Pop - American Valhalla (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I have no plans, I have no debts <br>The mind is not the carefree set <br>I'm looking for American Valhalla <br>So if it passes by give me a holler <br>Please <br><br>I've shot my gun, I've used my knife <br>This hasn't been an easy life <br>I'm hoping for American Valhalla <br>But if I have outlived my use <br>Please drink my juice <br><br>Innocence <br>It's so hard to figure it out <br>Innocence <br>It's so hard to figure it out <br>I don't know <br>I don't know <br>I don't know <br>I don't know <br>It's so hard to figure it out <br>I don't know <br>I don't know <br>I don't know <br>I don't know <br><br>Where is American Valhalla <br>Death is the pill that's tough to swallow <br>Is there anybody in there <br>Who do I have to kill <br>I'm not the man with everything <br>I've nothing, but my name <br><br>Lowly, lowly deeds <br>That no one sees <br>Lowly, lowly deeds <br>That no one sees <br><br>Where is American Valhalla <br>Death is the pill that's hard to swallow <br>Is anybody in there <br>And can I bring a friend <br>I'm not the man with everything <br>I've nothing, but my name <br>I've nothing, but my name <br>I've nothing, but my name <br>I've nothing, but my name <br>I've nothing, but my name]]></content><category term="Iggy Pop" label="Iggy Pop"/><category term="American Valhalla (Live)" label="American Valhalla (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Sister_Midnight_Live/</id><title>Iggy Pop - Sister Midnight (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:41:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:41:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Sister_Midnight_Live/" title="Iggy Pop - Sister Midnight (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Calling Sister Midnight <br>You've got me reaching for the moon <br>Calling Sister Midnight <br>You've got me playing the fool <br>Calling Sister Midnight <br><br>Calling Sister Midnight <br>Can you hear me call <br>Can you hear me well <br>Can you hear me at all <br>Calling Sister Midnight <br>I'm an Idiot for you <br>Calling Sister Midnight <br>I'm a breakage inside <br>Calling Sister Midnight <br>Calling Sister Midnight <br>You know I had a dream last night <br>Mother was in my bed <br>And I made love to her <br>Father he gunned for me <br>Hunted me with his six gun <br>Calling Sister Midnight <br>What can I do about my dreams <br><br>Listen to me Sister Midnight <br>You put a beggar in my heart <br>Calling Sister Midnight <br>You've got me walking in rags <br>Hey where are you Sister Midnight <br>Can you hear me call <br>Can you hear me well <br>Can you hear me at all]]></content><category term="Iggy Pop" label="Iggy Pop"/><category term="Sister Midnight (Live)" label="Sister Midnight (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Lust_For_Life_Live/</id><title>Iggy Pop - Lust For Life (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:41:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:41:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iggy_Pop/Lust_For_Life_Live/" title="Iggy Pop - Lust For Life (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here comes Johnny Yen again <br>With the liquor and drugs <br>And a flesh machine <br>He's gonna do another strip tease <br><br>Hey man, where'd you get that lotion <br>I've been hurting since I bought the gimmick <br>About something called love <br>Yeah, something called love <br>Well, that's like hypnotising chickens <br><br>Well, I'm just a modern guy <br>Of course, I've had it in the ear before <br>'Cause of a lust for life <br>'Cause of a lust for life <br><br>I'm worth a million in prizes <br>With my torture film <br>Drive a GTO <br>Wear a uniform <br>All on government loan <br><br>I'm worth a million in prizes <br>Yeah, I'm through with sleeping on the sidewalk <br>No more beating my brains <br>No more beating my brains <br>With the liquor and drugs <br>With the liquor and drugs <br><br>Well, I'm just a modern guy <br>Of course, I've had it in my ear before <br>'Cause, of a lust for life lust for life <br>'Cause of a lust for life lust for life, oooo <br>I've got a lust for life oooh <br>Got a lust for life oooh <br>Oh, a lust for life oooh <br>Oh, a lust for life oooh <br>A lust for life oooh <br>I got a lust for life oooh <br>Got a lust for life <br><br>Well, I'm just a modern guy <br>Of course, I've had it in my ear before <br>'Cause I've a lust for life <br>'Cause I've a lust for life <br><br>Well, here comes Johnny Yen again <br>With the liquor and drugs <br>And a flesh machine <br>I know he's gonna do another strip tease <br><br>Hey man, where'd ya get that lotion <br>Your skin starts itching once you buy the gimmick <br>About something called love <br>Oh Love, love, love <br>Well, that's like hypnotising chickens <br><br>Well, I'm just a modern guy <br>Of course, I've had it in the ear before <br>And I've a lust for life lust for life <br>'Cause I've a lust for life lust for life <br>Got a lust for life <br>Yeah, a lust for life <br>I got a lust for life <br>Oh, a lust for life <br>Got a lust for life <br>Yeah a lust for life <br>I got a lust for life <br>Lust for life]]></content><category term="Iggy Pop" label="Iggy Pop"/><category term="Lust For Life (Live)" label="Lust For Life (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matt_Redman/How_Far/</id><title>Matt Redman - How Far - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:44:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:44:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matt_Redman/How_Far/" title="Matt Redman - How Far - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In Nazareth of Galilee <br>An angel speaks the sacred words <br>Mary you will be with child <br>The miracle of virgin birth <br><br>Joseph heeds the angel sign <br>And takes her as his promised wife <br>Now through the night they journey on <br>How far is it to Bethlehem? <br><br>Wise men plan their course ahead <br>Searching for the promised King <br>Now from the east a guiding star <br>How far is it to Bethlehem? <br><br>How far, how far, to the place where hope was born? <br><br>The walls outside Jerusalem <br>O see the mount of Calvary <br>There lifted high upon a cross <br>The Saviour of humanity <br><br>He conquered sin and buried shame <br>Rose to life and burst the grave <br>Forever bridged the great divide <br>With perfect grace and sacrifice <br><br>How far, how far love has come to bring us home <br><br>How far they went to Bethlehem, <br>How far you went for Calvary! <br>No greater grace was ever known <br>No greater love was ever seen <br><br>We set our hearts on pilgrimage <br>We’re caught up in Your story too <br>From Bethlehem to Calvary <br>Our hearts will always follow You <br>How far, how far, Saviour, lead us to Your heart <br>How far, how far, Jesus lead us to Your heart]]></content><category term="Matt Redman" label="Matt Redman"/><category term="How Far" label="How Far"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matt_Redman/His_Name_Shall_Be/</id><title>Matt Redman - His Name Shall Be - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:44:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:44:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matt_Redman/His_Name_Shall_Be/" title="Matt Redman - His Name Shall Be - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Verse 1 <br> Oh, can you hear the angels' song <br> That rang so sweet and clear <br> When heaven's light and music fell <br> And mercy found us here <br> Glory in the highest <br> And on the earth be peace <br> Glory to God the angels sing! <br> Turnaround <br><br> Verse 2 <br> He came to tell the Father's love <br> His goodness and His grace <br> To show the brightness of His smile <br> The glory of His face <br> So glory in the highest <br> And on the earth be peace <br> Glory to God Your children sing <br><br> Chorus <br> His name shall be called Wonderful, Counselor <br> Mighty God, Everlasting Father <br> Prince of Peace for all eternity oh, <br> His name shall be <br><br> REPEAT TURNAROUND <br> Verse 3 <br> He came to lift the weary ones <br> Give peace and perfect rest <br> To take away our burdens and <br> To give a glorious gift <br> So glory in the highest <br> And on the earth be peace <br> Glory to God the world will sing! <br><br> Chorus 2 <br> His name shall be called Wonderful, Counselor <br> Mighty God, Everlasting Father <br> Prince of Peace for all eternity oh, <br> His name shall be Wonderful, Counselor <br> Mighty God, Everlasting Father <br> Prince of Peace for all eternity oh, <br> His name shall be Bridge <br> One name above all others <br> One name that came to save us <br> Oh sing, His name is <br> His name is Jesus! <br><br> One name above all others <br> One name that came to save us <br> Oh sing, His name is <br> His name is Jesus! <br> Chorus <br> His name shall be called Wonderful, Counselor <br> Mighty God, Everlasting Father <br> Prince of Peace for all eternity oh, <br> His name shall be <br> His name shall be <br> His name shall be]]></content><category term="Matt Redman" label="Matt Redman"/><category term="His Name Shall Be" label="His Name Shall Be"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matt_Redman/These_Christmas_Lights/</id><title>Matt Redman - These Christmas Lights - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:44:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:44:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matt_Redman/These_Christmas_Lights/" title="Matt Redman - These Christmas Lights - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Verse 1 <br> All the lights are shining brightly <br> As the choir of angels sing <br> Singing praise now in the highest <br> At the birth of Christ the King <br> Yes all the lights are shining brightly <br> As the choir of angels sing <br> Singing praise now in the highest <br> At the birth of Christ the King <br><br> Chorus <br> Open my eyes, O heart believe <br> The wonder of that Christmas night <br> Be born in me <br> Verse 2 <br> Sing again the sacred song <br> Of how that star lit up the sky <br> And how this world lost in the darkness <br> Felt the hope of heaven’s light <br><br> REPEAT CHORUS <br> |2x| <br><br> Bridge <br> All the lights are shining brightly <br> At the glory of the King <br> All the lights are shining brightly <br> For the glory of Your name <br> Interlude <br><br> Verse 3 <br> We hold a flame in our hearts now <br> Say a prayer that in this world <br> All these lights, these Christmas lights <br> Will shine for You and You alone <br> REPEAT BRIDGE]]></content><category term="Matt Redman" label="Matt Redman"/><category term="These Christmas Lights" label="These Christmas Lights"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/채서윤/너너_Feat_OK명구/</id><title>채서윤 - 너너 (Feat. OK명구) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:46:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:46:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B1%84%EC%84%9C%EC%9C%A4/%EB%84%88%EB%84%88_Feat_OK%EB%AA%85%EA%B5%AC/" title="채서윤 - 너너 (Feat. OK명구) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너너 두고봐 <br>너너 두고봐 <br>그래 나 같은 남자는 잊어 <br>사랑 따윈 없었어 <br>그냥 한번 재미로 만난것 뿐야 <br>너도 좋았었자나 <br>OH MY GOD <br>사랑한다고 사랑따윈 몰라 <br>내 눈앞에서 그만 비켜줄래 <br>우리 사랑했던 날들 <br>모두 연극이였니 <br>내게 했던 모든 말들 <br>전부다 거짓이였니 <br>너 돌아가버려 <br>나를 모르던 지난날들로 <br>너 떠나가버려 <br>나를 모르던 지난날들로 <br>너너 두고봐 <br>너너 지켜봐 <br>너너 두고봐 <br>너너 지켜봐 <br>너너 두고봐 <br>우리 사랑했던 날들 <br>모두 연극이였니 <br>내게 했던 모든 말들 <br>전부다 거짓이였니 <br>너 돌아가버려 <br>나를 모르던 지난날들로 <br>너 떠나가버려 <br>나를 모르던 지난날들로 <br>너너 두고봐 <br>너너 지켜봐 <br>너너 두고봐 <br>너너 지켜봐 <br>너너 두고봐 <br>너너 지켜봐 <br>너너 두고봐 <br>너너 지켜봐 <br>너너 두고봐 <br>너너 지켜봐 <br>너너 두고봐 <br>너너 지켜봐 <br>너너 두고봐 <br>너너 지켜봐 <br>너너 두고봐 <br>너너 지켜봐 <br>]]></content><category term="채서윤" label="채서윤"/><category term="너너 (Feat. OK명구)" label="너너 (Feat. OK명구)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kensington/Fiji/</id><title>Kensington - Fiji - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:46:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:46:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kensington/Fiji/" title="Kensington - Fiji - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Whenever the day will break <br>Another mistake will take hold <br>Of every inch of an honest state <br>A hell of a case you'd make <br>If only the tides weren't so strong <br>You're letting it in all your darkest ways <br><br>Now how does it end <br><br>Not all we're building up is indestructible <br>But all we're hoping for <br>We'll know how to get it though <br>Not all we're building up is indestructible <br>But all we're hoping for <br>We'll know how <br><br>To get in a constant phase <br>Of digging a heart shaped grave for ourselves <br>Waste it all away <br>Inside of a king sized cage <br>Enough of the comforts of home <br>But none of it all takes the bars away <br><br>Now how does it end <br><br>Not all we're building up is indestructible <br>But all we're hoping for <br>We'll know how to get it though <br>Not all we're building up is indestructible <br>But all we're hoping for <br>We'll know how to get it <br><br>Hold on unless you want to go it alone <br>Hold on unless you want to go it alone <br>Hold on unless you want to go it alone <br>Hold on unless you want to go it alone <br>Hold on unless you want to go it alone <br><br>Not all we're building up is indestructible <br>But all we're hoping for <br>We'll know how to get it though <br>Not all we're building up is indestructible <br>But all we're hoping for <br>We'll know how to get it]]></content><category term="Kensington" label="Kensington"/><category term="Fiji" label="Fiji"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/장효경/여수어시장/</id><title>장효경 - 여수어시장 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:47:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:47:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%ED%9A%A8%EA%B2%BD/%EC%97%AC%EC%88%98%EC%96%B4%EC%8B%9C%EC%9E%A5/" title="장효경 - 여수어시장 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아직도 기억하고 있나요 <br>아직도 기억하고 있나요 <br>여수의 어시장을 <br>그 사람들 향기는 진하고 <br>난 그곳을 그리워하네 <br>꼭 전해 주세요 사랑 한다고 <br>여수에 갈 거예요 <br>지금도 모두 기억하고 있어요 <br>여수의 그 어시장을 <br>해풍으로 세월은 녹슬고 <br>내 어미의 손등은 주름지지만 <br>사랑하는 사람들의 <br>향기는 진해요 <br>때가 되면 나는 꼭 갈 거예요 <br>아직도 기억하고 있어요 <br>그 무덤에 바다 새 오나요 <br>새들에게 내 마음을 전해요 <br>그곳을 지금도 그리워 하죠 <br>난 기억하고 있어요 <br>여수의 조그만 섬을 <br>날개 접은 갈매기의 일생을 <br>그 섬은 나를 위해 비어있죠 <br>내 사랑의 내 마음 아시나요 <br>여수의 어시장에 가서 <br>갓김치와 동백꽃을 사겠어요 <br>동백꽃 향기가 퍼지겠죠 <br>아직도 기억하고 있어요 <br>영웅이 칼 차고 <br>왕래하던 그 시절을 <br>난 그곳을 그리워하죠 <br>아직도 기억하고 있나요 <br>아직도 기억하고 있나요 <br>아직도 기억하고 있나요 <br>]]></content><category term="장효경" label="장효경"/><category term="여수어시장" label="여수어시장"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lost_Weekend/Sleepyhead/</id><title>Lost Weekend - Sleepyhead - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:47:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:47:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lost_Weekend/Sleepyhead/" title="Lost Weekend - Sleepyhead - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[sleepyhead <br>i watch you sleeping <br>sleepy head <br>life's only good for dreaming <br><br>real life's too loud <br>people aren't worth meeting <br>days go too slow <br>time keeps on bleeding <br><br>real life is petty <br>people aren't too kind <br>he doesn't love you <br>it was all in your mind <br><br>sleepy head <br>there is no point in waking <br>sleepy head <br>life's only good for dreaming]]></content><category term="Lost Weekend" label="Lost Weekend"/><category term="Sleepyhead" label="Sleepyhead"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lost_Weekend/Ghosts/</id><title>Lost Weekend - Ghosts - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:47:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:47:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lost_Weekend/Ghosts/" title="Lost Weekend - Ghosts - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[feeling like I know the words <br>to a song I haven't wrote <br>like I know the sound <br>to a voice I haven't heard <br><br>another drink or two, my dear <br>i'd drink the whole menu <br>for you, if only for you <br>yeah, what I wouldn't do <br><br>and one day when you <br>realize the shit you <br>left me in I hope it churns inside your shameless gut <br><br>and when I make it <br>you'll grin and bear it <br>i'm sorry baby but this train don't wait for anyone <br><br>yeah, I want my vinyls back <br>what of my pride you might've kept <br>i won't wait by the phone <br>i've gotten good at being alone <br><br>won't be the fool who <br>writes songs about you <br>the abandoned heroine <br>the luckless harlequin <br>won't be expecting <br>a happy ending with you]]></content><category term="Lost Weekend" label="Lost Weekend"/><category term="Ghosts" label="Ghosts"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lost_Weekend/About_Forever/</id><title>Lost Weekend - About Forever - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:48:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:48:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lost_Weekend/About_Forever/" title="Lost Weekend - About Forever - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[i was young and you were free <br>etching wooden hearts in the tree <br>of our backyard where you fell <br><br>summer skin was salty sweet <br>musing over our destiny <br>of fame, fame and glory <br><br>we're just waiting for our time <br>always waiting to cross that line <br>and you know it's not about now <br>it's about forever <br><br>i was young and you were free <br>etching wooden hearts in the tree <br>of our backyard where you fell <br><br>i went slow but you were fast <br>i guess we knew these days would never last <br>till the early light of the morning <br><br>and when indie bands teach you about <br>love and responsibility <br>you better listen]]></content><category term="Lost Weekend" label="Lost Weekend"/><category term="About Forever" label="About Forever"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lost_Weekend/Red_Is_The_Colour/</id><title>Lost Weekend - Red Is The Colour - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T12:48:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T12:48:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lost_Weekend/Red_Is_The_Colour/" title="Lost Weekend - Red Is The Colour - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[bloodberry kisses on my skin <br>some pigment on my lips <br>crawling through glass on my knees <br>your belt around my hips <br>on and on, on and on <br>a violent song <br>on and on, on and on <br>red is the color of marital bliss <br><br>i will never get out alive <br>your love to me's a slow suicide <br>i will never get out alive <br>i don't wanna live i don't wanna die <br><br>blackberry bruises growing wild <br>the fruits i've learnt to pick <br>my broken body is your child <br>just take him away from me <br>and i never listened when mother said <br>that red is the color of marital bliss]]></content><category term="Lost Weekend" label="Lost Weekend"/><category term="Red Is The Colour" label="Red Is The Colour"/></entry></feed>