<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:29:13+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태연_TAEYEON/11_11/</id><title>태연_TAEYEON - 11:11 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:57:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:57:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%B0_TAEYEON/11_11/" title="태연_TAEYEON - 11:11 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It’s 11:11 <br>오늘이 한 칸이 채 <br>안 남은 그런 시간 <br>우리 소원을 빌며 웃던 그 시간 <br>별 게 다 널 떠오르게 하지 <br>네 맘 끝자락처럼 차가운 바람 <br>창을 열면 온통 네가 불어와 <br>이 시간이 전부 지나고 나면 <br>이별이 끝나 있을까 Yeah <br>널 다 잊었을까 <br>모든 게 자릴 찾아서 떠나가고 <br>넌 내 모든 걸 갖고서 떠나도 <br>내 맘은 시계 속의 두 바늘처럼 <br>같은 곳을 두고 맴돌기만 해 <br>Na na na na na na na <br>na na na na na na oh <br>Na na na na na na na na <br>I believe I will be over you <br>달력 안에 있는 <br>오래 전에 약속했던 몇 월의 며칠 <br>너에겐 다 잊혀져 있었다면 <br>내가 지워야지 뭐 <br>지나고 나면 별 거 아니겠지 뭐 <br>모든 게 자릴 찾아서 떠나가고 <br>넌 내 모든 걸 갖고서 떠나도 <br>내 맘은 시계 속의 두 바늘처럼 <br>같은 곳을 두고 맴돌기만 해 <br>Na na na na na na na <br>na na na na na na oh <br>Na na na na na na na na <br>I believe I will be over you <br>계절 틈에 잠시 피는 낯선 꽃처럼 <br>하루 틈에 걸려 있는 새벽 별처럼 <br>이 모든 건 언젠가는 <br>다 지나가고 말겠지 <br>모든 게 자릴 찾아서 돌아오고 <br>내가 아무 일 없는 듯이 웃게 되면 <br>너의 이름 한 번쯤 부르는 게 <br>지금처럼 아프지 않을 거야 <br>Na na na na na na na <br>na na na na na na oh <br>Na na na na na na na na <br>I believe I will be over you <br>Na na na na na na na <br>na na na na na na oh <br>Na na na na na na na na <br>I believe I will be over you <br>]]></content><category term="태연 (TAEYEON)" label="태연 (TAEYEON)"/><category term="11:11" label="11:11"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태연_TAEYEON/Lonely_Night/</id><title>태연_TAEYEON - Lonely Night - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:57:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:57:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%B0_TAEYEON/Lonely_Night/" title="태연_TAEYEON - Lonely Night - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이젠 익숙해질만 한데 <br>밤은 너무 길어 잠은 오지도 않네 Yeh <br>넌 지금 뭐 해 두어번 혹은 더 <br>전화기를 만지작대 <br>절대 그럴 나 아닌데 <br>낯선 곳을 가 <br>너의 흔적이 없는 세계를 만들래 <br>낯선 거리 사람들 그래 괜찮아 <br>바쁘게 지내다 또 네가 보여 <br>나를 뒤흔들 때마다 <br>Some things never change <br>잘 알아 너는 없단 걸 <br>추억 따윈 버리자 다 Yeh <br>환상일 뿐 였잖아 <br>Boy 끝났어 널 미워해 <br>I don't know your name <br>이 말 몇 번이나 되뇌야 하는지 <br>여지없이 새 아침이 와도 <br>깨어지지 않아 슬픈 꿈속을 헤매 Yeh <br>So why do I 변하지 못해 <br>자꾸 뒤돌아 보게 돼 <br>우리 둘이던 night and day <br>어딜 걸어도 너의 기억은 <br>갑자기 내 앞을 막아 <br>무심한 듯 지나쳐 제법 견뎌내 <br>나쁘지 않잖아 <br>어차피 네가 그리운 건 사실인데 <br>그것조차 아는 듯 나를 따라와 <br>추억 따윈 버리자 다 Yeh <br>환상일 뿐 였잖아 <br>Boy 끝났어 널 미워해 <br>I don't know your name <br>이 말 몇 번이나 되뇌야 하는지 <br>널 생각하는 밤이 줄어 가 <br>Enough is enough 더 울진 않아 <br>So let me redeem redeem redeem <br>전부 다 tonight <br>그래 널 다신 생각도 않게 <br>지워버려 Lonely Night 다 Yeh <br>난 괜찮을 거잖아 <br>널 이제야 잘 알듯 해 <br>더 외롭게 해 <br>추억 따윈 버리자 다 Yeh <br>환상일 뿐 였잖아 <br>Boy 끝났어 널 미워해 <br>I don't know your name <br>이 말 몇 번이나 되뇌야 하는지 <br>I’m sick of lonely nights <br>I’m sick of lonely nights <br>]]></content><category term="태연 (TAEYEON)" label="태연 (TAEYEON)"/><category term="Lonely Night" label="Lonely Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태연_TAEYEON/I_Blame_On_You/</id><title>태연_TAEYEON - I Blame On You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:57:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:57:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%B0_TAEYEON/I_Blame_On_You/" title="태연_TAEYEON - I Blame On You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 바람이 부르는 기억에 <br>먼지 쌓인 태엽을 돌리면 <br>선명해지는 지난 날의 너와 내가 <br>이 계절 속에 향기로 날 파고들어 <br>I Blame On You <br>닿을 수 없는 시간을 지나서 <br>I Blame On You <br>흩어지는 그날의 조각들 <br>그리움 닮은 파도 따라 <br>울컥해진 계절 안에서 <br>I Blame On You <br>닿을 수 없는 너에게 난 <br>따스하게 햇살이 비추면 <br>저 꽃처럼 내게로 피어나고 <br>몇 번의 밤을 더 보내면 잊게 될까 <br>매일 같은 기억 속을 <br>자꾸 맴도는 난 So <br>I Blame On You <br>닿을 수 없는 시간을 지나서 <br>I Blame On You <br>흩어지는 그날의 조각들 <br>그리움 닮은 파도 따라 <br>울컥해진 계절 안에서 <br>I Blame On You <br>닿을 수 없는 너에게 난 <br>떨리는 입술로 숨겨왔던 <br>내 비밀은 아직도 <br>Feel like I’m alone <br>I Blame On You <br>내 기도가 너에게 닿을까 <br>I Blame On You <br>언제쯤 널 무던히 말할까 <br>한참을 벗어날 수 없는 <br>너의 그림자에 갇힌 난 <br>I Blame On You <br>흔들리는 날 잡아줘 <br>너에게로 <br>]]></content><category term="태연 (TAEYEON)" label="태연 (TAEYEON)"/><category term="I Blame On You" label="I Blame On You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태연_TAEYEON/When_I_Was_Young/</id><title>태연_TAEYEON - When I Was Young - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:57:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:57:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%B0_TAEYEON/When_I_Was_Young/" title="태연_TAEYEON - When I Was Young - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wo Babe Ooh <br>이제 어쩌죠 난 안돼요 <br>아무리 불러도 돌아오질 않아 <br>혹시 그때 진작 우리 멈췄더라면 <br>더 좋았을지도 몰라 기억하나요 <br>When I When I was young 그때 <br>내가 그대고 그대가 나일 때 <br>When I When I was a fool 정말 <br>아무도 모르고 그대만 알 때 <br>어땠나요 괜찮았나요 <br>믿기지 않죠 마지막이래 <br>우리 나눈 말들 지워지지 않아 <br>혹시 그때 서로 많이 알았더라면 <br>더 좋았을지도 몰라 <br>When I When I was young 그때 <br>내가 그대고 그대가 나일 때 <br>When I When I was a fool 정말 <br>아무도 모르고 그대만 알 때 <br>어땠나요 기억하나요 <br>많이 어렸었잖아요 <br>우리 서툴렀잖아요 <br>아직 어제 일만 같아 Ooh <br>많이 힘들었나요 내가 그대고 <br>그대도 나일 때 우리 하나일 때 Ooh <br>When I When I was young 그때 <br>내가 그댈 그대가 날 Ooh <br>When I When I was a fool 정말 <br>그대만 바랬던 그런 나였을 때 <br>어땠나요 기억해줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="태연 (TAEYEON)" label="태연 (TAEYEON)"/><category term="When I Was Young" label="When I Was Young"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태연_TAEYEON/Sweet_Love/</id><title>태연_TAEYEON - Sweet Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:57:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:57:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%B0_TAEYEON/Sweet_Love/" title="태연_TAEYEON - Sweet Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh Oh boy you know it <br>I know you wanna fall in love with me <br>Crying for love <br>흘린 눈물만큼 <br>깊어질 수 있다면 우린 <br>푸른 바닷속을 헤매어 <br>서로의 불빛이 돼 주며 <br>따스히 안은 채 떠다니겠지 <br>I'm in love <br>I'll take you high <br>take you higher <br>So we can fly <br>so we can flyer <br>너 없이 혼자 지낸 날들 <br>기억조차 나지 않는데 Babe <br>Higher 간절히 서로가 서롤 당겼지 <br>사랑이란 게 뭔지 매일 난 배워가 <br>이 달콤함에 취했어 Give me your <br>Sweet Sweet Love <br>Lovin so Sweet Sweet Love <br>밤에 잠들 때마다 네가 필요해 <br>혼자 있는 날의 시간은 더딘데 <br>그래 내게 온 변화를 거부 안 해 <br>Mmm yea I know it <br>네 품에 안길 때마다 <br>네 숨소리 내게 감겨올 때마다 <br>I'm in love <br>Baby I'll take you high <br>take you higher <br>So we can fly <br>so we can flyer <br>너 없이 혼자 지낸 날들 <br>기억조차 나지 않는데 Babe <br>Higher 간절히 서로가 서롤 당겼지 <br>사랑이란 게 뭔지 매일 난 배워가 <br>이 달콤함에 취했어 Give me your <br>I I realize I need your love <br>긴 날 동안 Yes I do <br>I'll take you high <br>take you higher <br>So we can fly <br>so we can flyer <br>너 없이 혼자 지낸 날들 <br>기억조차 나지 않는데 Babe <br>Higher 간절히 서로가 서롤 당겼지 <br>사랑이란 게 뭔지 매일 난 배워가 <br>이 달콤함에 취했어 Give me your <br>Sweet Sweet Love <br>Lovin so Sweet Sweet Love <br>]]></content><category term="태연 (TAEYEON)" label="태연 (TAEYEON)"/><category term="Sweet Love" label="Sweet Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태연_TAEYEON/Time_Lapse/</id><title>태연_TAEYEON - Time Lapse - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:57:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:57:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%B0_TAEYEON/Time_Lapse/" title="태연_TAEYEON - Time Lapse - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여전히 그대로죠 <br>생일은 몇 번씩이나 지났고 <br>분명 나 역시 조금 더 <br>어른이 돼 있는 것 같은데 <br>아직도 너의 그 <br>이름을 떠올리면 <br>눈물이 맺히고 <br>잠시만 눈을 감으면 <br>니 모습이 보이고 <br>모든 게 변해가도 <br>너만은 항상 같은 자리에서 <br>똑같은 모습으로 계속 날 울려 <br>여전히 그대로죠 <br>계절은 몇 번씩이나 변했고 <br>이젠 너 없는 일상에 <br>조금은 익숙해질 법도 한데 <br>아직도 너의 그 <br>이름을 떠올리면 <br>눈물이 맺히고 <br>잠시만 눈을 감으면 <br>니 모습이 보이고 <br>모든 게 변해가도 <br>너만은 항상 같은 자리에서 <br>똑같은 모습으로 계속 날 울려 <br>계속 날 울려 <br>그래 이별이란 게 <br>다 그런 거지 뭐 <br>함께여서 행복했던 기억 <br>모두 지워 가는 것 <br>하지만 잊으려 하면 <br>눈물이 맺히고 <br>맺혀진 그 눈물 위로 <br>다시 니가 흐르고 <br>시간은 멈춰지고 <br>애써 숨겨왔던 나의 마음이 <br>조용히 고갤 들고 <br>애타는 목소리로 다시 널 불러 <br>그래 사랑이란 게 <br>다 그런 거지 뭐 <br>항상 시작과 끝은 <br>달라도 너무 다르고 <br>그래 이별이란 게 <br>늘 항상 그렇지 뭐 <br>더 깊이 사랑한 <br>마음을 찾아와 울려 <br>그래 이별이란 게 계속 날 울려 <br>]]></content><category term="태연 (TAEYEON)" label="태연 (TAEYEON)"/><category term="Time Lapse" label="Time Lapse"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태연_TAEYEON/Im_OK/</id><title>태연_TAEYEON - I`m OK - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:57:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:57:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%B0_TAEYEON/Im_OK/" title="태연_TAEYEON - I`m OK - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무렇지 않은 척해도 다 모른 척해도 <br>매일같이 나를 깨우던 너라는 악몽 <br>차가운 시선과 싫증 난 표정 <br>돌려보낼게 나도 지겨워 <br>하나 둘씩 모두 버릴게 <br>아무리 널 믿어보려고 노력해 봐도 <br>이리저리 내 눈을 피해 <br>네 입술은 또 또 <br>다 잊을게 잊어버릴래 <br>더는 관심도 흥미도 없어 <br>모두 깨끗이 남김없이 널 <br>영원히 함께라고 믿었던 한때도 Oh <br>저기 바람결에 날려 멀리 날려봐 <br>괜찮아 이젠 나도 <br>나만의 길을 찾아 Oh <br>내 꿈을 따라 갈래 <br>I'm OK O-K <br>무심한 척 떠보듯이 또 연락을 하고 <br>괜시리 날 신경 쓰는 척 눈길을 주지 <br>이 애매한 미지근한 Something <br>밀고 당기는 사이는 난 싫어 <br>No thanks baby <br>영원히 함께라고 믿었던 한때도 Oh <br>저기 바람결에 날려 멀리 날려봐 <br>괜찮아 이젠 나도 <br>나만의 길을 찾아 Oh <br>내 꿈을 따라 갈래 <br>I'm OK O-K <br>시간이 흘러가면 널 가끔 떠올려도 Oh <br>웃음 섞인 미소를 짓고 태연하겠지 <br>아픔도 눈물도 이젠 다 끝났어 Oh <br>너 없이 난 오늘부터 <br>너 없이도 난 OK <br>Right Alright Alright <br>Right Alright Alright <br>Right Alright Alright <br>Oh <br>Right Alright Alright <br>Right Alright Alright <br>Right Alright Alright <br>I'm OK <br>]]></content><category term="태연 (TAEYEON)" label="태연 (TAEYEON)"/><category term="I`m OK" label="I`m OK"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태연_TAEYEON/I_Got_Love/</id><title>태연_TAEYEON - I Got Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:57:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:57:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%B0_TAEYEON/I_Got_Love/" title="태연_TAEYEON - I Got Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[유희는 쉬워 <br>이 밤을 보낼 그 흔한 방법 <br>그러기엔 우린 좀 달라 분명 <br>그러자 밤의 마법이 <br>욕망이 달이 속삭여 <br>괜찮아 허니 <br>어둠이 깊어 비밀을 덮어줄 테니 <br>이끄는 대로 가 보고 싶은데 <br>자 말해봐 <br>want you baby <br>want you baby <br>우주 같은 <br>네 안으로 <br>need you closer <br>need you closer <br>빠져들면 <br>달뜬 한숨도 나부낀 나도 <br>취한 듯 꿈을 헤매 <br>너를 헤매 믿어지니 <br>긴밀히 쌓인 <br>너와 나 서로를 탐하던 단어 <br>열기 가린 가면 벗어던져 <br>끊어질 듯한 긴장은 <br>의심은 사라졌으니 <br>예 어서 와 허니 <br>눈 앞의 존재 <br>넌 살아 움직이는데 <br>오감에 취해 널 더 알고 싶어 <br>자 말해봐 <br>want you baby <br>want you baby <br>우주 같은 <br>네 안으로 <br>need you closer <br>need you closer <br>빠져들면 <br>달뜬 한숨도 나부낀 나도 <br>취한 듯 꿈을 헤매 <br>너를 헤매 믿어지니 <br>전부 무너지게 <br>다 녹아 버리게 <br>터무니 없이 미치게 해 <br>Come and turn me on <br>You don’t stop that fire <br>‘cause I got love <br>I got love I got love <br>자 말해봐 <br>want you baby <br>want you baby <br>우주 같은 <br>네 안으로 <br>need you closer <br>need you closer <br>빠져들면 <br>달뜬 한숨도 나부낀 나도 <br>취한 듯 꿈을 헤매 <br>너를 헤매 믿어지니 <br>꿈인 듯해 너를 헤매 <br>난 너만 원해 믿어지니 <br>]]></content><category term="태연 (TAEYEON)" label="태연 (TAEYEON)"/><category term="I Got Love" label="I Got Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태연_TAEYEON/날개_Feel_So_Fine/</id><title>태연_TAEYEON - 날개 (Feel So Fine) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:57:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:57:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%B0_TAEYEON/%EB%82%A0%EA%B0%9C_Feel_So_Fine/" title="태연_TAEYEON - 날개 (Feel So Fine) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어둠 속에 파고든 <br>내 안에 날 가두던 <br>시간은 이미 지나고 <br>It fades away <br>하염없이 떠돌다 <br>낯선 벽에 부딪혀 버린 <br>Oh 이제 난 어디로 <br>Please hold my hand <br>하나둘씩 열어 <br>감춰왔던 나를 깨워 <br>잊으려 했던 결국엔 늘 <br>잊을 수 없었던 꿈들 <br>한 번도 제대로 <br>날지 못한 내 두 날개 <br>새롭게 펼쳐봐 또 날아봐 이제 <br>그려만 왔던 지금 내 모습 <br>아직 난 믿기지 않아 <br>쏟아지는 햇살 스치는 바람 <br>Just realize I feel so fine <br>Oh oh 나의 날개 위 <br>Oh oh 찬란히 새긴 <br>I know you know <br>매일 꿈꾸던 World <br>I feel so fine <br>Oh oh 하늘 끝까지 <br>Oh oh 가득 펼쳐진 <br>I know you know <br>환히 빛나는 World <br>I feel so fine <br>말없이 앉아 방황했던 <br>길에서 마주했던 밤도 <br>전부 괜찮아 이젠 모두 다 <br>I don’t care <br>혼자라는 편안함 속 <br>피어오른 외로움도 <br>이제는 다 <br>I can let it go baby <br>지구 반대편 어딘가 <br>내게 외쳐온 메아리 Oh <br>네 눈앞에 펼쳐질 <br>저 벽 너머의 세상을 찾아 <br>둘러싼 현실 그보다 <br>먼저 넘어설 나란 벽 Oh <br>계속해서 지켜가 <br>내 자신이 할 수 있다 믿어 <br>그려만 왔던 지금 내 모습 <br>아직 난 믿기지 않아 <br>쏟아지는 햇살 스치는 바람 <br>Just realize I feel so fine <br>Oh oh 나의 날개 위 <br>Oh oh 찬란히 새긴 <br>I know you know <br>매일 꿈꾸던 World <br>I feel so fine <br>Oh oh 하늘 끝까지 <br>Oh oh 가득 펼쳐진 <br>I know you know <br>환히 빛나는 World <br>I feel so fine <br>Oh yeah I feel so fine <br>Oh yeah I feel so fine <br>Oh yeah Ooh oh yeah <br>Oh yeah Oh <br>내 안의 나를 넘어선 순간 <br>새로운 세상이 보여 <br>쏟아지는 햇살 스치는 바람 <br>Just realize I feel so fine <br>Oh oh 나의 날개 위 <br>Oh oh 찬란히 새긴 <br>I know you know <br>매일 꿈꾸던 World <br>I feel so fine <br>Oh oh 하늘 끝까지 <br>Oh oh 가득 펼쳐진 <br>I know you know <br>환히 빛나는 World <br>I feel so fine <br>]]></content><category term="태연 (TAEYEON)" label="태연 (TAEYEON)"/><category term="날개 (Feel So Fine)" label="날개 (Feel So Fine)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태연_TAEYEON/Cover_Up/</id><title>태연_TAEYEON - Cover Up - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:57:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:57:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%B0_TAEYEON/Cover_Up/" title="태연_TAEYEON - Cover Up - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘도 별처럼 네 마음을 따라 <br>또 너의 곁을 맴돌지 <br>Stop 난 어지러워 선명한 네 맘을 <br>이젠 알고 싶어져 <br>밤하늘에도 거리에도 <br>전부 너의 모습이 가득한 걸 <br>좀 더 시간이 필요하다면 <br>또 널 기다리겠지만 <br>Boy I can't cover up my heart <br>널 보면 난 웃음이 새어 나와 <br>아무도 몰래 내게 스며들어 <br>조금씩 커져 가는 맘 <br>Boy I can't cover up <br>Can't cover it up <br>can't can't cover it up no <br>Can't cover it up <br>no I just can't cover it up <br>come on <br>Can't cover it up <br>can't can't cover it up no <br>커져 가는 맘 <br>Boy I can't cover up <br>난 조심스럽게 네 색깔을 입고 <br>또 네 옆에 자릴 잡지 <br>내 맘과 같은지 얼마만큼 인지 <br>말을 해줘 Yes or no <br>밤하늘에도 거리에도 <br>전부 너의 모습이 가득한 걸 <br>좀 더 시간이 필요하다면 <br>또 널 기다리겠지만 <br>Boy I can't cover up my heart <br>널 보면 난 웃음이 새어 나와 <br>아무도 몰래 내게 스며들어 <br>조금씩 커져 가는 맘 <br>Boy I can't cover up <br>Yeah in my heart <br>언젠가 나의 곁에 와 줄 너와 <br>달콤한 꿈을 꾸는 상상을 해 <br>I want you <br>커져 가는 맘 <br>Boy I can't cover up <br>I said it I said it <br>I love you love you <br>I mean it I mean it <br>I love you love you <br>말하는 이 순간 <br>후회한대도 <br>너를 향한 진심인 걸 <br>Boy I can't cover up my heart <br>널 보면 난 웃음이 새어 나와 <br>아무도 몰래 내게 스며들어 <br>조금씩 커져 가는 맘 <br>Boy I can't cover up <br>Yeah in my heart <br>언젠가 나의 곁에 와 줄 너와 <br>달콤한 꿈을 꾸는 상상을 해 <br>I want you <br>커져 가는 맘 <br>Boy I can't cover up <br>Can't cover it up <br>can't cover it up no <br>I love you love you <br>Can't cover it up <br>can't cover it up no more <br>I love you love you <br>Can't cover it up <br>can't cover it up <br>커져 가는 맘 <br>Boy I can't cover up <br>]]></content><category term="태연 (TAEYEON)" label="태연 (TAEYEON)"/><category term="Cover Up" label="Cover Up"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태연_TAEYEON/Fine/</id><title>태연_TAEYEON - Fine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:58:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:58:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%B0_TAEYEON/Fine/" title="태연_TAEYEON - Fine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[찢어진 종잇조각에 <br>담아낸 나의 진심에 <br>선명해져 <br>somethin' bout you <br>Yeah 나를 많이 닮은 듯 다른 <br>넌 혹시 나와 같을까 지금 <br>괜한 기대를 해 <br>하루 한 달 일 년쯤 되면 <br>서로 다른 일상을 살아가 <br>나는 아니야 <br>쉽지 않을 것 같아 <br>여전하게도 넌 내 하루하루를 채우고 <br>아직은 아니야 <br>바보처럼 되뇌는 나 <br>입가에 맴도는 말을 삼킬 수 없어 <br>It's not fine <br>Ah Ah Ah Ah It's not fine <br>머릴 질끈 묶은 채 <br>어지러운 방을 정리해 <br>찾고 있어 somethin' new <br>가끔 이렇게 감당할 수 없는 <br>뭐라도 해야 할 것만 같은 기분에 <br>괜히 움직이곤 해 <br>하루 한 달 일 년 그쯤이면 <br>웃으며 추억할 거라 했지만 <br>나는 아니야 <br>쉽지 않을 것 같아 <br>여전하게도 넌 내 하루하루를 채우고 <br>아직은 아니야 <br>바보처럼 되뇌는 나 <br>입가에 맴도는 말을 삼킬 수 없어 <br>It's not fine <br>Ah Ah Ah Ah It's not fine <br>의미 없는 농담 주고받는 대화 <br>사람들 틈에 난 아무렇지 않아 보여 <br>무딘 척 웃음을 지어 보이며 <br>너란 그늘을 애써 외면해보지만 <br>우리 마지막 <br>그 순간이 자꾸 떠올라 <br>잘 지내란 말이 전부였던 담담한 이별 <br>아직은 아니야 <br>바보처럼 되뇌는 그 말 <br>입가에 맴도는 말을 삼킬 수 없어 <br>It's not fine <br>Ah Ah Ah It's not fine Oh <br>Ah Ah Ah It's not fine <br>]]></content><category term="태연 (TAEYEON)" label="태연 (TAEYEON)"/><category term="Fine" label="Fine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태연_TAEYEON/Make_Me_Love_You/</id><title>태연_TAEYEON - Make Me Love You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:58:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:58:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%B0_TAEYEON/Make_Me_Love_You/" title="태연_TAEYEON - Make Me Love You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Make me love you <br>Make me love you <br>어둠 속에 내린 빛 그림자 <br>더 외로워한 시간들 속의 난 <br>조심스레 내민 눈 앞의 손 <br>잡지 못하고 망설여 왔지만 <br>이미 떨린 맘이 자꾸 겁이 나 <br>비밀스레 네가 손을 내민 밤 <br>Make me kiss you <br>Ma make me kiss you <br>Make me touch you <br>Ma make me touch you <br>Make me want you <br>Ma make me want you <br>K kiss you t touch you <br>w want you <br>Make me love you <br>Make me love you <br>매일 다른 세계를 넘나들어 <br>난 나비였고 유혹에 이끌려 <br>어느새 달콤한 향기 가득히 <br>푹 빠져 버린 내 모습 어떤지 <br>멀리 좀더 멀리 하늘 높이 난 <br>저기 하얀 별이 되어 날아 가 <br>Make me kiss you <br>Ma make me kiss you <br>Make me touch you <br>Ma make me touch you <br>Make me want you <br>Ma make me want you <br>K kiss you t touch you <br>w want you <br>Make me love you <br>Make me love you <br>Make me love you <br>Make me love you <br>태어나 처음 마주 본 <br>너무 따스한 그 눈빛 <br>깊이 나를 담아 줘 <br>너란 우주 안에서 <br>모두 눈을 감을 거야 <br>멀리 나를 데려 가 <br>And make me love you <br>Make me kiss you <br>Ma make me kiss you <br>Make me touch you <br>Ma make me touch you <br>Make me want you <br>Ma make me want you <br>K kiss you t touch you <br>w want you <br>Make me love you <br>Make me love you <br>Make me love you <br>Make me love you <br>Make me love you <br>]]></content><category term="태연 (TAEYEON)" label="태연 (TAEYEON)"/><category term="Make Me Love You" label="Make Me Love You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍대광/별이_된다는_것은/</id><title>홍대광 - 별이 된다는 것은 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:58:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:58:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EB%8C%80%EA%B4%91/%EB%B3%84%EC%9D%B4_%EB%90%9C%EB%8B%A4%EB%8A%94_%EA%B2%83%EC%9D%80/" title="홍대광 - 별이 된다는 것은 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밤 하늘을 바라보면서 <br>작게 비추는 별빛들 소리에 <br>나도 모르게 자꾸 웃음 짓게 돼 <br>천천히 길을 걸으며 <br>너와 나누던 다정한 얘기에 <br>나도 모르게 잠시 눈을 감게 돼 <br>밤 하늘 아무도 없는 곳에 <br>혼자 밝게 비추는 별빛 <br>이젠 눈물이 나는 일 <br>누군가 기다리지 않아도 <br>가끔 외로움에 떨어도 <br>항상 늘 같은 자리에 있어 <br>별이 된다는 것은 <br>덩그러니 외로워지면 <br>내 모습처럼 작아져 보이는 <br>저 별들에게 마음을 터놓게 돼 <br>온종일 길을 걸으면 <br>문득 생각에 널 찾아 보려다 <br>나도 모르게 눈물이 흐르곤 해 <br>밤 하늘 아무도 없는 곳에 <br>혼자 밝게 비추는 별빛 <br>이젠 눈물이 나는 일 <br>누군가 기다리지 않아도 <br>가끔 외로움에 떨어도 <br>항상 늘 같은 자리에 있어 <br>별이 된다는 것은 <br>]]></content><category term="홍대광" label="홍대광"/><category term="별이 된다는 것은" label="별이 된다는 것은"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍대광/넌_나에게_제일_소중해/</id><title>홍대광 - 넌 나에게 제일 소중해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:58:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:58:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EB%8C%80%EA%B4%91/%EB%84%8C_%EB%82%98%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%BC_%EC%86%8C%EC%A4%91%ED%95%B4/" title="홍대광 - 넌 나에게 제일 소중해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 옆에 기대 잠이 든 네게 <br>해주고 싶은 말이 있어 <br>걱정 말고 지금처럼 <br>편히 잠들면 돼 <br>저 달은 밤을 지나서 가고 <br>지친 너의 손을 잡고 <br>괜찮아져 너의 옆엔 <br>내가 있으니까 <br>넌 나에게 제일 소중해 <br>넌 나에게 제일 소중해 <br>걱정되고 힘이 들어도 <br>괜찮아 괜찮아 <br>넌 나에게 제일 소중해 <br>혼자 견디기 힘이 들 때면 <br>날 바라봐 내 품에 안겨봐 <br>잠들어 있는 너의 얼굴에 <br>말없이 눈물이 흐르면 <br>내 마음도 널 닮아서 <br>같이 울게 됐어 <br>수없이 많은 날이 지나서 <br>서로가 달라진다 해도 <br>지금처럼 너의 옆엔 <br>내가 있으니까 <br>넌 나에게 제일 소중해 <br>넌 나에게 제일 소중해 <br>걱정되고 힘이 들어도 <br>괜찮아 괜찮아 <br>넌 나에게 제일 소중해 <br>혼자 견디기 힘이 들 때면 <br>날 바라봐 내 품에 안겨봐 <br>]]></content><category term="홍대광" label="홍대광"/><category term="넌 나에게 제일 소중해" label="넌 나에게 제일 소중해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍대광/봄의_기적/</id><title>홍대광 - 봄의 기적 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:58:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:58:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EB%8C%80%EA%B4%91/%EB%B4%84%EC%9D%98_%EA%B8%B0%EC%A0%81/" title="홍대광 - 봄의 기적 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기나긴 겨울 고독했던 추위 <br>다신 오지 않을 것 같았던 <br>봄날의 기적이 <br>따스한 햇살 조금씩 비춰 오면 <br>그늘에 얼어 있던 맘은 <br>눈처럼 녹아져 <br>하늘을 봐 유난히 더 밝아 보여 <br>저 바람은 다시 일어날 수 있게 <br>날 도와줘 <br>저기 높이 나는 작은 새들과 같이 <br>작은 날갯짓으로 아주 멀리 날아가 <br>저기 피어나는 봄의 나무와 같이 <br>일어날 수 있게 이겨낼 수 있게 <br>다시 걸어갈게 너와 <br>We're never stop the way <br>어쩌면 다른 길이 될 수 있었지 <br>내게는 처음과도 같았던 <br>봄날의 기적이 <br>따스한 햇살 조금씩 비춰오면 <br>그늘에 어두웠던 마음은 <br>눈처럼 밝아져 <br>하늘을 봐 유난히 더 밝아 보여 <br>저 바람은 다시 일어날 수 있게 <br>날 도와줘 <br>저기 높이 나는 작은 새들과 같이 <br>작은 날갯짓으로 아주 멀리 날아가 <br>저기 피어 나는 봄의 나무와 같이 <br>일어날 수 있게 <br>이겨낼 수 있게 <br>다시 걸어갈게 너와 <br>We're never stop the way <br>작은 날갯짓으로 아주 멀리 날아가 <br>저기 피어 나는 봄의 나무와 같이 <br>일어날 수 있게 <br>이겨낼 수 있게 <br>다시 걸어갈게 너와 <br>We're never stop the way <br>]]></content><category term="홍대광" label="홍대광"/><category term="봄의 기적" label="봄의 기적"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍대광/떠나자/</id><title>홍대광 - 떠나자 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:58:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:58:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EB%8C%80%EA%B4%91/%EB%96%A0%EB%82%98%EC%9E%90/" title="홍대광 - 떠나자 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 하루 어제보다 <br>조금 더 밝아 보여 <br>투명하게 내려오는 <br>파란 햇살과 공기 <br>잠시 눈을 감으면 날아가고 있어 <br>이 모든 것을 잊어둔 채 <br>아무래도 이런 날엔 <br>가만있을 순 없어 <br>어디로든 마음대로 <br>떠나야 할 것 같아 <br>가슴 두근거리는 발자욱을 따라 <br>다시 태어날 것만 같아 <br>So we can fly away <br>you can't stop way <br>두 눈을 질끈 감고 자 뛰어올라봐 <br>괜찮아 fly away to tell me <br>hold your hand <br>지금이 아니라면 다시 오지 않아 <br>그냥 해보는 거야 <br>오래 전에 숨어있던 <br>내 마음속 지도 하나 <br>어디로든 마음대로 <br>살아보고 싶었지 <br>돌아갈 수 있다면 떠날 수 있다면 <br>새로운 날 찾을 것 같아 <br>So we can fly away <br>you can't stop way <br>두 눈을 질끈 감고 자 뛰어올라봐 <br>괜찮아 fly away to tell me <br>hold your hand <br>지금이 아니라면 다시 오지 않아 <br>그냥 해보는 거야 <br>너와 함께라면 어디라도 난 <br>fly away <br>저 하늘 속에 안길 수 있다면 <br>So we can fly away <br>you can't stop way <br>불안한 걱정들도 다 시작이니까 <br>괜찮아 fly away to tell me <br>hold your hand <br>지금이 아니라면 다시 오지 않아 <br>So we can fly away <br>you can't stop way <br>불안한 걱정들도 다 시작이니까 <br>괜찮아 fly away to tell me <br>hold your hand <br>지금이 아니라면 다시 오지 않아 <br>그냥 떠나는 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="홍대광" label="홍대광"/><category term="떠나자" label="떠나자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍대광/이_노래가_끝나면/</id><title>홍대광 - 이 노래가 끝나면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:58:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:58:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EB%8C%80%EA%B4%91/%EC%9D%B4_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98%EA%B0%80_%EB%81%9D%EB%82%98%EB%A9%B4/" title="홍대광 - 이 노래가 끝나면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[친구잖아 우린 <br>오늘도 난 거짓말을 해 <br>말 대신 써 내린 이 노래로 <br>내 맘을 네게 전하려 해 <br>네가 있어 좋아 <br>술에 취해 내게 했던 말 <br>어쩌면 같은 맘일지 몰라 <br>뜬눈으로 고민했던 밤 <br>있잖아 가볍게 툭 <br>던진 너의 농담조차도 <br>나에겐 너라서 맘이 커지게 돼 <br>온종일 너로 물들게 해 <br>어쩜 이 노래 끝날 때쯤 너와나 <br>서로 어색해질지 몰라 겁이나 <br>사랑한단 얘기보다 <br>너무 달지 않게 말할게 <br>이 노래가 끝나면 <br>어떻게 생각해 <br>기억나니 그날 <br>날 찾아와 많이 울던 밤 <br>혹시나 내 맘이 들킬까 봐 <br>널 안아 주지도 못했어 <br>사실 네가 좋아 <br>삼키기엔 너무 컸던 말 <br>언제나 옆에 서있던 내가 <br>이제 널 마주 보고 싶어 <br>괜찮아 말하는 듯 <br>웃어주는 너의 눈빛이 <br>얼었던 내 맘을 녹여 햇살처럼 <br>조금씩 다가설 수 있게 <br>어쩜 이 노래 끝날 때쯤 너와나 <br>서로 어색해질지 몰라 겁이나 <br>사랑한단 얘기보다 <br>너무 달지 않게 말할게 <br>이 노래가 끝나면 <br>어떻게 생각해 <br>사랑한단 말이 내겐 <br>아직 어색하긴 하지만 <br>이 노래가 끝나면 <br>한걸음 더 갈게 <br>]]></content><category term="홍대광" label="홍대광"/><category term="이 노래가 끝나면" label="이 노래가 끝나면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍대광/비처럼_fall_in_love/</id><title>홍대광 - 비처럼 fall in love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T23:58:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T23:58:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EB%8C%80%EA%B4%91/%EB%B9%84%EC%B2%98%EB%9F%BC_fall_in_love/" title="홍대광 - 비처럼 fall in love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기억해 비 오던 그날에 <br>우리 둘 하나의 우산에 <br>짧은 한 순간 사랑이 내게 왔어 <br>창을 두드린 빗방울처럼 <br>Oh my love 비처럼 내게 <br>말도 없이 내 맘에 <br>한 방울씩 한 방울씩 <br>사랑이 젖어 들어 <br>내게도 똑같이 비를 내려줘 <br>언젠간 네 맘도 꼭 나처럼 <br>비처럼 fall in love <br>난 너에게 우산을 기울여 <br>그만큼 내 맘도 기울어 <br>날 흠뻑 적시고 번지길 너에게도 <br>옅게 물드는 꽃잎 비처럼 <br>Oh my love 비처럼 내게 <br>말도 없이 내 맘에 <br>한 방울씩 한 방울씩 <br>사랑이 젖어 들어 <br>내게도 똑같이 비를 내려줘 <br>언젠간 네 맘도 꼭 나처럼 <br>비처럼 fall in love <br>참 맑은 날에도 <br>너를 생각만 하면 <br>거짓말처럼 비가 내려와 <br>내리는 비처럼 <br>똑같은 맘으로 물들었으면 <br>fall in love <br>한 방울씩 한 방울씩 <br>내게로 스며들어 <br>손을 꼭 잡고 비를 걸어줘 <br>그때는 네 맘도 꼭 나처럼 <br>비처럼 fall in love <br>]]></content><category term="홍대광" label="홍대광"/><category term="비처럼 fall in love" label="비처럼 fall in love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wando/Menina_Dos_Olhos_De_Lua/</id><title>Wando - Menina Dos Olhos De Lua - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:00:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:00:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wando/Menina_Dos_Olhos_De_Lua/" title="Wando - Menina Dos Olhos De Lua - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Vale ate levar o amor na brincadeira e falar todas as besteiras <br>Pra prender meu coracao, vale ate usar seus artificios <br>pra aumentar o seu feitico <br>E seu poder de seducao Vale revistar meu bolso <br>as escondidas e cheirar a minha roupa <br>Perguntar pra onde eu vou <br>So o que nao ta valendo a pena e voce <br>fazer a cena de duvidar do meu amor <br>Voce e minha menina dos olhos <br>minha sina e viver pros seus desejos <br>Nada me fascina mais que os seus beijos <br>eu so penso em voce <br>Posso ate flertar alguem por vaidade <br>abusar um pouco da liberdade <br>Mas no fundo eu sei que a minha metade <br>vive dentro de voce <br>Vale fazer cara feia de vez enquando <br>quando te deixo esperando pra sair ou pra jantar <br>Vale tudo o que voce me apronta <br>quando gasta alem da conta <br>e meio tonta, vem contar <br>Ta valendo ate queles dias em que voce fica fria <br>e dezpreza meu calor <br><br>Voce e minha menina dos olhos <br>minha sina e viver pros seus desejos <br>Nada me fascina mais que os seus beijos,]]></content><category term="Wando" label="Wando"/><category term="Menina Dos Olhos De Lua" label="Menina Dos Olhos De Lua"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wando/Mordida_Na_Maca/</id><title>Wando - Mordida Na Maca - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:01:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:01:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wando/Mordida_Na_Maca/" title="Wando - Mordida Na Maca - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Eu queria me esconder um dia desses <br>Num cantinho dos seus olhos so pra ser <br>Uma lagrima rolando no seu rosto <br>Pra molhar o seu sorriso ao me ver <br><br>Eu queria revirar seu pensamento <br>Pra fazer seu corpo desejar o meu <br>Ser a forca que de amor te deixa doida <br>Pra te ouvir pedir que eu seja sempre seu <br><br>Quero ser o vento forte em seus cabelos <br>A saudade apertando o coracao <br>Quero ser o pensamento mais ardente <br>Em sua boca o retoque do baton <br><br>Se for noite de calor eu faco chuva <br>Pra molhar seu corpo quente so pra mim <br>Nessa hora te ilumino de estrelas <br>Viro flores e perfumo seu jardim humm <br><br>Quero ser o arrepio no seu corpo todo ou ou <br>A mordida na maca que nao se esquece o gosto hum <br>O beijo que te deixa tonta e que te molha a boca ou ou <br>Quero ser aquela coisa que te deixa louca aimm <br>hum hum hum hum hum]]></content><category term="Wando" label="Wando"/><category term="Mordida Na Maca" label="Mordida Na Maca"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wando/Anjo_Vagabundo/</id><title>Wando - Anjo Vagabundo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:01:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:01:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wando/Anjo_Vagabundo/" title="Wando - Anjo Vagabundo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Da uma dor no peito <br>Quando me levanto <br>E nao te vejo <br>Como eu sinto falta <br>Dessa boca quente <br>Que me dava beijo <br>Sim virou mania <br>Ja virou saudade <br>Ja virou apego <br>Voce fez maldade <br>Levou a metade <br>Tirou meu sossego <br><br>Lagrimas nos olhos <br>Tento te esquecer <br>Mas sem querer te chamo <br>Sei nao vale a pena <br>Te amar assim <br>Mas como eu te amo <br>Anjo vagabundo <br>Que deixou a alma <br>Mas levou o corpo <br>Sempre te querendo <br>Sem o seu amor <br>Eu me sinto morto <br><br>Quem sabe hoje, quem sabe um dia <br>Traga seu corpo pra me dar calor <br>Quem sabe a noite, quem sabe a lua <br>Me amanheca nesse ceu de amor <br><br>Lagrimas nos olhos <br>Tento te esquecer <br>Mas sem querer te chamo <br>Sei nao vale a pena <br>Te amar assim <br>Mas como eu te amo <br>Anjo vagabundo <br>Que deixou a alma <br>Mas levou o corpo <br>Sempre te querendo <br>Sem o seu amor <br>Eu me sinto morto <br><br>Quem sabe hoje, quem sabe um dia <br>Traga seu corpo pra me dar calor <br>Quem sabe a noite, quem sabe a lua <br>Me amanheca nesse ceu de amor]]></content><category term="Wando" label="Wando"/><category term="Anjo Vagabundo" label="Anjo Vagabundo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Glass_Animals/Pork_Soda_Radio_Edit/</id><title>Glass_Animals - Pork Soda (Radio Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:01:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:01:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Glass_Animals/Pork_Soda_Radio_Edit/" title="Glass_Animals - Pork Soda (Radio Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Somewhere in Southend when you were fun <br>You took my hand and you made me run <br>Up past the prison to the seafront <br>You climbed the cliff edge and took the plunge <br><br>Why can't we laugh now like we did then <br>How come I see you and ache instead <br>How come you only look pleased in bed <br>Let's climb the cliff edge and jump again <br><br>Pineapples are in my head <br>Pineapples are in my head <br>Got nobody 'cause I'm brain dead <br>Got nobody 'cause I'm brain dead <br><br>I know I'm no genius of love <br>Don't know where I belong <br>Maybe I'm deaf and dumb <br>Maybe I'm just a bum <br>Maybe I never loved <br>Don't you go psycho 'cause <br>I want you for the world <br>I want you all the time <br><br>Pineapples are in my head <br>When you were fun <br>Got nobody 'cause I'm brain dead <br>You made me run <br>Pineapples are in my head <br>To the seafront <br>Got nobody 'cause I'm brain dead <br>You took the plunge <br><br>Five thousand footsteps in your wet dress <br>Back to the house with your arms 'round my neck <br>We drank pork soda with tangled legs <br>I won't forget how you looked at me then <br><br>I know I'm no sweet prince of love <br>Those times that we got drunk <br>Maybe Jamaica rum <br>Maybe some Jonnie Dub <br>Maybe you still think of us <br>Phone buzz, and still I jump <br>Why don't I say it then <br>I want you all the time <br><br>Why can't we laugh now like we did then <br>How come I see you and ache instead <br>How come you only look pleased in bed <br>Let's climb the cliff edge and jump again <br><br>Pineapples are in my head <br>Pineapples are in my head <br>Got nobody 'cause I'm brain dead <br>Got nobody 'cause I'm brain dead <br>Pineapples are in my head <br>Pineapples are in my head <br>Got nobody 'cause I'm brain dead <br>Got nobody 'cause I'm brain dead <br>Pineapples are in my head <br>Pineapples are in my head <br>Got nobody 'cause I'm brain dead <br>Got nobody 'cause I'm brain dead]]></content><category term="Glass Animals" label="Glass Animals"/><category term="Pork Soda (Radio Edit)" label="Pork Soda (Radio Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코로나_CORONA/너의_손잡고/</id><title>코로나_CORONA - 너의 손잡고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:01:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:01:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%A1%9C%EB%82%98_CORONA/%EB%84%88%EC%9D%98_%EC%86%90%EC%9E%A1%EA%B3%A0/" title="코로나_CORONA - 너의 손잡고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너의 손잡고 <br>벚꽃 핀 길을 <br>너의 손잡고 <br>봄바람 부는 길을 <br>너의 손잡고 <br>눈부신 이 길을 <br>오오오 <br>우리 함께 걸어요 <br>너의 손잡고 <br>봄비 오는 길을 <br>너의 손잡고 <br>시원한 바닷길을 <br>너의 손잡고 <br>따뜻한 이 길을 <br>오오오 <br>우리 함께 걸어요 <br>너무나 길었던 추운 겨울이 가고 <br>어느새 이렇게 봄바람이 불어 <br>나의 마음도 이젠 녹아 드네요 <br>너의 따스한 숨결로 <br>Oh Kiss me 그대 shine on me <br>저 따뜻한 햇살처럼 <br>너의 손잡고 <br>낙엽이 진 길을 <br>너의 손잡고 <br>함박눈 오는 길을 <br>너의 손잡고 <br>추워도 따뜻한 길을 <br>오오오 <br>우리 함께 걸어요 <br>어느새 이렇게 계절이 지나고 <br>따뜻하던 길 위로 찬 바람이 불어 <br>나의 마음은 시리지가 않아요 <br>너의 따스한 숨결로 <br>Oh kiss me 그대 shine on me <br>저 따뜻한 햇살처럼 <br>너의 손잡고 <br>눈부신 이 길을 <br>너의 손잡고 <br>햇살 가득한 길을 <br>Oh kiss me 그대 shine on me <br>저 따뜻한 햇살처럼 <br>우리 함께 <br>우리 함께 <br>걸어요 <br>]]></content><category term="코로나 (CORONA)" label="코로나 (CORONA)"/><category term="너의 손잡고" label="너의 손잡고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anda/아무도_모르게_Inst/</id><title>Anda - 아무도 모르게 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:01:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:01:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anda/%EC%95%84%EB%AC%B4%EB%8F%84_%EB%AA%A8%EB%A5%B4%EA%B2%8C_Inst/" title="Anda - 아무도 모르게 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새벽을 가르는 별빛 따라가 <br>그대가 부르는 곳으로 <br>따뜻한 햇살 아래 쪽빛 꽃 향기 <br>수줍은 내 마음 물드네 <br>어릴 적 웃던 소년 그대로 <br>갈색 눈빛 내게 머물면 <br>파란 나비 춤을 추며 <br>함께 피어 올라 <br>달빛은 나만을 비추고 <br>시간은 날 위해 멈추네 <br>잊혀진 꿈들이 깨어나 <br>사랑하는 그댈 부르네 <br>가슴 속에 묻어 뒀던 <br>그댈 그리네 <br>아무도 모르게 <br>저 산에 날으는 철새 따라서 <br>그대가 머무는 곳으로 <br>가을빛 나뭇잎에 부는 바람이 <br>수줍은 내 마음 흔드네 <br>그대가 내게 전한 꽃들을 <br>물빛 하늘 위로 던지면 <br>여린 꽃잎 흩날리며 <br>나도 날아 올라 <br>달빛은 나만을 비추고 <br>시간은 날 위해 멈추네 <br>잊혀진 꿈들이 깨어나 <br>사랑하는 그댈 부르네 <br>가슴 속에 묻어 뒀던 <br>그댈 그리네 <br>아무도 모르게 <br>]]></content><category term="Anda" label="Anda"/><category term="아무도 모르게 (Inst.)" label="아무도 모르게 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anda/아무도_모르게/</id><title>Anda - 아무도 모르게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:01:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:01:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anda/%EC%95%84%EB%AC%B4%EB%8F%84_%EB%AA%A8%EB%A5%B4%EA%B2%8C/" title="Anda - 아무도 모르게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새벽을 가르는 별빛 따라가 <br>그대가 부르는 곳으로 <br>따뜻한 햇살 아래 쪽빛 꽃 향기 <br>수줍은 내 마음 물드네 <br>어릴 적 웃던 소년 그대로 <br>갈색 눈빛 내게 머물면 <br>파란 나비 춤을 추며 <br>함께 피어 올라 <br>달빛은 나만을 비추고 <br>시간은 날 위해 멈추네 <br>잊혀진 꿈들이 깨어나 <br>사랑하는 그댈 부르네 <br>가슴 속에 묻어 뒀던 <br>그댈 그리네 <br>아무도 모르게 <br>저 산에 날으는 철새 따라서 <br>그대가 머무는 곳으로 <br>가을빛 나뭇잎에 부는 바람이 <br>수줍은 내 마음 흔드네 <br>그대가 내게 전한 꽃들을 <br>물빛 하늘 위로 던지면 <br>여린 꽃잎 흩날리며 <br>나도 날아 올라 <br>달빛은 나만을 비추고 <br>시간은 날 위해 멈추네 <br>잊혀진 꿈들이 깨어나 <br>사랑하는 그댈 부르네 <br>가슴 속에 묻어 뒀던 <br>그댈 그리네 <br>아무도 모르게 <br>]]></content><category term="Anda" label="Anda"/><category term="아무도 모르게" label="아무도 모르게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/빨간의자/그대_내_맘에_들어오면은/</id><title>빨간의자 - 그대 내 맘에 들어오면은 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:01:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:01:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%A8%EA%B0%84%EC%9D%98%EC%9E%90/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80_%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%98%EC%97%90_%EB%93%A4%EC%96%B4%EC%98%A4%EB%A9%B4%EC%9D%80/" title="빨간의자 - 그대 내 맘에 들어오면은 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다가가면 뒤돌아 뛰어가고 <br>쳐다보면 하늘만 바라보고 <br>내 맘을 모르는지 <br>알면서 그러는지 <br>시간만 자꾸 자꾸 흘러가네 <br>스쳐가듯 내 곁을 지나가고 <br>돌아서서 모른척하려 해요 <br>내 마음에 강물처럼 <br>흘러가는 그대는 무지갠가 <br>뛰어갈 텐데 훨훨 날아갈 텐데 <br>그대 내 맘에 들어오면은 <br>아이처럼 뛰어가지 않아도 <br>나비 따라 떠나가지 않아도 <br>그렇게 오래 오래 <br>그대 곁에 남아서 <br>강물처럼 그대 곁에 흐르리 <br>뛰어갈 텐데 날아갈 텐데 <br>그대 내 맘에 들어오면은 <br>스쳐가듯 내 곁을 지나가고 <br>돌아서서 모른척하려 해요 <br>내 마음에 강물처럼 <br>흘러가는 그대는 무지갠가 <br>뛰어갈 텐데 훨훨 날아갈 텐데 <br>그대 내 맘에 들어오면은 <br>아이처럼 뛰어가지 않아도 <br>나비 따라 떠나가지 않아도 <br>그렇게 오래 오래 <br>그대 곁에 남아서 <br>강물처럼 그대 곁에 흐르리 <br>뛰어갈 텐데 날아갈 텐데 <br>그대 내 맘에 들어오면은 <br>뛰어갈 텐데 날아갈 텐데 <br>그대 내 맘에 들어오면은 <br>]]></content><category term="빨간의자" label="빨간의자"/><category term="그대 내 맘에 들어오면은" label="그대 내 맘에 들어오면은"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/1_Tag/</id><title>Bligg - 1 Tag - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:05:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:05:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/1_Tag/" title="Bligg - 1 Tag - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wann ich no 1 Tag zum labe hett und Gott uf mich wartet <br>Gab's no so viel wo no z'sage war und ich wusst nod mal wo starte <br><br>Wann ich wusst dass Gott uf mich wartet mit offena Arme <br>Und er schankt mir no da letscht Tag us Gnad und Verbarme <br>Wurd mini Alba nomal lose imane Lamborghini Gallardo <br>Mim Chef a Flattere geh und sage Suech es anders Arschloch <br><br>Mir as aktuells Familieportrait uf da Rugge tattowiere <br>Und jedi nur erdankbari Form vo Droge usprobiere <br>Da Frau en Kuss uf d'Stirn geh und mit ihre schlafa <br>Batt zu Gott dass en Nachfahre entstaht us mim Same <br>Amen <br><br>Wann ich no 1 Tag zum Labe hett und Gott uf mich wartet <br>Gabs no so viel wo no z'sage war und ich wusst nod mal wo starte <br>Wann ich no 1 Tag zum labe hett und fur Ewig musst gah <br>Gabs no so viel wo no z'mache war doch da defur langt kein Tag <br><br>Ich musst es paar Brief schriibe churz vor mim Kollaps <br>Und imna lichchaufwageli da Zuriberg durab <br>Ich wurd mis Bankkonto leere und's mit Frunde verprassa <br>Fudliblut Fallschirmspringa dorf ich ja nod verpassa <br><br>Ich han viel Scheisse baut und ich han vieles bereut <br>Ihr chonnd jetzt alles vo mir ha ich wunsch mir s'Beschte fur eu <br>a letschti Umarmig an letschte Kuss <br>Nachdem da Sargdeckel schlusst isch Schluss <br>Ich bin duss <br><br>Wann ich no 1 Tag zum Labe hett und Gott uf mich wartet <br>Gabs no so viel wo no z'sage war und ich wusst nod mal wo starte <br>Wann ich no 1 Tag zum labe hett und fur Ewig musst gah <br>Gabs no so viel wo no z'mache war doch da defur langt kein Tag <br><br>Ich flug jetzt frei wie en Vogel und gsehn eu vo da oba Erwiised mir en letschte Wunsch truured nod um mich gonnd mit eme Lache dur s'Labe und meislet ？？Hart aber herzlich' i min Grabstei <br><br>Wann ich no 1 Tag zum Labe hett und Gott uf mich wartet <br>Gabs no so viel wo no z'sage war und ich wusst nod mal wo starte <br>Wann ich no 1 Tag zum labe hett und fur Ewig musst gah <br>Gabs no so viel wo no z'mache war doch da defur langt kein Tag]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="1 Tag" label="1 Tag"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Ciao_Bella/</id><title>Bligg - Ciao Bella - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:05:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:05:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Ciao_Bella/" title="Bligg - Ciao Bella - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sie will kontrolliere dis Labe dominiere Dini Frundin isch a Plag <br>Schafft sie bim KGB oder bim CIA Wieso spioniert sie eus nah <br><br>Du gahsch mit ihra an es Picknick und du pflucksch ihra paar Blueme <br>Aber sie ha hatt Heuschnupfa <br>Du ladsch sie i is Kino sie wott lieber is Theater dafur find sie David Hasselhof super <br><br>Alte fass din Muet zamme du musch s'Chind bim Name nanne und ihra sage was Sache isch zum Bispiel so <br><br>Ciao Ciao Bella Mir mund zamme reda <br>Was jetzt chunnt findsch du sicher nod cool <br>Ciao Ciao Bella Ciao Bella Ciao Ich muss dir sage eigentlich bin ich schwul <br><br>Ciao Ciao Bella Mir mund zamme reda <br>5 Anderi hand Chind vo mir <br>Ich has dir nie chonne sage <br>Wunsch dir a schon's Labe und wott dass du weisch ich ha dich immer gliebt <br>Irgendwie <br><br>Du hasch zwar gern Sex doch Wiehnachte isch ofter <br>Alte du hasch es Problem <br>Wo fruehner Frunde gsi sind sind hutt Schwigereltera <br>Dia Frau isch acht es Phanomen <br><br>Sie hatt dich a da Leine wie en chlina Vierbeiner <br>Du bisch ihra ganz personlich Sponsor <br>Chasch sie genauso wenig bruche wie es Solarium im Summer <br>Schank ihra es 1 Wag Ticket nach Hongkong <br><br>Alte fass din Muet zamme du musch s'Chind bim Name nanne und ihra sage was Sache isch zum Bispiel so <br><br>Ciao Ciao Bella Mir mund zamme reda <br>Was jetzt chunnt findsch du sicher nod cool <br>Ciao Ciao Bella Ciao Bella Ciao Ich muss dir sage eigentlich bin ich schwul <br><br>Ciao Ciao Bella Mir mund zamme reda <br>5 Anderi hand Chind vo mir <br>Ich has dir nie chonne sage <br>Wunsch dir a schon's Labe und wott dass du weisch ich ha dich immer gliebt <br>Irgendwie <br><br>Ciao Ciao Bella Mir mund zamme reda <br>Was jetzt chunnt findsch du sicher nod cool <br>Ciao Ciao Bella Ciao Bella Ciao Ich muss dir sage eigentlich bin ich schwul <br>Ciao Ciao Bella Mir mund zamme reda <br>5 Anderi hand Chind vo mir <br>Ich has dir nie chonne sage <br>Wunsch dir a schon's Labe und wott dass du weisch ich ha dich immer gliebt <br>Irgendwie]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Ciao Bella" label="Ciao Bella"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Hollywood/</id><title>Bligg - Hollywood - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:05:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:05:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Hollywood/" title="Bligg - Hollywood - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Danke Hollywood <br>Danke Hollywood <br><br>Danke Hollywood dini Sterne wiised da Wag <br>Und du hilfsch eus fluchte vo da Realitat <br>Playboy Bunny Mansion <br>Silikon und Extensions <br>Irgendwo zwusched Monroe und Marilyn Manson <br><br>Du fahrsch a eus verbi i dim Benz <br>Eusi Kidz gsehnd's und sie wannd's und sie folged dim Trend <br>Und d'Essenz isch verbrannt <br>Kei Wert kei Kompetenz <br>Chli Michi dankt er seg 50 Cent <br>Pam Pam <br><br>Mir sind chranki Seele im Garten Eden <br>Immitiered dis Verhalte wie Pantomime <br>Din American Dream wird zum na bose Traum <br>Erica halted da Druck nod us und hangt am Baum <br><br>Hollywood Du hasch d'Walt veranderet <br>Hollywood Dini Sterne blandet <br>Ich setz d'Sunnebrulle uf und gseh mal wider klar <br>Wach uf us dim Traum und dank das isch nod wahr <br>Ohh nei Ohh nei <br><br>Danke Holly dass du eus hilfsch z'vergasse <br>Und eusi Tochter dur es Wunschbild nuut meh frassed <br>Du luegsch Pornos wie Tierfilm und haltisch's fur d'Liebi <br>Figgsch ohni Gummi bis mit HIV invisziert bisch <br><br>Mir sind verwirrt sind verwirrt nur wag dir <br>Wussed numme wo ussa wo ia <br>Folged dir wie Schaaf am Hirt <br><br>Die Bahn isch schief man was isch da passiert <br>Oder bis am End nur ich wo da Panik schiebt <br>Dini Luge und Gschichte hand d'Luut vergifted <br>Vor dim Schonheits Wahnsinn isch nuut meh sicher <br>Dini VIP Party hatt da Tuufel gmischlet <br>Und din Name schtaht z'oberscht uf da Gaschtelischte <br><br>Danke Hollywood fur dini Gschichte und Luge <br>Und dass mir eus dur dich viel wichtiger fuhled <br>Es warted Barbie and Ken uf es Happy End <br>Danke Hollywood <br><br>Hollywood Du hasch d'Walt veranderet <br>Hollywood Dini Sterne blandet <br>Ich setz d'Sunnebrulle uf und gseh mal wider klar <br>Wach uf us dim Traum und dank das isch nod wahr <br>Ohh nei Ohh nei <br><br>Hollywood Du hasch d'Walt veranderet <br>Hollywood Dini Sterne blandet <br>Ich setz d'Sunnebrulle uf und gseh mal wider klar <br>Wach uf us dim Traum und dank das isch nod wahr <br>Ohh nei Ohh nei]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Hollywood" label="Hollywood"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Signal/</id><title>Bligg - Signal - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:05:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:05:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Signal/" title="Bligg - Signal - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oho oho <br>Oho oho <br><br>Weisch no <br>Mir zwei wie Bonnie and Clyde <br>Hand euses Herz euses Gald euses Bett und d'Wohnig teilt <br>Weisch no <br>Wie mir gseit hand eus chonnt nut tranne <br>Mir hebed zamme egal was irgendwelchi Luut saged <br>Weisch no <br>Euses erschte mal Sex zu Barry White <br>Mir hand Trane glacht zu King of Queens und all de Scheiss <br>Und weisch no <br>Bi Vollmond go bade mitsamt de Chleider <br>Du hasch gschwore bis da Tod eus scheidet <br><br>Und was isch jetzt <br>Jetzt bini nur irgend es Arschloch <br>Und was isch jetzt <br>Wie's mir gaht isch dir doch glich <br>Und was isch jetzt <br>Und du weisch ich hasse Lovesongs <br>Und was isch jetzt <br>Aber schrib das Lied fur dich <br><br>Gib es Signal <br>Wann du d'Liebi liebsch <br>Gib es Signal <br>Wann du wirkli d'Liebi liebsch <br>Dann lieb nur mich, wil niemmert liebt dich so wie ich <br>Gib es Signal <br>Wann du d'Liebi liebsch <br>Gib es Signal <br>Wann du wirkli d'Liebi liebsch <br>Dann lieb nur mich, wil niemmert liebt dich so wie ich <br><br>Ich weiss no <br>Du und ich sind stock verlada heicho <br>Ich lueg si hut no ah eusi Videos uf em iPhone <br>Ich weiss no <br>Was ich der gseit han uf sabere Insle <br>Du hasch mer eini klatscht und ich han musse grinse <br>Ich weiss no <br>Du hasch's mer gfluschtered im Rage <br>Uf was mir hand warted anderi es Labe <br>Ich weiss no <br>Wie du gseit hasch du wellsch das nie <br>Es Laben in Angscht allei eso wie dia <br><br>Und was isch jetzt <br>Jetzt bini nur irgend es Arschloch <br>Und was isch jetzt <br>Wie's mir gaht isch dir doch glich <br>Und was isch jetzt <br>Und du weisch ich hasse Lovesongs <br>Und was isch jetzt <br>Aber schrib das Lied fur dich <br><br>Gib es Signal <br>Wann du d'Liebi liebsch <br>Gib es Signal <br>Wann du wirkli d'Liebi liebsch <br>Dann lieb nur mich Wil niemmert liebt dich so wie ich <br>Gib es Signal <br>Wann du d'Liebi liebsch <br>Gib es Signal <br>Wann du wirkli d'Liebi liebsch <br>Dann lieb nur mich, wil niemmert liebt dich so wie ich <br><br>Gib es Signal <br>Wann du d'Liebi liebsch <br>Gib es Signal <br>Wann du wirkli d'Liebi liebsch <br>Dann lieb nur mich, wil niemmert liebt dich so wie ich <br><br>Gib es Signal <br>Wann du d'Liebi liebsch <br>Gib es Signal <br>Wann du wirkli d'Liebi liebsch <br>Dann lieb nur mich, wil niemmert liebt dich so wie ich <br>Gib es Signal <br>Wann du d'Liebi liebsch <br>Gib es Signal <br>Wann du wirkli d'Liebi liebsch <br>Dann lieb nur mich, wil niemmert liebt dich so wie ich]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Signal" label="Signal"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/DHeimat/</id><title>Bligg - D`Heimat - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:05:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:05:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/DHeimat/" title="Bligg - D`Heimat - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Helvetia und Willhelm sind stolz uf eusi Chinde <br>Gruezi Frau Kuenzi mit em Arsch gwaggla muend sie <br><br>S'isch eusi Heimat Ohh S'isch eusi Heimat Hey S'isch d'Heimat fur eus alli fur eus <br>d'Heimat fur eus <br>Dis Land mis Land <br>Grosses Land chlises Land <br>4 verschiedeni Spracha <br>i26 Farbe <br>REFRAIN <br><br>S'isch eusi Heimat Ohh S'isch eusi Heimat Hey S'isch d'Heimat fur eus alli Fur dich und fur mich <br>d'Heimat fur eus <br>Gmischti Kulture <br>Stadter and Buure <br>Fliisig si und gnueg ha <br>Bescheideheit chunnt guet a jajaja <br><br>S'isch eusi Heimat Ohh S'isch eusi Heimat Hey S'isch d'Heimat fur eus alli <br>d'Heimat fur eus <br>S'isch d'Heimat fur eus alli <br>d'Heimat fur eus <br>Vo Vreneli's Gartli bis wohere bis nach Genf dann isch fertig aber Ende Gelande <br>Uuswandere chonnt mer doch dehei isch's am schonschte <br><br>S'isch eusi Heimat Ohh S'isch eusi Heimat Hey S'isch d'Heimat fur eus alli]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="D`Heimat" label="D`Heimat"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Nur_En_Soldner/</id><title>Bligg - Nur En Soldner - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:05:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:05:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Nur_En_Soldner/" title="Bligg - Nur En Soldner - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm only a soldier, in' that sorrow <br><br>Ich bin en Sohn Gottes <br>Frei wia da Wind <br>Ha nie a Flagge wella <br>Wo mer seit wer ich bin <br><br>Ich flug wie nen Vogel <br>Schwomm gag da Strom <br>Los nor uf mis Herz <br>Ond ich ha kei Mission <br><br>Bin vom Drack unna ue cho <br>Dirakt de Sonne empor <br>Dann wag uf und dervo <br>Ich spreiz d'Flugel <br><br>Ich chan e Meinig akzeptieren <br>Aber muess si nod teile <br>Ben allei uf d walt cho <br>Und gang au allei ge <br><br>Hey <br><br>Ich bin nur en Soldner <br>Und laufe min Wag entlang <br>Freiheit isch Schonste <br>Wil mer d'Freiheit nod chaufe chan <br><br>Ich bin nur en Soldner <br>Met Liebi em Korper <br>Und reise uf Strasse i Stadter und Dorfer <br><br>Sing mini Worter <br>Gepragt vom Schmerz <br>Und wanni gseh was zrogg chonnt <br>Dann esch es das wert <br><br>Ich erwiese min Stolz <br>Und schrib Ziilen us Gold <br>Schiss uf Erfolg und blib gschider bim Volk <br>Sie gsahnd mi als Poet als moderne Dichter <br>Gott isch's einzig uf da Walt wo ober mich cha richte <br><br>Hey <br><br>Ich bin nur en Soldner <br>Und laufe min Wag entlang <br>Freiheit isch's Schonste <br>Wil mer d'Freiheit nod chaufe chan <br><br>Schrib <br>Schrib <br>Schrib Ziilen us Gold <br><br>Ich bin nur en Soldner <br>Und laufe min Wag entlang <br>Freiheit isch Schonste <br>Wil mer d'Freiheit nod chaufe chan]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Nur En Soldner" label="Nur En Soldner"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Secondos/</id><title>Bligg - Secondos - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:05:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:05:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Secondos/" title="Bligg - Secondos - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Italie 1930 irgendwo in Benevento <br>Bringt e jungi Frau es Chind as Tagesliecht im Eiltempo <br>Er heisst Antonio und tuscht en warma Buch gag a chalti Walt <br><br>1 Familie 6 Gschwuschter 1 Zimmer 4 Wand <br>Ziit rast 16 jahr ziehnd is Land <br>Sin Vater schtirbt <br>Bluemeschtruss Trane flussed und da Pfarrer kondoliert <br><br>Toni chnuttled <br>Toni ruttled <br>Er isch jetzt da Maa im Huus <br>Miesi Jobs fur mieses Gald s'erschparte gaht langsam us <br>Sie verzelled vom'na Land mit freie Arbeitsplatz und Perspektive <br>Sini Muetter wunscht ihm Gluck als er in Zug iischtigt und als Saisonier i d'Schwiiz fahrt zum halfe uf ema Buurehof <br>Mit Schwile a da Hand fur Milch und Brot <br>Er verschtaht keis Wort <br><br>Das isch min Immigrante Song <br>Sie gand Bluet, Schweiss und Trane <br>Irgendwo imane andere Land <br>Was wared mir numme ohni sie <br><br>Das isch min Immigrante Song <br>Sie gand Bluet, Schweiss und Trane <br>Irgendwo imane andere Land <br>Was wared mir numme ohni sie <br><br>D'Ufenthaltsbewilligung lauft ab er muss usser Landesgranze <br>Jobt im Ruhrpott Chollebergwarch mit schwarze Hand <br>Nach eim Jahr Staub schlucke schicked's ihm d'Papier <br>Er chunnt zrugg i d'Schwiiz a d'Langstrass is Italo Quartier <br>Er hatt nod vill Bagage lernt Dutsch uf das da Schtarass <br>Und schafft sich sini Exischtanz als Mech in ere Garage <br><br>D'Kassiererin vom Lade gagenuber find er herzig <br>Amor spannt Pfiil and Boge und trifft mittais Herz ia <br>1958 hand die 2 da Bund fur s'Labe gschlosse <br>1959 chunnt s'erschte Chind Es isch a Tochter <br>Toni isch stolz wie no nie es gond 17 Jahr verbi <br>Die Tochter bringt es Baby zur Walt und das Baby bin ich <br>Hallo Schwiiz <br><br>Das isch min Immigrante Song <br>Sie gand Bluet, Schweiss und Trane <br>Irgendwo imane andere Land <br>Was wared mir numme ohni sie <br><br>Das isch min Immigrante Song <br>Sie gand Bluet, Schweiss und Trane <br>Irgendwo imane andere Land <br>Was wared mir numme ohni sie <br><br>Ohoh ohoh ohoh <br><br>Das isch min Immigrante Song <br>Sie gand Bluet, Schweiss und Trane <br>Irgendwo imane andere Land <br>Was wared mir numme ohni sie <br><br>Das isch min Immigrante Song <br>Sie gand Bluet, Schweiss und Trane <br>Irgendwo imane andere Land <br>Was wared mir numme ohni sie]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Secondos" label="Secondos"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/SLotti_Schilled/</id><title>Bligg - S`Lotti Schilled - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:05:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:05:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/SLotti_Schilled/" title="Bligg - S`Lotti Schilled - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sie hatt Summersprosse und drathigs Haar <br>Sie treit a Brulle dick wie Panzerglas <br>a Zahspange und chrummi Bei <br><br>Uf em Schuelhuusplatz isch sie drum allei <br><br>Sie lached uber sie ou sie lached uber sie <br>Haaa haaa haaa haaa Sie lached uber sie ou sie lached uber sie <br>Haaa haaa haaa haaa S'Lotti wird verspotted niemert wott sie all schreied <br><br>S'Lotti schilled Oh Yeahh Hey <br>Oh Yeah S'Lotti schilled <br>Oh Yeahh Hey Oh Oh Oh Yeah <br><br>D'Dorf Cliqua findet sich bsunders c c cool <br>S'Lotti bliibt ruhig aber hatt e Wuet im Buch <br>Allei dehei singt sie da Fruscht vor Seel <br>Wahrend die andere verusse sind <br><br>Sie lached uber sie ou sie lached uber sie <br>Haaa haaa haaa haaa Sie lached uber sie ou sie lached uber sie <br>Haaa haaa haaa haaa S'Lotti wird verspotted niemert wott sie all schreied <br><br>S'Lotti schilled Oh Yeahh Hey <br>Oh Yeah S'Lotti schilled <br>Oh Yeahh Hey Oh Oh Oh Yeah <br><br>Sie lached uber sie ou sie lached uber sie <br>Haaa haaa haaa haaa Sie lached uber sie ou sie lached uber sie <br>Haaa haaa haaa haaa Sie lached uber sie ou sie lached uber sie <br>Haaa haaa haaa haaa S'Lotti wird verspotted niemert wott sie all schreied <br><br>S'Lotti schilled Oh Yeahh Hey <br>Oh Yeah S'Lotti schilled <br>Oh Yeahh Hey Oh Oh Oh Yeah <br><br>S'Lotti schilled Oh Yeahh Hey <br>Oh Yeah S'Lotti schilled <br>Oh Yeahh Hey Oh Oh Oh Yeah]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="S`Lotti Schilled" label="S`Lotti Schilled"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/10_Chlini_Appenzeller/</id><title>Bligg - 10 Chlini Appenzeller - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:05:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:05:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/10_Chlini_Appenzeller/" title="Bligg - 10 Chlini Appenzeller - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[10 chliini Appenzeller wussed no vo nuud es git immer Grund zum suufe und scho sins nur no nuun <br><br>nuun chliini Appenzeller eine isch wie keine die ganz wuche hammer chrampfed also giz grad nomol eine <br><br>nur no acht chliini Appenzeller langsam wirds gschmeidig wer A seit muess Penzaller sage sunsch wirds zimmlich peinlich <br><br>siebe chliini Appenzeller sind verfolgt vom Pach s Glesli goht ufs Huus und scho sins nur no sachs <br><br>hoch das Glas eine gaht no eine gaht no es muess oppis gah eine gaht no eine gaht no mir hand gottlich Spass eine gaht no eine gaht no zigezagezigezage hoi hoi hoi <br><br>sachs Appenzeller on the rocks hand sich z frueh gfroit ich sing bsoffe We will rock you und scho sins nur no foif <br><br>am foifte schwahnt schlimms doch er rueft vergabets um Hilf und gaht uf d Tauchstation zwusche Labere und Milz <br><br>vier chliini Appenzeller hoppla langsam han i gnueg ich kopier de Helge Schneider und mach Breakdance uf em Stuel <br>wart no eine gaht no ich chruch uf allne Chnu dr Verstand seit NEI de Durscht seit JO und scho sins nur no dru <br><br>hoch das Glas eine gaht no eine gaht no es muess oppis gah eine gaht no eine gaht no mir hand gottlich Spass eine gaht no eine gaht no zigezagezigezage hoi hoi hoi <br><br>dru chliini Appenzeller stond in Reih und Glied ich han zwar ufghort Gras rauche aber hut isch mir das gliich ich wirf Prinzipie uber Bord nimm en Zug und ziehn e Frazze uf zmol deht d Barduse us wie d Rut Nezler in Strapse so viel Sex muess e weg uf exx und do sins nur no zwei gsehnt aber us wie sachs ich suuf grad nomol ein mein Gott bin ich breit <br><br>dr letscht git mir dr Rest mann ich muess go ligge d Ruth wott mr go halfe abr ich chotz er eifach <br><br>hoch das Glas eine gaht no eine gaht no es muess oppis gah eine gaht no eine gaht no mir hand gottlich Spass eine gaht no eine gaht no zigezagezigezage hoi hoi <br>zigezagezigezage hoi hoi <br>zigezagezigezage hoi hoi hoi]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="10 Chlini Appenzeller" label="10 Chlini Appenzeller"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Rosalie/</id><title>Bligg - Rosalie - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:05:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:05:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Rosalie/" title="Bligg - Rosalie - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Rosalie oh Rosalie was war dia Walt ohni sie <br>Sie sitzt im Kaffi Rex und dankt a ihri gmeinsami Ziit <br>Mit ihrem Ex doch er isch weg es sind scho 2 Jahr verbi <br>Sie isch nie richtig druber wag cho resigniert vor sich hi <br>a Trane flugt in Espresso uber ihre Gsicht lamped d'Haar <br>En attraktive Typ setzt sich an Tisch spricht sie aa <br>Hallo Sie luegt apathisch empor und isch wie troffe vom Blitz <br>Fur d'Rosalie isch's d'Liebi uf da erschti Blick <br><br>Rosalie Die Rose sind fur dich Mi Amor <br>Du gsehsch so truurig us als war opper gschtorbe <br>Wie cha das si a hubschi Frau mit Auge wie du <br>So ganz allei amne Sunntig Morge <br><br>Rosalie oh Rosalie sie fuhlt sich im Paradies <br>Er isch ihre vertraut und alles schtaht still rund um sie <br>Sit ara halbe Ewigkeit hatt niemert meh mit ihra gflirted <br>Er git ihra Kompliment bis sie sich schamt und vollig erroted <br>Er frogt sie nach em Name und sie seit Rosalie <br>Er seit lugg Mi Amor ich han a Rose fur dich <br>Hihihi das isch zwar nett aber ich cha's unmoglich aneh <br>Mir kanned eus grad mal paar Minute ich hoff du verschtahsch es <br><br>Sie nimmt dia Rose a und seit Wia chan ich dir numme danke <br>Er hebt a offni Hand entgage es machi numme 5 Franke <br>Das isch mies Das isch fies Ich ha gmeint sie seg fur mich <br>Er staht uf Uf widerseh und lauft zum Tisch vis a vis <br>Hallo hubschi Frau wie isch ihre Name <br><br>Melanie Die Rose sind fur dich Mi Amor <br>Du gsehsch so truurig us als war opper gschtorbe <br>Wie cha das si a hubschi Frau mit Auge wie du <br>So ganz allei amne Sunntig Morge]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Rosalie" label="Rosalie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Musigg_I_Da_Schwiiz/</id><title>Bligg - Musigg I Da Schwiiz - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:05:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:05:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Musigg_I_Da_Schwiiz/" title="Bligg - Musigg I Da Schwiiz - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jo lo lo lo lo di jo di oh <br><br>Hi my name isch George min iPod wiis rot <br>Ich bi Mother's Pride und Grandmother's Funk was' los <br>Fahr im Taxi von der Heide met Peter, Sue und Marc <br>Seng as doubel vom Mani Matter Captain of my Heart <br>Song's so flauschig wie Plusch oder hart ond grober <br>Und sie gond under d'Huut wie Tattoo's vom Gola <br>Warum sprengt jetzt die Platte und s'Liecht wurkt wie Strobo <br>Fahrt de Lockstoff scho i oder hat de DJ es Bobo <br>Du ghorsch eusi Musig uf Radio 200'000 <br>Bevors of YouTube isch, aber numme wells du bisch <br>Es weht e neuie wend liebi Schlieremer Chend <br> dann de Haas blibt numme langer still <br><br>Ich mach Musig i da Schwiiz <br>Mag d'Musig us de Schwiiz <br>Alles was ich bruch isch en Melodie und en Beat <br>Ich mach Musig i da Schwiiz <br>Mag d'Musig us de Schwiiz <br>Ich chont ned ohni sie und sie ned ohni mich <br>Ich mach d'Musig i da Schwiiz <br>Mag d'Musig us de Schwiiz <br>Alles was ich bruch isch en Melodie und en Beat <br>Ich mach Musig i da Schwiiz <br>Mag d'Musig us de Schwiiz <br>Ich chont ned ohni sie und sie ned ohni mich <br><br>Sterne Foifi, eusi Musig heilt wie n'es Wunder <br>Sie macht d'Heidi Happy und stillt de Sophie ehre Hunger <br>Ich lug dumm is Von Rohr, betracht's met chli Abstand <br>D'Francine Jordi met Mash, esch e geili Katz man <br>D'Schwiiz ohni Musi isch es laar's Sektion Chuchichaschtli <br>Gahd nod, wie Bundner Fleisch in ere Vegi Chuchi fresse <br>Gschichte und Bilder, Verbe und Silber <br>Froog de Adrian, er holt der no en Stern vo sim Hemmel <br>Sie frooged Bligg, wie fendsch de Baschi Ich sag, froog mi oppis neuis <br> Zum Biispiel was isch d Wurzel vo Foif <br>Vo luuter Schmetterbands chum i no gschwind in Stress <br>Ich fahr dure Gotthard, aber sott noch Zuri West <br><br>Ich mach Musig i da Schwiiz <br>Mag d'Musig us de Schwiiz <br>Alles was ich bruch isch en Melodie und en Beat <br>Ich mach Musig i da Schwiiz <br>Mag d'Musig us de Schwiiz <br>Ich chont ned ohni sie und sie ned ohni mich <br>Ich mach Musig i da Schwiiz <br>Mag d'Musig us de Schwiiz <br>Alles was ich bruch isch en Melodie und en Beat <br>Ich mach Musig i da Schwiiz <br>Mag d'Musig us de Schwiiz <br>Ich chont ned ohni sie und sie ned ohni mich <br><br>Jo lo lo lo lo di jo di oh das isch Musig <br><br>Ich mach Musig i da Schwiiz <br>Mag d'Musig us de Schwiiz <br>Alles was ich bruch isch en Melodie und en Beat <br>Ich mach Musig i da Schwiiz <br>Mag d'Musig us de Schwiiz <br>Ich chont ned ohni sie und sie ned ohni mich <br><br>Hatte mir set em Sommer 68 ewigi Liebi for eusi Volksmusig <br>Und mogted lieber Lieder als Alperose <br>Denn war de Ferdinand vellecht bis hot ned gschtorbe <br>Aber Wunder passiered und war weiss <br>Vellecht treff ich eines Tages d'Venus vo Bumpliz und sie seid <br>Irgendeinisch find's Gluck eim <br>Denn legg ich mich met ehre uf's Balpmoos und schankere mis Harz]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Musigg I Da Schwiiz" label="Musigg I Da Schwiiz"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/0816_Intro/</id><title>Bligg - 0816 Intro - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:05:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:05:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/0816_Intro/" title="Bligg - 0816 Intro - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ich nimm Eu uf Reise mit <br>Lass Bilder reda wie d'Annie Leibovitz <br>Wann ich Volksmusigg und Rap zu Eim vermisch <br>Isch's wie d'Volkerverbindig us da Heilig Schrift <br>En neue Tag a neui Aera <br>Helvetia wacht uf und hatt Freudetrane <br>Emotione verpackt i goldige Strophe <br>Eua MBliggensdorfer <br><br>Mach d'Auge zue und flug mit mir <br>Zwusched Morgerot und Nabelmeer <br>uber Walder See und Tal <br>In en neue Tag]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="0816 Intro" label="0816 Intro"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Okay/</id><title>Bligg - Okay - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:06:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:06:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Okay/" title="Bligg - Okay - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Willkomma i sim Huus <br>Willkomma i sim Kerker <br>Willkomma zu sim Film voller Freude und Schmerza <br><br>S'isch en junge Ma gsi <br>Im Armuet und Zwiifel <br>Ohni Perspektive <br>Wott nach de Sterna grife <br><br>Es Laba innere Mulda <br>Berga vo Schulda <br>Es Meer us Problem <br>D'Wulcha warded dunkler <br>Vaters Sohn fuhlt sich wie de bruellend Clown <br>Er git nod uf es Fuur entfacht dur sini Emotion <br><br>Sini Walt isch so hart gsi und Ziite sind schwar gsi <br>Aber Gott hatt ghulfe mit aller Chraft <br>En Bueb flugt im Waltall <br>Da Bueb hatt en Traum gha <br>Wo langer dured als nur e Nacht <br><br>Sie hand em immer gseit <br>Lah di gah mis Chind <br>Da usse blast de Wind dini Flugel sind frei <br>Chunnt scho guet isch okay <br>Bliib starch mis Chind <br>Lugg wo Gfahre sind <br>Mangisch tueds chli weh <br>Chunnt scho guet isch okay <br><br>Bevor er sich verluurt isch s'Hobby sini Zueflucht <br>Das isch sini Chance mit dere chunnt de Durchbruch <br>All In entweder alles oder nuut <br>Sie chonnd fuhle was er macht dann er redt d'Sprach vo de Luut <br><br>Er hatt's gschafft vo schiss Job's <br>Zu Steve Jobs <br>Vom Arbetnahmer zum Arbetgaber <br>Isch numme langer en Mythos <br>Kei Sand meh im Zahrad <br>Jetzt lueged's en als Star a <br>Doch tuuf i sim Herz isch er no de Bueb vo damals <br><br>Sini Walt isch so hart gsi und Ziite sind schwar gsi <br>Aber Gott hatt ghulfe mit aller Chraft <br>En Bueb flugt im Waltall <br>Da Bueb hatt en Traum gha <br>Wo langer dured als nur e Nacht <br><br>Sie hand em immer gseit <br>Lah di gah mis Chind <br>Da usse blast de Wind dini Flugel sind frei <br>Chunnt scho guet isch okay <br>Bliib starch mis Chind <br>Lugg wo Gfahre sind <br>Mangisch tueds chli weh <br>Chunnt scho guet isch okay <br><br>Trotz em ganze Erfolg <br>Dem Glitter und dem Gold <br>Hatt er nie vergasse wer er isch und woher er chunnt <br>All die schware Ziite sind de alles entscheidend Schlussel gsi <br>Es isch kein Zuefall <br>Das alles hatt musse si <br><br>Er freut sich uf d'Zuekunft mit Frau und Chind <br>Uf es Labe wo nen glucklich macht frei wie de Wind <br>Und wann s'Schicksal so will isch das Kapitel s'letschti <br>Er nimmt de Exit Macht Platz fur de neggscht Bligg <br><br>Lah di gah mis Chind <br>Da usse blast de Wind dini Flugel sind frei <br>Chunnt scho guet isch okay <br>Sie hand mir immer gseit <br>Bliib starch mis Chind <br>Lugg wo Gfahre sind <br>Mangisch tueds chli weh <br>Chunnt scho guet isch okay]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Okay" label="Okay"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/SOS/</id><title>Bligg - S.O.S - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:06:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:06:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/SOS/" title="Bligg - S.O.S - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ich sing da Song <br>Fur die Chind vom Zorn <br>Sie rebelliered und sind verwirrt <br><br>Sie sueched sich de Wag usem Labyrinth <br>Das Labyrinth hand mir kreiert <br><br>Ihra Frust isch gross <br>Ihri Chance chli sie hand kei Fuhrig und kei Halt <br>Fur chindlichi Ohre <br>Z'vill Informationa sie gsend vor luuter Baum kein Wald <br><br>Sie triibed ufem Ozean dur Wind und Sturm <br>S'git wiit und breit kein Luchtturm <br>Jedesmal wann sie versueched uber ihre Schatte z'springe <br>Knippst irgend opper s'Liecht us <br><br>SoS Sie schreied Hilfe <br>Use i d'Walt aber keina merkt's <br>SoS Sie schribed Hilfe <br>Mit Neonschrift doch de Stift isch leer <br><br>Sie mund ach so gli scho erwachsa si i dem stetiga Wettbewerb <br>Und ohh jaa Sie konsumiered Betaubigsmittel wills ohni unuustehlich war <br><br>Hilfe Ohh Hilfe ich schreis i ihrem Nama <br>Hilfe sie bruuched eus Fraua wie Manna <br><br>Sie triibed ufem Ozean dur Wind und Sturm <br>S'git wiit und breit kein Luchtturm <br>Jedesmal wann sie versueched uber ihre Schatte z'springe <br>Knippst irgend opper s'Liecht us <br><br>SoS Sie schreied Hilfe <br>Use i d'Walt aber keina merkt's <br>SoS Sie schribed Hilfe <br>Mit Neonschrift doch de Stift isch leer <br><br>SoS Sie schreied Hilfe <br>Use i d'Walt aber keina merkt's <br>SoS Sie schribed Hilfe <br>Mit Neonschrift doch de Stift isch leer <br><br>SoS mir schreied Hilfe <br>Use i d'Walt aber keina merkt's <br>SoS mir schribed Hilfe <br>Mit Neonschrift doch de Stift isch leer <br><br>SoS mir schreied Hilfe <br>Use i d'Walt aber keina merkt's <br>SoS mir schribed Hilfe <br>Mit Neonschrift doch de Stift isch leer <br><br>SoS mir schreied Hilfe <br>Use i d'Walt aber keina merkt's <br>SoS mir schribed Hilfe <br>Mit Neonschrift doch de Stift isch leer]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="S.O.S" label="S.O.S"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Rendezvous/</id><title>Bligg - Rendezvous - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:06:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:06:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Rendezvous/" title="Bligg - Rendezvous - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Es isch fritig de 13 Ich bin allei <br>Mit chips und bier bi mir dihei <br>Zapp durch de tv had fuess ufem tisch <br>Und bi garn da wo d walt no in ornig isch <br>Es lauft nur schrott und werbespotts <br>Als s us heiterem himmel a ture chlopft <br>Wer chonnt das si miner ex bini glich <br>Au schusch interessiert sich keis schwein fur mich <br><br>Ich mach d ture uf es liecht erstrahlt <br>Und vor mir staht de sensema <br>Hallo bligg de rapper wer bisch du <br>Ich bi jack the ripper hey jack alts hus <br>Dini zit isch abglofe sisch ende gelande <br>Fur dich isch hut I'm wahrschte sinn vom wort sense <br>Jetzt scho jetzt scho nei doch <br>Ich chonnt wanni wett aber han kei bock <br><br>Ich han es rendezvous, es rendezvous mit em tod <br>Er staht vor minere tur meint mini zit sigi cho <br>Fur mich gsehts anderscht us <br>Ich han no einiges vor <br>Cih han no einiges vor <br><br>Hasch du z gfuhl will du promi bisch lass di schlufe <br>Ha ha ha da chasch di tusche <br>Ich sag weniger <br>Ich bin en junggselligge ledige typ <br>Und sott no so viel erledige <br>Ich han meh plan als en architakt <br>Z B Musikalisch no s paar projakt <br>E hubschi frau zwei chind oder meh <br>Es hus mit bootsalegeplatz am see <br><br>Hor jetzt z diskutiere, mach ja keis gezether <br>Mini fahre min frund lauft nach taxometer <br>Vergisses, was isch das Ich bi no viel z jung <br>De befehl chunt vo ganz obe Ja das isch tumm <br>Ich muss jedes waltwunder und jedes land gseh <br>Und uf de durch reis em dalai lama d hand geh <br>D rihanna no traffe mit ihre ga asse <br>Und si nachher #*and doffi ja nid vergasse <br><br>Ich han es rendezvous, es rendezvous mit em tod <br>Er staht vor minere tur meint mini zit sigi cho <br>Fur mich gsehts anderscht us <br>Ich han no einiges vor <br>Ich han no einiges vor <br><br>Sag dim chef er isch dr bescht <br>Aber holl der min nachber wo dauernd nur stresst <br>Mir argumentierent, es eskaliert <br>Er schiebt e krise und explodiert <br>Bisch du weich Was soll de scheiss <br>Er verlurt d beherschig und chlopft mer eis <br>De sensema het schlachti charte <br>Den er verspurt grad min rachte hagge <br><br>Ich han es rendezvous, es rendezvous mit em tod <br>Er staht vor minere tur meint mini zit sigi cho <br>Fur mich gsehts anderscht us <br>Ich han no einiges vor <br>Ich han no einiges vor <br><br>S isch wienen schlachte witz <br>Min kontrahent schlipft <br>I'm stagehus us <br>Und bricht sech z gnick <br>So isch es cho <br>De tod isch tot <br>Und waner nod hut chunt dann chunter morn]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Rendezvous" label="Rendezvous"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Fahr_E_Mal/</id><title>Bligg - Fahr E Mal - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:06:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:06:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Fahr_E_Mal/" title="Bligg - Fahr E Mal - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Das glaub ich nod, das isch nod wahr, was isch das fur en tubel <br>Wo zum teufel hatt da weichbacher sin fahruuswis nur gunne <br>Ja Rechts blinke, aber links fahre <br>Mein gott mini nerva <br>Ich ha ganz sicher bessers z'tue <br>Als dis nummereschild uswandig lerne <br><br>Eigentlich bin ich ganz nett und stahn uf harmonie <br>Hey Eigentlich halt ich nod vill vo sinnlosem schtriit <br>Hey Und eigentlich isch minereiner I'm reine mit mir <br>Aber sitz ich erscht mal hinterm stuur mutier ich zum tier <br><br>Fahr emal herrgott was isch nur los <br>Fahr emal ich krieg s'tourette syndrom <br>Fahr emal gruener chas nod werda <br>Fahr emal ich verluur grad mini nerva <br><br>Fahr mit dinere lauba <br>Das isch ja nod zum glauba <br>Parkiert da uf de autobahn oder wo hatt da sini auge <br>No bitzli langsamer und er wurd ruckwarts fahre <br>Mit sonere soifechischta mahied andri ihre rasa <br><br>Eigentlich bin ich ganz nett und stahn uf harmonie <br>Hey Eigentlich halt ich nod vill vo sinnlosem schtriit <br>Hey Und eigentlich isch minereiner I'm reine mit mir <br>Aber sitz ich erscht mal hinterm stuur mutier ich zum tier <br><br>Fahr emal herrgott was isch nur los <br>Fahr emal ich krieg s'tourette syndrom <br>Fahr emal gruener chas nod werda <br>Fahr emal ich verluur grad mini nerva <br><br>Gib gas, gib gas, gib gas, hey <br>Gib gas, gib gas, gib gas und fahr <br>Gib gas, gib gas, gib gas, hey <br>Gib gas, gib gas, gib gas und fahr <br>Gib gas, gib gas, gib gas, hey <br>Gib gas, gib gas, gib gas und fahr <br>Gib gas, gib gas, gib gas, hey <br>Gib gas, druck ufs pedal <br><br>Was macht da da Was isch da los <br>Hey Hey Gsehsch de finger <br>Chum zeig ich de mittelfinger da blinked d'warnblinker <br>De charre haltet, d'tuur gaht uf, es tont nach billy holiday <br>Er chunnt zu mir, grinst und seit Guete tag Polizei <br><br>Fahr emal herrgott was isch nur los <br>Fahr emal ich krieg s'tourette syndrom <br>Fahr emal gruener chas nod werda <br>Fahr emal ich verluur grad mini nerva <br><br>Fahr emal herrgott was isch nur los <br>Fahr emal ich krieg s'tourette syndrom <br>Fahr emal gruener chas nod werda <br>Fahr emal ich verluur grad mini nerva]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Fahr E Mal" label="Fahr E Mal"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Id_Kill_For_You_Feat_Jessy_Howe/</id><title>Bligg - I`d Kill For You (Feat. Jessy Howe) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:06:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:06:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Id_Kill_For_You_Feat_Jessy_Howe/" title="Bligg - I`d Kill For You (Feat. Jessy Howe) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ich hoff dir gahts guet und du hasch was du willsch <br>Jetzt gits keis zrugg meh s'isch alles verspillt <br>Bander sind grisse und d'brugga verbrannt <br>Eusi wag hand sich kruzt und dann wieder trannt <br>Ich chan ohni dich lacha, ohni dich bruella <br>Chan ohni dich sterba und es laba fuehre <br>Ohni dich schlafa au wanns tuppig isch <br>Aber chan ohni dich niemals glucklich si <br><br>I'd kill for you <br>I'd even die for you <br>You know no one can love you <br>As much as I do <br>Never gonna lie to you <br><br>I'd kill for you <br>My love will shine on you <br>You know no one can love you <br>As much as I do <br>Never gonna lie to you <br><br>Du hasch mich gfroget was ich lieb <br>Un dich han dir gseit Mis labe <br>Du bisch truurig devo gloffe <br>Aber du hasch nod verstande Mis labe bisch du <br><br>Hoffentlich gnusst er mis labe und schatzts <br>Ich hoff, das sin gschlachtsname mine ersetzt <br>Ich hoff er isst mit eusem bsteck <br>Und hoffentlich fuhlt er sich wohl I mim bett <br><br>Sag em, dass ich dich als frau nod verdient han <br>Sag em, dass ich dich I'm labe nie gliebt han <br>Sag em, ich wunsch eu nur s'gluck uf erde <br>Aber sag em nod, dass ich das sag unter trane <br><br>I'd kill for you <br>I'd even die for you <br>You know no one can love you <br>As much as I do <br>Never gonna lie to you <br><br>I'd kill for you <br>My love will shine on you <br>You know no one can love you <br>As much as I do <br>Never gonna lie to you <br><br>I never lie to you <br>I'd kill for you <br>I'd even die for you <br>You know no one can love you <br>As much as I do <br>Never gonna lie to you <br><br>I'd kill for you <br>My love will shine on you <br>You know no one can love you <br>As much as I do <br>Never gonna lie to you]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="I`d Kill For You (Feat. Jessy Howe)" label="I`d Kill For You (Feat. Jessy Howe)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Manhattan/</id><title>Bligg - Manhattan - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:06:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:06:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Manhattan/" title="Bligg - Manhattan - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Entweder Manhattan oder nod, Manhattan oder nod <br>S gaht bestimmt au ohni doch mit ihm is Lebe schon <br><br>Mode chamer chaufe aber Style das mumer ha <br>Was die eint vo beid im Usgang traget si zum schlafe a <br>Er versteckt sich i dim Chleiderschrank <br>Schliecht sich i din Wortschatz <br>Beiflusst dini Gangart und er luret ufem Parkplatz <br>Begleitet dich zur Arbet und chunt mit as nogste Date <br>Und entscheidet au gad selber schnell <br>obs seb isch was vergheit <br><br>Machs mit Style, Style oder lass es si <br>Style bringt dich as Ziel egal wo her egal wo hi <br>Ja Style muss si <br>Machs mit Style, Style oder lass es si <br>Style bringt dich as Ziel egal wo her egal wo hi <br>Ja Style muss si <br><br>Entweder Manhattan oder nod, Manhattan oder nod <br>Sgaht bestimmt au ohni doch mit ihm is Lebe schon <br><br>Er macht Party i dim iPod und fugiert als Undermieter <br>Macht sich breit uf dine Mobel wienen Konig und regiert det <br>Style chamer nod lerne nei Manhattan oder nod <br>Art und Charme und Umgangsform und sottigs ischer gfrogt <br>Er hat billione Gsichter aber eis das mumer sage <br>Es git leider viel zviel Lut dene ischer nie begegnet <br><br>Machs mit Style, Style oder lass es si <br>Style bringt dich as Ziel egal wo her egal wo hi <br>Ja Style muss si <br>Machs mit Style, Style oder lass es si <br>Style bringt dich as Ziel egal wo her egal wo hi <br>Ja Style muss si <br><br>Entweder Manhattan oder nod, Manhattan oder nod <br>Sgaht bestimmt au ohni doch mit ihm is Lebe schon <br><br>Es isch t'Art wiemer lauft wiemer denkt wiemer red <br>Wiemer isst, wiemer fahrt, wiemer sich chleidet und bewegt <br>Es isch t'Art wiemer lauft wiemer denkt wiemer red <br>Wiemer isst, wiemer fahrt, wiemer sich chleidet und bewegt <br><br>Entweder Manhattan oder nod, Manhattan oder nod <br>Sgaht bestimmt au ohni doch mit ihm is lebe schon <br><br>Entweder Manhattan oder nod x3 <br>Sgaht bestimmt au ohni doch mit ihm is Lebe schon]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Manhattan" label="Manhattan"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Annie_May/</id><title>Bligg - Annie May - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:06:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:06:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Annie_May/" title="Bligg - Annie May - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ich bin zu dere Party gange ohni Dis Ok Mami <br>Das tuet mer leid ich wunscht Du hettsch mich chonne gseh Mami <br>Ich han Din Rat befolgt <br><br>Kein tropfe Alkohol <br>Wann anderi Vodka trunke hand hatt Dini Tochter Cola gholt <br><br>Du hasch mer immer gseit da usse luured Gfahre <br>Und ich soll nod trinke wanni nacher no muss fahre <br>Und Du warsch so stolz uf mich <br>Bin suuber gsi vo Chopf bis Fuess <br>Obwohl all Andere gseit hand Annie nimm doch eis es chunt scho guet <br><br>Annie May, so jung und unschuldig <br>Annie May, warum a dem Dunnschtig <br>Annie May, was immer de Grund isch <br>Wo isch nur Gott gsi <br>Das isch nod okay <br><br>Annie May, so jung und unschuldig <br>Annie May, warum a dem Dunnschtig <br>Annie May, was immer de Grund isch <br>Wo isch nur Gott gsi <br>Das isch nod okay <br><br>Ich han alles richtig gmacht, dank jetzt nuut Schlachts naha <br>Glaub mir ich los uf Dich dann Du hasch immer Recht aha <br>Wo d'Party fertig gsi isch, sind die andere blibe <br>Ich han nur no tschuss gseit und bin sofort is Auto gschtige <br><br>Du hasch mich guet erzoge <br>Ufracht, lieb und warm <br>Ha nur no welle hei uf direktem Wag i Dini Arm <br>Ich bin losgfahre, gfahre uf nassem Teer <br>Doch da Wage uf da Gagefarbahn hatt mich nod gseh <br><br>Annie May, so jung und unschuldig <br>Annie May, warum a dem Dunnschtig <br>Annie May, was immer de Grund isch <br>Wo isch nur Gott gsi <br>das isch nod okay <br><br>Annie May, so jung und unschuldig <br>Annie May, warum a dem Dunnschtig <br>Annie May, was immer de Grund isch <br>Wo isch nur Gott gsi <br>Das isch nod okay <br><br>Er hat mich eifach uberfahre und jetzt ligg i uf dem Asphalt <br>uberall um mich isch Bluet <br>Mir isch so krass chalt <br>Ich ghor wie Polizei sait de Ander seg betrunke <br>Alles tut so weh alles wird so dunkel <br><br>Richt am Papi us isch lieb en <br>Gib mim Brueder en Kuss vo mir <br>De Chrankewage chunnt vill z'spat ich gseh scho s'wisse Liecht <br>E letschti Frag bevor ich abschied nimm vo Dir Mami <br>Ich han kein Tropfe trunke, wiso bin ich jetzt die wo stirbt Mami <br><br>So jung und unschuldig <br>Annie May, warum a dem Dunnschtig <br>Annie May, was immer de Grund isch <br>Wo isch nur Gott gsi <br>Das isch nod okay <br><br>Annie May, so jung und unschuldig <br>Annie May, warum a dem Dunnschtig <br>Annie May, was immer de Grund isch <br>Wo isch nur Gott gsi <br>Das isch nod okay <br><br>Oh Annie, oh oh oh Annie Annie]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Annie May" label="Annie May"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Stadt___Land/</id><title>Bligg - Stadt / Land - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:06:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:06:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Stadt___Land/" title="Bligg - Stadt / Land - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Die Einte hand s'Herz i de Stadt wieder anderi hands uf em Land <br>Am and vom Tag isch alles s'gliche, es existiert kei Wand <br>Kei Granza, kei Barriera, chumm mir gand eus d'Hand <br>Lass es eus wie d'Strasse mache, sie fuehrend zunenand <br><br>Ich nimm d'Autoschlussel und stieg i min Wage <br>Und fahr ohni Ziel dur d'Prarie mit mim Charre <br>Schieb aba, frischa Wind is Gsicht <br>Landluft macht erfinderisch <br>Ich lieb d'Liechter vo da City und Bergpanorama <br>Platz von ich gspielt han als Chind anno damals <br>Ich mag Action, ich mag Ruha <br>Ich han beid Extrem extrem i mim Bluet <br><br>Ufem Land Isch es gediege und es kannt au jede jede <br>mer begruesst sich uf de Strass <br>I de Stadt Gnusst mer Anonymitat <br>mer hatt alles was mer het da andauernd oppis gaht <br>Landeier und Grossstadt Models <br>wer mit Drack ruehrt verluut a Boda <br>De Kontonsgeischt chunnt bi Ziita <br>und Grosses verluhrt wer sich um Chlises schtriitet <br><br>Die Einte hand s'Herz i de Stadt wieder anderi hands uf em Land <br>Am and vom Tag isch alles s'gliche, es existiert kei Wand <br>Kei Granza, kei Barriera, chumm mir gand eus d'Hand <br>Lass es eus wie d'Strasse mache, sie fuehrend zunenand <br><br>Ich fahr vom Dschungel i d'Agglo dur d'Stadt i d'Provinz <br>Im Gsicht d'Sunne und im Rugge de Wind <br>uber Brugga und Viadukt, Berg und Pass <br>de See entlang a die schonschta Platz <br>Ich liebs wie sich d'Optik verschiebt <br>wahrend dem mer imC Cockpit regiert <br>Die Einte liebed d'Stadt, die Andere liebed s'Land <br>minereiner fuhlt sich uberall entspannt <br><br>Ufem Land Isch es gediege und es kannt au jede jede <br>mer begruesst sich uf de Strass <br>I de Stadt Gnusst mer Anonymitat <br>mer hatt alles was mer het da andauernd oppis gaht <br>Landeier und Grossstadt Models <br>wer mit Drack ruehrt verluut a Boda <br>De Kontonsgeischt chunnt bi Ziita <br>und Grosses verluhrt wer sich um Chlises schtriitet <br><br>Die Einte hand s'Herz i de Stadt wieder anderi hands uf em Land <br>Am and vom Tag isch alles s'gliche, es existiert kei Wand <br>Kei Granza, kei Barriera, chumm mir gand eus d'Hand <br>Lass es eus wie d'Strasse mache, sie fuehrend zunenand <br><br>Die Einte hand s'Herz i de Stadt wieder anderi hands uf em Land <br>Am and vom Tag isch alles s'gliche, es existiert kei Wand <br>Kei Granza, kei Barriera, chumm mir gand eus d'Hand <br>Lass es eus wie d'Strasse mache, sie fuehrend zunenand]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Stadt / Land" label="Stadt / Land"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Spiegel_Feat_Xavier_Naidoo/</id><title>Bligg - Spiegel (Feat. Xavier Naidoo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:06:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:06:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Spiegel_Feat_Xavier_Naidoo/" title="Bligg - Spiegel (Feat. Xavier Naidoo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wo isch s'and, wie wiit chommer gah <br>Wann bliibt euse wage stah <br>I'm himmel isch d'holl los, s'windet und ragned <br>Das hammer devo wammer immer nur nahmed <br><br>Chommer no in spiegel luege ohni eus z'schame <br>Oder sind eventuell eusi sinn scho vernabled <br>Vo droge und medis wo's eus z'viel devo gabed <br>Sie hand hand eus I'm griff, gorillas I'm nabel <br><br>Das macht angscht, raubt de verstand <br>Schweiss a de hand euses herz rast rasant <br>Rugge zur wand, ziehnd bilanz <br>Lauf wer chan Forrest gump <br><br>Mir hend <br>Kein respekt und keine liebe <br>Nur defekte sind uns geblieben <br>Wir meinen der tod wird dem leben weichen <br>Simmer scho z'blind fur die viele zeicha <br><br>Konnen wir noch in den spiegel sehn <br>Oder wurden wir auf knien gehn <br>War's ohne aufputschmittel wirklich schon <br>Werden wir deshalb alle zugedrohnt <br><br>Mir folged am trott, boxed mit gott <br>Fahred ohni limit und mir kanned kein stopp <br>Kanned kei granze und falled innes loch <br>Erlaged de gier wo scho ewig lockt <br><br>Es strebe nach gluck, ohni and <br>Wurklichs gluck isch wammers erkannt <br>Mer nahmed kei rucksicht s'wird langsam ang <br>Ich schetz so isch es, so isch de mansch <br><br>Ich richt das a eus, mich inklusiv <br>Alles wird besser doch alles bliibt glich <br>Mir chond d'walt nod andere, sie hat schluckweh <br>Aber chondere en chliine schupf geh <br>Mir hend <br>Kein respekt und keine liebe <br>Nur defekte sind uns geblieben <br>Wir meinen der tod wird dem leben weichen <br>Simmer scho z'blind fur die viele zeicha <br><br>Konnen wir noch in den spiegel sehn <br>Oder wurden wir auf knien gehn <br>War's ohne aufputschmittel wirklich schon <br>Werden wir deshalb alle zugedrohnt <br><br>Lasst uns in den spiegel sehn <br>Erkenn das kind in dir <br>Es ist liebenswert <br>Und es ist wild in dir <br>Das ist uberlebenswert <br>Doch sei nie blind in dir <br>Das war so verkehrt <br>Und nicht ehrenwert <br>Doch du bist ehrenwert <br><br>Konnen wir noch in den spiegel sehn <br>Oder wurden wir auf knien gehn <br>War's ohne aufputschmittel wirklich schon <br>Werden wir deshalb alle zugedrohnt <br>Konnen wir noch in den spiegel sehn <br>Oder wurden wir auf knien gehn <br>War's ohne aufputschmittel wirklich schon <br>Werden wir deshalb alle zugedrohnt <br><br>Mir chond d'walt nod andere, sie hat schluckweh <br>Sie hat schluckwen <br>Mir chond d'walt nod andere, sie hat schluckweh <br>Sie hat schluckweh <br>Aber chondere en chliine schupf geh <br>Mir chond d'walt nod andere, sie hat schluckweh <br>Aber chondere en chliine schupf geh]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Spiegel (Feat. Xavier Naidoo)" label="Spiegel (Feat. Xavier Naidoo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Romeo__Julia/</id><title>Bligg - Romeo &amp; Julia - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:06:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:06:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Romeo__Julia/" title="Bligg - Romeo &amp; Julia - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Du bisch mini Lady, Baby <br>mir ghored zeme wie Adam and Eva oder Donald Duck und Daisy <br>Die Schone und das Biest <br><br>Beyonce, Jay Z <br>fascht so glamouros wie Victoria David <br>Tarzan und Jane <br>en Hit und Charts <br>wie Roger und Mirka oder Homer und Marge <br>Fascht wie Oli Pocher und Sandy Meyer Wolden <br>nur es paar Meter cooler und um einiges schoner <br><br>Ich bin din King <br>du bisch min Kong <br>Ich bin din Artist <br>du bisch min Song <br>Wann ich dis Ying bin <br>bisch du mis Yang <br>Lass eus alt und fett und hasslich werde aber Hauptsach mitenand <br><br>Mir zwei sind cooler als <br>cooler als Romeo und Julia <br>Ich bliib bi dir wie es Tattoo am Arm <br>Mir gond as and nur bringt eus usenand <br><br>Mir sind wie MrBig und Carry <br>Russel Brand und Katy Perry <br>Al und Peggy <br>oder Clever und Smart <br>Ich bin de Takt du bisch d'Melodie wie Brangelina <br>Strelanie <br>Wann du Camilla bisch, bin ich Charles <br>Eso wies d'Michelle und Barack oder Harry und Sally sind <br>Marilyn Monroe und John F Kennedy <br>Ich chonnt no locker uber hundert sonig Name nanne <br>doch ich glaub es isch klar Mir ghored zamme <br><br>Ich bin s'Benzin <br>du bisch s'Fuur <br>Wann ich dis Ying bin <br>bisch du mis Yang <br>Lass eus alt und fett und hasslich werde Hauptsach mitenand <br><br>Mir zwei sind cooler als <br>cooler als Romeo und Julia <br>Ich bliib bi dir wie es Tattoo am Arm <br>Mir gond as and nur bringt eus usenand <br><br>Du du du und ich <br>Mir mir gond as and <br><br>Mir zwei sind cooler als <br>cooler als Romeo und Julia <br>Ich bliib bi dir wie es Tattoo am Arm <br>Mir gond as and nur bringt eus usenand <br><br>Cooler als Romeo und Julia <br>Mir zwei sind cooler als Romeo und Julia]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Romeo &amp; Julia" label="Romeo &amp; Julia"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Leganda__Helda/</id><title>Bligg - Leganda &amp; Helda - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:06:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:06:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Leganda__Helda/" title="Bligg - Leganda &amp; Helda - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Mir gand Bluet, Schweiss und Trane fur die Walt <br>Dur Niederlag und Sieg, bis as bittre and <br>Blatere a de Hand, Schlachte ufem Fald <br>Gfuehrt vo Gottes Hand und schaffed Fundamant <br>Kampfed gage angst, Parole a de Wand <br>Bis i all Ewigkeit staht es Monumant <br>Es Labe im Momant, wo zu asche vebrannt <br>Und isches nod furd Zuekunft, fur was isches dann <br><br>S gaht berguf, s gaht bergab <br>S isch en lange Pfad, wo ois belehrt wie Galilleo eo eo eo <br>Sie gond dur Sturm und Gwitter fur oisi Tradition <br>Dann ihri Helda vo hut sind t Leganda vo morn <br>Sie werdet t Flagge hisse, kampfed fur ihren Thron <br>Und schaffed so es Fundamant fur die nogst Generation <br><br>Oisi Tate vo hut sind Gschichte vo morn <br>Vo Muetter zu Tochter, vo Vater zu Sohn <br>Mir schaffed fude Lohn, kampfed um de Thron <br>Frassed Staub und Drack fur t Statussymbol <br>Mit bisse und pickle, isch t Granze de Himmel <br>Was elei nod gat, chommer zame erklimme <br>Im Krisegebiet us Liebi und Chrieg <br>Helda labed lang doch Legande sterbed nie <br>S gaht berguf, s gaht bergab <br>S isch en lange Pfad, wo ois belehrt wie Galilleo eo eo eo <br>Sie gond dur Sturm und Gwitter fur oisi Tradition <br>Dann ihri Helda vo hut sind t Leganda vo morn <br>Sie werdet t Flagge hisse, kampfed fur ihren Thron <br>Und schaffed so es Fundamant fur die nogst Generation <br><br>Schnaufen 4x hahahaha <br>Ooh ooh ooh oohooh <br><br>Sie gond dur Sturm und Gwitter fur oisi Tradition <br>Dann ihri Helda vo hut sind t Leganda vo morn <br>Sie werded t Flagge hisse, kampfed fur ihren Thron <br>Und schaffed so s Fundamant fur die nochst Generatioohoohoohoon <br>Legande vo Moohoohoorn Legande vo Moohoorn <br>Sind t Legande vo <br>MORN]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Leganda &amp; Helda" label="Leganda &amp; Helda"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Chef/</id><title>Bligg - Chef - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:06:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:06:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Chef/" title="Bligg - Chef - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wo Gott als Menschearchitekt <br>Menschekorper gschaffe hett <br>Hett jedes Korperteil wolle Chef sii <br>S'Hirn hett gsait ich lenke alles <br>Und ich denk zu allem ane <br>Isch jo logisch dass ich de Chef bi <br>Do chommed d'Fuess <br>Und meined, ein Moment <br>Schliesslich traged mir de Mensch <br>Ohni eus lauft ja wohl gar nut <br>Die beide Hand finded das unverschamt <br>Wer macht di ganzi Arbet denn <br>Hored uf de Fall isch doch klar Lut <br>Das gsehmer denn schreied d'Auge <br>Mached mal e churzi Pause <br>Mir sinds wo eu zeiged wo dure <br>Isch doch logisch dass mir Chef sind <br>Besser als de Rest sind <br>Oh mann das gseht doch jede Tubel <br><br>Chef, sie sind de Best <br>Schon dass sie git <br>Ohni sie war mis Lebe so trist <br>Sie sind de Best <br>So dynanisch und nett <br>So sympathisch und frisch <br>Chef <br><br>Und so chommed au no d'Ohre <br>Herz und Lunge und oh wunder <br>Zu gueter Letst naturli no s'Arschloch <br>Es gseht sich i de Chefetage <br>Das bringt anderi in Rage <br>Und sie finded einstimmig Gahts no <br>S'Arschloch hett sich eng verschlosse <br>Und mol ebe schnell beschlosse <br>Bis uf wiiters numm z'funktioniere <br>Uf zmol schieled d'Auge <br>Fuess sind Schwach <br>S'Herz rast <br>D'Hand schlaff <br>S'Hirni hett i hochem Grad Fieber <br>Die ganz Abteilig Korperteil <br>Finds gad langsam numm so geil <br>In Wahrheit, sie kampfed ums Lebe <br>Und bevors bitter wird <br>Gebeds uf und bittets Hirn <br>S'Arschloch zum Chef z'ernenne <br><br>Chef, sie sind de Best <br>Schon dass sie git <br>Ohni sie war mis Lebe so trist <br>Sie sind de Best <br>So dynanisch und nett <br>So sympathisch und frisch <br>Chef <br><br>Und so isches denn au worde <br>S'Arschloch isch zum Chef erkore <br>Obwohl das niemertem richtig wohl isch <br>Alli andere mached d'arbet <br>Es kommandiert bloss nur ume <br>Und git en huufe Scheisse vor sich <br>Moral vo dere Gschicht isch <br>Falls du jemols wotsch Chef sii <br>Bruchsch du huttzutags e kas Machtwort <br>Nai du bruchsch kai Kompetenze <br>Und du bruchsch kei Fachwusse <br>Alles was du musch sii isch es Arschloch <br><br>Chef, sie sind de Best <br>Schon dass sie git <br>Ohni sie war mis Lebe so trist <br>Sie sind de Best <br>So dynanisch und nett <br>So sympathisch und frisch <br>Chef <br>Schon dass sie git <br>Ohni sie war mis Lebe so trist <br>So dynanisch und nett <br>So sympathisch und frisch <br>Chef <br>Schon dass sie git <br>Ohni sie war mis Lebe so trist <br>So dynanisch und nett <br>So sympathisch und frisch <br>Oh Chef]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Chef" label="Chef"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Exklusiv_Introview_Feat_Samurai/</id><title>Bligg - Exklusiv Introview (Feat. Samurai) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:06:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:06:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bligg/Exklusiv_Introview_Feat_Samurai/" title="Bligg - Exklusiv Introview (Feat. Samurai) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hallo Bligg, schon dass dir ziit nimmsch fur das Interview Meeting <br>Ready <br>Ready <br><br>Mir nameds mit Ton uf <br>Ok <br>Die ganz Schwiiz isch gspannt wie e Vorhuut <br>Erschti Frag Warum BART ABER HERZLICH <br>So bin ich, Punkt, aus fertig <br>Ok Was erwarted eus uf dem Album <br>Loses bis zum End und du ghorsch was da chunnt <br>Mhm dis letschte isch 4 Fach Platin, bi somene <br>Erfolg isch de Druck doch Wahnsinn <br>Grober Ich bin dur d'Holl und wider zrugg <br>und han alles was i han inegeh i jedes Stuck <br>Sag wie isch das Schribsch dini Text all selber <br>Nei, ich han en Schwarzarbeiter i mim Challer <br>Aso guet Spass beiseite, Ja naturlich <br>Dich kannt jedi Sau, wie isch das fur dich <br>Ganz ehrlich Mir isch das nod so wohl <br>Dann ich chum mer amigs vor wie es Tier im Zoo <br>Aber jetzt kokettiersch hasch's ja welle eso oder <br>Welle scho aber nie so gross <br><br>Er schriibt die Ziile mit sim Bluet <br>Nimm ruhig Platz und luegem zue <br>Gseh dia Welt dur sini Auge <br>Chumm und lauf i sine Schueh <br><br>Isch das no Rap was du machsch oder fahrsch ez x spurig <br>Nanneds wieners wannd, isch nanns BLIGG MUSIGG <br>Fur die wibliche Fans, wie eroberet sie dich <br>Ha uberhaupt nod, ich erobere sie <br>Hasch scho mal oppis bereut, wann ja was isch das <br>Ich han kei Schiss z'bereue <br>Bereue Schiss z'ha <br>Dini beschte Frunde <br>Das isch Privat <br>Dini groschte Feinde <br>Ouh, noggschti Frag <br>Und vor was hasch Angscht <br>Z'verluure was i han <br>Angscht dass ich irgendwenn mal unheilbar erchrank <br>Welli Comic Figur representiert dis Labe <br> hmm Spiderman, Peter Parker wuri sage <br>Chumm, verrat eus es Gheimniss, was vo dir <br>Sie hand mer Aafang vo dem Jahr d'Stimmbander operiert <br>Und ich han ehrlich gseit nod gwusst ob mit dem <br>Album oppis wird, oder ob am Bligg sini Karriere sogar stirbt <br><br>Er schriibt die Ziile mit sim Bluet <br>Nimm ruhig Platz und luegem zue <br>Gseh dia Welt dur sini Auge <br>Chumm und lauf i sine Schueh <br><br>BART ABER HERZLICH, willkomme zu minere neue Show sehr geehrti <br>Dame und Herre <br>Nehmed Platz <br>Ich wird oft aagsproche in letschter Ziit uf min Erfolg <br>Bligg din Erfolg da din Erfolg det <br>Ha Es schint als hetted sie vergasse um was es wurklich gaht Musigg <br><br>Er schriibt die Ziile mit sim Bluet <br>Nimm ruhig Platz und luegem zue <br>Gseh dia Welt dur sini Auge <br>Chumm und lauf i sine Schueh <br><br>Bligg Blizo]]></content><category term="Bligg" label="Bligg"/><category term="Exklusiv Introview (Feat. Samurai)" label="Exklusiv Introview (Feat. Samurai)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CPM22/Conta_Comigo/</id><title>CPM22 - Conta Comigo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:07:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:07:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CPM22/Conta_Comigo/" title="CPM22 - Conta Comigo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sempre com muita fe, suor e sacrificio <br>O caminho a verdade nos mantem <br>Seguir com os pes no chao, alta fidelidade <br>Nossa dignidade manter nosso respeito e importante <br>Penso nisso toda tarde, todo dia, toda hora todo instante <br><br>Um pouco se perdeu <br>Guardei o que brilhou daquele monte <br>Cuidei pra nao morrer <br>Plantei cada semente no horizonte, me ouve <br>Eu quero levar voce comigo <br><br>Sabemos bem a vida nao ta facil <br>Mas com sinceridade lembrar do que passou e empolgante <br>Me faz acreditar temos que nos dar mais uma chance <br><br>Um pouco se perdeu <br>Guardei o que brilhou daquele monte <br>Cuidei pra nao morrer <br>Plantei cada semente no horizonte, me ouve <br>Eu quero levar voce comigo <br>Eu quero levar voce]]></content><category term="CPM22" label="CPM22"/><category term="Conta Comigo" label="Conta Comigo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Assim_Assim/</id><title>Zizi_Possi - Assim, Assim - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:08:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:08:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Assim_Assim/" title="Zizi_Possi - Assim, Assim - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sinceramente, nao vou ficar <br>Passando a limpo meu coracao <br>Roendo as unhas, pensando em voz alta <br>Botando os pingos nos is <br><br>Falando serio eu ja cansei <br>De revirar minhas emocoes <br>De vasculhar as gavetas <br>Do armario embutido da nossa paixao <br>Beijos, estou de saida <br>Vou reinventar minha vida <br>Vida, vida <br>Eu preciso viver <br>Hei, amiga <br>Pra que disfarcar nossa solidao <br><br>Se continuasse assim, assim <br>Um dia a gente ia terminar <br>Saindo pela tangente <br>Ou desidratado de tanto chorar <br><br>Na certa ainda vais remexer <br>Nisso ou naquilo ate concordar <br>Que o nosso erro foi nao conjugar <br>Aos limites o verbo amar <br><br>Registra minha partida <br>No arquivo da tua vida <br><br>Vida, vida <br>Eu preciso viver <br>Hei, amiga <br>Pra que disfarcar nossa solidao]]></content><category term="Zizi Possi" label="Zizi Possi"/><category term="Assim, Assim" label="Assim, Assim"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Balao_Balao/</id><title>Zizi_Possi - Balao, Balao - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:08:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:08:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Balao_Balao/" title="Zizi_Possi - Balao, Balao - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ceu <br>Balao, balao <br>Uma cancao <br>Depois dormir <br>Meu coracao <br>Espera tanto <br>Tanto <br>Eu me entreguei <br>E isso e bom <br>Deixo o amor entrar em mim <br>Como esse ceu <br>Permite o instante de um balao <br>Ainda que sendo <br>Temporariamente]]></content><category term="Zizi Possi" label="Zizi Possi"/><category term="Balao, Balao" label="Balao, Balao"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Eu_Velejava_Em_Voce/</id><title>Zizi_Possi - Eu Velejava Em Voce - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:08:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:08:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Eu_Velejava_Em_Voce/" title="Zizi_Possi - Eu Velejava Em Voce - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Eu velejava em voce <br>Nao finja <br>Como coisa que nao me ve <br>E foge de mim <br>A boca tremia <br>Os olhos ardiam <br>Oh Doce agonia <br>Oh Dor de viver <br>De ver sua imagem <br>Que eu nunca via <br>Sua boca molhada <br>Seu olhar assanhado <br>Convite pra se perder <br>Minha alma cansada <br>Nao faz cerimonia <br>Voce pode entrar sem bater <br>Pois eu ja velejei em voce <br>E foi bom de doer <br>Mas foi, como sempre, um sonho <br>Tao longe, risonho <br>Sinto falta <br>Queria lhe ver]]></content><category term="Zizi Possi" label="Zizi Possi"/><category term="Eu Velejava Em Voce" label="Eu Velejava Em Voce"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Agora_So_Falta_Voce/</id><title>Zizi_Possi - Agora So Falta Voce - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:08:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:08:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Agora_So_Falta_Voce/" title="Zizi_Possi - Agora So Falta Voce - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Um belo dia resolvi mudar <br>E fazer tudo o que eu queria fazer <br>Me libertei daquela vida vulgar <br>Que eu levava estando junto a voce <br>E em tudo que eu faco <br>Existe um porque <br>Eu sei que eu nasci <br>Sei que eu nasci pra saber <br><br>E fui andando sem pensar em voltar <br>E sem ligar pro que me aconteceu <br>Um belo dia vou lhe telefonar <br>Pra lhe dizer que aquele sonho cresceu <br>No ar que eu respiro <br>Eu sinto prazer <br>De ser quem eu sou <br>De estar onde estou <br>Agora so falta voce <br>Agora so falta voce <br><br>Um belo dia resolvi mudar <br>E fazer tudo o que eu queria fazer <br>Me libertei daquela vida vulgar <br>Que eu levava estando junto a voce <br>E em tudo que eu faco <br>Existe um porque <br>Eu sei que eu nasci <br>Eu sei que eu nasci pra saber <br>Saber o que <br><br>E fui andando sem pensar em voltar <br>E sem ligar pro que me aconteceu <br>Um belo dia vou lhe telefonar <br>Pra lhe dizer que aquele sonho cresceu <br>No ar que eu respiro <br>Eu sinto prazer <br>De ser quem eu sou <br>De estar onde estou <br>Agora so falta voce <br>Agora so falta voce <br>Agora so falta voce <br>Agora so falta voce <br><br>No ar que eu respiro <br>Eu sinto prazer <br>De ser quem eu sou <br>De estar onde estou <br>Agora so falta voce <br>Agora so falta voce <br>Agora so falta voce <br>Agora so falta voce]]></content><category term="Zizi Possi" label="Zizi Possi"/><category term="Agora So Falta Voce" label="Agora So Falta Voce"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Engracadinha/</id><title>Zizi_Possi - Engracadinha - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:08:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:08:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Engracadinha/" title="Zizi_Possi - Engracadinha - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nua <br>Dentro do quarto <br>Dentro do espelho <br>Sou toda tua <br>Mas nao es so meu <br>Pois me seduzes <br>Mas me desprezas <br>Apago as luzes <br>a tua espera <br>Te ensino amar <br>E a malquerer <br>O amor tao virgem, principiante e eu <br>Tao sabia amante <br><br>A te chamar <br>Oculta femea <br>Engracadinha <br>Sabes meu nome <br>Pois es meu homem <br>E tambem es minha mulher <br>O amor antigo verdejante e eu <br>Tao tola amante <br>A te esperar <br>Inutilmente]]></content><category term="Zizi Possi" label="Zizi Possi"/><category term="Engracadinha" label="Engracadinha"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Ca_Entre_Nos/</id><title>Zizi_Possi - Ca Entre Nos - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:08:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:08:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Ca_Entre_Nos/" title="Zizi_Possi - Ca Entre Nos - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ca entre nos <br>Luz demais pode cegar <br>Se voce aceitar esse fim <br>Nao sera mais para mim <br>O alguem que eu sempre quis <br><br>Seja feliz <br>Pra que medo de errar <br><br>O seu tempo para me entender <br>Nao e maior que o meu pra te descrer <br><br>Como lutar contra a mare, nao sei <br>Esse engano e so seu <br>Descubra se quiser, se puder, se souber <br>Eu nada perderei <br>So lhe transformarei <br>No sempre eu nao quis]]></content><category term="Zizi Possi" label="Zizi Possi"/><category term="Ca Entre Nos" label="Ca Entre Nos"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Meio-Dia/</id><title>Zizi_Possi - Meio-Dia - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:08:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:08:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Meio-Dia/" title="Zizi_Possi - Meio-Dia - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[e meio dia <br>Nao se deve mais falar <br>Das feridas que a noite inventou <br>e meio dia <br>Nao se deve lamentar <br>As armadilhas de quem diz que tem amor <br><br>Voce foi a calmaria das lagoas <br>Mas agora e terremoto <br>Nas raizes dos meus sonhos <br><br>Voce foi e e porque sabe do caminho <br>Mas nao pense mais no brilho <br>Que brilhava em meu olhar]]></content><category term="Zizi Possi" label="Zizi Possi"/><category term="Meio-Dia" label="Meio-Dia"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Caminhos_Do_Sol/</id><title>Zizi_Possi - Caminhos Do Sol - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:08:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:08:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zizi_Possi/Caminhos_Do_Sol/" title="Zizi_Possi - Caminhos Do Sol - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sem voce a vida pode parecer <br>Um porto alem de mim <br>Coracao sangrando <br>Caminhos de sol no fim <br><br>Nada resta mas o fruto que se tem <br>e o bastante pra querer <br>Um minuto alem <br>Do que eu possa andar com voce <br><br>Te amo e o tempo nao varreu isso de mim <br>Por isso estou partido <br>E tao forte assim <br><br>O amor fez parte <br>De tudo que nos guiou <br>Na inocencia cega <br>No risco das palavras e ate no risco da palavra Amor <br><br>Nada resta mas o fruto que se tem <br>e o bastante pra querer <br>Um minuto alem <br>Do que eu possa andar com voce <br><br>Te amo e o tempo nao varreu isso de mim <br>Por isso estou partido <br>E tao forte assim <br><br>O amor fez parte <br>De tudo que nos guiou <br>Na inocencia cega <br>No risco das palavras e ate no risco da palavra Amor <br><br>O amor fez parte <br>De tudo que nos guiou <br>Na inocencia cega <br>No risco das palavras e ate no risco da palavra Amor]]></content><category term="Zizi Possi" label="Zizi Possi"/><category term="Caminhos Do Sol" label="Caminhos Do Sol"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Moritz_Garth/Auf_Repeat/</id><title>Moritz_Garth - Auf Repeat - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Moritz_Garth/Auf_Repeat/" title="Moritz_Garth - Auf Repeat - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[wenn wir mal eins und eins zusammen zahln <br>passt bei uns nicht viel <br>wenn du diskutieren willst <br>dann bin ich lieber still <br>sind wir ehrlich miteinander verstehts immer einer falsch <br>du willst alles jetzt und heute <br>ich verschiebs dann mal auf bald <br>es sind hundert tausend Stucke <br>von dem Puzzle doch nichts passt <br>sag mir finden wir am ende fur jedes einen platz <br>und ich weiss ich weiss nicht viel <br>doch scheiss egal was jetzt passiert <br>solang ich dih hab hb ich zu viel zu verliern <br>Jeder ton von diesem Lied machts zu unsrer Melodie <br>na na na <br>na na na <br>und klingts auch noch so schief <br>manchmal konnen wirs nicht mehr horen doch dann beginnt wieder der Beat <br>na na na <br>na na na <br>ich druck einfach repeat <br>na na na <br>na na na <br>ich druck einfach repeat <br>na na na <br>na na na <br>du bist ein fruher vogel und ich verschlafe gern den tag <br>hau noch funf mal auf een Wecker <br>doch du bist gleich am Start <br>druckst das Gaspedal ganz durch <br>linke Spur der Autobahn <br>steck ich in der Einbahnstrasse <br>hab mich wieder mal verfahren <br>jede Hohe jede tiefe macht aus uns Musik <br>du horst lieber Klassik ich juju on the beat <br>und ich weiss ich weiss nicht viel <br>doch scheiss egal was jetzt passiert <br>solang ich dih hab hb ich zu viel zu verliern <br>Jeder ton von diesem Lied machts zu unsrer Melodie <br>na na na <br>na na na <br>und klingts auch noch so schief <br>manchmal konnen wirs nicht mehr horen doch dann beginnt wieder der Beat <br>na na na <br>na na na <br>ich druck einfach repeat <br>na na na <br>na na na <br>ich druck einfach repeat <br>na na na <br>na na na <br>zu lange schon versucht den staub um uns einzufangen <br>festgefahren auf Gefuhlen zieht siemich in ihren Bann <br>liebe die nicht wehtut <br>gibt's das uberhaupt <br>egal wir holen das beste raus <br>Jeder ton von diesem Lied machts zu unsrer Melodie <br>na na na <br>na na na <br>und klingts auch noch so schief <br>manchmal konnen wirs nicht mehr horen doch dann beginnt wieder der Beat <br>na na na <br>na na na <br>ich druck einfach repeat <br>na na na <br>na na na <br>ich druck einfach repeat <br>na na na <br>na na na <br>ich druck einfach repeat]]></content><category term="Moritz Garth" label="Moritz Garth"/><category term="Auf Repeat" label="Auf Repeat"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Im_Going_Back_Home_Album_Ver/</id><title>Nina_Simone - I`m Going Back Home (Album Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Im_Going_Back_Home_Album_Ver/" title="Nina_Simone - I`m Going Back Home (Album Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm going back home where I was born <br>First I planned to stay but I can't live this way <br>I'm going back home where I was born <br><br>Try to understand I think this city's grand <br>But with all its charme give me the little country farm <br>I'm going back home where I was born <br><br>Oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah now oh yeah <br>I tell you all about it I think you ought to know <br>Tell you all about it why I wanna go <br><br>I miss the country preacher and the house of prayer <br>I miss the bootlegger smelling in the air <br>Miss friendly faces and the country smiles <br>The crickets singing you can hear it for miles <br><br>Miss the rooster crowing at the break of dawn <br>Yes it all happens where I was born <br>Miss the fried chicken colored greens <br>Miss the hot biscuits and the lima beans <br>Miss the prayer meeting where the people pray <br>With the drum beating till the break of day <br><br>You can have it you can have it <br>You can have it you can have it <br>You can have thy town I won't be around <br>This here life's too fast but 'll never never last <br><br>I'm going back home where I was born <br>I got to go home got to go home <br>Where the people are real people can feel <br>Got to go down got to go down <br>Leave here today on my way so long so long <br>Going back home going back home <br>Got to go home got to go home <br>Got to go home got to go home <br>Where I where I was born]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="I`m Going Back Home (Album Ver.)" label="I`m Going Back Home (Album Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/The_Gal_From_Joes_Album_Ver/</id><title>Nina_Simone - The Gal From Joe`s (Album Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/The_Gal_From_Joes_Album_Ver/" title="Nina_Simone - The Gal From Joe`s (Album Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Way down at Mister Joe's Cafe <br>They're takin' someone far away <br>And if you hear a song today <br>It's a sad tune that you'll be playin' <br>She's leavin' and folks are feelin' so low <br>They're grievin' and they're consolin' poor Joe <br><br>Gonna miss her song <br>Gonna miss her smile <br>She'll be travlin' alone down <br>That last long mile <br>They're sighin' <br>With all thei trouble and woes <br>They're Cryin' 'cause they all loved <br>The gal from Joe's]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="The Gal From Joe`s (Album Ver.)" label="The Gal From Joe`s (Album Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Marriage_Is_For_Old_Folks_Album_Ver/</id><title>Nina_Simone - Marriage Is For Old Folks (Album Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Marriage_Is_For_Old_Folks_Album_Ver/" title="Nina_Simone - Marriage Is For Old Folks (Album Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I love dancing <br>Crazy romancing <br>Fellas advancing constantly <br><br>Marriage is for old folks <br>Old folks, not for me <br>One husband <br>One wife <br>Whaddya got <br>Two people sentenced for life <br><br>I love singing <br>Good healthy clinging <br>Quietly bringing on a spree <br><br>Marriage is for old folks <br>Cold folks <br>One married he <br>One married she <br>Whaddya got <br>Two people watchin' tv <br><br>I'm not ready <br>To quit bein' free <br>And I'm not willing <br>To stop being me <br>I've gotta sing my song <br>Why should I belong <br>To some guy who says <br>That I'm wrong <br><br>Doo doo dooo <br>De doo de doo <br>De doo de doo <br>Doo doo doo <br>Dooo <br><br>Cookin' dinner <br>Lookin' no thinner <br>Gray elbows and <br>A sudsy sea <br><br>Marriage is for old folks <br>Cold folks <br>And it's not for me <br>One husband <br>One wife <br>Whaddya got <br>Two people sentenced for life <br><br>I'm exploding <br>With youth and with zest <br>Who needs corroding <br>In some vulture's nest <br>I've gotta fly my wings <br>Go places, do things <br>My freedom bell's really <br>Gonna ring <br><br>Doo doo doooetc <br><br>I've been through years <br>Too many blue years <br>Now I want New Year's every eve <br><br>Marriage is for old folks <br>Marriage is for cold folks <br>One husband <br>One wife <br>Whaddya got <br>Two people sentenced for life <br><br>Marriage is for old folks <br>Marriage is for cold folks <br>Not for me <br>Can't you see <br>Marriage ain't for me]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="Marriage Is For Old Folks (Album Ver.)" label="Marriage Is For Old Folks (Album Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Brown_Eyed_Handsome_Man_Album_Ver/</id><title>Nina_Simone - Brown Eyed Handsome Man (Album Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Brown_Eyed_Handsome_Man_Album_Ver/" title="Nina_Simone - Brown Eyed Handsome Man (Album Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Arrested on charges of unemployment <br>He was sitting in the witness stand <br>The judge's wife called up the district attorney <br>Said you free that brown eyed man <br>You want your job you better free that brown eyed man <br><br>Flying across the desert in a TWA <br>I saw a woman walking across the sand <br>She been a walkin' thirty miles en route to Bombay <br>To get a brown eyed handsome man <br>Her destination was a brown eyed handsome man <br><br>Way back in history three thousand years <br>Back every since the world began <br>There's been a whole lot of good women shed a tear <br>For a brown eyed handsome man <br>That's what the trouble was brown eyed handsome man <br><br>Beautiful daughter couldn't make up her mind <br>Between a doctor and a lawyer man <br>Her mother told her daughter go out and find yourself <br>A brown eyed handsome man <br>That's what your daddy is a brown eyed handsome man <br><br>Milo Venus was a beautiful lass <br>She had the world in the palm of her hand <br>But she lost both her arms in a wrestling match <br>To get brown eyed handsome man <br>She fought and won herself a brown eyed handsome man <br><br>Two, three count with nobody on <br>He hit a high fly into the stand <br>Rounding third he was headed for home <br>It was a brown eyed handsome man <br>That won the game it was a brown eyed handsome man]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="Brown Eyed Handsome Man (Album Ver.)" label="Brown Eyed Handsome Man (Album Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Mood_Indigo_Album_Ver/</id><title>Nina_Simone - Mood Indigo (Album Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Mood_Indigo_Album_Ver/" title="Nina_Simone - Mood Indigo (Album Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You ain't never been blue, no, no, no <br>You ain't never been blue <br>Till you've had that mood indigo <br>That feeling goes stealing right down to my shoes <br>While I just sit here and sigh <br>Go along blues <br><br>I always get that mood indigo <br>Since my baby said goodbye <br>And in the evening when the lights are low <br>I'm so lonely I could cry <br>For there's nobody who cares about me <br>I'm just a poor fool that's bluer than blue can be <br>When I get that mood indigo <br>I could lay me down and die <br><br>You ain't been blue, no, no, no <br>You ain't never been blue <br>Till you've had that mood indigo <br>That feeling goes stealing right down to my shoes <br>While I just sit here and sigh <br>Go along blues]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="Mood Indigo (Album Ver.)" label="Mood Indigo (Album Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Nobody_Knows_You_When_Youre_Down_And_Out_Live_In_New_York___1965/</id><title>Nina_Simone - Nobody Knows You When You`re Down And Out (Live In New York / 1965) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Nobody_Knows_You_When_Youre_Down_And_Out_Live_In_New_York___1965/" title="Nina_Simone - Nobody Knows You When You`re Down And Out (Live In New York / 1965) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well once I lived the life of a millionaire <br>Spending my money, I didn't care <br>Takin' my friends out for a mighty good time <br>Buyin' boot leg liquor, champagne and wine <br>Then I began to fall so low <br>Couldn't find me no friends <br>Had no place to go <br>If I ever get my hands on a dollar again <br>I'm gonna hold on to it, till the eagle grins <br><br>I said nobody knows you <br>When you're down and out <br>In your pocket, you ain't got one penny <br>And your friends, you didn't have any <br>Just as soon as you get up on your feet again <br>Here they all come, they say that they're your long lost friend <br>Oh lord without a doubt <br>Nobody wants you <br>Nobody needs you <br>Nobody wants you <br>When you're down and out <br><br>I say <br><br>Nobody wants you <br>Nobody needs you <br>Nobody wants you when you're down and out]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="Nobody Knows You When You`re Down And Out (Live In New York / 1965)" label="Nobody Knows You When You`re Down And Out (Live In New York / 1965)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Tomorrow_Is_My_Turn_Album_Ver/</id><title>Nina_Simone - Tomorrow Is My Turn (Album Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Tomorrow_Is_My_Turn_Album_Ver/" title="Nina_Simone - Tomorrow Is My Turn (Album Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Though some may reach for the stars <br>Others will end behind bars <br>What the future has in store no one ever knows before <br>Yet we would all like the right to find the key to success <br>That elusive ray of light that will lead to happiness <br>Tomorrow is my turn <br>No more doubts no more fears <br>Tomorrow is my turn <br>When my luck is returning <br>All these years I've been learning to save fingers from burning <br>Tomorrow is my turn <br>No more doubts no more fears <br>Tomorrow is my turn to receive without giving <br>Make life worth living <br>Now it's my life I'm living <br>My only concern for tomorrow is my turn <br>Now the summer is gone, there's another to come <br>You can't stop years from drifting by even if you want to try <br>Though time may help you forget all that has happened before <br>But honey it's too late to regret what is gone will be no more <br>Tomorrow is my turn <br>When my luck is returning <br>All these years I've been learning to save fingers from burning <br>Tomorrow is my turn <br>No more doubts no more fears <br>Tomorrow is my turn to receive without giving <br>Make life worth living <br>Now it's my life I'm living <br>My only concern for tomorrow is my turn]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="Tomorrow Is My Turn (Album Ver.)" label="Tomorrow Is My Turn (Album Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/How_Can_I_/</id><title>Nina_Simone - How Can I? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/How_Can_I_/" title="Nina_Simone - How Can I? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How can I help but love you <br>Help but want you <br>Help but need you <br>How can I hide this feeling <br>Feeling as I do <br><br>How can I make you see me <br>Make you to me <br>Take you to me <br>And I <br>How can I pic the secret <br>It's so plan to see <br><br>Be mine, please be mine, my darling <br>I can't ask nothing more <br>Be mine, please be mine, my darling <br>You're the one I adore <br><br>How can I help but love you <br>Help but want you <br>Help but need you <br>I have one wish <br>I'm wishing only love me too <br><br>How can I make you see me <br>Wake you to me <br>Take you to me and I <br>How can I keep the secret <br>It's so plan to see <br><br>So how can I help but love you <br>Help but want you <br>Help but need you <br>I have one wish <br>I'm wishing only love me too <br><br>How can I help but love you <br>How can I help but want you <br>How can I help but need you]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="How Can I?" label="How Can I?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Dont_You_Pay_Them_No_Mind_Album_Ver/</id><title>Nina_Simone - Don`t You Pay Them No Mind (Album Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Dont_You_Pay_Them_No_Mind_Album_Ver/" title="Nina_Simone - Don`t You Pay Them No Mind (Album Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[People laugh each time they see us walking by and their whispering just make <br>You feel like you wanna cry Keep on walking by my side don't look behind You <br>Know I love you, so don't you pay 'em no mind <br><br>People say our love ain't gonna last too long And they point at us, just like <br>We've been only carry on, keep on looking in my eyes and we'll be fine You see <br>I love you, so don't you pay 'em no mind <br><br>Stay with me and let 'em see, let 'em know that you love me, that you love me, if <br>It's true who cares what they do Cause I don't need anyone but you Just you <br>And me, we're gonna make it all alone Let them laugh at us, we're gonna build <br>A world all our own, Keep on then, keep on holdin' on to me, they'll learn in <br>Time I really love you, so don't you pay em' no mind You know I love you, you <br>Know I can't be without you]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="Don`t You Pay Them No Mind (Album Ver.)" label="Don`t You Pay Them No Mind (Album Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/The_Laziest_Gal_In_Town/</id><title>Nina_Simone - The Laziest Gal In Town - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/The_Laziest_Gal_In_Town/" title="Nina_Simone - The Laziest Gal In Town - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's not 'cause I wouldn't <br>It's not 'cause I shouldn't <br>And, you know though well, it's not 'cause I couldn't <br>It's simply because I'm the laziest gal in town <br><br>My poor heart is achin' <br>To bring home the bacon <br>And if I find myself alone and forsaken <br>It's simply because I'm the laziest gal in town <br><br>Though I'm more than willing to learn <br>How these gals get so much extra money to burn <br>Every little proposition I just turn it down <br>'Way down <br><br>It's not 'cause I wouldn't <br>It's not 'cause I shouldn't, honey <br>And, you know, that it's not 'cause I couldn't <br>It's simply because I'm the laziest, laziest gal in town]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="The Laziest Gal In Town" label="The Laziest Gal In Town"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Sugar_In_My_Bowl_1987___Live_At_Vine_St_Bar__Grill/</id><title>Nina_Simone - Sugar In My Bowl (1987 / Live At Vine St. Bar &amp; Grill) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Sugar_In_My_Bowl_1987___Live_At_Vine_St_Bar__Grill/" title="Nina_Simone - Sugar In My Bowl (1987 / Live At Vine St. Bar &amp; Grill) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want some sugar in my bowl <br>I want a little sweetness <br>down in my soul <br>I could stand some lovin' Oh so bad <br>Feel so lonely and I feel so sad <br>I want a little steam on my clothes <br>Maybe I could fix things up so they'll go <br>Whatsa matter Daddy <br>Come on, save my soul <br>Drop a little sugar in my bowl <br>I ain't foolin' <br>Drop a little sugar in my bowl <br>Well I want a little sugar in my bowl <br>Well I want a little sweetness down in my soul <br>You been acting strangely I've been told <br>Move me daddy <br>I want some sugar in my bowl <br>I want a little steam on my clothes <br>Maybe I can fix things up so they'll go <br>Whatsa matter Daddy <br>Come on save my soul <br>Drop a little sugar in my bowl <br>I ain't foolin <br>Drop some sugar yeah in my bowl]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="Sugar In My Bowl (1987 / Live At Vine St. Bar &amp; Grill)" label="Sugar In My Bowl (1987 / Live At Vine St. Bar &amp; Grill)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Old_Jim_Crow_Live_In_New_York___1964/</id><title>Nina_Simone - Old Jim Crow (Live In New York / 1964) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Old_Jim_Crow_Live_In_New_York___1964/" title="Nina_Simone - Old Jim Crow (Live In New York / 1964) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Old Jim Crow <br>Where you been baby <br>Down Mississippi and back again <br>Old Jim Crow don't you know <br>It's all over now <br><br>Old Jim Crow <br>What's wrong with you <br>It ain't your name <br>It's the things you do <br>Old Jim Crow don't you know <br>It's all over now <br><br>Old Jim Crow <br>You've been around too long <br>Gotta work the devil <br>'Til your dead and gone <br>Old Jim Crow <br>Yes, don't you know <br>It's all over now <br>It's all over now <br><br>Old Jim Crow <br>You know it's true <br>When you hurt my brother <br>You hurt me too <br>Old Jim Crow don't you know <br>It's all over now <br><br>Old Jim Crow <br>I thought I had you beat <br>Now I see you walkin' <br>And talkin' up and down my street <br>Old Jim Crow don't you know <br>It's all over now <br><br>Old Jim Crow <br>You've been around too long <br>Gotta work the devil <br>'Til your dead and gone <br>Old Jim Crow don't you know <br>It's all over <br>All over <br>Oh Lord, it's all over <br>All over <br>It's all over <br>It's all over <br>It's all over now]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="Old Jim Crow (Live In New York / 1964)" label="Old Jim Crow (Live In New York / 1964)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Work_Song_Album_Ver/</id><title>Nina_Simone - Work Song (Album Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Work_Song_Album_Ver/" title="Nina_Simone - Work Song (Album Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking rocks out here on the chain gang <br>Breaking rocks and serving my time <br>Breaking rocks out here on the chain gang <br>Because they done convicted me of crime <br>Hold it steady right there while I hit it <br>Well reckon that ought to get it <br>Been <br>Working and working <br>But I still got so terribly far to go <br><br>I commited crime Lord I needed <br>Crime of being hungry and poor <br>I left the grocery store man bleeding breathing <br>When they caught me robbing his store <br>Hold it steady right there while I hit it <br>Well reckon that ought to get it <br>Been <br>Working and working <br>But I still got so terribly far to go <br><br>I heard the judge say five years <br>On chain gang you gonna go <br>I heard the judge say five years labor <br>I heard my old man scream Lordy, no <br>Hold it right there while I hit it <br>Well reckon that ought to get it <br>Been <br>Working and working <br>But I still got so terribly far to go <br><br>Gonna see my sweet honey bee <br>Gonna break this chain off to run <br>Gonna lay down somewhere shady <br>Lord I sure am hot in the sun <br>Hold it right there while I hit it <br>Well reckon that ought to get it <br>Been <br>Workin' and workin' <br>Been <br>Workin' and slavin' <br>An' <br>Workin' and workin' <br>But I still got so terribly far to go]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="Work Song (Album Ver.)" label="Work Song (Album Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Feeling_Good_Album_Ver/</id><title>Nina_Simone - Feeling Good (Album Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Feeling_Good_Album_Ver/" title="Nina_Simone - Feeling Good (Album Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Birds flyin' high, you know how I feel <br>Sun in the sky, you know how I feel <br>Breeze driftin' on by, you know how I feel <br>It's a new dawn, it's a new day, it's a new life for me <br>Yeah, it's a new dawn, it's a new day, it's a new life for me, ooooooooh <br>And I'm feelin' good <br><br>Fish in the sea, you know how I feel <br>River runnin' free, you know how I feel <br>Blossom on the tree, you know how I feel <br>It's a new dawn, it's a new day, it's a new life for me <br>And I'm feelin' good <br><br>Dragonfly out in the sun, you know what I mean, don't you know <br>Butterflies all havin' fun, you know what I mean <br>Sleep in peace when day is done that's what I mean <br>And this old world is a new world and a bold world for me <br><br>Stars when you shine, you know how I feel <br>Scent of the pine, you know how I feel <br>Yeah, freedom is mine, and I know how I feel <br>It's a new dawn, it's a new day, it's a new life for me <br><br>And I'm feelin' good]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="Feeling Good (Album Ver.)" label="Feeling Good (Album Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Little_Girl_Blue_Live_In_New_York___1964/</id><title>Nina_Simone - Little Girl Blue (Live In New York / 1964) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Little_Girl_Blue_Live_In_New_York___1964/" title="Nina_Simone - Little Girl Blue (Live In New York / 1964) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sit there and count your fingers <br>What can you do <br>Old girl you're through <br>Sit there, count your little fingers <br>Unhappy little girl blue <br><br>Sit there and count the raindrops <br>Falling on you <br>It's time you knew <br>All you can ever count on <br>Are the raindrops <br>That fall on little girl blue <br><br>Won't you just sit there <br>Count the little raindrops <br>Falling on you <br>'Cause it's time you knew <br>All you can ever count on <br>Are the raindrops <br>That fall on little girl blue <br><br>No use old girl <br>You might as well surrender <br>'Cause your hopes are getting slender and slender <br>Why won't somebody send a tender blue boy <br>To cheer up little girl blue]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="Little Girl Blue (Live In New York / 1964)" label="Little Girl Blue (Live In New York / 1964)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/My_Baby_Just_Cares_For_Me_Live_At_Vine_St_Bar__Grill___1987/</id><title>Nina_Simone - My Baby Just Cares For Me (Live At Vine St. Bar &amp; Grill / 1987) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/My_Baby_Just_Cares_For_Me_Live_At_Vine_St_Bar__Grill___1987/" title="Nina_Simone - My Baby Just Cares For Me (Live At Vine St. Bar &amp; Grill / 1987) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My baby don't care for shows <br>My baby don't care for clothes <br>My baby just cares for me <br>My baby don't care for cars and races <br>My baby don't care for high tone places <br><br>Liz Taylor is not his style <br>And even Lana Turner's smile <br>Is somethin' he can't see <br>My baby don't care who knows <br>My baby just cares for me <br><br>Baby, my baby don't care for shows <br>And he don't even care for clothes <br>He cares for me <br>My baby don't care <br>For cars and races <br>My baby don't care for <br>He don't care for high tone places <br><br>Liz Taylor is not his style <br>And even Liberace's smile <br>Is something he can't see <br>Is something he can't see <br>I wonder what's wrong with baby <br>My baby just cares for <br>My baby just cares for <br>My baby just cares for me <br><br>Original lyrics <br><br>My baby don't care for shows <br>My baby don't care for clothes <br>My baby just cares for me <br>My baby don't care for cars and races <br>My baby don't care for high tone places <br><br>Liz Taylor is not his style <br>And even Lana Turner's smile <br>is somethin' he can't see <br><br>My baby don't care who knows it <br>My baby just cares for me <br><br>My baby don't care for shows <br>And he don't even care for clothes <br>My baby just cares for me <br><br>My baby don't care for cars and races <br>My baby don't care for <br>he don't care for high tone places <br><br>I wonder what's wrong with baby <br>My baby just cares for <br>Just says his prayers for <br>My baby just cares for me]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="My Baby Just Cares For Me (Live At Vine St. Bar &amp; Grill / 1987)" label="My Baby Just Cares For Me (Live At Vine St. Bar &amp; Grill / 1987)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Trouble_In_Mind_Live_In_New_York___1965/</id><title>Nina_Simone - Trouble In Mind (Live In New York / 1965) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Trouble_In_Mind_Live_In_New_York___1965/" title="Nina_Simone - Trouble In Mind (Live In New York / 1965) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Trouble in mind, I'm blue <br>But I won't be blue always <br>'cause the sun's gonna shine <br>In my backdoor some day <br><br>I'm all alone at midnight <br>And my lamp is burnin' low <br>Ain't never had so much <br>Trouble in my life before <br><br>Trouble in mind, that's true <br>I have almost lost my mind <br>Life ain't worth livin <br>Sometimes I feel like dyin' <br><br>Goin' down to the river <br><br>Gonna take my ol' rockin' chair <br>And if the blues don't leave me <br>I'll rock away from there <br><br>You been a hard hearted mama <br>Great god you been unkind <br>Gonna be a cold, cold papa <br>Cause you to lose your mind <br><br>I'm gonna lay my head down <br>On some lonesome railroad line <br>And let the two nineteen <br>Pacify my mind <br><br>Well it's trouble, oh trouble <br>Trouble on my worried mind <br>When you see me laughin' <br>I'm laughin' just to keep from cryin']]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="Trouble In Mind (Live In New York / 1965)" label="Trouble In Mind (Live In New York / 1965)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Love_Me_Or_Leave_Me_Album_Ver/</id><title>Nina_Simone - Love Me Or Leave Me (Album Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nina_Simone/Love_Me_Or_Leave_Me_Album_Ver/" title="Nina_Simone - Love Me Or Leave Me (Album Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love me or leave me and let me be lonely <br>You won't believe me but I love you only <br>I'd rather be lonely than happy with somebody else <br><br>You might find the night time the right time for kissing <br>Night time is my time for just reminiscing <br>Regretting instead of forgetting with somebody else <br><br>There'll be no one unless that someone is you <br>I intended to be independently blue <br><br>I want your love, don't wanna borrow <br>Have it today to give back tomorrow <br>Your love is my love <br>There's no love for nobody else <br><br>Say, love me or leave me and let me be lonely <br>You won't believe me but I love you only <br>I'd rather be lonely than happy with somebody else <br><br>You might find the night time the right time for kissing <br>Night time is my time for just reminiscing <br>Regretting instead of forgetting with somebody else <br><br>There'll be no one unless that someone is you <br>I intended to be independently blue <br><br>Say I want your love, don't wanna borrow <br>Have it today to give back tomorrow <br>Your love is my love <br>My love is your love <br>There's no love for nobody else]]></content><category term="Nina Simone" label="Nina Simone"/><category term="Love Me Or Leave Me (Album Ver.)" label="Love Me Or Leave Me (Album Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Ill_Never_Smile_Again/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - I`ll Never Smile Again - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Ill_Never_Smile_Again/" title="Billie_Holiday - I`ll Never Smile Again - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll never smile again <br>Until I smile at you <br>I'll never laugh again <br>What good would it do <br><br>For tears would fill my eyes <br>My heart would realize <br>That our romance is true <br><br>I'll never love again <br>I'm so in love with you <br>I'll never thrill again <br>To somebody new <br><br>Within my heart <br>I know I will never start <br>To smile again <br>Until I smile at you <br><br>Within my heart <br>I know I will never start <br>To smile again <br>Until I smile at you]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="I`ll Never Smile Again" label="I`ll Never Smile Again"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/One_For_My_Baby_And_One_More_For_The_Road/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - One For My Baby (And One More For The Road) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/One_For_My_Baby_And_One_More_For_The_Road/" title="Billie_Holiday - One For My Baby (And One More For The Road) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's quarter to three, there's no one in the place <br>Except you and me <br>So set 'em' up joe, I got a little story <br>I think you should know <br><br>We're drinking my friend, to the end <br>Of a brief episode <br>Make it one for my baby <br>And one more for the road <br><br>I know the routine, put another nickel <br>In the machine <br>I feel kind of bad, can't you make the music <br>Easy and sad <br><br>I could tell you a lot, but it's not <br>In a gentleman's code <br>Make it one for my baby <br>And one more for the road <br><br>You'd never know it, but buddy I'm a kind of poet <br>And I've got a lot of things I'd like to say <br>And if I'm gloomy, please listen to me <br>Till it's talked away <br><br>Well that's how it goes, and joe I know your gettin' <br>Anxious to close <br>Thanks for the cheer <br>I hope you didn't mind <br>My bending your ear <br><br>But this torch that I found, it's gotta be drowned <br>Or it's gonna explode <br>Make it one for my baby <br>And one more for the road]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="One For My Baby (And One More For The Road)" label="One For My Baby (And One More For The Road)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/I_Must_Have_That_Man/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - I Must Have That Man! - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/I_Must_Have_That_Man/" title="Billie_Holiday - I Must Have That Man! - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't want my mammy <br>I don't need a friend <br>My heart is broken <br>It won't ever mend <br>I ain't much carin' <br>Just where I will end <br>I must have that man <br><br>I'm like an oven <br>That's crying for heat <br>He treats me awfully <br>Each time that we meet <br>It's just unlawful <br>How that boy can cheat <br>But I must have that man <br><br>He's hot as Hades <br>A lady's not safe in his arms <br>When she's kissed <br>But I'm afraid that he's cooled off <br>And maybe I'm ruled off his list <br>I'll never be missed <br><br>I need that person much worse 'n just bad <br>I'm half alive and he's drivin' me mad <br>He's only human if he's to be had <br>I must have that man]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="I Must Have That Man!" label="I Must Have That Man!"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/When_Your_Lover_Has_Gone/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - When Your Lover Has Gone - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/When_Your_Lover_Has_Gone/" title="Billie_Holiday - When Your Lover Has Gone - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you're alone, who cares for starlit skies <br>When you're alone, the magic moonlight dies <br>At break of dawn there is no sunrise <br>When your lover has gone <br><br>What lonely hours the evening shadows bring <br>What lonely hours with memories lingering <br>Like faded flowers life can't mean anything <br>When your lover has gone <br><br>When you're alone, who cares for starlit skies <br>When you're alone, the magic moonlight dies <br>At break of dawn there is no sunrise <br>When your lover has gone <br><br>What lonely hours the evening shadows bring <br>What lonely hours with memories lingering <br>Like faded flowers life can't mean anything <br>When your lover, when your lover has gone]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="When Your Lover Has Gone" label="When Your Lover Has Gone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Stormy_Weather/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - Stormy Weather - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Stormy_Weather/" title="Billie_Holiday - Stormy Weather - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't know why there's no sun up in the sky <br>Stormy weather <br>Since my man and I ain't together <br>Keeps rainin' all the time <br><br>Life is bare, gloom and mis'ry everywhere <br>Stormy weather <br>Just can't get my poor self together <br>I'm weary all the time, the time <br>So weary all the time <br><br>When he went away <br>The blues walked in and met me <br>If he stays away, old rockin' chair will get me <br>All I do is pray, the Lord above will let me <br>Walk in the sun once more <br><br>Can't go on, ev'rything I had is gone <br>Stormy weather <br>Since my man and I ain't together <br>Keeps rainin' all the time <br>Keeps rainin' all the time <br><br>When he went away <br>The blues walked in and met me <br>If he stays away, old rockin' chair will get me <br>All I do is pray, the Lord above will let me <br>Walk in the sun once more <br><br>Can't go on, ev'rything I had is gone <br>Stormy weather <br>Since my man and I ain't together <br>Keeps rainin' all the time <br>Keeps rainin' all the time]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="Stormy Weather" label="Stormy Weather"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/My_Man/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - My Man - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/My_Man/" title="Billie_Holiday - My Man - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It cost me a lot <br>But there's one thing that I've got <br>It's my man <br>It's my man <br><br>Cold or wet <br>Tired, you bet <br>All of this I'll soon forget <br>With my man <br><br>He's not much on looks <br>He's no hero out of books <br>But I love him <br>Yes, I love him <br><br>Two or three girls <br>Has he <br>That he likes as well as me <br>But I love him <br><br>I don't know why I should <br>He isn't true <br>He beats me, too <br>What can I do <br><br>Oh, my man, I love him so <br>He'll never know <br>All my life is just despair <br>But I don't care <br>When he takes me in his arms <br>The world is bright <br>All right <br><br>What's the difference if I say <br>I'll go away <br>When I know I'll come back <br>On my knees someday <br><br>For whatever my man is <br>I'm his forevermore]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="My Man" label="My Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Its_Not_For_Me_To_Say/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - It`s Not For Me To Say - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:10:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:10:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Its_Not_For_Me_To_Say/" title="Billie_Holiday - It`s Not For Me To Say - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's not for me to say you love me <br>It's not for me to say you'll always care <br>Oh, but here for the moment I can hold you fast <br>And press your lips to mine <br>And dream that love will last <br>As far as I can see this is heaven <br>And speaking just for me <br>It's ours to share <br>Perhaps the glow of love will grow <br>With every passing day <br>Or we may never meet again <br>But then, it's not for me to say <br><br>And speaking just for me <br>It's ours to share <br>Perhaps the glow of love will grow <br>With every passing day <br>Or we may never meet again <br>But then, it's not for me to say]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="It`s Not For Me To Say" label="It`s Not For Me To Say"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Willow_Weep_For_Me/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - Willow Weep For Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:11:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:11:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Willow_Weep_For_Me/" title="Billie_Holiday - Willow Weep For Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Willow weep for me <br>Willow weep for me <br>Bent your branches down along the ground and cover me <br>Listen to my plea <br>Hear me willow and weep for me <br>Gone my lovely dreams <br>Lovely summer dreams <br>Gone and left me here <br>To weep my tears along the stream <br>Sad as I can be <br>Hear me willow and weep for me <br>Whisper to the wind and say that love has sinned <br>To leave my heart a sign <br>And crying alone <br>Murmur to the night <br>Hide her starry light <br>So none will find me sighing <br>Crying all alone <br>Weeping willow tree <br>Weeping sympathy <br>Bent your branches down along the ground and cover me <br>Listen to me plead <br>Hear me willow and weep for me <br>Willow <br>Willow <br>Weep for me]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="Willow Weep For Me" label="Willow Weep For Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/I_Dont_Want_To_Cry_Anymore/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - I Don`t Want To Cry Anymore - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:11:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:11:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/I_Dont_Want_To_Cry_Anymore/" title="Billie_Holiday - I Don`t Want To Cry Anymore - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Each night, just about sunset <br>I watch you passing my door <br>It's all I can do <br>Not to run to you <br>'Cause I don't want to cry anymore <br><br>Nighttime, when there is moonlight <br>The same old moon I knew before <br>It's all I can do <br>Not to run to you <br>'Cause I don't want to cry anymore <br><br>All that I know about happiness <br>I found just being with you <br>Then I would find myself losing my mind <br>Over some careless thing you would do <br><br>Oh, why can't I forget you <br>I know so well what is in store <br>A moment or two <br>Up in the clouds with you <br>Then back where I was before <br><br>No I don't want to cry anymore <br>All that I've known about happiness <br>I found just being with you <br>Then I would find myself losing my mind <br>Over some careless thing you would do <br><br>Oh, why can't I forget you <br>I know so well what is in store <br>A moment or two <br>Up in the clouds with you <br>Then back where I was before <br><br>No I don't want to cry anymore]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="I Don`t Want To Cry Anymore" label="I Don`t Want To Cry Anymore"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Dont_Worry_Bout_Me/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - Don`t Worry `Bout Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:11:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:11:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Dont_Worry_Bout_Me/" title="Billie_Holiday - Don`t Worry `Bout Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't worry 'bout me <br>I'll get along <br>Just you forget about me <br>Be happy my love <br><br>Just say that our little show is over <br>And so the story ends <br>Why not call it a day, the sensible way <br>And we'll remain friends <br><br>Look out for yourself <br>Should be the rule <br>Just give your heart and your love, to whom ever you love <br>Don't you be a fool <br><br>Baby why stop and cling, to some fading thing <br>That used to be <br>So if you can't forget <br>Don't you worry 'bout me]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="Don`t Worry `Bout Me" label="Don`t Worry `Bout Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Autumn_In_New_York/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - Autumn In New York - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:11:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:11:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Autumn_In_New_York/" title="Billie_Holiday - Autumn In New York - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Autumn in New York, why does it seem so inviting <br>Autumn in New York, it spells the thrill of first nighting <br>Glittering crowds and shimmering clouds in canyons of steel <br>they're making me feel I'm home <br><br>It's autumn in New York that brings the promise of new love <br>Autumn in New York is often mingled with pain <br>Dreamers with empty hands may sigh for exotic lands <br>It's autumn in New York <br>It's good to live it again <br><br>Autumn in New York, the gleaming rooftops at sundown <br>Autumn in New York, it lifts you up when you're let down <br>jaded roues and gay divorces who lunch at the Ritz <br>will tell you that it's devine <br><br>It's autumn in New York transforms the slums into Mayfair <br>Autumn in New York, you'll need no castle in Spain <br>Lovers that bless the dark <br>On benches in Central Park <br>Greet autumn in New York <br>It's good to live it again]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="Autumn In New York" label="Autumn In New York"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Ill_Wind/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - Ill Wind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:11:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:11:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Ill_Wind/" title="Billie_Holiday - Ill Wind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Blow <br>Ill wind blow away <br>Let me rest today <br>You're blowing me no good <br>No good <br><br>Go <br>Ill wind go away <br>Skies are oh so gray <br>Around my neighborhood <br>And that's no good <br><br>You're only misleading <br>The sunshine I'm needing <br>Ain't that a shame <br>It's so hard to keep up <br>With troubles that creep up <br>From out of nowhere <br>When love's to blame <br><br>So <br>Ill wind blow away <br>Let me rest today <br>You're blowing me no good <br>No good <br>No good <br><br>You're only misleading <br>The sunshine I'm needing <br>Ain't that a shame <br>It's so hard to keep up <br>With troubles that creep up <br>From out of nowhere <br>When love's to blame <br><br>So <br>Ill wind go away <br>Let me rest today <br>You're blowing me no good <br>No good <br><br>Ill wind]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="Ill Wind" label="Ill Wind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Baby_Wont_You_Please_Come_Home/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - Baby Won`t You Please Come Home - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:11:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:11:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Baby_Wont_You_Please_Come_Home/" title="Billie_Holiday - Baby Won`t You Please Come Home - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby, won't you please come home <br>'Cause your mama's all alone <br>I have tried in vain <br>Never no more to call your name <br><br>When you left, you broke my heart <br>Because I never thought we'd part <br>Every hour in the day, you will hear me say <br>Baby, won't you please come home <br><br>Baby, won't you please come home <br>'Cause your mama's all alone <br>I have tried in vain <br>Never no more to call your name <br><br>When you left, you broke my heart <br>Because I never thought we'd part <br>Every hour in the day, you will hear your mama say <br>Oh baby, won't you please come on home <br><br>Mama needs daddy, hey baby <br>Won't you please come home]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="Baby Won`t You Please Come Home" label="Baby Won`t You Please Come Home"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/God_Bless_The_Child/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - God Bless The Child - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:11:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:11:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/God_Bless_The_Child/" title="Billie_Holiday - God Bless The Child - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Them that's got shall have <br>Them that's not shall lose <br>So the Bible says and it still is news <br>Mama may have, Papa may have <br>But God bless the child that's got his own, that's got his own <br><br>Yes the strong get smart <br>While the weak ones fade <br>Empty pockets don't ever make the grade <br>Mama may have, Papa may have <br>But God bless the child that's got his own, that's got his own <br><br>Money, you've got lots of friends <br>They're crowding around your door <br>But when you're gone and spending ends <br>They don't come no more <br>Rich relations give crusts of bread and such <br>You can help yourself, but don't take too much <br>Mama may have, Papa may have <br>But God bless the child that's got his own, that's got his own <br><br>Money you've got lots of friends <br>They're crowding around your door <br>But when you're gone and spending ends <br>They don't come no more <br>Rich relations give crusts of bread and such <br>You can help yourself, but don't take too much <br>Mama may have, Papa may have <br>But God bless the child that's got his own, that's got his own <br><br>Here just don't worry about nothing cause he's got his own <br>Yes, he's got his own]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="God Bless The Child" label="God Bless The Child"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Good_Morning_Heartache/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - Good Morning Heartache - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:11:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:11:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Good_Morning_Heartache/" title="Billie_Holiday - Good Morning Heartache - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Good morning, heartache, you ole gloomy sight <br>Good morning, heartache, thought we'd said goodbye last night <br>I turned and tossed until it seemed you had gone <br>But here you are with the dawn <br>Wish I'd forget you <br>but you're here to stay <br>It seems I met you <br>When my love went away <br>Now everyday I start by saying to you <br>Good morning, heartache, what's new <br><br>Stop haunting me now <br>Can't shake you, no how <br>Just leave me alone <br>I've got those Monday blues <br>Straight through Sunday blues <br><br>Good morning, heartache, here we go again <br>Good morning, hearache, you're the one who knew me when <br>Might as well get used to you hangin around <br>Good morning, heartache, sit down <br><br>Stop haunting me now <br>Can't shake you, no how <br>Just leave me alone <br>I've got those Monday blues <br>Straight through Sunday blues <br><br>Good morning, heartache, here we go again <br>Good morning, hearache, you're the one who knew me when <br>Might as well get used to you hangin around <br>Good morning, heartache, sit down]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="Good Morning Heartache" label="Good Morning Heartache"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Blue_Moon/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - Blue Moon - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:11:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:11:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Blue_Moon/" title="Billie_Holiday - Blue Moon - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Blue moon <br>You saw me standing alone <br>Without a dream in my heart <br>Without a love of my own <br><br>Blue moon <br>You knew just what I was there for <br>You heard me saying a prayer for <br>Someone I really could care for <br><br>And then they suddenly appeared before me <br>The only one my arms will ever hold <br>I heard somebody whisper <br>Please adore me <br>And when I looked <br>The moon had turned to gold <br><br>Blue moon <br>Now I'm no longer alone <br>Without a dream in my heart <br>Without a love of my own <br><br>Blue moon <br>You saw me standing alone <br>Without a dream in my heart <br>Without a love of my own <br><br>Blue moon <br>You knew just what I was there for <br>You heard me saying a prayer for <br>Someone I really could care for <br><br>And then they suddenly appeared before me <br>The only one my arms will ever hold <br>I heard somebody whisper <br>Please adore me <br>And when I looked <br>The moon had turned to gold <br><br>Blue moon <br>Now I'm no longer alone <br>Without a dream in my heart <br>Without a love of my own <br><br>Blue moon]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="Blue Moon" label="Blue Moon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Come_Rain_Or_Come_Shine/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - Come Rain Or Come Shine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:11:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:11:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Come_Rain_Or_Come_Shine/" title="Billie_Holiday - Come Rain Or Come Shine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm gonna love you <br>Like nobody's loved you <br>Come rain or come shine <br>High as a mountain <br>And deep as a river <br>Come rain or come shine <br><br>I guess when you met me <br>It was just one of those things <br>But don' t ever bet me <br>Cause I'm gonna be true <br>If you let me <br><br>You're gonna love me <br>Like nobody's loved me <br>Come rain or come shine <br>Happy together, unhappy together <br>And won't it be fine <br><br>Days may be cloudy or sunny <br>We're in, or we're out of the money <br>But I'm with you always <br>I'm with you rain or shine <br><br>I'm gonna love you <br>Like nobody's loved you <br>Come rain or come shine <br>High as a mountain <br>Deep as a river <br>Come rain or come shine <br><br>I guess when you met me <br>It was just one of those things <br>But don't ever bet me <br>Cause I'm gonna be true <br>If you let me <br><br>You're gonna love me <br>Like nobody's loved me <br>Come rain or come shine <br>Happy together, unhappy together <br>And won't it be fine <br><br>Days may be cloudy or sunny <br>We're in, or we're out of the money <br>But I'll love you always <br>I'm with you rain or shine <br><br>Rain or shine]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="Come Rain Or Come Shine" label="Come Rain Or Come Shine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Lady_Sings_The_Blues/</id><title>Billie_Holiday - Lady Sings The Blues - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:11:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:11:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Lady_Sings_The_Blues/" title="Billie_Holiday - Lady Sings The Blues - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lady sing the blues <br>she's got them bad <br>she feels so sad <br><br>And wants the world to know <br>just what her blues are all about <br><br>Lady sings the blues <br>She tells her side <br>nothing to hide <br><br>Now the world will know <br>just what her blues is all about <br><br>The blues ain't nothin' like a pain in your heart <br>when you get a bad start <br>when you and your man have to part <br><br>I ain't gonna just sit around and cry <br>i know i won't die <br>'cause i love him <br><br>Lady sings the blues <br>i'm tellin' you, she's got 'em bad <br>but now the world will know <br>she's never gonna sing them no more <br><br>The blues ain't nothin' but a pain in your heart <br>when you get a bad start <br>when you and your man have to part <br><br>Ain't gonna just sit around and cry <br>i know i won't die <br>'cause i love him <br><br>Lady sings the blues <br>i'm tellin' you, she's got them bad <br>but now the world will know <br>she's never gonna sing them no more]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="Lady Sings The Blues" label="Lady Sings The Blues"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MILK/Following_The_Sun/</id><title>MILK - Following The Sun - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:24:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:24:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MILK/Following_The_Sun/" title="MILK - Following The Sun - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Float away with me baby <br>I'm hungry for the change <br>Float away with me baby <br>I know you feel the same <br>Let me chase away the shadows <br>And paint a happy smile across your face <br>Bae <br>Like the birds leave for summer <br>Let's find a better beach <br>Somewhere with space <br>Following the sun <br>Down where we belong <br>Summertime has come <br>But we have just begun <br>Float away with me baby <br>I'm longing for the sea <br>Float away with me baby <br>You know we could be <br>We could float accross the ocean <br>And stop at every coast <br>Along the way <br>Bae <br>Set the world in motion <br>And go before the will be too late <br>Following the sun <br>Down where we belong <br>Summertime has come <br>And we have just begun]]></content><category term="M.I.L.K." label="M.I.L.K."/><category term="Following The Sun" label="Following The Sun"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rin/Ich_Will_Dass_Du_Mich_Brauchst/</id><title>Rin - Ich Will Dass Du Mich Brauchst - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:28:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:28:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rin/Ich_Will_Dass_Du_Mich_Brauchst/" title="Rin - Ich Will Dass Du Mich Brauchst - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Draussen regnet's, draussen regnet's <br>Ich krieg' Angst, ich krieg' Angst <br>Ich krieg' Angst, ich krieg' Angst <br>Ey, yeah <br><br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br><br>Ich bin alleine hier, ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich bin alleine dort, ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich hab' kein Selbstbewusstsein, brauch's dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, keine Ehre, Babe, ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst, ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst, ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich brauch's, du bist weg, ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst, ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br><br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br><br>Ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br>Ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst <br>Merkst, ich will dich hier im Haus <br>Ich bin allein, ich bin besoffen, bin allein <br>Ich bin allein, ich bin besoffen, bin allein <br>Ich ruf' dich an, du gehst nicht ran <br>Ich bin besoffen und bin allein <br>Doch Babe, ich brauch's, dass du mich brauchst <br>Babe, ich will, dass du mich brauchst, aye]]></content><category term="Rin" label="Rin"/><category term="Ich Will Dass Du Mich Brauchst" label="Ich Will Dass Du Mich Brauchst"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bajii/바람처럼/</id><title>Bajii - 바람처럼 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-11T00:29:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-11T00:29:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bajii/%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C%EC%B2%98%EB%9F%BC/" title="Bajii - 바람처럼 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기억하나요 <br>우리 약속들을 <br>함께 나누었던 <br>많은 추억들과 시간들 <br>다시 되돌릴 수 없나요 <br>다 잊혀져 가겠죠 <br>우리의 추억들 <br>그렇게 소중했었는데 이젠 다 <br>다 잊혀져 가겠죠 <br>우리의 추억들 <br>흩어지겠죠 모두 다 <br>기억하나요 <br>우리 약속들을 <br>함께 나누었던 <br>많은 추억들과 시간들 <br>다시 되돌릴 수 없나요 <br>다 잊혀져 가겠죠 <br>우리의 추억들 <br>그렇게 소중했었는데 이젠 다 <br>다 잊혀져 가겠죠 <br>우리의 추억들 <br>흩어지겠죠 모두 다 <br>]]></content><category term="Bajii" label="Bajii"/><category term="바람처럼" label="바람처럼"/></entry></feed>