<feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T20:48:36+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fleming__John/The_Way_We_Are/</id><title>Fleming & John - The Way We Are - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T20:48:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T20:48:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fleming__John/The_Way_We_Are/" title="Fleming & John - The Way We Are - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Would I need ya if I got amnesia? <br>Would you be the one for me if I lost my memory? <br>And would I look at you the way that I used to? <br>Would I fall in love all over again <br>Or would I have to pretend? <br><br>Are we gonna stay the way we are? <br>Are we gonna break and fall apart? <br>Are we gonna make it when our love is tested? <br>Are we gonna stay the way we are? <br>I don't wanna break and fall apart <br>Are we gonna make it through the shark infested water? <br>Hearts entrusted to each other <br><br>And I don't know what I'd do <br>If I found out you were untrue <br>Would I find it in my heart to forgive? <br>Would I be able to forget? <br><br>Will I be beautiful? <br>Or will I just be a fool? <br>Can you keep me fresh and young? <br>What if I make you deaf and dumb? <br><br>Are we gonna stay the way we are? <br>Are we gonna break and fall apart? <br>Are we gonna make it when our love is tested? <br>Are we gonna stay the way we are? <br>I don't wanna break and fall apart <br>Are we gonna make it through the shark infested water? <br>Hearts entrusted to each other <br><br>Can we still have adventures <br>When we're old and wear dentures? <br>Will you kiss me on the lips? <br>Do you think we'll dance with our plastic hips? <br>And when you look at me <br>Will you see the girl you met when you were nineteen? <br>Will you see a lady with a limber heart <br>Swimming in the water with the sharks? <br><br>Are we gonna stay the way we are are? <br>Are we gonna break and fall apart? <br>Are we gonna make it when our love is tested? <br>Are we gonna stay the way we are? <br>I don't wanna break and fall apart <br>Are we gonna make it through the shark infested water? <br>Hearts entrusted to each other]]></content><category term="Fleming & John" label="Fleming & John"/><category term="The Way We Are" label="The Way We Are"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fleming__John/Dont_Let_It_Fade_Away/</id><title>Fleming & John - Don`t Let It Fade Away - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T20:48:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T20:48:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fleming__John/Dont_Let_It_Fade_Away/" title="Fleming & John - Don`t Let It Fade Away - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't let it fade away <br>Be strong enough to tell me goodbye <br>Don't let it fade away <br>Just because you don't wanna see me cry <br>If it's over now, I'll be okay <br>Just don't let it fade away <br>You keep me dangling <br>From a string you cannot sever <br>It's time to end all indecision <br>Curiosity is killing me <br>Don't let it fade away <br>Be strong enough to tell me goodbye <br>Don't let it fade away <br>Just because you don't wanna see me cry <br>If it's over now, I'll be okay <br>Just don't let it fade away <br>Look me in the eye <br>And tell me you don't love me <br>Put me out of my misery <br>Your silence is giving me too much hope <br>Don't let it fade away <br>Be strong enough to tell me goodbye <br>Don't let it fade away <br>Just because you don't wanna see me cry <br>If it's over now, I'll be okay <br>Just don't let it fade away <br>Don't let it fade away <br>Be strong enough to tell me goodbye <br>Don't let it fade away <br>Just because you don't wanna see me cry <br>If it's over now, I'll be okay <br>Just don't let it fade]]></content><category term="Fleming & John" label="Fleming & John"/><category term="Don`t Let It Fade Away" label="Don`t Let It Fade Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fleming__John/Comfortable/</id><title>Fleming & John - Comfortable - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T20:48:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T20:48:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fleming__John/Comfortable/" title="Fleming & John - Comfortable - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You know how to hold my hand <br>You know how to make me mad <br>You know everything about me <br>We've been together longer <br>Than most of our friends have <br>But they don't know that it's not always a party <br><br>I gotta tell you how I'm feeling <br>In case you haven't noticed <br>The mystery is gone <br>Infatuation's wearing off <br>I gotta tell you how I'm feeling <br>I think that you'll agree <br>That we've become predictable <br>But I really don't mind being this comfortable <br><br>Sometimes I try to shake it up <br>Tickle the passion, wake it up <br>It's time to breathe a little fire <br>But you just put your arms around me <br>And I let go of all my anxiety <br>You know you're my lazy boy recliner <br><br>I gotta tell you how i'm feeling <br>I hope you don't take it wrong <br>You know that I love you and I'm not giving up]]></content><category term="Fleming & John" label="Fleming & John"/><category term="Comfortable" label="Comfortable"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fleming__John/The_Pearl/</id><title>Fleming & John - The Pearl - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T20:48:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T20:48:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fleming__John/The_Pearl/" title="Fleming & John - The Pearl - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh look I've found it <br>Oh I've really found it <br>How could such a thing be happening to me? <br>Oh please don't drop it <br>I'd die if you lost it <br>You see it means the world to me <br><br>Now everything we ever wanted <br>Lies within our reach <br>Patiently anticipating <br>The world lies at our feet <br><br>It could be the pearl <br>It could be our hope, our dream, our life <br>It could be the pearl <br>The end of all our pain and strife could be the pearl <br><br>Run, keep on running <br>Oh I hear them coming <br>How could they try to take what is ours? <br>Please run faster <br>Oh they're right behind us <br>How much farther can we go? <br><br>It possesses me, controls me <br>It makes me run, it makes me kill <br>The very thing that made me strong <br>Has taken all my will <br><br>It could be the pearl <br>Tt could be our hope, our dream, our life <br>Tt could be the pearl <br>The end of all our pain and strife could be the pearl <br><br>I must take it, throw it in the ocean <br>Far, far away from me <br>We were happy, oh we were so happy <br>When things were the way they used to be <br><br>It could be the pearl <br>It could be our hope, our dream, our life <br>It could be the pearl <br>The end of all our pain and strife could be the pearl]]></content><category term="Fleming & John" label="Fleming & John"/><category term="The Pearl" label="The Pearl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fleming__John/Sssh/</id><title>Fleming & John - Sssh! - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T20:48:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T20:48:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fleming__John/Sssh/" title="Fleming & John - Sssh! - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You had the prettiest blue-green eyes I'd ever seen <br>And I got a kick out of the way they looked at me, <br>Like I was a two-headed creature from another planet <br>That thrilled and excited you, <br>But you couldn't understand it <br><br>Don't tell my ears, <br>'Cause they're not listening. <br>Don't tell my heart, <br>It doesn't know what it is missing. <br>Don't tell my eyes, <br>I know they won't believe, <br>That you're not in love with me <br><br>We were inseparable, <br>You followed me around, <br>And I got used to this new friend that i had found. <br>I pictured us together, <br>I pictured us apart, <br>And I knew from that moment, <br>You were capable of breaking my heart apart. <br><br>Don't tell my ears, <br>'Cause they're not listening. <br>Don't tell my heart, <br>It doesn't know what it is missing. <br>Don't tell my eyes, <br>I know they won't believe, <br>That you're not in love with me]]></content><category term="Fleming & John" label="Fleming & John"/><category term="Sssh!" label="Sssh!"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fleming__John/Im_So_Small/</id><title>Fleming & John - I`m So Small - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T20:48:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T20:48:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fleming__John/Im_So_Small/" title="Fleming & John - I`m So Small - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm so small <br>Do you think I matter at all? <br>When I call your name out loud <br>Can you hear me in the crowd? <br>When I look up into the starry sky <br>I think my oh my <br>I get dizzy and weak and it makes me think <br>I have the life span of a fly <br>Can you see me breathing? <br>Hear me screaming <br>For you, for you <br>I'm so small <br>But if I was a movie star <br>My youth would be sealed in a can on a reel <br>Then I could be twelve feet tall <br>That's why I wear my hair so big <br>Some people think it might be a wig <br>But it's all part of my plot <br>To prove I'm not a dot <br>Can you see me breathing? <br>Hear me screaming <br>For you, for you <br>Can you see me breathing? <br>Hear me screaming <br>For you, for you <br>I'm so small, I'm so small <br>I'm so small, I'm so small <br>Can you see me, see me breathing? <br>Can you hear me, hear me screaming? <br>Can you see me breathing? <br>Hear me screaming <br>For you, for you <br>Can you see? <br>Hear me breathing <br>For you, for you, for you]]></content><category term="Fleming & John" label="Fleming & John"/><category term="I`m So Small" label="I`m So Small"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Manila_Killa__AObeats/Im_OK_Feat_Shaylen/</id><title>Manila Killa & AObeats - I`m OK (Feat. Shaylen) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T20:54:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T20:54:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Manila_Killa__AObeats/Im_OK_Feat_Shaylen/" title="Manila Killa & AObeats - I`m OK (Feat. Shaylen) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Take a look at my bank account <br>It's emptier than our conversations <br>But I'm okay, yeah I'm okay <br>And take a look at this broken heart <br>It's all out of good vibrations <br>But it's beating, I don't need it <br><br>Now it’s so pathetic <br>How I can’t ever get through to you, you <br>Cause you’re always somewhere else <br>Still wear that perfume you got me <br>Cause I’m no longer thinking of you, you <br>Now it’s time for someone else so <br><br>Now It’s so pathetic <br>How I got your initials tattooed, tattooed <br>But I’m ok, yeah I’m ok <br>Yeah I got another letter added <br>and now it spells something new, new <br>But I'm okay, yeah I'm okay <br><br>(Okay!) <br>But I'm okay, yeah I'm okay <br>(Okay!) <br>But I'm okay, yeah I'm okay <br><br>I took you off my Instagram and told my mom, now it's official <br>And I'm okay, really okay <br>And every time I hear our song I turn it up 'cause I don't miss you <br>And I'm okay, really okay <br><br>Now it’s so pathetic <br>How I can’t ever get through to you, you <br>Cause you’re always somewhere else <br>Still wear that perfume you got me <br>Cause I’m no longer thinking of you, you <br>Now it’s time for someone else so <br><br>Now It’s so pathetic <br>How I got your initials tattooed, tattooed <br>But I’m ok, yeah I’m ok <br>Yeah I got another letter added <br>and now it spells something new, new <br>But I'm okay, yeah I'm okay <br><br>(Okay!) <br>But I'm okay, yeah I'm okay <br>(Okay!) <br>But I'm okay, yeah I'm okay <br>(Okay!) <br>But I'm okay, yeah I'm okay <br>(Okay!) <br>But I'm okay, yeah I'm okay <br><br>But I'm okay, yeah I'm okay <br>But I'm okay, yeah I'm okay <br>But I'm okay, yeah I'm okay <br>But I'm okay, yeah I'm okay]]></content><category term="Manila Killa & AObeats" label="Manila Killa & AObeats"/><category term="I`m OK (Feat. Shaylen)" label="I`m OK (Feat. Shaylen)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Grouplove/Adios_Amigos/</id><title>Grouplove - Adios Amigos - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T20:55:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T20:55:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Grouplove/Adios_Amigos/" title="Grouplove - Adios Amigos - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Adios amigos I'm gone <br>Left all my belongings in a box <br>Didn't I know the things I had <br>Oh all the things <br><br>Adios amigos so long <br>Didn't I know my hands were both cut off <br>Everyone was like hold up, man get up <br>Yeah shut up, you're on the clock <br><br>So catch me catch me catch me if you can <br>Yeah call the operator <br>Catch me catch me catch me if you can <br>Sayonara, see you later <br>All in the moment, I could live forever <br>Catch me catch me catch me if you can <br><br>Adios amigos so gone <br>Call me up when you're in Tarascon <br>Didn't I know the things I had <br>Oh all the things <br>Yeah that's what I said <br><br>So catch me catch me catch me if you can <br>Yeah call the operator <br>Catch me catch me catch me if you can <br>Sayonara, see you later <br>All in the moment, I could live forever <br>Catch me catch me catch me if you can <br>Sayonara see you later now <br><br>Catch me catch me catch me if you can <br>You catch me catch me catch me if you can <br>All in the moment, I could live forever <br>Catch me catch me catch me if you can <br>Sayonara see you later <br>All in the moment <br><br>All in the moment, we can live forever <br>All in the moment, we can live forever <br>All in the moment, we can live forever <br>All in the moment, we can live forever <br>All in the moment, we can live forever <br>All in the moment, we can live forever <br>All in the moment, we can live forever <br>All in the moment, we can live forever]]></content><category term="Grouplove" label="Grouplove"/><category term="Adios Amigos" label="Adios Amigos"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Grouplove/Enlighten_Me_Live/</id><title>Grouplove - Enlighten Me (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T20:55:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T20:55:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Grouplove/Enlighten_Me_Live/" title="Grouplove - Enlighten Me (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let's call it quits and see what the future holds <br>I've been here before, yeah, we just went down this road <br>A long time to feel young, short time to get old <br>I was holding onto something, knowing you would just let me go <br>Yeah, I was holding onto something, knowing you would just let me go <br>I love it when I get high, hate it when it gets cold <br>Indiscretion is a blessing if you know how the truth is told <br><br>But I don't feel my life is real <br>I'm on the fence with common sense <br><br>The tendency of time is to never understand it <br>The lesson of my life is to never comprehend it <br>No matter how much you spend trying to blend in <br>Or maybe on my deathbed I finally get an answer <br>Yeah, maybe on my deathbed I finally get an answer <br>Or tell me why it's always been this way <br>Indiscretion is a blessing if you know what you want to say <br><br>But I don't feel my life is real <br>I'm on the fence with common sense <br>Won't you enlighten me <br>Won't you just set me free <br><br>Let's call it quits to see what the future holds <br>Been here before, yeah, we just went down this road <br>A long time to feel young, short time to get old <br>I was holding onto something, knowing you would just let me go <br><br>But I don't feel my life is real <br>I'm on the fence with common sense <br>Won't you enlighten me <br>Won't you just set me free]]></content><category term="Grouplove" label="Grouplove"/><category term="Enlighten Me (Live)" label="Enlighten Me (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Grouplove/MRI/</id><title>Grouplove - MRI - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T20:55:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T20:55:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Grouplove/MRI/" title="Grouplove - MRI - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Before you feel like everything's gone wrong <br>Let's laugh and sing and think about this song <br>Yeah think about this song <br>Yeah think about this song <br>Yeah think about this song <br><br>Before you feel like everything's gone wrong <br>Let's laugh and sing and think about this song <br>Yeah think about this song <br>Yeah think about this song <br><br>Can't you see the sunlight <br>Can't you see it's moving on <br>Even in the darkest hours <br>Can't you see there's someone <br>Don't you feel the love <br>Can't you feel the love <br><br>Even when you feel just like the sky is falling down <br>You've got it right <br>And all you've got to do in times so hard you fall apart <br>Is let them pass by <br><br>So give it what you want <br>And then give it what you want <br>And then give it what you want <br>And then give it what you want <br><br>And all you've got to do is just to make it past this <br>You've got to make it past this <br>You've got to make it <br><br>Can't you see the sunlight <br>Can't you see it's moving on <br>Even in the darkest hours <br>Can't you see there's someone <br>Don't you feel this love <br>Can't you feel this love <br>Can't you feel this love <br><br>Before you feel like everything's gone wrong <br>Let's laugh and sing and think about this song <br>Yeah think about this song <br>Yeah think about this song <br>Yeah think about this song]]></content><category term="Grouplove" label="Grouplove"/><category term="MRI" label="MRI"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Grouplove/Torso/</id><title>Grouplove - Torso - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T20:55:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T20:55:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Grouplove/Torso/" title="Grouplove - Torso - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I had a dream when I woke up today in bed <br>I crawled around the ground, yeah, looking for my golden egg <br>I lost my feet, I lost my hand, I lost my head <br>When I looked up I saw a girl and this is what she said <br><br>Living without my shadow, living far away <br>Living without my shadow, living far away <br>And I said <br>Living without my shadow, living far away <br>Living without my shadow, living far away <br><br>Three times we climed the stairs that never went no where <br>Tied up in basket, and she carried me to Febuary <br>Three times she marries me, but I was never there <br>Can't keep the family from changing me to what I am Yeah <br><br>Living without my shadow, living far away <br>Living without my shadow, living far away <br>And I said <br>Living without my shadow, living far away <br>Living without my shadow, living far away <br><br>Oh <br>Nobody wants me here <br>Oh <br>Nobody wants me here <br><br>We saw a better life that came another way <br>Another set of eyes, surrounded me so natural <br>I trust the things in life that come another way <br>She has Velouria, a pile of bones is all I am <br><br>Living without my shadow, living far away <br>Living without my shadow, living far away <br>And I said <br>Living without my shadow, living far away <br>Living without my shadow, living far away <br><br>Oh <br>Nobody wants me here <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>Nobody wants me here <br>Oh <br>Nobody wants me here <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>Nobody wants me <br><br>Oh <br>Nobody wants me here <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>Nobody wants me here <br><br>Oh <br>Nobody wants me here <br>Oh, oh, oh <br>Nobody wants me]]></content><category term="Grouplove" label="Grouplove"/><category term="Torso" label="Torso"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Grouplove/Tell_Me_A_Story/</id><title>Grouplove - Tell Me A Story - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T20:55:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T20:55:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Grouplove/Tell_Me_A_Story/" title="Grouplove - Tell Me A Story - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, I am guilty <br>Of feeling one way then the other <br>I looked the other way when I realized <br>Maybe I'm broken bread <br>'Cause where there's bread there's butter <br>Well, maybe I'm broken bread <br>When I realize I don't sleep <br>Yeah, I don't break <br><br>So tell me a story <br>Well, I'm in no hurry <br>I lay my head down <br>Against our baby now <br><br>Well maybe I've broken bone <br>But at least we're coming <br>We're gonna plant a tree on your birthday <br>Oh, I can't wait <br><br>So tell me a story <br>Well, I'm in no hurry <br>I lay my head down <br>Against our baby now]]></content><category term="Grouplove" label="Grouplove"/><category term="Tell Me A Story" label="Tell Me A Story"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Prince/Electric_Intercourse_Studio_Ver/</id><title>Prince - Electric Intercourse (Studio Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T20:55:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T20:55:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Prince/Electric_Intercourse_Studio_Ver/" title="Prince - Electric Intercourse (Studio Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I feel some kind of love for you <br>And I don't even know your name <br>This is the kind of love that takes two <br>I want you and I'm not ashamed <br><br>'Cause baby, you shock my wild <br>With a sexual electricity extraordinaire <br>Come and take advantage, undress me <br>I don't even know you, I don't even care <br><br>I feel some kind of sexual current <br>Tell me do you feel it too <br>Our bodies want to be together <br>Girl, I wanna be with you <br><br>Electric is my body, baby <br>I will shock you with my lips <br>Darling, don't you know <br>Your Technicolor climax is at my fingertips <br><br>Electric intercourse, electric intercourse <br>Don't you wanna <br>Electric intercourse, electric intercourse <br>Don't you wanna make love, love, love <br><br>Electric is my body, baby <br>I will shock you with my lips <br>Darling, don't you know <br>Your Technicolor climax is at my fingertips <br><br>Electric intercourse <br>Don't you wanna <br>Electric intercourse, electric intercourse <br>Don't you wanna make love <br>Don't you wanna make <br><br>Electric intercourse, electric intercourse <br>Don't you wanna <br>Electric intercourse, electric intercourse <br>Don't you want to make love <br>Yeah, yeah]]></content><category term="Prince" label="Prince"/><category term="Electric Intercourse (Studio Ver.)" label="Electric Intercourse (Studio Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mike_Curb_Congregation/Softly_Whispering_I_Love_You/</id><title>Mike Curb Congregation - Softly Whispering I Love You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T20:56:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T20:56:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mike_Curb_Congregation/Softly_Whispering_I_Love_You/" title="Mike Curb Congregation - Softly Whispering I Love You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Softly whispering I love you <br>echoes of your voice are calling <br>still through my dreams <br>softening the chill of the breeze <br>through my window <br>I can see the moonglow <br>painting silver shadows on a rose <br>coloured land <br>a world that we walked hand in hand <br>in a day of gold coloured by the glow of new love <br>Oh woman, I can feel your warm face <br>ever close to my lips <br>and the scent of you invades <br>the cool evening air <br>I can close my eyes <br>and you're there in my arms <br>still and I know your soft kiss <br>turning into music ev'ry beat of my heart <br>when I hold you close to my heart <br>and I hear your voice whispering <br>I love you. <br><br>I can feel your warm face <br>ever close to my lips <br>and the scent of you invades <br>the cool evening air <br>I can close my eyes and you're there in my arms <br>still and I know your soft kiss turning into music ev'ry beat <br>of my heart <br>when I hold you close to my heart <br><br>and I hear your voice whispering <br>I love you]]></content><category term="Mike Curb Congregation" label="Mike Curb Congregation"/><category term="Softly Whispering I Love You" label="Softly Whispering I Love You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더필름/파노라마_Panorama_P96/</id><title>더필름 - 파노라마 (Panorama) (P.96) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:00:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:00:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%ED%95%84%EB%A6%84/%ED%8C%8C%EB%85%B8%EB%9D%BC%EB%A7%88_Panorama_P96/" title="더필름 - 파노라마 (Panorama) (P.96) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잘 있었니 <br>어젠 너를 너를 꿈에 만났어 <br>I just called you <br>in midnight to be met <br>넌 그대로더라 <br>넌 참 예쁘더라 <br>얼마만이지 <br>니가 그렇게 함께 보길 원했던 <br>before sunrise and If Only <br>Eternal Sunshine <br>돌려보고 있어 <br>다시 보고 있어 <br>니가 했던 많은 대사 어제 일처럼 <br>내 옆에 생생한데 <br>너는 없고 니 그림자만 남아 흔들려 <br>우 너는 내게 없고 <br>우 너는 내게 없고 <br>꿈인 거니 <br>아님 깨어난 여기 이 곳이 꿈이니 <br>제발 맞다고 그렇다고 소리쳐줘 <br>우 난 너 없이 살아 <br>우 난 나 없이 살아 <br>니가 했던 많은 대사 어제 일처럼 <br>내 옆에 생생한데 <br>너는 없고 니 그림자만 남아 흔들려 <br>우 난 너 없이 살아 <br>우 난 너 없이 살아 <br>Come back to me <br>If you can not come <br>Just please go away <br>우 니가 그리운데 <br>우 니가 보고 싶어 <br>니가 말한 많은 약속 생각나 <br>풍경처럼 펼쳐지면 <br>너는 여기 익숙한 모습으로 내게 와 <br>우 널 만지고 싶어 <br>우 널 껴안고 싶어 파노라마 <br>우 널 만지고 싶어 <br>우 널 껴안고 싶어 파노라마 <br>우 내가 참 미안해 <br>우 니가 보고 싶어 파노라마 <br>]]></content><category term="더필름" label="더필름"/><category term="파노라마 (Panorama) (P.96)" label="파노라마 (Panorama) (P.96)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kasabian/Youre_In_Love_With_A_Psycho/</id><title>Kasabian - You`re In Love With A Psycho - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:01:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:01:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kasabian/Youre_In_Love_With_A_Psycho/" title="Kasabian - You`re In Love With A Psycho - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You know it's the place I need <br>But you got me walking <br>circles like a dog on a lead <br>And the doctors say I'm crazy <br>that I'm eight miles thick <br>I'm like the taste of macaroni <br>on a seafood stick <br>And you got me switched on <br>baby like electric eel <br>And I'm tight with Axel Foley <br>that's just how I feel <br>Like a grapefruit and a magic trick <br>the prodigal son <br>I'm walking I'm walking <br>I'm walking I walk so quick <br>And it just don't mean a thing <br>We've been waiting far too long <br>We'll play it out again <br>This is just my serenade <br>You're in love with a psycho <br>You're in love with a psycho <br>And there's nothing <br>you can do about it <br>I got you running all around it <br>You're in love with a psycho <br>You're in love with a psycho <br>And there's nothing <br>you can do about it <br>You never gonna be without it <br>Jibber jabber at the bargain booze <br>And reciting Charles Bukowski <br>I got nothing to lose <br>And I wait for you <br>to follow me to share my chips <br>But you're walking you're walking <br>you walk you walk so quick <br>Nobody's gonna take you there <br>I stick around for the thousand <br>yard stare <br>I go to sleep in a duffle bag <br>I'm never up never down <br>down down down <br>Hey you're in love with a psycho <br>You're in love with a psycho <br>And there's nothing <br>you can do about it <br>I got you running all around it <br>You're in love with a psycho <br>You're in love with a psycho <br>And there's nothing <br>you can do about it <br>You're never gonna be with <br>Maybe this way <br>we'll find a solution <br>Maybe this way <br>we'll find a solution of problems <br>Oh to love we gotta find love <br>You're in love with a psycho <br>You're in love with a psycho <br>And there's nothing <br>you can do about it <br>I got you running all around it <br>You're in love with a psycho <br>Tu amor es muy loco <br>And there's nothing <br>you can do about it <br>You never gonna be without it <br>]]></content><category term="Kasabian" label="Kasabian"/><category term="You`re In Love With A Psycho" label="You`re In Love With A Psycho"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stone_Sour/Fabuless/</id><title>Stone Sour - Fabuless - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:03:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:03:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stone_Sour/Fabuless/" title="Stone Sour - Fabuless - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh yeah <br><br>I can't recall the last time I was caught between the walls <br>Those razors in the pillowcases seem to cut em all <br>But old foes, dead things, take a toll <br>Remember, it's just a game <br><br>Been a long time since I rock and rolled <br>It's only rock and roll but I like it, like it <br>Don't talk, walk, don't feel, real <br>Don't stay, say, you'll need it anyway <br><br>Oh, it's my own damn fault <br>I guess it's good to be the enemy <br>That don't mean it ain't so bad, bad, bad <br><br>Because it's all downhill from here <br>It's all downhill from here motherfucker <br>It's all downhill from here <br>It's all downhill, you can't get home from here <br><br>Your beast is just a burden that you never keep in line <br>This fabulous is really less, gets em every time <br>You roll your eyes for money, don't act like you're impressed <br>You spread your legs for TV time, baby, who fucks you best <br><br>Been a long time since I rock and rolled <br>It's only rock and roll but I like it, like it <br>Don't talk, walk, don't feel, real <br>Don't stay, say, you'll need it anyway <br><br>Oh, it's my own damn fault <br>I guess it's good to be the enemy <br>That don't mean it ain't so bad, bad, bad <br><br>Because it's all downhill from here <br>It's all downhill from here motherfucker <br>It's all downhill from here <br>It's all downhill, you can't get home from here <br><br>Oh, it's my own damn fault <br>I guess it's good to be the enemy <br>That don't mean it ain't so bad, bad, bad, ohh <br><br>Admit it, when you fall <br>You'll make peace with your gravity <br>We all know it drives you mad, mad, mad <br><br>Because it's all downhill from here <br>It's all downhill from here motherfucker <br>It's all downhill from here <br>It's all downhill from here motherfucker <br>You can't get home from here <br>You can't get home from here motherfucker <br>You can't get home from here <br>You can't get home from here]]></content><category term="Stone Sour" label="Stone Sour"/><category term="Fabuless" label="Fabuless"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stone_Sour/Song_3/</id><title>Stone Sour - Song #3 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:03:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:03:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stone_Sour/Song_3/" title="Stone Sour - Song #3 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If you take a step towards me <br>You will take my breath away <br>So I'll keep you close <br>And keep my secret safe <br><br>No one else has ever loved me <br>No one else has ever tried <br>I never understood <br>How much I could take <br><br>Then I saw the worst was over <br>When I laid my eyes on you <br>It was all that I could do to know my place <br><br>I don't follow past illusions <br>I don't bother, dreams come true <br>I was gone until <br>I finally saw your face <br><br>If you cried out for more <br>If you reached out for me <br>I would run into the storm <br>Just to keep you here with me <br><br>I have gone beyond my years <br>I've wasted half my life <br>But I found it all in you <br>Did I save you <br>Cause I know you saved me too <br><br>Let me take a step towards you <br>Let me feel you in my hands <br>Let me cross this line <br>And show you where it leads <br><br>There's a darkness down inside me <br>That I know we'll both enjoy <br>And it's screaming from within <br>To set it free <br><br>I have left this bloody nightmare <br>In my wake, bored out of time <br>And I won this deviation by design <br><br>I don't follow past confusion <br>Out of all the common spite <br>Just tell me I am yours <br>Cause you are mine <br><br>And if you cried out for more <br>If you reached out for me <br>I would run into the storm <br>Just to keep you here with me <br><br>I have gone beyond my years <br>I've wasted half my life <br>But I found it all in you <br>Did I save you <br>Cause I know you saved me too <br><br>It doesn't really matter what you do or say <br>I'm never going anywhere anyway <br>Cause when I'm dying for you <br>I've never felt so alive <br><br>If you cried out for more <br>If you reached out for me <br>I would run into the storm <br>Just to keep you here with me <br><br>I have gone beyond my years <br>I've wasted half my life <br>But I found it all in you <br>Did I save you <br>Cause I know you saved me too <br><br>I know you saved me too]]></content><category term="Stone Sour" label="Stone Sour"/><category term="Song #3" label="Song #3"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aryay/Always_Wanted_You_Feat_Kimbra/</id><title>Aryay - Always Wanted You (Feat. Kimbra) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:03:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:03:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aryay/Always_Wanted_You_Feat_Kimbra/" title="Aryay - Always Wanted You (Feat. Kimbra) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1] <br>All your lies are tearing my eyes <br>'Cause oh I want it <br>Oh do I want it <br>Storms of tears I may have cried <br>And still I want it <br>Oh do I want it <br><br>[Chorus] <br>'Cause when we're in the middle of a fight <br>Panic, crash, another broken tail light, finish <br>All the worst is left behind <br>I always wanted <br>Always wanted you <br>Always wanted you <br>Always wanted you <br>Always wanted you <br>Always wanted you <br><br>[Post-Chorus] <br>Always wanted you <br>Always wanted you <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>All your lies surrounding my mind <br>Inside I love it <br>Oh do I love it <br>Don't see past my blurring eyes <br>I always want it <br>More than I'm wanted <br><br><br>[Chorus] <br>Because when we're in the middle of a fight <br>Panic, crash, another broken tail light, finish <br>All the worst is left behind <br>I always wanted <br>Always wanted you <br>Always wanted you <br>Always wanted you <br>Always wanted you <br>Always wanted you <br><br>[Post-Chorus] <br>Always wanted you <br>Always wanted you <br><br>[Outro] <br>(Always wanted you) <br>Always wanted you]]></content><category term="Aryay" label="Aryay"/><category term="Always Wanted You (Feat. Kimbra)" label="Always Wanted You (Feat. Kimbra)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/달무리/들꽃에게_Vocal_유용호/</id><title>달무리 - 들꽃에게 (Vocal 유용호) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:04:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:04:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%AC%EB%AC%B4%EB%A6%AC/%EB%93%A4%EA%BD%83%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_Vocal_%EC%9C%A0%EC%9A%A9%ED%98%B8/" title="달무리 - 들꽃에게 (Vocal 유용호) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[작은 손으로 나의 투박한 <br>검지손가락을 네가 꼭 잡았을 때 <br>그때 생각했지 <br>네가 말할 때쯤엔 <br>꼭 피아노를 가르치겠다고 <br>자그맣게 뛰는 너의 심장이 <br>나의 귓가에 오롯이 담겨 질 때 <br>그때 생각했지 <br>네가 기댈 수 있는 <br>건강한 내가 되어야겠다고 <br>아가야 나는 너를 <br>들꽃처럼 키우고 싶었단다 <br>거친 바람을 견뎌낼 <br>깊은 뿌릴 지닌 <br>여리지만 단단한 꽃 <br>가끔씩 힘이 들 때면 <br>고갤 들어 하늘을 바라봐주련 <br>보이지 않을 먼 곳에 <br>가만히 반짝이는 <br>빛으로 널 안아줄게 <br>아가야 나는 너를 <br>들꽃처럼 키우고 싶었단다 <br>거친 바람을 견뎌낼 <br>깊은 뿌릴 지닌 <br>여리지만 단단한 꽃 <br>가끔씩 힘이 들 때면 <br>고갤 들어 하늘을 바라봐주련 <br>보이지 않을 먼 곳에 <br>가만히 반짝이는 <br>빛으로 널 안아줄게 <br>사랑한다 나의 기적 <br>]]></content><category term="달무리" label="달무리"/><category term="들꽃에게 (Vocal 유용호)" label="들꽃에게 (Vocal 유용호)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/허각/너란_이유_Inst/</id><title>허각 - 너란 이유 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:05:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:05:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%88%EA%B0%81/%EB%84%88%EB%9E%80_%EC%9D%B4%EC%9C%A0_Inst/" title="허각 - 너란 이유 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈 앞에서 점점 멀어지는 <br>뒷모습 보면서 <br>내 맘속 깊은 바람들 <br>하마터면 전할 뻔했어 <br>오랫동안 아마 넌 몰랐겠지 <br>난 항상 여기 있는데 <br>지난 계절처럼 사라질까 <br>곁에 있어도 넌 그리워 <br>보이지 않는 시간 속의 <br>널 지킬게 내 모든 사랑을 <br>두 눈을 감고 가만히 불러 <br>나의 소중한 단 하나의 사람 너뿐야 <br>내가 지금도 숨쉬는 그 이유 <br>길을 걷다 아무런 말도 없이 <br>내려버린 비처럼 <br>어느새 두 눈에 맺혀있다 <br>흘러버린 너란 사람아 <br>언제부턴가 무거운 하루 끝에 <br>믿는 건 하나뿐이야 <br>길을 잃고 헤매이던 <br>날 이끌어 준 향기처럼 넌 <br>보이지 않는 시간 속의 <br>널 지킬게 내 모든 사랑을 <br>두 눈을 감고 가만히 불러 <br>나의 소중한 단 하나의 사람 너뿐야 <br>나 숨쉬는 그 이유 <br>아무리 반대로 나 걸어도 <br>아무리 모르는 척 해봐도 <br>그래도 결국 <br>이 길의 끝에 만나겠지 <br>닫혀 있던 맘조차 <br>조금씩 열고 나를 바라볼 때 <br>너를 부른다 <br>이런 내 전부를 걸고 널 지킬게 <br>가끔은 믿을 수가 없어 꿈 속에서도 <br>우리 둘은 항상 함께 있겠지 <br>가끔은 너무나 아픈 꿈이래도 <br>웃을 수 있는 건 <br>나의 아름다운 너란 이유 때문이야 <br>]]></content><category term="허각" label="허각"/><category term="너란 이유 (Inst.)" label="너란 이유 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/허각/너란_이유/</id><title>허각 - 너란 이유 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:05:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:05:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%88%EA%B0%81/%EB%84%88%EB%9E%80_%EC%9D%B4%EC%9C%A0/" title="허각 - 너란 이유 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈 앞에서 점점 멀어지는 <br>뒷모습 보면서 <br>내 맘속 깊은 바람들 <br>하마터면 전할 뻔했어 <br>오랫동안 아마 넌 몰랐겠지 <br>난 항상 여기 있는데 <br>지난 계절처럼 사라질까 <br>곁에 있어도 넌 그리워 <br>보이지 않는 시간 속의 <br>널 지킬게 내 모든 사랑을 <br>두 눈을 감고 가만히 불러 <br>나의 소중한 단 하나의 사람 너뿐야 <br>내가 지금도 숨쉬는 그 이유 <br>길을 걷다 아무런 말도 없이 <br>내려버린 비처럼 <br>어느새 두 눈에 맺혀있다 <br>흘러버린 너란 사람아 <br>언제부턴가 무거운 하루 끝에 <br>믿는 건 하나뿐이야 <br>길을 잃고 헤매이던 <br>날 이끌어 준 향기처럼 넌 <br>보이지 않는 시간 속의 <br>널 지킬게 내 모든 사랑을 <br>두 눈을 감고 가만히 불러 <br>나의 소중한 단 하나의 사람 너뿐야 <br>나 숨쉬는 그 이유 <br>아무리 반대로 나 걸어도 <br>아무리 모르는 척 해봐도 <br>그래도 결국 <br>이 길의 끝에 만나겠지 <br>닫혀 있던 맘조차 <br>조금씩 열고 나를 바라볼 때 <br>너를 부른다 <br>이런 내 전부를 걸고 널 지킬게 <br>가끔은 믿을 수가 없어 꿈 속에서도 <br>우리 둘은 항상 함께 있겠지 <br>가끔은 너무나 아픈 꿈이래도 <br>웃을 수 있는 건 <br>나의 아름다운 너란 이유 때문이야 <br>]]></content><category term="허각" label="허각"/><category term="너란 이유" label="너란 이유"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/육찬미/너의_조각_Feat_김소윤/</id><title>육찬미 - 너의 조각 (Feat. 김소윤) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:05:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:05:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A1%EC%B0%AC%EB%AF%B8/%EB%84%88%EC%9D%98_%EC%A1%B0%EA%B0%81_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EC%86%8C%EC%9C%A4/" title="육찬미 - 너의 조각 (Feat. 김소윤) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 기억 속 오래된 <br>흩어진 너의 조각 <br>다시 너를 그리며 꺼내봐 <br>무뎌져 버린 희미해진 <br>널 다시 맞춰보니 <br>그저 행복했었던 <br>조각 속 비춰진 우리 모습이 <br>먼지 쌓인 채 놓여 있어 <br>그렇게 아름다웠었던 너 <br>가만히 있어도 빛이 났었어 <br>하지만 지금 내 앞에 있는 넌 <br>지치고 힘들어 쓰러질 것 같아 <br>내 기억 속에 남겨진 <br>조각 하나로 <br>하나둘씩 널 그려 보면서 <br>힘겨운 지금을 잊고 <br>처음 널 만난 그때로 <br>새로운 우리가 될 수 있어 <br>그렇게 아름다웠었던 너 <br>가만히 있어도 빛이 났었어 <br>하지만 지금 내 앞에 있는 넌 <br>지치고 힘들어 쓰러질 것 같아 <br>내 기억 속에 남겨진 <br>조각 하나로 <br>하나둘씩 널 그려 보면서 <br>힘겨운 지금을 잊고 <br>처음 널 만난 그때로 <br>새로운 우리가 될 수 있어 <br>멈추지 말고 걸어가 <br>잘못된 길이라 해도 <br>그럴 땐 우리 빛나던 <br>그때를 바라보면 돼 <br>언제나 너와 난 함께니까 <br>내 기억 속에 남겨진 <br>조각 하나로 <br>하나둘씩 널 그려 보면서 <br>힘겨운 지금을 잊고 <br>처음 널 만난 그때로 <br>새로운 우리가 될 수 있어 <br>]]></content><category term="육찬미" label="육찬미"/><category term="너의 조각 (Feat. 김소윤)" label="너의 조각 (Feat. 김소윤)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김페리/Sunday_Love/</id><title>김페리 - Sunday Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:08:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:08:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%8E%98%EB%A6%AC/Sunday_Love/" title="김페리 - Sunday Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꽃잎이 춤추던 <br>여의도 하늘 아래는 <br>꽃잎 떨어지던 <br>그 탁한 하늘 아래에도 난 <br>I’m fall in love with you <br>I wanna be with you <br>늦은 봄을 찾아 <br>겨울을 보낸 우리는 <br>꺼질 수 없었네 <br>바람 부는 언덕에도 <br>I’m fall in love with you <br>I wanna be with you <br>꽃길 사이 그대가 있네 <br>반짝 비친 햇살과 함께 <br>살짝 그대 두 손을 잡고 <br>난 날아가네 <br>Sunday love Sunday love <br>긴 밤을 지나왔네 <br>널 그리던 봄을 보며 <br>잿빛하늘은 여전하지만 <br>푸른 꽃은 빛나네 <br>Sunday love Sunday love <br>꽃길 사이 그대가 있네 <br>반짝 비친 햇살과 함께 <br>살짝 그대 두 손을 잡고 <br>난 날아가네 <br>Sunday love Sunday love <br>긴 밤을 지나왔네 <br>널 그리던 봄을 보며 <br>잿빛하늘은 여전하지만 <br>푸른 꽃은 빛나네 <br>Sunday love Sunday love <br>]]></content><category term="김페리" label="김페리"/><category term="Sunday Love" label="Sunday Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Majid_Jordan/Phases/</id><title>Majid Jordan - Phases - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:08:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:08:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Majid_Jordan/Phases/" title="Majid Jordan - Phases - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I keep going through different phases <br>I stay going through different phases <br>My life's changing and I gotta face it <br>My heart's taking me to different places <br><br>I came to this country, didn't know a damn thing <br>18 year old and in need of planning <br>Thought I was ready, I wasn't ready <br>Guess it's me and myself again <br>Time to go make some friends <br>Find me somebody to keep me safe <br><br>All of these people and all of their names <br>All of this love and all this disdain <br>All of these seasons and all of this change <br>Dreaming of my paradise <br><br>I keep going through different phases <br>I stay going through different phases <br>I keep going through different phases <br>I keep going through different phases <br>I keep going through different phases <br>I keep going through different phases <br><br>Keep thinking am I gonna make it <br>Right now my life is changing <br>Too much for me to take in <br>Feels like the world is going crazy <br><br>All of these people and all of their names <br>All of this love and all this disdain <br>All of these seasons and all of this change <br>Dreaming of my paradise <br><br>I keep going through different phases <br>I keep going through different phases <br>I keep going through different phases <br>I keep going through different phases <br><br>Almost quit on myself, lost my mind at 2AM <br>Have nobody to turn to, had to call on all my strengths <br>It felt like it was over before it even began <br>Dreaming of my paradise <br><br>I keep going through different phases <br>I keep going through different phases <br>I keep going through different phases <br>I keep going through different phases]]></content><category term="Majid Jordan" label="Majid Jordan"/><category term="Phases" label="Phases"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유리애/그대였을까요_Inst/</id><title>유리애 - 그대였을까요 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:08:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:08:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EB%A6%AC%EC%95%A0/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EC%98%80%EC%9D%84%EA%B9%8C%EC%9A%94_Inst/" title="유리애 - 그대였을까요 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대였을까요 내 가슴에 <br>아련한 그리움으로만 남아 <br>이토록 내 맘을 깨어나게 한 <br>그대 이름만으로 <br>그대도 내 맘과 같다면 <br>그 모든 시간 속에 또 내가 산다면 <br>그저 내게는 모든 게 그대인 걸 <br>이렇게 스쳐가는 저 바람처럼 <br>그대 때문에 난 살 수 있었던 거죠 <br>또다시 다가가도 괜찮을까요 <br>그대였을까요 내 하루에 <br>온종일 날 따라다니던 기억 <br>이토록 나의 맘을 멈춰 서게 한 <br>그대 기억만으로 <br>그대도 내 맘과 같다면 <br>그 모든 시간 속에 또 내가 산다면 <br>그저 내게는 모든 게 그대인 걸 <br>이렇게 스쳐가는 저 바람처럼 <br>그대 때문에 난 살 수 있었던 거죠 <br>또다시 다가가도 괜찮을까요 <br>모든 순간이 그대였죠 <br>한 걸음만 내게 다가와 줘 <br>기억만으로 버텨왔던 시간들 <br>그 많은 추억으로 난 살아왔죠 <br>하루 또 하루 나는 기다릴 수 있죠 <br>또다시 시작할 수 있을까요 <br>그대였나 봐요 <br>]]></content><category term="유리애" label="유리애"/><category term="그대였을까요 (Inst.)" label="그대였을까요 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유리애/그대였을까요/</id><title>유리애 - 그대였을까요 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:08:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:08:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EB%A6%AC%EC%95%A0/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EC%98%80%EC%9D%84%EA%B9%8C%EC%9A%94/" title="유리애 - 그대였을까요 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대였을까요 내 가슴에 <br>아련한 그리움으로만 남아 <br>이토록 내 맘을 깨어나게 한 <br>그대 이름만으로 <br>그대도 내 맘과 같다면 <br>그 모든 시간 속에 또 내가 산다면 <br>그저 내게는 모든 게 그대인 걸 <br>이렇게 스쳐가는 저 바람처럼 <br>그대 때문에 난 살 수 있었던 거죠 <br>또다시 다가가도 괜찮을까요 <br>그대였을까요 내 하루에 <br>온종일 날 따라다니던 기억 <br>이토록 나의 맘을 멈춰 서게 한 <br>그대 기억만으로 <br>그대도 내 맘과 같다면 <br>그 모든 시간 속에 또 내가 산다면 <br>그저 내게는 모든 게 그대인 걸 <br>이렇게 스쳐가는 저 바람처럼 <br>그대 때문에 난 살 수 있었던 거죠 <br>또다시 다가가도 괜찮을까요 <br>모든 순간이 그대였죠 <br>한 걸음만 내게 다가와 줘 <br>기억만으로 버텨왔던 시간들 <br>그 많은 추억으로 난 살아왔죠 <br>하루 또 하루 나는 기다릴 수 있죠 <br>또다시 시작할 수 있을까요 <br>그대였나 봐요 <br>]]></content><category term="유리애" label="유리애"/><category term="그대였을까요" label="그대였을까요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서예안/쉬는날/</id><title>서예안 - 쉬는날 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:08:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:08:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EC%98%88%EC%95%88/%EC%89%AC%EB%8A%94%EB%82%A0/" title="서예안 - 쉬는날 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너와 입맞추고 <br>익숙한 니 손잡고 <br>걸어가던 길을 지나쳐왔어 <br>평소처럼 우리 많이 바빠 <br>만나지 못했던 그날이 <br>너무 길어져 가 <br>요즘 널 생각할 때면 <br>눈물이 나는걸 <br>왜 우리 쉬는 날이 많은 건지 <br>나는 왜 자꾸 그리워하는데 <br>이렇게 붙잡고 싶은데 <br>너는 보이지 않아 <br>I wanna meet you <br>널 기다리는 밤이 <br>왜 자꾸 길어만 지는 건지 <br>I want you go back <br>우리 사랑했던 그날들로 <br>다시 돌아가 <br>I miss you babe <br>너와 꿈을 꾸고 <br>너와 약속했었던 <br>수많은 시간이 지나가버리고 <br>텅 빈 방에 앉아 <br>돌아오지 않는 날들을 <br>다시 또 그리워하는데 <br>사진 속 날 바라볼 때면 <br>날 웃게 했던 니 흔적이 <br>왜 이렇게 많은 건지 <br>너는 왜 자꾸 멀어져 가는데 <br>이렇게 보내긴 싫은데 <br>너는 보이지 않아 <br>I wanna meet you <br>널 기다리는 밤이 <br>왜 자꾸 길어만 지는 건지 <br>I want you go back <br>우리 사랑했던 그날들로 <br>다시 돌아가 <br>I miss you babe <br>니가 너무 보고 싶어서 <br>두 눈을 감아도 <br>자꾸 니가 떠올라 <br>Don't leave me babe <br>You Don't leave me babe <br>Hold me tight in your arms <br>I wanna meet you <br>널 기다리는 밤이 <br>왜 자꾸 길어만 지는 건지 <br>I want you go back <br>우리 사랑했던 그날들로 <br>다시 돌아가 <br>I miss you babe <br>]]></content><category term="서예안" label="서예안"/><category term="쉬는날" label="쉬는날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GURBAN_지어반/줄거야_Inst/</id><title>G.URBAN (지어반) - 줄거야 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:08:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:08:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GURBAN_%EC%A7%80%EC%96%B4%EB%B0%98/%EC%A4%84%EA%B1%B0%EC%95%BC_Inst/" title="G.URBAN (지어반) - 줄거야 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하얀 시트 위에 배인 <br>너의 향기가 너무 좋아 <br>헝클어진 네 모습이 <br>귀여워 귀여워 뿌우 <br>이 음악 어때 널 위해 만들었어 <br>너무 지칠 때 잠이 안 올 때 <br>들어주면 좋겠어 <br>Feeling in your eyes <br>넌 웃을 때 제일 예뻐 <br>오늘 밤은 <br>baby close your eyes <br>아무 걱정하지마 <br>You and me <br>내 품에 하루 종일 안겨서 baby <br>잠이 들 때까지 노래 불러줄 거야 <br>아이처럼 나를 보는 너를 <br>꽉 안아주고 싶어 <br>사랑스런 그 눈빛이 <br>내 맘을 설레게 해 <br>나의 품속에 안긴 너를 볼 때면 <br>너무 예뻐서 눈을 뜨고도 <br>꿈을 꾸는 것 같아 <br>Feeling in your eyes <br>넌 웃을 때 제일 예뻐 <br>오늘 밤은 <br>baby close your eyes <br>아무 걱정하지마 <br>You and me <br>내 품에 하루 종일 안겨서 baby <br>잠이 들 때까지 노래 불러줄 거야 <br>너의 작은 무엇 하나도 놓치지 않게 <br>모두 내 맘속에 담아둘 거야 oh <br>너의 조각들이 지금처럼 <br>내 안에 반짝일 수 있게 <br>Feeling in your eyes <br>넌 웃을 때 제일 예뻐 <br>오늘 밤은 <br>baby close your eyes <br>아무 걱정하지마 <br>You and me <br>내 품에 하루 종일 안겨서 baby <br>잠이 들 때까지 노래 불러줄 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="G.URBAN (지어반)" label="G.URBAN (지어반)"/><category term="줄거야 (Inst.)" label="줄거야 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GURBAN_지어반/줄거야/</id><title>G.URBAN (지어반) - 줄거야 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:08:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:08:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GURBAN_%EC%A7%80%EC%96%B4%EB%B0%98/%EC%A4%84%EA%B1%B0%EC%95%BC/" title="G.URBAN (지어반) - 줄거야 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하얀 시트 위에 배인 <br>너의 향기가 너무 좋아 <br>헝클어진 네 모습이 <br>귀여워 귀여워 뿌우 <br>이 음악 어때 널 위해 만들었어 <br>너무 지칠 때 잠이 안 올 때 <br>들어주면 좋겠어 <br>Feeling in your eyes <br>넌 웃을 때 제일 예뻐 <br>오늘 밤은 <br>baby close your eyes <br>아무 걱정하지마 <br>You and me <br>내 품에 하루 종일 안겨서 baby <br>잠이 들 때까지 노래 불러줄 거야 <br>아이처럼 나를 보는 너를 <br>꽉 안아주고 싶어 <br>사랑스런 그 눈빛이 <br>내 맘을 설레게 해 <br>나의 품속에 안긴 너를 볼 때면 <br>너무 예뻐서 눈을 뜨고도 <br>꿈을 꾸는 것 같아 <br>Feeling in your eyes <br>넌 웃을 때 제일 예뻐 <br>오늘 밤은 <br>baby close your eyes <br>아무 걱정하지마 <br>You and me <br>내 품에 하루 종일 안겨서 baby <br>잠이 들 때까지 노래 불러줄 거야 <br>너의 작은 무엇 하나도 놓치지 않게 <br>모두 내 맘속에 담아둘 거야 oh <br>너의 조각들이 지금처럼 <br>내 안에 반짝일 수 있게 <br>Feeling in your eyes <br>넌 웃을 때 제일 예뻐 <br>오늘 밤은 <br>baby close your eyes <br>아무 걱정하지마 <br>You and me <br>내 품에 하루 종일 안겨서 baby <br>잠이 들 때까지 노래 불러줄 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="G.URBAN (지어반)" label="G.URBAN (지어반)"/><category term="줄거야" label="줄거야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Error_Of_Our_Ways/</id><title>The Temptations - Error Of Our Ways - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:10:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:10:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Error_Of_Our_Ways/" title="The Temptations - Error Of Our Ways - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Listen <br>Somethin's goin wrong <br>Is it in the homes <br>Kids killin kids <br>Ain't nothing safe <br>They take guns to school <br>And break all the rules <br>It's a shame the way that we're livin <br>They're fighting in Bosnia <br>And starving in Sumaria <br>From free loving days <br>And now there is AIDS <br>Our values have changed Oh, yes they've changed <br>People acting strange yeah <br>You have to watch your backooh <br>Babies born on crack, oh <br><br>The error of our ways <br>Can we correct the mistakes we've made <br>I hope it's not too late <br>God only knows our fate <br>The error of our ways <br>Let's hope for a better day <br>Somethin's got to change <br>Let us pray <br>Famlies accused of child abuse <br>You don't know who's tellin the truth <br>Society is like a sword <br>That needs killing that's for sure <br>Great forest are dying <br>People standing in Welfare lines <br><br>Ecology is unbalanced <br>It's a challenge <br>A strange situation <br>We lost a whole generation <br>The news on the air <br>Beware of the colors that you wear <br>The police are undefined oh, yes they are <br>Beware when you drive or you might get jacked <br>We gotta make a stand oh, yes we do <br>Cause things are out of hand <br><br>Why Are there so many guns <br>Tell me why So much death among the young <br>Why Oh tell me why <br>Tell me why It's not easy for you to see <br>Why Can't there be any peace <br>Tell me why Can't we undo all the wrong that we've done <br>Why Oh it's up to you and me <br>They're fighting in Bosnia <br>And starving in Sumaria <br>From free loving days <br>And now there is AIDS <br>Our values have changed Oh <br>People acting strange yeah <br>You have to watch your back oh, yeah <br>Babies born on crack]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Error Of Our Ways" label="Error Of Our Ways"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Hoops_Of_Fire/</id><title>The Temptations - Hoops Of Fire - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:10:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:10:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Hoops_Of_Fire/" title="The Temptations - Hoops Of Fire - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Finding you was incredible <br>Losing you would be unbearable <br>For you woman, I'd go through hoops of fire <br><br>Somethings are impossible <br>'Cause some folks never try <br>Some folks see an obstacle <br>And they never get by <br><br>I used to be that way before <br>I met you, baby <br>But the force of your gentle touch <br>Too much is not enough for me <br><br>Whoa, I'll go through hoops of fire <br>I'll do anything <br>Anything <br>To get close to you <br><br>I'll go through hoops of fire <br>To prove to you <br>To prove to you <br>That no one else will do <br><br>And nothing can keep me from you <br>No, no, no, no, baby <br><br>Finding you was incredible <br>In every way, you show me why <br>Why girl <br>Losing you would be unbearable <br>I'd lose the meaning you've brought to my life <br><br>You've done for me <br>What no one else could ever do <br>Through your love I've got the strength <br>To face up to anything <br>God, I'm telling you the truth <br><br>I would go through <br>Hoops of fire <br>To prove to you <br>To prove to you <br>That no one else will do <br><br>Nothing <br>Nothing <br>Will keep me <br>Keep me from you <br><br>I'll take a chance <br>I'd risk it all <br>I'll get back on my feet <br>If I should happen to fall <br><br>It's all because of you <br>That I am what I am <br>I'll get down on my knees <br>If you ask me to, don't you know <br><br>I'd go through <br>Hoops <br>Oh yes I will baby <br>Of fire <br>Whoa, I'll do anything <br>Anything <br>To get close to you <br><br>Ah hoops <br>Ah my, my, my, my, my, my, my, baby <br>Of fire <br>Oh yes I will, I'll prove to you <br>Prove to you <br>That no one else is gonna do <br><br>No <br>Nothing <br>Nothing <br>Could keep me <br>Is gonna keep me from you, baby, baby <br><br>Oh oh, hoops of fire <br>I'll go through hoops of fire <br>Oh I'll do anything <br>Anything <br>To get close to you, baby]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Hoops Of Fire" label="Hoops Of Fire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Special/</id><title>The Temptations - Special - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Special/" title="The Temptations - Special - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey there pretty lady <br>Love has come my way <br>So nice to be involved <br>It's tough out there these days <br><br>I got my weather 'cause I'm so wrapped up in you <br>My heart is on the line <br>Tell me what more can I do, pretty baby <br>'Cause you're special, hey <br>Girl, you make me feel real good <br>Special to me, you see, you are special <br>Baby, you're so special to me <br><br>Hey baby, I can't believe the things you've done for me <br>You put me back on the right track <br>Think about you constantly <br>And I know in your heart that you feel the same way for me, baby <br>Late nights with me all alone, it's total ecstasy <br><br>All I can do is think about the the times <br>When I'm making sweet love to you <br>And there seems to be, I'm tellin' you girl <br>Some kind of magic when we touch <br>Don't you leave <br>Special, yeah, you are <br><br>Girl you make me feel real good <br>So special to me, you see <br>Baby girl, you're special <br>So special to me, baby <br>Hey baby <br><br>Girl, you make me feel so good <br>You make me feel so good, hey <br>And all I can do is think about the the times <br>When I'm making sweet love to you, baby <br>And there seems to be <br>Some kinda magic when we touch <br>Don't you go nowhere, don't you leave <br><br>Special, so special, special to me, you see <br>You're a special part of me, love <br>So special to me, baby <br>Oh, you put me back on the right track, baby <br>And I like that, oh you're so good <br>So special to me, you see <br><br>I put my heart on the line any time <br>'Cause I know that you'll let us guarantee, baby <br>You're so special]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Special" label="Special"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Soul_To_Soul/</id><title>The Temptations - Soul To Soul - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Soul_To_Soul/" title="The Temptations - Soul To Soul - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Mmmmmmh mmmmh mmmmh <br>Mmmh mmmh mmmh <br>Mmmmmmh mmmh mmmh mmmh mmmh mmmh <br>Soul to Soul Soul to soul <br>Sooooul mmmh mmmh mmmmmmh <br>Oh whoa whoa soul to soul <br><br>Piece of newspaper At my feet <br>We go blowing down the street <br>Got out stories old and new <br>Need someone to tell 'em to <br><br>We don't have to be eye to eye face to face <br>I'm not asking for miracles nor saving grace <br>And I don't need another heart to have and hold <br>All I want is a friend I can talk to soul to soul <br>Oh soul to soul soul to soul <br>Mmmmmh <br><br>Like a notebook On a shelf <br>Tired of talking to myself <br>Wishing somebody somebody passing by passing by <br>Would pick me up and look inside <br><br>We don't have to be eye to eye or face to face <br>I'm not asking for miracles miracles or saving grace <br>And I don't need another heart I don't need another heart to have and hold <br>All I want is a friend I can talk to soul to soul <br>Soul to soul Oh soul to soul soul to soul <br>Mmmmmh <br><br>Everyone needs someone to turn to <br>When they walk in their line got to hold that line <br>And we all need a friend we can cry to <br>And I'm out on that line I'm on that line <br>Hehe <br>It's been so long now you know I'm needing mine <br><br>Oh whoaaaa whoaaaa whoaaa <br>Oh my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my <br>All I want is a friend I can talk to woe woe woe woe soul to soul <br>I just call and there you are soul to soul <br>Shining on me like a star shining down <br>Smile in my direction in the night oooooh oooooh oooooh <br>And I feel your light yeah oh oh soul to soul <br>I'm feeling stronger now, so much stronger now soul to soul <br>Won't you shine a little longer, a little longer right now <br>I'm still holding that line got to hold that line yeah <br>Keep me holding that line <br>Oh oh my <br><br>We don't have to be eye to eye or meet face to face <br>I'm not asking for miracles or saving grace <br>And I don't need another heart to have and hold <br>All I want is someone I can talk to soul to soul <br>Oh I need a friend right now <br>sooooul to soul <br>Someone I can talk to <br><br>I'm feeling lonely right now right now baby <br>I just need to know you're there anytime of the day and night <br>I need somebody who's willing to listen <br>Shining, shining, shining, shining so brightly right now <br>I feel like I'm carrying the weight of the world on my shoulders <br>So much soul <br>Does anyone hear me calling]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Soul To Soul" label="Soul To Soul"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Wonder_Who_Shes_Seeing_Now/</id><title>The Temptations - I Wonder Who She`s Seeing Now - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Wonder_Who_Shes_Seeing_Now/" title="The Temptations - I Wonder Who She`s Seeing Now - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was playin for keeps <br>But she was playin' a game <br>Now she's gone and left <br>And I don't know if I'll ever be the same <br><br>I wonder who she's seeing now <br>I wonder who she's holding now <br>I wonder who she's seeing now <br>I wonder who she's foolin' <br><br>She doesn't know now <br>She's tearing me apart <br>Breaking my heart, well <br>Doesn't know what I'm goin' through <br>I don't know what I'm gonna do <br>It's getting harder every single day <br><br>Without her <br>I wonder who she's seeing now <br>Oh I wish that I knew <br>I wonder who she's holding now <br>I wonder who she's seeing now <br>I wonder who she's foolin' <br><br>If I could find a way to turn back the tide <br>When she was still mine <br>To the love I'll remember with <br>I'll hold her in my arms again <br>And never let her slip away <br><br>I wonder who she's seeing now <br>I wonder who she's holding now <br>I guess it's more than breathing hard <br>I wonder who she's foolin' <br><br>I wonder who she's seeing now <br>I wonder who the girl's seeing right now <br><br>Even though she'd be gone today <br>Now I got to find my own way, yeah <br>Even though I need her more each day <br><br>I wonder, I wonder who she's seeing now <br>I wonder who's holding her right now <br>I don't know, I wonder who's she seeing now <br>I wonder who she's foolin', baby <br><br>I wonder, I wonder who she's foolin' now <br>I wonder who she's foolin' now <br>I wonder who she's seeing now <br>I wonder who she's fooling <br><br>If they got everything you need <br>But they gave you all the love you want <br>'Cause they know how to love you baby, love you baby <br>Love you baby]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="I Wonder Who She`s Seeing Now" label="I Wonder Who She`s Seeing Now"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Lady_Soul/</id><title>The Temptations - Lady Soul - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Lady_Soul/" title="The Temptations - Lady Soul - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh <br>Oh wo oh wo oh wo oh wo <br>Oh wo oh wo oh wo oh wo <br>Oh wo oh wo oh wo oh wo <br>My lady soul <br><br>Lying here beside you <br>Close as we can be <br>I know what this leads to <br>I know what you need, yeah <br><br>I'm ready to surrender, my love <br>Lay it all in your hands <br>Give you my forever <br>Everything I am <br><br>'Cause you are my, my, my, my lady soul <br>You warm my heart <br>When I grow cold <br>Oh you are my, my, my, my lady soul <br>You are my life <br>You make me whole <br>Oh wo oh wo oh wo oh wo <br>Oh wo oh wo oh wo oh wo <br>My lady soul <br><br>I feel it in your heartbeat <br>Hear it in your crys <br>This is where our hearts meet <br>I see it in your eyes <br><br>I've waited for this moment, my love <br>It's a dream come alive <br>Heaven must have sent me <br>An angel of the night <br><br>'Cause you are my, my, my, my lady soul <br>You warm my heart <br>When I grow cold <br>'Cause you are my, you're my, you're my, my lady soul <br>You're my lady soul <br>You are my life <br>You make me whole <br><br>I always knew we'd end up together <br>Right from the very start <br>And I believe we'll make it forever <br>It's written right here in my heart <br><br>Oh yeah Aii Hoo <br>You're my, you're my, my lady soul <br>You warm my heart <br>When I grow cold <br>Oh you are my, my, my, my lady soul <br>You are my life <br>You make me whole <br>Oh wo oh wo oh wo oh wo <br>Oh wo oh wo oh wo oh wo <br>My lady soul]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Lady Soul" label="Lady Soul"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Do_You_Really_Love_Your_Baby/</id><title>The Temptations - Do You Really Love Your Baby - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Do_You_Really_Love_Your_Baby/" title="The Temptations - Do You Really Love Your Baby - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do you really love your baby <br>Do you care <br>Do you really love your baby <br>Do you really really care <br>I really wanna know <br><br>Do you mean what you say <br>When you say that you love me, baby <br>Tell me now <br><br>If you're going away <br>Will she come back to find me playing <br>Never <br><br>You're away on your love boat <br>Now do you love any other <br>Do you dare if the temptation is there <br>How much do you dare <br><br>Do you really love her <br>Do you love her <br>Do you really love your baby <br>Do you love her <br><br>Now I know what it is <br>When you're touched by that lovely feeling <br>And if you're going away <br>If you need someone for sensual healing, all right <br><br>There comes a time when you hunger <br>And you hate being, being far away <br>What do you do when the temptation is there <br>How much do you dare <br><br>Do you really love your baby <br>Do you care <br>Do you really love your baby <br>Do you love her <br><br>It's not easy to love someone <br>'Cause being free is a lot of fun <br>Do you know what you're gonna do <br>I've got me feeling, don't you ever lose <br><br>Do you love your baby <br>Do you love her <br><br>There comes a time when you hunger <br>And you hate being, being far away <br>What do you do when the temptation is there <br>How much do you dare <br><br>Do you really love your baby <br>Do you care <br>Do you love her <br><br>Do you really love your baby <br>Do you really, really care <br>Do you love her <br><br>Do you love your baby <br>Do you love her <br>Do you love your baby <br>Do you care]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Do You Really Love Your Baby" label="Do You Really Love Your Baby"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/My_Love_Is_True_Truly_For_You/</id><title>The Temptations - My Love Is True (Truly For You) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/My_Love_Is_True_Truly_For_You/" title="The Temptations - My Love Is True (Truly For You) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh <br>oh, oh, oh, oh <br>oh, yeah, baby <br>Whoa, whoa, oh, oh <br>Mm <br><br>Now I, m the kinda guy who don't believe <br>That chivalry is dead, no <br>'Cause I believe a woman should be treated <br>With the utmost respect, mm, hm <br><br>Don't be afraid, don't turn and walk away <br>I wanna get to know ya, well <br>Don't be ashamed, don't say that love's to blame <br>Just come and look me over <br><br>You'll find a heart that you've always been lookin' for <br>How could anybody ask for much more, woo, ho <br><br>Now I like openin' doors <br>Pickin' up Yeah her hanky Yeah off the floor <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br>Light her cigarette if she smokes <br>Even Help her with her coat, well <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br><br>In this world of liberation <br>It's so easy to forget, mmm <br>That it's so nice to have a man around <br>To lend a helping hand, you can bet, bet you can, baby <br><br>When I was young, my mama used to say, Boy <br>A woman's like a flower, with love on her you shower <br>Ever since that day, her words never went away <br>I always will remember to treat my baby tender <br><br>You'll find a heart that you've always been lookin' for <br>How could anybody ask for much more, whoa, oh, oh <br><br>Now I like openin' doors <br>Pickin' up Yeah her hanky Yeah off the floor <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br>Light her cigarette if she smokes <br>Even Help her with her coat, oh, whoa <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br><br>Compliment her in her hair <br>Even help her with her chair <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br>She's a bad son, of, a, gun <br>I'm her lovin' Don Juan <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br><br>oh, ho, ho, ho, ho, oh <br>Whoa, oh, oh <br>Hey, hey <br>Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, baby <br>Every day, ever way <br>Hey, hey <br>Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey <br><br>You'll find a heart that you've always been lookin' for <br>How could anybody ask for much more, whoa, whoa, oh, oh <br><br>Now I like openin' doors <br>Pickin' up Yeah her hanky Yeah off the floor <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br>Light her cigarette if she smokes <br>Even Help her with her coat, help her out <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br><br>Compliment her in her hair <br>Even help her with her chair <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br>Now boy, you should remember <br>To be a gentleman <br>Treat her like a lady <br><br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like a lady <br>Treat her like, treat her like Hey, hey <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like a lady <br><br>Treat her like Well, treat her like <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like a lady <br>Treat her like, treat her like oh, ho <br>Treat her like a lady Ho, ho, oh, my, my, treat her like a lady]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="My Love Is True (Truly For You)" label="My Love Is True (Truly For You)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Treat_Her_Like_A_Lady/</id><title>The Temptations - Treat Her Like A Lady - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Treat_Her_Like_A_Lady/" title="The Temptations - Treat Her Like A Lady - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ooh ooh oh ooh oh ooh <br>Ooh ooh oh ooh <br>Ooh, yeah, baby <br>Whoa whoa oh oh <br>Mmm <br><br>Now I m the kinda guy who don't believe <br>That chivalry is dead, no <br>'Cause I believe a woman should be treated <br>With the utmost respect, mmm hmm <br><br>Don't be afraid, don't turn and walk away <br>I wanna get to know ya, well <br>Don't be ashamed, don't say that love's to blame <br>Just come and look me over <br><br>You'll find a heart <br>You'll find a heart that you've always been lookin' for <br>How could anybody ask for much more, woo hoo <br><br>Now I like openin' doors <br>Pickin' up Yeah her hanky Yeah off the floor <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br>Light her cigarette if she smokes <br>Even Help her with her coat, well <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br><br>In this world of liberation <br>It's so easy to forget, mmm <br>That it's so nice to have a man around <br>To lend a helping hand, you can bet, bet you can, baby <br><br>When I was young, my mama used to say, Boy <br>A woman's like a flower, with love on her you shower <br>Ever since that day, her words never went away <br>I always will remember to treat my baby tender <br><br>You'll find a heart <br>You'll find a heart that you've always been lookin' for <br>How could anybody ask for much more, whoa ooh ooh <br><br>Now I like openin' doors <br>Pickin' up Yeah her hanky Yeah off the floor <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br>Light her cigarette if she smokes <br>Even Help her with her coat, oh, whoa <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br><br>Compliment her in her hair <br>Even help her with her chair <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br>She's a bad son of a gun <br>I'm her lovin' Don Juan <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br><br>Ooh hoo hoo hoo hoo ooh <br>Whoa oh oh <br>Hey hey <br>Whoa oh oh oh oh baby <br>Every day, ever way <br>Hey, hey <br>Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey <br><br>You'll find a heart <br>You'll find a heart that you've always been lookin' for <br>How could anybody ask for much more, whoa whoa oh ooh <br><br>Now I like openin' doors <br>Pickin' up Yeah her hanky Yeah off the floor <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br>Light her cigarette if she smokes <br>Even Help her with her coat, help her out <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br><br>Compliment her in her hair <br>Even help her with her chair <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like lady <br>Now boy, you should remember <br>To be a gentleman <br>Treat her like a lady <br><br>You better Treat her like Well, treat her like Ho <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like a lady <br>Treat her like, treat her like Hey ey <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like a lady <br><br>Treat her like Well, treat her like <br>Treat her like a lady Treat her like a lady <br>Treat her like, treat her like Ooh hoo <br>Treat her like a lady Hoo hoo oh, my, my, treat her like a lady]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Treat Her Like A Lady" label="Treat Her Like A Lady"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Sail_Away/</id><title>The Temptations - Sail Away - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Sail_Away/" title="The Temptations - Sail Away - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know what your folks got against me, girl <br>But I do know that I want you permanently in my world <br>What's age or color or money when you love one another <br>I know you keep saying to me 'Our love will win and then you'll see' <br><br>But baby, sail away with me <br>I can't wait another day <br>So you and I can be free, oh baby <br>To share our love under the stars above <br>We'll spend the rest of our lives making love <br>Morning, noon, and night <br><br>Take the wings from a bird and don't you know it can't fly <br>If they take your love from me, I will surely die <br>Don't get lost in all they're saying <br>Games are all that they're playing <br>I know you keep saying to me 'Our Love will win and then you'll see' <br><br>But baby, sail away with me <br>I can't wait another day, girl <br>So you and I can be free, oh baby <br>To share our love under the stars above <br>We'll spend the rest of our lives making love <br>Morning, noon, and night baby <br><br>Yeah baaby <br>True love is a once in a lifetime thing, my dear <br>We can't let what others think about us destroy what we share <br>You said 'We can take the rejection <br>We can build a wall of protection' <br>I can feel the pressure closing in all around us <br>Girl don't let them destroy our love <br><br>But baby, sail away with me <br>Where you, girl, and I can be free <br>We're gonna share our love under the stars above <br>We'll spend the rest of our lives making love morning, noon and night]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Sail Away" label="Sail Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Standing_On_The_Top_Pt1___Single_Ver_Feat_Rick_James/</id><title>The Temptations - Standing On The Top (Pt.1 / Single Ver.) (Feat. Rick James) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Standing_On_The_Top_Pt1___Single_Ver_Feat_Rick_James/" title="The Temptations - Standing On The Top (Pt.1 / Single Ver.) (Feat. Rick James) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yi yi yi yi yi yi yi <br><br>When you're on the top <br>There's no place you can really go but down, down, down <br>People on the street congratulate you <br>They say they love the way you sound, well <br><br>When you're on the low <br>No one wants to chit or chat or even know your name <br>Your agent's never there <br>Your manager has ripped you off and gone somewhere <br>Standing on the top <br><br>Standing on the top, top <br>On the top getting down, yeah <br>Standing on the top Yeah, top <br>On the top getting down, Temptations sing <br><br>Standing on the top, top <br>Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh <br>Standing on the top, top <br>Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh <br><br>When you're on the top <br>Everyone you meet they wanna be your long lost friend <br>They say how great you are, a superstar <br>But do you have any money to lend <br>Hey, man, can you loan me a few bucks <br><br>When you're on the low <br>Where do all the freaks and fancy people go, I don't know I don't know <br>People sit and stare <br>Askin' crazy questions, Do you braid your hair and What's L 7 Square <br><br>Standing on the top, top <br>On the top getting down, ho <br><br>Heyhoo <br><br>Standing on the top, top <br>On the top getting down, down, down, down <br>Standing on the top Sing <br>Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh Well, well, well, well, well, well <br>Standing on the top Well <br>Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh Standing on the top getting down <br><br>Can you understand it We understand it <br>Can you understand it what I'm talkin' about <br>When I say that funk is here to stay We understand it <br>Can you understand it what I'm talkin' about <br>That funk is here to stay, oh We understand it <br>If you understand it say, Yeah Yeahyeah <br><br>We want the funk <br>We want the funk and nothing else We want the funk <br>We want the funk and nothing else will do <br><br>We want the funk <br>We want the funk and nothing else We want the funk <br>We want the funk and nothing else will do <br><br>We want the funk <br>We want the funk and nothing else We want the funk <br>We want the funk and nothing else will do <br><br>We want the funk <br>We want the funk and nothing else We want the funk]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Standing On The Top (Pt.1 / Single Ver.) (Feat. Rick James)" label="Standing On The Top (Pt.1 / Single Ver.) (Feat. Rick James)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Aiming_At_Your_Heart/</id><title>The Temptations - Aiming At Your Heart - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Aiming_At_Your_Heart/" title="The Temptations - Aiming At Your Heart - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tell me how you been <br>Well, it's so good to be seein' you again <br>Lady, you're so fine <br>I wish there was a way I could share your time <br><br>I need someone in my life <br>'Cause I'm lonely, yeah, for your lovin' <br>You make me feel so alive <br>You're the woman and nobody else will do <br><br>That's why I'm aimin' at your heart, aimin' <br>Aimin' at your heart, aimin', aimin' <br>Aimin' at your heart, aimin' <br>Aimin' at your heart <br><br>Why don't you love me, don't be shy <br>Like the wings of an eagle, let your feelings fly <br>Precious shinin' star <br>Do I need me a rocket to be where you are <br><br>I need someone in my life <br>'Cause I'm lonely for your lovin' <br>Ooh, girl, you make me feel so alive <br>You're the woman and nobody else would do <br><br>That's why I'm aimin' at your heart, aimin' <br>Aimin' at your heart, aimin', aimin' <br>Aimin' at your heart, aimin' <br>Aimin' at your heart <br><br>Aimin' at your heart]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Aiming At Your Heart" label="Aiming At Your Heart"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Power/</id><title>The Temptations - Power - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Power/" title="The Temptations - Power - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Power, boom boom boom <br><br>My hands are clean <br>My heart is so pure <br>The world is sick <br>I am the cure <br>I don't want no money, gold or gifts <br>Give me your minds and souls to lift <br>Put you faith and trust in me <br>I'll move your mountains <br>Part your sea <br>All you poor, all you needy <br>All you're doin' is givin' to the greedy <br>All you poor, all you needy <br>All you're doin' is givin' to the greedy <br>Get off your knees, believe in me <br>I'll set you free <br><br>All I need's a little more power <br>Power, power, power, power, power <br>Power, power, power, power <br><br>I have for you a master plan <br>To lead you to the promised land <br>I give you peace, I give you pride <br>I save you from mass suicide <br>I'm your hope, your one salvation <br>I'm your one man United Nation <br>All you poor, all you needy <br>All you're doin' is givin' to the greedy <br>All you poor, all you needy <br>All you're doin' is givin' to the greedy <br>Tell me your sins, I'll be your friend <br>I won't do you in <br><br>All I need's a little more power <br>Power, power, power, power, power <br>Power, power, power, power <br><br>Gotta have, gotta have, gotta have, gotta have, more power <br>Got to have more power <br>Gotta have, gotta have, gotta have, gotta have, more power <br><br>I'll open up Heaven's door <br>Take from the rich, give to the poor <br>Take the heart of a country, work on the mind <br>Of the old and the young, one at a time <br>Give them a new identity <br>Make them all dress like you and me <br>Get off your knees, believe in me <br>I'll set you free <br>All I need's a little more power <br><br>I'll make you all the master race <br>Just put me in my godly place <br>We'll march the world down in defeat <br>Take the fields of oil and the lands of wheat <br>Power, I need it, more, I got to have it <br>More, I want it, more <br><br>One thing I must make perfectly clear <br>Nuclear weapons, all men fear <br>Their hands sweat, their fingers itch <br>I'm the only one you can trust with the switch <br>Give it to me <br><br>Give it to me, more <br>Give it to me, more <br>I need it, gotta have it <br>I must have it, more <br>Give it to me, more <br>Give it to me, more <br>More, more, more, more <br><br>More power]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Power" label="Power"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/In_A_Lifetime/</id><title>The Temptations - In A Lifetime - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/In_A_Lifetime/" title="The Temptations - In A Lifetime - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What am I going to do <br><br>Since you went away <br>I ain't had nothing much to say, no <br>I been keeping to myself the reasons why you left <br>I walked around bewildered <br>Because she caught me in the wrong <br>There was nothing I could say <br>To keep her from leaving home <br><br>I'll never find another love like yours in a lifetime <br>In a lifetime baby <br>I'll never find another love like yours in a lifetime <br>In a lifetime <br><br>I know that I was wrong <br>Because you can't share love with two <br><br>I just took a chance <br>A chance on losing you <br>I lost my pride and joy because <br>I was careless with her heart <br>I didn't believe nothing could ever tear us apart <br><br>I'll never find another love like yours in a lifetime <br>In a lifetime baby <br>I'll never find another love like yours in a lifetime <br>In a lifetime baby <br><br>I'll never find oh never find <br>Another love never ever find <br>In a lifetime, in a lifetime <br>Oh I'll never find oh never find <br>Another love never ever find <br>In a lifetime, in a lifetime <br><br>It'll shake your world over <br>I ain't never found no loving like you do <br>I'll never find another love like yours in a lifetime <br>In a lifetime <br>In a lifetime baby <br>I'll never find another love like yours in a lifetime <br>In a lifetime <br>In a lifetime baby]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="In A Lifetime" label="In A Lifetime"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Darling_Stand_By_Me_Song_For_My_Woman/</id><title>The Temptations - Darling, Stand By Me (Song For My Woman) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Darling_Stand_By_Me_Song_For_My_Woman/" title="The Temptations - Darling, Stand By Me (Song For My Woman) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When the night has come <br>And the land is dark <br>And the moon is the only light we see <br>No I won't be afraid <br>No I won't be afraid <br>Just as long as you stand, stand by me <br><br>And darling, darling stand by me <br>Oh, now, now, stand by me <br>Stand by me, stand by me <br><br>If the sky that we look upon <br>Should tumble and fall <br>And the mountain should crumble to the sea <br>I won't cry, I won't cry <br>No I won't shed a tear <br>Just as long as you stand, stand by me <br><br>And darling, darling stand by me <br>Oh, stand by me <br>Stand by me, stand by me, stand by me <br><br>Whenever you're in trouble won't you stand by me <br>Oh, now, now, stand by me <br>Oh, stand by me, stand by me, stand by me <br><br>Darling, darling stand by me <br>Stand by me <br>Oh stand by me, stand by me, stand by me]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Darling, Stand By Me (Song For My Woman)" label="Darling, Stand By Me (Song For My Woman)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Keep_Holding_On/</id><title>The Temptations - Keep Holding On - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Keep_Holding_On/" title="The Temptations - Keep Holding On - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Your truth is like <br>A woman brought me <br>Since I've been here <br>A woman taught me <br><br>Don't worry about <br>What you can't control <br>Do your best <br>And leave the rest alone <br><br>Keep holding on <br>Sometimes your back is against the wall <br>Keep hanging on <br>Hang on <br>You gotta keep holding on <br>You know I <br><br>Enjoy these chains <br>Your so bright <br>'Cause you never <br>You gotta celebrate, celebrate <br>Every day you live <br><br>I still remember <br>Since I was just a child <br>My mother held me in her arms <br>Mama said, that every day <br><br>You got to keep holding on <br>Don't let nothin' get around you <br>Keep holding on <br>Hang on <br>You gotta keep holding on <br><br>Son, gotta keep holding on <br>Crowd cheers <br>Hang on tight <br>Give your life a fight <br>You gotta be strong <br>Keep on pushing on <br><br>Bridge <br>Hold on, hold on, hold on <br>Hold on, hold on, hold on <br>Hold on, hold on, hold on <br>Hold on, hold on, hold on <br><br>Keep holding on, hang on <br>Hold on, keep holding on <br><br>Hold on, hold on, hold on <br>Hold on, hold on, hold on <br>Hold on, hold on, hold on <br>Hold on, hold on, hold on]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Keep Holding On" label="Keep Holding On"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Memories/</id><title>The Temptations - Memories - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Memories/" title="The Temptations - Memories - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[wish that i could wind <br>like a spiral spare through time <br>to your body next to mine <br>warm and satisfied <br>wish that i could catch <br>a night train to the past <br>climb aboard and hear you ask <br>darling come inside <br><br>memories, memories <br>sweet, sweet memories <br>of days gone by <br>that make me cry <br>memories, memories, memories <br>sweet memories <br>that make me sad <br>they take me back <br>to you <br>memories, memories <br>ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br>ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba <br><br>watching falling stars <br>on the grass by my own car <br>making love there in the dark <br>thinking we're alone <br>old man shined his light <br>trying not to act suprised <br>he left hard and all uptight <br>told us to get on home <br><br>memories, memories <br>sweet sweet memories <br>of love we shared <br>of love we shared <br>memories memories <br>sweet memories <br>of love we shared <br>we will never <br>share them again <br>memories memories <br>ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br>ba ba ba ba ba ba ba <br><br>wish that i could wind <br>like a spiral spare through time <br>to your body next to mine <br>warm and satisfied <br>wish that i could catch <br>a night train to the past <br>climb aboard and hear you ask <br>darling come inside <br><br>memories, memories <br>sweet, sweet memories <br>of days gone by <br>that make me cry <br>memories, memories, memories <br>sweet memories <br>that make me sad <br>they take me back <br>to you <br>memories, memories <br>ah ah ah ah ah ah ah <br>ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Memories" label="Memories"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/A_Song_For_You/</id><title>The Temptations - A Song For You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/A_Song_For_You/" title="The Temptations - A Song For You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been so many places in my life and time <br>I've sung a lot of songs, I've made some bad rhyme <br>I've acted out my love in stages <br>With ten thousand people watching <br>But we're alone now and I'm singin' this song for you <br>I know your image of me is what I hope to be <br>I've treated you unkindly but baby can't you see <br>baby can't you see now <br><br>There's no one more important to me baby <br>Baby can't you please see through me 'cause we're alone now and <br>I'm singin' this song for you <br><br>You taught me precious secrets of the truth, withholdin' nothin' <br>You came out in front and I was hiding <br>But now I'm so much better and if my words don't come together <br>Listen to the melody listen to the melody <br>cause my love's in there hiding <br>I love you in a place where there's no space or time <br>I love you for my life, you are a friend of mine you are a friend of mine <br>And when my life is over, remember when we were together <br>We were alone and <br><br>I was singin' this song for you <br>We were alone and <br>I was singin' this song for you <br>We were alone and <br>I was singin' this song, singin' this song for you]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="A Song For You" label="A Song For You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Glasshouse/</id><title>The Temptations - Glasshouse - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Glasshouse/" title="The Temptations - Glasshouse - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If you're living in a glasshouse Watch out, watch out <br>Don't throw no stones Watch out, watch out <br><br>If you're living in a glasshouse Watch out, watch out <br>Don't throw no stones <br><br>We're all made with 3 plays apiece <br>We're born alone, and we die alone <br>Why can't we live in between <br><br>I don't care what goes on in your house when you close your door <br>If you quit lookin' in my bedroom window, I'll quit lookin' in yours <br><br>My Girl came home and she caught me with Alice <br>And she threw me out the door, nah, nah, nah <br><br>But the real reason that she was so mad <br>Was that she was with Alice before Say what <br>See there People always doin' that <br><br>If you're living in a glasshouse Yeah, y'all <br>Don'tcha throw no stones It's a shame <br><br>If you're living in a glasshouse <br>Don'tcha throw no stones <br><br>I ain't no fool <br><br>Sweet talkin', Bar hoppin', Pill poppin', Wife swappin' <br>Swapping <br>Swapping <br>Swapping <br><br>Sweet talkin', Bar hoppin', Pill poppin', Wife swappin' <br>Swapping <br>Swapping <br>Swapping <br><br>If you're living in a glasshouse <br>You don't throw no stones <br>If you're living in a glasshouse <br>Don't throw no stones <br>If you're living in a glasshouse <br>Don't throw no stones <br><br>Sweet talkin', Bar hoppin', Pill poppin', Wife swappin' <br>Swapping <br>Swapping <br>Swapping <br><br>Sweet talkin', Bar hoppin', Pill poppin', Wife swappin' <br>Swapping <br>Swapping <br>Swapping <br><br>I said livin', I said livin' <br><br>If you're living in a glasshouse]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Glasshouse" label="Glasshouse"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Shakey_Ground/</id><title>The Temptations - Shakey Ground - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Shakey_Ground/" title="The Temptations - Shakey Ground - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lady luck and the four leaf clover <br>Won't be as hurt as I feel all over <br>My life for one special occasion <br>'Til you leave in depth the situation <br><br>Well well well standing on shakey ground <br>Ever since you put me down <br>Standing on shakey ground <br>Ever since you put me down <br><br>My car got repossessed this morning <br>Harder times I haven't seen in years <br>Able to throw me a life preserver <br>'Cos I'm about to drown in my own tears <br><br>Well well well standing on shakey ground <br>Ever since you put me down <br>Standing on shakey ground <br>Ever since you put me down <br><br>Well well well standing on shakey ground <br>Ever since you put me down <br><br>Standing on shakey ground <br>Ever since you put me down <br>Standing on shakey ground <br>Ever since you put me down <br><br>Well well well standing on shakey ground <br>Shaking, shakey ground <br>Standing, standing <br>Standing on shakey ground]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Shakey Ground" label="Shakey Ground"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Happy_People/</id><title>The Temptations - Happy People - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Happy_People/" title="The Temptations - Happy People - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Get up everybody <br>Happy people are we <br>Happy people are we <br><br>Throw away your life long pain and follow, yeah <br>I'll take you to a land of peace and a new tomorrow, hey <br>Brothers, sisters, come and take my hand <br>I will take you to a better land <br>Sunshine people love is all you bring <br>Dawn of a new day and here's the song we sing <br><br>Happy people are we well, well, well, well <br>Happy people are we hey <br>Listen children, now <br><br>Don't believe in this troubled world <br>We can get higher higher <br>Come on along and I'll take you there <br>People, my people, let's party and get down <br>Life is for livin now let's don't mess around <br>Dance to the music, throw your cares away <br>It's a song of hope and better days <br><br>Happy people are we everybody <br>Happy people are we <br><br>Happy happy <br>You and me both gotta be happy <br>Everybody's gonna be happy <br>Everybody's gonna be happy <br>Brothers and sisters got to be happy <br>Mothers and fathers got to be happy <br>Everybody got to be <br><br>Happy people are we <br>Get on up, get on up, let me hear ya <br>Happy people are we <br><br>Get up, get up everybody <br>Happy happy well, well, well, well <br>Happy happy hey, everybody got to be <br>Happy get on up, get on up, let me hear ya <br>Happy get on up, get on up, let me hear ya <br>Happy well, well, well, well]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Happy People" label="Happy People"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Youve_Got_My_Soul_On_Fire/</id><title>The Temptations - You`ve Got My Soul On Fire - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Youve_Got_My_Soul_On_Fire/" title="The Temptations - You`ve Got My Soul On Fire - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby, you better quit, umm <br><br>Well, keep on doin' whatcha doin', yeah <br>Feels so good to me, girl <br>Keep on doin' whatcha doin', lady <br>Ohh, you feel so good to me <br><br>Girl, I went to see my doctor and he told me <br>Well, from your lovin' I've got to stay away <br>He told me to let you go for my heart can't stand much mo' <br>And there oughta be a law against lovin' a man this way <br><br>Aww, but I can't get enough of your lovin', no, Lord <br>And my need keeps getting stronger everyday <br>Girl, I've got just one life to live and a lotta love to give and give <br>And let it be known that I ain't ashamed to say <br><br>You've got my soul on fire <br>On fire <br>Don't you ever stop it, baby, what you doin' to me <br>Girl, now you've got my soul on fire <br>On fire <br>Oh, yeah, baby, baby <br>I like it, like it, like it, baby, like it, hey, girl <br><br>When it comes to lovin', you're one of a kind <br>Satisfaction guaranteed, every doggone time, whoa, baby <br>You ain't got to worry about me ever leaving you <br>'Cause they ain't made a woman yet that can do the things you do <br>Oh, oh <br><br>When you press your sweet lips to mine, whoo, baby <br>My blood starts boiling and my temperature starts to rise <br>Girl, I shudder, baby, and I ain't ashamed to admit it <br>And even if it kills me, girl, I don't want you to quit it <br><br>You've got my soul on fire, oh, yeah <br>On fire <br>Baby, I like it, I like it, like it, like it <br>You've got my soul on fire <br>On fire <br>Ho, fire, aw, baby <br>I like it, like it, like it, like it, like it, baby, oh, baby <br><br>Eww, girl, I like it <br>Eww, eww, whoo, whoo, whoo, Umm, umm, umm <br>Don't stop, Lord, don't stop, I like it <br>Eww, eww, eww, eww, eww, ohh, baby <br><br>When you put your loving arms around me <br>Girl, my mind, body and soul you control <br>You control <br>I'm your puppet on a string, hey, and one more thing <br>Woman, your love is too hot to hold <br><br>You've got my my soul on fire <br>On fire <br>Oh, baby, baby, I like it, like it, like it, like it <br>You've got my soul on fire <br>On fire <br>Oh, yeah, heh, heh, my baby <br><br>I like it, like it, like it, you've got my soul on fire <br>On fire <br>Hey, don't you ever stop it, baby, don't you stop it <br>Baby, now you've got my soul on fire <br>On fire <br>Oh, yeah <br><br>Baby, oh, baby <br>Don't you stop it, baby]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="You`ve Got My Soul On Fire" label="You`ve Got My Soul On Fire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Heavenly/</id><title>The Temptations - Heavenly - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Heavenly/" title="The Temptations - Heavenly - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Laaalaaala la la <br><br>So you're through with love <br>Any you say <br>It's just a waste of time <br><br>Waste of time you blew my mind <br><br>There are two sides to love <br>And if you will <br>I'd like to show you mine <br>Girl love has it's ups and downs <br>Sometimes like a merry go round, going round and around and around and around <br>Never knowing where you're bound <br><br>I may not be the one you want <br>But I'm sure the one you need <br><br>Give me a chance to prove <br>Love shared by me and you can be <br><br>Heavenly <br>Heavenly <br>Heavenly <br><br>That's how <br><br>That's how love is when it's right it's right <br><br>Simply <br><br>Heavenly <br>Heavenly <br>Heavenly <br><br>That's how <br><br>That's how love is when it's right <br><br>Hey girl, be fair to your heart <br>Don't turn your back on love <br><br>back on love <br>No, no, cuz love is the one thing everybody needs <br>everybody needs love <br>Hey girl, open up your heart again, please won't you let me in, give me a chance to undo, all the hurt he's put you through <br><br>I may not be the one you want, but I'm sure the one you need <br><br>Girl give me a chance and you'll see, sharing your love with me will be <br><br>Heavenly <br>Heavenly <br>Heavenly <br><br>That's how how <br><br>That's how love is when it's right <br><br>Simply <br><br>Heavenly <br>Heavenly <br>Heavenly <br><br>That's how <br><br>That's how love is when it's right <br><br>Hey girl, give love another try <br><br>Ooooh, love can pass you by <br><br>Love can be <br><br>Heavenly <br>Heavenly <br>Heavenly <br><br>I know, I know it's gonna be <br><br>Heavenly <br>Heavenly <br>Heavenly <br><br>Love can be, love can be aaah aah ah aaah]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Heavenly" label="Heavenly"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Let_Your_Hair_Down/</id><title>The Temptations - Let Your Hair Down - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Let_Your_Hair_Down/" title="The Temptations - Let Your Hair Down - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well <br>Get down <br>Nah nah <br>Hi yah hi hi hi <br>Ah yah ha <br><br>Hey <br>Let your hair down Oh, doctor and lawyer <br>Get up and let your reputation sit a while <br>Hey hey let your hair down <br>Hey, mister businessman let it down <br>All work and no play makes Jack a dull boy <br><br>Hey mister businessman you're always on the go <br>You've made your fortune <br>Yet you're working harder than ever before <br><br>All those pills you're taking daily will never see you through <br>'Cause none of them are prescribed for what's really ailing you let it down <br>It don't take no doctor long to see what you got, well <br>Your life has turned into one great big knot <br><br>Hey yay hey now <br><br>Can you let it down <br>Let it down, let it down, aww <br>Get up and let your reputation sit a while <br>Hey let your hair down <br>Don't you ever be ashamed of what you're doin' let it down <br>All work and no play makes Jack a dull boy, hey hey hey <br><br>How do you do, Mr Ditty <br>Uptight you look such a pity <br>I've got some advice for you <br>Take this record in your room <br>Lock the door, and get some groove <br><br>Let it down let it down <br>Let your hair down let it down <br>Ay hey <br>Let it down, let it down, let it all the way down <br>All you got to do is let the music take your mind <br><br>Show your partners <br>Anything they can do, you can do better <br>Anything they can do, you can do better well, well, well, well <br>This is the part of the song where the horns take the throne <br>Down blow dih down down hey <br><br>Let it down, let it down, hey <br>Let it down, let it down, hey <br>Let it down, let it down <br>Hey, let it down <br><br>Let your hair down <br>Hey doctors and lawyers <br>Get up and let your reputation sit a while <br>Hey hey let your hair down <br>Hey, mister businessman let it down <br>Don't you know, all work and no play makes Jack a dull boy <br><br>Hey ay hey let your hair down <br>Let it down, let it down, let it down, let it down <br>Get up and let your reputation sit a while, do it]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Let Your Hair Down" label="Let Your Hair Down"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Law_Of_The_Land/</id><title>The Temptations - Law Of The Land - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:11:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:11:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Law_Of_The_Land/" title="The Temptations - Law Of The Land - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are always heaven made <br>Some people will live impermanent for the rest of their days <br>Time marches on <br>Yesterday is better than tomorrow <br>Life is uncertain, let me hear you say 'yeah' <br>That is that, oh yes it is <br>There'll be days of sunshine and laughter <br>But don't forget you will have to shed some tears oho <br><br>It's the law of the land my brother oh <br>Whether you like it or you'll understand ah hey hey <br>It's the law of the land hey hey hey hey <br>'Cause made by almighty men <br><br>Live by the good book if you're able <br>You must play your cards on top of the table <br>When you gather you either win or lose <br>In life's ev'rybody's got to pay some dues well <br><br>It's the law of the land well well well <br>Whether you'll like it or you'll understand you can't change it <br>It's the law of the land ah how <br>'Cause made by almighty men oh hey <br><br>Hey, it's the law, the law of the land <br>Whether you'll like it or you'll understand <br>It's the law, the law of the land <br>'Cause made by almighty men <br><br>A teacher man can't be found <br>Until you find yourself think about it <br>You might not like being, well you ought, but you'd better start like it <br>But you sure can't be nobody else <br>In other words I can't be you ain't no quit, yeah you can't be me <br>Well well, that's all with you, my sister an' brother <br>And that's the way that good life meant to be hey ho <br><br>It's the law of the land well <br>Whether you like it or you'll understand say say <br>It's the law of the land hey yeah oh <br>'Cause made by almighty men <br><br>Look at here <br>The tools of a man's day has got him by corrupt <br>For your own protection your Gods you must love <br>What goes around comes around <br>And what goes up, yeah, must come down aha <br><br>It's the law of the land well well well well <br>Whether you like it or you'll understand <br>It's the law of the land well well well <br>'Cause made by almighty men aha <br><br>It's the law of the land ev'rybody else say <br>Whether you like it or you'll understand]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Law Of The Land" label="Law Of The Land"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Hey_Girl_I_Like_Your_Style/</id><title>The Temptations - Hey Girl (I Like Your Style) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Hey_Girl_I_Like_Your_Style/" title="The Temptations - Hey Girl (I Like Your Style) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey girl, I want you to know <br>I'm going to miss you so much if you go <br>And hey girl, I'll tell you no lie <br>Something deep inside of me is going to dye <br>If you say so long, if this is goodbye <br>Whoa <br><br>Hey girl, this can't be true <br>How am I suppose to exist without you <br>And hey girl, now don't put me on <br>What's going to happen to me when you're gone <br>How will I live, how can I go on <br>How can I go on, hey girl <br><br>Hey girl, now sit yourself down <br>I'm not ashame to get down on the ground <br>And beg you, baby Beg you to stay <br>Don't go away <br><br>Hey girl <br>Naw, naw, don't go away <br>Hey girl, little girl, don't go away <br>I'm beggin' you to stay <br>Little girl, don't go away <br>Hey girl, little girl, don't go away]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Hey Girl (I Like Your Style)" label="Hey Girl (I Like Your Style)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Plastic_Man/</id><title>The Temptations - Plastic Man - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Plastic_Man/" title="The Temptations - Plastic Man - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, he specializes in talking trash <br>Carries himself like the <br>World's biggest spender <br>But ain't never got no cash <br><br>The clothes he wears <br>Are second to none <br>He's a jack of all trades <br>And a master of none <br><br>Agrees with everything <br>He knows nothing about <br>So he doesn't feel left out <br><br>Secondary all the things in life he really wants <br>is his thing so he's got to <br>Keep up his front <br><br>Plastic Man <br>Trying to get it over <br>Any way he can <br>Plastic Man <br>Trying to get it over <br>Any way he can <br><br>He always borrows <br>Never lends <br>He says, you know me, man <br>I'm with him, let me in <br><br>Yes, he's willing to <br>Stick through thick and thin <br>But when the chips are down <br>He won't help you if he can <br>Plastic Man <br><br>Claim to fame, he has none <br>Friends in this world, maybe one <br>He hates being just <br>Another face in the crowd <br>Giving another brother five <br>And talking loud <br><br>Plastic Man <br>Trying to get it over <br>Any way he can <br>Plastic Man <br>Trying to get it over <br>Any way he can <br><br>I guess you know he does a <br>Little dipping and dabbing <br>In a gang, they go on <br>Backstabbing <br><br>You better stop your fantasizing <br>Start, boo boo boo boom <br>To realizing that black is black <br>And white is white <br>Wrong is wrong and right is right <br><br>Plastic Man <br>Trying to get it over <br>Any way he can <br>Plastic Man <br>Trying to get it over <br>Any way he can <br><br>Plastic Man <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Trying to get it over <br>Any way he can <br>Plastic Man]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Plastic Man" label="Plastic Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Masterpiece/</id><title>The Temptations - Masterpiece - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Masterpiece/" title="The Temptations - Masterpiece - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Where I was born ev'rything was dull and dingy <br>I lived in a place they called the inner city <br>Getting ahead huh was strictly a nono <br>Cause nobody cares what happens to the folks <br>That live in the ghetto <br>Thousands of lives wasting away <br>People living from day to day <br>It's a challenge just staying alive <br>'Cause in the ghetto only the strong survive <br><br>Money I ain't got none, job can't find one <br>The streets raised me from a baby, ooh <br>Thousands of lives wasting away <br>People living from day to day <br>It's a challenge just staying alive <br>'Cause in the ghetto only the strong survive <br><br>Broken down homes, kids strung out <br>They don't even know what life's all about <br>Stealin' cars, robbin' bars <br>Mugging drugs, rat infested <br>And no one's interested <br><br>Kids dodging cars for recreation <br>Only adds to a mother's frustration <br>Breakings, folks comin' home <br>And finding all their possessions gone <br>Oh it's an ev'ry day thing well well in the ghetto <br>Oh it's an ev'ry day thing in the ghetto]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Masterpiece" label="Masterpiece"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Papa_Was_A_Rollin_Stone/</id><title>The Temptations - Papa Was A Rollin` Stone - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Papa_Was_A_Rollin_Stone/" title="The Temptations - Papa Was A Rollin` Stone - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It was the third of September <br>That day I'll always remember <br>Yes, I will <br>'Cause that was the day that my daddy died <br>I never got a chance to see him <br>Never heard nothin' but bad things about him <br>Mama, I'm depending on you <br>To tell me the truth <br>Mama just hung her head and said, Son <br><br>Papa was a rolling stone <br>Wherever he laid his hat was his home <br>And when he died, all he left us was alone <br>Papa was a rolling stone, my son <br>Wherever he laid his hat was his home <br>And when he died, all he left us was alone <br><br>Hey, mama <br>Is it true what they say that papa never worked a day in his life <br>And, mama, some bad talk goin' round town sayin' that papa had three outside children and another wife <br>And that ain't right <br>Heard them talking papa doing some store front preachin' <br>Talked about saving souls and all the time leechin' <br>Dealing in debt and stealing in the name of the Lord <br>Mama just hung her head and said <br><br>Papa was a rolling stone, my son <br>Wherever he laid his hat was his home <br>And when he died, all he left us was alone <br>Papa was a rolling stone <br>Wherever he laid his hat was his home <br>And when he died, all he left us was alone <br><br>Hey, mama <br>I heard papa called himself a Jack Of All Trades <br>Tell me is that what sent papa to an early grave <br>Folks say papa would beg, borrow, steal <br>To pay his bills <br>Hey, mama <br>Folks say papa never was much on thinking <br>Spent most of his time chasing women and drinking <br>Mama, I'm depending on you <br>To tell me the truth <br>Mama looked up with a tear in her eye and said, Son <br><br>Papa was a rolling stone well, well <br>Wherever he laid his hat was his home <br>And when he died, all he left us was alone <br>Papa was a rolling stone <br>Wherever he laid his hat was his home <br>And when he died, all he left us was alone <br><br>I said, Papa was a rolling stone yes, he was, my son <br>Wherever he laid his hat was his home <br>And when he died, all he left us was alone <br>My daddy was papa was a rolling stone, yes, he was <br>Wherever he laid his hat was his home <br>And when he died, all he left us was alone]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Papa Was A Rollin` Stone" label="Papa Was A Rollin` Stone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Mother_Nature/</id><title>The Temptations - Mother Nature - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Mother_Nature/" title="The Temptations - Mother Nature - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Go on and take your course <br>And a take me with you <br>Hey, I wanna leave here, oh <br><br>Mother Nature <br>Take the chains off me <br>As long as I'm livin', livin' <br>Hey, I wanna be free, hey <br><br>Come on and let your sweet wine <br>Rush to my head <br>And make me feel fine <br><br>Let me stand naked in the sun <br>Hiding from no one <br>Hey, hey, hey <br><br>Mother Nature <br>Come on and do your thing <br>I want to start feeling, hey <br>All those good things you can bring <br>Hey, hey <br><br>Day in, day out I learn to find <br>Leaves me half alive <br>And I'm going nowhere <br>I can't live in this classic world <br>It's killing me <br>Can't you see <br>You're the only one to turn to <br><br>Mother Nature <br>Go on and take your course <br>But take me with you, with you <br>Hey, I wanna leave here <br><br>Mother, I wanna leave here <br>Oh, Mother]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Mother Nature" label="Mother Nature"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Aint_Got_Nothin/</id><title>The Temptations - I Ain`t Got Nothin` - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Aint_Got_Nothin/" title="The Temptations - I Ain`t Got Nothin` - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You know, every house has a door and every room has a floor <br>Every fence has a gate and every beast has a mate <br>Everybody, everybody's got something but me <br>I ain't got nothing <br><br>Every stove has a fire and every car has a tire <br>Every fish has a bowl and every shoe has a sole <br>Everybody, everybody's got something but me <br>I ain't got nothing <br><br>Now I don't care about politics and things across the sea <br>All I want all I want to do is love <br>And have somebody love me I need I need somebody <br><br>Every lion has a den and every little pig has its pen <br>Every road has a way and they tell me every dog has its day <br>Everybody, everybody's got something but me <br>I ain't got nothing I ain't got nothing Oh no]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="I Ain`t Got Nothin`" label="I Ain`t Got Nothin`"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Superstar_Remember_How_You_Got_Where_You_Are_Promo_Single_Ver/</id><title>The Temptations - Superstar (Remember How You Got Where You Are) (Promo Single Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Superstar_Remember_How_You_Got_Where_You_Are_Promo_Single_Ver/" title="The Temptations - Superstar (Remember How You Got Where You Are) (Promo Single Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Higher, higher <br>Fire <br><br>Don't change your style now that you've reached the top <br>Don't choose your friends by what they've got <br>Remember beneath the glitter and gleam <br>Like everyday people you're just a human being <br><br>Superstar, good God <br>Enjoy your champagne and caviar <br>And your chauffeur drivin' fancy car <br>But remember how you got where you are <br>Oh ho ho, 'cause the same folks that made you <br>Um hum, you better believe they can break you <br><br>No you didn't make it all by yourself <br>You had help from somebody else <br>The truth is the light, don't let it depress you <br>You just be thankful that the good Lord made you <br><br>Superstar, ah do you know who your real friends are <br>Ah, talkin' to you <br>Superstar, remember how you got where you are <br>Ah ah down, down, down, down <br><br>Drummer keep it going, going <br>Horns star blowin', right on time blow my mind <br>Blow my mind <br>Higher higher, higher higher <br><br>It's easy for you to look down <br>Turn up your nose and frown <br>Now that you're on top <br>Top <br><br>Bright lights <br>Don't let the bright lights blind you <br>Bridge <br>Don't burn 'em behind you <br><br>Superstar, superstar do you know who your real friends are <br>Ah, talkin' to you <br>Superstar, remember how you got where you are <br>Um hum, um hum <br><br>Don't change your style now that you've reached the top <br>Don't choose your friends by what they've got <br>Remember beneath the glitter and gleam <br>Like everyday people you're just a human being <br><br>Superstar, superstar do you know who your real friends are <br>Ah, talkin' to you <br>Superstar remember how you got where you are]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Superstar (Remember How You Got Where You Are) (Promo Single Ver.)" label="Superstar (Remember How You Got Where You Are) (Promo Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Its_Summer/</id><title>The Temptations - It`s Summer - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Its_Summer/" title="The Temptations - It`s Summer - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Outside my window a robin builds a nest <br>At last winter's gone away to rest <br>Once again the leaves has return to the trees <br>I can just feel that soft summer breeze <br><br>There's magic in the air <br>Winter disappear, it's summer <br><br>Children will be playing in the park <br>Days will be longer till the dark <br>Nights will be warm with star filled skies <br>A perfect setting for a girl and a guy <br><br>There's magic in the air <br>Green grass every everywhere <br>It's summer <br><br>Don't you know it's summer time Time Time Time <br>And the livin' is easy Oh, so easy <br>Everybody sing summer time Time Time Time <br>Now that summer's here there be million things to do <br>Vacation near or far, whatever pleases you <br>Summer is the happiest season of them all <br>So everybody get together and have yourselves a ball <br><br>There's magic in the air <br>Green grass every everywhere <br>It's summer <br>Oh <br><br>There's magic in the air <br>Green grass every everywhere <br>It's summer <br>Woo <br><br>It's summer time Magic in the air, green grass everywhere <br>Oh, it's summer <br>Take a look around you <br>It's summer time Magic in the air, green grass everywhere <br>Oh, it's summer <br>Hmm <br>It's summer time]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="It`s Summer" label="It`s Summer"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Take_A_Look_Around/</id><title>The Temptations - Take A Look Around - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Take_A_Look_Around/" title="The Temptations - Take A Look Around - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Feather in your cap if you catch a robber <br>Dirt in your face if your scheme falls through <br>Pay close attention to my story <br>Youll find every word is true <br>Junk man standing on the corner <br>Selling death, no concience has he <br>In the name of God, wont somebody stop him <br>stop him, think about the children <br>Its a matter of life and death, you see <br>Aint no time to stand back and point your finger <br>Weve got to face reality <br>No, no, no, no, no <br>Dont turn your back on this problem, people <br>too much depends on you and me <br>Desprate with no sense of value <br>just an evil mind lurking through the night <br>Because of you, the streets aint safe no more for walking <br>cause youre feeling so up tight <br>Take a look around]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Take A Look Around" label="Take A Look Around"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Just_My_Imagination_Running_Away_With_Me/</id><title>The Temptations - Just My Imagination (Running Away With Me) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Just_My_Imagination_Running_Away_With_Me/" title="The Temptations - Just My Imagination (Running Away With Me) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ooo <br>Each day through my window I watch her as she passes by <br>I say to myself, you're such a lucky guy <br>To have a girl like her is truly a dream come true <br>Out of all the fellas in the world, she belongs to you <br><br>But it was just my 'magination, running away with me <br>It was just my 'magination, running away with me <br><br>Soon Soon we'll be married and raise a family Oh, yeah <br>A cozy little home out in the country with two children, maybe three <br>I tell you, I can visualize it all This couldn't be a dream, for too real it all seems <br><br>But it was just my 'magination, once again <br>Running away with me <br>Tell you it was just my 'magination <br>Running away with me <br><br>Every night on my knees I pray <br><br>Dear Lord, hear my plea <br>Don't ever let another take her love from me <br>Or I will surely die Hmm <br><br>Her love is heavenly <br>When her arms enfold me <br>I hear a tender rhapsody <br>But in reality, she doesn't even know me <br><br>Just my 'magination, once again <br>Running away with me <br>Oh, tell you it was just my 'magination <br>Running away with me <br><br>I never met her but I can't forget her <br>Just my 'magination <br>Ooo yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Running away with me <br><br>Ooo, just my 'magination running away with me <br>She's in my mind and hard to find <br>Just my 'magination]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Just My Imagination (Running Away With Me)" label="Just My Imagination (Running Away With Me)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Ungena_Za_Ulimwengu_Unite_The_World/</id><title>The Temptations - Ungena Za Ulimwengu (Unite The World) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Ungena_Za_Ulimwengu_Unite_The_World/" title="The Temptations - Ungena Za Ulimwengu (Unite The World) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sick minds, sad sights <br>Never ending sleepless nights have been accepted as an everyday thing <br>Wire tapping, kidnapping <br><br>Will the Russians push the button <br><br>I tell you, people, our thoughts and values have got to change <br>They say love is the strongest force on this earth <br>Uh, but to me, peace among people surpasses love and worth <br>People jobs don't come no bigger than the one we've got to do <br>If we don't give peace a chance, what do you think is gonna happen to me and you <br><br>Think about it <br><br>That's why I am reaching out my hand to be your friend <br>This unrest between races has got to come to an end <br>Don't let the color of my skin confuse you <br>I swear on a stack of bibles I won't misuse you <br>So put your hand in mine <br>Huh, we're gonna form a human chain, mightier than a hurricane <br><br>And walk this land, hand in hand, day and night, black and white <br>We gotta unite the world <br>Walk this land, day and night, hand in hand, black and white <br>Come on and sing it, sing it, sing it, sing it, sing it <br><br>We got to unite the world <br>Walk this land, day and night, hand in hand, black and white <br>Log on to kill this message <br>Come on and sing it, sing it, sing it, sing it, sing it with me <br><br>We got to unite the world <br>Walk this land, day and night, hand in hand, black and white <br>God almighty, Sing it, sing it, sing it <br>Aww, unite the world <br><br>Come on <br>Come on <br>Come on <br>Awww <br><br>Oh, ding dong ding let the freedom bell ring <br>The good Lord made you and me, what he wanted us to be <br>Free all those people you got chained up in your mind <br>Hmmm mm hmmm, now there's truth in what I'm saying <br>We gotta stop the games we're playing <br>Two wrongs ain't never made a right Right <br><br>Hung up, tripped out, whatever you may be <br>Now is the time to set yourself free <br>Put your hand in mine Huh, come on <br>Oh, and let's walk <br><br>Oh, we gonna walk this land, day and night, hand in hand, black and white <br>Sing it with me now walk this land, day and night, hand in hand, black and white <br>Raise your voices and sing along with me <br><br>Come on, we gonna unite the world <br>Walk this land, day and night, hand in hand, black and white <br>We gonna walk this land, day and night, hand in hand, black and white <br><br>We gonna unite the world <br>Walk this land, day and night, hand in hand, black and white <br>Sing it, sing it, sing it, sing it, sing it <br>Aw, come on, come on, come on, come on <br><br>Walk this land, day and night, hand in hand, black and white <br>Walk this land, day and night, hand in hand, black and white <br>Walk this land, day and night, hand in hand, black and white]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Ungena Za Ulimwengu (Unite The World)" label="Ungena Za Ulimwengu (Unite The World)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Ball_Of_Confusion_Thats_What_The_World_Is_Today/</id><title>The Temptations - Ball Of Confusion (That`s What The World Is Today) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Ball_Of_Confusion_Thats_What_The_World_Is_Today/" title="The Temptations - Ball Of Confusion (That`s What The World Is Today) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1, 2 1, 2, 3, 4, Ow <br><br>People moving out, people moving in Why, because of the color of their skin <br>Run, run, run but you sure can't hide An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth <br>Vote for me and I'll set you free Rap on, brother, rap on <br>Dennis Well, the only person talking about love thy brother is the preacher <br>And it seems nobody's interested in learning but the teacher <br>Segregation, determination, demonstration, integration, Aggravation, humiliation, obligation to our nation <br>Ball of confusion Oh yeah, that's what the world is today Woo, hey, hey <br><br>The sale of pills are at an all time high <br>Young folks walking round with their heads in the sky <br>The cities ablaze in the summer time <br>And oh, the beat goes on <br><br>Evolution, revolution, gun control, sound of soul <br>Shooting rockets to the moon, kids growing up too soon <br>Politicians say more taxes will solve everything <br><br>And the band played on <br>So, round and around and around we go <br>Where the world's headed, nobody knows <br><br>Oh, great googalooga, can't you hear me talking to you <br>Just a ball of confusion <br>Oh yeah, that's what the world is today <br>Woo, hey, hey <br><br>Fear in the air, tension everywhere <br>Unemployment rising fast, the Beatles new record's a gas <br><br>And the only safe place to live is on an Indian reservation <br><br>And the band played on <br>Eve of destruction, tax deduction, city inspectors, bill collectors <br>Mod clothes in demand, population out of hand, suicide, too many bills <br>Hippies moving to the hills People all over the world are shouting, 'End the war' <br><br>And the band played on <br><br>Great googalooga, can't you hear me talking to you <br>Sayin' ball of confusion <br>That's what the world is today, hey, hey <br>Let me hear ya, let me hear ya, let me hear ya <br>Sayin' ball of confusion <br>That's what the world is today, hey, hey <br>Let me hear ya, let me hear ya, let me hear ya, let me hear ya, let me hear ya <br>Sayin' ball of confusion]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Ball Of Confusion (That`s What The World Is Today)" label="Ball Of Confusion (That`s What The World Is Today)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Hum_Along_And_Dance/</id><title>The Temptations - Hum Along And Dance - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Hum_Along_And_Dance/" title="The Temptations - Hum Along And Dance - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ain't no words to this song <br>You just dance and hum along <br>Ain't no words to this song <br>You just dance and hum along <br><br>Dance, hum, dance, dance, dance <br>Dance, dance, dance, dance <br><br>Ain't no words to this song <br>You just dance an hum along <br>Ain't no words to this song <br>You just dance and hum along <br><br>Dance, dance, dance, dance, dance <br>Dance, dance, dance, dance <br><br>Ain't no words to this song <br>Well, you just dance an hum along <br>Now listen, ain't no words to this song, people <br>You just dance and hum along, now listen <br><br>Dance <br><br>Come on man, take the drag <br>Don't be afraid it ain't gonna hurt you <br>Come on man, take the drag <br>Don't be afraid it ain't gonna hurt you <br><br>Come on man, take the drag <br>Don't be afraid it ain't gonna hurt you <br>Come on man, take the drag <br>Don't be afraid it ain't gonna hurt you <br><br>Come on man, take the drag <br>Don't be afraid it ain't gonna hurt you <br>Come on]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Hum Along And Dance" label="Hum Along And Dance"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Psychedelic_Shack/</id><title>The Temptations - Psychedelic Shack - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Psychedelic_Shack/" title="The Temptations - Psychedelic Shack - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Psychedelic shack, that's where it's at <br>Psychedelic shack, that's where it's at <br>Psychedelic shack, that's where it's at <br>Psychedelic shack, that's where it's at <br>People let me tell you about a place I know <br>To get in it don't take much dough <br>Where you can really do your thing, oh yeah <br>It's got a neon sign outside that says <br>Come in and take a look at your mind <br>You'd be surprised what you might find, yeah <br>Strobe lights flashin' way till after sundown <br>People gather there from all parts of town <br>Oh yeah, what do I call it <br>You know it's just across the track <br>People I'm talking about the psychedelic shack <br><br>Psychedelic shack, that's where it's at <br>Psychedelic shack, that's where it's at, oh yeah <br>You can have your fortune told <br>You can learn the meaning of soul <br>There ain't no such thing as time <br>Incense in the air <br>'In signs painted everywhere <br>I guarantee you this place will blow your mind <br>Music so high, you can't get over it <br>So love you can't get under it <br>Right around the corner just across the track <br>People I'm talking about the psychedelic shack <br><br>Psychedelic shack, that's where it's at <br>Psychedelic shack, that's where it's at <br>Millionaires, kings and queens go there to do their things <br>You might see anybody there, yeah <br>Bear skin rugs, tails and beads <br>Don't really matter what you wear <br>You can take off your shoes, sit on the floor <br>Join in and be what you wanna be <br>Don't you know that it's right <br>Around the corner just across the track <br>People I'm talking about the psychedelic shack <br><br>Psychedelic shack, that's where it's at <br>Psychedelic shack, that's where it's at <br>They got a cat there shouting the blues <br>Talking about payin some dues <br>People walking around reciting poetry <br>Screamin guitars and a thousand colored lights <br>People I'm telling you this place is really out of sight <br>You can have your fortune told <br>You can learn the meaning of soul <br>I guarantee this place will blow your mind <br>Don't you know it's right around the corner <br>Just across the track <br>People I'm talking about the psychedelic shack]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Psychedelic Shack" label="Psychedelic Shack"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/War/</id><title>The Temptations - War - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/War/" title="The Temptations - War - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh no there's got to be a better way <br>Say it again <br>There's got to be a better way yeah <br>What is it good for <br>War has caused unrest <br>Among the younger generation <br>Induction then destruction <br>Who wants to die <br>War huh <br>What is it good for <br>Absolutely nothing <br>Say it again <br>War huh <br>What is it good for <br>Absolutely nothing <br>Yeah <br>War I despise <br>'Cause it means destruction <br>Of innocent lives <br>War means tears <br>To thousands of mothers how <br>When their sons go off to fight <br>And lose their lives <br>I said <br>War huh <br>It's an enemy of all mankind <br>No point of war <br>'Cause you're a man <br>War has caused unrest <br>Among the younger generation <br>Induction then destruction <br>Who wants to die <br>Give it to me one time now <br>Give it to me one time now <br>War has shattered <br>Many young men's dreams <br>We've got no place for it today <br>They say we must fight to keep our freedom <br>But Lord, there's just got to be a better way <br>It ain't nothing but a heartbreaker <br>War <br>Friend only to the undertaker <br>War <br>War <br>War good God, now <br>Now <br>Give it to me one time now <br>Now now <br>What is it good for]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="War" label="War"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Message_From_A_Black_Man/</id><title>The Temptations - Message From A Black Man - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Message_From_A_Black_Man/" title="The Temptations - Message From A Black Man - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, my skin is black <br>But that's no reason to hold me back <br>Why don't you think about it <br>Think about it, think about it, think about it <br>Think about it <br>I have wants and desires <br>Just like you <br>So move on the side <br>'Cause I'm comin' through, oh <br><br>No matter how hard you try <br>You can't stop me now <br>Eddie and Temptations No matter how hard you try <br>You can't stop me now, oooh <br><br>Yes, your skin is white <br>Does that make you right <br>Why don't you think about it <br>Think about it, think about it, think about it <br>Think about it <br>This is a message <br>A message to y'all <br>Together we stand <br>Divided we fall, oh <br><br>Black is a color <br>Just like white <br>Tell me how can a color determine whether <br>You're wrong or right <br>We all have our faults <br>Yes we do <br><br>So look in your mirror <br>Look in the mirror <br>What do you see <br>What do you see <br>Two eyes <br>Two eyes <br>A nose, and a mouth just like me, oh <br><br>Your eyes are open <br>But you refuse to see <br>The laws of society <br>Were made for both you and me <br>Because of my color <br>I struggle to be free <br>Sticks and stones <br>May break my bones <br>But in the end <br>You're gonna' see my friend, oh <br><br>No matter how hard you try <br>You can't stop me now <br><br>Say it loud <br>No matter how hard you try <br>You can't stop me now <br><br>Say it loud <br>No matter how hard you try <br>You can't stop me now <br><br>Say it <br>No matter how hard you try <br>You can't stop me now <br><br>Say it loud <br>No matter how hard you try <br>You can't stop me now <br><br>Say it loud <br>I'm black and I'm proud <br>No matter how hard you try <br>You can't stop me now <br><br>Say it loud <br>I'm black and I'm proud <br>No matter how hard you try <br>You can't stop me now]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Message From A Black Man" label="Message From A Black Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Cant_Get_Next_To_You/</id><title>The Temptations - I Can`t Get Next To You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Cant_Get_Next_To_You/" title="The Temptations - I Can`t Get Next To You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I <br>Can turn a gray sky blue <br>I can make it rain, whenever I wanted to <br>Oh, I <br>I can build a castle from a single grain of sand <br>I can make a ship sail, uh, on dry land <br><br>But my life is incomplete and I'm so blue 'Cause I can't get next to you <br><br>I can't get next to you, babe Next to you <br>I can't get next to you I just can't get next you <br>I can't get next to you, babe <br>I can't get next to you <br><br>I <br>Can fly like a bird in the sky <br>Hey, and I can buy anything that money can buy <br>Oh, I <br>I can turn a river into a raging fire <br>I can live forever if I so desired <br><br>Unimportant are all the things I can do 'Cause I can't get next to you <br><br>I can't get next to you, babe No matter what I do <br>I can't get next to you <br>Uh ya <br><br>Ooo Ooo <br>Ooo Ooo <br>Chica boom, chica boom <br>Chica boom, boom, boom <br><br>I can turn back the hands of time, you better believe I can <br>I <br>I can make the seasons change, just by waving my hand <br>Oh, I <br>I can change anything from old to new <br>The things I want to do the most, I'm unable to do <br><br>Unhappy am I with all the powers I possess <br>'Cause girl you're the key to my happiness <br>And I <br><br>Can't get next to you <br><br>Girl, you're blowing my mind 'cause I can't get Next to you <br>Can't you see these tears I'm crying I can't get Next to you <br>Girl, it's you that I need I gotta get Next to you <br>Can't you see these tears I'm crying I can't get Next to you <br>I, I, I, I I can't get Next to you <br>I, I, I, I I can't get Next to you <br>Girl, you're blowing my mind]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="I Can`t Get Next To You" label="I Can`t Get Next To You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Dont_Let_The_Joneses_Get_You_Down/</id><title>The Temptations - Don`t Let The Joneses Get You Down - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Dont_Let_The_Joneses_Get_You_Down/" title="The Temptations - Don`t Let The Joneses Get You Down - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ow, people gather round me, it's whom it may concern <br>I'm not trying to run your life <br><br>But you're never too old to learn, huh <br><br>Stop worrying about your neighbors and the fancy things they got <br>'Cause if you do you'll find it sure, you're gonna wind up on the spot <br><br>Don't let the Jones <br>Don't let the Jones <br>Don't let the Joneses <br>Get you down, oh down <br><br>One more time <br><br>Don't let the Joneses <br>Don't let the Jones <br>Don't let the Joneses <br>Get you down, oh down <br><br>Woo, woo oo oo oo <br><br>Huh, you may not believe it but nine times out of ten it's true <br>The people you're trying to keep up with <br><br>Are trying to keep up too <br><br>Remember that old saying, All that glitters ain't gold <br>Take heed, don't ignore it until your money time will hold Oh <br><br>Don't let the Jones <br>Don't let the Jones <br>Don't let the Joneses <br>Get you down, oh down <br><br>Hear me now, now <br><br>Don't let the Joneses <br>Don't let the Jones <br>Don't let the Joneses <br>Get you down, oh down <br><br>Who har har who who, Who har har do do do do <br><br>You're lying to yourself but you don't even know it <br>You're so busy following the Joneses, you ain't got time to show it <br>Keeping up with the Joneses, it'll only makes your life a mess <br>Bill collectors, tranquilizers and getting deeper in debt <br><br>You better leave <br>The Joneses alone <br>Tell 'em one more time <br>You better leave, oh leave <br>The Joneses alone <br><br>Joneses got a new car today <br>Here's what you should say <br>Harray for the Joneses <br>Instead you worry till your whole head turns gray <br>Worry 'bout the Joneses <br><br>Remember it's their car and they're the ones who had to pay <br>So leave Jo Jo Joneses alone <br>Listen, your car might be old, but remember it never fails to get you where you want to go <br><br>Oh, don't let the Jones <br>Don't let the Jones <br>Don't let the Joneses <br>Get you down, oh down <br><br>Hear me now, now <br><br>Don't let the Joneses <br>Don't let the Jones <br>Don't let the Joneses <br>Get you down, oh down <br><br>Do do do do do do <br><br>You're doing fine <br>Don't let the Joneses get you down <br>Now listen, if you see something you want and you know you can't afford it <br>The very next thing for you to do is start saving towards it <br>The Joneses have been a downfall for many persons, you see <br>So people, take my advice and let the Joneses be Ow <br><br>Don't let the Jones <br>Don't let the Jones <br>Don't let the Joneses <br>Get you down, oh down <br><br>Hear me now, now <br><br>Don't let the Joneses <br>Don't let the Jones <br>Don't let the Joneses <br>Get you down, oh down <br><br>You're doing fine <br>Don't let the Joneses get you down Whoo <br>You're doing fine <br>Don't let the Joneses get you down Whoo <br><br>Do do do do do do Boom boom boom boom]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Don`t Let The Joneses Get You Down" label="Don`t Let The Joneses Get You Down"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Runaway_Child_Running_Wild/</id><title>The Temptations - Runaway Child, Running Wild - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Runaway_Child_Running_Wild/" title="The Temptations - Runaway Child, Running Wild - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You played hooky from school <br>And you can't go out to play, yeah <br>Mama said for the rest of the week <br>In your room you gotta stay, yeah <br>Now you feel like <br>The whole world's pickin on you <br>But deep down inside you know it ain't true <br>You've been punished cause your mother <br>Wants to raise you the right way, yeah <br>But you don't care <br>Cause you already made up your mind <br><br>You wanna run away, yeah <br>You're on your way <br>Run away child, running wild <br>Run away child, running wild <br>Better come back home <br>Better come back home <br>Where you belong <br>Where you belone <br><br>Roaming through the city <br>Going nowhere fast <br>You're on your own at last <br>Hey it's getting late, where will you sleep <br>Gettin kind a hungry <br>You forgot to bring something to eat <br>Oh lost with no money, you start to cry <br>But remember you left home <br>Wanting to be grown <br>So dry your weepin eyes <br>Siren screamin down, neon light is flickin <br>You want your mama <br>Ah there's nothing for you <br>You're frightened and confused I want my mama <br>But she's much too far away <br>She can't hear a word you say <br>You heard some frightening news on the radio <br>About little boys running away from home <br>And their parents don't see them no more <br>You wanna hitch a ride and go home <br>But your mama told you never trust a stranger <br>And you don't know which way to go <br>Streets are dark and deserted <br>Not a sound nor sign of life <br>How you long to hear your mother's voice <br>Cause you're lost and alone <br>But remember you make the choice <br><br>Run away child, running wild <br>Better go back home where you belong <br>Run away child, running wild <br>Better go back home where you belong <br><br>You're lost in this great big city <br>Go back home where you belong <br>Not one familiar face <br>Ain't it a pity <br>Go back home where you belong <br>Oh run away child, running wild <br>You better go back home where you belong <br>Mama, mama please come and see about me <br>But she's much too far away <br>She can't hear a word you say I want my mama <br>You're frightened and confused <br>Which way will you choose]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Runaway Child, Running Wild" label="Runaway Child, Running Wild"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diana_Ross/Ill_Try_Something_New/</id><title>Diana Ross - I`ll Try Something New - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diana_Ross/Ill_Try_Something_New/" title="Diana Ross - I`ll Try Something New - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I will build you a castle with a tower so high, till it reach as the moon <br>I'll gather melodies from birdies that fly, and compose you a tune <br>Give you lovin' as warm as Mama's oven <br>And if that don't do, then I'll try something new I'll try something new <br><br>Oh, I will take you away with me as far as I can <br>To Venus or Mars <br>There we will love with your hand in my hand <br>You'll be king of the stars <br>Every day we can play on the Milky Way <br>If that don't do <br>I'll have to try something new I'll try something new <br><br>I will bring you a flower from the floor of the sea <br>Yeah, to wear in your hair <br><br>Thank you <br>I'll do anything and everything to make you happy, boy <br>To show you that I care I care <br><br>I'll pretend I'm jealous of all the fellas and if that don't do <br>I'll try something new <br><br>Ooo, something new I'll try something new <br>I'll try something new I'll try something new <br>Something new I'll try something new <br>I'll try something new I'll try something new <br>If that boy don't succeed, try again and then you'll see I'll try something new <br>Something new I'll try something new <br>Something new]]></content><category term="Diana Ross" label="Diana Ross"/><category term="I`ll Try Something New" label="I`ll Try Something New"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diana_Ross/Im_Gonna_Make_You_Love_Me/</id><title>Diana Ross - I`m Gonna Make You Love Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Diana_Ross/Im_Gonna_Make_You_Love_Me/" title="Diana Ross - I`m Gonna Make You Love Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh <br>Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh <br><br>I'm gonna do all the things for you <br>A girl wants a man to do, oh baby oh baby <br>I'll sacrifice for you <br>I'll even do wrong for you, oh baby oh baby <br><br>Every minute, every hour <br>I'm gonna shower <br>You with love and affection <br>Look out, it's comin' in your direction <br><br>And I'm, I'm gonna make you love me <br>Oh, yes I will, yes I will <br>I'm gonna make you love me <br>Oh, yes I will, yes I will <br><br>Lookie here <br>My love is strong, you see <br>I know you'll never get tired of me, oh baby Sure won't Oh baby <br>And I'm gonna use every trick in the book <br>I'll try my best to get you hooked, hey baby Take me, I'm yours Oh baby <br><br>And every night, every day <br>I'm gonna say <br>I'm gonna get ya, I'm gonna get ya <br>Look out, boy, 'cause I'm gonna get ya <br><br>I'm gonna make you love me <br>Ooh, yes I will, yes I will <br>And I'm gonna make you love me <br>Ooh, yes I will, you know I will Yes I will <br><br>Every breath I take <br>And each and every step I make <br>Brings me closer, baby <br>Closer to you <br><br>And with each beat of my heart <br>For every day we're apart <br>I'll hunger for every wasted hour <br><br>And oh, every night and every day <br>I'm gonna get ya, I'm gonna get ya <br>Look out, 'cause I'm gonna get ya <br><br>And I'm gonna make, I'm gonna make you love me <br>Yes I will, I will, yes I will <br>I'm gonna make you love me, ooh, oh <br>Yes I will, yes, I will Come on and love me <br>I'm gonna make you love me ooh <br>Yes I will Yes I will, I will, yes I will <br>Come on and love me <br>I'm gonna make you love me <br>Yes I will Yes I will, I will, yes I will]]></content><category term="Diana Ross" label="Diana Ross"/><category term="I`m Gonna Make You Love Me" label="I`m Gonna Make You Love Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Why_Did_She_Have_To_Leave_Me_Why_Did_She_Have_To_Go/</id><title>The Temptations - Why Did She Have To Leave Me (Why Did She Have To Go) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Why_Did_She_Have_To_Leave_Me_Why_Did_She_Have_To_Go/" title="The Temptations - Why Did She Have To Leave Me (Why Did She Have To Go) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There were times I knew <br>But I found it hard to say <br>You were special in my life <br>Never thought youd go away <br><br>I'll be strong <br>I'll get by <br>Without you in my life <br>I can see <br>Through your lies <br>Did you ever love me <br>I never found your love <br><br>You and I know <br>Love is leaving <br>And you don't want me anymore <br>Why should I <br>Even try <br><br>You and I know <br>Love is leaving <br>Now you're the last thing on my mind <br>Someone else <br>I will find <br>A memory I've left behind <br><br>If I ever made you cry <br>Any reason I can't find <br>It was lonely by your side <br>Like a fool, I stood by you <br>I'll be strong <br>I'll get by <br>Without you in my life <br>I can see <br>Through your lies <br>Did you ever love me <br>I never found your love <br><br>You and I know <br>Love is leaving <br>And you don't want me anymore <br>Why should I <br>Even try <br><br>You and I know <br>Love is leaving <br>Now you're the last thing on my mind <br>Someone else <br>I will find <br>A memory I've left behind <br><br>Is there something I could do <br>Is there something I should say <br>Is there someone else to keep you from <br>And now Woah, woah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah <br><br>You and I know <br>Love is leaving <br>And you don't want me anymore <br>Why should I <br>Even try <br><br>You and I know <br>Love is leaving <br>Now you're the last thing on my mind <br>Someone else <br>I will find <br>A memory I've left behind <br><br>You and I know <br>Love is leaving <br>And you don't want me anymore <br>Why should I <br>Even try <br><br>You and I know <br>Love is leaving <br>Now you're the last thing on my mind <br>Why should I <br>Even try]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Why Did She Have To Leave Me (Why Did She Have To Go)" label="Why Did She Have To Leave Me (Why Did She Have To Go)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Cloud_Nine/</id><title>The Temptations - Cloud Nine - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Cloud_Nine/" title="The Temptations - Cloud Nine - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A who, who, awho, who <br><br>The childhood part of my life wasn't very pretty <br>You see, I was born and raised in the slums of the city <br>It was a one room shack we slept in, other children beside me <br>We hardly had enough food or room to sleep <br>It was a hard times, needed something to ease my troubled mind <br><br>Ooo, listen <br>My father didn't know the meaning of work <br>He disrespected Mama and treated us like dirt <br>I left home seekin' a job that I never did find <br>Depressed and down hearted, I took to Cloud 9 <br>I'm doing fine <br>Up here On cloud nine <br>Listen one more time <br>I'm doing fine <br>Up here On cloud nine <br><br>Folks now they tell me <br>They say, give yourself a chance and don't let life pass you by <br>But the world around you is a rat race <br>Where only the strong survive <br>It's a dog eat dog world and that ain't no lie Ain't no lie <br>Listen, it ain't even safe no more, to walk the streets at night <br><br>I'm doing fine on Cloud 9 <br>Let me tell you about Cloud 9 <br><br>Cloud 9 You can be what you wanna be <br>Cloud 9 You ain't got no responsibility <br>Cloud 9 Every man, every man is free <br>Cloud 9 You're a million miles from reality <br><br>Reality I'm gonna sail up, up higher up, up up, up and away Cloud 9 <br><br>I wanna say I love the life I live <br>And I'm gonna live the life I love <br>Up here on Cloud 9 <br>Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, I'm riding high on Cloud 9 <br><br>You're as free as a bird in flight <br>Cloud 9 There's no diff'rence between day and night <br>Cloud 9 It's a world of love and harmony <br>Cloud 9 You're a million miles from reality <br><br>Reality I'm gonna sail up, up higher up, up up, up and away Cloud 9 <br><br>You can be what you wanna be <br>Cloud 9 You ain't got no responsibility <br>Cloud 9 Every man in his mind is free <br>Cloud 9 You're a million miles from reality <br>Cloud 9 You can be what you wanna be <br><br>Boom boom boom boom boom <br>I'm feeling fine on Cloud 9]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Cloud Nine" label="Cloud Nine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/My_Girl_A_Cappella/</id><title>The Temptations - My Girl (A Cappella) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/My_Girl_A_Cappella/" title="The Temptations - My Girl (A Cappella) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've got sunshine on a cloudy day <br>When it's cold outside I've got the month of May <br><br>I guess you'd say <br>What can make me feel this way <br>My girl my girl, my girl <br>Talkin' 'bout my girl my girl <br><br>I've got so much honey the bees envy me <br>I've got a sweeter song than the birds in the trees <br><br>Well, I guess you'd say <br>What can make me feel this way <br>My girl my girl, my girl <br>Talkin' 'bout my girl my girl <br><br>Hey hey hey <br>Hey hey hey <br>Ooooh <br><br>I don't need no money, fortune or fame <br>I've got all the riches, baby, one man can claim <br><br>Well, I guess you'd say <br>What can make me feel this way <br>My girl my girl, my girl <br>Talkin' 'bout my girl my girl <br><br>I've got sunshine on a cloudy day <br>With my girl <br>I've even got the month of May <br>With my girl <br>Talkin' 'bout <br>Talkin' 'bout <br>Talkin' 'bout <br>My girl <br>Ooooh <br>My girl <br>As long as I can talk about my girl]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="My Girl (A Cappella)" label="My Girl (A Cappella)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/For_Once_In_My_Life_Live_TCB_Ver___1968/</id><title>The Temptations - For Once In My Life (Live `TCB` Ver. / 1968) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/For_Once_In_My_Life_Live_TCB_Ver___1968/" title="The Temptations - For Once In My Life (Live `TCB` Ver. / 1968) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[For once in my life <br>I have someone who needs me <br>Someone I needed so long <br><br>For once unafraid <br>I can go where life leads me <br>Some how I know I'll be strong <br><br>For once I can touch <br>What my heart used to dream of <br>Long before I knew <br>Aww, someone like you <br>Would make my dream come true <br><br>For once in my life <br>I won't let sorrow hurt me <br>Not like it's hurt me before <br><br>For once I have something <br>I know won't desert me <br>I'm not alone anymore <br><br>For once I can say <br>This is mine, you can't take it <br>As long as I know <br>I have love I can make it <br><br>For once in my life <br>I have someone who needs me <br><br>For once I can say <br>This is mine, you can't take it <br>Long as I know <br>I have love I can make it <br><br>For once I can feel <br>That somebody heard my plea <br>For once in my life <br>I have someone who needs me <br><br>For once in my life <br>In my life]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="For Once In My Life (Live `TCB` Ver. / 1968)" label="For Once In My Life (Live `TCB` Ver. / 1968)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/How_Can_I_Forget/</id><title>The Temptations - How Can I Forget - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/How_Can_I_Forget/" title="The Temptations - How Can I Forget - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You asked me to forget about you <br>Go out and find someone knew <br>That won't be easy you see <br>After all the things you've done for me <br>Though I'm a man, I ain't too proud to say <br>With you I stand tall and strong <br>Without you girl, I'm nothing at all <br><br>Like a snowman in the sun, my life was wasting away <br>Your love gave me hope and strength, you're the reason I'm alive today <br><br>How, I wanna know <br>How can I forget ya, woman <br>After all you've done for me <br>You'll always be apart of me <br><br>Girl, you don't realize what your love means to me <br>It's more precious than the air I breathe <br><br>I wanna know, how <br>How can I forget ya, woman <br>After all you've done for me <br>Girl, you'll always be apart of me <br><br>How, I wanna know <br>How can I forget ya, woman <br>After all you've done for me <br>You'll always be apart of me <br><br>How, how, how how can I forget ya, woman <br>You've been so good, good baby <br>How can I forget ya <br>It's impossible to do <br>How can I forget ya, woman <br>You've been so good, good, good to me <br>How can I forget ya <br>I want to know <br>Ha ha ha how can I forget ya]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="How Can I Forget" label="How Can I Forget"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Please_Return_Your_Love_To_Me/</id><title>The Temptations - Please Return Your Love To Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:12:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:12:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Please_Return_Your_Love_To_Me/" title="The Temptations - Please Return Your Love To Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Please return your love to me, girl <br>Forgive me for the wrong I've done <br><br>And, oh, baby <br>I cry myself to sleep at night <br>For fear of a never holdin' you tight at all, baby whoa, baby <br>I miss ya more with each passin' day <br>Every night on my knees I pray <br>Oh, oh, baby please <br><br>Return your love to me, girl <br>Forgive me for the wrong I've done <br>Without your love, I'm just no good <br>For I am just a lonely boy <br><br>I'm sorry for the wrong I've done <br>Now I know how it feels to lose that special someone whoa, baby <br>I need you more than words can say <br>Without your love I can't face another day <br>Oh, please <br><br>Return your love to me, girl <br>Forgive me for the wrong I've done <br>Without your love, I'm just no good <br>I am just a lonely one <br><br>Oh, no, no o o o, babe <br><br>If there's a heav'n above you'll be my one and only love and, oh, baby <br>I can't control the glow in me <br>Girl, come on and an' see about me <br><br>Oh, ple ea ease <br><br>Return your love to me, girl <br>Forgive me for the wrong I've done <br>Without your love, I'm just no good <br>I am just a lonely one <br><br>I'm a lonely one <br>I'm a lonely one <br>I'm a lonely one <br>I'm just a lonelyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy onnnnnnnnnnnnne I am just a <br><br>Please, return your love to me, girl <br>Forgive me for the wrong I've done <br>Without your love, I'm just no good <br>I am just a lonely one]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Please Return Your Love To Me" label="Please Return Your Love To Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Could_Never_Love_Another_After_Loving_You/</id><title>The Temptations - I Could Never Love Another (After Loving You) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Could_Never_Love_Another_After_Loving_You/" title="The Temptations - I Could Never Love Another (After Loving You) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Girl, I can't believe my ears <br>Are you really telling my goodbye <br>See, you've taken away my reason for livin' <br>And you won't even tell me why <br>Before you walk out the door <br>There's something I want you to know <br><br>That I could never, ever love another, after loving you <br>Ooo hoo <br>No other love will I share 'cause none could compare <br>After loving you <br><br>It was only yesterday <br>Your words are still fresh in my mind <br>Baby, you said <br>Long as rivers flow <br>Each day you'd love me more <br>Now you wanna leave me behind <br>Listen baby, I don't know what it's gonna take to make you stay <br>I just know I've got to find a way <br><br>'Cause I could never, never, never ever love another, after loving you <br>Ooo hoo <br>No other love will I share 'cause none, none could compare <br>After loving you <br><br>So baby, please stay beside me <br>I need your sweet love to guide me <br>Oh, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby <br>Ooo, after loving you <br><br>I could never love another, after loving you <br><br>Baby, baby, baby <br>It was only, only, only, only yesterday <br>Your words are still fresh in my mind <br>I remember you said <br>Long as rivers flow <br>Each day you'd love me more <br>Now you wanna leave, leave me behind <br>Listen baby, I don't know what it's gonna take to make you stay <br>I just know I've got to find a way <br><br>'Cause I could never <br>Never, never, never, ever love another, after loving you <br>Ooo hoo <br>No other love will I share 'cause none, none could compare <br>After loving you <br><br>Ooo, baby <br>On my bended knees <br>I'm begging you to stay here with me <br>Oh, oh, baby, baby, baby, baby <br><br>I could never, never, never, never love another, after loving you <br>Ooo hoo <br>No other love will I share 'cause none could compare <br>After loving you <br>Baby, baby, baby, baby <br>Never love another, after loving you]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="I Could Never Love Another (After Loving You)" label="I Could Never Love Another (After Loving You)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Truly_Truly_Believe/</id><title>The Temptations - I Truly, Truly Believe - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Truly_Truly_Believe/" title="The Temptations - I Truly, Truly Believe - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm sending you red roses and violets <br>Violets of blue, girl <br>The roses mean I love you <br>The violets mean I'll always be true, girl Be true, girl <br><br>Because I really love you <br>And I truly, truly believe, yes I do <br>Inspite of the way you acting, that you love me too <br>Come on and say it dear <br><br>Hmm, you try, to keep me away, girl <br>Just to prove you don't really care <br>But I believe you feel the same way I do <br>And this torture just ain't fair No, this torture just ain't fair <br><br>I'm sending you a bracelet <br>In grave in gold that, I love you girl Love you, girl <br>And I'll send my heart if I could, to prove I'll always be true, girl <br><br>Because I really love you <br>And I truly, truly believe, yes I do <br>Inspite of the way you acting, that you love me too <br>Come on and say it dear <br>Oh, say it dear <br><br>I hope you'd understand <br>That the red roses and violets of blue, girl, Hope you'd understand <br>And that bright shining bracelet, help me, baby, say 'I love you' I love you Love you <br><br>And I really love you <br>And I truly, truly believe, yes I do Yes, I do <br>I believe that you love me <br>So baby, come on and say it <br><br>A Say it I truly believe, yes I do, yes I do, yes I do <br>I truly, truly believe I truly believe, yes I do, yes I do, yes I do <br>I truly believe, yes I do, yes I do, yes I do]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="I Truly, Truly Believe" label="I Truly, Truly Believe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Wish_It_Would_Rain/</id><title>The Temptations - I Wish It Would Rain - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Wish_It_Would_Rain/" title="The Temptations - I Wish It Would Rain - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hmmm <br>Sunshine, blue skies, please go away <br>My girl has found another and gone away <br>With her went my future, my life is filled with gloom <br>So day after day, I stayed locked up in my room <br>I know to you it might sound strange <br>But I wish it would rain How I wish that it would rain <br>Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br><br>'Cause so badly I wanna go outside Such a lovely day <br>But everyone knows that a man ain't suppose to cry, listen <br>I gotta cry 'cause cryin' eases the pain, oh yeah <br>People this hurt I feel inside, words can never explain <br>I just wish it would rain Oh, how I wish that it would rain <br><br>Oh, let it rain <br>Rain, rain, rain Oh, how I wish that it would rain <br>Ooo, baby Let it rain <br>Let it rain Oh yeah, let it rain <br><br>Day in, day out, my tear stained face <br>Pressed against the window pane <br>My eyes search the skies, desperately for rain <br>'Cause raindrops will hide my teardrops <br>And no one will ever know <br>That I'm cryin' cryin' when I go outside <br>To the world outside my tears, I refuse to explain <br>Oh, I wish it would rain Oh, how I wish that it would rain <br>Ooo, baby <br><br>Let it rain, let it rain <br>I need rain to disguise the tears in my eyes <br>Oh, let it rain <br>Oh, yeah, yeah listen <br>I'm a man and I got my pride <br>Give me rain or I'm gonna stay inside <br>Let it rain <br><br>Let it rain <br>Let it rain rain rain rain, rain]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="I Wish It Would Rain" label="I Wish It Would Rain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Ol_Man_River/</id><title>The Temptations - Ol` Man River - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Ol_Man_River/" title="The Temptations - Ol` Man River - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here we all work 'long the Mississippi <br>Here we all work while the white folk play <br>Pullin' them boats from the dawn till sunset <br>Gettin' no rest till the judgment day <br>Don't look up and don't look down <br>Ya don't dast make the white boss frown <br>Bend your knees and bow your head <br>And pull that rope until you're dead <br>Let me go 'way from the Mississippi <br>Let me go 'way from the white man boss <br>Show me that stream called the River Jordan <br>That's the old stream that I long to cross <br><br>Ol' Man River, that Ol' Man River <br>He must know somepin', but he don't say nothin' <br>He just keeps rollin', he keeps on rollin' along <br>He don't plant taters, and he don't plant cotton <br>And them what plants 'em is soon forgotten <br>But Ol' Man River, jest keeps rollin' along <br>You and me, we sweat and strain <br>Bodies all achin' and wracked with pain <br>Tote that barge and lift that bale <br>Ya get a little drunk and ya lands in ja ail <br>I gets weary and so sick of tryin' <br>I'm tired of livin', but I'm feared of dyin' <br>And Ol' Man River, he just keeps rollin' along]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Ol` Man River" label="Ol` Man River"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Hello_Young_Lovers/</id><title>The Temptations - Hello Young Lovers - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Hello_Young_Lovers/" title="The Temptations - Hello Young Lovers - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, young lovers whoever you are <br>I hope your troubles are few <br>All my good wishes go with you tonight <br>I've been in love like you <br><br>Be brave Be brave <br>Young lovers, why don't you come home <br>Follow your sorrow Oh, yeah <br><br>Be brave and faithful and true Be brave and faithful and true <br>Be very close to each other tonight Whoa, yeah <br>I've been in love like you <br><br>I know how it feels to have wings on your heels <br>And to fly, and to fly, and to fly down the street in a trance <br>In a trance, in a trance, in a trance <br>Fly down the street on a chance that you'll meet <br>And you'll meet, not ready by chance <br><br>Don't cry, young lovers, whatever you do <br>Don't cry because I'm alone <br>Don't cry because I'm all alone, now <br>All of my memories are happy tonight <br>I had a love of my own <br>I had a love of my own, like yours <br>I had a love of my own <br><br>Hello, young lovers, whatever you do <br>Don't cry because I'm alone <br>Don't cry because I'm all alone, now <br>All of my memories are happy tonight <br>I had a love of my own <br>I had a love of my own, like yours <br>I had a love of my own, like yours <br>I had a love of my own, like yours <br>I had a love of my own <br><br>Hello young lovers whoever you are <br>Hello young lovers whoever you are <br>Hello young lovers whoever you are <br>Hello young lovers whoever you are <br><br>Hello <br>Hello <br>Hello]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Hello Young Lovers" label="Hello Young Lovers"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Dont_Send_Me_Away/</id><title>The Temptations - Don`t Send Me Away - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Dont_Send_Me_Away/" title="The Temptations - Don`t Send Me Away - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't send me away Don't send me away <br>I've hurt you it's true <br>Don't close the door Don't close the door <br>I'll make it up to you <br>'Cause you know that I need your your wonderful love <br>Whoa <br>Don't send me away Don't send me away <br>I may have been wrong <br>But please let me stay Please let me stay <br>Here, where I belong <br>Darling, you know that I need your your wonderful love <br>I need I need your love your love <br>Dear, through all my days of mine, I need your love <br>Dear, through every phase of mine, I need you love <br>Everyday and in everyway <br>Hmmm <br><br>Don't send me away Don't send me away <br>For I surely be lost <br>I'm willing to pay Willing to pay <br>My life as the cost <br>'Cause you know that I need your love <br>Oh, you know I do I need your love <br>Oh, I'll cherish you I need your love <br>Oh, don't be cruel I need your love]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Don`t Send Me Away" label="Don`t Send Me Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Loneliness_Made_Me_Realize_Its_You_That_I_Need/</id><title>The Temptations - (Loneliness Made Me Realize) It`s You That I Need - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Loneliness_Made_Me_Realize_Its_You_That_I_Need/" title="The Temptations - (Loneliness Made Me Realize) It`s You That I Need - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ooooh Lonely man am I, ever since you said goodbye <br>girl I know that I should have woke up, cuz it seems now that we've broke up <br>your fairwell kiss is haunting mee, my two lips cry out constantly <br>let your heart let your heart be your guide <br>forget about your foolish prid <br>forget about your foolish pride <br><br>Baby I keep tellin, I keep tellin, baby I keep tellin <br>starting tomorrow I keep telling myself <br>im gonna get out and find me somebody else <br>somebody thats sweet and kind who will erase you out of my miiind <br>but tell me how can I find somebody new baby <br>when my two arms keep reaching out for you <br>and my two lips keep right on repeating <br>its you that I need oooooohh <br>you know that even when I close my eyes to forget ya <br>I see your face and your memories too <br>girl I've never felt this lonelyness before, and hooo girl I just cant take it no more <br><br>Every night a million tears I shed, Girl <br>girl i'm only goin out of my head <br>just take a good look and you'll see what this lonelyness is doin to meee <br>paul uh baby its you that need ooooh paul dont you know that its you that I need eddie baaaby Oh I cant take this lonelyness, its you that I need <br>Awww baby I need ya, Its you that I need oooooh Baby <br><br>You that I need Some fool im gonna be no more <br>cuz i'll soon be knockin', knockin' on your door <br>gonna get down on my bending knees <br>beg and plead giiirl come back to me <br>its you that I need ever night a million tears I shed <br>giirl its you that I need every morning goin out of my head <br>girl take a good look and you'll see a, what does this lonelyness]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="(Loneliness Made Me Realize) It`s You That I Need" label="(Loneliness Made Me Realize) It`s You That I Need"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Angel_Doll/</id><title>The Temptations - Angel Doll - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Angel_Doll/" title="The Temptations - Angel Doll - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Angel doll <br>Angel doll <br><br>You excite me everytime you speak <br>When you touch me I get, oh, so weak <br>I have never met a girl like you, baby <br>You're the one that I'll give my whole life to <br><br>All I wanna say is angel doll <br>When I met you there with holiness <br>You're my everything I must confess <br>I have never known such tenderness <br><br>Baby, you can't compare this love we share <br>That takes away my feels, yeah <br>This love and real I can't conceal <br>And I'm so, so, so glad you're here <br><br>Angel doll, it will be a great catastrophe, baby <br>And my whole world would comin' down on me <br>If our love would ever seize to be <br><br>That's why I call you, angel doll <br>You're the substance of my every prayer, baby <br>I'll be happy with you anywhere <br>Let me shield you with my loving care <br><br>Heaven must have sent you, honey <br>You're an angel in disguise, yeah <br>'Cause all the love I wanted so long <br>I can see it in your eyes <br><br>Angel doll, you're the reason that I carry on, baby <br>I can't make it, I can't make it by myself alone <br>You're the one that I'm depending upon <br><br>Angel doll, you know that I love you <br>Angel doll, I put no one above you <br>Angel doll, you knock me off of my feet <br>Angel doll, you make my whole life complete <br>Angel doll]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Angel Doll" label="Angel Doll"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Just_One_Last_Look/</id><title>The Temptations - Just One Last Look - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Just_One_Last_Look/" title="The Temptations - Just One Last Look - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stop right there <br>Let me picture you in my mind for the last time <br>Soon you'll be walking out of my life <br>Let me gaze upon you for the last time <br><br>I need something to hold on to <br>Something to carry me through <br>All I need is one last look before you go <br>So I'll have memories where ever I go <br>One last look before you're gone <br>So in my heart you'll live on and on <br><br>Just one last look before we part <br>So memories of you will fill my heart <br>Let me remember my whole life through <br>'Cause my happiest days, I've spent with you <br>I remember your eyes that was my treasure <br>Your tender lips that brought me pleasure <br>Oh, loving you, I don't regret <br>And all these things I don't want to forget <br>How being without you will be hard to do <br>But I want, I want what's best for you <br>I rather see you happy with someone new, baby <br>Than to bring, bring sorrow to you <br>As you leave <br>If you see tears in my eyes, just keep on walking <br>Don't you worry <br>All these tears you see, are tears of joy <br>The joy of loving you and knowing you'd loved me <br>It's given me enough happiness, so true <br>To last my whole life through <br>Just one last look before you go <br>Let sweet memories overflow <br>So the thought of you will live on and on <br>Long after, after you're gone <br>If I never see your face again <br>Never feel your, your embrace again <br>The happiness I've known with you <br>Will stay with me, baby <br>My whole through <br>Just, just one last look before we part <br>Just one last look to fill my heart <br>Just one last look]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Just One Last Look" label="Just One Last Look"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Youre_My_Everything/</id><title>The Temptations - You`re My Everything - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Youre_My_Everything/" title="The Temptations - You`re My Everything - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You surely must know magic girl <br>Cause you changed my life <br>It was dull and ordinary <br>But you made it sunny and bright <br><br>Now, I was blessed the day I found you <br>Gonna build my whole world around you <br>You're everything good, girl <br>And you're all that matters to me <br><br>When my way was dark and troubles were near <br>Your love provided the light so I could see, girl <br>Just knowin' your love was near when times were bad <br>Kept the world from closin' in on me girl <br><br>I was blessed the day I found you <br>Gonna build my whole world around you <br>You're everything good girl <br>And you're all that matters to me <br><br>Baby, you're part of every thought I think each day <br>Your name is in every phrase my lips say <br>Every dream I dream is about you <br>Honey I can't live without you <br><br>Baby baby, baby baby, baby <br>You're my everything, you're my everything, yes you are <br>Don't you know you're my everything <br><br>You're the girl I sing about <br>In every love song I sing <br>You're my everything <br>You're my winter baby <br>My summer, my fall and spring <br>You're my everything <br><br>Now, now, I was blessed the day I found you <br>Gonna build my whole world around you <br>You're everything good girl and you're all that matters to me <br>You're my everything, you're my everything, yes you are <br>Don't you know you're my everything <br>You're my everything, you're my everything <br>Don't you know you're my everything <br>You're my everything, you're my everything <br><br>When my way was dark and troubles were near, don't you know that <br>Don't you know you're my everything]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="You`re My Everything" label="You`re My Everything"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/No_More_Water_In_The_Well/</id><title>The Temptations - No More Water In The Well - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/No_More_Water_In_The_Well/" title="The Temptations - No More Water In The Well - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No more water in the well, no more <br>No more water in the well, no more <br>You take my love for granted <br>like water, water you spill and you waste <br>Though love is thicker than water <br>it spills quicker than water <br>and you'll lookup one of these days <br>and there'll be no more water in the well <br>How long do you think my love can last <br>through sorrow pain and mistrust <br>Today my love is strong <br>but keep doing me wrong <br>and tomorrow it may turn to dust]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="No More Water In The Well" label="No More Water In The Well"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Im_Doing_It_All/</id><title>The Temptations - I`m Doing It All - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Im_Doing_It_All/" title="The Temptations - I`m Doing It All - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Said I would never be the one to give up us <br>If you and I should ever break up <br>Said I'd never be weak enough to break down <br>And speak of a chance that we might make up <br><br>But I'm doing it all now baby, doing it all <br>Yes, I'm doing it all now baby, doing it all <br>To make sure, oh, that you never, never, never, never, never leave me <br>Please don't ever, ever, ever, ever, ever leave me <br>Don't leave me, don't leave me <br><br>Said that extra things that takes to make a woman sure <br>That a man's love is really true <br>Well, the thing's that I was too strong of a guy <br>To ever break down and do <br><br>But I'm doing it all now, baby, doing it all <br>Yes, I'm doing it all now, baby, doing it all <br>To make sure, oh, that you never, never, never, never, never leave me <br>Please don't ever, ever, ever, ever, ever leave me <br><br>Don't leave me <br>Baby <br>Don't leave me <br>Incomprehensible <br>Yes I am on, ooh babe, yes I am on]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="I`m Doing It All" label="I`m Doing It All"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Sorry_Is_A_Sorry_Word/</id><title>The Temptations - Sorry Is A Sorry Word - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Sorry_Is_A_Sorry_Word/" title="The Temptations - Sorry Is A Sorry Word - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Remember me the one who heard your cries <br>And reached out and dried your eyes <br><br>Remember me the one who found you and wrapped all my love around you <br>When you were all alone and your dreams were all gone <br>When you were nothing but a tear stained face I did feel for you <br>Girl your broken wing is mended and your need for me has ended <br>Girl you say you must be free <br>You wanna fly away from me <br>You were lost and your yesterday is my tomorrow <br>And now you say you must be free, baby <br><br>Sorry is a sorry word after all I've done for you <br>Sorry is a sorry word when I need a love that's true <br><br>Out of sympathy and all you feel for me <br>After all the sweet love I've given to you given you baby <br>Girl you walk away with the best part of me <br>The love I gave to you to give it to someone new <br>And sorry won't ease the feeling <br><br>Sorry is a sorry word after all I've done for you <br>Sorry is a sorry word when I need a love that's true]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Sorry Is A Sorry Word" label="Sorry Is A Sorry Word"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/All_I_Need/</id><title>The Temptations - All I Need - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/All_I_Need/" title="The Temptations - All I Need - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Forgive this fool, my darlin' <br><br>Oh, this heart of mine <br>Carries a heavy load <br>When I think about <br>How I've hurt you so <br><br>After you've been <br>Been so good to me <br>I've been unfaithful, darlin' <br>I've caused you misery <br><br>A feeling of guilt <br>How it tortures me <br>And only you, my darlin' <br>Oh, can set me free and <br><br>Darlin', all <br>All I need <br>Is just to hear you say <br>You'll forgive me <br>Forgive me, baby <br>All, all I need <br>To have you touch my hand <br>Say you'll understand <br><br>A moment of weakness, darlin' <br>Caused me to stray <br>Your trust in me, dear <br>I threw away <br><br>When I look <br>Look into your eyes <br>I can see the hurt, baby <br>That you feel inside <br><br>Although I hurt you, baby <br>You never once complained <br>It makes me feel, sweet darlin' <br>That much more ashamed <br>Tears of guilt, tears of guilt <br>Runnin' down my face <br>Tears that only you, baby <br>Only you can erase and <br><br>Darlin', all <br>All I need <br>Is just to hear you say <br>You'll forgive me <br>Forgive me, baby <br>All, all I need <br>To have you touch my hand <br>Say you'll understand <br><br>Forgive this fool, my darlin' <br><br>I know I made a big mistake <br>When all your love, darlin' <br>Yes, I did forsake <br>It's on my mind <br>It's in my heart <br>This guilty feeling <br>Tearin' me apart <br><br>With every step I make <br>Every breath I take <br>I'll make it up to you <br>I'll make it up to you <br><br>Undo the wrong I've done <br>Undo the wrong I've done <br>I've been unfaithful <br>I know it's true <br>But I'll make it up to you, baby <br><br>All, all I need <br>Is just to hear you say <br>You'll forgive me <br>Forgive me baby <br>All, all I need <br>To have you touch my hand <br>Say you'll understand]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="All I Need" label="All I Need"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Know_Im_Losing_You/</id><title>The Temptations - (I Know) I`m Losing You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Know_Im_Losing_You/" title="The Temptations - (I Know) I`m Losing You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Your love is fading, I can feel your love fading <br>Girl, it's fading away from me <br>'Cause your touch, your touch has grown cold <br>As if someone else controls your very soul <br>I've fooled myself long as I can <br>Can feel the presence of another man <br><br>It's there when you speak my name <br>It's just not the same <br>Ooh baby, I'm losing you <br>It's in the air <br>It's everywhere <br>Ooh baby, I'm losing you <br><br>When I look into your eyes <br>A reflection of a face I see <br>I'm hurtin', downhearted and worried girl <br>'Cause that face doesn't belong to me <br><br>Oh, it's all over your face <br>Someone's taken my place <br>Ooh baby, I'm losing you <br>You try hard to hide <br>The emptiness inside <br>Ooh, I can tell I'm losing you <br>Ooh <br>I don't wanna lose you <br><br>Ooh, I can tell when we kiss <br>From the tenderness I miss <br>Ooh, little girl, I'm losing you <br>Girl, I can feel it in my bones <br>Any day you'll be gone <br>Oh baby, I'm losing you <br>Oh my dear <br>What happened to the love we shared <br>Oh baby, I'm losing you <br>I know it's true <br>There's someone new <br>Oh baby, baby, baby, I'm losing you]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="(I Know) I`m Losing You" label="(I Know) I`m Losing You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Got_Heaven_Right_Here_On_Earth/</id><title>The Temptations - I Got Heaven Right Here On Earth - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/I_Got_Heaven_Right_Here_On_Earth/" title="The Temptations - I Got Heaven Right Here On Earth - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Got myself an angel <br>Straight from the heavens above <br>And I'm truly, truly thankful Thankful <br>For having such a heavenly love <br><br>Just standing she's got it Tell the world about it <br>Found a four leaf clover You put all over <br>And I love her And I love her <br>Listen to me now, she's in love with me <br><br>I got a girl, won't trade her for the world <br>'Cause nothing can match what she's worth <br>She's sweet as can be and she's crazy about me <br>I've got heaven right here on earth <br><br>She's got eyes, that sparkle like diamonds, yeah <br>Listen to me, she's got a heart <br>Talkin' about her heart, that's made of pure gold <br><br>Woo <br>She's sugar and spice, baby Everything nice <br>Peaches and cream The little, little things <br>And I love her And I love her <br>I want to tell you that, she's in love with me <br><br>I got a girl, won't trade her for the world <br>'Cause nothing can match what she's worth <br>She's sweet as can be and she's crazy about me <br>I've got heaven right here on earth <br><br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, ye ye ye yeah <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, ye ye ye yeah <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, ye ye ye yeah <br><br>Whenever we go steppin' out <br>I can't tell you how proud I feel <br>Her beauty so passes for Mona Lisa <br>Sometimes I can't believe she's here <br><br>She's a living dream She's my protection <br>From lonely night nights She's my protection <br>And I love her And I love her <br>Listen to me, she's in love with me <br><br>Let me tell you, 'bout girl won't trade her for the world <br>'Cause nothing can match what she's worth <br>She's sweet as can be and she's crazy about me <br>I've got heaven right here on earth <br><br>Listen to me now, I got a girl won't trade her for the world <br>Listen, nothing can match what she's worth <br>She's sweet as can be and she's crazy about me <br>I've got heaven right here on earth]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="I Got Heaven Right Here On Earth" label="I Got Heaven Right Here On Earth"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Beauty_Is_Only_Skin_Deep/</id><title>The Temptations - Beauty Is Only Skin Deep - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Beauty_Is_Only_Skin_Deep/" title="The Temptations - Beauty Is Only Skin Deep - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So in love, sad as could be <br>'Cause a pretty face got the best of me <br>Suddenly, you came into my life <br>And gave it meaning and pure delight <br>Now, good looks, I've learned to do without <br>'Cause now I know it's love that really counts <br><br>'Cause I know that <br>Beauty's only skin deep, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>I know that <br>Beauty's only skin deep, yes indeed <br><br>Now you speak your words warm and sincere <br>And let's me know that your love is near <br>A pretty face you may not possess <br>But what I like about you is your tenderness <br>A pretty face maybe some guys taste <br>But I'll take lovin' in it's place <br><br>'Cause I know that <br>Beauty's only skin deep, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>And you know that <br>Beauty's only skin deep, oh baby, oh yeah <br>Oh yeah, Oh yeah <br><br>Beauty's only skin deep, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Ooo <br>Beauty's only skin deep, oh yeah <br>Yes it is <br><br>My friends ask, what do I see in you <br>But it goes deeper than the eye can view <br>You have a pleasin' personality <br>And that's an ever lovin' rare quality <br>Now show me a girl, a girl that's fine <br>And I'll choose the one with true lovin' every time <br><br>I know that <br>Beauty's only skin deep, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>And I believe that <br>Beau know that beauty's only skin deep <br><br>So if you're lookin' for a lover Oh yeah <br>Don't judge a book by it's cover Oh yeah <br>She may be fine on the outside Oh yeah <br>But so untrue on the inside Oh yeah <br>Ooo]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Beauty Is Only Skin Deep" label="Beauty Is Only Skin Deep"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Who_You_Gonna_Run_To/</id><title>The Temptations - Who You Gonna Run To - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T21:13:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T21:13:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/Who_You_Gonna_Run_To/" title="The Temptations - Who You Gonna Run To - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you're feeling alright, I never see you coming <br>But when you're hurt, you always come a runnin' <br>But one of these days I know, I gonna have to let you go <br>Then, tell me, who you gonna to run to <br>baby where you gonna hide <br>I wanna know who you gonna tell that you're hurting ing inside <br><br>When you're going strong, when you're going strong <br>I don't see you at all I don't see you at all <br>But when something goes wrong <br>when something goes wrong <br>that's when you call that's when you call <br>But if you keep doing me like you do <br>then I'm gonna turn my back on you <br>Then tell me, who you gonna run to <br><br>Hmmm mm <br><br>When you climbed love's tree, you thought that love was a game <br>but now you're out on a limb, oh yes, and you're calling my name <br>But one of these days I'm bound, to let you come tumbe ling down <br>Then tell me who you gonna run to]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="Who You Gonna Run To" label="Who You Gonna Run To"/></entry></feed>