<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:46:08+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김혜리/우린_없어/</id><title>김혜리 - 우린 없어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:25:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:25:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%98%9C%EB%A6%AC/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%B0_%EC%97%86%EC%96%B4/" title="김혜리 - 우린 없어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[시간이 흐르고 내 모습은 변하고 <br>내 마음속 어딘가에 자꾸 머물러 <br>지나간 기억을 애써 웃어보아도 <br>그대가 올까 봐 매일 잠에서 깨요 <br>널 보려 널 그려 <br>선명하게 비추어진 그 날을 <br>그때의 너와의 순간을 <br>Someday somehow <br>I just hold you again <br>I know you're too far away <br>to get back to me <br>우연히 라도 널 볼 수 있길 바란 <br>내 바램 욕심인 걸까 <br>널 지워 널 잊어 <br>선명하게 비추어지던 그 날을 <br>그때의 너와 내 순간을 <br>Someday somehow <br>I just hold you again <br>I know you're too far away <br>to get back to me <br>우연히 라도 널 볼 수 있길 바란 <br>내 바램 이젠 없어 <br>Someday somehow <br>I will forget you <br>Whenever you go <br>You can't not be better forever <br>날 기억하지 마 <br>난 널 잊고 살 테니 <br>그때의 우린 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="김혜리" label="김혜리"/><category term="우린 없어" label="우린 없어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김태우/선물_Inst/</id><title>김태우 - 선물 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:32:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:32:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%83%9C%EC%9A%B0/%EC%84%A0%EB%AC%BC_Inst/" title="김태우 - 선물 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[처음 너를 만났던 그날 <br>마치 꿈같던 그때 <br>기분 좋은 설렘이 가득 차 <br>매일이 기적 같은 걸 <br>늘 같은 자리에 서서 <br>항상 날 웃게 해주던 너 <br>말로 표현은 잘 못했지만 <br>니가 있어서 고마워 <br>믿기지 않아 니가 주었던 사랑 <br>너무나 부족했던 나였기에 <br>우리 걷는 길이 다신 아프지 않길 <br>언제까지 너만을 위해 노래할게 <br>알면서도 계속해서 읊어봐 <br>추억은 추억으로 <br>남겨질 때 이쁜 것 <br>기억은 앞으로 <br>새겨질 것이기에 이쁠 것 <br>남몰래 흘린 눈물도 <br>혼자 앓았던 그 아픔도 <br>모두 지우고 웃을 수 있게 <br>더 큰 사랑을 네게 줄게 <br>믿기지 않아 니가 주었던 사랑 <br>너무나 부족했던 나였기에 <br>우리 걷는 길이 다신 아프지 않길 <br>언제까지 너만을 위해 노래할게 <br>시간이 흘러 내가 추억이 될 때 <br>웃으며 손잡아줄래 <br>너와 함께 할 수 있다면 <br>어떤 것도 난 두렵지 않아 <br>믿기지 않아 내가 받았던 사랑 <br>이젠 내가 너에게 다가갈게 <br>누가 뭐라 해도 내겐 너뿐이란 걸 <br>기억해줘 <br>and you’re the only one for my life <br>]]></content><category term="김태우" label="김태우"/><category term="선물 (Inst.)" label="선물 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김태우/선물/</id><title>김태우 - 선물 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:32:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:32:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%83%9C%EC%9A%B0/%EC%84%A0%EB%AC%BC/" title="김태우 - 선물 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[처음 너를 만났던 그날 <br>마치 꿈같던 그때 <br>기분 좋은 설렘이 가득 차 <br>매일이 기적 같은 걸 <br>늘 같은 자리에 서서 <br>항상 날 웃게 해주던 너 <br>말로 표현은 잘 못했지만 <br>니가 있어서 고마워 <br>믿기지 않아 니가 주었던 사랑 <br>너무나 부족했던 나였기에 <br>우리 걷는 길이 다신 아프지 않길 <br>언제까지 너만을 위해 노래할게 <br>알면서도 계속해서 읊어봐 <br>추억은 추억으로 <br>남겨질 때 이쁜 것 <br>기억은 앞으로 <br>새겨질 것이기에 이쁠 것 <br>남몰래 흘린 눈물도 <br>혼자 앓았던 그 아픔도 <br>모두 지우고 웃을 수 있게 <br>더 큰 사랑을 네게 줄게 <br>믿기지 않아 니가 주었던 사랑 <br>너무나 부족했던 나였기에 <br>우리 걷는 길이 다신 아프지 않길 <br>언제까지 너만을 위해 노래할게 <br>시간이 흘러 내가 추억이 될 때 <br>웃으며 손잡아줄래 <br>너와 함께 할 수 있다면 <br>어떤 것도 난 두렵지 않아 <br>믿기지 않아 내가 받았던 사랑 <br>이젠 내가 너에게 다가갈게 <br>누가 뭐라 해도 내겐 너뿐이란 걸 <br>기억해줘 <br>and you’re the only one for my life <br>]]></content><category term="김태우" label="김태우"/><category term="선물" label="선물"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최한솔/사르르With_손민경/</id><title>최한솔 - 사르르(With. 손민경) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:32:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:32:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%ED%95%9C%EC%86%94/%EC%82%AC%EB%A5%B4%EB%A5%B4With_%EC%86%90%EB%AF%BC%EA%B2%BD/" title="최한솔 - 사르르(With. 손민경) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 자꾸 보면 볼수록 <br>사랑스러운 걸 두눈에 담으면 <br>어느새 <br>입가에는 웃음꽃 <br>또 살랑살랑 불어와 내게와 <br>Uhm 너와 손을 잡고 걸으면 <br>분홍빛 바람은 날 안아주고 <br>뭐랄까 내 마음은 <br>두근대는 설렘 가득 하곤해 <br>넌 마치 꿀처럼 <br>달콤하게 녹아 사르르르 <br>그 말투 표정 온통 예쁜 너 <br>하나 둘 셋 하면 너 <br>그땐 말해줄래 <br>더 많이 사랑 한다고 <br>한여름 꿈처럼 <br>나를 설레게해 Du ru ru ru <br>아마도 이런게 사랑 인가봐 <br>속삭여줘 매일 더 날 좋아한다고 <br>이 여름밤의 우리둘 <br>가끔씩 배배 꼬인 짓 해도 <br>그것 마저 귀여운 너 그런 너 <br>Uhm 너와 손을 잡고 걸을 때면 <br>날아갈 것 같이 부푸는 기분 <br>너를 안을때면 <br>두근대는 설렘 가득 하곤해 <br>넌 마치 꿀처럼 <br>달콤하게 녹아 사르르르 <br>그 말투 표정 온통 예쁜 너 <br>하나 둘 셋 하면 너 <br>그땐 말해줄래 <br>더 많이 사랑 한다고 <br>한여름 꿈처럼 <br>나를 설레게해 Du ru ru ru <br>아마도 이런게 사랑 인가봐 <br>속삭여줘 매일 더 날 좋아한다고 <br>나에게 말해줘 <br>가끔 넌 밉기도 <br>그런 날도 있지 뭐 <br>그래도 니가 <br>너무 좋은걸 <br>말하지 않아도 <br>알아 네맘 다 <br>이렇게 매일 널 사랑해 <br>품에 안으면 <br>달콤하게 녹아 사르르르 <br>나는 니가 있어 행복한걸 <br>하루 이틀 시간이 흘러 지난대도 <br>더 많이 사랑한다고 <br>한여름 꿈처럼 <br>나를 설레게해 Du ru ru ru <br>아마도 이런게 사랑 인가봐 <br>속삭여줘 매일 더 날 좋아한다고 <br>이 여름밤의 우리둘 <br>]]></content><category term="최한솔" label="최한솔"/><category term="사르르(With. 손민경)" label="사르르(With. 손민경)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/2ffect/Goodbye/</id><title>2ffect - Goodbye - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:33:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:33:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/2ffect/Goodbye/" title="2ffect - Goodbye - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 헤어지자 입술 떨리며 말하는 <br>너의 마지막 그 말 <br>너무 사랑했는데 눈물로 <br>보내줄 수 밖에 없었지 <br>모두 꿈일 거라고 나 혼자 멍하니 <br>생각했지만 이제는 <br>내 곁에 없는 널 <br>웃으며 보내 주려 해 <br>안녕 GoodBye 안녕 <br>널 잊는 게 쉽지 않겠지만 <br>이제는 너를 지우려고 해 <br>안녕 GoodBye 안녕 <br>너와 행복했던 시간들 꿈이라 믿을게 <br>꿈에서 깨보니 내 방에 사진은 <br>그대로지만 이제는 <br>내 곁에 없는 널 <br>웃으며 보내 줘야만 하는데 <br>안녕 GoodBye 안녕 <br>널 잊는 게 쉽지 않겠지만 <br>이제는 너를 지우려고 해 <br>안녕 GoodBye 안녕 <br>너와 행복했던 시간들 꿈이라 믿을게 <br>널 지워볼게 잊으려 노력해볼게 <br>안녕이란 말 너를 처음 만나 웃으면서 <br>설레이며 말을 했었던 그 말 <br>안녕 반가워 날 반기던 <br>너의 모습 기억 속에서 <br>지울 수가 없나 봐 <br>안녕 안녕 <br>이젠 헤어진 이 순간을 꿈처럼 잊을게 <br>이젠 안녕 <br>]]></content><category term="2ffect" label="2ffect"/><category term="Goodbye" label="Goodbye"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/2ffect/Im_sorry_Feat_김예지/</id><title>2ffect - I`m sorry (Feat. 김예지) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:33:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:33:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/2ffect/Im_sorry_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EC%98%88%EC%A7%80/" title="2ffect - I`m sorry (Feat. 김예지) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[낙엽이 지던 가을 어느 날 <br>너와 크게 다퉜던 그날 <br>이미 뱉어버린 말을 주워 담을 수 없어 <br>네게 상처를 줬지 <br>그 상처로 인해 <br>연락이 되지 않던 너를 <br>이젠 돌릴 순 없겠지 <br>낙엽 지던 차디찬 가을 날 같았어 <br>잠시 욱했던 마음에 <br>나의 말 실수로 인해 <br>너의 맘을 <br>너의 맘을 <br>아프게 했어 <br>그 말 진심이 아니야 <br>욱했던 말일 뿐이야 <br>미안해 <br>미안해 <br>그때 하지 못한 말 <br>I'm Sorry <br>싸울 때 마다 했던 말 <br>헤어지자는 그 말을 쉽게 <br>하는 게 아니었는데 <br>그 상처로 인해 연락이 되지 않던 너 <br>이젠 돌릴 순 없겠지 <br>낙엽 지던 차디 찬 가을 날 그날 <br>잠시 욱했던 마음에 <br>나의 말 실수로 인해 <br>너의 맘을 <br>너의 맘을 <br>아프게 했어 <br>그 말 진심이 아니야 <br>욱했던 말일 뿐이야 <br>미안해 <br>미안해 <br>그때 하지 못한 말 <br>I'm Sorry <br>왜 시간이 지나야 아는지 <br>그때 알았다면 <br>널 떠나 보내지 않을 텐데 <br>우 워 우 워 예 <br>잠시 욱했던 마음에 <br>나의 말 실수로 인해 <br>너의 맘을 <br>너의 맘을 <br>아프게 했어 <br>그 말 진심이 아니야 <br>욱했던 말일 뿐이야 <br>미안해 <br>미안해 <br>그때 하지 못한 말 <br>I'm Sorry <br>]]></content><category term="2ffect" label="2ffect"/><category term="I`m sorry (Feat. 김예지)" label="I`m sorry (Feat. 김예지)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제타_ZETTA/Poker_Face/</id><title>제타_ZETTA - Poker Face - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:34:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:34:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%ED%83%80_ZETTA/Poker_Face/" title="제타_ZETTA - Poker Face - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey girls <br>brother Just hurry up <br>We back are you ready <br>This is Zetta Time <br>She is Poker face <br>She is Poker face <br>She is Poker face <br>She is Poker face <br>Z.E.T.T.A <br>거침없는 목소리 <br>뭔가 끝없는 자신감 <br>애써 말하지 않아도 <br>날 다 아는 것 같아 <br>hey 도도한 그 눈빛이 <br>날 더더더 미치게 해 <br>어쩜 그렇게도 빤히 날 보는지 <br>넌 정말 미스테리 <br>이건 이건 아닌데 <br>왜 매일 매일 네가 보고싶어 <br>I am chill 나름대로 멋진 놈인데 <br>네 앞에서면 왜 난 작아져 <br>어제까지 매달리며 내게 넘어오던 <br>네가 아니잖아 <br>네 속을 모르겠어 <br>come it come it come it <br>She is pokerface <br>Don't stop me <br>come on come on come on <br>She is pokerface <br>내 삶에 단 한번 질 수 없는 게임 <br>She is pokerface <br>It's time to play play play <br>She is pokerface <br>Too much time panic panic panic <br>날카로운 긴장감 <br>애써 버티고 있지만 <br>결국에 난 정신을 놓쳐버릴 것 같아 <br>빈틈없는 표정이 <br>날 더더더 미치게 해 <br>어쩜 그렇게도 훤히 나를 아는지 <br>넌 정말 미스테리 <br>이건 이건 아닌데 <br>왜 매일 매일 네가 보고싶어 <br>I am chill 나름대로 멋진 놈인데 <br>네 앞에서면 왜 난 작아져 <br>어제까지 매달리며 내게 넘어오던 <br>네가 아니잖아 <br>네 속을 모르겠어 <br>come it come it come it <br>She is pokerface <br>Don't stop me <br>come on come on come on <br>She is pokerface <br>내 삶에 단 한번 질 수 없는 게임 <br>She is pokerface <br>It's time to play play play <br>She is pokerface <br>Too much time panic panic panic <br>Three Two one Tell'em her <br>네가 점점 좋아진 걸까 <br>멈출 수도 없는 맘에 너의 마음 So <br>점점 더욱 커지네 <br>Ain't NOBODY LOVE GIRL'S <br>HELLO BODY THAT GIRL <br>Just hold me back to your hands <br>baby come on come on come on <br>She is pokerface <br>Don't stop me <br>come on come on come on <br>She is pokerface <br>내 삶에 단 한번 질 수 없는 게임 <br>She is pokerface <br>It's time to play play play <br>She is pokerface <br>Too much time panic panic panic <br>She is pokerface <br>]]></content><category term="제타 (ZETTA)" label="제타 (ZETTA)"/><category term="Poker Face" label="Poker Face"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제타_ZETTA/ZTA/</id><title>제타_ZETTA - Z.T.A - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:34:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:34:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%ED%83%80_ZETTA/ZTA/" title="제타_ZETTA - Z.T.A - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모두 숨죽인 지금 이 순간 <br>이 무대 위엔 무대 위엔 <br>오직 너만이 <br>나를 진짜로 만들어줘 Real ZETTA <br>가만있어도 숨죽여 <br>느낄 수 있어 느낄 수 있어 <br>네가 원하는 <br>그게 뭐든 간에 말만 해 내가 줄게 <br>이 밤은 점점 깊어가 <br>나에게 빠져가는 사이에 <br>고민은 하지마 넌 결국 내게로 와 <br>Just let me talk to you <br>말해봐 네 맘을 <br>미쳐봐 이 시간 <br>가져가 내 모든 것 <br>넌 너무 예뻐서 <br>모두가 원하지 <br>나는 널 놓지 않아 WE'RE ZETTA <br>보여줘 네 REACTION <br>너의 EMOTION <br>show me what you got emotion <br>보여줘 네 REACTION <br>너의 EMOTION Z.T.A ZETTA <br>내가 별로서 반짝일 수 있게 <br>넌 밤하늘이 되어주기에 <br>절대 버려두지 않아 계속 따라와 <br>환한 빛이 되어 비춰줄게 <br>내딛고 Let it go 너에게로 Go <br>가지려 가려도 가질 수 없고 <br>마음속 귀를 열어줘 네 길을 보여줘 <br>우린 We are one ZETTA <br>이 밤은 점점 깊어가 <br>나에게 빠져가는 사이에 <br>고민은 하지마 넌 결국 내게로 와 <br>Just let me talk to you <br>말해봐 네 맘을 <br>미쳐봐 이 시간 <br>가져가 내 모든 것 <br>넌 너무 예뻐서 <br>모두가 원하지 <br>나는 널 놓지 않아 WE'RE ZETTA <br>보여줘 네 REACTION <br>너의 EMOTION <br>show me what you got emotion <br>보여줘 네 REACTION <br>너의 EMOTION Z.T.A ZETTA <br>말해봐 네 맘을 <br>미쳐봐 이 시간 <br>가져가 내 모든 것 <br>넌 너무 예뻐서 <br>모두가 원하지 <br>나는 널 놓지 않아 WE'RE ZETTA <br>보여줘 네 REACTION <br>너의 EMOTION <br>show me what you got emotion <br>보여줘 네 REACTION <br>너의 EMOTION Z.T.A ZETTA <br>]]></content><category term="제타 (ZETTA)" label="제타 (ZETTA)"/><category term="Z.T.A" label="Z.T.A"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/어쿠스틱클라우드/꿈꾸는해변/</id><title>어쿠스틱클라우드 - 꿈꾸는해변 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:34:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:34:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%B4%EC%BF%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B1%ED%81%B4%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B0%EB%93%9C/%EA%BF%88%EA%BE%B8%EB%8A%94%ED%95%B4%EB%B3%80/" title="어쿠스틱클라우드 - 꿈꾸는해변 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[시원한 바다 뜨거운 햇살 <br>야자나무 아래 흔들리는 해먹 <br>시원한 맥주 느긋한 음악 <br>파도소리 함께 밀려드는 바람 <br>시간이 이대로 멈췄으면 <br>영원히 이대로 <br>시간이 이대로 멈췄으면 <br>영원히 이대로 <br>너와 함께 <br>꿈꾸는 해변 달콤한 와인 <br>에메랄드 파도 부서지는 별빛 <br>낭만 가득한 향기로운 음악 <br>부드러운 입술 아름다운 그대 <br>시간이 이대로 멈췄으면 <br>영원히 이대로 <br>시간이 이대로 멈췄으면 <br>영원히 이대로 <br>오 아 <br>오 아 <br>시간이 이대로 멈췄으면 <br>영원히 이대로 <br>너와 함께 <br>너와 함께 <br>너와 함께 <br>]]></content><category term="어쿠스틱클라우드" label="어쿠스틱클라우드"/><category term="꿈꾸는해변" label="꿈꾸는해변"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Robe/조금이라도_With_루오/</id><title>Robe - 조금이라도 (With 루오) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:34:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:34:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Robe/%EC%A1%B0%EA%B8%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%9D%BC%EB%8F%84_With_%EB%A3%A8%EC%98%A4/" title="Robe - 조금이라도 (With 루오) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무렇지 않을 거라고 말했었죠 <br>후회할 거 알면서도 <br>그대 생각날 때마다 <br>아파할 거면서 <br>마음이 움직이는 걸 <br>막을 수 없었죠 <br>우린 인연이 아닌 걸 알면서 <br>멀어지길 바란 건 아니에요 <br>아파하길 바란 건 아니에요 <br>잠시라도 같이 있고 싶은 <br>내 마음 아나요 <br>조금이라도 나를 기억해줘요 <br>몇 안 되는 추억조차도 <br>나는 생각이 나죠 <br>눈 뜨는 순간 다시 잠들 때까지 난 <br>하루 종일 그대 생각만 <br>한번 보면 생각나 아파하면서 <br>떠나간 걸 지켜볼 수밖에 없었죠 <br>아파하길 바란 건 아니에요 <br>예전처럼 시간도 <br>되돌릴 수는 없나요 <br>조금이라도 나를 기억해줘요 <br>몇 안 되는 추억조차도 <br>나는 생각이 나죠 <br>눈 뜨는 순간 다시 잠들 때까지 난 <br>하루 종일 그대 생각만 <br>이런 내가 그댈 <br>사랑하고 있습니다 <br>]]></content><category term="Robe" label="Robe"/><category term="조금이라도 (With 루오)" label="조금이라도 (With 루오)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박준오/You_Feat_Jenna_Nicholls/</id><title>박준오 - You (Feat. Jenna Nicholls) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:34:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:34:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A4%80%EC%98%A4/You_Feat_Jenna_Nicholls/" title="박준오 - You (Feat. Jenna Nicholls) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[life made me dry <br>it was like perfume in the air <br>I threw out my innocence <br>never to be hurt again <br>don't say i'm wrong <br>i need some warmth <br>don't say i'm wrong <br>just be with me <br>but you now came to me <br>i feel different <br>and you can show to me <br>that i was wrong <br>life was so new but now i find <br>everything ends the same way <br>i feel my heart closed not to <br>waste time anymore <br>don't say i'm wrong <br>i need some warmth <br>don't say i'm wrong <br>just be with me <br>but you now came to me <br>i feel different <br>and you can show to me <br>that i was wrong <br>oh I'm <br>oh I'm afraid you know <br>You make me pure <br>You can you hold me <br>oh hold me <br>hold me <br>]]></content><category term="박준오" label="박준오"/><category term="You (Feat. Jenna Nicholls)" label="You (Feat. Jenna Nicholls)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Wicked_Little_Town_Hedwig_Version/</id><title>Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Wicked Little Town (Hedwig Version) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:36:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:36:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Wicked_Little_Town_Hedwig_Version/" title="Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Wicked Little Town (Hedwig Version) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You know, the sun is in your eyes <br>And hurricanes and rains <br>and black and cloudy skies. <br>You're running up and down that hill. <br>You turn it on and off at will. <br>There's nothing here to thrill <br>or bring you down. <br>And if you've got no other choice <br>You know you can follow my voice <br>through the dark turns and noise <br>of this wicked little tow n. <br><br><br>Oh Lady, luck has led you here <br>and they're so twisted up <br>they'll twist you up. I fear. <br>the pious, hateful and devout, <br>you're turning tricks til you're turned out, <br>the wind so cold it burns, <br>you're burning out and blowing round. <br>And if you've got no other choice <br>you know you can follow my voice <br>through the dark turns and noise <br>of this wicked little town. <br><br><br>The fates are vicious and they're cruel. <br>You learn too late you've used two wishes <br>like a fool <br>and then you're someone you are not, <br>and Junction City ain't the spot, <br>remember Mrs. Lot <br>and when she turned around. <br>And if you've got no other choice <br>You know you can follow my voice <br>through the dark turns and noise <br>of this wicked little town.]]></content><category term="Hedwig And The Angry Inch" label="Hedwig And The Angry Inch"/><category term="Wicked Little Town (Hedwig Version)" label="Wicked Little Town (Hedwig Version)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/In_Your_Arms_Tonight/</id><title>Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - In Your Arms Tonight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:36:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:36:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/In_Your_Arms_Tonight/" title="Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - In Your Arms Tonight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Running head on <br>To things that knock me down <br>Over again <br>He picked me off the ground <br>And I wasn't strong enough to fight <br>Anymore, but In Your Arms Tonight <br>Hold me close and tight <br>In your arms tonight <br>In your arms tonight <br>In your arms tonight <br>Oh my love <br>God only knows <br>Why I don't just retreat <br>'Stead of riding the rails <br>Back to the place of my worst defeat <br>'Cause I'm not fooling anyone, not quite <br>Convincing You <br>But when your arms are in mine <br>Try not to be strong <br>Cry 'til it's all gone <br>If you hold me tight <br>In your arms tonight <br>Oh my love <br>For years you've seen in me the one who'd be there for you <br>The way I need you, here tonight <br>Yeah yeah yeah <br>In your arms tonight <br>In your arms tonight <br>In your arms tonight <br>ooh in your arms ooh my love oh yah ooh ooh ooh yah]]></content><category term="Hedwig And The Angry Inch" label="Hedwig And The Angry Inch"/><category term="In Your Arms Tonight" label="In Your Arms Tonight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Midnight_Radio/</id><title>Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Midnight Radio - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:37:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:37:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Midnight_Radio/" title="Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Midnight Radio - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Rain falls hard <br>Burns dry <br>A dream <br>Or a song <br>That hits you so hard <br>Filling you up <br>And suddenly gone <br><br>Breath Feel Love <br>Give Free <br>Know in you soul <br>Like your blood knows the way <br>From you heart to your brain <br>Know that you're whole <br><br>And you're shining <br>Like the brightest star <br>A transmission <br>On the midnight radio <br>And you're spinning <br>Like a 45 <br>Ballerina <br>Dancing to your rock and roll <br><br>Here's to Patti <br>And Tina <br>And Yoko <br>Aretha <br>And Nona <br>And Nico <br>And me <br><br>And all the strange rock and rollers <br>You know you're doing all right <br>So hold on to each other <br>You gotta hold on tonight <br><br>And you're shining <br>Like the brightest stars <br>A transmission <br>On the midnight radio <br><br>And you're spinning <br>Your new 45's <br>All the misfits and the losers <br>Yeah, you know you're rock and rollers <br>Spinning to your rock and roll <br><br><br>Lift up your hands]]></content><category term="Hedwig And The Angry Inch" label="Hedwig And The Angry Inch"/><category term="Midnight Radio" label="Midnight Radio"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Hedwigs_Lament/</id><title>Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Hedwig`s Lament - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:37:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:37:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Hedwigs_Lament/" title="Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Hedwig`s Lament - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was born on the other side <br>of a town ripped in two <br>And no matter how hard I've tried <br>I end up black and blue <br>I rose from off of the doctor's slab <br>I lost a piece of my heart <br>Now everyone gets to take a stab <br>They cut me up into parts <br>I gave a piece to my mother <br>I gave a piece to my man <br>I gave a piece to the rock star <br>He took the good stuff and ran]]></content><category term="Hedwig And The Angry Inch" label="Hedwig And The Angry Inch"/><category term="Hedwig`s Lament" label="Hedwig`s Lament"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/The_Long_Grift/</id><title>Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - The Long Grift - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:37:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:37:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/The_Long_Grift/" title="Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - The Long Grift - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look what you've done, <br> you gigolo. <br> You know that I loved you, hon, <br> and I didn't want to know <br> that your cool, <br> seductive serenade <br> was a tool <br> of your trade, <br> you gigolo. <br><br> Of all the riches you've surveyed, <br> and all that you can lift, <br> I'm just another dollar that you made <br> in you long, long grift. <br><br> Look what you've done, <br> you gigolo. <br> Another hustle has been run, <br> and now you ought to know <br> that this fool <br> can no longer be swayed <br> by the tools <br> of your trade, <br> you gigolo. <br><br> I'm just another john you've gypped, <br> another sucker stiffed, <br> a walk on role in the script <br> to your long, long grift. <br> The love that had me in your grip <br> was just a long, long grift. <br><br>7. Hedwig's Lament <br><br>I was born on the other side <br> of a town ripped in two <br> And no matter how hard I've tried <br> I end up black and blue <br><br> I rose from off of the doctor's slab <br> I lost a piece of my heart <br> Now everyone gets to take a stab <br> They cut me up into parts <br><br> I gave a piece to my mother <br> I gave a piece to my man <br> I gave a piece to the rock star <br> He took the good stuff and ran]]></content><category term="Hedwig And The Angry Inch" label="Hedwig And The Angry Inch"/><category term="The Long Grift" label="The Long Grift"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Wig_In_A_Box/</id><title>Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Wig In A Box - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:37:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:37:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Wig_In_A_Box/" title="Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Wig In A Box - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[On nights like this <br>When the world's a bit amiss <br>And the lights go down <br>Across the trailer park <br>I get down <br>I feel had <br>I feel on the verge of going mad <br>And then it's time to punch the clock <br><br>I put on some make-up <br>Turn on the tape deck <br>And put the wig back on my head <br>Suddenly i'm miss midwest <br>Midnight checkout queen <br>Until i head home <br>And i put myself to bed <br><br>I look back on where i'm from <br>Look at the woman i've become <br>And the strangest things <br>Seem suddenly routine <br>I look up from my vermouth on the rocks <br>A gift-wrapped wig still in the box <br>Of towering velveteen <br><br>I put on some make-up <br>And some lavern baker <br>And pull the wig down from the shelf <br>Suddenly i'm miss beehive 1963 <br>Until i wake up <br>And turn back to myself <br><br>Some girls they got natural ease <br>They wear it any way they please <br>With their french flip curls <br>And perfumed magazines <br>Wear it up <br>Let it down <br>This is the best way that i've found <br>To be the best you've ever seen <br><br>I put on some make-up <br>And turn up the eight-track <br>I'm pulling the wig down from the shelf <br>Suddenly i'm miss farrah fawcett <br>From tv <br>Until i wake up <br>And turn back to myself <br><br>Shag, bi-level, bob <br>Dorothy hammil do, <br>Sausage curls, chicken wings <br>It's all because of you <br>With your blow dried, feather back, <br>Toni home wave, too <br>Flip, fro, frizz, flop, <br>It's all because of you <br>It's all because of you <br>It's all because of you <br><br>I put on some make-up <br>Turn up the eight-track <br>I'm pulling the wig down from the shelf <br>Suddenly i'm this punk rock star <br>Of stage and screen <br>And i ain't never <br>I'm never turning back]]></content><category term="Hedwig And The Angry Inch" label="Hedwig And The Angry Inch"/><category term="Wig In A Box" label="Wig In A Box"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Wicked_Little_Town_Tommy_Gnosis_Version/</id><title>Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Wicked Little Town (Tommy Gnosis Version) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:37:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:37:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Wicked_Little_Town_Tommy_Gnosis_Version/" title="Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Wicked Little Town (Tommy Gnosis Version) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Forgive me, <br>For I did not know. <br>'Cause I was just a boy <br>And you were so much more <br>Than any god could ever plan, <br>More than a woman or a man. <br>And now I understand how much I took from you: <br>That, when everything starts breaking down, <br>You take the pieces off the ground <br>And show this wicked town <br>something beautiful and new. <br>You think that Luck <br>Has left you there. <br>But maybe there's nothing <br>up in the sky but air. <br>And there's no mystical design, <br>No cosmic lover preassigned. <br>There's nothing you can find <br>that can not be found. <br>'Cause with all the changes <br>you've been through <br>It seems the stranger's always you. <br>Alone again in some new <br>Wicked little town. <br>So when you've got no other choice <br>You know you can follow my voice <br>Through the dark turns and noise <br>Of this wicked little town. <br>Oh it's a wicked, little town. <br>Goodbye, wicked little town.]]></content><category term="Hedwig And The Angry Inch" label="Hedwig And The Angry Inch"/><category term="Wicked Little Town (Tommy Gnosis Version)" label="Wicked Little Town (Tommy Gnosis Version)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Angry_Inch/</id><title>Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Angry Inch - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:37:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:37:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Angry_Inch/" title="Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Angry Inch - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My sex-change operation got botched <br>My guardian angel fell asleep on the watch <br>Now all I got is a Barbie Doll-crotch <br>I got an angry inch <br><br>Six inches forward and five inches back <br>I got a <br>I got an angry inch <br><br>Six inches forward and five inches back <br>I got a <br>I got an angry inch <br><br>I’m from the land where you still hear the cries <br>I had to get out, had to sever all ties <br>I changed my name and assumed a disguise <br>I got an angry inch <br><br>Six inches forward and five inches back <br>I got a <br>I got an angry inch <br><br>Six inches forward and five inches back <br>I got a <br>I got an angry inch <br><br>Six inches forward and five inches back <br>The train is coming and I’m tied to the track <br>I try to get up but I can’t get no slack <br>I got a <br>Angry Inch Angry Inch <br><br>My mother made my tits out of clay <br>My boyfriend told me that he’d take me away <br>They dragged me to the doctor one day <br>I've got an angry inch <br><br>Six inches forward and five inches back <br>I got a <br>I got an angry inch <br><br>Six inches forward and five inches back <br>I got a <br>I got an angry inch <br><br>Long story short <br><br>When I woke up from the operation <br>I was bleeding down there <br>I was bleeding from the gash between my legs <br><br>My first day as a woman <br>and already it’s that time of the month <br>But two days later <br>the hole closed up <br>The wound healed <br>and I was left with a one inch mound of flesh <br><br>where my penis used to be <br>where my vagina never was <br>A one inch mound of flesh with a scar running down it <br>like a sideways grimace <br>on an eyeless face <br>Just a little bulge <br>It was an angry inch <br><br>Six inches forward and five inches back <br>The train is coming and I’m tied to the track <br>I try to get up but I can’t get no slack <br>I got an <br>Angry Inch Angry Inch <br><br>Six inches forward and five inches back <br>stay under cover till the night turns to black <br>I got my inch and I’m set to attack <br>I got an Angry Inch Angry Inch]]></content><category term="Hedwig And The Angry Inch" label="Hedwig And The Angry Inch"/><category term="Angry Inch" label="Angry Inch"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Origin_of_Love/</id><title>Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Origin of Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:37:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:37:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Origin_of_Love/" title="Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Origin of Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When the earth was still flat <br>And clouds made of fire <br>And mountains stretched up to the sky <br>Sometimes higher <br>Folks roamed the earth like big rolling kegs <br>They had two sets of arms <br>They had two sets of legs <br>They had two faces peering <br>Out of one giant head <br>So they could watch all around them <br>As they talked; while they read <br>And they never knew nothing of love <br>It was before the origin of love <br>The origin of love <br><br>And there were three sexes then <br>One that looked like two men <br>Glued up back to back <br>Called the children of the sun <br>And similiar in shape and girth <br>Was the children of the earth <br>They looked like two girls rolled up in one <br>And the children of the moon <br>Were like a fork stuck on a spoon <br>They were part sun, part earth, part daughter, part son <br>The origin of love <br><br>Now the gods grew quite scared <br>Of our strength and defiance <br>And Thor said "I'm gonna kill them all with my hammer <br>Like I killed the giants" <br>But the Zeus said "No <br>You better let me use my lightning like scissors <br>Like I cut the legs off the whales <br>Dinosaurs into lizards" <br>Then he grabbed up some bolts <br>And he let out a laugh <br>Said "I'll split them right down the middle <br>Gonna cut them right up in half" <br>And the storm clouds gathered above <br>Into great balls of fire <br><br>And then fire shot down from the sky in bolts <br>Like shining blades of a knife <br>And it ripped right through the flesh <br>Of the children of the sun and the moon <br>And the earth <br>And some Indian god sewed the wound up <br>Into a hole <br>Pulled it 'round to our bellies <br>To remind us the price we pay <br>And Osiris and the gods of the nile <br>Gathered up a big storm <br>To blow a hurricane <br>To scatter us away <br>In a flood of wind and rain <br>And a sea of tidal waves <br>To wash us all away <br>And if we don't behave <br>They'll cut us down again <br>We'll be hopping around on one foot <br>And looking through one eye <br><br>Last time I saw you <br>We just split in two <br>You was looking at me <br>I was looking at you <br>You had a way so familiar <br>But I could not recognize <br>'cause you had blood in your face <br>And I had blood in my eyes <br>But I could swear by your expression <br>That the pain down in your soul <br>Was the same as the one down in mine <br>That's the pain <br>That cuts a straight line down through the heart <br>We call it love <br>We wrapped our arms around each other <br>Trying to shove ourselves back together <br>We were making love <br>Making love <br>It was a cold dark evening such a long time ago <br>When by the mighty hand of Jove <br>It was a sad story how we became <br>Lonely two-legged creatures <br>It's the story <br>The origin of love <br>That's the origin of love]]></content><category term="Hedwig And The Angry Inch" label="Hedwig And The Angry Inch"/><category term="Origin of Love" label="Origin of Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Tear_Me_Down/</id><title>Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Tear Me Down - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:37:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:37:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch/Tear_Me_Down/" title="Hedwig_And_The_Angry_Inch - Tear Me Down - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was born on the other side <br>Of a town ripped in two <br>I made it over the great divide <br>Now I'm coming for you <br><br>Enemies and adversaries <br>They try and tear me down <br>You want me baby, I dare you <br>Try and tear me down <br><br>I rose from off of the doctor's slab <br>Like Lazarus from the pit <br>Now everyone wants to take a stab <br>And decorate me <br>With blood, graffiti and spit <br><br>Enemies and adversaries <br>They try to tear me down <br>You want me, baby, I dare you <br>Try and tear me down <br><br>On August 13, 1961 <br>A wall was erected <br>Down the middle of the city of Berlin <br>The world was divided by a cold war <br>And the Berlin Wall <br>Was the most hated symbol of that divide <br>Reviled, graffitied, spit upon <br>We thought the wall would stand forever <br>And now that it's gone <br>We don't know who we are anymore <br>Ladies and gentlemen <br>Hedwig is like that wall <br>Standing before you in the divide <br>Between East and West <br>Slavery and freedom <br>Man and woman <br>Top and bottom <br>And you can try and tear her down <br>But before you do <br>You must remember one thing--Hed: <br><br>There ain't much of a difference <br>Between a bridge and a wall <br>Without me right in the middle, babe <br>You would be nothing at all <br><br>Enemies and adversaries <br>They try and tear me down <br>You want me, baby, I dare you <br>Try and tear me down]]></content><category term="Hedwig And The Angry Inch" label="Hedwig And The Angry Inch"/><category term="Tear Me Down" label="Tear Me Down"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박준한/기억_추억/</id><title>박준한 - 기억 추억 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:37:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:37:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A4%80%ED%95%9C/%EA%B8%B0%EC%96%B5_%EC%B6%94%EC%96%B5/" title="박준한 - 기억 추억 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[함께한 추억들이 많아서 <br>이제는 다시 너를 <br>잊을 수가 없는가 봐 <br>너라는 사람 밖에 몰랐던 내가 <br>이렇게 혼자 버텨내 보려 한다 <br>돌아보면 아쉬움만 남은 <br>그날이 다시 온다면 <br>단 하루도 변치 못한 <br>우리의 사랑을 <br>이렇게 흘려 보낼 자신이 없어 <br>기억 추억 가슴 안에 남아 <br>아직도 비워내 보려 하지만 <br>한때는 운명 같았던 <br>그날의 추억이 <br>모두 지워지지가 않아 <br>돌아보면 아쉬움만 남은 <br>그날이 다시 온다면 <br>단 하루도 변치 않아 <br>널 떠나 보내고 <br>이렇게 하루하루 널 기다리잖아 <br>기억 추억 가슴 안에 남아 <br>아직도 비워내 보려 하지만 <br>한때는 운명 같았던 <br>그날의 추억이 <br>모두 지워지지가 않아 <br>결국엔 이것밖에 안 되는 <br>아무것도 아닌 나를 <br>사랑해줬던 <br>너 다시 돌아와 준다면 <br>나 다시 데려가 준다면 <br>온종일 이 생각들이 이어져 간다 <br>그리워 그리워 니가 내게 했던 <br>그 말투와 행동 그 표정까지도 <br>고스란히 간직해둘게 <br>꺼내볼 수 있도록 <br>다시 니가 내 곁에 올 그날에 <br>다시 니가 내 곁에 올 그날에 <br>]]></content><category term="박준한" label="박준한"/><category term="기억 추억" label="기억 추억"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BOP/물생활사랑/</id><title>BOP - 물생활사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:37:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:37:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BOP/%EB%AC%BC%EC%83%9D%ED%99%9C%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="BOP - 물생활사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[매일 아침 일어나 니 안부를 물어 <br>밤엔 춥지 않았는지 잠은 잤는지 <br>오늘 아침 하룬 어떻게 지낼 건지 <br>그러면 넌 밝게 웃어주면서 <br>동그란 눈빛을 내게 주면서 오늘 하룰 <br>날 살 수 있게 만들어 <br>난 그저 널 바라만 보며 서있어 <br>혹시 다치진 않을까 만지진 못해도 <br>난 웃으며 너에게 인사를 건네 <br>그런 넌 나를 보며 <br>호기심에 찬 눈빛으로 <br>배고프다 하고 심심하다 하고 <br>매일 나에게 웃음만을 주는걸 <br>난 오늘밤 일찍 퇴근할거야 <br>너에게 아침밥을 주는걸 까먹은 거야 <br>혹시 너가 용왕님 만날까 봐 <br>난 그저 널 바라만 보며 서있어 <br>혹시 용왕님 만날까 만지진 못해도 <br>일주일에 한번씩 물은 갈아주잖아 <br>그런 넌 나를 보며 <br>호기심에 찬 눈빛으로 <br>물 좀 그만 갈라 하고 <br>손 좀 넣지 말라고 <br>매일 나에게 웃음만을 주는걸 <br>오 구피 <br>오 코리도라스 <br>오 체리새우 <br>오 물생활 <br>난 그저 널 바라만 보며 서있어 <br>혹시 다치진 않을까 만지진 못해도 <br>난 웃으며 너에게 인사를 건네 <br>난 그저 널 바라만 보며 서 있을게 <br>혹시 용왕님 만날까 만지진 못해도 <br>일주일에 한번씩 물은 갈아주잖아 <br>]]></content><category term="BOP" label="BOP"/><category term="물생활사랑" label="물생활사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/워십무브먼트/로마로_가는_길_Feat_이재영＆김찬양/</id><title>워십무브먼트 - 로마로 가는 길 (Feat. 이재영＆김찬양) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:37:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:37:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD%EB%AC%B4%EB%B8%8C%EB%A8%BC%ED%8A%B8/%EB%A1%9C%EB%A7%88%EB%A1%9C_%EA%B0%80%EB%8A%94_%EA%B8%B8_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%EC%9E%AC%EC%98%81%EF%BC%86%EA%B9%80%EC%B0%AC%EC%96%91/" title="워십무브먼트 - 로마로 가는 길 (Feat. 이재영＆김찬양) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나의 달려갈 길과 <br>주 예수께 받은 사명으로 <br>주 은혜의 복음 증거하며 <br>나의 생명을 다하리라 <br>나의 달려갈 길과 <br>주 예수께 받은 사명으로 <br>주 은혜의 복음 증거하며 <br>나의 생명을 다하리라 <br>주님을 기뻐해 주님을 찬양해 <br>주님이 행하신 위대하신 일 <br>주님을 기뻐해 주님을 찬양해 <br>주님이 행하신 위대하신 일 <br>나의 달려갈 길과 <br>주 예수께 받은 사명으로 <br>주 은혜의 복음 증거하며 <br>나의 생명을 다하리라 <br>주님을 기뻐해 주님을 찬양해 <br>주님이 행하신 위대하신 일 <br>주님을 기뻐해 주님을 찬양해 <br>주님이 행하신 위대하신 일 <br>풍랑가운데 나를 지켜주시는 <br>주님의 은혜를 찬양해 <br>폭풍가운데 나를 보호하시는 <br>주님의 사랑을 찬양해 <br>풍랑가운데 나를 지켜주시는 <br>주님의 은혜를 찬양해 <br>폭풍가운데 나를 보호하시는 <br>주님의 사랑을 찬양해 <br>주님을 기뻐해 주님을 찬양해 <br>주님이 행하신 위대하신 일 <br>주님을 기뻐해 주님을 찬양해 <br>주님이 행하신 위대하신 일 <br>풍랑가운데 나를 지켜주시는 <br>주님의 은혜를 찬양해 <br>폭풍가운데 나를 보호하시는 <br>주님의 사랑을 찬양해 <br>풍랑가운데 나를 지켜주시는 <br>주님의 은혜를 찬양해 <br>폭풍가운데 나를 보호하시는 <br>주님의 사랑을 찬양해 <br>]]></content><category term="워십무브먼트" label="워십무브먼트"/><category term="로마로 가는 길 (Feat. 이재영＆김찬양)" label="로마로 가는 길 (Feat. 이재영＆김찬양)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/워십무브먼트/주의_그_사랑으로_Feat_홍의석/</id><title>워십무브먼트 - 주의 그 사랑으로 (Feat. 홍의석) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:37:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:37:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD%EB%AC%B4%EB%B8%8C%EB%A8%BC%ED%8A%B8/%EC%A3%BC%EC%9D%98_%EA%B7%B8_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9C%BC%EB%A1%9C_Feat_%ED%99%8D%EC%9D%98%EC%84%9D/" title="워십무브먼트 - 주의 그 사랑으로 (Feat. 홍의석) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[전능하신 왕 영원하신 주 <br>공의와 사랑으로 다스리시네 <br>주님의 마음 강물 같아서 <br>그 자비 그 은혜 넘쳐흐르네 <br>주의 그 사랑으로 <br>주의 그 사랑으로 <br>십자가에서 나를 구원한 <br>주의 그 사랑 <br>주의 그 사랑으로 <br>주의 그 사랑으로 <br>영원 영원히 함께하시는 <br>주의 그 사랑 <br>전능하신 왕 영원하신 주 <br>공의와 사랑으로 다스리시네 <br>주님의 마음 강물 같아서 <br>그 자비 그 은혜 넘쳐흐르네 <br>주의 그 사랑으로 <br>주의 그 사랑으로 <br>십자가에서 나를 구원한 <br>주의 그 사랑 <br>주의 그 사랑으로 <br>주의 그 사랑으로 <br>영원 영원히 함께하시는 <br>주의 그 사랑 <br>주의 그 사랑으로 <br>주의 그 사랑으로 <br>십자가에서 나를 구원한 <br>주의 그 사랑 <br>주의 그 사랑으로 <br>주의 그 사랑으로 <br>영원 영원히 함께하시는 <br>주의 그 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="워십무브먼트" label="워십무브먼트"/><category term="주의 그 사랑으로 (Feat. 홍의석)" label="주의 그 사랑으로 (Feat. 홍의석)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박광복/실화야/</id><title>박광복 - 실화야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:37:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:37:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EA%B4%91%EB%B3%B5/%EC%8B%A4%ED%99%94%EC%95%BC/" title="박광복 - 실화야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[향기로운 너의 입술에 <br>입맞춤 하고 싶은 날 <br>나의 주변엔 모든 사람들 <br>사랑을 하고 있는 세상 <br>기다린다고 너에게 말했을 때 <br>넌 미안하다 말했었지 <br>기다림 그게 너라서 <br>난 기다릴 수 있게 돼 <br>하루에 너보다 많은걸 <br>생각 한 적은 없으니까 <br>그런 내 맘에 피어난 <br>그 향기 어린 너의 향기 어린 <br>너를 닮은 꽃들이 피어나서 <br>그 아름다운 모습에 눈이 멀어 <br>다른 여자는 보이지가 않는 건 <br>너무 향기로운 사실 <br>향기로운 너의 입술에 <br>키스를 하고 싶은 날 <br>네가 좋아한 초코 브라우니에 <br>커피를 마시고 있는데 <br>한참을 먹다 보니까 알게 됐어 <br>넌 촉촉하고 부드러운걸 <br>달콤한걸 더 원한단 걸 <br>난 이제서야 알게 됐어 <br>하루에 너보다 많은걸 <br>생각 한 적은 없으니까 <br>나의 이야기는 모두 다 <br>내 실화니까 너의 얘기니까 <br>내 목소리를 지금 듣고 있다면 <br>꼭 돌아와 줄 거라고 믿고 있어 <br>너와 내가 다시 또 만나는 건 <br>너무 향기로운 사실 <br>너 아닌 다른 여자의 <br>향기는 너무 싫은걸 <br>나의 차가운 향수 향기가 <br>니 향기만을 찾고 있어 <br>하루에 너보다 많은걸 <br>생각 한 적은 없으니까 <br>그런 내 맘에 피어난 <br>그 향기 어린 너의 향기 어린 <br>너를 닮은 꽃들이 피어나서 <br>그 아름다운 모습에 눈이 멀어 <br>다른 여자는 보이지가 않는 건 <br>너무 향기로운 사실 <br>]]></content><category term="박광복" label="박광복"/><category term="실화야" label="실화야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/투스토리/요즘_그_녀석/</id><title>투스토리 - 요즘 그 녀석 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:37:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:37:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%88%AC%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EB%A6%AC/%EC%9A%94%EC%A6%98_%EA%B7%B8_%EB%85%80%EC%84%9D/" title="투스토리 - 요즘 그 녀석 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 그 녀석 <br>지금 그 녀석 <br>요즘 그 녀석 <br>지금 그 녀석 <br>열쇠를 잃어버렸네 <br>그냥 산책을 나온 것뿐인데 <br>열쇠를 잃어버렸네 <br>지갑도 전화기도 없는데 <br>어떻게 하나 <br>아무것도 할 수 없네 <br>어떻게 하나 <br>그 녀석 집이 제일 가까운데 <br>열쇠를 잃어버렸네 <br>그냥 집 앞을 나온 것 뿐인데 <br>열쇠를 잃어버렸네 <br>날은 점점 어두워지는데 <br>요즘 그 녀석 연애한다는데 <br>지금 그 녀석 집에 있을까 <br>요즘 그 녀석 연애한다는데 <br>불만 켜져 있는지 확인만 해볼까 <br>요즘 그 녀석 <br>지금 그 녀석 <br>요즘 그 녀석 <br>지금 그 녀석 <br>요즘 그 녀석 연애한다는데 <br>지금 그 녀석 혼자 있을까 <br>요즘 그 녀석 연애한다는데 <br>낯선 사람이 문 열어 주는 건 아닐까 <br>요즘 그 녀석 <br>지금 그 녀석 <br>요즘 그 녀석 <br>지금 그 녀석 <br>요즘 그 녀석 <br>]]></content><category term="투스토리" label="투스토리"/><category term="요즘 그 녀석" label="요즘 그 녀석"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jaden_Smith/Batman/</id><title>Jaden_Smith - Batman - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:38:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:38:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jaden_Smith/Batman/" title="Jaden_Smith - Batman - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro] <br>Yeah, yeah! <br><br>[Verse 1] <br>Batman, Batman, Batman <br>Joker just put me on acid <br>Huh, you on the wave like a Maverick <br>You need to make something happen <br>Batman, Batman, Batman <br>Please put me on new fashion <br>Huh, I ain't learn nothing since last year <br>You got the renegade fabrics <br>Batman, Batman, Batman <br>Please put me up on a Tesla (skrrt!) <br>I'm tryna be hella extra <br>Please hand-me-down a new sweatshirt <br>Batman, Batman, Batman <br>Heard that you ain't got a mattress <br>Heard that you king of Manhattan (Queens) <br>So why you stay in the 'Basas? <br>Batman, Batman, Batman <br>We need to settle the scores <br>Jokers they still want a war <br>Watch out, I'm closing the doors <br>Batman, Batman, Batman <br>I heard you married a Porsche <br>That shit is all in the past <br>Plus, we got very divorced <br>You ain't ready for the war <br>Skywalker with the Force <br>1, 2, 3, 4 D'artiste is making noise <br>In the suburbs with the boys <br>On a roll, no Royce <br>Had to save the day, every single way <br>We don't really got a choice <br>Batman, Batman, Batman <br>Please save the day from the demons <br>I was sipping, he was leaning <br>We drove right into a precinct <br><br><br>[Chorus] <br>Batman, Batman, Batman <br>Why you look flyer than hell? <br>Don't think the album will sell <br>But this shit might fly off the shelf <br>Batman, Batman, Batman <br>So fly that you mad at yourself <br>You the one who got the juice <br>City crying for your help <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>Shooting up on Skid Row <br>Out your window look and you could tell <br>Get it from under their spell <br>If I don't do it, then who else? <br>Need me to shoot up the signal <br>I'll be there to get the info <br>Skrrtin' through the residential (skrrt!) <br>I wish it wasn't plain and simple <br>Lemme pull up to the party <br>Need like 35 credentials <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Batman, Batman, Batman <br>Why you look flyer than hell? <br>Don't think the album will sell <br>But this shit might fly off the shelf <br>Batman, Batman, Batman <br>We need to settle the scores <br>Jokers they still want a war <br>Hold up, I'm closing the doors <br>Batman, Batman, Batman <br>So fly that you mad at yourself <br>You the one who got the juice <br>City crying for your help <br>Batman, Batman, Batman <br>That was not part of the deal <br>You was protecting the bank <br>And then you walked off with a mill']]></content><category term="Jaden Smith" label="Jaden Smith"/><category term="Batman" label="Batman"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/앙상블_뷰티풀_랑데부/사랑이_없으면_Feat_최재도__김지수/</id><title>앙상블_뷰티풀_랑데부 - 사랑이 없으면 (Feat. 최재도 &amp; 김지수) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:40:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:40:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%99%EC%83%81%EB%B8%94_%EB%B7%B0%ED%8B%B0%ED%92%80_%EB%9E%91%EB%8D%B0%EB%B6%80/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4_%EC%97%86%EC%9C%BC%EB%A9%B4_Feat_%EC%B5%9C%EC%9E%AC%EB%8F%84__%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%80%EC%88%98/" title="앙상블_뷰티풀_랑데부 - 사랑이 없으면 (Feat. 최재도 &amp; 김지수) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 사람의 방언과 <br>천사의 말을 한다 하여도 <br>사랑이 없으면 <br>나는 요란한 소리일 뿐 <br>내가 예언하는 능력과 <br>산을 옮길만한 믿음 가져도 <br>사랑이 없으면 나는 아무것도 아니요 <br>내가 내게 있는 모든 것으로 <br>내 몸을 불사를지라도 <br>사랑이 없으면 <br>내겐 아무 소용이 없네 <br>사랑은 오래 참고 사랑은 온유하며 <br>사랑은 시기하지 않으며 <br>사랑은 자만찮고 사랑은 교만찮고 <br>사랑은 무례하지 않으며 <br>사랑은 자기의 유익을 <br>구하지 않으며 <br>성내지 아니하며 <br>불의를 기뻐하지 않으며 <br>진리를 기뻐하며 <br>모든 것을 참으며 모든 것을 믿으며 <br>모든 것을 바라며 모든 것을 견디네 <br>사랑이 없으면 사랑이 없으면 <br>사랑이 없으면 <br>나는 아무 것도 아니라 <br>]]></content><category term="앙상블 뷰티풀 랑데부" label="앙상블 뷰티풀 랑데부"/><category term="사랑이 없으면 (Feat. 최재도 &amp; 김지수)" label="사랑이 없으면 (Feat. 최재도 &amp; 김지수)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/Waste/</id><title>Oh_Wonder - Waste - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:41:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:41:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/Waste/" title="Oh_Wonder - Waste - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a space in between <br>Like a grey evergreen <br>Where the hurt never meant <br>Starts to linger <br>On the pavement below <br>See a crack that I know <br>All the corners of you <br>All the bones that I knew <br>I said I would never come back <br>Screaming at the walls in jet black <br>Hurt until my words are out flat <br>Can I whisper it back? <br>What a waste, what a waste <br>What a waste to be so alone <br>A waste, what a waste <br>What a waste to be so alone <br>A waste, what a waste <br>What a waste to be so alone <br>There's a space in between <br>Like a grey evergreen <br>Where the hurt never mend <br>Starts to linger <br>On the pavement below <br>See a crack that I know <br>All the corners of you <br>All the bones that I knew <br>I said I would never come back <br>Screaming at the walls in jet black <br>Hurt until my words are out flat <br>Can I whisper it back? <br>I said I would never come back <br>Screaming at the walls in jet black <br>Hurt until my words are out flat <br>Can I whisper it back? <br>What a waste, what a waste <br>What a waste to be so alone <br>A waste, what a waste <br>What a waste to be so alone <br>A waste, what a waste <br>What a waste to be so alone <br>So alone, so alone <br>A waste, what a waste <br>What a waste to be so alone <br>A waste, what a waste <br>What a waste to be so alone <br>A waste, what a waste <br>What a waste to be so alone <br>A waste, what a waste <br>What a waste to be so alone <br>A waste, what a waste <br>What a waste to be so alone <br>A waste, what a waste <br>What a waste to be so alone <br>A waste, what a waste <br>What a waste to be so alone <br>A waste, what a waste <br>What a waste to be so alone <br>A waste, what a waste <br>What a waste to be so alone]]></content><category term="Oh Wonder" label="Oh Wonder"/><category term="Waste" label="Waste"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/Overgrown/</id><title>Oh_Wonder - Overgrown - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:41:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:41:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/Overgrown/" title="Oh_Wonder - Overgrown - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hanging on a silver string <br>All the love that we could’ve been <br>Summer fading out the spring <br>Feel the warmth underneath your wings <br>And I will never let you go <br>All the words you want to scream <br>Take my heart slowly out of me <br>Forever falling in a dream <br>All the love that we could’ve been <br>I never get high when you’re feeling low <br>I’m pulling down stars just to make you glow <br>It’s just the way you are when you’re overgrown <br>And in the middle of the night when you’re on your own <br>I’m chasing down light in the indigo <br>It’s just the way you are when you’re overgrown <br>And I will never let you go <br>And I will never let you go <br>Promise I will never run <br>Catching fire, let the light become <br>Shallow edges of the sun <br>Feel the heat, hold it in your lungs <br>Never could’ve loved you more <br>By your side in a quiet roar <br>This is what my hope is for <br>Watch you float when the water’s gone <br>I never get high when you’re feeling low <br>I’m pulling down stars just to make you glow <br>It’s just the way you are when you’re overgrown <br>And in the middle of the night when you’re on your own <br>I’m chasing down light in the indigo <br>It’s just the way you are when you’re overgrown <br>And I will never let you go <br>No I will never let you go <br>Did I, did I, did I do you wrong? <br>Did I, did I, did I do you right? <br>Did I, did I, did I, do you wrong? <br>Did I, did I, did I, did I, did I? <br>Did I, did I, did I do you wrong? <br>Did I, did I, did I do you right? <br>Did I, did I, did I, do you wrong? <br>Did I, did I, did I, did I, did I? <br>Did I, did I, did I do you wrong? <br>Did I, did I, did I do you right? <br>Did I, did I, did I, do you wrong? <br>Did I, did I, did I, did I, did I? <br>And I will never let you go <br>I never get high when you’re feeling low <br>I’m pulling down stars just to make you glow <br>It’s just the way you are when you’re overgrown <br>And in the middle of the night when you’re on your own <br>I’m chasing down light in the indigo <br>It’s just the way you are when you’re overgrown <br>And I will never let you go <br>And I will never let you go <br>And I will never let you]]></content><category term="Oh Wonder" label="Oh Wonder"/><category term="Overgrown" label="Overgrown"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/Slip_Away/</id><title>Oh_Wonder - Slip Away - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:41:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:41:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/Slip_Away/" title="Oh_Wonder - Slip Away - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I sleep away all the light <br>I keep away, out of sight, out of sight <br>And when the day turns to night <br>I slip away and lose my mind, lose my mind <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh, how I tried <br>And as we lie silently <br>Your body soft, so close to me, close to me <br>I creep away and let you sleep <br>I dream today, tomorrow speaks <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh, how I tried <br>And as the sun comes out to play <br>So soon I wish the day away, day away <br>Still left unsaid, the things to say <br>I lost my heart to window panes <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh, how I tried <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh, how I tried <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh, how I tried <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh, how I tried <br>And my, my, my <br>My, my, my <br>Oh, how I tried <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh, how I tried <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh, how I tried <br>Oh, how I tried <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh, how I tried <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh, how I tried <br>Oh, how I tried <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh, how I tried <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh, how I tried <br>Oh my, my, my <br>Oh, how I tried]]></content><category term="Oh Wonder" label="Oh Wonder"/><category term="Slip Away" label="Slip Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/Heart_Strings/</id><title>Oh_Wonder - Heart Strings - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:41:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:41:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/Heart_Strings/" title="Oh_Wonder - Heart Strings - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Like two satellites in separate orbit <br>Like a quiet life that's slowly distorted <br>I was so lonely in love <br>I guess I was never enough <br>Like two chemicals erupting in thunder <br>Up high in vertigo, you left me to wonder <br>I was so lonely in love <br>I guess I was never enough <br>'Cause you were the best thing for me <br>Stole my mind and found my dreams <br>Baby, if only you could see heartstrings, heartstrings <br>Heartstrings, heartstrings <br>Best thing for me <br>Open the doors and set me free <br>Baby, if only you could see heartstrings, heartstrings <br>Heartstrings, heartstrings <br>Like two radios, our frequency fading <br>Why can't we start again without tessellating <br>I was so lonely in love <br>I guess I was never enough <br>Like the afterglow, your words were a million <br>Cut short, now heaven knows a love without feeling <br>I was so lonely in love <br>I guess I was never enough <br>'Cause you were the best thing for me <br>Stole my mind and found my dreams <br>Baby, if only you could see heartstrings, heartstrings <br>Heartstrings, heartstrings <br>Best thing for me <br>Open the doors and set me free <br>Baby, if only you could see heartstrings, heartstrings <br>Heartstrings, heartstrings <br>Stop pulling my heartstrings, my heartstrings <br>You got a grip on my heartstrings and I don't wanna take it no more <br>Stop pulling my heartstrings, my heartstrings <br>You got a grip on my heartstrings and I don't wanna take it no more <br>'Cause you were the best thing for me <br>Stole my mind and found my dreams <br>Baby, if only you could see heartstrings, heartstrings <br>Heartstrings, heartstrings <br>Best thing for me <br>Open the doors and set me free <br>Baby, if only you could see heartstrings, heartstrings <br>Heartstrings, heartstrings <br>Baby, if only you could see heartstrings, heartstrings <br>Heartstrings, heartstrings]]></content><category term="Oh Wonder" label="Oh Wonder"/><category term="Heart Strings" label="Heart Strings"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/Bigger_Than_Love/</id><title>Oh_Wonder - Bigger Than Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:41:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:41:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/Bigger_Than_Love/" title="Oh_Wonder - Bigger Than Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Heading west to where the sun sleeps <br>City fallout let our lungs breathe <br>Can you hold me, I can't even speak <br>Oh my, here it goes <br>And so the echoes slip in slowly <br>The edges of you keep me holy <br>Can I hold you, I can't even speak <br>Oh my, here it goes <br>We found love on an empty page <br>Kill the stars above trying to fight the fade <br>And now my heart skips heavy underneath the waves <br>We are done, we are gone <br>'Cause this is already bigger <br>This is already bigger than love <br>This is already bigger <br>This is already bigger than us <br>It's bigger than you <br>It's bigger than me <br>It's bigger than you <br>It's bigger than me <br>It's bigger than love <br>Waste away into the nightfall <br>Hands are shaking at the last call <br>In the silence can you hear me scream <br>Oh my, here it goes <br>We found love on an empty page <br>Kill the stars above trying to fight the fade <br>And now my heart skips heavy underneath the waves <br>We are done, we are gone <br>'Cause this is already bigger <br>This is already bigger than love <br>This is already bigger <br>This is already bigger than us <br>It's bigger than you <br>It's bigger than me <br>It's bigger than you <br>It's bigger than me <br>It's bigger than love <br>So I'll hold steady like a tiger in the dark <br>All my days are ready to be hopeless at the stars <br>'Cause this is already bigger than it oh <br>Oh it's bigger than us <br>Yeah, this is already bigger <br>This is already bigger than love <br>This is already bigger <br>This is already bigger than us <br>It's bigger than you <br>It's bigger than me <br>It's bigger than you <br>It's bigger than me <br>It's bigger than love]]></content><category term="Oh Wonder" label="Oh Wonder"/><category term="Bigger Than Love" label="Bigger Than Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/All_About_You/</id><title>Oh_Wonder - All About You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:41:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:41:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/All_About_You/" title="Oh_Wonder - All About You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You walk around the town <br>like you born in a golden crown <br>You're speaking with the angels loud <br>but no one understands ya <br>You got the sharpest bite as <br>any killer sharker might <br>And you control the water like the <br>desert doesn't matter <br>You're so full of it <br>And we're so sick of it <br>You're so full of it <br>And we're so sick of it <br>'Cause it's all about you <br>It's all about you <br>It's all about you <br>It's all about you <br>You say it's not enough <br>you're sipping from a silver cup <br>But is that how she brought you up <br>to blame the hand that feeds ya? <br>You counting green at night <br>but blessings you will never find <br>You only seek to undermine <br>you only seek to never die <br>You're so full of it <br>And we're so sick of it <br>You're so full of it <br>And we're so sick of it <br>'Cause it's all about you <br>It's all about you <br>It's all about you <br>It's all about you <br>And every time you get stars in your eyes <br>And the planets align in the centre <br>Pushing on out 'til the walls are all wide <br>And you're out of your mind in the centre <br>We see your cover, we see another <br>Fooling yourself in the mirror <br>Where is your heart? Where is the truth? <br>When it's all about you <br>It's not about you <br>It's not about you <br>It's not about you <br>You're so full of it <br>And we're so sick of it <br>You so full of it <br>And we so sick of it all <br>'Cause it's all about you <br>It's all about you <br>It's all about you <br>It's not about you]]></content><category term="Oh Wonder" label="Oh Wonder"/><category term="All About You" label="All About You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/Lifetimes/</id><title>Oh_Wonder - Lifetimes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:41:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:41:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/Lifetimes/" title="Oh_Wonder - Lifetimes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA['Cause I found love in you <br>Doing it right, doing it right <br>I'll walk the world for you <br>Doing it right, doing it right <br>Seconds, minutes, hours, lifetimes <br>Doing it right, doing it right <br>I found love in you <br>Doing it right, doing it right <br>Hands up for a miracle <br>Up high for a miracle <br>Oh the smoke don’t stop but we let it go <br>But we let it go on and on <br>Flash back to a year ago <br>Count stacks, fifty-two ago <br>All the hope, drop down like a domino <br>But we let it go on and on <br>Will someone take a ride with me? <br>Back to the world where we can see <br>Echo strong, river deep <br>Concrete hazy <br>Won’t you take a ride with me? <br>Take a ride with me <br>It’s easy come never go <br>Please make way for telephones <br>Call me crazy, call me slow <br>Go hang up but <br>Won’t you take a ride with me? <br>Come on take a ride with me <br>'Cause I found love in you <br>Doing it right, doing it right <br>I’ll walk the world for you <br>Doing it right, doing it right <br>Seconds, minutes, hours, lifetimes <br>Doing it right, doing it right <br>I found love in you <br>Doing it right, doing it right <br>Hands up for a miracle <br>Up high for a miracle <br>Oh the smoke don’t stop but we let it go <br>But we let it go on and on <br>Flash back to a year ago <br>Count stacks, fifty-two ago <br>All the hope, drop down like a domino <br>But we let it go on and on <br>Will someone take a ride with me? <br>Back to the planet sanity <br>Desert plain, ocean wave <br>Techno crazy <br>Won’t you take a ride with me? <br>Take a ride with me <br>It’s easy come, never go <br>Please make way for climaphobes <br>Two degrees, you’re spilling seas <br>Toupee queen <br>Oh, won’t you take a ride with me? <br>Come on take a ride with me <br>Swing sweet light this earth of mine <br>'Cause I found love in you <br>Doing it right, doing it right <br>I’ll walk the world for you <br>Doing it right, doing it right <br>Seconds, minutes, hours, lifetimes <br>Doing it right, doing it right <br>I found love in you <br>Doing it right, doing it right <br>Swing sweet light this earth of mine]]></content><category term="Oh Wonder" label="Oh Wonder"/><category term="Lifetimes" label="Lifetimes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/Solo/</id><title>Oh_Wonder - Solo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:41:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:41:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Oh_Wonder/Solo/" title="Oh_Wonder - Solo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A room filled up with faces and <br>the air so thick I taste it <br>Locking lips like they all wasted <br>tangled hips like it's a spaceship <br>Heavy heads are racing down the <br>hallways to the basement <br>Where the darkness fills the space and <br>they can feel themselves erasing <br>Can you feel yourself erasing? <br>They're bursting at the corners as <br>the ceiling's getting shorter <br>And I'm stuck between a talker and <br>a VHS recorder <br>The heat seeps through the border as <br>our ice melts down to water <br>Can you feel it getting smaller? <br>I need to be solo <br>Freedom in the mono <br>Find a space and let go <br>I need to be solo, solo <br>Now I'm breathing in and I'm breathing out <br>Breathing in and I'm breathing out <br>I'm breathing in and I'm breathing out <br>Breathing in and I'm breathing out <br>Their mouths are dripping dryer as <br>their souls are slipping higher <br>It's like treading on a wire laced <br>with kerosene and fire <br>The night will soon expire as <br>their bodies soon retire <br>Limbs entangled in kaleidoscopes <br>of prima donna choirs <br>Ahh, ahh, ahh, ohh, ohh, ohh, ohh <br>I need to be solo <br>Freedom in the mono <br>Find a space and let go <br>I need to be solo, solo <br>Now I'm breathing in <br>and I'm breathing out <br>Breathing in and I'm breathing out <br>I'm breathing in and I'm breathing out <br>Breathing in and I'm breathing out <br>I need to be solo <br>Breathing in and I'm breathing out <br>Freedom in the lie low <br>Breathing in and I'm breathing out <br>Find a space and let go <br>Breathing in and I'm breathing out <br>I need to be solo, solo <br>Breathing in and I'm breathing out <br>I need to be solo <br>Breathing in and I'm breathing out <br>Freedom in the lie low <br>Breathing in and I'm breathing out <br>Find a space and let go <br>Breathing in and I'm breathing out <br>I need to be solo, solo <br>Breathing in and I'm breathing out]]></content><category term="Oh Wonder" label="Oh Wonder"/><category term="Solo" label="Solo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Blu_Feat_Damon_Albarn/</id><title>Mura_Masa - Blu (Feat. Damon Albarn) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:41:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:41:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Blu_Feat_Damon_Albarn/" title="Mura_Masa - Blu (Feat. Damon Albarn) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You don't seem to understand me <br>when I say I'm feeling blu love <br>Blu love <br>When you touch me in that way <br>I just don't know what to do love <br>I'm so in love <br>I can't get you out my mind <br>You send me pictures <br>I ain't calling crisis <br>You send the pictures <br>You don't seem to understand me <br>when I say I'm feeling blu love <br>Blu love <br>When you touch me in that way <br>I just don't know what to do love <br>I'm so in love <br>If your harp is charged and loaded <br>Wait for time to come <br>It might take you to Rome <br>It's all about religion <br>It's all about constructing <br>the chemical reliance on <br>You don't seem to understand me <br>when I say I'm feeling blu love <br>Blu love <br>When you touch me in that way <br>I just don't know what to do love <br>I'm so in love <br>]]></content><category term="Mura Masa" label="Mura Masa"/><category term="Blu (Feat. Damon Albarn)" label="Blu (Feat. Damon Albarn)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Who_Is_It_Gonna_B_Feat_A_K_Paul/</id><title>Mura_Masa - Who Is It Gonna B (Feat. A. K. Paul) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:41:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:41:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Who_Is_It_Gonna_B_Feat_A_K_Paul/" title="Mura_Masa - Who Is It Gonna B (Feat. A. K. Paul) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Babe, every day you deny me, love gets stronger <br>Maybe one day you'll hear me <br>See the way we're going <br>Don't you know you confuse me <br>Don't you know that you're breaking me down <br>Oh, yeah <br>One line is settled, baby, making you look at me <br>Tell me, who is it gonna be? <br>I'm thinking, should I put down the time? <br>Can see that you're the cautious kind <br>And I know that you're a wildcard warning me <br>Tell me, who is it gonna be, yeah <br>Ooh, don't know how you feel <br>Ooh, tell me how you feel <br>Ooh, don't know how you feel <br>Ooh, tell me how you feel <br>Babe, every step you take backwards, I get closer <br>Inner strength to hold back you <br>I need guidance and light <br>Don't you know you could lose me <br>Don't you know (don't you know) <br>That you're breaking us down, oh <br>One line is settled, baby, making you look at me <br>Tell me, who is it gonna be? <br>I'm thinking, should I put down the time? <br>Can see that you're the cautious kind <br>And I know that you're a wildcard warning me <br>Tell me, who is it gonna be, yeah <br>Ooh, don't know how you feel <br>Ooh, tell me how you feel <br>Ooh, don't know how you feel <br>Ooh, tell me how you feel <br>Ever since I craved the scene where I kissed you <br>I've been waiting in a crazy love <br>I need that special (you're safe with me) <br>Don't you know, you, breaking me down <br>Then you call, you wander on the frozen ground <br>Don't you know, you, testing me now <br>Don't you serve ghost (serve ghost), love me (love me) <br>(Do you love me, do you love me now?) <br>Wanna hurt me? <br>Don't you know, you, breaking me down <br>Then you call, you wander on the frozen ground <br>Don't you know, you, testing me now <br>Don't you serve ghost <br>(serve ghost), love me (love me) <br>(Do you love me, do you love me now?) <br>Wanna hurt me?]]></content><category term="Mura Masa" label="Mura Masa"/><category term="Who Is It Gonna B (Feat. A. K. Paul)" label="Who Is It Gonna B (Feat. A. K. Paul)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Second_2_None_Feat_Christine_And_The_Queens/</id><title>Mura_Masa - Second 2 None (Feat. Christine And The Queens) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:41:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:41:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Second_2_None_Feat_Christine_And_The_Queens/" title="Mura_Masa - Second 2 None (Feat. Christine And The Queens) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You broke my heart by stayin' <br>Under the Earth forsaken <br>They broke my heart by meanin' <br>All of the words <br>they said this evenin' <br>Outside the world is reachin' <br>None of me is engagin' <br>It broke my heart to see you <br>So tall and ready <br>in the early mornin' <br>And what do they think they've done <br>You'll never be second to them <br>you're second to none <br>And how can they think you've gone <br>You'll never be second to them <br>you're second to none <br>You said this world was fallin' <br>Feet on the ground then jumpin' <br>It used to live all through you <br>This sense of hope <br>remorse of belonging <br>Rockin' my head right to you <br>Hard workers are still lied to <br>My point sent back for your sake <br>I know there are more wishes to make <br>And what do they think they've done <br>You'll never be second to them <br>you're second to none <br>And how can they think you've gone <br>You'll never be second to them <br>you're second to none <br>You'll never be second to them <br>you're second to none <br>Second to them you're <br>You'll never be second to them <br>you're second to none <br>You'll never be second to them <br>you're second to none <br>]]></content><category term="Mura Masa" label="Mura Masa"/><category term="Second 2 None (Feat. Christine And The Queens)" label="Second 2 None (Feat. Christine And The Queens)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/NOTHING_ELSE_Feat_Jamie_Lidell/</id><title>Mura_Masa - NOTHING ELSE! (Feat. Jamie Lidell) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:41:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:41:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/NOTHING_ELSE_Feat_Jamie_Lidell/" title="Mura_Masa - NOTHING ELSE! (Feat. Jamie Lidell) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I used to live in magazines <br>Yeah, they had me dreaming of another world <br>Thought that all those shiny things <br>Might give a little meaning to my lonely world <br>Ooh, distractions <br>Needless to say, I was caught up <br>with them everyday <br>But you can take my shit, burn my clothes <br>I know this is it <br>Your love's more precious than gold <br>Your love's more precious than gold, gold <br>Your love's more precious <br>your love's more precious than gold <br>'Cause nothing else matters <br>Yeah, nothing else matters now I have you <br>Nothing else matters <br>Yeah, nothing else matters now I have you <br>I miss so many unrepeatable things <br>Living in my material world <br>Convinced myself time and <br>time again that I could win <br>Without giving anything of myself <br>Ooh, distractions <br>Needless to say, I was caught up <br>with them everyday <br>But you can take my shit, burn my clothes <br>I know this is it <br>Your love's more precious than gold <br>Your love's more precious than gold, gold <br>Gold, your love's more precious than gold, gold <br>Nothing else matters <br>Yeah, nothing else matters now I have you <br>Nothing else matters <br>Yeah, nothing else matters now I have you <br>I was caught up in the bling bling bling <br>But diamond candy, it don't mean a thing, no <br>'Cause nothing else matters <br>Yeah, nothing else matters now I have you <br>Could live it up in a mansion <br>Sleeping in a single bed <br>They used to get my attention <br>But now I choose you instead, instead]]></content><category term="Mura Masa" label="Mura Masa"/><category term="NOTHING ELSE! (Feat. Jamie Lidell)" label="NOTHING ELSE! (Feat. Jamie Lidell)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/give_me_The_ground/</id><title>Mura_Masa - give me The ground - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/give_me_The_ground/" title="Mura_Masa - give me The ground - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't try and fuck with my head <br>Don't try and make me feel a fool <br>Give me the ground to stand on <br>Play with me in the grass field I used to love <br>Struggle when I'm gone, that's all you deserve <br>My dear]]></content><category term="Mura Masa" label="Mura Masa"/><category term="give me The ground" label="give me The ground"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Messy_Love/</id><title>Mura_Masa - Messy Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Messy_Love/" title="Mura_Masa - Messy Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro] <br>'New Park Road' <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Take me, break me <br>Use me for your messy love <br>Steal me, beat me <br>Use me for your messy love <br>Chain me, break me <br>Use me for your messy love <br>Steal me, beat me <br>Use me for your messy love <br><br>[Verse] <br>Yeah, girl, I've always been a hard hitter <br>Deep convictions to the bone <br>I never wanted you to try me <br>But you refuse to take my note <br>Don't you think that we should be together? <br>Say our prayers to the same Gods <br>We know that we don't have forever <br>So tell me what it is you want <br>(Yeah) <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Take me, break me <br>Use me for your messy love <br>Steal me, beat me <br>Use me for your messy love <br><br>[Hook: Chopped Vocals] <br>Now, will, be my girl]]></content><category term="Mura Masa" label="Mura Masa"/><category term="Messy Love" label="Messy Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Vamps/Sad_Song/</id><title>The_Vamps - Sad Song - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Vamps/Sad_Song/" title="The_Vamps - Sad Song - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So many nights, so many days <br>To all of the fights, 'cause I never behave <br>And I'm putting it right, hope it isn't too late <br>And I know, you know, I know I can't let it end this way <br><br>Though I stopped calling you <br>And I stopped taking your messages <br>Never stopped loving you <br>And the one thing I regret is <br>I stopped calling you <br>And I stopped taking your messages <br>Never stopped loving you <br>You're still running through my head <br><br>So hold on, baby <br>Know you drive me crazy <br>It's a sad song really <br>She could make me happy, oh <br>Ain't always cool <br>But it's alright <br>It's not a sad song really <br>She used to make me happy <br>She used to make me happy <br>Missing nights, staying up late <br>Scratches and bites, screamin' my name <br>Is he loving you right, or am I too late? <br>'Cause I know, you know, I know I can't let it end this way <br><br>Though I stopped calling you <br>And I stopped taking your messages <br>Never stopped loving you <br>You're still running through my head <br><br>So hold on, baby <br>Know you drive me crazy <br>It's a sad song really <br>She could make me happy, oh <br>Ain't always cool <br>But it's alright <br>It's not a sad song really <br>She used to make me happy <br><br>She used to make me happy <br>She used to make me happy <br>Ain't always cool <br>But it's alright <br>It's not a sad song really <br>She could make me happy <br><br>Hold on, hold on <br>It's not a sad song, sad song, yeah <br>Hold on, hold on <br>It's not a sad song, sad song, baby <br><br>Hold on, hold on <br>It's not a sad song, sad song, yeah <br>Hold on, hold on <br>It's not a sad song, sad song, baby <br><br>So hold on, baby <br>Know you drive me crazy <br>It's a sad song really <br>She could make me happy, oh <br>Ain't always cool <br>But it's alright <br>It's not a sad song really <br>She used to make me happy <br><br>Hold on, hold on <br>It's not a sad song, sad song, yeah <br>Hold on, hold on <br>It's not a sad song, sad song, baby <br>Hold on, hold on <br>It's not a sad song, sad song, yeah <br>Hold on, hold on <br>She used to make me happy]]></content><category term="The Vamps" label="The Vamps"/><category term="Sad Song" label="Sad Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Vamps/Shades_On/</id><title>The_Vamps - Shades On - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Vamps/Shades_On/" title="The_Vamps - Shades On - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I got my shades on <br>Like I'm rocking Barbados <br>All night <br>To get you out my mind now, baby <br>Taking my jeans off <br>But I'm keeping my shades on <br>All night (all night) <br>To keep you out my sight now, baby <br>Picture perfect pictures <br>And I'm looking like I just got laid <br>Got the sunshine on my face <br>Starting up a party <br>On the pavement like I just got paid <br>And it's alright <br>I got my shades on <br>Like I'm rocking Barbados <br>All night <br>And everybody thinks I'm high <br>Taking my jeans off <br>But I'm keeping my shades on <br>All night <br>And everybody's blind <br>'Cause I look so cool like this <br>And I feel so good like this <br>Got me feeling brand new like this <br>You know <br>'Cause I look so cool like this <br>And I feel so good like this <br>Got me feeling brand new like this <br>You know <br>Let's talk about that face <br>He got the big blue eyes and all that bass <br>Oh father, let me pray <br>'Cause I won't see another woman like this for a day <br>I'm like "Oh boy, look at that ass" <br>"Oh boy, look at that ass" <br>Get your eyes up to my face <br>'Cause I see right through your shades <br>I got my shades on <br>Like I'm rocking Barbados <br>All night <br>And everybody thinks I'm high <br>Taking my jeans off <br>But I'm keeping my shades on <br>All night <br>And everybody's blind <br>'Cause I look so cool like this <br>And I feel so good like this <br>Got me feeling brand new like this <br>You know <br>'Cause I look so cool like this <br>And I feel so good like this <br>Got me feeling brand new like this <br>You know <br>I oh I oh oh I oh oh I <br>I got my shades on <br>I got my shades on all night <br>I got my shades on <br>Like I'm rocking Barbados all night <br>And everybody thinks I'm high <br>Taking my jeans off <br>But I'm keeping my shades on all night <br>And everybody's blind <br>'Cause I look so cool like this <br>And I feel so good like this <br>Got me feeling brand new like this <br>You know <br>'Cause I look so cool like this <br>And I feel so good like this <br>Got me feeling brand new like this <br>You know <br>Uh-oh]]></content><category term="The Vamps" label="The Vamps"/><category term="Shades On" label="Shades On"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Vamps/Paper_Hearts/</id><title>The_Vamps - Paper Hearts - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Vamps/Paper_Hearts/" title="The_Vamps - Paper Hearts - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a lot of things that I may not know <br>But missing you baby is the only thing I know <br>I know <br>And who am I to say what the future holds <br>But missing you baby is the only thing I know <br>I know <br><br>If my heart was paper, I'd fold it <br>Throw it to the wind and just hope it <br><br>Ends up with you <br>I'd sign it with love from me to you <br>I'd try to be cool <br>But my feelings, they don't allow me to <br>And all that I ask <br>Is that at least you write me back <br>I'm waiting <br>Here's my paper heart, won't you hold it <br>Hold it <br><br>Said you needed space so I gave you time <br>A year has gone by and I'm thinking you're still mine <br>In my mind <br><br>And I've written you this letter like a hundred times <br>To start a conversation that we should've had that night <br>I tried <br><br>If my heart was paper, I'd fold it <br>Throw it to the wind and just hope it <br><br>Ends up with you <br>I'd sign it with love from me to you <br>I'd try to be cool <br>But my feelings, they don't allow me to <br>And all that I ask <br>Is that at least you write me back <br>I'm waiting <br>Here's my paper heart, won't you hold it <br>Hold it <br><br>Flying through fields all the same <br>Hoping one day it will land <br>And end up with you <br><br>I'd sign it with love from me to you <br>I'd try to be cool <br>But my feelings, they don't allow me to <br>And all that I ask <br>Is that at least you write me back <br>I'm waiting <br>Here's my paper heart, won't you hold it <br><br>Ends up with you <br>I'd sign it with love from me to you <br>I'd try to be cool <br>But my feelings, they don't allow me to <br>And all that I ask <br>Is that at least you write me back <br>I'm waiting <br>Here's my paper heart, won't you hold it <br>Hold it <br><br>Hold it, hold it <br><br>There's a lot of things that I may not know <br>But missing you baby is the only thing I know <br>I know]]></content><category term="The Vamps" label="The Vamps"/><category term="Paper Hearts" label="Paper Hearts"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mike_Perry/Hands_Feat_The_Vamps__Sabrina_Carpenter/</id><title>Mike_Perry - Hands (Feat. The Vamps &amp; Sabrina Carpenter) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mike_Perry/Hands_Feat_The_Vamps__Sabrina_Carpenter/" title="Mike_Perry - Hands (Feat. The Vamps &amp; Sabrina Carpenter) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come on lay your hands your hands on me <br>We don't have to talk 'cause talk is cheap <br>In the dark silence so loud <br>You only gotta lay your hands on me <br><br>You say you're better with <br>Hands yeah yeah yeah <br>Hands yeah yeah yeah <br>You say you're better with <br>Hands yeah yeah yeah <br>Hands yeah yeah yeah <br><br>I've been thinking about it <br>I've been thinking all night <br>Every time I try to learn your body language <br>Never get it right <br>You're so hard to read baby <br>So I turn off the light <br>And you just drop that dress to the floor <br>We can talk until sunrise <br>I've been thinking about it <br>The way that you blow my mind <br>I've been thinking about it all night <br><br>Come on lay your hands your hands on me <br>We don't have to talk 'cause talk is cheap <br>In the dark silence so loud <br>You only gotta lay your hands on me <br><br>You say you're better with <br>Hands yeah yeah yeah <br>Hands yeah yeah yeah <br>You say you're better with <br>Hands yeah yeah yeah <br>Hands yeah yeah yeah <br><br>Don't tell me about it <br>Keep on blowing my mind <br>'Cause your lips are made for kissing baby <br>So I put them on mine <br>No conversation <br>I've heard every line <br>So leave your shit at the door <br><br>Come on lay your hands your hands on me <br>We don't have to talk <br>Cause talk is cheap <br>In the dark silence so loud <br>You only gotta lay your hands on me <br><br>You say you're better with <br>Hands yeah yeah yeah <br>Hands yeah yeah yeah <br>You say you're better with <br>Hands yeah yeah yeah <br>Hands yeah yeah yeah]]></content><category term="Mike Perry" label="Mike Perry"/><category term="Hands (Feat. The Vamps &amp; Sabrina Carpenter)" label="Hands (Feat. The Vamps &amp; Sabrina Carpenter)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마인드유_어쿠루브舊/사랑노래_같은_이별노래_Inst/</id><title>마인드유_어쿠루브舊 - 사랑노래 같은 이별노래 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B8%EB%93%9C%EC%9C%A0_%EC%96%B4%EC%BF%A0%EB%A3%A8%EB%B8%8C%E8%88%8A/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98_%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98_Inst/" title="마인드유_어쿠루브舊 - 사랑노래 같은 이별노래 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리가 마지막일 때 난 그때 <br>널 마지막으로 안았지 <br>어색한 대화를 계속 나눌 땐 <br>이별을 예상했었지 <br>아침에 눈을 뜨고 못 일어나 <br>우우우 우우우 <br>사실 좀 힘들어 너는 어떠니 <br>우우우 우우우 <br>난 아직 너를 사랑해 <br>널 많이 사랑해 <br>나는 여기 그대로 서 있는데 <br>사랑한다 말하는 걸 아꼈었는데 <br>니가 이제 없다 난 고장이 났다 <br>모든게 끝이 났을 때 난 그때 <br>오히려 담담했었지 <br>집으로 돌아오던 길 집 앞에 <br>한참을 서성거렸지 <br>눈물이 흐르고 몸이 떨려와 <br>우우우 우우우 <br>정말 끝이란 걸 그때 알았어 <br>우우우 우우우 <br>난 아직 너를 사랑해 <br>널 많이 사랑해 <br>나는 여기 그대로 서 있는데 <br>사랑한다 말하는 걸 아꼈었는데 <br>니가 이제 없다 난 고장이 났다 <br>너 떠난 뒤로 난 더 웃는 척하고 <br>친구들 만나서 난 괜찮은 척을 했어 <br>이래야 살 것만 같아 <br>나 살고 싶어서 죽을 것 같아서 <br>난 니가 너무 그리워 <br>정말 그리워 <br>아직 너를 사랑하는 것 같아 <br>난 아직 너를 사랑해 <br>널 많이 사랑해 <br>나는 여기 그대로 서 있는데 <br>사랑한다 말하는 걸 아꼈었는데 <br>니가 이제 없다 난 고장이 났다 <br>난 아직 너를 사랑해 <br>널 많이 사랑해 <br>나는 여기 그대로 서 있는데 <br>사랑한다 말하는 걸 아꼈었는데 <br>니가 이제 없다 난 고장이 났다 <br>]]></content><category term="마인드유 (어쿠루브舊)" label="마인드유 (어쿠루브舊)"/><category term="사랑노래 같은 이별노래 (Inst.)" label="사랑노래 같은 이별노래 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마인드유_어쿠루브舊/잡지_않았어/</id><title>마인드유_어쿠루브舊 - 잡지 않았어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B8%EB%93%9C%EC%9C%A0_%EC%96%B4%EC%BF%A0%EB%A3%A8%EB%B8%8C%E8%88%8A/%EC%9E%A1%EC%A7%80_%EC%95%8A%EC%95%98%EC%96%B4/" title="마인드유_어쿠루브舊 - 잡지 않았어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언제부턴가 얘기 나눌 때 <br>재미없다는 표정을 짓던 너 <br>그래 난 알고 있었어 <br>우리 어느 날 함께 들었던 <br>우리 얘기 같던 노래 가사가 <br>이제는 남 얘기가 됐어 <br>널 보며 웃어도 보고 <br>울어도 보고 매달리기도 했어 <br>애써 널 지우려 해도 덮으려 해도 <br>자꾸 생각나는데 <br>잡지 않았어 널 그때는 몰랐어 <br>이렇게 아플 줄은 <br>이제야 알았어 <br>니가 없는 나의 모습이 이래 <br>같이 걸었던 그 길을 지날 땐 <br>혹시라도 너와 마주칠까 봐 <br>괜히 둘러보곤 해 <br>하고 싶은 말 아껴뒀던 말 <br>이제는 전부 다 소용이 없어 이제 <br>잡지 않았어 널 그때는 몰랐어 <br>이렇게 아플 줄은 <br>이제야 알았어 <br>니가 없는 나의 모습이 이래 <br>이제 너는 없고 혼자 남아서 <br>너와 함께 웃던 사진들을 봐 <br>가끔 뜬금없이 니가 꿈속에 <br>잘 견뎌 왔는데 <br>잡지 않았어 널 그때는 몰랐어 <br>이렇게 아플 줄은 <br>이제야 알았어 <br>니가 없는 나의 모습이 이래 <br>]]></content><category term="마인드유 (어쿠루브舊)" label="마인드유 (어쿠루브舊)"/><category term="잡지 않았어" label="잡지 않았어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마인드유_어쿠루브舊/그게_뭐라고/</id><title>마인드유_어쿠루브舊 - 그게 뭐라고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B8%EB%93%9C%EC%9C%A0_%EC%96%B4%EC%BF%A0%EB%A3%A8%EB%B8%8C%E8%88%8A/%EA%B7%B8%EA%B2%8C_%EB%AD%90%EB%9D%BC%EA%B3%A0/" title="마인드유_어쿠루브舊 - 그게 뭐라고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너의 소식을 듣고 난 멍하니 있어 <br>하루 온종일 널 생각 하나 봐 <br>일도 잘 안 잡히고 집중이 안 돼 <br>괜찮았는데 요즘 따라 <br>니가 생각나 이맘때쯤에 <br>웃고 있던 너와 내가 생각 나는데 <br>니 무릎을 베고 하늘을 보며 <br>먼 훗날 우리 얘길 했는데 <br>사랑한다고 <br>내 귓가에 말해주던 <br>너의 목소리 <br>그게 뭐라고 또 생각나 <br>하나 둘씩 떠오르지 <br>함께한 추억들이 그리워지네 <br>난 다짐을 했었지 너의 근황들을 <br>안 보고 지내고 싶었는데 <br>그게 말처럼 안 돼 <br>나 혼자 아픈 건가 봐 <br>넌 잘 지내나 봐 <br>저녁이 오면 사람들 속에 <br>우리도 섞여 걸었었지 손을 잡고서 <br>하지만 이제 네가 없어서 <br>너무 외로워 <br>사랑한다고 <br>내 귓가에 말해주던 <br>너의 목소리 <br>그게 뭐라고 또 생각나 <br>하나 둘씩 떠오르지 <br>함께한 추억들이 그리워지네 <br>그 누군가 내게 말을 했지 <br>세월이 곧 약일 꺼라고 <br>널 많이 사랑했나 봐 그랬나 봐 <br>이젠 잊을 때도 됐는데 <br>사랑한다고 좋아한다고 <br>매일 같이 말해주던 <br>네 목소리 잊지 못하고 <br>하나 둘씩 떠오르지 <br>함께 한 추억들이 <br>그리워지네 <br>]]></content><category term="마인드유 (어쿠루브舊)" label="마인드유 (어쿠루브舊)"/><category term="그게 뭐라고" label="그게 뭐라고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마인드유_어쿠루브舊/사랑노래_같은_이별노래_Feat_소정_of_레이디스_코드/</id><title>마인드유_어쿠루브舊 - 사랑노래 같은 이별노래 (Feat. 소정 of 레이디스 코드) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B8%EB%93%9C%EC%9C%A0_%EC%96%B4%EC%BF%A0%EB%A3%A8%EB%B8%8C%E8%88%8A/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98_%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98_Feat_%EC%86%8C%EC%A0%95_of_%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4_%EC%BD%94%EB%93%9C/" title="마인드유_어쿠루브舊 - 사랑노래 같은 이별노래 (Feat. 소정 of 레이디스 코드) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리가 마지막일 때 난 그때 <br>널 마지막으로 안았지 <br>어색한 대화를 계속 나눌 땐 <br>이별을 예상했었지 <br>아침에 눈을 뜨고 못 일어나 <br>우우우 우우우 <br>사실 좀 힘들어 너는 어떠니 <br>우우우 우우우 <br>난 아직 너를 사랑해 <br>널 많이 사랑해 <br>나는 여기 그대로 서 있는데 <br>사랑한다 말하는 걸 아꼈었는데 <br>니가 이제 없다 난 고장이 났다 <br>모든게 끝이 났을 때 난 그때 <br>오히려 담담했었지 <br>집으로 돌아오던 길 집 앞에 <br>한참을 서성거렸지 <br>눈물이 흐르고 몸이 떨려와 <br>우우우 우우우 <br>정말 끝이란 걸 그때 알았어 <br>우우우 우우우 <br>난 아직 너를 사랑해 <br>널 많이 사랑해 <br>나는 여기 그대로 서 있는데 <br>사랑한다 말하는 걸 아꼈었는데 <br>니가 이제 없다 난 고장이 났다 <br>너 떠난 뒤로 난 더 웃는 척하고 <br>친구들 만나서 난 괜찮은 척을 했어 <br>이래야 살 것만 같아 <br>나 살고 싶어서 죽을 것 같아서 <br>난 니가 너무 그리워 <br>정말 그리워 <br>아직 너를 사랑하는 것 같아 <br>난 아직 너를 사랑해 <br>널 많이 사랑해 <br>나는 여기 그대로 서 있는데 <br>사랑한다 말하는 걸 아꼈었는데 <br>니가 이제 없다 난 고장이 났다 <br>난 아직 너를 사랑해 <br>널 많이 사랑해 <br>나는 여기 그대로 서 있는데 <br>사랑한다 말하는 걸 아꼈었는데 <br>니가 이제 없다 난 고장이 났다 <br>]]></content><category term="마인드유 (어쿠루브舊)" label="마인드유 (어쿠루브舊)"/><category term="사랑노래 같은 이별노래 (Feat. 소정 of 레이디스 코드)" label="사랑노래 같은 이별노래 (Feat. 소정 of 레이디스 코드)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마인드유_어쿠루브舊/사랑해줘요/</id><title>마인드유_어쿠루브舊 - 사랑해줘요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B8%EB%93%9C%EC%9C%A0_%EC%96%B4%EC%BF%A0%EB%A3%A8%EB%B8%8C%E8%88%8A/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4%EC%A4%98%EC%9A%94/" title="마인드유_어쿠루브舊 - 사랑해줘요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어디로 가고 있나요 <br>어디쯤 그대 있나요 <br>시간이 가면 갈수록 <br>더 조급해지는 걸요 <br>그대 이름을 모래에 <br>선명히 새겨 놓아도 <br>파도에 지워져요 <br>어디 있나요 <br>그대 마음이 <br>나에게로 살며시 앉길 <br>그댈 믿어요 <br>좋아해요 다 <br>평화로운 오후 길에 <br>두리번 돌아다녀도 <br>그대는 이곳에 없어 <br>이어폰에는 달달한 노랫말 <br>친구들의 자랑들도 <br>밉다가도 부러워져 <br>그대는 어디 있나요 <br>궁금해 <br>어디 있나요 <br>그대 마음이 <br>나에게로 살며시 앉길 <br>그댈 믿어요 <br>좋아해요 다 <br>사랑해줘요 <br>나의 마음이 <br>그대에게 날아가기를 <br>매일 그대를 <br>사랑해요 다 <br>]]></content><category term="마인드유 (어쿠루브舊)" label="마인드유 (어쿠루브舊)"/><category term="사랑해줘요" label="사랑해줘요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lana_Del_Rey/Groupie_Love_Feat_AAP_ROCKY/</id><title>Lana_Del_Rey - Groupie Love (Feat. A$AP ROCKY) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lana_Del_Rey/Groupie_Love_Feat_AAP_ROCKY/" title="Lana_Del_Rey - Groupie Love (Feat. A$AP ROCKY) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're in the bar playing guitar <br>I'm trying not to <br>let the crowd next to me <br>It's so hard sometimes with the star <br>When you have to share him <br>with everybody <br>You're in the club living it up <br>I'm trying not to <br>let the crowd notice me <br>It's so sweet swingin' to the beat <br>When I know that you're doing <br>it all for me <br>And every time you look up <br>I know what you're thinking of <br>I know what you're thinking of <br>You want my <br>Groupie love <br>Groupie love <br>Groupie love <br>Time after time writing my lines <br>Having my baby there next to me <br>It's so sweet pouring you a drink <br>And pretending that nothing <br>means anything <br>This is my life you by my side <br>Key lime and perfume and festivals <br>Taking our dreams <br>turning them to things <br>It's like magic babe <br>isn't life wonderful <br>And every time we hook up <br>I know what you're thinking of <br>I know what you're thinking of <br>You want my <br>Groupie love <br>Groupie love <br>Groupie love <br>Front row every show <br>like a hype man hmm <br>Sing along word for word <br>while she my bae yeah <br>Side stage fans <br>screamin' causin' migraines <br>Yamborghini-high <br>but she ain't on my grade <br>hmm hmm <br>God dang got a nigga acting irate <br>hmm hmm <br>My babe my babe <br>stay on my brain yeah <br>My babe made me sing to a fire escape <br>City girl but she grew up <br>in the tri-state <br>She ain't got no time <br>for no groupie love hmm <br>We don't pay no minds <br>to the thug with a hmm <br>Love girls you and I <br>so who do we trust <br>You and I 'til the day we die <br>Groupie love <br>Groupie love <br>Groupie love <br>You are my babe <br>Groupie love <br>Groupie love <br>Groupie love <br>Groupie love <br>]]></content><category term="Lana Del Rey" label="Lana Del Rey"/><category term="Groupie Love (Feat. A$AP ROCKY)" label="Groupie Love (Feat. A$AP ROCKY)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lana_Del_Rey/Summer_Bummer_Feat_AAP_ROCKY__Playboi_Carti/</id><title>Lana_Del_Rey - Summer Bummer (Feat. A$AP ROCKY &amp; Playboi Carti) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lana_Del_Rey/Summer_Bummer_Feat_AAP_ROCKY__Playboi_Carti/" title="Lana_Del_Rey - Summer Bummer (Feat. A$AP ROCKY &amp; Playboi Carti) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Lana Del Rey:] <br>It's never too late <br>To be who you wanna be <br>To say what you wanna say <br>It's never too late <br>To leave if you wanna leave <br>Or to stay if you wanna stay <br>But, baby <br>I got a feeling in my bones <br>Can't get you out of my veins <br>You can't escape my affection <br>Wrap you up in my daisy chains <br><br>Hip-hop in the summer <br>Don't be a bummer, babe <br>Be my undercover lover, babe <br>High tops in the summer <br>Don't be a bummer, babe <br>Be my undercover lover, babe, mmm <br><br>[A$AP Rocky:] <br>Uh, her sophistication makes you wanna quit the bitch you datin' <br>Let's skip the games, let's quit the playin' <br>Boo, let's get acquainted <br>Notifications sync in place even when we're on vacation <br>I knew she'd notice like I missed the payment, dang it <br>But bang it like my fingers <br>She pray to God I made it <br>But bankin' like my Franklins <br>My neighbors stopped the hatin' <br>What? <br>Huh? <br>Slide inside it <br>Diddy Boppin' <br>Milly Rockin' <br>She just might become my lover for real <br>I might fuck with her all summer for real <br>They better not holla if I cuff her for real <br>Niggas better run for cover for real <br>Goin' bell how I feel, close the deal, pop a seal <br>Take the whip, two pills on the lips on the real <br>Truthfully between you and me I'm usually single <br>When it's hot outside this, I ride through any hood with the top out <br>Hop out <br><br>[Lana Del Rey:] <br>Hip-hop in the summer <br>Don't be a bummer, babe <br>Be my undercover lover, babe <br>High tops in the summer <br>Don't be a bummer, babe <br>Be my undercover lover, babe, mmm <br><br>White lights and black beaches <br>Miles in between us <br>Is this love or lust or some game on repeat? <br>It's like making me crazy <br>Tell me, "have patience" <br>Baby, I need this <br>White lines and black beaches <br>White lights and black beaches <br>And blood red sangrias <br>We traveled for weeks <br>Just to escape your demons <br>But you've got your reasons <br>In making me crazy <br>But you've got your reasons <br>White lights and black beaches <br><br>Like doves in the summer <br>Don't be a bummer, babe <br>Don't be a bummer <br>Don't be a bummer <br><br>Hip-hop in the summer <br>Don't be a bummer, babe <br>Be my undercover lover, babe <br>High tops in the summer <br>Don't be a bummer, babe <br>Be my undercover lover, babe <br>Don't be a bummer, babe]]></content><category term="Lana Del Rey" label="Lana Del Rey"/><category term="Summer Bummer (Feat. A$AP ROCKY &amp; Playboi Carti)" label="Summer Bummer (Feat. A$AP ROCKY &amp; Playboi Carti)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제시_Jessi/Arrived/</id><title>제시_Jessi - Arrived - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%8B%9C_Jessi/Arrived/" title="제시_Jessi - Arrived - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tell em I've arrived yea <br>see them holding up <br>the sign yeah <br>Took forever and a day <br>They still comin at me side ways <br>I ain't never known a feeling <br>this good <br>Don't give me a reason <br>Bitch i wish you would <br>Being bad never looked <br>or felt better uh <br>Ya girls a rebel never <br>been the type to settle uh <br>I ain't playin games <br>only tryna level up <br>I'm here to regulate <br>never be regular <br>It's only the beginning <br>so you better slow your roll <br>Addicted to chanel <br>I'm in love wit the coco <br>Every rose has a thorn <br>bitch i'm rose gold <br>thought i'd be a no show <br>But i pulled up <br>tell em I arrived yea <br>Tell the valet bring my ride yea <br>feeling so alive yea <br>But the doors are suicide yea <br>Tell em I've arrived yea <br>see them holding up the sign yeah <br>Took forever and a day <br>They still comin at me side ways <br>I ain't never known a feeling <br>this good <br>Don't give me a reason <br>Bitch i wish you would <br>They want me to fail <br>Just got a check in the mail <br>Young girl checkin the males <br>Gimmie a second i'm feelin myself <br>God damn i'm feelin myself <br>i derseve a day off <br>Don't forget to smell <br>the flowers in the chaos <br>countin down on all days <br>i waited patiently <br>And all these years i never <br>let my haters get to me <br>Hol up <br>Don't question me <br>My destiny <br>I manifested <br>Count my blessings <br>Hold me down <br>you can count on jessi <br>Don't let em' blind you <br>Its hard to see who's fake or real <br>Let me remind you <br>I'm here to stay i came to kill <br>Now Who the fuck gon <br>gonna take it from me <br>I'm finally happy <br>i'm makin money <br>So when i pull up <br>Tell em I've arrived yea <br>see them holding up the sign yeah <br>Took forever and a day <br>They still comin at me side ways <br>I ain't never known a feeling <br>this good <br>Don't give me a reason <br>Bitch i wish you would <br>This journey is a lonely road <br>But when i look at who i do it for <br>for you <br>It's the beginning of <br>this rollercoaster <br>Ain't no sign of slowing <br>anytime soon <br>It's worth while It's worth while <br>To put a smile upon ur face <br>Brighten up your day <br>Hope you shine in every way <br>So when you walk into <br>that crowded room <br>Its All eyes on you <br>So live your life loud and <br>Tell em I've arrived yea <br>see them holding up the sign yeah <br>Took forever and a day <br>They still comin at me side ways <br>I ain't never known a feeling <br>this good <br>Don't give me a reason <br>Bitch i wish you would <br>Bitch i wish you would <br>Bitch i wish you would <br>Bitch i wish you would <br>Bitch i wish you would <br>]]></content><category term="제시 (Jessi)" label="제시 (Jessi)"/><category term="Arrived" label="Arrived"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제시_Jessi/Spirit_Animal/</id><title>제시_Jessi - Spirit Animal - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%8B%9C_Jessi/Spirit_Animal/" title="제시_Jessi - Spirit Animal - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Omg omg omg is that jessi <br>Omg yo i fucken love that bitch <br>like seriously <br>she's like my spirit animal <br>i'm all about the mula <br>earrings like a hula <br>jessi from the block <br>homie don’t believe the rumors <br>i treat you like my junior <br>the 오빠s call me 누나 <br>they starin at matatas <br>no worries hakuna <br>see me on running man <br>and takeover the show <br>pull up on show me the money <br>take your chain and your dough <br>before i showed up on tv <br>women aint know how to flow <br>i gave the country a makeover <br>bitches I’m in control <br>who you callin unpretty <br>ya girl run cities <br>they gave me second place <br>how am I still winning <br>Who u think u kidding <br>Im a lion you kitten <br>just saying what you thinkin <br>let me guide you baby girl like <br>1 Learn the game huh <br>2 Go and slay huh <br>Slay All my Down girls down <br>We going way up <br>If you want that unnie money <br>better save up <br>Love your haters let it motivate ya <br>Motivator motivator <br>love your haters let it motivate ya <br>Motivator motivator <br>go and get it girl <br>what are you afraid you <br>Killin all the male competition <br>I’m a widow <br>i got all the men <br>on a leash like a jindo <br>im a sex symbol <br>in a stretch limo <br>tiny little girl but the voice is <br>heavy metal <br>shout out to my jebbies <br>they hold me down heavy <br>always keep an eye out <br>for me like fetty <br>shout out to new jersey <br>they knew me mad early <br>i made it in the motherland <br>its been a long journey <br>Wait Me plastic <br>hmm I’m fantastic <br>my momma says I’m pretty <br>yo momma she a fan bitch <br>blonde hair tight body with a tan <br>Let me break it down for you <br>Help you understand <br>1 Learn the game huh <br>2 Go and slay huh <br>Slay All my Down girls huh <br>going way up <br>If you want that unnie money <br>better save up <br>Love your haters let it motivate ya <br>Motivator motivator <br>love your haters let it motivate ya <br>Motivator motivator <br>go and get it girl <br>what are you afraid you <br>Spirit animal <br>bitch I wrote the manual <br>Let me teach you <br>how to slay slay <br>Spirit animal <br>what you make in the annual <br>Bitch I make that in a day day <br>Watch 언니 dance on em <br>Watch 언니 dance on em <br>Watch 언니 dance on em <br>Watch 언니 dance dance <br>Watch 언니 dance on em <br>Watch 언니 dance on em <br>Watch 언니 dance on em <br>Watch 언니 dance dance <br>1 Learn the game huh <br>2 Go and slay huh <br>Slay All my Down girls huh <br>We going way up <br>If you want that unnie money <br>better save up <br>Love your haters let it motivate ya <br>Motivator motivator <br>love your haters let it motivate ya <br>Motivator motivator <br>go and get it girl <br>what are you afraid you of <br>Omg i love that bitch <br>]]></content><category term="제시 (Jessi)" label="제시 (Jessi)"/><category term="Spirit Animal" label="Spirit Animal"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제시_Jessi/걸음걸이_Feat_Year_of_the_OX/</id><title>제시_Jessi - 걸음걸이 (Feat. Year of the OX) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%8B%9C_Jessi/%EA%B1%B8%EC%9D%8C%EA%B1%B8%EC%9D%B4_Feat_Year_of_the_OX/" title="제시_Jessi - 걸음걸이 (Feat. Year of the OX) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어디로 가는지 나도 잘 몰라 <br>이대로 괜찮아 몰라도 좋아 <br>평소완 조금 다르대 <br>왜 자꾸 걸음이 이상하대 <br>비틀비틀 걷는 게 조금 어때서 <br>아무도 나를 걱정 안 해 모두 못됐어 <br>너가 날 피해서 가길 바래 <br>알아서 지나가는 게 편해 <br>오 어디로 가는지 나도 잘 몰라 <br>이대로 괜찮아 몰라도 좋아 <br>가고 싶은 곳은 같은데 <br>왜 자꾸 걸음이 이상하대 <br>내 걸음걸이가 우습지 않게 <br>그저 그런 말이 들리지 않게 <br>난 더 난 더 <br>It's been a long road <br>Still not at the top yet <br>Nah not yet <br>Still lots to accomplish <br>It's been a little bit more than a 산책 <br>We did it the way that we wanted <br>and disregarded what the signs said <br>I don't know where this path leads <br>But I just know that this is me <br>So put this on repeat <br>And get lost in ya thoughts <br>And remember the road to ur dreams <br>is never a walk in the park <br>오 어디로 가는지 나도 잘 몰라 <br>이대로 괜찮아 몰라도 좋아 <br>가고 싶은 곳은 같은데 <br>왜 자꾸 걸음이 이상하대 <br>내 걸음걸이가 우습지 않게 <br>그저 그런 말이 들리지 않게 <br>난 더 난 더 <br>remember when this wasn’t real <br>when we were just dreaming it still <br>imaginary concerts <br>with the comb as the mic <br>just to see how it feel <br>living my life as a thrill <br>there is no stopping me now <br>what are you talking about <br>it’s hard to hear you <br>when i’m walking it out <br>damn they don’t know me at all <br>It’s not their fault though <br>but check the outro <br>they just me winning <br>they just see me get it <br>they just see the image <br>they don’t really get it <br>I don’t need a critic <br>talking about my bidness <br>they don’t know my struggle <br>or the way i did it <br>내 걸음걸이가 우습지 않게 <br>그저 그런 말이 들리지 않게 <br>난 더 난 더 <br>Yeah 우습지 않게 <br>내 걸음걸이가 내 걸음걸이가 <br>]]></content><category term="제시 (Jessi)" label="제시 (Jessi)"/><category term="걸음걸이 (Feat. Year of the OX)" label="걸음걸이 (Feat. Year of the OX)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제시_Jessi/Boing_Feat_창모/</id><title>제시_Jessi - Boing (Feat. 창모) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%8B%9C_Jessi/Boing_Feat_%EC%B0%BD%EB%AA%A8/" title="제시_Jessi - Boing (Feat. 창모) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Workin and paying these bills <br>Workin and workin these heals <br>Don’t really care how you feel <br>Don’t really care how you feel <br>Hey girls <br>Keep it bossy <br>Keep it flossy <br>Keep it saucy <br>make it boing <br>I don’t want no want <br>no want no issues <br>But 내 일상은 너희에겐 issue <br>턱은 살짝 위로 <br>가슴 들어 위로 <br>Blame it on the boing <br>Make it boing boing <br>Boing boing boing <br>Make it boing boing <br>Make it Make it boing boing <br>Boing boing boing <br>Make it boing boing <br>Make it Make it boing boing <br>뭘 그렇게 눈치를 봐 <br>원하는걸 밀고 나가 <br>내 인생의 주인은 나 <br>이 영화의 주연은 나 <br>Ay girls <br>Don’t ever let nobody stop you <br>Just keep walkin <br>Make it boing boing <br>I dont want no want <br>no want no issues <br>But 내 일상은 너희에겐 issue <br>턱은 살짝 위로 <br>가슴 들어 위로 <br>Blame it on the boing <br>Make it boing boing <br>Boing boing boing <br>Make it boing boing <br>Make it Make it boing boing <br>Boing boing boing <br>Make it boing boing <br>Make it Make it boing boing <br>덕소 GD in the building <br>언제나 왼손은 illin 허예 <br>날 보면 여자들 달려와 <br>혹시 걔네 힐 밑이 힐리스 <br>허 예 <br>oh Yeah I’m so independent <br>없어 파파라치 붙을 일 <br>그 말인 즉슨 애매히 유명해서 <br>얘랑 아주 놀 수 있다고 hit it <br>나오긴 글러 부렀지 <br>나의 몸 안에 사리 <br>그녀는 나의 볼을 꼬집어대네 <br>나의 손안엔 aight <br>넌 자존감이 쎄 그러니 <br>baby make 그대 자매 dance <br>난 Jay park의 fan 오 너도 그래 <br>Do the 자매 dance <br>No i don’t want no want <br>no want no issues <br>But 내 일상은 너희에겐 issue <br>턱은 살짝 위로 <br>가슴 들어 위로 <br>Blame it on the boing <br>Make it boing boing <br>Boing boing boing <br>Make it boing boing <br>Make it Make it boing boing <br>Boing boing boing <br>Make it boing boing <br>Make it Make it boing boing <br>Boing boing boing <br>Make it boing boing <br>Make it Make it boing boing <br>Boing boing boing <br>Make it boing boing <br>Make it Make it boing boing <br>Bounce bounce wit it <br>Bounce bounce wit it <br>Bounce bounce wit it <br>Bounce bounce wit it <br>]]></content><category term="제시 (Jessi)" label="제시 (Jessi)"/><category term="Boing (Feat. 창모)" label="Boing (Feat. 창모)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제시_Jessi/Gucci/</id><title>제시_Jessi - Gucci - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%8B%9C_Jessi/Gucci/" title="제시_Jessi - Gucci - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[돈 많은 척 하는 애들은 저리가 <br>네 연봉을 내 어깨에다 거니까 <br>I‘m way to fly to be one of yall <br>내 위치에선 넌 숨도 못 쉬어 <br>내가 왜 굳이 너네랑 앉어 <br>한 병 보낼게 형들이랑 마셔 <br>이 언니 네 언니 넌 영보이 <br>저 돌아가는 길에 <br>저기 웨이터 불러줘 <br>Cause i'm self made <br>Ain‘t no body ever made me <br>I’m in the party going crazy <br>이건 거의 movie <br>And i feel like Gucci <br>I feel like Gucci yuh <br>I feel like Gucci baby <br>I feel like Gucci <br>I feel like Gucci baby <br>I’m a bad motha’ fucka <br>in the room <br>I feel like Gucci <br>I feel like Gucci <br>내 차는 내가 몰아 그냥 옆에 앉아 <br>보여줄게 많아 저녁 먹자 내가 밥사 <br>맨 위에 맨 위로 그게 나의 미션 <br>내 엉덩이에다 뽀뽀해라 컴퍼티션 <br>내가 왜 굳이 너한테 붙어 <br>어디가도 내가 받는 것은 오직 love <br>이 언니 네 언니 넌 영보이 <br>저 돌아가는 길에 <br>저기 웨이터 불러줘 <br>Cause i'm self made <br>Ain‘t no body ever made me <br>I’m in the party going crazy <br>이건 거의 movie <br>And i feel like Gucci <br>I feel like Gucci yuh <br>I feel like Gucci baby <br>I feel like Gucci <br>I feel like Gucci baby <br>I’m a bad motha’ fucka <br>in the room <br>I feel like Gucci <br>I feel like Gucci <br>And i speak nothing but the truth <br>난 나야 너도 너대로 <br>And i don‘t give a F-U-C-K <br>what you say about me <br>Got gangsta in my attitude <br>내가 늘 원하는대로 <br>And i don‘t give a F-U-C-K <br>what ya think <br>And i feel like Gucci <br>I feel like Gucci yuh <br>I feel like Gucci baby <br>I feel like Gucci <br>I feel like Gucci baby <br>I’m a bad motha’ fucka <br>in the room <br>I feel like Gucci <br>I feel like Gucci <br>Gucci Gucci Gucci <br>Gucci Gucci Gucci <br>Gucci Gucci Gucci <br>Gucci Gucci Gucci <br>I’m a bad motha <br>I feel like Gucci <br>I feel like Gucci Baby <br>]]></content><category term="제시 (Jessi)" label="제시 (Jessi)"/><category term="Gucci" label="Gucci"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/보이스퍼_VOISPER/반했나봐_Inst/</id><title>보이스퍼_VOISPER - 반했나봐 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4%ED%8D%BC_VOISPER/%EB%B0%98%ED%96%88%EB%82%98%EB%B4%90_Inst/" title="보이스퍼_VOISPER - 반했나봐 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오 몸의 작은 떨림만 봐도 <br>머릴 쓸어 넘길 때 손목의 각도 <br>어딜 봐도 너를 갖고 싶어져 <br>안고 싶어져 <br>자꾸 생각나 또 <br>오 힘들 때마다 살짝 다가와 <br>따스한 말 한 마디에 난 다시 살아나 <br>너무 예뻐 정말 웬걸 <br>지금도 생각나 <br>성큼 다가가기엔 조심스런 맘 <br>선뜻 사랑이라기엔 부끄러운 맘 <br>하지만 널 볼 때마다 <br>점점 커져 가는 맘 <br>먼저 한발 내딛어 용길 내볼래 <br>먼저 손을 내밀어 고백해볼래 <br>내 이런 맘을 알까 <br>이런 감정 믿기지 않아 <br>반했나봐 빠졌나봐 <br>난 너에게 너에게 <br>모든 걸 보여주고 싶어 <br>난 너 뿐이잖아 <br>꿈만 같아 오 나에게 나에게 <br>완전한 단 한 사람 너 하나 <br>오 설렘에 반짝이는 눈빛 <br>귀를 기울일 때에 너만의 몸짓 <br>어딜 봐도 너를 갖고 싶어져 <br>안고 싶어져 <br>자꾸 생각나 또 <br>오 이제는 때가 된 것만 같아 <br>서로의 맘이 같다는 걸 너도 알잖아 <br>너무 예뻐 정말 웬걸 <br>참을 수가 없어 <br>꼭 한 사람을 위해 아껴왔던 말 <br>진짜 사랑을 위해 하고 싶은 말 <br>전할게 이제 너만을 위해 <br>준비해둔 말 <br>먼저 한발 내딛어 용길 내볼래 <br>먼저 손을 내밀어 고백해볼래 <br>이제 널 잡고 싶어 <br>이런 감정 믿기지 않아 <br>반했나봐 빠졌나봐 <br>난 너에게 너에게 <br>모든 걸 보여주고 싶어 <br>난 너 뿐이잖아 <br>꿈만 같아 오 나에게 나에게 <br>완전한 단 한 사람 너 하나 <br>감사해 이런 느낌을 준 너에게 <br>좋아해 영원토록 변치 않을게 <br>내겐 정말 꿈만 같아 이런 감정 <br>믿기지 않아 <br>나 너에게 너에게 너에게 <br>이제 말할래 사랑해 <br>반했나봐 빠졌나봐 <br>난 너에게 너에게 <br>모든 걸 보여주고 싶어 <br>난 너 뿐이잖아 <br>꿈만 같아 오 나에게 나에게 <br>완전한 단 한 사람 너 하나 <br>반했나봐 빠졌나봐 <br>난 너에게 너에게 <br>모든 걸 보여주고 싶어 <br>난 너 뿐이잖아 <br>꿈만 같아 오 나에게 나에게 <br>완전한 단 한 사람 너 하나 <br>]]></content><category term="보이스퍼 (VOISPER)" label="보이스퍼 (VOISPER)"/><category term="반했나봐 (Inst.)" label="반했나봐 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/보이스퍼_VOISPER/지난_날_Original_Song_by_유재하/</id><title>보이스퍼_VOISPER - 지난 날 (Original Song by 유재하) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4%ED%8D%BC_VOISPER/%EC%A7%80%EB%82%9C_%EB%82%A0_Original_Song_by_%EC%9C%A0%EC%9E%AC%ED%95%98/" title="보이스퍼_VOISPER - 지난 날 (Original Song by 유재하) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지난 옛 일 모두 <br>기쁨이라고 하면서도 <br>아픈 기억 찾아 헤매이는 건 왜일까 <br>가슴 깊이 남은 건 때늦은 후회 <br>덧없는 듯 쓴웃음으로 <br>지나온 날들을 돌아보네 <br>예전처럼 돌이킬 순 없다고 하면서도 <br>문득문득 흐뭇함에 젖는 건 왜일까 <br>그대로 그 나름대로 의미가 있어 <br>세상 사람 얘기하듯이 <br>옛 추억이란 아름다운 것 <br>다시 못 올 지난 날을 <br>난 꾸밈없이 영원히 간직하리 <br>그리움을 가득 안은 채 <br>가버린 지난 날 <br>잊지 못할 그 추억 속에 <br>난 우리들의 미래를 비춰보리 <br>하루하루 더욱 새로웁게 <br>그대와 나의 지난 날 <br>언제 어디 누가 <br>이유라는 탓하면 뭘 해 <br>잘했었건 못했었건 간에 <br>다시 못 올 지난 날을 <br>난 꾸밈없이 영원히 간직하리 <br>아쉬움을 가득 안은 채 <br>그대와 나의 지난 날 <br>생각 없이 헛되이 <br>지낸다고 하지 말아요 <br>그렇다고 변하는 것은 <br>아닐 테니까 지난 날 <br>다시 못 올 지난 날을 <br>난 꾸밈없이 영원히 간직하리 <br>그리움을 가득 안은 채 <br>가버린 지난 날 <br>잊지 못할 그 추억 속에 <br>난 우리들의 미래를 비춰보리 <br>하루하루 더욱 새로웁게 <br>그대와 나의 지난 날 <br>다시 못 올 나의 지난 날 <br>그대와 나의 지난 날 <br>]]></content><category term="보이스퍼 (VOISPER)" label="보이스퍼 (VOISPER)"/><category term="지난 날 (Original Song by 유재하)" label="지난 날 (Original Song by 유재하)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/보이스퍼_VOISPER/반했나봐/</id><title>보이스퍼_VOISPER - 반했나봐 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4%ED%8D%BC_VOISPER/%EB%B0%98%ED%96%88%EB%82%98%EB%B4%90/" title="보이스퍼_VOISPER - 반했나봐 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오 몸의 작은 떨림만 봐도 <br>머릴 쓸어 넘길 때 손목의 각도 <br>어딜 봐도 너를 갖고 싶어져 <br>안고 싶어져 <br>자꾸 생각나 또 <br>오 힘들 때마다 살짝 다가와 <br>따스한 말 한 마디에 난 다시 살아나 <br>너무 예뻐 정말 웬걸 <br>지금도 생각나 <br>성큼 다가가기엔 조심스런 맘 <br>선뜻 사랑이라기엔 부끄러운 맘 <br>하지만 널 볼 때마다 <br>점점 커져 가는 맘 <br>먼저 한발 내딛어 용길 내볼래 <br>먼저 손을 내밀어 고백해볼래 <br>내 이런 맘을 알까 <br>이런 감정 믿기지 않아 <br>반했나봐 빠졌나봐 <br>난 너에게 너에게 <br>모든 걸 보여주고 싶어 <br>난 너 뿐이잖아 <br>꿈만 같아 오 나에게 나에게 <br>완전한 단 한 사람 너 하나 <br>오 설렘에 반짝이는 눈빛 <br>귀를 기울일 때에 너만의 몸짓 <br>어딜 봐도 너를 갖고 싶어져 <br>안고 싶어져 <br>자꾸 생각나 또 <br>오 이제는 때가 된 것만 같아 <br>서로의 맘이 같다는 걸 너도 알잖아 <br>너무 예뻐 정말 웬걸 <br>참을 수가 없어 <br>꼭 한 사람을 위해 아껴왔던 말 <br>진짜 사랑을 위해 하고 싶은 말 <br>전할게 이제 너만을 위해 <br>준비해둔 말 <br>먼저 한발 내딛어 용길 내볼래 <br>먼저 손을 내밀어 고백해볼래 <br>이제 널 잡고 싶어 <br>이런 감정 믿기지 않아 <br>반했나봐 빠졌나봐 <br>난 너에게 너에게 <br>모든 걸 보여주고 싶어 <br>난 너 뿐이잖아 <br>꿈만 같아 오 나에게 나에게 <br>완전한 단 한 사람 너 하나 <br>감사해 이런 느낌을 준 너에게 <br>좋아해 영원토록 변치 않을게 <br>내겐 정말 꿈만 같아 이런 감정 <br>믿기지 않아 <br>나 너에게 너에게 너에게 <br>이제 말할래 사랑해 <br>반했나봐 빠졌나봐 <br>난 너에게 너에게 <br>모든 걸 보여주고 싶어 <br>난 너 뿐이잖아 <br>꿈만 같아 오 나에게 나에게 <br>완전한 단 한 사람 너 하나 <br>반했나봐 빠졌나봐 <br>난 너에게 너에게 <br>모든 걸 보여주고 싶어 <br>난 너 뿐이잖아 <br>꿈만 같아 오 나에게 나에게 <br>완전한 단 한 사람 너 하나 <br>]]></content><category term="보이스퍼 (VOISPER)" label="보이스퍼 (VOISPER)"/><category term="반했나봐" label="반했나봐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Olivia_OBrien/RIP/</id><title>Olivia_OBrien - RIP - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Olivia_OBrien/RIP/" title="Olivia_OBrien - RIP - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You don't make time <br>like you used to <br>Got a new girl new friends <br>brand new <br>I swear it's like <br>I don't even know you <br>Yeah I miss the old you <br>I kinda want to fight like <br>we used to <br>To make it alright like we used to <br>Anything 'cause I didn't want <br>to lose you <br>But this time we've gone too far <br>We've gone too far <br>This new you this new dude <br>Don't know him don't want to <br>I wish that I still knew <br>the old him the old you <br>R-I-P to the old you <br>I miss the old you <br>It's like you're dead to me now <br>R-I-P to the old you <br>I fucking miss you <br>I would have never let you down <br>like you did to me <br>Now you're dead to me <br>R-I-P <br>You're acting like the people <br>that we hated <br>You're hanging <br>with the worst and I hate it <br>All you do now is get too faded <br>You think you're the shit now <br>Now everything is too complicated <br>You can try <br>but there's no way to save it <br>Because you're too caught up <br>in the fake shit <br>I wish we could <br>just restart just restart <br>This new you this new dude <br>Don't know him don't want to <br>I wish that I still knew <br>the old him the old you <br>R-I-P to the old you <br>I miss the old you <br>It's like you're dead to me now <br>R-I-P to the old you <br>I fucking miss you <br>I would have never let you down <br>like you did to me <br>Now you're dead to me <br>R-I-P <br>R-I-P to the old you <br>I fucking miss you <br>It's like you're six feet <br>in the ground <br>One day you gon' miss me <br>You'll come running back <br>and you'll hit me up <br>But I won't answer that shit <br>now I won't answer that shit now <br>One day I won't miss you <br>When I'm drunk <br>instead I won't hit you up <br>Because I'll be over that shit <br>yeah I'll be over that shit yeah <br>R-I-P to the old you <br>R-I-P to you <br>I miss the old you I miss you <br>It's like you're dead to me now <br>dead to me <br>R-I-P to the old you R-I-P <br>I fucking miss you I miss you <br>I would have never let you down <br>never let you down <br>Like you did to me <br>like you did to me <br>Now you're dead to me <br>dead to me now <br>R-I-P <br>R-I-P to the old you R-I-P <br>I fucking miss you I miss you <br>It's like you're six feet <br>in the ground <br>]]></content><category term="Olivia O`Brien" label="Olivia O`Brien"/><category term="RIP" label="RIP"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Christopher/Lot_To_Learn/</id><title>Luke_Christopher - Lot To Learn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:42:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:42:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Christopher/Lot_To_Learn/" title="Luke_Christopher - Lot To Learn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If I was the question, would you be my answer? <br>If I was the music, would you be the dancer? <br>If I was the student, would you be the teacher? <br>If I was the sinner, would you be the preacher? <br><br>Would you be my <br>N' dun ddun dun <br>I still got a lot of shit to learn, I'll admit it <br>N' dun ddun dun <br>I still got a lot of shit to learn, I'll admit it <br><br>Feeling like a digit in a system, just another stupid number <br>I don't know, know, know <br>Everything is twisted i can feel it <br>It's another stupid summer where it's cold, cold, cold <br>And we can do it on our own <br>Head up to a place where baby no one goes <br>A rocket full of Liquor, a Polaroid for Pictures <br>Baby you should stop me, 'fore I lose control <br>How a perfect a person am I, go through your purse and put on your disguise <br>You see the stars, but they just see the skies <br>And you see my scars what do they see? <br><br>If I was the question, would you be my answer? <br>If I was the music, would you be the dancer? <br>If I was the student, would you be the teacher? <br>If I was the sinner, would you be the preacher? <br><br>Would you be my <br>N' dun ddun dun <br>I still got a lot of shit to learn I'll admit it <br>N' dun ddun dun <br>I still got a lot of shit to learn I'll admit it <br>And the dun ddun dun <br>We still got a lot of shit to learn just admit it <br>And the dun ddun dun <br>We still got a lot of shit to learn don't you get it? <br><br>Got your finger on the trigger and you aiming at the mirror <br>Don't you shoot that ain't you, nah <br>Cause on the outside you pretend but you hurting in the inner <br>What's the truth, <br>What's the truth, now <br>How a perfect a person am I, go through your purse and put on your disguise <br>You see the stars, but they just see the skies <br>And you see my scars what do they see? <br><br>If I was the question would you be my answer? <br>If I was the music would you be the dancer? <br>If I was the student would you be the teacher? <br>If I was the sinner would you be the preacher? <br><br>Would you be my <br>N' dun ddun dun <br>I still got a lot of shit to learn I'll admit it <br>N' dun ddun dun <br>I still got a lot of shit to learn I'll admit it <br><br>Cheers to the fact you living and this is your world <br>They say they ain’t feeling you they living in their own world <br>Work to my O girl, and work to me to <br>I only said there no mic <br>because I need to feeling like im see through and life is a window <br>I be running opposite the wait that the wind blow <br>You pick up the pieces for the days that you didn’t know <br>So when you hear the tab <br>you better scream that you didn't though <br><br>If I was the question would you be my answer? <br>If I was the music would you be the dancer? <br>If I was the student would you be the teacher? <br>If I was the sinner would you be the preacher? <br><br>Would you be my <br>N' dun ddun dun <br>I still got a lot of shit to learn I'll admit it <br>N' dun ddun dun <br>I still got a lot of shit to learn I'll admit it <br><br>If I was the question, would you be my answer? <br>If I was the music, would you be the dancer? <br>If I was the student, would you be the teacher? <br>If I was the sinner, would you be the preacher? <br><br>If I was the question, would you be my answer? <br>If I was the music, would you be the dancer? <br>If I was the student, would you be the teacher? <br>If I was the sinner, would you be the preacher? <br><br>Would you be my <br>N' dun ddun dun <br>I still got a lot of shit to learn I'll admit it <br>N' dun ddun dun <br>I still got a lot of shit to learn I'll admit it]]></content><category term="Luke Christopher" label="Luke Christopher"/><category term="Lot To Learn" label="Lot To Learn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Avenged_Sevenfold/Dose/</id><title>Avenged_Sevenfold - Dose - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:43:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:43:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Avenged_Sevenfold/Dose/" title="Avenged_Sevenfold - Dose - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What's the matter dear <br>Seems the ghost <br>Is in your stall <br>For a thousand years <br>Taured lived within us all <br>I've come from <br>Somewhere beyond <br><br>Lost in a world <br>Voyage in time <br>Shot through the worm <br>Scaling the vine <br><br>Here in '54 <br>Tastes of napalm fill the sky <br>Axis wins the war <br>Seems the crop of our divide <br>I've slipped through <br>Bodies aligned <br><br>Lost in the world <br>Voyage in time <br>Shot through the worm <br>Scaling the vine <br><br>Solo <br><br>All that's me <br>And all that's you <br>All that's false <br>And all that's true <br>On the sea you sailed away <br>Another time <br>You'd surely stay <br>It's only fabric so it seems <br>Our intimate reality <br>We're living simultaneously <br>While parallel in possibilities <br><br>Lost in the world <br>Voyage in time <br>Shot through the worm <br>Scaling the vine <br><br>Lost in the world <br>Voyage in time <br>Shot through the worm <br>Scaling the vine]]></content><category term="Avenged Sevenfold" label="Avenged Sevenfold"/><category term="Dose" label="Dose"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/터보트로닉_Turbotronic/봄디기_Original_Mix/</id><title>터보트로닉_Turbotronic - 봄디기 (Original Mix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:43:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:43:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%84%B0%EB%B3%B4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A1%9C%EB%8B%89_Turbotronic/%EB%B4%84%EB%94%94%EA%B8%B0_Original_Mix/" title="터보트로닉_Turbotronic - 봄디기 (Original Mix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>봄디기 <br>봄디기 <br>봄디기 <br>봄디기 <br>봄봄봄봄봄봄봄봄 <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>봄디기 <br>봄디기 <br>봄디기 <br>봄디기 <br>봄봄봄봄봄봄봄봄 <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>봄 <br>봄 <br>봄 <br>봄 <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>]]></content><category term="터보트로닉 (Turbotronic)" label="터보트로닉 (Turbotronic)"/><category term="봄디기 (Original Mix)" label="봄디기 (Original Mix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/터보트로닉_Turbotronic/봄디기_Original_Edit/</id><title>터보트로닉_Turbotronic - 봄디기 (Original Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:43:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:43:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%84%B0%EB%B3%B4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A1%9C%EB%8B%89_Turbotronic/%EB%B4%84%EB%94%94%EA%B8%B0_Original_Edit/" title="터보트로닉_Turbotronic - 봄디기 (Original Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>봄디기 <br>봄디기 <br>봄디기 <br>봄디기 <br>봄봄봄봄봄봄봄봄 <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>Booya Booya Booya <br>Shake Shake <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>봄디기 <br>봄디기 <br>봄디기 <br>봄디기 <br>봄봄봄봄봄봄봄봄 <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>봄디기디기디기 봄디기봄 <br>]]></content><category term="터보트로닉 (Turbotronic)" label="터보트로닉 (Turbotronic)"/><category term="봄디기 (Original Edit)" label="봄디기 (Original Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Christopher/Lost/</id><title>Luke_Christopher - Lost - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:43:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:43:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Christopher/Lost/" title="Luke_Christopher - Lost - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So lost <br>I'm so lost whoa ooh whoa <br>Yeah feeling like make-believe <br>Homie good luck with that <br>All of this for you girl <br>you better love me back <br>I should probably write you <br>or somethin' <br>Baby I should fight you <br>or somethin' <br>Maybe you're another girl <br>that likes guys <br>that don't like you for nothing <br>Colors all black <br>and white food tastes like water <br>Not used to being <br>the one trying harder <br>My homies say <br>Dawg save some thoughts <br>for your barber <br>You gon' be tripping your way <br>down the altar that's real <br>Am I cool but twisted <br>I just can't let you <br>push my love aside <br>I'm a fool but I'm living <br>I'm wrapped in your fever <br>you dance in my mind <br>What's this game <br>What's my purpose <br>And is there a time <br>or a limit for finding your heart <br>Where do I start <br>Is there a train ticket <br>I could obtain <br>'Cause I'm lost and I love it <br>I can't seem to make <br>any sense of you girl <br>'Cause I'm off but I love it <br>How can something <br>so beautiful orbit my world <br>I'm so lost I'm so lost <br>I'm so lost I'm so lost <br>I'm so lost I'm so lost <br>I'm so lost whoa ooh whoa <br>I'm so <br>Notice me bitch notice me <br>I'm sorry these Barbies <br>all over me <br>I need something real <br>Girl your body so sincere <br>We could be at your house <br>Now girl why are we still here <br>Uh I see them drown in your wave <br>Walk through the spot <br>watch the energy change <br>Two more drinks here's your tip <br>I'ma speak with this chick <br>When I get back <br>have 'em waiting ready to sip <br>Girl I'm gone hardly standing <br>Losing my balance <br>I'm grabbing the walls <br>And your love it's demanding <br>I'm going savage <br>I'm way too involved <br>Won't you show me baby <br>Are you holding aces <br>You got me feeling like <br>I should be stealing your heart <br>Where do I start <br>No point in hoping <br>or trying to control it <br>I'm lost and I love it <br>I can't seem to make <br>any sense of you girl <br>'Cause I'm off but I love it <br>How can something <br>so beautiful orbit my world <br>I'm so lost Where are we <br>I'm so lost Where are we <br>I'm so lost Where are we <br>I'm so lost <br>I'm so lost Where are we <br>I'm so lost Where are we <br>I'm so lost Where are we now <br>whoa ooh whoa <br>I'm so <br>Where are we Where are we <br>Where are we now <br>Ooh where are we Where are we <br>Whoa ooh whoa <br>]]></content><category term="Luke Christopher" label="Luke Christopher"/><category term="Lost" label="Lost"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정세영/Reunion/</id><title>정세영 - Reunion - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:44:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:44:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%84%B8%EC%98%81/Reunion/" title="정세영 - Reunion - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우연히 널 마주쳤을 때 <br>머릿속이 복잡해졌지 <br>먼저 말을 건네볼까 <br>못 본 척 지나쳐갈까 <br>그렇게 멍하니 서있었지 나는 <br>한발 두발 너는 점점 내게 다가오고 <br>두근대는 내 심장은 말을 듣지 않고 <br>괜찮을 줄 알았었는데 <br>반갑게 인사하려 했는데 <br>여전히 널 잊지 못했나 봐 <br>해줄 말이 많았었는데 <br>하나도 기억나지를 않아 <br>여전히 널 잡고 싶지만 <br>차마 그럴 수가 없네 <br>짧은 눈인사를 하고 <br>어색한 미소 지으며 <br>아무 말하지 못하겠지 <br>그토록 간절하게 바래왔던 순간이 <br>허무하게 끝나가네 <br>한발 두발 너는 점점 내게 멀어지고 <br>두근대는 내 심장은 말을 듣지 않고 <br>괜찮을 줄 알았었는데 <br>반갑게 인사하려 했는데 <br>여전히 널 잊지 못했나 봐 <br>해줄 말이 많았었는데 <br>하나도 기억나지를 않아 <br>여전히 널 잡고 싶지만 <br>차마 그럴 수가 없네 <br>한발 두발 너는 점점 내게 다가오고 <br>두근대는 내 심장은 말을 듣지 않고 <br>한발 두발 너는 점점 내게 멀어지고 <br>두근대는 내 심장은 말을 듣지 않고 <br>]]></content><category term="정세영" label="정세영"/><category term="Reunion" label="Reunion"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이동윤/너_하나/</id><title>이동윤 - 너 하나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:44:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:44:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%EC%9C%A4/%EB%84%88_%ED%95%98%EB%82%98/" title="이동윤 - 너 하나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그저 아무말 못하지 <br>너의 앞에서 난 <br>애써 내 마음 감춰보려고 <br>일부러 나는 딴 생각만 해 <br>그게 나란 말야 <br>오늘 아침엔 유난히 <br>더 예쁘게 보여 <br>밤새 그리워 했던 탓일까 <br>나 정말 바보같고 <br>너 정말 어렵다 <br>사랑때문에 정말 아프다 <br>사랑이라서 <br>기다리고 기다려도 괜찮아 <br>내 사랑이라서 <br>하루종일 눈물나도 괜찮아 <br>말 못한 채 늘 스쳐만 갔던 <br>입술끝에서만 맴돌던 내 마음이야 <br>사랑해 <br>자꾸 너에게 내 마음 <br>들키고만 싶어 <br>괜히 니 앞을 서성거리는 <br>나 정말 바보같고 <br>너 정말 어렵다 <br>사랑때문에 정말 아프다 <br>사랑이라서 <br>기다리고 기다려도 괜찮아 <br>내 사랑이라서 <br>하루종일 눈물나도 괜찮아 <br>말 못한 채 늘 스쳐만 갔던 <br>입술끝에서만 맴돌던 내 마음이야 <br>사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>이 말 하나면 되는데 <br>미워질만큼 난 니가 그립다 <br>사랑하니까 <br>내 소원을 다버려도 너하나 <br>널 사랑하니까 <br>내 전부를 가져가도 너하나 <br>숨겨둔 채 늘 그림자처럼 <br>너의 뒷모습만 바라본 내 마음이야 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="이동윤" label="이동윤"/><category term="너 하나" label="너 하나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이태종/다_이루었다/</id><title>이태종 - 다 이루었다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:44:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:44:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%83%9C%EC%A2%85/%EB%8B%A4_%EC%9D%B4%EB%A3%A8%EC%97%88%EB%8B%A4/" title="이태종 - 다 이루었다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다 이루었다 <br>나는 다 이루었다 <br>창세기로부터 <br>계시록까지 <br>나는 다 이루었다 <br>다 이루었다 <br>아버지의 영원 섭리 <br>내 아버지의 <br>영원 진리 <br>나는 다 이루었다 <br>하늘과 땅의 <br>모든 비밀 <br>그 계시들을 <br>다 열어 놓았다 <br>사도 요한이 <br>가슴 치며 통곡했던 <br>하늘 일곱 인봉을 <br>다 떼어 놓았다 <br>우주의 신비들은 <br>다 펼쳐졌다 <br>하늘과 땅은 <br>하나로 결합되었다 <br>창세전의 <br>내 아버지 모든 계획 <br>나는 다 이루었다 <br>영원한 오묘들은 <br>다 드러났다 <br>하나님의 <br>깊은 심정까지도 <br>우주에 광포되었다 <br>아버지여 나는 <br>세상에서 당신의 뜻을 <br>다 이루었나이다 <br>아버지여 이제 이 소자 <br>당신의 품속으로 <br>다시 데려가소서 <br>우주의 신비들은 <br>다 펼쳐졌다 <br>하늘과 땅은 하나로 <br>결합되었다 <br>창세전의 내 아버지 <br>모든 계획 <br>나는 다 이루었다 <br>다 이루신 인자대왕 <br>찬양하라 천지 만물 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 <br>할렐루야 <br>영광의 문들아 <br>너희 머리 들지어다 <br>호산나 호산나 <br>찬양하라 <br>하늘과 땅 찬양하라 <br>삼라만상 찬양하라 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 <br>할렐루야 <br>여호와의 이름으로 <br>오신 주께 찬양하라 <br>호산나 호산나 <br>찬양하라 <br>다 이루신 인자대왕 <br>찬양하라 천지 만물 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 <br>할렐루야 <br>영광의 문들아 <br>너희 머리 들지어다 <br>호산나 호산나 <br>찬양하라 <br>하늘과 땅 찬양하라 <br>삼라만상 찬양하라 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 <br>할렐루야 <br>여호와의 이름으로 <br>오신 주께 찬양하라 <br>호산나 호산나 <br>찬양하라 <br>찬양하라 찬양하라 <br>대영광 <br>]]></content><category term="이태종" label="이태종"/><category term="다 이루었다" label="다 이루었다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이태종/개선날을_기다리는_왕자님/</id><title>이태종 - 개선날을 기다리는 왕자님 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:44:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:44:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%83%9C%EC%A2%85/%EA%B0%9C%EC%84%A0%EB%82%A0%EC%9D%84_%EA%B8%B0%EB%8B%A4%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_%EC%99%95%EC%9E%90%EB%8B%98/" title="이태종 - 개선날을 기다리는 왕자님 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모든 사명 <br>숱한 전쟁 <br>다 마친 후에 <br>한가로이 개선식을 <br>기다리는 하늘의 용사 <br>내 아버지 영광 위해 <br>지난 숱한 전쟁 <br>목숨을 초개같이 <br>던졌던 하늘의 왕자 <br>싸우고 또 싸워 <br>승리만 거뒀던 <br>지난 날들 <br>하늘과 온 땅의 <br>천추의 한을 풀어주신 <br>우주 무적의 미가엘 <br>그 이름 <br>우주에 가득하네 <br>번뜩이는 진리의 번개검 <br>억조창생 무릎 꿇어 <br>경배하네 <br>진리의 번개검 <br>칼집에 꽂고 <br>하늘 입성 <br>개선날을 기다리는 <br>대군 미가엘 <br>찬란한 무훈으로 <br>빛났던 그 이름 <br>우주에 가득하고 <br>그 무훈 빛나네 <br>싸우고 또 싸워 <br>승리만 거뒀던 <br>지난 날들 <br>하늘과 온 땅의 <br>천추의 한을 풀어주신 <br>우주 무적의 미가엘 <br>그 이름 <br>우주에 가득하네 <br>번뜩이는 진리의 번개검 <br>억조창생 무릎 꿇어 <br>경배하네 <br>우주 무적의 미가엘 <br>그 이름 <br>우주에 가득하네 <br>번뜩이는 진리의 번개검 <br>억조창생 무릎 꿇어 <br>경배하네 <br>우주 무적의 미가엘 <br>그 이름 <br>우주에 가득하네 <br>번뜩이는 진리의 번개검 <br>억조창생 무릎 꿇어 <br>경배하네 <br>]]></content><category term="이태종" label="이태종"/><category term="개선날을 기다리는 왕자님" label="개선날을 기다리는 왕자님"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이태종/새_세상의_주인들/</id><title>이태종 - 새 세상의 주인들 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:44:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:44:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%83%9C%EC%A2%85/%EC%83%88_%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81%EC%9D%98_%EC%A3%BC%EC%9D%B8%EB%93%A4/" title="이태종 - 새 세상의 주인들 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[높은 산이 부르네 <br>먼 바다가 부르네 <br>하늘에서 부르네 <br>하나님이 부르네 <br>새 세상 차지할 <br>주인들을 부르네 <br>누가 누가 대답할까 <br>누가 누가 주인 될까 <br>질병 없는 행복 나라 <br>죽음 없는 영원 나라 <br>오 오 누가 차지할까 <br>물이 된 자 <br>발이 된 자 <br>형제 위해 <br>소금 된 자 <br>에녹처럼 <br>허유처럼 <br>신선 된 자 <br>주인 되지 <br>높은 산이 부르네 <br>먼 바다가 부르네 <br>하늘에서 부르네 <br>하나님이 부르네 <br>누가 누가 <br>주인 될까 <br>누가 누가 차지할까 <br>밥 안 먹고 <br>사는 사람 <br>에덴 낙원 <br>회복자들 <br>오 오 <br>누가 차지할까 <br>우주 대왕 친자녀들 <br>하나님이 된 사람들 <br>하나님 신부들로 <br>단장 마친 자들 <br>높은 산이 부르네 <br>먼 바다가 부르네 <br>새 세상에 뛰놀을 <br>아이들을 부르네 <br>높은 산이 부르네 <br>먼 바다가 부르네 <br>하늘에서 부르네 <br>하나님이 부르네 <br>하나님이 부르네 <br>]]></content><category term="이태종" label="이태종"/><category term="새 세상의 주인들" label="새 세상의 주인들"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이태종/진리는_영원히_빛났다/</id><title>이태종 - 진리는 영원히 빛났다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:44:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:44:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%83%9C%EC%A2%85/%EC%A7%84%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_%EC%98%81%EC%9B%90%ED%9E%88_%EB%B9%9B%EB%82%AC%EB%8B%A4/" title="이태종 - 진리는 영원히 빛났다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여호와는 발하신다 <br>오류는 물러가라 <br>하나님은 명하신다 <br>가면은 벗겨져라 <br>여호와는 발하신다 <br>교만은 엎어져라 <br>하나님은 명하신다 <br>완고는 깨어져라 <br>가식은 파헤쳐라 <br>외식은 불사르라 <br>거짓은 나타나라 <br>이리는 내쫓아라 <br>진리는 <br>영원히 빛났다 <br>여호와는 발하신다 <br>오류는 물러가라 <br>하나님은 명하신다 <br>가면은 벗겨져라 <br>여호와는 발하신다 <br>교만은 엎어져라 <br>하나님은 명하신다 <br>완고는 깨어져라 <br>가식은 파헤쳐라 <br>외식은 불사르라 <br>거짓은 나타나라 <br>이리는 내쫓아라 <br>진리는 <br>영원히 빛났다 <br>진리는 <br>영원히 빛났다 <br>]]></content><category term="이태종" label="이태종"/><category term="진리는 영원히 빛났다" label="진리는 영원히 빛났다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이태종/전능하신_창조주_하나님/</id><title>이태종 - 전능하신 창조주 하나님 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:44:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:44:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%83%9C%EC%A2%85/%EC%A0%84%EB%8A%A5%ED%95%98%EC%8B%A0_%EC%B0%BD%EC%A1%B0%EC%A3%BC_%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EB%8B%98/" title="이태종 - 전능하신 창조주 하나님 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[더 이상 타락할 수 없이 <br>발 밑 진흙같이 타락해 버린 <br>죄인들을 하나님께서 <br>토기장이 되시어 <br>전능하신 창조주 하나님 <br>타락한 이 진흙으로 <br>깨끗한 의인 만들어 내신다 <br>영원토록 감사 찬양을 <br>드리리라 드리리라 <br>더 이상 망가질 수 없이 <br>발 밑 진흙같이 망가져 버린 <br>죄인들을 하나님께서 <br>토기장이 되시어 <br>전능하신 창조주 하나님 <br>망가진 이 진흙으로 <br>완전한 예수 만들어 내신다 <br>전능하신 능력 하나님 <br>찬양하라 찬양하라 <br>더 이상 더러워질 수 없이 <br>완전 진흙같이 더러워진 <br>죄인들을 하나님께서 <br>토기장이 되시어 <br>전능하신 창조주 하나님 <br>더러워진 이 진흙으로 <br>거룩한 하나님들로 만드신다 <br>홀로 영광 감사 찬양을 <br>바치리라 바치리라 <br>바치리라 바치리라 <br>]]></content><category term="이태종" label="이태종"/><category term="전능하신 창조주 하나님" label="전능하신 창조주 하나님"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이태종/낙원에서_노래할_사람들/</id><title>이태종 - 낙원에서 노래할 사람들 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:44:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:44:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%83%9C%EC%A2%85/%EB%82%99%EC%9B%90%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98%ED%95%A0_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C%EB%93%A4/" title="이태종 - 낙원에서 노래할 사람들 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어둡고 캄캄한 밤이 <br>극성을 부리지만 <br>영락없이 찾아오는 <br>의의 태양 빛 앞에 <br>맥도 못 추고 사라진다네 <br>에헤야 데헤야 경사로다 <br>사랑 행복 가득하여 <br>만물이 춤추며 <br>에헤야 데헤야 경사로다 <br>노래하는 영생 낙원 <br>천국 돌아왔다네 <br>심술궂은 겨울이 <br>온 세계를 얼리고 <br>풀 한 포기 꽃 한 그루 <br>살아남게 못했지만 <br>봄 태양과 여름 태양 <br>얼음덩이 다 녹이고 <br>기화요초 만발하는 <br>행복 낙원 만든다네 <br>캄캄한 죄악이 뒤덮고 <br>온 세상 다 썩히지만 <br>영락없이 찾아오는 <br>정의의 태양 빛 앞에 <br>다 사라지고 꽃들 핀다네 <br>에헤야 데헤야 경사로다 <br>사랑 행복 가득하여 <br>만물이 춤추며 <br>에헤야 데헤야 경사로다 <br>노래하는 영생 낙원 <br>천국 돌아왔다네 <br>누가 누가 낙원에서 <br>춤을 추며 살게 될까 <br>사랑의 모닥불을 <br>피워 올린 이들이지 <br>추위 속에 꽁꽁 얼어 <br>찾아오는 사람들을 <br>따스한 모닥불로 <br>우리 모두 녹여주세 <br>에헤야 데헤야 경사로다 <br>사랑 행복 가득하여 <br>만물이 춤추며 <br>에헤야 데헤야 경사로다 <br>노래하는 영생 낙원 <br>천국 돌아왔다네 <br>에헤야 데헤야 경사로다 <br>사랑 행복 가득하여 <br>만물이 춤추며 <br>에헤야 데헤야 경사로다 <br>노래하는 영생 낙원 <br>천국 돌아왔다네 <br>]]></content><category term="이태종" label="이태종"/><category term="낙원에서 노래할 사람들" label="낙원에서 노래할 사람들"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이태종/영원한_자유_율법/</id><title>이태종 - 영원한 자유 율법 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%83%9C%EC%A2%85/%EC%98%81%EC%9B%90%ED%95%9C_%EC%9E%90%EC%9C%A0_%EC%9C%A8%EB%B2%95/" title="이태종 - 영원한 자유 율법 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[영원한 자유율법 <br>십계 자유 율법 <br>얼마나 고귀하고 <br>소중한 자유인가 <br>십계 하나님을 <br>잃었던 육천년 <br>얼마나 두렵고 <br>무서운 속박인가 <br>우리의 해방이요 <br>우리의 행복이라 <br>얼마나 고귀한 <br>친아빠의 사랑인가 <br>영원한 자유율법 <br>십계 자유율법 <br>사랑의 자유율법은 <br>우리의 춤과 노래라 <br>영원한 자유율법 <br>영원한 사랑 율법 <br>이 사랑을 수호하는 <br>우주 십계 <br>별님들 되자 <br>회복된 십계 율법 <br>다시 찾은 십계의 행복 <br>두 번 다시 잃지 않도록 <br>순리대로 살아가자 <br>얼마나 자유가 없는 <br>고통과 죽음인가 <br>우리의 평화의 나라 <br>영원히 수호하자 <br>영원한 자유율법 <br>십계 자유 율법 <br>사랑의 자유율법은 <br>우리의 춤과 노래라 <br>]]></content><category term="이태종" label="이태종"/><category term="영원한 자유 율법" label="영원한 자유 율법"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이태종/진리는_승리한다/</id><title>이태종 - 진리는 승리한다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%83%9C%EC%A2%85/%EC%A7%84%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_%EC%8A%B9%EB%A6%AC%ED%95%9C%EB%8B%A4/" title="이태종 - 진리는 승리한다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[진리는 빛났다 <br>진리는 이겼다 <br>진리는 가릴 수 없다 <br>진리는 힘차게 비추인다 <br>진리와 싸울 자 그 누구뇨 <br>진리와 겨룰 자 나오라 <br>거짓 교회 조직이냐 <br>세상 나라 권세냐 <br>너희 깃발 내세우라 <br>전능하신 여호와 <br>힘센 그 빛 앞에서 <br>그들은 참패했네 <br>진리는 승리한다 <br>진리는 빛났다 <br>진리는 이겼다 <br>진리는 가릴 수 없다 <br>진리는 힘차게 비추인다 <br>진리와 싸울 자 그 누구뇨 <br>진리와 겨룰 자 나오라 <br>원수 핍박 조롱이냐 <br>노한 추방 죽음이냐 <br>그들은 엎어졌네 <br>전능하신 여호와 <br>힘센 그 빛 앞에서 <br>그들은 참패했네 <br>진리는 승리한다 <br>진리와 싸울 자 그 누구뇨 <br>진리와 겨룰 자 나오라 <br>원수 핍박 조롱이냐 <br>노한 추방 죽음이냐 <br>그들은 엎어졌네 <br>전능하신 여호와 <br>힘센 그 빛 앞에서 <br>그들은 참패했네 <br>진리는 승리한다 <br>]]></content><category term="이태종" label="이태종"/><category term="진리는 승리한다" label="진리는 승리한다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이태종/아들에게_주는_좌우명/</id><title>이태종 - 아들에게 주는 좌우명 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%83%9C%EC%A2%85/%EC%95%84%EB%93%A4%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_%EC%A3%BC%EB%8A%94_%EC%A2%8C%EC%9A%B0%EB%AA%85/" title="이태종 - 아들에게 주는 좌우명 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑하는 <br>내 아들아 <br>너는 어디를 가든지 <br>명예나 은총을 <br>택하지 말라 <br>아름다움보다는 <br>초라함이 나으며 <br>강함보단 <br>약함이 나으니라 <br>부보다는 가난이 <br>영광보다는 그늘이 <br>유명보다는 무명이 <br>나으니라 <br>너는 평생 동안 <br>명심하여 <br>이 길을 걸어가라 <br>배부른 죄인보다 <br>궁핍한 의인이 돼라 <br>사랑하는 내 아들아 <br>이것이 천상천하에 <br>가장 평안한 길이요 <br>생명의 길이니라 <br>사랑하는 <br>내 아들아 <br>너는 어디를 가든지 <br>칭찬이나 높음을 <br>택하지 말라 <br>총명함보다는 <br>어리석음이 나으며 <br>보좌보단 의자가 <br>나으니라 <br>영화로움보다는 <br>고요한 도가 나으며 <br>궁전보다는 <br>초야가 나으니라 <br>너는 평생 동안 <br>명심하여 <br>이 길을 걸어가라 <br>배부른 죄인보다 <br>궁핍한 의인이 돼라 <br>사랑하는 내 아들아 <br>이것이 천상천하에 <br>가장 평안한 길이요 <br>생명의 길이니라 <br>이것이 천상천하에 <br>가장 행복한 길이요 <br>생명의 길이니라 <br>]]></content><category term="이태종" label="이태종"/><category term="아들에게 주는 좌우명" label="아들에게 주는 좌우명"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이태종/나_영광_없는_용사_되리/</id><title>이태종 - 나 영광 없는 용사 되리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%83%9C%EC%A2%85/%EB%82%98_%EC%98%81%EA%B4%91_%EC%97%86%EB%8A%94_%EC%9A%A9%EC%82%AC_%EB%90%98%EB%A6%AC/" title="이태종 - 나 영광 없는 용사 되리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 영광 없는 <br>용사 되리 용사 되리 <br>지구 사막 <br>광풍 불어오든지 <br>원수들이 몰려와도 <br>생수 끊겨도 <br>전진 전진 <br>나 오직 하늘 대명 <br>완수키 위해 <br>오직 전진 전진 <br>사단 머리 <br>부수기 위해 <br>목적지를 행군하노라 <br>나 또한 영광 없는 <br>용사 되리 <br>이제 가노라 <br>하늘의 대명 받은 <br>오직 한 몸 용사 되리 <br>아무도 알아주는 <br>자가 없어도 <br>상과 훈장 없어도 <br>오직 목적 <br>하늘 대명 <br>전진 전진 <br>모래바람 휘날리는 <br>사막 행군하노라 <br>전진 전진 <br>임무 완수 후엔 <br>이 목숨 지구 사막에 <br>던지리니 <br>나 또한 영광 없는 <br>용사 되리 <br>사단 머리 부수기 위해 <br>목적지를 행군하노라 <br>나 또한 영광 없는 <br>용사 되리 <br>이제 가노라 <br>이제 가노라 <br>이제 가노라 <br>]]></content><category term="이태종" label="이태종"/><category term="나 영광 없는 용사 되리" label="나 영광 없는 용사 되리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이태종/선구자들_가신_길/</id><title>이태종 - 선구자들 가신 길 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%83%9C%EC%A2%85/%EC%84%A0%EA%B5%AC%EC%9E%90%EB%93%A4_%EA%B0%80%EC%8B%A0_%EA%B8%B8/" title="이태종 - 선구자들 가신 길 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[억울해도 <br>울지 말라 <br>원통해도 통곡 말라 <br>원망스러워도 <br>불평하지 말라 <br>가슴이 파열돼도 <br>신음하지 말라 <br>외롭고 서러워도 <br>울진 말라 <br>이 모든 일은 <br>다 먼저 가신 <br>우리 주님 <br>선배 형님들 <br>가신 길이기에 <br>영광으로 알고 <br>기뻐하며 걸어가라 <br>억울해도 울지 말라 <br>원통해도 통곡 말라 <br>원망스러워도 <br>불평하지 말라 <br>가슴이 파열돼도 <br>신음하지 말라 <br>외롭고 서러워도 <br>울진 말라 <br>세상이 <br>모르는 길 <br>선구자들 <br>가신 이 길 <br>악인들이 <br>갈 수 없는 <br>은총의 길 <br>영광 찬양하면서 <br>걸어가라 특별한 길 <br>선구자들 가신 이 길 <br>이 모든 일은 <br>다 먼저 가신 <br>우리 주님 <br>선배 형님들 <br>가신 길이기에 <br>영광으로 알고 <br>기뻐하며 걸어가라 <br>억울해도 울지 말라 <br>원통해도 통곡 말라 <br>원망스러워도 <br>불평하지 말라 <br>가슴이 파열돼도 <br>신음하지 말라 <br>외롭고 서러워도 <br>울진 말라 <br>억울해도 울지 말라 <br>원통해도 통곡 말라 <br>원망스러워도 <br>불평하지 말라 <br>가슴이 파열돼도 <br>신음하지 말라 <br>외롭고 서러워도 <br>울진 말라 <br>억울해도 울지 말라 <br>원통해도 통곡 말라 <br>원망스러워도 <br>불평하지 말라 <br>가슴이 파열돼도 <br>신음하지 말라 <br>외롭고 서러워도 <br>울진 말라 <br>]]></content><category term="이태종" label="이태종"/><category term="선구자들 가신 길" label="선구자들 가신 길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이태종/구속의_계획/</id><title>이태종 - 구속의 계획 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%83%9C%EC%A2%85/%EA%B5%AC%EC%86%8D%EC%9D%98_%EA%B3%84%ED%9A%8D/" title="이태종 - 구속의 계획 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[태초에 <br>비밀 있었으니 <br>창세에 나타났느니라 <br>아담과 하와를 <br>조성하실 때에 <br>구속의 계획 <br>시작되었다 <br>천지와 만물이 <br>다 이루니라 <br>선포하신 후에 <br>사람을 낳으시고 <br>생육하고 번성하라 <br>명하시니라 <br>너희는 지존자의 <br>친자녀들이라 <br>인간은 하나님의 <br>대를 잇기 위해 <br>낳으신 바 되었노라 <br>이를 위해 <br>주님 오셨다 <br>이것이 오메가 <br>인자 하나님의 <br>구속의 십자가 위에 <br>펼쳐진 새 빛이라 <br>들으라 <br>너는 내 아들이다 <br>내가 너를 <br>친히 낳았다 <br>너희는 신들이요 <br>지존자의 아들들이라 <br>나 여호와의 말이니라 <br>하늘 위에 땅 위에 <br>드넓은 바닷속에 <br>나는 새들 뛰는 동물 <br>헤엄치는 물고기들 <br>천연계를 바라보라 <br>아름다운 순리 따라 <br>어미 닮은 씨 퍼지듯 <br>신들의 순리 따라 <br>아름답게 자유롭게 <br>십계 위를 걸어갈 때 <br>하늘의 대를 이을 <br>거룩한 씨 낳으리라 <br>이것이 오메가 <br>인자 하나님의 <br>구속의 십자가 위에 <br>펼쳐진 새 빛이라 <br>태초에 비밀 있었으니 <br>현세에 나타났느니라 <br>태초에 비밀 있었으니 <br>현세에 나타났느니라 <br>창세에 빛이 있었으니 <br>현세에 나타났느니라 <br>]]></content><category term="이태종" label="이태종"/><category term="구속의 계획" label="구속의 계획"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Struts/One_Night_Only/</id><title>The_Struts - One Night Only - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Struts/One_Night_Only/" title="The_Struts - One Night Only - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll give you one night only <br>For your eyes only <br>Oh, oh, oh <br><br>Like an eagle in the sky <br>You can't control it <br>There's a magic in my eyes <br>And I can't stop it burning down <br>On the edge of tonight <br>Cause tomorrow we'll be owning the world <br><br>All my scars have got a tune <br>There's a fire in my heart <br>And I can't stop it burning down <br>On the edge of tonight <br>Cause tomorrow we'll be ruling the world <br><br>And you know like pure, white gold <br>I'll give you one night only <br>For your eyes only <br>If entertaining's what you want <br>Then honey, I'm the best <br>I know that we're together <br>For all your pleasure <br>Forever, forever, forever <br>This is how we burn <br><br>Yeah I wanna run into the night <br>Supersonic <br>Like a dragon in the sky <br>Riding on it <br>Screaming loud <br>At the edge of tonight <br>Cause tomorrow we'll be ruling the world <br><br>On the run, I'm in the mood <br>There's a bullet in the gun <br>And I'm gonna shoot it above the clouds <br>I'll get it tonight <br>Cause tomorrow we'll be ruling the world <br><br>You know like pure, white gold <br>I'll give you one night only <br>For your eyes only <br>If entertaining's what you want <br>Then honey, I'm the best <br>I know that we're together <br>For all your pleasure <br>Forever, forever, forever <br>This is how we burn <br><br>This is how we burn <br>This is how we burn <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah <br><br>I just wanna ride <br>I just wanna turn and face the strange <br>Sometimes the fear in us <br>Turns to the best of us <br><br>I just wanna have some fun <br>I just wanna throw that one, two punch <br>Sometimes the tear in us <br>Turns to the best of us <br><br>I'll give you one night only <br>For your eyes only <br>If entertaining's what you want <br>Then honey, I'm the best <br><br>I'll give you one night only <br>For your eyes only <br>If entertaining's what you want <br>Then honey, I'm the best <br>I know that we're together <br>For all your pleasure <br>Forever, forever, forever <br>This is how we burn <br><br>This is how we burn <br>This is how we burn]]></content><category term="The Struts" label="The Struts"/><category term="One Night Only" label="One Night Only"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/When_Your_Light_Goes_Out_Feat_Lianne_La_Havas/</id><title>Mr_Jukes - When Your Light Goes Out (Feat. Lianne La Havas) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/When_Your_Light_Goes_Out_Feat_Lianne_La_Havas/" title="Mr_Jukes - When Your Light Goes Out (Feat. Lianne La Havas) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wondering what you’ve done <br>Run, run, run <br>You've done it all wrong <br><br>Make it through the night <br>You just might <br>But they'll get you alright <br>They'll see you go <br><br>When the fire goes down, you're gasping now <br>And the smoke in your throat is singing out <br>They say "na na na" over and over <br>They say "na na na" when your world is blacking out <br><br>If the song you sung ain't right <br>Then you'll get hung out to dry <br><br>When they find you kneeling down <br>It won't be enough <br>They'll just write you off <br><br>When the rain comes down and hailstone round <br>And the groans from your bones are singing out <br><br>When your light goes out <br>when your light goes out <br>when your light goes out <br>when your light goes out <br><br>They say "na nana" <br>When your world is over]]></content><category term="Mr Jukes" label="Mr Jukes"/><category term="When Your Light Goes Out (Feat. Lianne La Havas)" label="When Your Light Goes Out (Feat. Lianne La Havas)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Tears_Feat_Alexandria/</id><title>Mr_Jukes - Tears (Feat. Alexandria) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Tears_Feat_Alexandria/" title="Mr_Jukes - Tears (Feat. Alexandria) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I keep on falling in love <br>You keep on falling in trouble <br>I keep on falling in love <br>With you <br>You know it’s hard when love can <br>Get in your mind and tell you this is one of a kind <br>You know that I hide them, dry them <br>You won’t find them <br>Not one tear will fall from my eye <br>You know that I hide them, dry them <br>But if I’m crying surely this is one of a kind <br>I keep on falling in love <br>You keep on falling in trouble <br>I keep on falling in love <br>With you <br>Falling in love with you <br>You keep on falling <br>You keep on falling <br>You keep on falling <br>You keep on falling <br>You keep on falling <br>You keep on falling in love <br>You know that I hide them, dry them <br>You won’t find them <br>Not one tear will fall from my eye <br>You know that I hide them, dry them <br>But if I’m crying surely this is one of a kind]]></content><category term="Mr Jukes" label="Mr Jukes"/><category term="Tears (Feat. Alexandria)" label="Tears (Feat. Alexandria)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Magic/</id><title>Mr_Jukes - Magic - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Magic/" title="Mr_Jukes - Magic - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All the walls are painted white <br>Faded light <br>Faded light <br><br>You wandered through the shades of night <br>Now take flight <br>Take flight <br><br>And there's the wind that fills your sail <br>I won't tell <br>I won't tell <br>So draw the blast, draw the veil <br>Now exhale <br>Exhale <br><br>Try to find the word to say <br>But it's all magic <br>All the way <br>Make the last step worth the climb <br>'Cause it's all magic <br>All the time <br><br>'Cause it's all magic <br>All the time <br><br>Stop your sadness <br>Stop your madness <br>Automatically <br>Stop your sadness <br>Stop your madness <br>Automatically <br><br>Feral shrieking from the throne <br>Overtone <br>Overtone <br>No, don't let the spirit call <br>Let it grow <br>With a burned glow <br><br>Make the last step worth the climb <br>'Cause it's all magic <br><br>Stop your sadness <br>Stop your madness <br>Stop your sadness <br>Stop your madness <br>Automatically <br>Stop your sadness <br>Stop your madness <br>Stop your sadness <br>Stop your madness <br>Automatically]]></content><category term="Mr Jukes" label="Mr Jukes"/><category term="Magic" label="Magic"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/From_Golden_Stars_Comes_Silver_Dew_Feat_Lalah_Hathaway/</id><title>Mr_Jukes - From Golden Stars Comes Silver Dew (Feat. Lalah Hathaway) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/From_Golden_Stars_Comes_Silver_Dew_Feat_Lalah_Hathaway/" title="Mr_Jukes - From Golden Stars Comes Silver Dew (Feat. Lalah Hathaway) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sifting all the voices through the noises pink and white <br>Turning round the dial on this slow and silent night <br><br>For all you see <br>All you know <br>Mountain high and valley low <br>From golden stars comes silver dew <br>Every morning waking next to you <br><br>I'm a pop another one and weave the thread <br>Crossing all the wires that are rusting in my head <br><br>For all you see <br>All you know <br>Mountain high and valley low <br>From golden stars comes silver dew <br>Every morning waking next to you <br><br>Making up my bed <br>Count the days ahead <br>There's nowhere to hide <br><br>For all you see <br>All you know <br>Mountain high and valley low <br>From golden stars comes silver dew <br>Every morning waking next to you]]></content><category term="Mr Jukes" label="Mr Jukes"/><category term="From Golden Stars Comes Silver Dew (Feat. Lalah Hathaway)" label="From Golden Stars Comes Silver Dew (Feat. Lalah Hathaway)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Leap_Of_Faith_Feat_De_La_Soul__Horace_Andy/</id><title>Mr_Jukes - Leap Of Faith (Feat. De La Soul &amp; Horace Andy) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Leap_Of_Faith_Feat_De_La_Soul__Horace_Andy/" title="Mr_Jukes - Leap Of Faith (Feat. De La Soul &amp; Horace Andy) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You can be my girl <br>You can let it all, let it go <br>You can lift all lingering doubts <br>You can be all that ever counts <br><br>It's the taste, divine living that fit <br>For every cake candle that's lit <br>My wish, my blow, my gift <br>My prayer, my god, no myth <br>She want a man IN sleeves with no tricks <br>I wanna Gladys TONIGHT with no pips <br>We take a leap of faith towards this <br>Hoping for the blessings that come after bliss <br><br>You can be my girl <br>You can let it all, let it go <br>You can lift all lingering doubts <br>You can be all that ever counts <br><br>I'm on tour for some Toussant <br>That scrumptious blue funk <br>Madame you are tragically unreal <br>Or maybe it's mystic, that other dude missed it <br>Your true religion unbuckled my bible belt <br>The bridal shower felt like reign supreme <br>Shoot, she got me hook, my name's Kareem <br>Just ball courts, divorce court is no option <br>Our chemistry is but a strange concoction <br><br>You can be my girl <br>You can let-t-t-t-t-t <br>You can lift all lingering doubts <br>You can be all-l-l-l-l]]></content><category term="Mr Jukes" label="Mr Jukes"/><category term="Leap Of Faith (Feat. De La Soul &amp; Horace Andy)" label="Leap Of Faith (Feat. De La Soul &amp; Horace Andy)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Grant_Green_Feat_Charles_Bradley/</id><title>Mr_Jukes - Grant Green (Feat. Charles Bradley) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Grant_Green_Feat_Charles_Bradley/" title="Mr_Jukes - Grant Green (Feat. Charles Bradley) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I need you (baby) <br>You can make my heart go round <br>You, oh (alright) <br><br>You can make my heart go round <br><br>Why do I always have to wait? <br>Still your love's upstate <br>Putting my love up on a plate <br>Baby, can't you hear me say? <br><br>I need you (baby) <br>You can make my heart go round <br>You, oh (alright) <br>You can make my heart go round <br><br>Ever since you said goodbye <br>My tears never dried <br>It needs work to survive <br>I know true love never dies <br><br>You kept me by your side <br>You told me when I had to hide <br>Love me baby, feel my love <br>I can't go on this way <br>I won't go down into the light <br>If you can't go on, look at my love <br>My love grows strong <br>You kept me by your side <br>You told me when we had to hide <br><br>I know you're not this way <br>I know you're not this kind <br>Just take me high <br>Take me higher <br>Higher (higher) <br><br>I need you (baby) <br>You can make my heart go round <br>You (alright) <br>You can make my heart go round <br><br>Take me, take me, take me higher <br>Take me, take me, take me higher <br>Take me, take me, take me higher <br>Take me, take me, take me higher]]></content><category term="Mr Jukes" label="Mr Jukes"/><category term="Grant Green (Feat. Charles Bradley)" label="Grant Green (Feat. Charles Bradley)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Somebody_New_Feat_Elli_Ingram/</id><title>Mr_Jukes - Somebody New (Feat. Elli Ingram) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Somebody_New_Feat_Elli_Ingram/" title="Mr_Jukes - Somebody New (Feat. Elli Ingram) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She wants to wipe her tears on my cold shoulder <br>I've tried but i can't keep on telling her it's over <br><br>She's been crying almost for three months <br>Stuck in bed drinking red at home <br>All alone <br>All alone <br><br>But this shit it ain't my problem <br>He broke your heart - I'm sorry <br>But life ain't like no chocolate box <br><br>You got to quit acting so blue <br>And please stop dragging me down with you <br>Girl go find somebody new <br><br>She talks for hours says she'll never love again <br>I said you'll move on soon and forget this whole thing <br><br>But she's been crying almost for three months <br>Stuck in bed drinking red at home <br>All alone <br>All alone <br><br>But this shit it ain't my problem <br>He broke your heart - I'm sorry <br>But life ain't like no chocolate box <br><br>You got to quit acting so blue <br>And please stop dragging me down with you <br>Girl go find somebody new]]></content><category term="Mr Jukes" label="Mr Jukes"/><category term="Somebody New (Feat. Elli Ingram)" label="Somebody New (Feat. Elli Ingram)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Ruby/</id><title>Mr_Jukes - Ruby - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Ruby/" title="Mr_Jukes - Ruby - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh how you flow there through <br>The halls of heed and wade <br>The world was mad but you <br>Made all the curves look straight <br><br>Let them sing in ecstasy <br>Let them drink their wine <br>Let me sip the words between <br>Your ruby lips and mine <br><br>They can sing in ecstasy <br>They can drink their wine <br>But i won't let them pass between <br>Your ruby lips, oh so close to mine <br><br>Oh how I've waited for your fickle feet to stray <br>To leave the jagged sounds and hear them fade away <br>So take me up and I can see the clouds below <br>Oh how I long for change and you can make it so <br><br>Let them sing in ecstasy <br>Let them drink their wine <br>Let me sip the words between <br>Your ruby lips and mine <br><br>They can sing in ecstasy <br>They can drink their wine <br>But i won't let them pass between <br>Your ruby lips, oh so close to mine]]></content><category term="Mr Jukes" label="Mr Jukes"/><category term="Ruby" label="Ruby"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Angels___Your_Love_Feat_BJ_The_Chicago_Kid/</id><title>Mr_Jukes - Angels / Your Love (Feat. BJ The Chicago Kid) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Angels___Your_Love_Feat_BJ_The_Chicago_Kid/" title="Mr_Jukes - Angels / Your Love (Feat. BJ The Chicago Kid) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Scene on the moonlight, tales summer saw <br>Gazing at stars, I wake before the dawn <br>See all the angels, serve them above <br>If you are able, you could be my love <br><br>Scene on the moonlight, tales summer saw <br>Gazing at stars, I wake before the dawn <br>See all the angels, serve them above <br>If you are able, you could be my love <br><br>It makes no sense <br>Traveling the distance <br>To get so far <br>And something's been missing <br>I thought I was good <br>But I really wasn't living <br>'Cause I ain't have <br>The feeling you're giving <br><br>Thinking 'bout your love <br>(Now I feel it taking over me) <br>Thinking 'bout your love <br>(Now I feel it taking over me) <br>Thinking 'bout your love <br>(Now I feel it taking over me) <br>Baby, I need your love <br>(Now I feel it taking over me) <br>Your love <br>Yeah, my love <br>(Now I feel it taking over me) <br>Yeah, would you be my love? (my love?) <br>(Now I feel it taking over me) <br>My baby, b-baby, my love <br>(Now I feel it taking over me) <br>Yeah, would you be my love? (would you be) <br>(Now I feel it taking over me) <br>(Would you be) be my love, baby? <br>(Now I feel it taking over me) <br>Would you be my love? <br>(Now I feel it taking over me) <br>(Yeah, yeah) My love (be my love, baby) <br>(Now I feel it taking over me) <br>Ooh, would you be my love? <br>(Now I feel it taking over me) <br>My love?]]></content><category term="Mr Jukes" label="Mr Jukes"/><category term="Angels / Your Love (Feat. BJ The Chicago Kid)" label="Angels / Your Love (Feat. BJ The Chicago Kid)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Typhoon/</id><title>Mr_Jukes - Typhoon - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Jukes/Typhoon/" title="Mr_Jukes - Typhoon - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When a storm <br>Blows the sea <br>In the wind <br>You'll wait for me <br>And we'll meet <br>By the quay <br>Sad and sweet <br>And fair and free <br>So I go <br>And it blows <br>From a place <br>Where no man knows <br>And it holds <br>And it grips <br>And it sings <br>To sunken ships <br>So we ride <br>By the tide <br>To the fates <br>That hide inside <br>By the deep; <br>By the dive; <br>By the dark <br>I will survive <br>By the foam; <br>By the spray <br>I shall meet <br>The coming day <br><br>Man the oars <br>Beat the drums! <br>Hold tight <br>Here it comes <br><br>No more sweat <br>No more blood <br>Only God <br>Only God]]></content><category term="Mr Jukes" label="Mr Jukes"/><category term="Typhoon" label="Typhoon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Holy_Hoon/You_n_Me_Feat_선우정아/</id><title>Holy_Hoon - You n Me (Feat. 선우정아) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Holy_Hoon/You_n_Me_Feat_%EC%84%A0%EC%9A%B0%EC%A0%95%EC%95%84/" title="Holy_Hoon - You n Me (Feat. 선우정아) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[약속을 잃어버린 듯 <br>움직임이 없는 몸짓 <br>부서질 것 같은 얼굴 <br>어두움만 가득한데 <br>체념한 듯 내버려둔 <br>묶여있던 끈을 풀고 <br>Woo 내 손을 꼭 붙잡아 <br>Woo 숨을 크게 쉬고 <br>Everything is gonna be alright <br>Everything is gonna be OK <br>You n Me 너와 나 둘이서 <br>You n Me 더 뭐가 필요해 <br>하루 하루가 파라다이스 <br>밤하늘의 별처럼 <br>여름날 파도처럼 <br>알 수 없어도 <br>지금처럼이면 돼 <br>You n Me <br>Everything is gonna be <br>alright with You <br>Feeling You <br>I'm Feeling You <br>I'm Loving You <br>I'm Loving You <br>baby <br>한동안 그 자리에 <br>떨어지지 않는 걸음 <br>깊이를 모를 만큼 <br>쓸쓸함만 가득한데 <br>체념한 듯 내버려둔 <br>묶여있던 끈을 풀고 <br>Woo 내 손을 꼭 붙잡아 <br>Woo 숨을 크게 쉬고 <br>Everything is gonna be alright <br>Everything is gonna be OK <br>You n Me 너와 나 둘이서 <br>You n Me 더 뭐가 필요해 <br>하루 하루가 파라다이스 <br>밤하늘의 별처럼 <br>여름날 파도처럼 <br>알 수 없어도 <br>지금처럼이면 돼 <br>You n Me <br>Everything is gonna be <br>alright with You <br>지루했던 짙은 안개를 걷어내고 <br>그저 너 자신답게 가는 거야 <br>이 순간을 아름답게 <br>I wanna be make you feel my love <br>You n Me 너와 나 둘이서 <br>You n Me 더 뭐가 필요해 <br>You n Me 너와 나 둘이서 <br>You n Me 더 뭐가 필요해 <br>You n Me 너와 나 둘이서 <br>You n Me 더 뭐가 필요해 <br>You n Me 너와 나 둘이서 <br>You n Me 더 뭐가 필요해 <br>You n Me 너와 나 둘이서 <br>You n Me 더 뭐가 필요해 <br>You n Me 너와 나 둘이서 <br>You n Me 더 뭐가 필요해 <br>]]></content><category term="Holy Hoon" label="Holy Hoon"/><category term="You n Me (Feat. 선우정아)" label="You n Me (Feat. 선우정아)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Portugal_The_Man/Mornings/</id><title>Portugal_The_Man - Mornings - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:45:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:45:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Portugal_The_Man/Mornings/" title="Portugal_The_Man - Mornings - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Mornings go best with the sunrise <br>The sunrise I used to see <br>But will never see now <br>Even if I was waiting, we would just build it all up <br>We'd look around until we find, we find <br><br>The people found the mountain <br>Climbed up from that hole in the ground <br>Through the cracks in the sky <br>And threatened to fall <br>Still I don't believe, no I don't believe <br>And we'll be just fine, and we'll be just fine <br><br>The future was born with the sunrise <br>The sunrise that builds into days and even more years <br>And as it rolls burning <br>Burning up like the trails of the comets pulled tails <br>We'd look around until we find, we find <br><br>The people found the mountain <br>Climbed up from that hole in the ground <br>Through the cracks in the sky <br>And threatened to fall <br>Still I don't believe, I don't believe <br>And we'll be just fine, and we'll be just fine <br><br>As the sun it rose up from the belly of sea <br>Found his bedding of clouds where it hung for years <br>Still I don't believe <br>While colors rained and poured from the cotton bound pools and the drips <br>The drips stained us all, painted us all <br>Still I don't believe <br><br>The people found the mountain <br>Climbed up from that hole in the ground <br>Through the cracks in the sky <br>Still I don't believe, I don't believe <br><br>The people found the mountain <br>Climbed up from that hole in the ground <br>Through the cracks in the sky <br>And I don't believe, I don't believe <br>And we'll be just fine, we'll be just fine <br>We'll be just fine, I don't believe <br>No, I don't believe No, I don't believe]]></content><category term="Portugal. The Man" label="Portugal. The Man"/><category term="Mornings" label="Mornings"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Portugal_The_Man/Let_You_Down/</id><title>Portugal_The_Man - Let You Down - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:46:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:46:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Portugal_The_Man/Let_You_Down/" title="Portugal_The_Man - Let You Down - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's a shame that we need everything <br>Still everything I see, I need <br>Just go, please don't go <br>I, I want all, all, all that I see, see, see <br>Just go, please don't go <br>'Cause I'll only let you down <br>And I'll only let you down <br><br>And watch the world spinnin' 'round <br>And know that it's alright, alright, alright, alright, alright, alright <br>Just go, please don't go <br>'Cause I'll only let you down <br>And I'll only let you down <br>And watch the world <br>Watch the world <br>Watch the world <br>Watch the world <br>Watch the world <br>'Cause I'll only let you down <br>Only let you down <br>Let you down]]></content><category term="Portugal. The Man" label="Portugal. The Man"/><category term="Let You Down" label="Let You Down"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Portugal_The_Man/Everyone_Is_Golden/</id><title>Portugal_The_Man - Everyone Is Golden - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:46:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:46:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Portugal_The_Man/Everyone_Is_Golden/" title="Portugal_The_Man - Everyone Is Golden - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Diamonds shine like stars beneath the ground <br>Little rivers run in rings around the town <br>And everyone's a soldier just marching towards the ocean <br>Then we know we've packed up all we had to move from '93 <br><br>Everyone is golden, everyone is golden <br>And nobody will love them, and nobody will love them <br>Everyone is golden, everyone is golden <br>Everyone is golden, everyone is golden <br><br>And we took a train into the town <br>And stuck another needle in the ground <br>If we never get another sound <br>Then we know we've packed up all we had to move from '93 <br><br>Everyone is golden, everyone is golden <br>Nobody will love them, nobody will love them <br>Everyone is golden, everyone is golden <br>Everyone is golden, everyone is golden <br><br>And they can't lift you up <br>We gathered around the school <br>To hear just what they found <br>But they told us they had tried <br>Still the little boy had died <br><br>We gathered around to hear just what they'd done <br>Yeah, they shine like stars under the ground <br>And everyone's a soldier just marching towards the ocean <br>Then we know we've packed up all we had to move from '93 <br><br>Everyone is golden, everyone is golden <br>Nobody will love them, nobody will love them <br>Everyone is golden, everyone is golden <br>Everyone is golden, everyone is golden <br><br>Nobody will love you, nobody will love you <br>Nobody will love you, nobody will love you <br>Nobody will love you, nobody will love you <br>Nobody will love you, nobody will love you <br><br>Nobody will love you, nobody will love you <br>Nobody will love you, nobody will love you <br>Nobody will love you, nobody will love you <br>Nobody will love you, nobody will love you]]></content><category term="Portugal. The Man" label="Portugal. The Man"/><category term="Everyone Is Golden" label="Everyone Is Golden"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Portugal_The_Man/Do_You/</id><title>Portugal_The_Man - Do You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:46:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:46:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Portugal_The_Man/Do_You/" title="Portugal_The_Man - Do You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do you understand the people that we are <br>Do you believe right from the start <br>Do you see that everybody needs <br>Do you feel when you're burning in that hell <br>Yeah, we can make it here <br><br>Did you find your fear <br>Did you find your fear <br>Did you find your fear <br>Did you find your fear <br><br>Do you fear the marching of the lamb <br>Do you believe there is loyalty in man <br>Do you see when others turn away <br>Do you hear it swimming in that head <br>Yeah, we can make it here <br><br>Did you find your fear <br>Did you find your fear <br>Did you find your fear <br>Did you find your fear <br><br>He came down from the moon and rained down on all of us <br>Rained down on all of us and everyone was saved <br>He fell into the sea just to swim around <br>Just to feel the clouds on the way down <br>And everyone was saved <br>And everyone was saved <br>And everyone was saved <br><br>Did you find your fear <br>Did you find your fear <br>Did you find your fear <br>Did you find your fear]]></content><category term="Portugal. The Man" label="Portugal. The Man"/><category term="Do You" label="Do You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Portugal_The_Man/Guns_And_Dogs/</id><title>Portugal_The_Man - Guns And Dogs - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:46:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:46:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Portugal_The_Man/Guns_And_Dogs/" title="Portugal_The_Man - Guns And Dogs - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We took a trip down in '87 <br>We were looking for a place where we don't fear heaven <br>Yeah, we got some guns, got some dogs <br>But just like them dogs, well those guns just get bigger <br><br>Looking to the town to show us what they got <br>We'll take it to the cabin and we'll show ya what we got <br>We got space to do what you please <br>If you'll ever make it out <br><br>If I never stand at another corner trying hard to be a father <br>Let's be, let's be love <br>If I never need again I'll find that sleep again <br>Let's be, let's be love <br>We took a trip down in '87 <br>We were looking for a place where we don't need heaven <br>Oh, once you crawl in you'll never come back again <br>Oh, once you crawl in you'll never come back again <br><br>If I never stand at another corner trying hard to be a father <br>Let's be, let's be love <br>If I never need again I'll find that sleep again <br>Let's be, let's be love <br><br>Though I never pray God reigns today <br>Though I never pray God reigns today <br>Though I never pray God reigns today <br>Though I never pray God reigns today <br><br>And if you catch us coming up around the bend <br>And if we step a little higher will we find it then <br>There's gotta be something roaming up around the bend <br><br>Oh, once you crawl in you'll never come back again <br>Oh, once you crawl in you'll never come back again <br><br>Though I never pray God reigns today <br>Though I never pray God reigns today <br>Though I never pray God reigns today <br>Though I never pray God reigns today]]></content><category term="Portugal. The Man" label="Portugal. The Man"/><category term="Guns And Dogs" label="Guns And Dogs"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Portugal_The_Man/The_Woods/</id><title>Portugal_The_Man - The Woods - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T15:46:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T15:46:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Portugal_The_Man/The_Woods/" title="Portugal_The_Man - The Woods - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I lived in the woods <br>When I lived in the woods <br>When I lived in the woods <br>Everything was alright <br>Everything, everything was alright <br>Never knew where we are <br>Never needed enough <br>Never need enough, just where we are <br>Everything was alright <br>All the people, all the people were living the light <br><br>As I breathe in time <br>To be where I was <br>And if I need you <br>Baby, give me all your love <br>If we need <br>To find the time <br>We'll never see <br>All your love <br><br>If you find yourself in need <br>If we gotta go then bring along some company <br>And if you find yourself alone <br>If we got it all then we got just what we need <br><br>Why Why Why <br><br>As I breathe in time <br>To be where I was <br>And if I need you <br>Baby, give me all your love <br>If we need <br>To find the time <br>We'll never see <br>All your love <br><br>When I lived in the woods <br>When I lived in the woods <br>When I lived in the woods <br>Everything was alright <br>Everything, everybody was alright <br>Well ya gotta get out, gotta make some money <br>Baby, gotta grow <br>Baby, gotta get bigger <br>All the people will lift it up <br>All the people, all the people will help you out <br><br>As I breathe in time <br>To be where I was <br>And if I need you <br>Baby, give me all your love <br>If we need <br>To find the time <br>We'll never see <br>All your love <br><br>Why Why Why]]></content><category term="Portugal. The Man" label="Portugal. The Man"/><category term="The Woods" label="The Woods"/></entry></feed>