<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:51:22+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/악동뮤지션/Be_With_You/</id><title>악동뮤지션 - Be With You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:33:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:33:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%85%EB%8F%99%EB%AE%A4%EC%A7%80%EC%85%98/Be_With_You/" title="악동뮤지션 - Be With You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[괜시리 웃음이나 또 생각이나 <br>사랑이란게 비슷한걸까 <br>낮의 해와 밤의 달도 <br>내맘을 모르죠 be with you <br>cry cry don’t ever cry <br>슬프지않길 바래 baby <br>사랑 이제야 알겠죠 <br>fly fly forever fly <br>너와 둘이 온종일 평생 <br>I want you I want your love <br>그대 맘 속엔 내가 없나요 <br>나 혼자 쉽게 될 일이라면 <br>마음 졸이며 애태우지 않고 <br>내꺼인듯 하고 싶은데 <br>with you <br>어색하게 걸어 가긴 먼거리 <br>우리 사이에 적당한 보폭은 <br>얼마정도일까 <br>너와 내눈이 마주친 그순간 <br>부터 난 고민하는걸 매일밤 <br>어떡하면 널 헷갈리지 않게 할까 <br>괜시리 웃음이나 또 생각이나 <br>사랑이란게 비슷한걸까 <br>낮의 해와 밤의 달도 <br>내맘을 모르죠 be with you <br>둘만의 시간이 <br>당장은 어쩔 줄 몰라도 <br>바로 내 앞에 그대 품이 있고 <br>내 꺼인듯 느끼고싶어 <br>널 보면 기침이 나온듯 <br>콜록했지만 실은 <br>웃음이 나온 걸 가린거야 <br>때때로 피곤해 <br>그런듯 하품했지만 <br>너무 좋아서 눈물이 흐른거야 <br>난 감출 수 없어 나의 감정 <br>왜냐면 난 너가 <br>너무나도 간절 하니까 <br>당당하게 우리가 <br>하나라고 말해줘 <br>Baby I just want to be your love <br>널 사랑할거야 <br>한 해를 보내고 <br>다시 오늘이 와도 wo <br>괜시리 웃음이 나 네 곁이라면 <br>가슴 아픈 날도 울고 싶지 않아 <br>눈 감고 기다릴거면 <br>먼저 다가가도 되죠 be with you <br>cry cry don’t ever cry <br>슬프지않길 바래 baby <br>사랑 이제야 알겠죠 <br>fly fly forever fly <br>너와 둘이 온종일 평생 <br>I want you I want your love <br>]]></content><category term="악동뮤지션" label="악동뮤지션"/><category term="Be With You" label="Be With You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정승환/바람/</id><title>정승환 - 바람 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:33:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:33:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%8A%B9%ED%99%98/%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C/" title="정승환 - 바람 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그 눈물은 가슴속에 숨기고 <br>추억들은 지워버려요 <br>끝내 못다할 인연 <br>여기서 멈춰둬요 <br>그리워 눈물로 산다 해도 우리 <br>흩어지는 바람같아서 <br>찾으려 해도 <br>찾을 수 없는 길 같아서 <br>멀어지는 인연은 <br>잡을 수가 없어서 <br>그대를 보내는 마음 <br>해가 지면 사라질 그대라서 <br>마음껏 눈에 담으려 해 <br>어둠이 내려오면 <br>잊어야 하는 사람 <br>이대로 떠나 보내야 하는거죠 <br>흩어지는 바람같아서 <br>찾으려 해도 <br>찾을 수 없는 길 같아서 <br>멀어지는 인연은 <br>잡을 수가 없어서 <br>그대를 보내는 마음 <br>그대 날 돌아서서 <br>떠나는 발걸음에 <br>참아왔던 눈물이 흘러내려 <br>떨어지는 꽃잎같아서 <br>가여운 사람 <br>이대로 끝내야만해서 <br>언젠가 우리 다시 <br>만나는 날이 오면 <br>그땐 헤어지지 마요 나의 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="정승환" label="정승환"/><category term="바람" label="바람"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이하이/내_사랑/</id><title>이하이 - 내 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:33:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:33:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4/%EB%82%B4_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="이하이 - 내 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[늘 멀리서 지켜만봤죠 <br>내 사랑인 것 같아서 그대 <br>같은 마음인 줄 알았죠 <br>다른 곳을 보았지만 <br>바람처럼 이 먼지처럼 <br>잡히지가 않아 <br>보이지않아 <br>Remember love you <br>I love you <br>사랑인 줄 믿었고 <br>운명이라 불렀죠 <br>Remember love you <br>I love you <br>그대 눈동자 속에 <br>내가 살고있는데 <br>나에게만 대답해줘요 <br>휘청이는 날 붙잡아줘요 <br>내 사랑 내 사랑 <br>내 마음의 창에 <br>내리는 눈물이 <br>대답해주네 <br>내게 이룰 수 없는 <br>인연이란 잊어야만 <br>하는 사람 <br>멀어지는 나의 사랑을 <br>보내줘야해요 <br>내가 아니니 <br>Remember love you <br>I love you <br>사랑인 줄 믿었고 <br>운명이라 불렀죠 <br>Remember love you <br>I love you <br>그대 눈동자 속에 <br>내가 살고있는데 <br>나에게만 대답해줘요 <br>휘청이는 날 붙잡아줘요 <br>내 사랑 내 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="이하이" label="이하이"/><category term="내 사랑" label="내 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임선혜/꼭_돌아오리/</id><title>임선혜 - 꼭 돌아오리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:33:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:33:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%84%A0%ED%98%9C/%EA%BC%AD_%EB%8F%8C%EC%95%84%EC%98%A4%EB%A6%AC/" title="임선혜 - 꼭 돌아오리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[계절에 흩날려 <br>떨어진 꽃잎은 <br>홀로 남아 외로워 <br>슬프도록 <br>별들이 떠나간 <br>하늘은 서글퍼 <br>내리는 빗물처럼 <br>울고만 있네 <br>꽃들은 피고 또 지듯 <br>보내는 마음 <br>바람에 전해주오 <br>첫눈이 내리면 <br>이뤄지는 소원 <br>그 말을 난 믿어요 <br>간절한 소원 <br>애달픈 나의 마음을 <br>그대 안다면 <br>다시 꼭 돌아오리 <br>]]></content><category term="임선혜" label="임선혜"/><category term="꼭 돌아오리" label="꼭 돌아오리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SG_워너비/고백합니다/</id><title>SG 워너비 - 고백합니다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:33:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:33:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SG_%EC%9B%8C%EB%84%88%EB%B9%84/%EA%B3%A0%EB%B0%B1%ED%95%A9%EB%8B%88%EB%8B%A4/" title="SG 워너비 - 고백합니다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 바람이 되어 그댈 감싸안을게 <br>하루만 오늘만 내 곁에 머물러줘 <br>난 달빛이 되어 환하게 비춰줄게 <br>어디로든 어디에 있든 갈게 <br>사랑합니다 그댈 <br>그저 원하고 원합니다 <br>멀리서만 바라보다 <br>또 돌아섰지만 <br>고백합니다 그대에게 <br>온 힘을 다해서 <br>my love my love my love <br>나의 말 들리나요 그대 <br>해가 뜨고 지듯 나 그댈 사랑함은 <br>나에게 나에겐 너무나 당연한데 <br>하루를 살아도 그대 하나만 보는 <br>바보니까 난 그대뿐이니까 <br>사랑합니다 그댈 <br>그저 원하고 원합니다 <br>멀리서만 바라보다 <br>또 돌아섰지만 <br>고백합니다 그대에게 <br>온 힘을 다해서 <br>my love my love my love <br>나의 말 들리나요 그대 <br>그대 외롭고 지쳐서 무너질때 <br>내가 곁에서 지켜줄게 <br>그대가 웃도록 <br>기억하나요 그대 <br>처음 만났던 그날부터 <br>내 가슴은 그댈 향해 <br>뛰고 있었단걸 <br>고백합니다 그대에게 <br>온 힘을 다해서 <br>my love my love my love <br>나의 말 들리나요 그대 <br>]]></content><category term="SG 워너비" label="SG 워너비"/><category term="고백합니다" label="고백합니다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백아연/사랑인_듯_아닌_듯/</id><title>백아연 - 사랑인 듯 아닌 듯 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:33:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:33:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%EC%95%84%EC%97%B0/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B8_%EB%93%AF_%EC%95%84%EB%8B%8C_%EB%93%AF/" title="백아연 - 사랑인 듯 아닌 듯 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어쩌면 어쩌다 말하지 못한 <br>감춰놓은 비밀이 있어 <br>어디서 어떻게 시작된 건지 <br>기억 못해도 너를 향해있어 <br>너도 나와 같은 <br>생각을 하고 있는지 <br>그게 제일 궁금해 지금도 난 <br>사랑인 듯 아닌 듯 헷갈려 한다면 <br>지금 나를 안아줘 고민없이 <br>가슴이 뛴다면 사랑이 맞아 <br>그땐 고백해줄래 <br>니 곁에 니 옆에 내가 있는데 <br>왜 넌 모른 척 나를 피해가니 <br>들켜버릴까봐 <br>가슴을 치고 있었어 <br>두근거리는 이 심장소리 <br>사랑인 듯 아닌 듯 헷갈려 한다면 <br>지금 나를 안아줘 고민없이 <br>가슴이 뛴다면 사랑이 맞아 <br>그땐 고백해줄래 <br>우리 서로 멀리 돌아온 만큼 <br>널 사랑하고 싶은데 <br>저 파란 하늘 위로 <br>내 마음을 고백해볼까 <br>숨겨왔던 내 사랑을 I love you <br>사랑인 듯 아닌 듯 헷갈려 한다면 <br>지금 나를 안아줘 고민없이 <br>가슴이 뛴다면 사랑이 맞아 <br>그땐 고백해줄래 <br>너도 바로 나라고 <br>]]></content><category term="백아연" label="백아연"/><category term="사랑인 듯 아닌 듯" label="사랑인 듯 아닌 듯"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/에픽하이_EPIK_HIGH/내_마음_들리나요_Feat_이하이/</id><title>에픽하이 (EPIK HIGH) - 내 마음 들리나요 (Feat. 이하이) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:33:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:33:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%90%ED%94%BD%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4_EPIK_HIGH/%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C_%EB%93%A4%EB%A6%AC%EB%82%98%EC%9A%94_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4/" title="에픽하이 (EPIK HIGH) - 내 마음 들리나요 (Feat. 이하이) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대 듣고 있나요 <br>나의 목소리 그댈 향한 이고백 <br>지금 듣고 있나요 <br>이런 내 마음 들리나요 <br>창가에 떨어지는 빗방울처럼 <br>내 맘속에 물들어가는 너 <br>I need u I need u I miss u <br>널 잊으려 말을 아끼다가 <br>정말 잊었다며 결국 너 얘기 <br>잊으려 하고 있었다는 것도 <br>잊혀져야 잊은거겠지 <br>you gotta give me time <br>I ain’t perfect <br>but I’m tryin’ to <br>erase you perfectly <br>돌이키려하면 너무 먼데 <br>돌아보면 넌 언제나 어깨 뒤 <br>I know <br>지울수는 없겠지 미완한 나에게 <br>그 추억이 너무 완벽했기에 <br>But I try again <br>사랑에 빠질 때보다 그 사랑에서 <br>빠져나오는 게 훨씬 어렵군 <br>you make me live and die again <br>I’m not alive without you <br>I’m not alive without you <br>You know I'd die without you <br>잊지말아요 <br>그대 듣고 있나요 <br>나의 목소리 그댈 향한 이고백 <br>지금 듣고 있나요 <br>이런 내 마음 들리나요 <br>창가에 떨어지는 빗방울처럼 <br>내 맘속에 물들어가는 너 <br>I need u I need u I miss u <br>한 여름밤의 장마처럼 <br>쏟아져 내리고 다시 오려나봐 <br>기억의 소나기 <br>너에겐 우산이 필요할 것 같은데 <br>걱정이 되네 많이 창 밖으로 보여 <br>어딘가로 바삐 달리는 <br>차들의 경망스런 불빛 <br>내 목적지는 <br>묻지 않아도 알겠지만 <br>언제나 두 손에 잡히던 <br>네 모든 것들이 <br>다 투명하게 번지고 <br>눈물에 눈이 흐려 <br>돌아보면 제자리 <br>늘 맘이 무거워서 <br>내 이별은 발걸음이 느려 <br>모든 걸 되돌릴 수 없다면 <br>받아들이는 것도 방법이겠지만 <br>난 여기 서 있어 난 여전히 서 있어 <br>그대 듣고 있나요 <br>나의 목소리 그댈 향한 이고백 <br>지금 듣고 있나요 <br>이런 내 마음 들리나요 <br>창가에 떨어지는 빗방울처럼 <br>내 맘속에 물들어가는 너 <br>I need u I need u I miss u <br>Don’t forget me ever Never ever <br>Don’t forget me ever Never ever <br>Never ever girl <br>Don’t forget me ever Never ever <br>Don’t forget me ever Never ever <br>나를 <br>]]></content><category term="에픽하이 (EPIK HIGH)" label="에픽하이 (EPIK HIGH)"/><category term="내 마음 들리나요 (Feat. 이하이)" label="내 마음 들리나요 (Feat. 이하이)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태연_TAEYEON/All_With_You/</id><title>태연 (TAEYEON) - All With You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:33:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:33:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%B0_TAEYEON/All_With_You/" title="태연 (TAEYEON) - All With You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 그대 곁에 있어서 <br>행복합니다 <br>내가 그대 곁에 있어서 <br>꿈을 꿉니다 <br>내가 그대 곁에 있어서 <br>웃을 수 있습니다 <br>내 사람이길 또 기도합니다 <br>내 맘이 보여서 <br>내 진심이 느껴진다면 <br>내 맘이 보여서 <br>내게 오는 길 찾는다면 <br>나의 모든 마음 주고 싶어 <br>나의 곁에 그대 <br>영원토록 있는다면 <br>그대 나의 곁에 있어서 <br>고맙습니다 <br>그대 나의 곁에 있어서 <br>따뜻합니다 <br>그대 나의 곁에 있어서 <br>다시 힘을 냅니다 <br>바라만봐도 눈물이 납니다 <br>내 맘이 보여서 <br>내 진심이 느껴진다면 <br>내 맘이 보여서 <br>내게 오는 길 찾는다면 <br>나의 모든 마음 주고 싶어 <br>나의 곁에 그대 <br>영원토록 있는다면 <br>세상에 지쳐가도 <br>우리 서로 곁에 항상 <br>옆에 잡은 그 손 놓지마 <br>마지막 사랑을 <br>그댈 위해 쓰고 싶은데 <br>마지막 운명이 <br>그대라면 행복할텐데 <br>나의 모든 마음 주고 싶어 <br>나의 곁에 그대 <br>영원토록 있는다면 <br>All With You All With You <br>]]></content><category term="태연 (TAEYEON)" label="태연 (TAEYEON)"/><category term="All With You" label="All With You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/다비치/그대를_잊는다는건/</id><title>다비치 - 그대를 잊는다는건 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:33:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:33:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EB%B9%84%EC%B9%98/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9E%8A%EB%8A%94%EB%8B%A4%EB%8A%94%EA%B1%B4/" title="다비치 - 그대를 잊는다는건 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 숨을 꾹 참고 <br>그대를 바라보네요 <br>세상이 꼭 멈춘것처럼 <br>스쳐 지나가는 바람처럼 <br>나를 못본다해도 <br>내마음은 그대를 향하네 <br>그댈 사랑하는건 <br>참 아픈일이야 <br>비우지 못할 마음이란건 <br>참 슬픈일이야 <br>그대여 우 잊지는 말아요 <br>멈춰지지않는 사랑 <br>그대의 눈동자 <br>날 바라보고있네요 <br>내 맘을 다 아는 것처럼 <br>멀어지려해도 기억들이 <br>우리를 묻고있죠 <br>다른 공간 속에 나 있어도 <br>그댈 사랑하는건 <br>참 아픈일이야 <br>비우지못할 마음이란건 <br>참 슬픈일이야 <br>그대여 우 잊지는 말아요 <br>멈춰지지 않는 사랑 <br>조금 늦어도 괜찮아요 <br>운명이라면 <br>우리 다시 만나질텐데 <br>그댈 잊는다는건 <br>어려운일이야 <br>또 뒤돌아서 울어버리는 <br>내 슬픈 꿈이야 <br>언젠가 우 마음껏 그대를 <br>사랑하게 되길 바래 <br>]]></content><category term="다비치" label="다비치"/><category term="그대를 잊는다는건" label="그대를 잊는다는건"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아이오아이_IOI/사랑해_기억해/</id><title>아이오아이 (I.O.I) - 사랑해 기억해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:33:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:33:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%98%A4%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4_IOI/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4_%EA%B8%B0%EC%96%B5%ED%95%B4/" title="아이오아이 (I.O.I) - 사랑해 기억해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너의 미소 너의 향기까지 <br>항상 기다려왔죠 손꼽아 왔죠 <br>어느 곳에 있다해도 <br>난 그대뿐이죠 <br>무엇을 꿈꿔왔는지 <br>내가 바랬는지 알고 있나요 <br>그댄 모르죠 <br>너만을 소원했다고 <br>고백하고 싶어 기다렸다고 <br>매일 매일 널 사랑한다고 외치면 <br>매일 매일 네 이름 부르면 <br>내 앞에 그대가 서 있는 순간을 <br>생각해 생각해 생각해 <br>하루 하루 니 생각에 잠 못 들어요 <br>하루 하루 그대뿐이죠 <br>떨려오는 내 심장 소리 들려오나요 <br>사랑해 사랑해 사랑해 <br>시간 지나 다시 세월 지나 <br>우리 함께 한다면 곁에 있다면 <br>난 생각만해도 자꾸 눈물이 나요 <br>무엇을 꿈꿔왔는지 <br>내가 바랬는지 알고 있나요 <br>그댄 모르죠 <br>너만을 소원했다고 <br>고백하고 싶어 기다렸다고 <br>매일 매일 널 사랑한다고 외치면 <br>매일 매일 니 이름 부르면 <br>내 앞에 그대가 서 있는 순간을 <br>생각해 생각해 생각해 <br>피할 수도 없어요 또 멈출 수 없죠 <br>내게로 다가온 운명을 <br>모두 변한대도 난 그댈 영원히 <br>바라볼텐데 또 지켜줄텐데 <br>사랑해요 내 가슴이 <br>네게 하는 말 고마워요 <br>두 눈이 하는 말 <br>두 눈이 하는 말 <br>언제나 나는 여기 서 있을게요 <br>서 있을게요 <br>기억해 기억해 기억해 기억해 <br>기억해 기억하고 있을게 <br>하루 하루 니 생각에 잠 못들어요 <br>하루 하루 그대뿐이죠 <br>그대뿐이죠 <br>떨려오는 내 심장소리 들려오나요 <br>들려오나요 <br>사랑해 사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="아이오아이 (I.O.I)" label="아이오아이 (I.O.I)"/><category term="사랑해 기억해" label="사랑해 기억해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로꼬/Say_Yes/</id><title>로꼬 - Say Yes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:33:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:33:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EA%BC%AC/Say_Yes/" title="로꼬 - Say Yes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니 눈앞에 왔잖아 <br>내가 여기 있잖아 <br>너의 입술로 말을 해줘 <br>say yes say yes <br>나도 모르게 <br>너에게 가고 있나봐 <br>부는 바람에 내 맘 전할래 <br>love is true <br>간지럽게만 느껴지던 눈 빛이 <br>이제는 익숙 하단듯이 웃음 짓지 <br>그 쪽으로 걸어가기만 하면 돼 <br>라고 친구들은 <br>계속해서 날 부추기지만 <br>아직은 무거운 구두의 뒷 굽 <br>차라리 벗어버리고 <br>싶은 이 밤의 끝 <br>손을 내밀어 줬으면 해 <br>맨발로 너에게 <br>뛰어갈 수 있게 끔 <br>복잡하기만한 하루에 <br>매 시간 머리를 <br>굴리지만 난 <br>지금에서야 깨달은 건데 <br>결국 다 버려지고 <br>너만 남아 <br>지난 봄에는 <br>널 우연히 봤고 <br>더 이상은 우연이 <br>아니였으면 해 <br>스치기만 했던 <br>너의 손을 잡고 <br>어떤 길이라도 <br>같이 걸었으면 해 <br>니 눈앞에 왔잖아 <br>내가 여기 있잖아 <br>너의 입술로 말을 해줘 <br>say yes say yes <br>나도 모르게 <br>너에게 가고 있나봐 <br>부는 바람에 내 맘 전할래 <br>love is true <br>i need u <br>baby 너에게 하고 픈 말 <br>내가 못다한 말 <br>baby baby baby boy <br>love is true <br>어디든 갈 수 있어 <br>이건 거짓말이 아니야 <br>이제부터는 나의 옆이 <br>제일 편한 자리야 <br>입술을 오므리고 <br>내는 소리와 같이 <br>내 이름을 <br>불러줬음 좋겠어 <br>내가 뒤로 떨어져서 <br>걷더라도 단지 <br>이 목소리를 <br>들어줬음 좋겠어 <br>니 눈앞에 왔잖아 <br>내가 여기 있잖아 <br>너의 입술로 말을 해줘 <br>say yes say yes <br>나도 모르게 <br>너에게 가고 있나봐 <br>부는 바람에 내 맘 전할래 <br>love is true <br>내가 바라는 단 한가지 <br>니가 내곁에 있어주는 것 <br>니가 날 보며 웃어주는것도 <br>내 얘길 들어주는것도 <br>난 그걸로도 충분한데 you <br>너를 보며 웃잖아 <br>두 눈이 말하잖아 <br>너도 이렇게 대답해줘 <br>say yes say yes <br>너라서 좋아 <br>니가 날 울려도 좋아 <br>너는 나의 모든 전부니까 <br>love is true <br>i need u <br>baby 너에게 하고 픈 말 <br>내가 못다한 말 <br>baby baby baby boy <br>love is true <br>]]></content><category term="로꼬" label="로꼬"/><category term="Say Yes" label="Say Yes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/첸_CHEN/너를_위해/</id><title>첸 (CHEN) - 너를 위해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:33:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:33:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%B8_CHEN/%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9C%84%ED%95%B4/" title="첸 (CHEN) - 너를 위해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다른 공간의 다른 시간이지만 <br>내 사랑이 맞을거야 <br>바람에 스치는 너의 향기로도 <br>난 너인걸 알수 있어 <br>but i don`t know <br>내 맘속에 언제부터 니가 산건지 <br>i don`t know <br>너를 보면 설레는 이유 <br>나를 스쳐 지나가도 돼 <br>니가 날 다 잊었으니까 <br>니가 기억할 때까지 <br>나는 너를 기다릴테니까 <br>그대여 나를 바라봐줘요 <br>여전히 그대도 나를 사랑하나요 <br>그대여 내눈을 보고 얘기해줘요 <br>사랑하는 맘은 숨겨지지 않아요 <br>너에겐 내가 곁에 있었단 <br>사실을 절대로 잊지는 마 <br>널 위해 모든걸 바칠 수 있었던 <br>내 마음을 지우지마 <br>but i don`t know <br>내맘속에 언제부터 니가 산건지 <br>i don`t know <br>너를 보면 설레는 이유 <br>나를 스쳐 지나가도 돼 <br>니가 날 다 잊었으니까 <br>니가 기억할 때까지 <br>나는 너를 기다릴테니까 <br>같은 공간 같은 시간 함께 있잖아 <br>언제라도 내 곁에 와 너의 자리로 <br>With you <br>너를 위해서 <br>그대여 나를 바라봐줘요 <br>여전히 그대도 나를 사랑하나요 <br>]]></content><category term="첸 (CHEN)" label="첸 (CHEN)"/><category term="너를 위해" label="너를 위해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아리/오늘_같은_날/</id><title>아리 - 오늘 같은 날 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:36:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:36:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EB%A6%AC/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98_%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EB%82%A0/" title="아리 - 오늘 같은 날 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자꾸 눈을 뗄 수가 없어 <br>여전히 예뻐서 죽겠어 <br>yeah <br>매번 나를 보며 웃는 너 <br>혹시 내 맘 알아버렸나 <br>모르겠어 <br>어쩜 그리 둔하니 <br>이렇게 티를 내도 <br>감이 없어 <br>이렇게 좋은 날 <br>우연히 둘인데 <br>좀처럼 오지 않는 기횐데 <br>바보처럼 눈치만 봐 <br>답답해 죽겠지만 <br>그런 니가 난 좋아 <br>Maybe love <br>애만 자꾸 타들고 <br>Maybe love <br>Maybe this is love <br>사랑 그 한마디 <br>우리를 맺어주죠 <br>너만 보면 자꾸 얼어서 <br>말을 걸지 못해 죽겠어 <br>yeah <br>자주 내 주위에 있는 널 <br>설마 너도 애태우는지 <br>모르겠어 <br>어쩜 그리 둔하니 <br>이렇게 티를 내도 <br>감이 없어 <br>이렇게 좋은 날 <br>우연히 둘인데 <br>좀처럼 오지 않는 기횐데 <br>바보처럼 눈치만 봐 <br>답답해 죽겠지만 <br>그런 니가 난 좋아 <br>Maybe love <br>애만 자꾸 타들고 <br>Maybe love <br>Maybe this is love <br>사랑 그 한마디 <br>우리를 맺어주죠 <br>항상 네 옆에서 <br>발맞추고 싶어 <br>하얀 너의 미소 내 눈 속에 <br>담아두고 싶어 <br>매일 바래다주면서 <br>안아주고 싶어 <br>이쯤에서 니 의견 어떤지 <br>묻고 싶어 <br>이렇게 좋은 날 <br>우연히 둘인데 <br>좀처럼 오지 않는 기횐데 <br>바보처럼 눈치만 봐 <br>답답해 죽겠지만 <br>그런 니가 난 좋아 <br>Maybe love <br>애만 자꾸 타들고 <br>Maybe love <br>Maybe this is love <br>사랑 그 한마디 <br>우리를 맺어주죠 <br>]]></content><category term="아리" label="아리"/><category term="오늘 같은 날" label="오늘 같은 날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/40/품에_안으면/</id><title>40 - 품에 안으면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:36:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:36:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/40/%ED%92%88%EC%97%90_%EC%95%88%EC%9C%BC%EB%A9%B4/" title="40 - 품에 안으면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너의 그 미소를 볼 때면 <br>왜 그런 거 있잖아 <br>너무 사랑해서 <br>불안한 마음 같은 거 <br>혹시 너도 매일 내 생각에 <br>흐뭇한 미소 지으며 <br>베개를 끌어안고서 <br>이리저리 뒹굴며 잠 못 이루니 <br>너를 품에 안고 있으면 <br>자꾸 미안해져 눈물이 나 <br>세상 가장 행복한 여자로 <br>만들어 주겠다던 말들이 자꾸 <br>Baby I'm sorry sorry <br>항상 웃게 만들어주지 못 해서 <br>My baby lady <br>여전히 넌 나를 미소 짓게 하는데 <br>그대 <br>사소한 일로 헤어지자고 <br>몹쓸 말들도 난 무심코 <br>그저 뱉기도 했었어 <br>네 맘 얼마나 아플지 모르고 <br>너를 품에 안고 있으면 <br>자꾸 미안해져 눈물이 나 <br>세상 가장 행복한 여자로 <br>만들어 주겠다던 말들이 자꾸 <br>Baby I'm sorry sorry <br>항상 웃게 만들어주지 못 해서 <br>My baby lady <br>여전히 넌 나를 미소 짓게 하는데 <br>눈 감아도 네가 자꾸 보여 <br>매번 널 곁에 두고 싶어 <br>눈에 담아둘 수 있게 <br>너를 품에 안고 있으면 <br>자꾸 미안해져 눈물이 나 <br>세상 가장 행복한 여자로 <br>만들어 주겠다던 말들이 자꾸 <br>Baby I'm sorry sorry <br>항상 웃게 만들어주지 못 해서 <br>My baby lady <br>여전히 넌 나를 미소 짓게 하는데 <br>그대 <br>]]></content><category term="40" label="40"/><category term="품에 안으면" label="품에 안으면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/바닐라_어쿠스틱/나와_With_Me/</id><title>바닐라 어쿠스틱 - 나와 (With Me) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:36:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:36:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%90%EB%9D%BC_%EC%96%B4%EC%BF%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B1/%EB%82%98%EC%99%80_With_Me/" title="바닐라 어쿠스틱 - 나와 (With Me) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아침 공기에 못내 눈을 뜨고 <br>거울 속 내게 인사를 하죠 <br>내 발소리로 가득 채워지는 <br>이 작은 공간 내 하루의 시작 <br>그게 싫지가 않죠 <br>혼자라는 느낌도 <br>지쳐버린 내 맘에 <br>쉴 틈을 내줘요 <br>말을 하지 않아도 <br>들려오지 않아도 <br>외롭지 않은 적막 <br>Because I'm not alone <br>I'm not alone I'm not alone <br>With me With me With me <br>늦은 저녁은 끝내 거른 채로 <br>재촉한 걸음 긴 하루에 끝에 <br>손에 들린 비닐봉투 하나 <br>그 속에 담긴 술 한 잔의 위로 <br>그게 싫지가 않죠 <br>혼자라는 느낌도 <br>지쳐버린 내 맘에 <br>쉴 틈을 내줘요 <br>말을 하지 않아도 <br>들려오지 않아도 <br>외롭지 않은 적막 <br>Because I'm not alone <br>감당하지 못할 많은 얘기로 <br>피곤해져가는 웃음소리로 <br>지쳐가겠죠 <br>아늑한 이 공간은 <br>혼자만의 시간은 <br>막혀버린 내 맘에 <br>빈틈을 내줘요 <br>말을 하지 않아도 <br>들려오지 않아도 <br>외롭지 않은 적막 <br>Because I'm not alone <br>I'm not alone I'm not alone <br>With me With me With me <br>]]></content><category term="바닐라 어쿠스틱" label="바닐라 어쿠스틱"/><category term="나와 (With Me)" label="나와 (With Me)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오마이걸/너의_귓가에_안녕/</id><title>오마이걸 - 너의 귓가에 안녕 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:36:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:36:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B4%EA%B1%B8/%EB%84%88%EC%9D%98_%EA%B7%93%EA%B0%80%EC%97%90_%EC%95%88%EB%85%95/" title="오마이걸 - 너의 귓가에 안녕 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대를 본 순간 난 설레었다는 <br>그치만 오늘은 나 참 별로라는 <br>그래도 그대를 만나게 된다면 <br>너의 인사에 안녕 <br>비 내린 오늘은 참 센치하구요 <br>그대가 내 맘에 또 가득찼구요 <br>보고픈 이 맘을 그대는 알까요 <br>너의 귓가에 안녕 <br>그댄 내 맘 알까 살짝 쿵 떠보면 <br>아무것도 몰라 바보처럼 <br>내 맘 속에 그댄 누구보다 멋진 <br>하나 뿐인 내 사랑 <br>달콤한 로맨스 바라지 않아요 <br>뜨거운 19금 바라지 않아요 <br>따뜻한 사랑해 한마디면 돼요 <br>너의 귓가에 안녕 <br>그댄 내 맘 알까 살짝 쿵 떠보면 <br>아무것도 몰라 바보처럼 <br>내 맘 속에 그댄 누구보다 멋진 <br>하나 뿐인 내 사랑 <br>이젠 말해볼까 그대 앞에 서면 <br>아무것도 생각나지 않아 <br>포근한 그대 품 나를 안아줘요 <br>하나 뿐인 내 사랑 <br>너의 귓가에 안녕 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라라라라 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라라라라 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라라라라 <br>라라라라라 라라 <br>너의 귓가에 안녕 <br>]]></content><category term="오마이걸" label="오마이걸"/><category term="너의 귓가에 안녕" label="너의 귓가에 안녕"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/잔나비/웃어도_될까요/</id><title>잔나비 - 웃어도 될까요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:36:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:36:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%94%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84/%EC%9B%83%EC%96%B4%EB%8F%84_%EB%90%A0%EA%B9%8C%EC%9A%94/" title="잔나비 - 웃어도 될까요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어여쁜 거짓말들 <br>알아도 모른 척 <br>덩실덩실 춤을 출꺼야 <br>히히하하호호호 <br>웃어도 될까요 <br>오늘도 즐거웁구나 <br>안정적인 직장을 팔아요 <br>그대의 젊음과 <br>공평히 바꿉시다 <br>빈손으로 돌아갈껀가요 <br>알아서 하세요 <br>책임을 못집니다 저흰 <br>어머니 이게 맞나요 <br>그렇단다 <br>말이 틀리잖아요 <br>어여쁜 거짓말들 <br>알아도 모른 척 <br>덩실덩실 춤을 출꺼야 <br>히히하하호호호 <br>웃어도 될까요 <br>오늘도 즐거웁구나 <br>아직 결정을 못내리셨군요 <br>찬란한 노후도 <br>덤으로 드릴께요 <br>당신도 언젠가 <br>가정을 꾸리면 <br>요긴히 쓰세요 <br>자 어서 책상에 앉아요 <br>어머니 이게 맞나요 <br>그렇단다 <br>말이 틀리잖아요 <br>어여쁜 거짓말들 <br>알아도 모른 척 <br>덩실덩실 춤을 출꺼야 <br>히히하하호호호 <br>웃어도 될까요 <br>오늘도 즐거웁구나 <br>어여쁜 거짓말들 <br>알아도 모른 척 <br>덩실덩실 춤을 출꺼야 <br>히히하하호호호 <br>웃어도 될까요 <br>오늘도 즐거웁구나 <br>]]></content><category term="잔나비" label="잔나비"/><category term="웃어도 될까요" label="웃어도 될까요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/옥상달빛/떠날_수_있을까/</id><title>옥상달빛 - 떠날 수 있을까 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:36:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:36:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A5%EC%83%81%EB%8B%AC%EB%B9%9B/%EB%96%A0%EB%82%A0_%EC%88%98_%EC%9E%88%EC%9D%84%EA%B9%8C/" title="옥상달빛 - 떠날 수 있을까 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나씩 기억하고 <br>하나씩 버리고는 <br>다시금 꺼낼 수 없는 <br>깊은 곳에 닿는다 <br>창문에 남은 손자국 <br>모서리에 찢겨 상처가 난 벽 <br>난 난 떠날 수 있을까 <br>모든 게 그대로 그 자린데 <br>변한 건 너 없는 빈자리뿐 <br>변한 건 너 없이 찾아온 겨울 <br>난 떠날 수 있을까 <br>텅 빈 집 돌아보면 <br>한참을 머뭇거린다 <br>난 난 떠날 수 있을까 <br>모든 게 그대로 그 자린데 <br>변한 건 너 없는 빈자리뿐 <br>변한 건 너 없이 찾아온 겨울 <br>난 떠날 수 있을까 <br>]]></content><category term="옥상달빛" label="옥상달빛"/><category term="떠날 수 있을까" label="떠날 수 있을까"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오종혁/시들어/</id><title>오종혁 - 시들어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:36:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:36:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EC%A2%85%ED%98%81/%EC%8B%9C%EB%93%A4%EC%96%B4/" title="오종혁 - 시들어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[햇살이 가득 채우는 <br>따뜻한 공기마저 <br>차갑게 느껴지는 <br>너와 나의 시간 <br>아무런 할 말이 없어 <br>어색한 웃음 짓는 건 <br>마치 어제처럼 오늘도 <br>우린 시들어 너무 힘들어 <br>더 이상 너를 <br>바라보는 것도 이젠 <br>우릴 믿으려 했던 건 <br>미련일까 <br>떠나지 못하는 나처럼 <br>함께 걷던 거리는 <br>아직 그대로인데 <br>너와 난 손을 잡는 것도 <br>이젠 싫어 <br>같은 곳을 보고 있다고 <br>같은 생각할 거라 믿던 <br>우리 모습들이 싫어 <br>내 맘이 변했다고 <br>이유를 묻는 너에게 <br>아무런 말도 <br>할 수 없는 나라서 <br>서로가 조금씩 더 <br>아파해줄 수 없는 우리 <br>이제 그만하자 <br>이제 그만해 이제 그만하자 <br>우린 시들어 너무 힘들어 <br>더 이상 너를 <br>바라보는 것도 이젠 <br>우릴 믿으려 했던 건 <br>미련일까 <br>떠나지 못하는 나처럼 <br>우린 서로 사랑했던 시간들 <br>없던 일처럼 잊혀질 동안은 <br>아파해야 하니까 <br>우린 시들어 너무 힘들어 <br>더 이상 너를 <br>바라보는 것도 이젠 <br>우릴 믿으려 했던 건 <br>미련일까 <br>떠나지 못하는 나처럼 <br>우린 시들어 너무 힘들어 <br>]]></content><category term="오종혁" label="오종혁"/><category term="시들어" label="시들어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김장훈/어머니는_내_마음을_아세요/</id><title>김장훈 - 어머니는 내 마음을 아세요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:37:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:37:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9E%A5%ED%9B%88/%EC%96%B4%EB%A8%B8%EB%8B%88%EB%8A%94_%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C%EC%9D%84_%EC%95%84%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94/" title="김장훈 - 어머니는 내 마음을 아세요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어머니는 내 마음을 아세요 <br>내가 저 먼 바다로 <br>나가는 그 이유 <br>내가 이 세상에 한 사람 이란 거 <br>누가 뭐라 해도 나의 길이란 걸 <br>나만의 이유 <br>꽃을 보면 어릴 때가 생각나요 <br>다시는 돌아갈 수 없는 <br>너무 늦어 버렸나요 어머니 <br>너무 늦지 않았어요 어머니 <br>나만의 이유 <br>그 누가 뭐라 해도 <br>정해버린 나의 길 <br>힘겨워 다시 돌아왔어요 <br>그리고 또 가요 또 가요 <br>때로는 거짓말도 했어요 <br>때로는 거짓말도 했어요 <br>나만의 이유 <br>그 누가 뭐라 해도 <br>정해버린 나의 길 <br>힘겨워 다시 돌아왔어요 <br>그리고 또 가요 또 가요 <br>어머니는 말씀하시겠지요 <br>오 나의 아들아 <br>]]></content><category term="김장훈" label="김장훈"/><category term="어머니는 내 마음을 아세요" label="어머니는 내 마음을 아세요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/치타_CHEETAH/NOT_TODAY/</id><title>치타 (CHEETAH) - NOT TODAY - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:37:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:37:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B9%98%ED%83%80_CHEETAH/NOT_TODAY/" title="치타 (CHEETAH) - NOT TODAY - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My soul My body good <br>I feel so good <br>My friends errbody good <br>I'm all ready <br>I just I need somebody today <br>I want some more <br>Too bad y u mad at me <br>내 하루 like party good <br>여기가 어디든 <br>느껴 끝나지 않을 듯 <br>혹시 내게 화났니 <br>왜 그렇게 쳐다봐 난 단지 잘 지내 <br>Too bad y u mad at me <br>요즘 난 잘 지내 <br>그 누구 부럽지 않게 g-good <br>날 비추어 주는 불빛 I'll eat you up <br>always huh and I beat beat up <br>금 토일 밤엔 밤에 취해 나가지 <br>몸을 던지려 그 열기에 또 비비러 <br>혹시 나와 마주치면 <br>괜히 아는 척은 말어 <br>난 너의 누나 언니보단 <br>친구가 좋아 걍 곧바로 <br>흔들어 그럼 여긴 <br>스테이지가 되고 내일 되어 <br>눈 뜨면 이게 진짜였나 싶다고 <br>장담해 의심 말고 날 따라와 <br>난 가식 떠는 거 싫어해 넌 잘 알지 <br>이리 와 놀면서 지켜봐 <br>쟤네의 거품은 얼마나 갈지 <br>걱정 마 이 분위기가 얼마나 갈지 <br>이 자린 또 값이 얼마나 갈지 <br>니 눈에 가치 없어 보일지 모르지 <br>이런 나의 사치 <br>넌 관심 없거나 갖고 싶거나 <br>하고 싶은데 못하는 거 <br>내가 한다고 욕하면 건 <br>니 속에 화만 더 보태는 거 <br>차라리 니가 이리로 <br>가까이 오는 게 나을지도 <br>그래놓고 넌 나의 <br>추락을 바라겠지 but Not today <br>My soul My body good <br>I feel so good <br>My friends errbody good <br>I'm all ready <br>I just I need somebody today <br>I want some more <br>Too bad y u mad at me <br>내 하루 like party good <br>여기가 어디든 <br>느껴 끝나지 않을 듯 <br>혹시 내게 화났니 <br>왜 그렇게 쳐다봐 난 단지 잘 지내 <br>Too bad y u mad at me <br>주위에 많은 것들이 <br>빠르게도 변해 <br>방금 가득 차있던 <br>잔마저도 비었네 <br>그래서인지 사람들은 <br>내게 좀 더 더 새로운 걸 바래 <br>정 붙일 틈 따윈 없지 <br>날 붙잡지 마 난 또 가야 돼 <br>내가 준비한 선물에 <br>포장을 니가 뜯을 때 <br>그 어떤 순간 보다 <br>내 가슴은 설레고 들떠 <br>인정을 바라지 않아 <br>그게 지금 뭐가 중요해 <br>이렇게 가만히 앉아서 <br>반응을 상상만 해도 난 짜릿해 <br>그러니 내 하루는 <br>파티일 수밖에 <br>눈 뜨는 순간부터 <br>종일 방에 처박혀 <br>널 놀라게 할 뭔갈 생각해 <br>도무지 멈출 길이 없어 <br>계속하는 수밖에 난 <br>기다림에 보답해 <br>난 진짜 쉼 없이 달려왔어 <br>언제부터 많은 게 딸려왔고 <br>근데 오늘은 잠깐만 <br>내려놓고 싶어 <br>날 알지도 모르면서 <br>끌어내리려 하는 이들에게 <br>이 말은 해야지 아직은 <br>때가 아니라고 Not today <br>My soul My body good <br>I feel so good <br>My friends errbody good <br>I'm all ready <br>I just I need somebody today <br>I want some more <br>Too bad y u mad at me <br>내 하루 like party good <br>여기가 어디든 <br>느껴 끝나지 않을 듯 <br>혹시 내게 화났니 <br>왜 그렇게 쳐다봐 난 단지 잘 지내 <br>Too bad y u mad at me <br>]]></content><category term="치타 (CHEETAH)" label="치타 (CHEETAH)"/><category term="NOT TODAY" label="NOT TODAY"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cheska_체스카/Panorama/</id><title>Cheska (체스카) - Panorama - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:37:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:37:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cheska_%EC%B2%B4%EC%8A%A4%EC%B9%B4/Panorama/" title="Cheska (체스카) - Panorama - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[we're goin deep <br>오늘 이 밤은 우리의 시간 <br>전화기를 붙들고서 <br>너의 목소리와 함께 <br>난 많이 고민됐지 <br>cause you know <br>I don't talk fake shit <br>너도 같은 생각이겠지 <br>cause there ain't nobody like you <br>we'll make it hot tonight <br>나에게 와 <br>it's goin down tonight <br>깊어가 babe <br>cause you know <br>I don't talk fake shit <br>babe babe <br>it's just the nights I like <br>the feelin that you're mine <br>there ain't no give and takes <br>fuck it I'm on my grind <br>it's just the nights I like <br>the feelin that you're mine <br>let’s get it <br>let’s get it <br>it's just the nights I like <br>the feelin that you're mine <br>there ain't no give and takes <br>fuck it I'm on my grind <br>it's just the nights I like <br>the feelin that you're mine <br>let’s get it <br>let’s get it <br>come visit my <br>너의 마음속에 기대를 안고 <br>널 움직이는 밤의 달빛이 <br>더 환하게 빛나도록 <br>다른 놈들은 못 믿겠지 <br>cause you know <br>they be talkin fake shit <br>하지만 너는 다르겠지 <br>cause there ain't nobody like you <br>we'll make it hot tonight <br>나에게 와 <br>it's goin down tonight <br>깊어가 babe <br>cause you know <br>I don't talk fake shit <br>babe babe <br>it's just the nights I like <br>the feelin that you're mine <br>there ain't no give and takes <br>fuck it I'm on my grind <br>it's just the nights I like <br>the feelin that you're mine <br>let’s get it <br>let’s get it <br>it's just the nights I like <br>the feelin that you're mine <br>there ain't no give and takes <br>fuck it I'm on my grind <br>it's just the nights I like <br>the feelin that you're mine <br>let’s get it <br>let’s get it <br>can't stop this feeling <br>higher than the ceiling <br>you make my body levitate <br>can't stop this feeling <br>higher than the ceiling <br>you make my body levitate <br>]]></content><category term="Cheska (체스카)" label="Cheska (체스카)"/><category term="Panorama" label="Panorama"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cheska_체스카/Swish_Feat_TakeOne/</id><title>Cheska (체스카) - Swish (Feat. TakeOne) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:37:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:37:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cheska_%EC%B2%B4%EC%8A%A4%EC%B9%B4/Swish_Feat_TakeOne/" title="Cheska (체스카) - Swish (Feat. TakeOne) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나의 실수였지 <br>내가 먼저 말을 걸게 <br>속은 답답해져 가 <br>전화기를 뗄 수 없어 <br>나의 실수였지 <br>내가 먼저 말을 걸게 <br>속은 답답해져 가 <br>전화기를 뗄 수 없어 <br>너보다 더 <br>이성적인 여자 난 그런 <br>논리적인 여자 난 그런 <br>이기적으로 느껴질 <br>정도로 감정적인 <br>여자 보다 난 그런 <br>자신감 많고 난 그런 <br>자존심 강하고 난 그런 <br>나보다 더 다혈질인 <br>여자보다도 난 그런 <br>모두 내게 맞춰주는 그런 <br>싸울 때면 다 져주는 그런 <br>아침엔 밥 차려주는 그런 <br>피시방까지 따라와 주는 그런 <br>사람이 필요해 <br>복종과 같은 사랑이 필요해 <br>너무도 피로해 <br>지금 내 머리속이 <br>누굴 견디기엔 <br>Swish <br>넌 매일 내게 말해 <br>더는 못 참겠어 <br>I should retire <br>retire on me huh <br>너의 모든 걸 맞출 순 없어 <br>너도 날 존중한다면 <br>you gotta know <br>what you're saying <br>what ya sayin huh <br>what ya sayin <br>what ya sayin <br>what ya sayin huh <br>cuz when I do it <br>너의 두 눈이 <br>날 못 잊게 만들 수 있어 <br>니가 아무리 날 <br>밀어내려 해도 <br>I know how to move it <br>걱정하지 마 <br>cuz I can prove it <br>너의 두 눈에 <br>너가 할 말은 <br>oh 말도 안 돼 <br>뿐이지 잘 봐 <br>나의 두 눈에 <br>너가 갇혔지 <br>cuz I'm workin at you <br>you've been tellin me excuses <br>you know I don't deal with <br>bullshit <br>I've been tellin you it's useless <br>a million times I've told this <br>man I know you gon be back <br>난 너를 숨 쉬게 해 <br>마주 볼 때 <br>you've been tellin me excuses <br>you know I don't deal with <br>bullshit <br>I've been tellin you it's useless <br>a million times I've told this <br>man I know you gon be back <br>난 너를 숨 쉬게 해 <br>마주 볼 때 <br>넌 매일 내게 돌아오네 <br>나의 머릿속에선 <br>say that it's about time <br>너가 아는 사람들 중에 <br>나만 보인다는 게 <br>조금은 이해될 것 같아 <br>I understand boy <br>I understand understand <br>understand boy <br>cuz when I do it <br>너의 두 눈이 <br>날 못 잊게 만들 수 있어 <br>니가 아무리 날 <br>밀어내려 해도 <br>I know how to move it <br>걱정하지 마 <br>cuz I can prove it <br>너의 두 눈에 <br>너가 할 말은 <br>oh 말도 안 돼 <br>뿐이지 잘 봐 <br>나의 두 눈에 <br>너가 갇혔지 <br>cuz I'm workin at you <br>you've been tellin me excuses <br>you know I don't deal with <br>bullshit <br>I've been tellin you it's useless <br>a million times I've told this <br>man I know you gon be back <br>난 너를 숨 쉬게 해 <br>마주 볼 때 <br>you've been tellin me excuses <br>you know I don't deal with <br>bullshit <br>I've been tellin you it's useless <br>a million times I've told this <br>man I know you gon be back <br>난 너를 숨 쉬게 해 <br>마주 볼 때 <br>]]></content><category term="Cheska (체스카)" label="Cheska (체스카)"/><category term="Swish (Feat. TakeOne)" label="Swish (Feat. TakeOne)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Camilla_Kerslake/You_Raise_Me_Up_Feat_Sing_To_Beat_Breast_Cancer_Choir_Radio_Edit/</id><title>Camilla Kerslake - You Raise Me Up (Feat. Sing To Beat Breast Cancer Choir) (Radio Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:37:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:37:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Camilla_Kerslake/You_Raise_Me_Up_Feat_Sing_To_Beat_Breast_Cancer_Choir_Radio_Edit/" title="Camilla Kerslake - You Raise Me Up (Feat. Sing To Beat Breast Cancer Choir) (Radio Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I am down and, oh my soul, so weary <br>When troubles come and my heart burdened be <br>Then, I am still and wait here in the silence <br><br>Until you come and sit awhile with me <br><br>You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains <br>You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas <br>I am strong, when I am on your shoulders <br>You raise me up To more than I can be <br><br>You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains <br>You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas <br>I am strong, when I am on your shoulders <br>You raise me up To more than I can be <br><br>You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains <br>You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas <br>I am strong, when I am on your shoulders <br>You raise me up To more than I can be <br><br>You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains <br>You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas <br>I am strong, when I am on your shoulders <br>You raise me up To more than I can be <br><br>You raise me up To more than I can be]]></content><category term="Camilla Kerslake" label="Camilla Kerslake"/><category term="You Raise Me Up (Feat. Sing To Beat Breast Cancer Choir) (Radio Edit)" label="You Raise Me Up (Feat. Sing To Beat Breast Cancer Choir) (Radio Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Camilla_Kerslake/You_Raise_Me_Up_Feat_Sing_To_Beat_Breast_Cancer_Choir/</id><title>Camilla Kerslake - You Raise Me Up (Feat. Sing To Beat Breast Cancer Choir) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:37:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:37:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Camilla_Kerslake/You_Raise_Me_Up_Feat_Sing_To_Beat_Breast_Cancer_Choir/" title="Camilla Kerslake - You Raise Me Up (Feat. Sing To Beat Breast Cancer Choir) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I am down and, oh my soul, so weary <br>When troubles come and my heart burdened be <br>Then, I am still and wait here in the silence <br><br>Until you come and sit awhile with me <br><br>You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains <br>You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas <br>I am strong, when I am on your shoulders <br>You raise me up To more than I can be <br><br>You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains <br>You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas <br>I am strong, when I am on your shoulders <br>You raise me up To more than I can be <br><br>You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains <br>You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas <br>I am strong, when I am on your shoulders <br>You raise me up To more than I can be <br><br>You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains <br>You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas <br>I am strong, when I am on your shoulders <br>You raise me up To more than I can be <br><br>You raise me up To more than I can be]]></content><category term="Camilla Kerslake" label="Camilla Kerslake"/><category term="You Raise Me Up (Feat. Sing To Beat Breast Cancer Choir)" label="You Raise Me Up (Feat. Sing To Beat Breast Cancer Choir)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeezy/G-Wagon/</id><title>Jeezy - G-Wagon - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:37:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:37:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeezy/G-Wagon/" title="Jeezy - G-Wagon - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Uh, yeah <br>Uh, whoop whoop, trey <br>Aye this one right here ain't even about the money bruh <br>Already know, yeah <br>Let's do this shit one more time on these niggas man <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br><br>Uh, I said I hopped up out that g wagon <br>Glock got my Balmain jeans sagging <br>Uh, and my wrist look like a disco <br>Uh, translation I'm the shit ho <br>Uh, half a ticket at your mama house <br>Uh, in all 20's in your mama couch <br>Uh, we drop them bitches in the microwave <br>Uh, I made a million with that microwave <br><br>Trey right back to shining on these pussy niggas <br>Uh, been a minute, perfect timing on these pussy niggas <br>Uh, ask about me state to state, bitch ain't nothing to fake <br>Uh, they know my new estate, yeah it got a lake <br>Bitch got a camera phone and she taking pictures <br>Bitch I'm shell shocked, it's making me suspicious <br>Right outside the spot, I'm like fuck em <br>And if I cut the nigga off you know I didn't trust him <br><br>Uh, I said I hopped up out that g wagon <br>Glock got my Balmain jeans sagging <br>Uh, and my wrist look like a disco <br>Uh, translation I'm the shit ho <br>Uh, half a ticket at your mama house <br>Uh, in all 20's in your mama couch <br>Uh, we drop them bitches in the microwave <br>Uh, I made a million with that microwave <br><br>These bitches on me, huh <br>These bitches want me, huh <br>They ain't gonna holler at you niggas cause you phony, huh <br>Well you ain't never lie <br>Yeah bitch I'm certified <br>I lost a million ran up, shit left me traumatized <br>You out here ball capping you like them rap niggas <br>I'm in the zone wrapping, I'm like them trap niggas <br>I'm sitting on new leather, I'm screaming who better <br>You came with that nigga Bitch you should do better <br>What's happening <br><br>Uh, I said I hopped up out that g wagon <br>Glock got my Balmain jeans sagging <br>Uh, and my wrist look like a disco <br>Uh, translation I'm the shit ho <br>Uh, half a ticket at your mama house <br>Uh, in all 20's in your mama couch <br>Uh, we drop them bitches in the microwave <br>Uh, I made a million with that microwave <br><br>Arm and hammer, here we go, here we go <br>He gon' be mad at him why water on the floor <br>Told my jeweler go make it flow, that water on my wrist <br>Canary diamonds in that motherfucker, I like yellow piss <br>Uh, glass handle, glass pot <br>Bounce back, yeah, I'm sir miss a lot <br>Looking at my Rollie, that bitch say 6 o'clock <br>That duffle bag from Wal Mart that bitch hold 60 blocks, trey <br><br>Uh, I said I hopped up out that g wagon <br>Glock got my Balmain jeans sagging <br>Uh, and my wrist look like a disco <br>Uh, translation I'm the shit ho <br>Uh, half a ticket at your mama house <br>Uh, in all 20's in your mama couch <br>Uh, we drop them bitches in the microwave <br>Uh, I made a million with that microwave <br><br>I just want to give a shoutout to all the niggas that turned their back on me <br>All the niggas that switched sides on me <br>All the niggas that ran to the other side like the grass is greener <br>Haha I want to shout out you pussy niggas, you'll see me ball <br>You will see me ball, you bitch ass niggas what's happening]]></content><category term="Jeezy" label="Jeezy"/><category term="G-Wagon" label="G-Wagon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kingsland_Road/Dirty_Dancer_Radio_Edit/</id><title>Kingsland Road - Dirty Dancer (Radio Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:41:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:41:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kingsland_Road/Dirty_Dancer_Radio_Edit/" title="Kingsland Road - Dirty Dancer (Radio Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey Hey <br><br>Head spins as the world goes round <br>Blurred eyes lost in this crowd <br>But it's alright 'cause the music's loud <br>Tonight, tonight, our feet don't touch the ground <br><br>We drink, we want to <br>You dance, you want to <br>We sing it's out of tune <br>We touch, it's down to you <br>You can sit on my shoulders <br>Honey let me hold ya <br>Tonight, tonight <br>My feet don't touch the ground <br><br>She's a dirty dancer <br>Keep you up all night <br>Running through your mind <br>Cherry chancer <br>Sweet from eye to eye <br>Keep you satisfied <br><br>Morning, eyes won't even open now <br>Sore feet, another drink will sort me out <br><br>We drink, we want to <br>You dance, you want to <br>We sing it's out of tune <br>We touch, it's down to you <br>You can sit on my shoulders <br>Honey let me hold ya <br>Tonight, tonight <br>My feet don't touch the ground <br><br>She's a dirty dancer <br>Keep you up all night <br>Running through your mind <br>Cherry chancer <br>Sweet from eye to eye <br>Keep you satisfied <br><br>She's a dirty dancer <br>Keep you up all night <br>Running through your mind <br>Cherry chancer <br>Sweet from eye to eye <br>Keep you satisfied <br><br>Oooooh <br>She'll keep you satisfied <br>Keep you satisfied <br><br>She's a dirty dancer <br>Keep you up all night <br>Running through your mind <br>Cherry chancer <br>Sweet from eye to eye <br>Keep you satisfied <br><br>She's a dirty dancer <br>Keep you up all night <br>Running through your mind <br>Cherry chancer <br>Sweet from eye to eye <br>Keep you satisfied]]></content><category term="Kingsland Road" label="Kingsland Road"/><category term="Dirty Dancer (Radio Edit)" label="Dirty Dancer (Radio Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kingsland_Road/Never_Too_Late/</id><title>Kingsland Road - Never Too Late - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:42:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:42:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kingsland_Road/Never_Too_Late/" title="Kingsland Road - Never Too Late - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You used to say pay attention to the things <br>You used to say to settle, get a job and never lose your way <br>Was the road so clear when you were my age <br><br>Let me make mistakes <br><br>Tell me that I don't know nothing <br>Tell me that I'll never learn <br>Tell me we're a generation destined to crash and burn <br>We'll tell you that you don't know nothing <br>Tell you how we just don't care <br>This is our generation <br>We'll scream out like it's the end <br><br>We are, We are the young <br>We are, We are the young <br>Don't take this away from me <br>We are, We are the young <br>We are, We are the young <br>This feeling means everything <br><br>Tell me that I don't know nothing <br>Tell me that I'll never learn <br>This is our generation <br>Don't take this away from me <br>Tell me that I don't know nothing <br>Tell me that I'll never learn <br>This is our generation <br>This feeling means everything <br><br>You had your time <br>to see the mess you made <br>You know you had your time <br>to grow and see the change <br>So won't you give me mine <br>'cause I would rather stumble and fall <br>Don't wanna miss it all <br><br>Tell me that I don't know nothing <br>Tell me that I'll never learn <br>Tell me we're a generation destined to crash and burn <br>We'll tell you that you don't know nothing <br>Tell you how we just don't care <br>This is our generation <br>We'll scream out like it's the end <br><br>We are, We are the young <br>We are, We are the young <br>Don't take this away from me <br>We are, We are the young <br>We are, We are the young <br>This feeling means everything <br><br>Tell me that I don't know nothing <br>Tell me that I'll never learn <br>This is our generation <br>Don't take this away from me <br>Tell me that I don't know nothing <br>Tell me that I'll never learn <br>This is our generation <br>This feeling means everything <br><br>We are, We are the young <br>We are, We are the young <br>Don't take this away from me <br>We are, We are the young <br>We are, We are the young <br>This feeling means everything]]></content><category term="Kingsland Road" label="Kingsland Road"/><category term="Never Too Late" label="Never Too Late"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kingsland_Road/Walk_Away/</id><title>Kingsland Road - Walk Away - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:42:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:42:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kingsland_Road/Walk_Away/" title="Kingsland Road - Walk Away - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Walk away, please go before you throw your life away <br>A life I could share for just a day <br>We could have met some years ago For your sake I'll say <br><br>Walk away, just go, walk away and live a life that's full with no regret <br>Don't look back to me, just try to forget <br>Why build a dream that cannot come true, so be strong <br><br>Reach the stars now, walk away, walk on <br>If I heard your voice, I'll beg you to stay <br>So don't say a word, just run away <br>Goodbye, my love, my tears will fall now that you're gone <br>I can't help but cry but I must go on <br>I'm sad that after searching so long <br>Knew I love you but told you, walk away, walk on]]></content><category term="Kingsland Road" label="Kingsland Road"/><category term="Walk Away" label="Walk Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kingsland_Road/Dirty_Dancer/</id><title>Kingsland Road - Dirty Dancer - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:42:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:42:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kingsland_Road/Dirty_Dancer/" title="Kingsland Road - Dirty Dancer - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey Hey <br><br>Head spins as the world goes round <br>Blurred eyes lost in this crowd <br>But it's alright 'cause the music's loud <br>Tonight, tonight, our feet don't touch the ground <br><br>We drink, we want to <br>You dance, you want to <br>We sing it's out of tune <br>We touch, it's down to you <br>You can sit on my shoulders <br>Honey let me hold ya <br>Tonight, tonight <br>My feet don't touch the ground <br><br>She's a dirty dancer <br>Keep you up all night <br>Running through your mind <br>Cherry chancer <br>Sweet from eye to eye <br>Keep you satisfied <br><br>Morning, eyes won't even open now <br>Sore feet, another drink will sort me out <br><br>We drink, we want to <br>You dance, you want to <br>We sing it's out of tune <br>We touch, it's down to you <br>You can sit on my shoulders <br>Honey let me hold ya <br>Tonight, tonight <br>My feet don't touch the ground <br><br>She's a dirty dancer <br>Keep you up all night <br>Running through your mind <br>Cherry chancer <br>Sweet from eye to eye <br>Keep you satisfied <br><br>She's a dirty dancer <br>Keep you up all night <br>Running through your mind <br>Cherry chancer <br>Sweet from eye to eye <br>Keep you satisfied <br><br>Oooooh <br>She'll keep you satisfied <br>Keep you satisfied <br><br>She's a dirty dancer <br>Keep you up all night <br>Running through your mind <br>Cherry chancer <br>Sweet from eye to eye <br>Keep you satisfied <br><br>She's a dirty dancer <br>Keep you up all night <br>Running through your mind <br>Cherry chancer <br>Sweet from eye to eye <br>Keep you satisfied]]></content><category term="Kingsland Road" label="Kingsland Road"/><category term="Dirty Dancer" label="Dirty Dancer"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/거인/Bloom/</id><title>거인 - Bloom - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:42:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:42:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B1%B0%EC%9D%B8/Bloom/" title="거인 - Bloom - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[할 거면 제대로 좀 하라고 <br>거울이 말을 걸어오네 <br>날개를 폈음 이제 날라고 <br>비둘기들이 걸어 다니면서 <br>말하네 어쩔 수 없지 <br>여긴 피어나지 못하면 <br>죽는 정원 온실은 아니지 <br>행운도 따라야 하지만 <br>실력이 반이지 누 <br>구도 내게 손가락질 <br>못 하게 칼을 갈아야지 <br>두 눈을 감고도 바라지 <br>내 모습이 당당하길 <br>랩을 시작한 지가 벌써 <br>오 년 가까이 <br>이제야 들어줄 만한데 <br>반 오십이야 아아 쓸 <br>데 없는 걱정은 묻어야 <br>거름이 돼 겨울 <br>바람을 견뎌야 여름이 돼 <br>니까 해내야 해 <br>별거 아닌 듯이 <br>눈 감았다 뜨니 계절이 <br>바뀐 듯이 틀에 박힌 것이 <br>불투명한 미래보다 <br>무서워 매일 더 새롭게 <br>오늘은 발밑이었어도 <br>내일은 어깨높이에 <br>난 흩날리지 꽃가루 <br>꿀벌 양들의 엉덩이에 <br>묻혀야겠어 <br>난 진지하지 진짜로 <br>이거 아니면 뭘로 <br>벌어 먹고살겠어 <br>피어나야 해 오직 <br>나만의 색채와 향기로 <br>감각을 사로잡아야 해 에 에 <br>어쨌건 난 많은 걸 원해 <br>원해 <br>지금부터 살고 <br>싶은 대로 살지 않으면 <br>결국 착취당할 것이 <br>뻔하지 벌써 그런 <br>애들이 많은걸 <br>시스템은 세뇌하지 <br>꿈은 사치라고 해 <br>부모가 부자면 가져 <br>애들이 많은 걸 <br>진짜 자유경쟁이라면 <br>상속을 폐 <br>지하든가 아님 닥치든가 <br>정원사 양반 <br>티비가 하느님인 <br>취향의 사망이 <br>씬의 확대라면 덕후인 <br>나는 정중히 사양함 <br>손사래를 칠래 손을 모아 비네 <br>삶 그 자체가 예술인 <br>시대가 오길 근 <br>데 넘치는 건 상품 <br>상품 상품뿐이야 <br>나도 팔리는 전체의 <br>일부분이야 <br>지루한 건 못 해 되지 <br>않아 초록색 <br>벌들이 배워가게 뇌내 <br>공책을 염색 후 연습해 <br>기어코 먹을래 <br>그 열매가 쓰든 달든 <br>아침부터 달렸어 <br>이젠 봐요 붉은 하늘 <br>난 흩날리지 꽃가루 <br>꿀벌 양들의 엉덩이에 <br>묻혀야겠어 <br>난 진지하지 진짜로 <br>이거 아니면 뭘로 벌어 <br>먹고살겠어 <br>피어나야 해 오직 <br>나만의 색채와 향기로 <br>감각을 사로잡아야 해 에 에 <br>어쨌건 난 많은 걸 원해 <br>원해 <br>올라갈래 어떤 경지에 <br>오히려 못 나는 게 범죄 <br>가 된 세상에서 걍 <br>벙찐 채로 살 순 없어 <br>멈춤 없이 정진 <br>하면서도 불안하지 계속 <br>달려야만 제자리에 <br>멈춰있을 수 있지 <br>알파고도 못 해 <br>현대사회 수 읽기 <br>뭔가 다르니까 달라져 <br>버린 분위기 <br>맛을 보니 꽃 속의 꿀이지 <br>어쩌면 랩이란 건 <br>나에겐 취미고 <br>놀지 뭐 예술이란 <br>단어를 빌미로 <br>어차피 의미 혹은 <br>사상의 깊이도 <br>랩퍼에게는 짐이고 <br>물어뜯길 핑계 <br>시라고 썼는데 <br>애완견보다 수준이 <br>낮은 애들보다 벌어야 <br>해서 꾸준히 <br>랩 해야 하는 궂은일 <br>도맡아 하고 있어 <br>나의 존재를 끄집어내는 <br>산파 직업 <br>거듭난 인생 이게 <br>내가 짠 꿈의 이름 <br>본 적이 없는 색으로 <br>칠하네 매일을 근데 <br>현재 수입은 알바보다 <br>못한 상태 허나 <br>여긴 과정일 뿐 안 해 <br>창조력의 낙태 <br>필요해 나에겐 빛이 생존하기 <br>위해서 뻗은 뿌리가 <br>깊이 닿을 때쯤 <br>처음 본 꽃이 <br>피어나는 걸 볼거야 <br>그 땐 내가 나의 노력의 증거야 <br>]]></content><category term="거인" label="거인"/><category term="Bloom" label="Bloom"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스컬하하/Buzzer_Beater_Feat_엠타이슨/</id><title>스컬&amp;하하 - Buzzer Beater (Feat. 엠타이슨) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:42:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:42:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%EC%BB%AC%ED%95%98%ED%95%98/Buzzer_Beater_Feat_%EC%97%A0%ED%83%80%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A8/" title="스컬&amp;하하 - Buzzer Beater (Feat. 엠타이슨) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[백 넘버 No.1 Who's reggae No.1 <br>두 눈 뜨고 읽어 저지네임 <br>불꽃남자 BURN <br>I'm on fire 넌 소방관처럼 날 쫓지 <br>치열하게 미안해 못 잡아 <br>불길하지 1쿼터 <br>Wow Yo Look at me now <br>Wow 준비물 챙겨줘 봐 숟가락 <br>내가 떠먹여줘 그냥 입만 벌려 Big man <br>알아 난 small but I move forward <br>like Scottie Pippen <br>공은 내 손을 떠나도 <br>절대 게임에선 손 안 떼 <br>누가 날 막아 시간도 <br>나를 막을 수 없는데 <br>난 저 Rim을 향해 쏘지만 <br>내 Goal은 더 높지 <br>점수보다 내가 끝까지 <br>오르는 게 목표 <br>Buzzer beater <br>Buzzer beater Buzzer beater <br>누가 뭐라건 믿어 니 자신 <br>흘려왔던 땀 Woh <br>If u wanna win Memba one ting <br>Don't u ever look down bwoy <br>앞만 보며 달려왔지 <br>뒤는 절대 안 봐 <br>머저리들은 말만 많아 <br>내 자리를 넘봐 <br>것 봐 일년이면 사라질 놈들 뮐 봐 <br>실패 없는 Shot Bwoy rememba <br>공은 내 손을 떠나도 <br>절대 게임에선 손 안 떼 <br>누가 날 막아 시간도 <br>나를 막을 수 없는데 <br>난 저 Rim을 향해 쏘지만 <br>내 Goal은 더 높지 <br>점수보다 내가 끝까지 <br>오르는 게 목표 <br>Buzzer beater <br>Buzzer beater Buzzer beater <br>4 3 2 1 백 넘버 No.1 <br>Who's reggae No.1 <br>4 3 2 1 실패 없는 Shot <br>Bwoy Rememba <br>4 3 2 1 백 넘버 No.1 <br>Who's reggae No.1 <br>4 3 2 1 실패 없는 Shot <br>Buzzer beater <br>Buzzer beater <br>Buzzer beater <br>Yo yo yo This is Skull&amp;Haha <br>and M.tyson <br>We play this game for life Ya zimi <br>Pon di street pon di court pon di stage <br>and pon di life. Zeen <br>It's not over til it's over <br>]]></content><category term="스컬&amp;하하" label="스컬&amp;하하"/><category term="Buzzer Beater (Feat. 엠타이슨)" label="Buzzer Beater (Feat. 엠타이슨)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/EDX/My_Friend/</id><title>EDX - My Friend - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:43:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:43:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/EDX/My_Friend/" title="EDX - My Friend - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Whenever I'm down, I call on you my friend <br><br>A helping hand you lend, in my time of need <br><br>Whenever I'm down, I call on you my friend <br><br>A helping hand you lend, in my time of need <br><br>Whenever I'm down]]></content><category term="EDX" label="EDX"/><category term="My Friend" label="My Friend"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김이지/다가갈수록/</id><title>김이지 - 다가갈수록 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:44:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:44:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80/%EB%8B%A4%EA%B0%80%EA%B0%88%EC%88%98%EB%A1%9D/" title="김이지 - 다가갈수록 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한 걸음 떼기가 <br>왜 이리 어렵죠 <br>여전히 그대는 <br>그곳에 서있지만 <br>여전히 내게는 <br>너무도 먼 거리 <br>사랑이 깊을수록 <br>난 자신 없어 <br>꿈 같은 시간을 <br>놓쳐버릴 것 같아 <br>가까이 갈수록 <br>지금이 두려워져 <br>눈 뜨면 사라질 것 <br>같은 그대 <br>술 마셔도 흩어질 <br>안개 같은 그대 <br>나에게 벅찬 <br>고마움 같은 그대에게 <br>다가갈수록 사랑할수록 <br>더 어려워요 <br>여전히 그대는 <br>그 곳에 서있지만 <br>여전히 내게는 <br>닿지 않을 것 같아 <br>눈 뜨면 사라질 것 <br>같은 그대 <br>손 대면 흩어질 <br>구름 같은 그대 <br>다가가 안으려 하면 <br>더 멀어질까 <br>두려워져서 사랑할수록 <br>더 어려워요 <br>]]></content><category term="김이지" label="김이지"/><category term="다가갈수록" label="다가갈수록"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/황진희/못난사랑_MR/</id><title>황진희 - 못난사랑 (MR) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:45:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:45:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%A9%EC%A7%84%ED%9D%AC/%EB%AA%BB%EB%82%9C%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_MR/" title="황진희 - 못난사랑 (MR) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑아 내 사랑아 <br>마음 변해 가는 사랑아 <br>나 없이 못산다고 애원한 사람 <br>그 사랑이 떠나려 하네 <br>정만 주고 가는 사람 미련은 <br>없겠지만 <br>그리워 마라 생각도 마라 <br>후회도 하지를 마라 <br>그리 쉽게 변하는 것이 <br>사랑이더냐 <br>이 못난 내 사랑아 <br>사랑아 내 사랑아 <br>마음 변해가는 사랑아 <br>나 없이 못산다고 애원한 사람 <br>그 사랑이 떠나버렸네 <br>정만 주고 떠난 사람 <br>미련은 없겠지만 <br>그리워 마라 생각도 마라 <br>후회도 하지를 마라 <br>그리 쉽게 변하는 것이 <br>사랑이더냐 <br>이 못난 내 사랑아 <br>이 못난 내 사랑아]]></content><category term="황진희" label="황진희"/><category term="못난사랑 (MR)" label="못난사랑 (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/황진희/못난사랑/</id><title>황진희 - 못난사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:45:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:45:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%A9%EC%A7%84%ED%9D%AC/%EB%AA%BB%EB%82%9C%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="황진희 - 못난사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그리워마라 생각도 마라 후회도 하지를마라 그리 쉽게 변하는게 사랑이더냐 이 못난 내 사랑아 <br>사랑아 내사랑아 마음변해 가는 사랑아 나없이 못 산다고 애원한 사람 <br>그사랑이 떠나려 하네 마음변해 가는사람 미련은 없겠지만 <br>그리워마라 생각도 마라 후회도 하지를마라 그리 쉽게 변하는게 사랑이더냐 이 못난 내 사랑아 <br><br>사랑아 내사랑아 마음변해 가는 사랑아 나없이 못 산다고 애원한 사람 <br>그사랑이 떠나버렸네 마음변해 떠난 사람 미련은 없겠지만 <br>그리워마라 생각도마라 후회도 하지를 마라 그리 쉽게 변하는게 사랑이더냐 이 못난 내 사랑아 이 못난 내 사랑아 <br>]]></content><category term="황진희" label="황진희"/><category term="못난사랑" label="못난사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최완수/어디야/</id><title>최완수 - 어디야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:45:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:45:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%99%84%EC%88%98/%EC%96%B4%EB%94%94%EC%95%BC/" title="최완수 - 어디야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어디야 너 지금 어디야 <br>어딨어 너 지금 어딨어 <br>내 사랑 다 줄 거야 어디야 <br>행복하게 해줄 거야 어디야 <br>내 사랑 내 님은 어디야 <br>새 옷 샀어 이 옷 어때 <br>파마 했어 머리 어때 <br>웃으며 물어보니 <br>여자들 하는 말 <br>너 키는 지금 어디야 <br>모임 나가 웃겨주고 <br>이런저런 기쁨주고 <br>분위기 다 올렸더니 <br>여자들 눈빛은 <br>너 외모 지금 어디야 <br>짧은 내 기럭지 <br>재개발이 필요한 내 얼굴도 <br>나 역시도 원했던 건 아니야 <br>항상 예뻐해주고 <br>항상 날 사랑해주는 <br>내 님은 어딨어요 <br>나타나주세요 <br>어디야 너 지금 어디야 <br>어딨어 너 지금 어딨어 <br>내 사랑 다 줄 거야 어디야 <br>행복하게 해줄 거야 어디야 <br>내 사랑 내 님은 어디야 <br>이 여자 저 여자 <br>장바구니 담아놨다 결국 품절 <br>도대체가 내 사랑은 어디야 <br>항상 예뻐해주고 <br>항상 널 사랑해주는 <br>그 남자 여깄어요 다가와 주세요 <br>여기야 나 지금 여기야 <br>여깄어 나 지금 여깄어 <br>내 사랑 다 줄 거야 여기야 <br>행복하게 해줄 거야 여기야 <br>내 사랑 내님아 여기야 <br>내 사랑 내님아 여기야 <br>]]></content><category term="최완수" label="최완수"/><category term="어디야" label="어디야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지하트/용기/</id><title>지하트 - 용기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:45:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:45:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%ED%95%98%ED%8A%B8/%EC%9A%A9%EA%B8%B0/" title="지하트 - 용기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[소리쳐도 들을 수 <br>없는곳에 있어도 <br>아무도 듣지 못한다해도 <br>실망하지마요 <br>언젠간 알아줄 누군갈위해 <br>힘겨운 날들에 지쳐 너 <br>너무 외로울때 <br>슬퍼진 맘에 멍이 들고 <br>한없이 작아질때 <br>두눈에 고인 그 눈물을 <br>꾹 참지 말아요 <br>감추지마요 그대의 마음 <br>마음껏 크게 한번 <br>소리쳐 봐요 <br>까만밤 길을 비추는 <br>저 별들보다 <br>그대 더 빛나는걸요 <br>보이지 않는 두려움 <br>모두 다 던져버려요 <br>소리쳐도 들을 수 <br>없는곳에 있어도 <br>아무도 듣지 못한다해도 <br>실망하지마요 <br>언젠간 알아줄 누군갈 위해 <br>자신을 믿어 <br>저 높은 하늘을 바라봐요 <br>보이지 않는 희망은 있죠 <br>그대울지마요 <br>오늘도 잘 이겨낸 <br>그대기에 웃어요 <br>그대 미소를 지어요 <br>활짝 웃어봐요 <br>수많은 걱정 던져버려요 <br>멍하니 포기하려 하지말아요 <br>까만밤 길을 비추는 <br>저 별들보다 <br>그대 더 빛나는걸요 <br>보이지않는 두려움 <br>모두 다 던져버려요 <br>소리쳐도 들을 수 <br>없는곳에 있어도 <br>아무도 듣지 못한다해도 <br>실망하지마요 <br>언젠간 알아줄 누군갈 위해 <br>자신을 믿어 <br>저 높은 하늘을 바라봐요 <br>보이지 않는 희망은 있죠 <br>그대울지마요 <br>오늘도 잘이겨낸 <br>그대기에 웃어요 <br>한걸음더 용기를 내요 <br>우린 해낼수있죠 <br>더 단단해질 저 세상을 위해 <br>소리쳐도 들을 수 <br>없는곳에 있어도 <br>아무도 듣지 못한다해도 <br>실망하지마요 <br>언젠간 알아줄 누군갈 위해 <br>자신을 믿어 <br>저 높은 하늘을 바라봐요 <br>보이지 않는 희망은 있죠 <br>그대울지마요 <br>오늘도 잘이겨낸 <br>그대기에 웃어요 <br>]]></content><category term="지하트" label="지하트"/><category term="용기" label="용기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/희망송/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 희망송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:45:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:45:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/%ED%9D%AC%EB%A7%9D%EC%86%A1/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 희망송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어젯밤 내리는 큰 빗소리에 <br>난 한숨도 못잤어 <br>해가 뜨고 난 다음 에서야 <br>간신히 눈을 붙였어 <br>어제 그렇게 내리던 비는 <br>어디로 또 숨었는지 <br>뜨거운 밝은 햇빛이 <br>겨우 감은 눈을 <br>살며시 간지럽히네 <br>아침에 밝은 해가 <br>어두운 먹구름을 밀어내듯 <br>모든 이에게도 <br>고통 대신 밝은 미래가 오겠지 <br>어제 그렇게 내리던 비는 <br>어디로 또 숨었는지 <br>뜨거운 밝은 햇빛이 <br>겨우 감은 눈을 <br>살며시 간지럽히네 <br>아침에 밝은 해가 <br>어두운 먹구름을 밀어내듯 <br>모든 이에게도 <br>고통 대신 밝은 미래가 오겠지 <br>밝은 미래가 오겠지 <br>밝은 미래가 오겠지 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="희망송" label="희망송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/가난하고_늙은_음악가/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 가난하고 늙은 음악가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:45:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:45:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/%EA%B0%80%EB%82%9C%ED%95%98%EA%B3%A0_%EB%8A%99%EC%9D%80_%EC%9D%8C%EC%95%85%EA%B0%80/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 가난하고 늙은 음악가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밖에 나가 내가 <br>음악 한다고 하면 <br>사람들은 모두 와 하지 <br>그렇지만 나는 아직 <br>못 뜬 음악가 <br>이걸로 들어오는건 <br>저작권료 3만원 <br>생계땜에 부업으로 가던 회사 <br>또 짤리게 생겼고 <br>앞으로 먹고 살 일 <br>걱정하게 생겼고 <br>이 음악 때려치고 <br>노가다를 해야하나 <br>고민해야 하고 <br>다른 직장 알아보며 <br>잡코리아 사람인을 뒤져봐 <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>난 아직 할 수 있을거라 믿는데 <br>왜 이리 나에게는 <br>기회가 안오는지 <br>내 음악이 아이들의 <br>취향은 아니지만 <br>그래도 누군가는 듣지 않을까 <br>이렇게 한달에 두 곡씩 <br>꾸준히 열심히 <br>작업해서 발표해도 <br>들어주는 사람이 없으면 <br>계속할 의미가 없어 <br>그래도 회사에 출근할때 <br>버스 안에서도 가사는 뭘 쓸까 <br>고민하고 퇴근할때 <br>어떤 음악을 만들까 <br>계속 궁리해 <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>난 믿어 언젠간 나에게도 <br>기회가 올거라고 HOPE <br>난 믿어 열심히 일하면 <br>나도 언젠간 뜰거라고 <br>The Hope <br>나같은 가난한 음악가 <br>가질수 있는 유일한 것 <br>The Hope <br>내가 지금 꿈꾸고 바라는 <br>Happy 한 미래 <br>가난하고 늙은 <br>음악가가 바라는건 <br>Only My Music <br>많은 사람들에게 들려주고 <br>희망과 즐거움을 주는것 <br>That's my only HOPE <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="가난하고 늙은 음악가" label="가난하고 늙은 음악가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/우수인/Espresso_Man_Feat_하재욱_손희진/</id><title>우수인 - Espresso Man (Feat. 하재욱, 손희진) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:45:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:45:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9A%B0%EC%88%98%EC%9D%B8/Espresso_Man_Feat_%ED%95%98%EC%9E%AC%EC%9A%B1_%EC%86%90%ED%9D%AC%EC%A7%84/" title="우수인 - Espresso Man (Feat. 하재욱, 손희진) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는야 에스프레소 <br>커피의 원액이지 <br>하지만 맛 없지 <br>쓴맛으로 인해서 <br>선택 받기 어렵고 <br>잘 팔리지도 않아 <br>하지만 나 없으면 <br>여러 가지 커피가 <br>탄생되지 않아 <br>수많은 라떼들과 <br>수많은 블랜디드 <br>역시 마찬가지야 <br>우유를 더해 맛과 함께 <br>라떼아트 탄생하고 <br>시럽을 더해 단 맛을 <br>더 깊이 내는 나 <br>에스프레소 <br>나 홀로 아무것도 <br>만들지도 못한다고 <br>해도 난 괜찮아요 <br>그 누구도 <br>나를 싫어해도 <br>난 괜찮아요 <br>다 함께 어울려서 <br>달달함이 느껴진다라면 <br>그걸로 충분해 <br>나 혼자 일 때보다 <br>함께 일 때 더욱 빛이 나는 <br>나 에스프레소 <br>수많은 나라에서 <br>수입된 커피콩들 <br>향마다 다르지 <br>브라질 콜롬비아 <br>케냐 에티오피아 <br>인도네시아까지 <br>하지만 나라별로 <br>맛은 다 다르지만 <br>똑같은 건 있어 <br>양마저 적으면서 <br>비추천 1위 메뉴 <br>에스프레소라네 <br>인기 없지만 <br>우직하게 자리하고 <br>있음으로 <br>약방의 감초가 되어 <br>더 돋보이는 나 <br>에스프레소 <br>나 홀로 아무것도 <br>만들지도 못한다고 <br>해도 난 괜찮아요 <br>그 누구도 <br>나를 싫어해도 <br>난 괜찮아요 <br>다 함께 어울려서 <br>달달함이 느껴진다라면 <br>그걸로 충분해 <br>나 혼자 일 때보다 <br>함께 일 때 <br>더욱 빛이 나는 나 <br>나 홀로 아무것도 <br>만들지도 못한다고 <br>해도 난 괜찮아요 <br>그 누구도 <br>나를 싫어해도 <br>난 괜찮아요 <br>다 함께 어울려서 <br>달달함이 느껴진다라면 <br>그걸로 충분해 <br>나 혼자 일 때보다 <br>함께 일 때 <br>더욱 빛이 나는 나 <br>더욱 빛이 나는 나 <br>더욱 빛이 나는 나 <br>에스프레소 <br>]]></content><category term="우수인" label="우수인"/><category term="Espresso Man (Feat. 하재욱, 손희진)" label="Espresso Man (Feat. 하재욱, 손희진)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/은하수공장/하룻밤의_꿈/</id><title>은하수공장 - 하룻밤의 꿈 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:45:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:45:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%80%ED%95%98%EC%88%98%EA%B3%B5%EC%9E%A5/%ED%95%98%EB%A3%BB%EB%B0%A4%EC%9D%98_%EA%BF%88/" title="은하수공장 - 하룻밤의 꿈 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 난 매일 널 만나 <br>우리 예전에 그 모습 그대로 <br>우리 함께 걷고 <br>우리 함께 하던 기억들 속에서 <br>오늘도 너를 볼 수 있다면 <br>네게 하고픈 말들이 많은 걸 <br>나를 떠나고서 너는 행복한지 <br>잘 지내고 있는지 아프진 않은지 <br>넌 어떻게 지내 <br>난 이렇게 살아 널 지우지 못해 <br>널 그리워하며 매일 밤 너를 찾아 <br>내게 말해 줄래 네가 보고파 <br>내 하루하루가 너무 힘들다고 <br>내게 돌아와 달라고 <br>하룻밤의 꿈 <br>너를 다시 볼 수 있는 꿈 <br>모두 거짓이라도 <br>나는 이 꿈 안에서 널 그리며 살아 <br>넌 어떻게 지내 <br>난 이렇게 살아 널 지우지 못해 <br>널 그리워하며 하고픈 말이 많아 <br>내게 말해 줄래 네가 보고파 <br>내 하루하루가 너무 힘들다고 <br>내게 돌아와 달라고 <br>하룻밤의 꿈 <br>너를 다시 볼 수 있는 꿈 <br>모두 거짓이라도 나는 <br>이 꿈 안에서 널 그리며 살아 <br>요즘 난 매일 널 만나 <br>우리 예전에 그 모습 그대로 <br>]]></content><category term="은하수공장" label="은하수공장"/><category term="하룻밤의 꿈" label="하룻밤의 꿈"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/달팽듀오/궁평항/</id><title>달팽듀오 - 궁평항 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:45:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:45:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%AC%ED%8C%BD%EB%93%80%EC%98%A4/%EA%B6%81%ED%8F%89%ED%95%AD/" title="달팽듀오 - 궁평항 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[차 문을 닫고 <br>출발 하는 거야 <br>우리 강아지도 데려 가자 <br>바다를 가르는 <br>도로를 찾아서 가자 <br>난 뒷자리에 앉아서 갈 꺼야 <br>눈물이 날지도 모르니까 <br>아무에게도 보이기 <br>싫은 거 있잖아 <br>이해 하지 <br>그곳에 닿으면 <br>바다에게 달려가 고백 할래 <br>내 눈물을 모두 가져 가라고 <br>더 이상 힘들긴 너무 싫다고 <br>도와 달라고 <br>파도에 실려 불어온 <br>시원한 바닷바람이 <br>내 마음을 데려 갔나 봐 <br>눈부시게 반짝이는 <br>햇살 같은 물결들이 <br>데려갔나 봐 <br>난 정말 고마워 <br>차 문을 열고 <br>내려보는 거야 <br>우리 강아지도 달려가게 <br>내 손을 잡아 당기는 <br>바람을 따라서 가자 <br>누구에게도 말 할 수 없었던 <br>내 슬픔을 넌 볼 수 있겠지 <br>멈출 수 없는 미련과 <br>그리움 까지도 <br>이해 하지 <br>그곳에 닿으면 <br>바다에게 달려가 고백 할래 <br>내 눈물을 모두 가져 가라고 <br>더 이상 힘들긴 너무 싫다고 <br>도와 달라고 <br>파도에 실려 불어온 <br>시원한 바닷바람이 <br>내 마음을 데려 갔나 봐 <br>눈부시게 반짝이는 <br>햇살 같은 물결들이 <br>데려갔나 봐 <br>난 정말 고마워 <br>]]></content><category term="달팽듀오" label="달팽듀오"/><category term="궁평항" label="궁평항"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/달팽듀오/Acoustic/</id><title>달팽듀오 - Acoustic - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:45:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:45:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%AC%ED%8C%BD%EB%93%80%EC%98%A4/Acoustic/" title="달팽듀오 - Acoustic - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여유론 토요일 아침 <br>뒤늦게 잠에서 깨어 <br>졸리운 두 눈 비비고 <br>햇살을 맞이하기 <br>피곤했던 한주의 일들은 <br>모두 잊어 버리고 <br>오늘 하루를 행복한 <br>음악으로 시작하기 <br>오늘은 <br>Acoustic Acoustic <br>Acoustic Acoustic <br>따뜻한 커피 한잔과 <br>상쾌한 공기 한 모금 <br>나른한 휴일 오후엔 <br>젤 좋은 나의 처방전 <br>복잡했던 한 주의 <br>일들과 수많은 고민들 <br>오늘 만큼은 행복한 <br>멜로디로 날려보내기 <br>오늘은 <br>Acoustic Acoustic <br>Acoustic Acoustic <br>수많은 노래가 내게 있지만 <br>오늘 하루 가장 듣고픈 <br>내 맘의 휴식 같은 너 그 노래 <br>Acoustic Acoustic <br>Acoustic Acoustic <br>Acoustic Acoustic <br>Acoustic Acoustic <br>]]></content><category term="달팽듀오" label="달팽듀오"/><category term="Acoustic" label="Acoustic"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신유준/눈물로_고하는_이별/</id><title>신유준 - 눈물로 고하는 이별 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:45:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:45:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9C%A0%EC%A4%80/%EB%88%88%EB%AC%BC%EB%A1%9C_%EA%B3%A0%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84/" title="신유준 - 눈물로 고하는 이별 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밤비 내리는 창밖을 보며 <br>아무 말 없는 두 사람 <br>오랜 그 옛날 내 곁을 떠난 <br>당신과 마주한 지금 <br>아름다운 그 추억이 <br>눈물로 되살아나 <br>내 가슴을 딛고 가지만 <br>안돼 이러면 안 돼 <br>내가 이러면 안 돼 <br>행복하냔 그 물음에 <br>쓴웃음만 남기고 <br>쓸쓸하게 고하는 이별 <br>밤비 내리는 창밖을 보며 <br>아무 말 없는 두 사람 <br>오랜 그 옛날 내 곁을 떠난 <br>당신과 마주한 지금 <br>아름다운 그 추억이 <br>눈물로 되살아나 <br>내 가슴을 딛고 가지만 <br>안 돼 이러면 안 돼 <br>내가 이러면 안 돼 <br>행복하냔 그 물음에 <br>쓴웃음만 남기고 <br>쓸쓸하게 고하는 이별 <br>행복하냔 그 물음에 <br>쓴웃음만 남기고 <br>쓸쓸하게 고하는 이별 <br>]]></content><category term="신유준" label="신유준"/><category term="눈물로 고하는 이별" label="눈물로 고하는 이별"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신유준/님_떠난_뒤/</id><title>신유준 - 님 떠난 뒤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:46:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:46:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9C%A0%EC%A4%80/%EB%8B%98_%EB%96%A0%EB%82%9C_%EB%92%A4/" title="신유준 - 님 떠난 뒤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한없이 흐르는 <br>눈물이여 <br>님 떠난 뒤라서 <br>더욱 슬퍼지네 <br>흐르는 눈물은 <br>닦으면 되지만 <br>떠나간 내 님은 <br>어이 할까요 <br>생각 말아요 <br>떠난 님인데 <br>생각하면 무얼 하나 <br>가버린 님인데 <br>멀리 멀리 <br>떠난 님이여 <br>생각 말아요 <br>떠난 님인데 <br>생각하면 무얼 하나 <br>가버린 님인데 <br>멀리 멀리 <br>떠난 님이여 <br>멀리 멀리 <br>떠난 님이여 <br>]]></content><category term="신유준" label="신유준"/><category term="님 떠난 뒤" label="님 떠난 뒤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신유준/비_내리는_거리에서/</id><title>신유준 - 비 내리는 거리에서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:46:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:46:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9C%A0%EC%A4%80/%EB%B9%84_%EB%82%B4%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_%EA%B1%B0%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C/" title="신유준 - 비 내리는 거리에서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비 내리는 거리 걸어봐요 <br>그곳에 빗물을 느껴봐요 <br>너무도 아련히 떠오르는 <br>추억이 생각나요 <br>밤거리를 나는 거닐어요 <br>희미한 불빛을 바라봐요 <br>흐르는 그대의 눈물 속에 <br>진실이 느껴지네 <br>나는 한줄기 <br>차가운 빗물이 되어 <br>가슴 속 마음을 <br>전해주고파 <br>너의 가슴에 흐르는 <br>애달픈 사랑을 <br>떨어지는 비여 <br>그대 위로해 줘요 <br>아 그대여 <br>외로움에 슬퍼야 하나 <br>비 내리는 거리에서 <br>나는 눈물 흘려요 <br>나는 한줄기 <br>차가운 빗물이 되어 <br>가슴 속 마음을 <br>전해주고파 <br>너의 가슴에 흐르는 <br>애달픈 사랑을 <br>떨어지는 비여 <br>그대 위로해 줘요 <br>아 그대여 <br>외로움에 슬퍼야 하나 <br>비 내리는 거리에서 <br>나는 눈물 흘려요 <br>비 내리는 거리에서 <br>나는 눈물 흘려요 <br>]]></content><category term="신유준" label="신유준"/><category term="비 내리는 거리에서" label="비 내리는 거리에서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신유준/보고_싶어요/</id><title>신유준 - 보고 싶어요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:46:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:46:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9C%A0%EC%A4%80/%EB%B3%B4%EA%B3%A0_%EC%8B%B6%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="신유준 - 보고 싶어요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대 너무 보고 싶어요 <br>그대 너무 보고 싶어요 <br>더 이상 나는 <br>참을 수 없어 <br>시간이 지나가면 <br>잊혀진다고 <br>그 누가 말을 했나요 <br>나는 너무 힘이 들어요 <br>그대가 없는 이 세상 <br>떨어져 살다 보면 <br>멀어진다고 <br>그 누가 말을 했나요 <br>지난밤 꿈속에서 <br>그대 모습이 <br>너무도 그리워져요 <br>너무나 보고 싶어요 <br>너무나 보고 싶어요 <br>그대가 보고 싶어요 <br>너무나 그리워져요 <br>너무나 그리워져요 <br>그대가 보고 싶어요 <br>그대 너무 보고 싶어요 <br>나는 너무 힘이 들어요 <br>그대가 없는 이 세상 <br>떨어져 살다보면 <br>멀어진다고 <br>그 누가 말을 했나요 <br>지난밤 꿈속에서 <br>그대 모습이 <br>너무도 그리워져요 <br>너무나 보고 싶어요 <br>너무나 보고 싶어요 <br>그대가 보고 싶어요 <br>너무나 그리워져요 <br>너무나 그리워져요 <br>그대가 보고 싶어요 <br>너무나 보고 싶어요 <br>너무나 보고 싶어요 <br>그대가 보고 싶어요 <br>너무나 그리워져요 <br>너무나 그리워져요 <br>그대가 보고 싶어요 <br>그대가 보고 싶어요 <br>]]></content><category term="신유준" label="신유준"/><category term="보고 싶어요" label="보고 싶어요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신유준/목척교_연가/</id><title>신유준 - 목척교 연가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:46:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:46:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9C%A0%EC%A4%80/%EB%AA%A9%EC%B2%99%EA%B5%90_%EC%97%B0%EA%B0%80/" title="신유준 - 목척교 연가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가버린 것과 <br>올 것의 그 중간을 <br>헤아릴 수 없는 <br>엇갈림 속에 끼여 <br>나는 지금은 어디쯤을 <br>걸어가고 있는 것일까 <br>치열한 도심은 <br>목이 타는데 <br>끝이랄까 시작이랄까 <br>이 멍청한 나의 시간아 <br>미움과 사랑의 <br>흐름 위에서 <br>다시는 못 만날 <br>그 절망의 거릴 두고 <br>헤아릴 수 없는 <br>엇갈림 속에 끼여 <br>지금 나는 어디쯤을 <br>건너고 있는 것일까 <br>치열한 도심은 <br>목이 타는데 <br>끝이랄까 시작이랄까 <br>이 멍청한 나의 시간아 <br>미움과 사랑의 <br>흐름 위에서 <br>다시는 못 만날 <br>그 절망의 거릴 두고 <br>헤아릴 수 없는 <br>엇갈림 속에 끼여 <br>지금 나는 어디쯤을 <br>건너고 있는 것일까 <br>지금 나는 어디쯤을 <br>건너고 있는 것일까 <br>]]></content><category term="신유준" label="신유준"/><category term="목척교 연가" label="목척교 연가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김동궁/리턴_Return_Feat_아이노스/</id><title>김동궁 - 리턴 (Return) (Feat. 아이노스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:46:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:46:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%8F%99%EA%B6%81/%EB%A6%AC%ED%84%B4_Return_Feat_%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8%EC%8A%A4/" title="김동궁 - 리턴 (Return) (Feat. 아이노스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[누군가 날 부르면 <br>아무런 말도 듣지못해 <br>늘 내곁에 머물러도 <br>난 아무것도 보지못해 <br>always when I fell in the swamp <br>so I just for needs in his name <br>Jesus you are my lord <br>you are my lord my lord <br>Because you are my soul <br>you are my soul <br>I pray in this name of all mighty god <br>걷다가 힘이들면 <br>잠시 어딘가 쉬고 싶어 <br>엉켜버린 감정과 <br>겁 없는 나를 내려놓고 <br>always when I fell in the swamp <br>so I just for needs in his name <br>Jesus you are my lord <br>you are my lord my lord <br>Because you are my soul <br>you are my soul <br>I pray in this name of all mighty god <br>I will praise the lord <br>I will praise the lord <br>I will praise the lord <br>I will bless the lord <br>I will bless the lord <br>I will bless the lord <br>we will praise the lord <br>we will praise the lord <br>we will praise the lord <br>we will bless the lord <br>we will bless the lord <br>we will bless the lord <br>Jesus you are my lord <br>you are my lord my lord <br>Because you are my soul <br>you are my soul <br>Jesus you are my lord <br>you are my lord my lord <br>Because you are my soul <br>you are my soul <br>I pray in this name of all mighty god <br>you are my lord <br>you are my soul <br>]]></content><category term="김동궁" label="김동궁"/><category term="리턴 (Return) (Feat. 아이노스)" label="리턴 (Return) (Feat. 아이노스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조인_ZOIN/요즘_널_생각해/</id><title>조인 (ZOIN) - 요즘 널 생각해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:46:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:46:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%9D%B8_ZOIN/%EC%9A%94%EC%A6%98_%EB%84%90_%EC%83%9D%EA%B0%81%ED%95%B4/" title="조인 (ZOIN) - 요즘 널 생각해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어떻게 지내는지 <br>잘 지내고 있는 건지 <br>갑자기 궁금해 <br>별 이유 없이 <br>잘 지내 나는 그때보다 더 <br>할 일도 많아지고 <br>요즘엔 통 바빠서 정신 없어 <br>그 골목에 너와 나 <br>남긴 흔적들 아직 있을까 <br>그땐 정말 바보같이 <br>우리 원 없이 그토록 좋았는데 <br>너와 나만 아는 <br>둘만의 그 작은 공간 <br>누구에게도 말할 수 없는 <br>우리 비밀 <br>서로를 눈에 담았던 <br>모든 순간까지 <br>참 철없이도 사랑한 <br>시간들 생각나서 <br>그 언젠가 너와 나 <br>약속했던 그 말 기억해 <br>오랜 시간이 흐른 뒤에도 <br>서로의 곁에서 <br>행복을 주자 <br>약속을 지키지 못해서 <br>내가 너무 미안해 <br>난 아직 여전히 못났어 <br>참 그리워 그때의 우리 <br>혹시라도 우리 정말 <br>괜찮아 진다면 <br>우연이라도 너와 나 <br>마주치는 날엔 <br>예전처럼은 아닌 거 <br>나도 잘 알지만 <br>참 철없이도 <br>사랑한 시간들 <br>너와 나만 아는 <br>둘만의 그 작은 공간 <br>누구에게도 말할 수 없는 <br>우리 비밀 <br>서로를 눈에 담았던 <br>모든 순간까지 <br>우리의 그날들을 <br>요즘 널 생각해 <br>요즘 널 생각해 <br>요즘 널 생각해 <br>요즘 널 생각해 <br>]]></content><category term="조인 (ZOIN)" label="조인 (ZOIN)"/><category term="요즘 널 생각해" label="요즘 널 생각해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정아름/궁금해/</id><title>정아름 - 궁금해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:46:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:46:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%95%84%EB%A6%84/%EA%B6%81%EA%B8%88%ED%95%B4/" title="정아름 - 궁금해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 니가 자기 전에 먹는 <br>시원한 캔맥주 맛을 알았으면 <br>나는 니가 삼겹살에 먹는 <br>소주 한잔을 좋아했으면 <br>Uh Uh 누구나 좋아하는 그런 <br>뻔하고 뻔한 시시한 것 말고 <br>Uh Uh 있잖아 아는 사람만 아는 <br>그런 멋진 거 <br>Oh 궁금해 궁금해 난 니가 <br>어떤 책을 보는지 너무 궁금해 <br>Oh 궁금해 궁금해 난 니가 <br>나 같은 여자는 <br>어떻게 생각하는건지 <br>너무나 궁금해 <br>나는 니가 계획 없이 떠난 <br>기차 여행의 낭만을 알았으면 <br>나는 니가 늦은 밤에 내리는 <br>빗소리를 좋아했으면 <br>Uh Uh 누구나 좋아하는 그런 <br>뻔하고 뻔한 시시한 것 말고 <br>Uh Uh 있잖아 아는 사람만 아는 <br>그런 멋진 거 <br>Oh 궁금해 궁금해 난 니가 <br>어떤 영활 보는지 너무 궁금해 <br>Oh 궁금해 궁금해 난 니가 <br>나 같은 여자는 <br>어떻게 생각하는건지 <br>너무나 궁금해 <br>너에게 물어볼까 <br>처음을 좋아하는지 <br>이슬을 더 좋아하는지 <br>용기내 물어볼까 <br>하루키를 좋아하는지 <br>반고흐를 좋아하는지 <br>Oh 궁금해 궁금해 난 니가 <br>어떤 노랠 듣는지 너무 궁금해 <br>Oh 궁금해 궁금해 난 니가 <br>나 같은 여자는 <br>어떻게 생각하는건지 <br>너무나 궁금해 궁금해 궁금해 <br>너무나 궁금해 궁금해 궁금해 <br>너무나 궁금해 궁금해 궁금해 <br>너무나 궁금해 궁금해 궁금해 <br>]]></content><category term="정아름" label="정아름"/><category term="궁금해" label="궁금해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이석준/라면연가/</id><title>이석준 - 라면연가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:46:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:46:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%9D%EC%A4%80/%EB%9D%BC%EB%A9%B4%EC%97%B0%EA%B0%80/" title="이석준 - 라면연가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[친구를 만나려 했는데 <br>여자친구에게서 <br>연락이 와 <br>집안일 도와준다면 <br>라면 같이 먹재 <br>친구야 미안해 <br>전철을 타고 <br>덜컹덜컹 <br>골목길 두리번 거리다 <br>담배한대 물고서 <br>심쿵심쿵 <br>웃으며 반기는 여자친구 <br>이게 모지 그녀얼굴 <br>청소하는데 화장을 했네 <br>짧은 반바지에 <br>마루에 먼지를 털어 <br>turn up <br>걸레질 하고서 <br>what up what up <br>whatelse umm <br>잠자리 인형들을 정돈 <br>더러운 건 <br>그냥 거기 내버려둬 <br>하루에 다하지는 못해 <br>수고비는 no thanks <br>나 너무 오래 했나봐 uh <br>허리 아파 오늘쉬고 <br>다음에 해야 될 것 같아 <br>음 상상속이 라면 그렇지 <br>웃으며 들어오는 그녀 아빠 <br>이게 모지 아빠 손에 <br>편의점 봉투에 라면이 가득 <br>삼분이면 ok <br>인사해 소개하는 그녀 얼굴 <br>왜 이리도 야속해 <br>나의 마음이 들키진 않았나 <br>친구야 미안해 <br>꿈이라면 fancy 라면 <br>과거 라면 돌아갈래 <br>꿈이라면 fancy 라면 <br>과거 라면 돌아갈래 <br>꿈이라면 돌아갈래 <br>꿈이라면 <br>꿈이라면 <br>]]></content><category term="이석준" label="이석준"/><category term="라면연가" label="라면연가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/국나향/인생은/</id><title>국나향 - 인생은 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:47:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:47:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B5%AD%EB%82%98%ED%96%A5/%EC%9D%B8%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%80/" title="국나향 - 인생은 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내인생은 어디에서 왔다가 <br>어디로 흘러 흘러 가는가 <br>덧없는 인생살이 <br>가도 가도 멀기만 한데 <br>아 아 세상사 헛된 꿈을 버리고 <br>미래를 향하여 <br>오늘을 사는 인생 <br>희망가를 불러보세 <br>돌고 도는 인생 벙글벙글 돌아 <br>발길 닿는 곳까지 <br>내인생은 어디에서 왔다가 <br>어디로 흘러 흘러 가는가 <br>덧없는 인생살이 <br>가도 가도 멀기만 한데 <br>아 아 세상사 헛된 꿈을 버리고 <br>미래를 향하여 <br>오늘을 사는 인생 <br>희망가를 불러보세 <br>돌고 도는 인생 벙글벙글 돌아 <br>발길 닿는 곳까지 <br>]]></content><category term="국나향" label="국나향"/><category term="인생은" label="인생은"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/국나향/목련꽃_사랑/</id><title>국나향 - 목련꽃 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:47:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:47:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B5%AD%EB%82%98%ED%96%A5/%EB%AA%A9%EB%A0%A8%EA%BD%83_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="국나향 - 목련꽃 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대를 향한 목련꽃 <br>꽃잎 벙그는 이 아침 <br>삶의 환희가 나를 감싸 <br>나는 행복하네 <br>불타는 태양이 열기속에 <br>해맑은 웃음을 가슴에 담고 <br>칠색빛 무지개 닦아오는 <br>하늘빛 봄햇볕 <br>아 아 나는 행복하네 <br>나는 행복하네 <br>그대를 향한 목련꽃 <br>꽃잎 벙그는 이 아침 <br>삶의 환희가 나를 감싸 <br>나는 행복하네 <br>불타는 태양이 열기 속에 <br>해맑은 웃음을 가슴에 담고 <br>칠색빛 무지개 닦아오는 <br>하늘빛 봄햇볕 <br>아 아 나는 행복하네 <br>나는 행복하네 나는 행복하네 <br>]]></content><category term="국나향" label="국나향"/><category term="목련꽃 사랑" label="목련꽃 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/국나향/열린세상/</id><title>국나향 - 열린세상 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:47:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:47:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B5%AD%EB%82%98%ED%96%A5/%EC%97%B4%EB%A6%B0%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81/" title="국나향 - 열린세상 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[정다운 거리마다 <br>활기찬 걸음으로 <br>푸른 꿈 희망 안고 <br>모두가 들로 산으로 <br>콧노래 흥얼대며 <br>휘파람을 부르네 <br>모두가 하나되는 미래를 만들자 <br>열린세상 평화위해 <br>행복의 열매씨를 뿌리자 <br>서로가 웃음꽃피는 <br>희망찬 걸음으로 <br>내일의 희망 안고 <br>우리 모두 달려가자 <br>정겨운 풍경속에 <br>강바람을 타고 가자 <br>행복의 희망봉을 향해 달려가자 <br>사랑의 열매맺어 <br>우리 모두 행복하리 <br>콧노래 흥얼대며 <br>휘파람을 부르네 <br>모두가 하나되는 <br>미래를 만들자 <br>열린세상 평화위해 <br>행복의 열매씨를 뿌리자 <br>찬란한 태양을 향해 <br>열린세상 만들어가자 <br>]]></content><category term="국나향" label="국나향"/><category term="열린세상" label="열린세상"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/국나향/신나게_노래하자/</id><title>국나향 - 신나게 노래하자 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:47:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:47:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B5%AD%EB%82%98%ED%96%A5/%EC%8B%A0%EB%82%98%EA%B2%8C_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98%ED%95%98%EC%9E%90/" title="국나향 - 신나게 노래하자 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리의 삶속에는 <br>수많은 역경이 있지만 <br>말끔히 걷어내고 <br>행복의 길을 달린다 <br>행복한 사회상을 <br>우리들이 만들고 <br>가슴속 희망채워 <br>신나게 노래하자 <br>다함께 손뼉치며 <br>즐겁게 노래하자 팡팡팡 <br>한세상 사노라면 <br>근심도 있겠지만 <br>강력한 힘으로 <br>말끔히 걷어내고 <br>온누리 청보라로 <br>행복의 길을 걷고 <br>가슴속 희망채워 <br>신나게 노래하자 다함께 <br>손뼉치며 즐겁게 <br>노래하자 팡팡팡 <br>행복한 사회상을 <br>우리들이 만들고 <br>가슴속 희망 채워 <br>신나게 노래하자 <br>다함께 손뼉치며 <br>즐겁게 노래하자 팡팡팡 <br>]]></content><category term="국나향" label="국나향"/><category term="신나게 노래하자" label="신나게 노래하자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/국나향/그때_그_시절/</id><title>국나향 - 그때 그 시절 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:47:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:47:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B5%AD%EB%82%98%ED%96%A5/%EA%B7%B8%EB%95%8C_%EA%B7%B8_%EC%8B%9C%EC%A0%88/" title="국나향 - 그때 그 시절 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그옛날 생각이 난다 <br>소꿉장난 뛰며놀던 <br>친구들 철들어서 <br>떠난고향 잊을 수 없는 <br>그시절이 그리워 <br>어린시절 자라던곳 <br>얼마나 변했을까 <br>세월가도 못잊을 <br>그리운 친구들 <br>어느곳에 살고있는지 <br>추억도 새로워라 <br>그때 그시절 <br>가고파라 가고파 <br>내가살던 고향집에 <br>지금은 그누가 <br>그누가 살고 있는지 <br>그옛날 생각이 난다 <br>소꿉장난 뛰며놀던 <br>친구들 철들어서 <br>떠난고향 잊을 수 없는 <br>그시절이 그리워 <br>어린시절 자라던곳 <br>얼마나 변했을까 <br>세월가도 못잊을 <br>그리운 친구들 <br>어느곳에 살고있는지 <br>추억도 새로워라 <br>그때 그시절 <br>가고파라 가고파 <br>내가살던 고향집에 <br>지금은 그누가 <br>그누가 살고 있는지 <br>]]></content><category term="국나향" label="국나향"/><category term="그때 그 시절" label="그때 그 시절"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/국나향/어머님_사랑/</id><title>국나향 - 어머님 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:47:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:47:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B5%AD%EB%82%98%ED%96%A5/%EC%96%B4%EB%A8%B8%EB%8B%98_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="국나향 - 어머님 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[부모님 살아생전 <br>철없어 몰랐다가 <br>이자식 부모되어 <br>이제야 알았습니다 <br>가슴풀어 생명주신 <br>우리 어머니 그은혜 <br>갚을 길 없어 <br>눈물만 고입니다 <br>어머니 내어머니 <br>그은혜 어찌 갚으리오 <br>어머님 참사랑을 <br>내어히 갚으리오 <br>바다보다 깊은사랑 <br>하늘보다 더 높은사랑 <br>이목숨 다하도록 <br>그어찌 갚으리오 <br>살아생전 고생하시던 <br>우리어머니 불러도 <br>대답없는 대답없는 <br>우리어머니 <br>불러도 <br>대답없는 대답없는 <br>우리어머니 어머니 <br>]]></content><category term="국나향" label="국나향"/><category term="어머님 사랑" label="어머님 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코넛/넌_나를_아름답게_해/</id><title>코넛 - 넌 나를 아름답게 해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:47:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:47:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%84%9B/%EB%84%8C_%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EC%95%84%EB%A6%84%EB%8B%B5%EA%B2%8C_%ED%95%B4/" title="코넛 - 넌 나를 아름답게 해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쳇바퀴 굴러가듯 매일 <br>똑같은 뻔한 하루 <br>그때 운명처럼 네가 <br>나타났어 거짓말처럼 <br>내게 무심한 듯 매번 <br>차가웁게 대하는 너 <br>갑자기 다정하게 <br>내게 다가와 <br>Please tell me I need you <br>지금 너는 나를 아름답게 해 <br>넌 나의 심장을 설레게 해 <br>내게로 다가와 나를 잡아줘 <br>내가 너에게 머물 수 있게 <br>언제 어디서나 매번 <br>달콤하게 감싸오네 <br>초콜릿처럼 내게 다가와 <br>Please tell me I love you <br>지금 너는 나를 아름답게 해 <br>넌나의 심장을 설레게 해 <br>내게로 다가와 나를 잡아줘 <br>내가 너에게 머물 수 있게 <br>지금 너는 나를 아름답게 해 <br>넌 나의 마음을 꿈꾸게 해 <br>내게로 다가와 나를 잡아줘 <br>지금 너는 나를 위태롭게 해 <br>넌 나의 마음을 꿈꾸게 해 <br>내게로 다가와 나를 잡아줘 <br>내가 너에게 머물 수 있게 <br>내가 너에게 남을 수 있게 <br>]]></content><category term="코넛" label="코넛"/><category term="넌 나를 아름답게 해" label="넌 나를 아름답게 해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Common/Home_Feat_Bilal/</id><title>Common - Home (Feat. Bilal) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:47:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:47:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Common/Home_Feat_Bilal/" title="Common - Home (Feat. Bilal) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A man who's genius <br>and freedoms and <br>Ability to communicate and <br>To talk and to touch chords <br>A man who has the ability <br>and the audacity <br>And the of God to stand up <br>to stand up <br>Heard the sound of the trumpets <br>the voice from the throne <br>Seen the twenty four elders <br>and I knew I was home <br>I was told to write songs <br>for the people <br>Take the original Hebrews <br>on an Exodus of Black Excellence <br>Tell them to invest in us <br>and make testaments <br>about each other <br>Or how we sisters <br>and brothers <br>Cover the land in corners <br>of poems and stone <br>Go hard with it <br>let em know you God with it <br>Even though I authored it <br>let no one margin it <br>And make it all about paper <br>or first weeks sales <br>Though this is from Heaven <br>give 'em verses from Hell <br>Those that fell off the path <br>bring them back to the Mass <br>The staff can be your microphone <br>Your name is Common <br>You was born to fight the norm <br>Take house niggas outta darkness <br>till they lights is on <br>I'm a put a hyphen on your name <br>Rapper actor activist <br>You the one that can reach <br>into the black abyss <br>Stars this asterix <br>show em what a classic is <br>Freedom riders need passengers <br>And your lyrics use scriptures <br>and passages <br>To make them rise like Lazarus <br>And resurrected again <br>they'll put disrespect <br>on your name <br>and respect it again <br>Every section you in <br>bless em and keep bussin' <br>If they don't like it <br>shake the dust <br>and say 'fuck em' <br>Until you get home <br>I'm the one you trust in <br>I'm happy to be in any place <br>Where God's name is remembered <br>Soon I will be gone <br>with the trouble of this world <br>Trouble of this world <br>trouble of this world <br>Soon I will be gone <br>with the trouble of this world <br>Going home to live <br>Going home to live <br>Going home to live <br>Go into the wilderness <br>like Mussa on a pilgrimage <br>Streets are villages <br>speak with diligence <br>And authority to fake God <br>of pharisees and sadducees <br>Give them that Gardley free <br>from the Black Odyssey <br>Yo pardon me <br>you the God bodily <br>Functioning on earth <br>as a part of me <br>That's why I gave you artistry <br>Go into the hoods <br>with the shooters <br>and the strippers <br>Forget the New World Order <br>New Jerusalem is with us <br>Tell sisters they earths <br>and goddesses <br>If they got bottom <br>don't get caught <br>in a bottomless <br>Pit there's a lot of us fit <br>for the kingdom is near <br>You can tell by the wars <br>and how the seasons appear <br>You'll appear in circles <br>in Hollywood <br>I birthed you <br>And Chicago you know <br>how to parlay good <br>You'll get Oscars <br>Emmys and Grammys <br>Give those to your family <br>don't get caught up in the vanity <br>Or the world's insanity <br>Soon I will be gone <br>with the trouble of this world <br>Trouble of this world <br>trouble of this world <br>Soon I will be gone <br>with the trouble of this world <br>Going home to live <br>Going home to live <br>Going home to live <br>With God <br>To those of you who are unfamiliar <br>with those words <br>They mean in English <br>Peace be unto you <br>]]></content><category term="Common" label="Common"/><category term="Home (Feat. Bilal)" label="Home (Feat. Bilal)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Not_One_Of_The_Lonely_Tonight/</id><title>Howard Jones - Not One Of The Lonely Tonight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Not_One_Of_The_Lonely_Tonight/" title="Howard Jones - Not One Of The Lonely Tonight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bring me down to earth Take this weight from tired shoulders Kiss me tenderly Let me drown in waves of your love You part the trees so I Can cherish things that matter Your single voice sounds through A room of din and chatter Oh take me home When the streetlights shine above Safe in your arms So simple to me Safe in your arms Oh so temporary Safe in you arms Oh so tenderly Not one of the lonely tonight Flying hectically Through a cloud of buts and maybes Passing frantically Over nights and days unended You turn my head and laugh When my world turns sour You give me strength to pass Through my darkest hour Oh take me home When the streetlights shine above]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Not One Of The Lonely Tonight" label="Not One Of The Lonely Tonight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Nothing_To_Fear/</id><title>Howard Jones - Nothing To Fear - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Nothing_To_Fear/" title="Howard Jones - Nothing To Fear - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What freezes love in your eyes What steals the force from your life What holds us ransom tonight What stops you seeing yourself? Only fear can stand On potential's hands This is the greatest day of your life If you make it And the old spells you know They can be broken Nothing to fear Nothing to fear The greatest faults can be beaten The grandest problems defeated Impossible choices completed Infinite pain will be treated Only fear can stand On potential's hands This is the greatest day of your life And we made it And the old spells you know 'Cause they can be broken Nothing to fear Nothing to fear This is the greatest day of your life And we've made it Break the old spells Oh, let them be broken Nothing to fear No, nothing to fear This is the greatest day Break the old spells and throw them away Break the old spells Don't y'know they can be broken No, Nothing to fear Nothing to fear Nothing to fear Nothing to fear]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Nothing To Fear" label="Nothing To Fear"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Let_Me_Be_The_First_To_Know/</id><title>Howard Jones - Let Me Be The First To Know - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Let_Me_Be_The_First_To_Know/" title="Howard Jones - Let Me Be The First To Know - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If you find a time when things just seem to fall apart And there's no way to keep a cheery face When the sight of your own reflection only breaks your heart And all your dreams have given up the chase Pick up the telephone You know I'm always home Any old time of night or day Let me be the first to know Let me be the first to know Let me be the first to know If you find a time when you just have to walk away Because of a call to pastures new You're in need of some fresh words to wish you on your way You need to fly on up and touch the moon Sharing this temporary weight No time to hesitate I will be everything you need Let me be the first to know Let me be the first to know Let me be the first to know Let me be the first... We're water breaking on an endless wave Potential bursting from the sea Compassion is what sets our minds apart Be cheerful when you break The chains of morality Oo, sharing this welcome weight Don't even hesitate I will be everything you need Let me be the first to know Let me be the first to know Let me be the first to know Let me be the first to know Let me be the first one to know]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Let Me Be The First To Know" label="Let Me Be The First To Know"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Dreamin_On/</id><title>Howard Jones - Dreamin` On - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Dreamin_On/" title="Howard Jones - Dreamin` On - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know but I've been told There's a place where dreams are bought and sold I'd like to steal me a dream with you Together we can sail the oceans blue Do you feel like I do? Don't get me wrong But I need your love And I feel like dreaming on But I wake to find you gone Hope you like the things I say I look forward to the day When I can take you into my life One day you just might say you'll be my wife And I don't want to push I don't want to rush you But I need your love And I feel like dreaming on But I wake to find you gone And I feel like dreaming... Throw this caution to the wind Be my lover, be my friend If it goes wrong we'll start anew What else are we going to do? And I feel like dreaming on But I wake to find you gone And I feel like dreaming on But I wake to find you gone And I feel like dreaming on]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Dreamin` On" label="Dreamin` On"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Wedding_Song/</id><title>Howard Jones - Wedding Song - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Wedding_Song/" title="Howard Jones - Wedding Song - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can see you On your wedding day With the one you love To share the way A life ahead of you Youth left behind Go out and make yourself Some memories Dispair and pleasure Faced at every turn And there's children To save from harm's way Three thousand doorways Reveal a thousand more Treasure each moment Forever more I promise to love you and do my best for you I need you to help me to find my strength Walk with me all through my life My lover my husband my wife Share this journey with me Write this story with me Life comes and it will go And there's no time to sit and watch the grass grow When we are old and grey you know we'll say We went and made ourselves some memories We're starting our life We're starting together now I need you to help me to find my strength Walk with me all through my life My lover my husband my wife Share this journey with me Write this story with me]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Wedding Song" label="Wedding Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Back_In_Your_Life/</id><title>Howard Jones - Back In Your Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Back_In_Your_Life/" title="Howard Jones - Back In Your Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Soon the warm night breezes roll on in A steamy blanket for the shore This is streetlight time You said you were mine So the fool believes What the night conceives The light of love is in your eyes Is in your smile again Is in your life again Was a time when love grew cold for you Turned your back on memories I was there for you I will see you through Darkest hours fade The promises we made Were not the kind to fade away We'll face another day We'll face another day When that was yesterday Will the ocean rollers bring you home Or will they take you out to sea This is real-time And you are still mine The fool that loves his dreams Breaks the cruelest schemes The light of love is in your eyes Is in your smile again Is in your life again Back in your smile again Back in your life again]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Back In Your Life" label="Back In Your Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/We_Make_The_Weather/</id><title>Howard Jones - We Make The Weather - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/We_Make_The_Weather/" title="Howard Jones - We Make The Weather - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Heaven is a somewhere locked inside and I must find the key Wish I'd never locked the door Ordinary things in life are where this heaven likes to be Hold the sky, feet on the floor Hold the sky, feet on the floor We make our sun to shine We make our space and time We make the weather We make it change Hell is not somewhere but a state of mind I choose to be When my faith in life has gone Cruelty rebounds to hurt itself puts shackles on the free Vicious circle carries on Hold the sky, feet on the floor We make our sun to shine We make our space and time We make the weather We make it change We make the weather We make it change Time to judge the act don't judge the actor of the circumstance Time to free compassion's world Life is not the end we're passing through like bubbles on the sea Time to learn and time to mend Hold the sky, feet on the floor We make our sun to shine We make our space and time We make the weather We made a change We make the weather We make a change]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="We Make The Weather" label="We Make The Weather"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Sleep_My_Angel/</id><title>Howard Jones - Sleep My Angel - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Sleep_My_Angel/" title="Howard Jones - Sleep My Angel - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sleep my angel It is time for bed I will be there To watch over you I'll protect you from the world And the voices in your head I'll be with you With my life I will defend I'll be with you I will be there in the end And I'll cry your tears As you feel every pain Coax out the sun From the endless rain Thought I'd never feel So much love for another I'll be with you I will be there in the end Love that is there Through the false and the real Love that desires No reward and no gain As I hold your tiny hand You'll never know how I feel There's a promise With my life I will defend I will be there with you 'til the end And I'll cry your tears As you feel every pain Coax out the sun From the endless rain Thought I'd never feel So much love for another I'll be with you I will be there 'til the end All that potential Bursting inside Let me help you on your journey Let me help you with life I will be there with you 'til the end]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Sleep My Angel" label="Sleep My Angel"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/If_You_Love/</id><title>Howard Jones - If You Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/If_You_Love/" title="Howard Jones - If You Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Chorus:] If you love You know you're gonna feel the hurt See the flowers Growin' from the muddy earth You never see the sun You're never gonna feel the rain With your life under glass In the middle lane You'll never feel the joy Never feel the pain [Chorus] Try to build a house on top of the highest tree It's dangerous and a bit risky But what about the view See the clouds and the mountains too [Chorus] Get your hands dirty Get a little insane Come out and play with me Barefoot in the rain If you love You know you're gonna feel the hurt (Feel the joy, feel the pain) See the flowers Growin' from the muddy earth (You see the sun and then you see the rain) You never see the sun You're never gonna feel the rain With your life under glass In the middle lane You'll never feel the joy Never feel the pain If you love You know you're gonna feel the hurt (Feel the joy, feel the pain) See the flowers Growin' from the muddy earth (You see the sun and then you see the rain) If you love You know you're gonna feel the hurt Growin' from the muddy earth (Feel the joy, feel the pain) Never feel the pain (You see the sun and then you see the rain)]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="If You Love" label="If You Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Let_The_People_Have_Their_Say/</id><title>Howard Jones - Let The People Have Their Say - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Let_The_People_Have_Their_Say/" title="Howard Jones - Let The People Have Their Say - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The tide is turning Its coming from the street Read your own wisdom Not the headlines Don't let them tell you Its fine the way it is Its our agenda We know better Let the people have their say Let the people show the way Every woman child and man Has the power in this land Now don't you worry The future will unfold If we are open and ready We all have choices Not just the chosen few So raise your voices Hold them steady Let the people have their say Let the people show the way Every woman child and man Has the power in this land (Let the people) The time has come now To realize our dream To claim our future...together Let the people have their say (Let the people have their say) Let the people show the way (Let the people show the way) Every woman child and man (Every woman child and man) Has the power in this land (Has the power in this land) Let the people have their say (Let the people have their say) Let the people show the way (Let the people show the way) Every woman child and man (Every woman child and man) Has the power in this land (Has the power in this land) Yeah yeah, yeah yo Yeah yeah Let the people have their say (Let the people have their say) Let the people show the way (Let the people show the way) Every woman child and man (Every woman child and man) Has the power in this land Yeah yeah, yeah yo Yeah yeah Yeah yeah, yeah yo Yeah yeah (Let the people show the way) Yeah yeah, yeah yo Yeah yeah (Let the people show the way) Yeah yeah, yeah yo Yeah yeah (Let the people show the way) Yeah yeah, yeah yo Yeah yeah (Let the people show the way)]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Let The People Have Their Say" label="Let The People Have Their Say"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Everything/</id><title>Howard Jones - Everything - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Everything/" title="Howard Jones - Everything - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want to be... The coffee in your pot I want to be the shower in the morning that's steamy and hot I want to be... The cherry that paints your lips I want to be the stick shift at your fingertips What ever I think of its never enough to show you my love I want to be your everything! I want to be... The wine that swirls around your tongue I want to be the Harley that you sit upon I want to be... The Elvis that makes you scream and shake I want to be the velvet that hugs your pretty shape What ever I think of its never enough to show you my love I want to be your everything! The trouble is you just don't know who the hell I am But I'll change that little detail, if I can What ever I think of its never enough to show you my love I want to be... I want to be your everything! [solo] The trouble is you don't even know who the hell I am But I'll change that little detail, if I can What ever I think of its never enough to show you my love I want to be... I want to be... I want to be your everything! I want to be your everything! (that's all just everything) I want to be your everything! (that's all just everything) I want to be your... I want to be your... I want to be your everything! (that's all just everything)]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Everything" label="Everything"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Tomorrow_Is_Now/</id><title>Howard Jones - Tomorrow Is Now - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Tomorrow_Is_Now/" title="Howard Jones - Tomorrow Is Now - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now You think the past is behind you But baby what's that on your back It looks to me like you're draggin' it around like a heavy pack Now we don't live in the present We're to busy hangin' on To what's been and gone so it comes again singin' the same old song Singin' na na-na na na Let it go oh oh Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now What are you going to ask for What are you going to create It's in you hands to build your own world forget about fate And I don't need to remind you Life is short and life is sweet And before you even know it past and future gonna meet Oh, every day and every way Good to go oh oh Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Not much to say It's all been said, anyway Not much to think about Just let go of yesterday Singin' na na-na na na Singin' na na-na na na Let it go oh oh Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Tomorrow Is Now" label="Tomorrow Is Now"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/YouRe_The_Buddah/</id><title>Howard Jones - You`Re The Buddah - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/YouRe_The_Buddah/" title="Howard Jones - You`Re The Buddah - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There were times when I thought there was nothin' in this world There was nothin' in this world for me Everywhere I looked there was trouble in my life Trouble far as I could see Hey there's a man doin' alright What's his philosophy? He come over here and whispered in my ear You're the Buddha, you're the Christ, You're the Mohammed, and the Mother Mary So who am I so nervous and shy To be brilliant and talented It's the light not the dark that frightens us most And the power lies in our head You playin' small doesn't help at all The world need the things you give Switch yourself on, turn the pressure on You're the Buddha, you're the Christ, You're the Mohammed, and the Mother Mary There are times when I think there's plenty in this world There's plenty in this world for me Anytime I see trouble in my life It becomes an opportunity Now there's a chance to make the world dance You do it unconsciously Help this Winter turn into Spring You're the Buddha, you're the Christ, You're the Mohammed, and the Mother Mary]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="You`Re The Buddah" label="You`Re The Buddah"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/EMMA_STEVENS/Its_Obvious/</id><title>EMMA STEVENS - It`s Obvious - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/EMMA_STEVENS/Its_Obvious/" title="EMMA STEVENS - It`s Obvious - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's obvious that we have a row <br>Before we even leave the house <br>It's obvious that something's going down <br><br>It's obvious so just confess <br>You hate my vintage dress <br>Well, guess what, I couldn't care less <br>You moan about the way I drive <br>Praise the Lord we're still alive <br>So glad I stuck to water all damn night <br>Could it be misogyny <br>Is it possible it's you not me <br>And it's obvious <br>That I got nothing to lose <br>And it's obvious <br>I'm sick and tired of listening to you <br>So you go back to lonely <br>While I find someone new <br>Cos it's obvious <br>It's obvious we're through <br>Why don't you turn the football down <br>My ukulele's drowned <br>It's obvious that you just hate the sound <br>It's obvious that something's wrong <br>You used to like my songs <br>When did everything we have go wrong]]></content><category term="EMMA STEVENS" label="EMMA STEVENS"/><category term="It`s Obvious" label="It`s Obvious"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/EMMA_STEVENS/Lazy/</id><title>EMMA STEVENS - Lazy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/EMMA_STEVENS/Lazy/" title="EMMA STEVENS - Lazy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Never get the time for us anymore <br>Rushin' around but what's it all for <br>Still together but we're drifting apart <br><br>Wasn't love meant to be easy <br>And real life the hardest part <br>So switch off your phone <br>Let's spend a little time on our own <br>I wanna get lazy <br>Lazy with you <br>Waste a little time <br>We can lose the afternoon <br>I miss you like crazy <br>So kick off your shoes <br>It's amazing what lazy can do <br>When it's me and you <br>How about today we cancel our plans <br>You choose the music and I'll run the bath <br>And I'll light the scented candles the way we used to do <br>I forgot how much I love that song <br>No one gets me like you <br>Let's take our time <br>Get back to how we used to unwind <br>Lazy like a Sunday morning <br>I don't care who's calling <br>I'm not picking up this time, no <br>Baby the hours that we're wasting <br>Let's keep the whole world waiting <br>I don't think it's such a crime]]></content><category term="EMMA STEVENS" label="EMMA STEVENS"/><category term="Lazy" label="Lazy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/EMMA_STEVENS/Sunflower/</id><title>EMMA STEVENS - Sunflower - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:48:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:48:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/EMMA_STEVENS/Sunflower/" title="EMMA STEVENS - Sunflower - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Like a sea of gold outside my garden gate <br>Behind that house that I grew up in <br>Our beautiful escape <br><br>We'd talk for hours and hours <br>And look up at the sky <br>I had all the questions <br>But you could tell me why <br>You told me <br>Sunflowers stare at the sun <br>And how the Milky Way <br>Is the galaxy called home <br>I thought the moon was a crescent <br>You showed me I was wrong <br>But where should this sunflower stare <br>Now that you're gone <br>Autumn rain began to wash away the dust <br>I never thought that gold could turn to rust <br>One morning they were gone and I could cry <br>Cos you're not here to tell me why <br>You told me <br>Sunflowers stare at the sun <br>And how the Milky Way <br>Is the galaxy called home <br>I thought the moon was a crescent <br>You showed me I was wrong <br>But where should this sunflower stare <br>Now that you're gone <br>Now that you're gone <br>Now that you're gone <br>You told me <br>Sunflowers stare at the sun <br>And how the Milky Way <br>Is the galaxy called home <br>I thought the moon was a crescent <br>You showed me I was wrong <br>But where should this sunflower stare <br>Now that you're gone <br>Now that you're gone]]></content><category term="EMMA STEVENS" label="EMMA STEVENS"/><category term="Sunflower" label="Sunflower"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Robert_Lonsdale/Fight_The_Fight_From_From_Here_To_Eternity/</id><title>Robert Lonsdale - Fight The Fight (From `From Here To Eternity`) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:49:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:49:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Robert_Lonsdale/Fight_The_Fight_From_From_Here_To_Eternity/" title="Robert Lonsdale - Fight The Fight (From `From Here To Eternity`) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What do I got, Well I got free will <br>So they won't get a lick from me til <br>I make my own choice, find my own voice <br><br>And I'll do it right <br>They wanna put this boy in their ring <br>A little pain and blood is their thing <br>Well listen here but you won't get my blood <br>Ain't gonna fight that fight <br>It's a long war <br>And I won't be walking their line <br>I won't fight that fight but you bet that I'm gonna fight mine <br>And I won't fall for either their truth or their lies <br>A man's on his own which ever condition applies <br>A man's on his own til he dies <br>I quit the bugle, no big deal <br>So don't you tell me how that should feel <br>Just cut me some slack, get off of my back <br>And let me fight that fight <br>It's like nothing more <br>There ain't no ideals on this ride <br>Just show me the underdog, I'm gonna be on their side <br>And this ain't no war <br>Well leastways it isn't so far <br>We're looking for love but only to find who we are <br>Might as well reach for a star <br>And yet the hardest man on Earth <br>Knows what a woman touch is worth <br>I turn on the light and maybe there's somebody there <br>And all along knowing that no one has returned to care <br>Fighting the fight <br>Statin' my case, singin' my song <br>An army around me i'm part of but I don't belong <br>And nobody knows what's gone wrong <br>A man's on his own whatever illision applies <br>A man's on his own til he dies]]></content><category term="Robert Lonsdale" label="Robert Lonsdale"/><category term="Fight The Fight (From `From Here To Eternity`)" label="Fight The Fight (From `From Here To Eternity`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Seize_The_Day/</id><title>Howard Jones - Seize The Day - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:49:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:49:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Seize_The_Day/" title="Howard Jones - Seize The Day - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Seize the day <br>Seize the day <br>This moment will not come again <br>This moment will not come again <br>Seize the day <br>Seize the day <br>This moment will not come again <br>This moment will not come again <br>Seize the day <br>Seize the day <br>This moment will not come again <br>This moment will not come again <br>Seize the day <br>Seize the day <br>Seize the day <br>Seize the day]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Seize The Day" label="Seize The Day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bashy/The_World_Feat_L_Marshall/</id><title>Bashy - The World (Feat. L. Marshall) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:49:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:49:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bashy/The_World_Feat_L_Marshall/" title="Bashy - The World (Feat. L. Marshall) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I come from the ends <br>You know, straight outta the manor <br>Had to find my way out, through policemen, hustlers and gangstas <br>My teacher said that I wouldn't make it, I put my foot on that ladder <br>Now I'm out of this world, you'd think I'm fucking with NASA <br>Oi, I ain't watching nobody, fuck what they do, I do me <br>Now it's Amsterdam, then Brussels back to London, now Paris <br>Sexy girls say oui oui cos, I'm taking the piss <br>And I do not give a shit, cause this all started from kid <br>Oi, This ain't no film as I am authentic on camera <br>Yeah I'm bang out of order, but I just do it for banter <br>I love girls and their money, but I prefer the latter]]></content><category term="Bashy" label="Bashy"/><category term="The World (Feat. L. Marshall)" label="The World (Feat. L. Marshall)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나무소년/Im_In_Love/</id><title>나무소년 - I`m In Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:49:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:49:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%AC%B4%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84/Im_In_Love/" title="나무소년 - I`m In Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 맘에 별빛 <br>별빛이 되어 <br>그득히 나를 안는다 <br>그대로 채워져 간다 <br>내 안의 사랑 <br>사랑이 되어 <br>천천히 어루만진다 <br>그대가 미소 짓는다 <br>어느 순간부터 인지 <br>내 머리 위로 <br>작은 별이 맴돌아 <br>바라만 보았던 <br>그때 나의 별은 <br>모두 그대인데 <br>I’m in love I say I’m in love <br>투명하게 비춰진 <br>이런 나의 모습을 <br>그대란 색깔로 <br>어서 칠해줘 <br>I’m in love I say I’m in love <br>고요만이 가득한 <br>메마른 내 마음에 <br>그대란 노래를 불러줘 <br>자꾸 수 없는 말들을 <br>난 생각하고 <br>만약이라는 답답한 <br>두 글자들이 <br>나비처럼 내 뱃속 안에서 <br>하루 종일 이렇게 <br>날아다니는데 <br>그렇고 그런 사이로 <br>나를 몰아도 <br>너의 진심은 전혀 <br>미소를 짓지 않아 <br>너의 작은 그 손 <br>잡고 말할게 <br>날 바라봐줘 <br>어느 순간부터 인지 <br>내 머리 위로 <br>작은 별이 맴돌아 <br>바라만 보았던 <br>그때 나의 별은 <br>모두 그대인데 <br>I’m in love I say I’m in love <br>투명하게 비춰진 <br>이런 나의 모습을 <br>그대란 색깔로 <br>어서 칠해줘 <br>I’m in love I say I’m in love <br>고요만이 가득한 <br>메마른 내 마음에 <br>그대란 노래를 불러줘 <br>어쩔 수 없는 거잖아 <br>텅 비어 있는 내 맘을 <br>채울 수 있는 건 <br>그래 그대만이 나를 <br>채워낼 수 있는 거잖아 <br>매일 밤 기도해 <br>나의 모든 순간들이 <br>오직 그대이기를 <br>이런 내 맘 받아줘 <br>I’m in love I say I’m in love <br>투명하게 비춰진 <br>이런 나의 모습을 <br>그대란 색깔로 <br>어서 칠해줘 <br>I’m in love I say I’m in love <br>고요만이 가득한 <br>메마른 내 마음에 <br>그대란 노래를 불러줘 <br>I’m in love I’m in love <br>I’m in love I’m in love <br>I’m in love I’m in love <br>I’m in love I’m in love <br>]]></content><category term="나무소년" label="나무소년"/><category term="I`m In Love" label="I`m In Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Things_Can_Only_Get_Better/</id><title>Howard Jones - Things Can Only Get Better - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:49:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:49:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Things_Can_Only_Get_Better/" title="Howard Jones - Things Can Only Get Better - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We're not scared to lose it all Security throw through the wall Future dreams we have to realize A thousand skeptic hands Won't keep us from the things we plan Unless we're clinging to the things we prize And do you feel scared, I do But I won't stop and falter And if we threw it all away Things can only get better Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa whoa-oh-oh (Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa whoa-oh-oh) Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa whoa-oh-oh (Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa whoa-oh-oh) Treating today as though it was The last, the final show Get to sixty and feel no regret It may take a little time A lonely path, an uphill climb Success or failure will not alter it And do you feel scared, I do And I won't stop and falter And if we threw it all away Things can only get better Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa whoa-oh-oh (Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa whoa-oh-oh) Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa whoa-oh-oh (Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa whoa-oh-oh) And do you feel scared, I do And I won't stop and falter And if we threw it all away Things can only get better Ah! Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa whoa-oh-oh (Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa whoa-oh-oh) Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa whoa-oh-oh (Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa whoa-oh-oh) Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa oh-oh-oh-oh (Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa whoa-oh-oh) Whoa whoa whoa-whoa oh-oh-oh (Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa whoa-oh-oh) Whoa whoa whoa-oh-oh whoa-whoa whoa-oh-oh]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Things Can Only Get Better" label="Things Can Only Get Better"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/New_Song_99/</id><title>Howard Jones - New Song 99 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:49:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:49:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/New_Song_99/" title="Howard Jones - New Song 99 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been waiting for so long To come here now and sing this song Don't be fooled by what you see Don't be fooled by what you hear This is a song to all of my friends They take the challenge to their hearts Challenging preconceived ideas Saying goodbye to long standing fears Don't crack up Bend your brain See both sides Throw off your mental chains I don't wanna be hip and cool I don't wanna play by the rules Not under the thumb of the cynical few Or laden down by the doom crew Don't crack up Bend your brain See both sides Throw off your mental chains Don't crack up Bend your brain See both sides Throw off your mental chains I've been waiting for so long To come here now and sing this song Don't be fooled by what you see Don't be fooled by what you hear This is a song to all of my friends They take the challenge to their hearts Challenging preconceived ideas Saying goodbye to long standing fears Don't crack up Bend your brain See both sides Throw off your mental chains]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="New Song 99" label="New Song 99"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Like_To_Get_To_Know_You_Well/</id><title>Howard Jones - Like To Get To Know You Well - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:49:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:49:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Like_To_Get_To_Know_You_Well/" title="Howard Jones - Like To Get To Know You Well - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well So we can be one We can be one together Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well So we can be one We can be one together Together we can cast away the fear Together we can wipe away the tear Together we can strip down the barriers And be one Don't wanna talk about the weather Don't wanna talk about the news Just wanna get to the real you inside Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well So we can be one We can be one together Don't you think now is the time We should be feelin' Just wanna simply say Won't let you slip away People wanna talk about the future Don't wanna linger on the past Just wanna reach the real you inside Forget cold glances and rejections Leave the things that separate Build on a trust that we can stand on Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well So we can be one We can be one together Finding all are insecure Opening the same door Leaving out a stubborn pride Seeing from the other side Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well So we can be one We can be one together Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well So we can be one We can be one together Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well So we can be one We can be one together Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well So we can be one We can be one together Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well Like to get to know you well So we can be one We can be one together]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Like To Get To Know You Well" label="Like To Get To Know You Well"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Let_The_People_Have_Their_Say/</id><title>Howard Jones - Let The People Have Their Say - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:49:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:49:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Let_The_People_Have_Their_Say/" title="Howard Jones - Let The People Have Their Say - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The tide is turning Its coming from the street Read your own wisdom Not the headlines Don't let them tell you Its fine the way it is Its our agenda We know better Let the people have their say Let the people show the way Every woman child and man Has the power in this land Now don't you worry The future will unfold If we are open and ready We all have choices Not just the chosen few So raise your voices Hold them steady Let the people have their say Let the people show the way Every woman child and man Has the power in this land (Let the people) The time has come now To realize our dream To claim our future...together Let the people have their say (Let the people have their say) Let the people show the way (Let the people show the way) Every woman child and man (Every woman child and man) Has the power in this land (Has the power in this land) Let the people have their say (Let the people have their say) Let the people show the way (Let the people show the way) Every woman child and man (Every woman child and man) Has the power in this land (Has the power in this land) Yeah yeah, yeah yo Yeah yeah Let the people have their say (Let the people have their say) Let the people show the way (Let the people show the way) Every woman child and man (Every woman child and man) Has the power in this land Yeah yeah, yeah yo Yeah yeah Yeah yeah, yeah yo Yeah yeah (Let the people show the way) Yeah yeah, yeah yo Yeah yeah (Let the people show the way) Yeah yeah, yeah yo Yeah yeah (Let the people show the way) Yeah yeah, yeah yo Yeah yeah (Let the people show the way)]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Let The People Have Their Say" label="Let The People Have Their Say"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/What_Is_Love_/</id><title>Howard Jones - What Is Love? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:49:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:49:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/What_Is_Love_/" title="Howard Jones - What Is Love? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I love you whether or not you love me I love you even if you think that I don't Sometimes I find you doubt my love for you But I don't mind Why should I mind Why should I mind What is love anyway Does anybody love anybody anyway What is love anyway Does anybody love anybody anyway Can anybody love anyone so much that they will never fear Never worry never be sad The answer is they cannot love this much nobody can This is why I don't mind you doubting What is love anyway Does anybody love anybody anyway What is love anyway Does anybody love anybody anyway And maybe love is letting people be just what they want to be The door always must be left unlocked To love when circumstance may lead someone away from you And not to spend the time just doubting What is love anyway Does anybody love anybody anyway What is love anyway Does anybody love anybody anyway What is love anyway Does anybody love anybody anyway What is love anyway Does anybody love anybody anyway What is love anyway Does anybody love anybody anyway What is love anyway Does anybody love anybody anyway]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="What Is Love?" label="What Is Love?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Hide_And_Seek/</id><title>Howard Jones - Hide And Seek - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:50:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:50:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Hide_And_Seek/" title="Howard Jones - Hide And Seek - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There was a time when there was nothing at all Nothing at all, just a distant hum There was a being and he lived on his own He had no one to talk to, and nothing to do He drew up the plans, learnt to work with his hands A million years passed by and his work was done And his words were these... Hope you find it in everything, everything that you see Hope you find it in everything, everything that you see Hope you find it, hope you find it Hope you find me in you So she had built her elaborate home With it's ups and it's downs, its rains and its sun She decided that her work was done, time to have fun and she found a game to play Then as part of the game She completely forgot where she'd hidden herself And she spent the rest of her time Trying to find the parts Hope you find it in everything, everything that you see Hope you find it in everything, everything that you see Hope you find it, hope you find it Hope you find me in you There was a time when there was nothing at all, nothing at all Just a distant hum]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Hide And Seek" label="Hide And Seek"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Pearl_In_The_Shell/</id><title>Howard Jones - Pearl In The Shell - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:50:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:50:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Pearl_In_The_Shell/" title="Howard Jones - Pearl In The Shell - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And the fear goes on shadows And the tear flows on for nothing And the fear goes on shadows And the tear flows on for nothing Under his nose was a dream come true Been there all the time and he almost knew And the fear goes on shadows And the tear flows on for nothing And the fear goes on shadows And the tear flows on for nothing Under his nose was a dream come true Been there all the time and he almost knew Thoughts of people in misfortune stopped him doing things well His duty was to use it - left his pearl in the shell]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Pearl In The Shell" label="Pearl In The Shell"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Tomorrow_Is_Now/</id><title>Howard Jones - Tomorrow Is Now - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:50:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:50:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Tomorrow_Is_Now/" title="Howard Jones - Tomorrow Is Now - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now You think the past is behind you But baby what's that on your back It looks to me like you're draggin' it around like a heavy pack Now we don't live in the present We're to busy hangin' on To what's been and gone so it comes again singin' the same old song Singin' na na-na na na Let it go oh oh Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now What are you going to ask for What are you going to create It's in you hands to build your own world forget about fate And I don't need to remind you Life is short and life is sweet And before you even know it past and future gonna meet Oh, every day and every way Good to go oh oh Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Not much to say It's all been said, anyway Not much to think about Just let go of yesterday Singin' na na-na na na Singin' na na-na na na Let it go oh oh Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now Tomorrow is... tomorrow is now]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Tomorrow Is Now" label="Tomorrow Is Now"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/I_Must_Go/</id><title>Howard Jones - I Must Go - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:50:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:50:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/I_Must_Go/" title="Howard Jones - I Must Go - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You let me paint The colours of your mind The love that remains wont fade over time You'll be alright So baby don't cry I'll be the sunset in your sky I'll be the soft winds you feel passing by So chin up my darlin' Ill be there on that distant horizon That hurts me so But I must go You let me be the person that I am Through my confusion you helped me stand I'll be alright So baby don't cry I'll be the sunset in your sky I'll be the soft winds you feel passing by So chin up my darling I'll be there on that distant horizon That hurts me so But I must go So chin up my darlin' I'll be there on that distant horizon It hurts be so But I must go I must go I will search every star 'till I find where you are And take you home So chin up my darlin' I'll be there on that distant horizon It hurts me so But I must go I must go]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="I Must Go" label="I Must Go"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Everlasting_Love/</id><title>Howard Jones - Everlasting Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:50:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:50:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Everlasting_Love/" title="Howard Jones - Everlasting Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Livin' From day to day By your side All the give and take Wouldn't change that For the universe You've always seen me Through the best and the worst And it's not like I'm tongue-tied Or words get in my way But I love you And it's still true today Even if I don't say Like a diamond With a thousand sides You sparkle And reflect the light In the dark days When I can barely see You find the blue sky Bring it out in me And it's not like I'm tongue-tied Or words get in my way But I love you And it's still true today Even if I don't say (Shoop da waddy Shoop da waddy Shoop da waddy bop Shoop da waddy waddy) Lookin' back on all our years Every battle won has laid the path we're walkin' on So let me be clear I'm so glad that you're here By my side From day to day Through hard times And the give and take Built a love strong As the universe Fighting beside you Through the best and the worst And it's not like I'm tongue-tied Or words get in my way But I love you And it's still true still true today And it's not like I'm tongue-tied Or words get in my way But I love you And it's still true Today Even if I don't say Even if I don't say Even if I don't say]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Everlasting Love" label="Everlasting Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Someone_You_Need/</id><title>Howard Jones - Someone You Need - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:50:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:50:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Someone_You_Need/" title="Howard Jones - Someone You Need - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The streets here are empty all the people went home well, I was just wondering if you're alone So how you've been lately? I hear you're a little down and do you think maybe I could come around? I could be someone you need wrap you in blankets on dark winter nights be your best confidante pay the right compliment I could be someone you need We had coffee on 3rd street and talked for a time I still have your letter I know every line I hope this ain´t coming from way out of the blue cause I got to thinking and I thought of you I could be someone you need keep you from burning in hot summer sun roll you in clover a coat for your shoulder I could be someone you need You need someone there when the world isn't fair or its all just too good to be true Someone to care for you issue a dare to you when the moment comes you need to fly, fly. I could be someone you need wrap you in blankets on dark winter nights be your best confidante pay the right compliment I could be someone you need]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Someone You Need" label="Someone You Need"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/No_One_Is_To_Blame/</id><title>Howard Jones - No One Is To Blame - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:50:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:50:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/No_One_Is_To_Blame/" title="Howard Jones - No One Is To Blame - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You can look at the menu but you just can't eat You can feel the cushions but you can't have a seat You can dip your foot in the pool but you can't have a swim You can feel the punishment but you can't commit the sin And you want her, and she wants you We want everyone And you want her, and she wants you No one, no one, no one ever is to blame You can build a mansion but you just can't live in You're the fastest runner but you're not allowed to win Some break the rules and live to count the cost The insecurity is the thing that won't get lost And you want her, and she wants you We want everyone And you want her, and she wants you No one, no one, no one ever is to blame You can see the summit but you can't reach it It's the last piece of the puzzle but you just can't make it fit Doctor says you're cured but you still feel the pain Aspirations in the clouds but your hopes go down the drain And you want her, and she wants you We want everyone And you want her, and she wants you No one, no one, no one ever is to blame No one ever is to blame No one ever is to blame]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="No One Is To Blame" label="No One Is To Blame"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Love_Is_A_Good_Thing/</id><title>Howard Jones - Love Is A Good Thing - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:50:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:50:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/Love_Is_A_Good_Thing/" title="Howard Jones - Love Is A Good Thing - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We stay up late We get no sleep My body's aching I got no money left My friends say I'm loosing it You so bad for me But that's a good thing Love is a good thing Every room we're in Gets trashed from floor to ceiling Your kiss is killing me When I part from your sweet lips My dreams of you are censored Restless end in sight But that's a good thing Love is a good thing Love is a good thing Love is a good thing The first law of love Is all the rules could be re written The second law of love Is just what we make it No question That's a good thing Love's a good thing The first law of love Is all the rules could be re written The second law of love Is just what we make it No question That's a good thing Love's a good thing The first law of love Is all the rules could be re written The second law of love Is just what we make it No question That's a good thing Love's a good thing]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="Love Is A Good Thing" label="Love Is A Good Thing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/You_Know_I_Love_You_Dont_You/</id><title>Howard Jones - You Know I Love You Don`t You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:50:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:50:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Howard_Jones/You_Know_I_Love_You_Dont_You/" title="Howard Jones - You Know I Love You Don`t You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You got the socket and I got the plug I am the floor and you are the rug I got the rhythm you got the beat We feel it shake us from our souls to our feet And you know I Love you You know I Love you...don't you You got the metal and I got the die We make a structure that no one can deny I need you and you need me I need your honey like a flower needs a bee You know I Love you You know I Love you...don't you No one is an island on that you can depend A person on his own is a sinking ship It will be that way til the time will end Now don't you worry when things get tough We'll stick together through the smooth and the rough Your the steam engine and I am the tracks Roll over me I'll be rolling right back 'cause]]></content><category term="Howard Jones" label="Howard Jones"/><category term="You Know I Love You Don`t You" label="You Know I Love You Don`t You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starley/Call_On_Me_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>Starley - Call On Me (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:50:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:50:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starley/Call_On_Me_Acoustic_Ver/" title="Starley - Call On Me (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you're low <br>And your knees can't rise <br>You feel helpless <br>And you're looking to the sky <br>Some people would say <br>To accept their fate <br>Well, if this is fate <br>Then we'll find a way to cheat <br><br>Cause, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh we'll say a little prayer <br>But, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh if the answer isn't fair <br><br>You know you can call on me <br>When you need somebody <br>You know you can call on me <br>When you can't stop the tears from falling down, down, down <br>You know you can call on me <br>Call on me, darling <br>You know you can call on me <br>Call on me, darling (call on me) <br><br>When you're weary <br>And the road is dark <br>And I'll guide you <br>With the beating of my heart <br>And if the calvary <br>And the help don't come <br>Well, then we'll find a way <br>To dodge a smoking gun <br><br>Cause, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh we'll say a little prayer <br>But, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh if the answer isn't fair (then call on me) <br><br>You know you can call on me <br>When you need somebody <br>You know you can call on me <br>When you can't stop the tears from falling down, down, down <br>You know you can call on me <br>Call on me, darling <br>You know you can call on me <br>Call on me, darling (call on me) <br><br>When you're, you need someone (just call on me) <br>You need somebody to cling to (call on me) <br>When you're, you need someone (just call on me) <br>You need somebody to dry your tears <br>When you're, you need someone (you can call me) <br>You need somebody to cling to (just call on me) <br><br>Just call on me, love (just call on me) <br>Just call on me, love (call on me) <br>Just call on me, love (just call on me) <br>Just call on me, love (call on me) <br>Just call on me, love, on me]]></content><category term="Starley" label="Starley"/><category term="Call On Me (Acoustic Ver.)" label="Call On Me (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanilla_Mousse/Flower/</id><title>Vanilla Mousse - Flower - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:51:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:51:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanilla_Mousse/Flower/" title="Vanilla Mousse - Flower - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우연히 너에게 마주쳤어 <br>난 한 눈에 빠져 버렸어 <br>혹시나 너만 괜찮다면 <br>좀 더 깊이 널 알고 싶어 <br>반짝이는 눈 <br>눈이 부신 콧날 <br>그 미소로 나를 감싸줘 <br>녹아버렸어 <br>난 빠져버렸어 <br>아침 해가 뜰 때 까지 <br>kiss me hold me <br>이 밤이 가기 전에 <br>touch me feel me <br>뜨겁게 날 안아줘 <br>날 태워줘 <br>너의 두 눈 속에 <br>비친 내가 <br>미쳐버릴 수 있도록 <br>kiss me hold me <br>이 밤이 가기 전에 <br>touch me feel me <br>뜨겁게 날 안아줘 <br>내일이면 새로운 태양이 <br>눈부시게 <br>우릴 비출 수 있도록 <br>화무십일홍 예쁜 꽃도 <br>열흘이 지나면 떨어지고 <br>흰 눈 가득히 쌓인 밤에 <br>너와 함께 하고 싶어 <br>kiss me hold me <br>이 밤이 가기 전에 <br>touch me feel me <br>뜨겁게 날 안아줘 <br>날 태워줘 <br>너의 두 눈 속에 <br>비친 내가 <br>미쳐버릴 수 있도록 <br>kiss me hold me <br>이 밤이 가기 전에 <br>touch me feel me <br>뜨겁게 날 안아줘 <br>내일이면 새로운 태양이 <br>눈부시게 <br>우릴 비출 수 있도록 <br>kiss me hold me <br>이 밤이 가기 전에 <br>touch me feel me <br>뜨겁게 날 안아줘 <br>날 태워줘 <br>너의 두 눈 속에 <br>비친 내가 <br>미쳐버릴 수 있도록 <br>kiss me hold me <br>이 밤이 가기 전에 <br>touch me feel me <br>뜨겁게 날 안아줘 <br>내일이면 새로운 태양이 <br>눈부시게 <br>우릴 비출 수 있도록 <br>]]></content><category term="Vanilla Mousse" label="Vanilla Mousse"/><category term="Flower" label="Flower"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/멜로우위크/작은_나/</id><title>멜로우위크 - 작은 나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:51:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:51:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A9%9C%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B0%EC%9C%84%ED%81%AC/%EC%9E%91%EC%9D%80_%EB%82%98/" title="멜로우위크 - 작은 나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[인사 없이 찰칵 <br>끊어버린 너의 전화 <br>통화버튼 위엔 <br>망설이는 얕은 한숨 <br>하루에도 열두 번 <br>수만 번 토라지는 <br>나의 작은 마음 <br>나도 몰래 움츠러드는 <br>오 내 맘을 어떻게 할까 <br>약속해 나 이제 뒤로 <br>숨지 않을래 <br>더이상 너에게 <br>투정부리지 않아 <br>작은 내 손을 잡아 준 <br>널 위해 난 변할거야 <br>아주 살짝 조금만 기다려 <br>잠수는 타지마 <br>서운한 건 바로 말해 <br>헤어지잔 말은 <br>어느 때도 절대 안 돼 <br>알면서도 지키지 못하는 <br>부드러운 너의 목소리들 <br>나도 몰래 웅크러드는 <br>오 내 모습 보이긴 싫어 <br>약속해 나 이제 뒤로 <br>숨지 않을래 <br>더이상 너에게 <br>투정부리지 않아 <br>작은 내 손을 잡아 준 <br>널 위해 난 변할거야 <br>아주 살짝 조금만 <br>약속해 나 이제 <br>실망시키지 않아 <br>이제는 너에게 <br>부끄럽지 않게 <br>나를 빛나게 해 주는 <br>널 위해 난 변할거야 <br>아주 살짝 조금만 기다려 <br>약속해 나 이제 <br>실망시키지 않아 <br>이제는 너에게 <br>부끄럽지 않게 <br>나를 빛나게 해 주는 <br>널 위해 난 변할거야 <br>아주 살짝 조금만 기다려 <br>]]></content><category term="멜로우위크" label="멜로우위크"/><category term="작은 나" label="작은 나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/크래커_CRACKER/태양/</id><title>크래커 (CRACKER) - 태양 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:51:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:51:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%81%AC%EB%9E%98%EC%BB%A4_CRACKER/%ED%83%9C%EC%96%91/" title="크래커 (CRACKER) - 태양 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너무 뜨거워 넌 나를 비출 때 <br>조금 떨어져도 돼 어디 안 갈게 <br>계속 바라보고 있으면 언제 <br>잠을 자는 거야 어 정말 대단해 <br>가끔 비가 그리워 좋단 말은 아냐 <br>그냥 비가 내리면 시원해지잖아 <br>금방 다시 찾게 될 거야 날 <br>따뜻하게 녹여줄 너 태양을 말야 <br>sunrise 뜨고 져도 돼 <br>12시가 되면 여기서 <br>매일 널 기다릴게 <br>sunset 뜨고 져도 돼 <br>거기서 넌 식지 않고 <br>계속 날 비춰줄래 <br>sunrise 뜨고 져도 돼 <br>빨리 보고 싶을 때는 <br>동쪽 하늘을 볼게 <br>sunset 뜨고 져도 돼 <br>시간 늦을 때면 <br>서쪽까지 바래다줄게 <br>머리가 점점 커져 갈수록 <br>햇살처럼 따스한 게 난 더 좋더라 <br>뜨거워지니 맘 <br>새까맣게 타들어 갔었어 <br>그러니 한 발짝 뒤에 서 비춰줄래 <br>그래도 원한다면 <br>언제든지 꼭 안아줄게 <br>sunrise 뜨고 져도 돼 <br>12시가 되면 여기서 <br>매일 널 기다릴게 <br>sunset 뜨고 져도 돼 <br>거기서 넌 식지 않고 <br>계속 날 비춰줄래 <br>sunrise 뜨고 져도 돼 <br>빨리 보고 싶을 때는 <br>동쪽 하늘을 볼게 <br>sunset 뜨고 져도 돼 <br>시간 늦을 때면 <br>서쪽까지 바래다줄게 <br>sunrise sunset sunrise sunset <br>]]></content><category term="크래커 (CRACKER)" label="크래커 (CRACKER)"/><category term="태양" label="태양"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/필로_PiLO/INTRO_Ive_Been_Wait_Feat_태일찬/</id><title>필로 (PiLO) - INTRO ((I)`ve Been Wait) (Feat. 태일찬) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T20:51:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T20:51:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%84%EB%A1%9C_PiLO/INTRO_Ive_Been_Wait_Feat_%ED%83%9C%EC%9D%BC%EC%B0%AC/" title="필로 (PiLO) - INTRO ((I)`ve Been Wait) (Feat. 태일찬) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm just begin <br>가진건 하나 없어 <br>Not a Building <br>처음엔 바닥에 서서 <br>남들같이 시작해 <br>이제 서서히 <br>발소리가 사라지고 <br>흐르는 정적 <br>그위로 날아갈 <br>준비를 해 흠 <br>어제보단 좋아진듯 해 <br>필요 없을 만큼 <br>쌓인 고통에 <br>피로만큼 쌓여가던 <br>내 노래 와 <br>자연스레 난 <br>트랙앞에 준비 땅 <br>소리에 마치 <br>바로 달려갈듯 한 <br>Runner가 된듯해 <br>보고가지 앞만 <br>무슨말을 한들 <br>안 들릴 것같아 <br>Yes I'm ready to go <br>Yes I'm ready to go <br>그저 기다렸어 <br>여기 앉아서 <br>Yes I'm ready to go <br>Yes I'm ready to go <br>Already on the floor cause <br>I've been waiting for long time <br>how about you <br>Have you been waiting <br>for long like I do <br>Sure we looking for more big one <br>Sure It's More than you thought <br>I've been waiting for long <br>I've been waiting for long <br>Have You been waiting <br>for me like I do <br>I've been waiting for long <br>]]></content><category term="필로 (PiLO)" label="필로 (PiLO)"/><category term="INTRO ((I)`ve Been Wait) (Feat. 태일찬)" label="INTRO ((I)`ve Been Wait) (Feat. 태일찬)"/></entry></feed>