<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:50:14+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BoYA/기회비용/</id><title>BoYA - 기회비용 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:05:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:05:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BoYA/%EA%B8%B0%ED%9A%8C%EB%B9%84%EC%9A%A9/" title="BoYA - 기회비용 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 집으로 돌아가야 했었는데 <br>너와의 대화들이 너무 신기해서 <br>난 잠이 들었어야 했었는데 <br>네가 건넨 말들이 너무 놀라워서 <br>그 순간순간 공기들조차 <br>날 붙잡고 있는 것 같아서 <br>모든 것들이 날 <br>놓지 않는 것 같아서 <br>그냥 하루 종일 이래 나도 <br>우리 집 앞에 그런 벤치가 있는지 <br>처음 알았어 <br>널 못 보게 된 내 못다 한 <br>마음은 어디로 <br>가야 하는지 모르겠어 <br>애초에 난 선택할 생각 없었어 <br>내 결론은 처음부터 너였어 <br>날 많이 좋아한다며 <br>내가 많이 좋다며 <br>겁났지만 무서웠지만 감당할 수 <br>있을 거라 생각했는데 <br>너무 늦었나 봐 어쩌겠어 <br>내가 어쩔 수 있니 <br>아니라는데 넌 이제 <br>내가 아니라는데 <br>아는척하지 말고 <br>지나가지 그랬어 <br>너의 고갯짓 하나에 <br>몇 날 며칠을 무너져 내려버렸어 <br>내 마음은 부서져 버렸어 <br>날 많이 좋아한다며 <br>내가 많이 좋다며 <br>그 말에 놓치기 싫어 조심스레 <br>다가갔던 것뿐이었는데 <br>너무 늦었나 봐 어쩌겠어 <br>내가 어쩔 수 있니 <br>아닌 거잖아 넌 이제 <br>내가 아닌 거잖아 <br>시작도 없었던 우릴 그리워하며 <br>오늘 밤 꿈에서 너를 또 만났어 <br>왜 나만 이렇게 괴로운지 <br>너도 나처럼 괜찮지 않았으면 <br>]]></content><category term="BoYA" label="BoYA"/><category term="기회비용" label="기회비용"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BoYA/위태위태/</id><title>BoYA - 위태위태 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:05:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:05:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BoYA/%EC%9C%84%ED%83%9C%EC%9C%84%ED%83%9C/" title="BoYA - 위태위태 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 무슨 일인데 <br>이젠 말해야겠어 <br>뭐가 또 문젠데 <br>너 요새 그거 알아 <br>또 시작이네 <br>너 요즘 몇 번짼지 <br>예전 같지가 않아 <br>너 들어나 볼게 <br>아니라 말하지만 <br>언제 그랬는데 <br>나 느낄 수가 있어 <br>무엇을 느껴 <br>너 변해가고 <br>그런 적 없어 <br>있다는 것을 <br>뭘 넌 바라는 게 많아 <br>바라는 게 아닌데 <br>아니라 하겠지만 <br>그저 그저 난 처음과 같길 <br>처음과 같길 바랄 뿐인데 <br>흔들흔들 우리는 <br>또 위태위태해 <br>떨어질 듯 우리는 <br>또 외줄타기를 하고 있네 <br>개와 고양이처럼 <br>엇갈린 듯해 <br>오늘 또 이렇게 <br>우리 으르렁 대네 <br>나 너무 힘들어 <br>너무나 두려워져 <br>네가 이럴 때마다 <br>상처받기 싫어 <br>내가 상처야 <br>적어도 너무 아파 <br>너에게만은 말이야 <br>널 날 사랑하긴 하니 <br>정말 사랑하는데 <br>아닌 것 같은데 <br>나 이제는 네가 나를 <br>점점 네가 무서워지네 <br>무서워하네 <br>흔들흔들 우리는 <br>또 위태위태해 <br>떨어질 듯 우리는 <br>또 외줄타기를 하고 있네 <br>개와 고양이처럼 <br>엇갈린 듯해 <br>오늘 또 이렇게 <br>우리 으르렁 대네 <br>내가 기억하는 <br>우린 이게 아닌데 <br>보고 싶어 내가 <br>사랑하던 그때 그 사람을 <br>흔들흔들 우리는 <br>또 위태위태해 <br>떨어질 듯 우리는 <br>또 외줄타기를 하고 있네 <br>개와 고양이처럼 <br>엇갈린 듯해 <br>오늘 또 이렇게 <br>우리 으르렁 대네 <br>]]></content><category term="BoYA" label="BoYA"/><category term="위태위태" label="위태위태"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BoYA/춤/</id><title>BoYA - 춤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:05:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:05:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BoYA/%EC%B6%A4/" title="BoYA - 춤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 내 안에서 춤을 춰 <br>보랏빛 몽환적인 <br>구름 속에 <br>난 네 안에서 춤을 춰 <br>우리의 실루엣은 <br>황홀할 지경 <br>음악은 시작되고 <br>내가 어떤 행동을 해도 <br>내가 무슨 표정을 지어도 <br>이곳에서 난 너만의 뮤즈 <br>우리는 춤을 춰 <br>더 아름답게 <br>우리는 춤을 춰 <br>더 우아하게 <br>넌 내 안에서 춤을 춰 <br>그렇게 우리 둘만의 파티엔 <br>아무도 들어오지 못하게 <br>난 네 안에서 춤을 춰 <br>음악은 시작되고 <br>내가 어떤 행동을 해도 <br>내가 무슨 표정을 지어도 <br>이곳에서 난 너만의 뮤즈 <br>우리는 춤을 춰 <br>더 아름답게 <br>우리는 춤을 춰 <br>더 우아하게 <br>Only your muse <br>음악이 희미해지고 <br>달콤한 향이 옅어질 때쯤 <br>나는 사라지고 <br>이 안엔 너만 남아 <br>나 홀로 춤을 춰 <br>더 아련하게 <br>나 홀로 춤을 춰 <br>또 다음번에 <br>우리를 위해서 <br>더 아름다운 <br>우리를 위해서 <br>I'm only your muse <br>]]></content><category term="BoYA" label="BoYA"/><category term="춤" label="춤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/반디/겨울/</id><title>반디 - 겨울 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:07:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:07:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%98%EB%94%94/%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8/" title="반디 - 겨울 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어느 초라한 겨울날 <br>내게 보낸 너의 선물 <br>나를 얼게 만들었어 <br>의미 없는 기도의 반복 <br>어딘가에 있을 너와 <br>어리석은 내 감정 <br>어딘가에 깊이 남을 <br>숨이 멎을 듯 날카로운 이별 <br>기억하지 않을 수만 있다면 <br>더운 내 맘을 <br>차갑게 잘라버릴 텐데 <br>초라하지 않을 수만 있다면 <br>남은 내 맘을 <br>네게서 빨리 감출 텐데 <br>어느 초라한 겨울날 <br>내게 남긴 너의 선물 <br>나를 울게 만들었어 <br>의미 없는 기도의 반복 <br>바램의 반복 <br>]]></content><category term="반디" label="반디"/><category term="겨울" label="겨울"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이도경_Lee_Do_Kyung/Bye_Bye_Bye/</id><title>이도경_Lee_Do_Kyung - Bye Bye Bye - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:11:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:11:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%84%EA%B2%BD_Lee_Do_Kyung/Bye_Bye_Bye/" title="이도경_Lee_Do_Kyung - Bye Bye Bye - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쓰라린 상처에 한번 더 상처 주네 <br>고요한 가슴에 살며시 돌 던지네 <br>이제와 돌아보니 나만 몰랐었네 <br>사랑에 눈 멀었네 바보 같은 내 맘 <br>그 사람을 정말로 사랑했었네 <br>아픔만이 내 가슴 속에 남았어 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>차라리 떠나버려 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>니가 필요 없어 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>모든 걸 다 버릴 거야 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>니가 후회해도 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>다시 찾는대도 <br>난 그냥 떠날 거야 <br>아물던 상처에 또 다시 상처 주네 <br>시리던 가슴에 또 한번 가슴 치네 <br>이제와 돌아보니 나만 몰랐었네 <br>사랑에 눈 멀었네 바보 같은 내 맘 <br>그 사람을 정말로 믿었었네 <br>미움만이 내 가슴 속에 남았어 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>차라리 떠나버려 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>니가 필요 없어 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>모든 걸 다 버릴 거야 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>니가 후회해도 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>다시 찾는대도 <br>난 그냥 떠날 거야 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>차라리 떠나버려 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>니가 필요 없어 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>모든 걸 다 버릴 거야 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>니가 후회해도 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>다시 찾는대도 <br>난 그냥 떠날 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="이도경 (Lee Do Kyung)" label="이도경 (Lee Do Kyung)"/><category term="Bye Bye Bye" label="Bye Bye Bye"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이도경_Lee_Do_Kyung/시월애_時越愛/</id><title>이도경_Lee_Do_Kyung - 시월애 (時越愛) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:11:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:11:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%84%EA%B2%BD_Lee_Do_Kyung/%EC%8B%9C%EC%9B%94%EC%95%A0_%E6%99%82%E8%B6%8A%E6%84%9B/" title="이도경_Lee_Do_Kyung - 시월애 (時越愛) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[시간아 제발 나를 데려가지마 <br>멀고먼 길을 돌아 왔는데 <br>아픈 기억 모두 다 잊어버리고 <br>행복하게 살 수 있다면 <br>우연히 스친 옷깃에 <br>날려오는 그 향기가 <br>한동안 나도 모르게 <br>잊고 있었던 그 기억들 <br>시간아 제발 나를 데려가지마 <br>멀고먼 길을 돌아 왔는데 <br>아픈 기억 모두 다 잊어버리고 <br>행복하게 살 수 있다면 <br>바람아 제발 나를 버려두고 가 <br>아련한 기억 느낄 수 있게 <br>잠시라도 그 때 그 시간 속에서 <br>사랑하며 살 수 있다면 <br>잊었던 그대 눈빛에 <br>볼을 타고 흐르는 눈물 <br>새하얀 세상 속으로 <br>돌아가야 할 지금 이 순간 <br>바람아 제발 나를 버려두고 가 <br>아련한 기억 느낄 수 있게 <br>잠시라도 그 때 그 시간 속에서 <br>사랑하며 살 수 있다면 <br>잠시라도 그 때 그 시간 속에서 <br>사랑하며 살 수 있다면 <br>사랑하며 살 수 있다면 <br>]]></content><category term="이도경 (Lee Do Kyung)" label="이도경 (Lee Do Kyung)"/><category term="시월애 (時越愛)" label="시월애 (時越愛)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이도경_Lee_Do_Kyung/황금빛_인생/</id><title>이도경_Lee_Do_Kyung - 황금빛 인생 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:11:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:11:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%84%EA%B2%BD_Lee_Do_Kyung/%ED%99%A9%EA%B8%88%EB%B9%9B_%EC%9D%B8%EC%83%9D/" title="이도경_Lee_Do_Kyung - 황금빛 인생 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[살면서 한번씩 <br>힘들어 지칠 때면 <br>세상을 탓하며 <br>술 한잔 기울이지 <br>그 잔에 털어놓는 <br>수많은 사연들 <br>불처럼 타오르는 <br>서글픈 인생사 <br>인생살이 시작은 <br>다르다지만 <br>모두에게 주어진 <br>하루는 똑같아 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>힘들어도 참고 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>서러워도 참는 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>힘없던 흙수저 인생 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>모두 털어내고 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>다시 일어서자 <br>황금빛 내 인생아 <br>언제나 비오고 <br>흐린 날 있었듯이 <br>누구나 한번쯤 <br>시련도 있겠지만 <br>돌이켜 생각하면 <br>황금빛 시간들 <br>버릴 것 하나 없는 <br>우리네 인생사 <br>인생살이 시작은 <br>다르다지만 <br>모두에게 주어진 <br>하루는 똑같아 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>힘들어도 참고 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>서러워도 참는 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>힘없던 흙수저 인생 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>모두 털어내고 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>다시 일어서자 <br>황금빛 내 인생아 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>힘들어도 참고 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>서러워도 참는 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>힘없던 흙수저 인생 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>모두 털어내고 <br>Bye Bye Bye <br>다시 일어서자 <br>황금빛 내 인생아 <br>]]></content><category term="이도경 (Lee Do Kyung)" label="이도경 (Lee Do Kyung)"/><category term="황금빛 인생" label="황금빛 인생"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김효종/경계선/</id><title>김효종 - 경계선 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:17:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:17:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%9A%A8%EC%A2%85/%EA%B2%BD%EA%B3%84%EC%84%A0/" title="김효종 - 경계선 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그렇게도 비가 내리던 <br>그 날 그렇게 우리 <br>한참 동안 말도 못하고 <br>그냥 그렇게 우리 <br>알 수 없는 너와 나에 경계선 <br>낯설어진 너와 나의 눈동자 <br>알 수 없는 너와 나에 경계선 <br>낯설어진 너와 나의 눈동자 <br>우리 이제 헤어져 <br>우리 이제 끝났어 <br>우리 이제 헤어져 <br>우리 이제 끝났어 <br>]]></content><category term="김효종" label="김효종"/><category term="경계선" label="경계선"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/데이브니어_Dave_Near/그리울거예요/</id><title>데이브니어_Dave_Near - 그리울거예요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:18:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:18:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%B8%8C%EB%8B%88%EC%96%B4_Dave_Near/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9A%B8%EA%B1%B0%EC%98%88%EC%9A%94/" title="데이브니어_Dave_Near - 그리울거예요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[안녕 안녕 이젠 안녕 <br>없으면 죽을 것 같던 것들과 이젠 <br>안녕 안녕 이젠 안녕 <br>없으면 죽을 것 같던 것들과 이젠 <br>헤어져야 할 시간 <br>그대 얼굴 이렇게 봐요 <br>사랑한단 말이 <br>너무나도 무색하지만 <br>한번 더 말할게 <br>사랑해요 그리울 거예요 <br>흘러가는 시간이 <br>아쉽게만 느껴지네요 <br>사랑한단 말이 <br>너무나도 무색하지만 <br>한번 더 말할게 <br>사랑해요 그리울 거야 <br>따뜻했던 너의 그 미소가 <br>빛나던 시간 <br>영원히 내 삶에 <br>기억할게 그리울 거예요 <br>]]></content><category term="데이브니어 (Dave Near)" label="데이브니어 (Dave Near)"/><category term="그리울거예요" label="그리울거예요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백지영/그대의_마음_Inst/</id><title>백지영 - 그대의 마음 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:18:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:18:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%EC%A7%80%EC%98%81/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EC%9D%98_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C_Inst/" title="백지영 - 그대의 마음 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루해가 지고 나면 <br>울고 웃는 사람 이야기 <br>술잔 앞에 모인 그대들의 얼굴이 <br>오늘따라 아름다워요 <br>힘든 하루를 걷다 보면 <br>가끔 울고 싶기도 하고 <br>혼자 인 듯 해도 <br>우린 알 수 있어요 <br>그대의 마음 그대의 마음 <br>그대의 마음 <br>그렇게 살아가는 걸 <br>서로 어깨에 기댄 채로 <br>믿고 기다려준 그대가 없었다면 <br>하루인들 견뎌냈을까 <br>포기하고 싶기도 했지 <br>너무 높은 벽에 부딪혀 <br>넓은 바다에 홀로 버려진 것처럼 <br>나만 빼고 모두 흘러갔지 <br>가슴 시린 사랑을 했지 <br>마치 영원히 살 것처럼 <br>한 순간이라도 기억할 수 있다면 <br>그대의 마음 그대의 마음 <br>그대의 마음 <br>그렇게 살아가는 걸 <br>서로 어깨에 기댄 채로 <br>믿고 기다려준 그대가 없었다면 <br>하루인들 견뎌냈을까 <br>그렇게 살아가는 걸 <br>서로 어깨에 기댄 채로 <br>믿고 기다려준 그대가 없었다면 <br>하루인들 견뎌냈을까 <br>하루해가 지고 나면 <br>울고 웃는 사람 이야기 <br>듣는 것만으로 우린 알 수 있어요 <br>그대의 마음 그대의 마음 <br>그대의 마음 <br>]]></content><category term="백지영" label="백지영"/><category term="그대의 마음 (Inst.)" label="그대의 마음 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백지영/그대의_마음/</id><title>백지영 - 그대의 마음 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:19:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:19:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%EC%A7%80%EC%98%81/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EC%9D%98_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C/" title="백지영 - 그대의 마음 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루해가 지고 나면 <br>울고 웃는 사람 이야기 <br>술잔 앞에 모인 그대들의 얼굴이 <br>오늘따라 아름다워요 <br>힘든 하루를 걷다 보면 <br>가끔 울고 싶기도 하고 <br>혼자 인 듯 해도 <br>우린 알 수 있어요 <br>그대의 마음 그대의 마음 <br>그대의 마음 <br>그렇게 살아가는 걸 <br>서로 어깨에 기댄 채로 <br>믿고 기다려준 그대가 없었다면 <br>하루인들 견뎌냈을까 <br>포기하고 싶기도 했지 <br>너무 높은 벽에 부딪혀 <br>넓은 바다에 홀로 버려진 것처럼 <br>나만 빼고 모두 흘러갔지 <br>가슴 시린 사랑을 했지 <br>마치 영원히 살 것처럼 <br>한 순간이라도 기억할 수 있다면 <br>그대의 마음 그대의 마음 <br>그대의 마음 <br>그렇게 살아가는 걸 <br>서로 어깨에 기댄 채로 <br>믿고 기다려준 그대가 없었다면 <br>하루인들 견뎌냈을까 <br>그렇게 살아가는 걸 <br>서로 어깨에 기댄 채로 <br>믿고 기다려준 그대가 없었다면 <br>하루인들 견뎌냈을까 <br>하루해가 지고 나면 <br>울고 웃는 사람 이야기 <br>듣는 것만으로 우린 알 수 있어요 <br>그대의 마음 그대의 마음 <br>그대의 마음 <br>]]></content><category term="백지영" label="백지영"/><category term="그대의 마음" label="그대의 마음"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/YD_와이디/길/</id><title>YD_와이디 - 길 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:20:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:20:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/YD_%EC%99%80%EC%9D%B4%EB%94%94/%EA%B8%B8/" title="YD_와이디 - 길 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[먼곳을 바라놨네 <br>가깝게 두고 싶지 않던 <br>꼴이 창피 했었기에 <br>때론 못 본 척 없던 일처럼 <br>숨기고 싶었어도 <br>내 자신한테는 거짓을 <br>요구하기 싫었고 <br>깜깜한 방 한구석 <br>어둡던 나를 꺼내서 <br>가사속에 비춰가는게 <br>내 일 이라며 <br>매일밤 채찍질 <br>하면서 버텼어 <br>깨진 거울속에 <br>날카롭고 철 없었던 <br>그때를 떠올리고 <br>늦은 후회가 <br>이제와서 아픈거겠지 <br>결국엔 흉터로 남겠지만 <br>말 못할만큼 쓰라린 <br>상처입은 그때 모습을 <br>가사란 퍼즐에 맞춰 <br>스물여섯 나는 <br>자화상을 완성시켜 <br>확신 할 수 없는 <br>내일의 연속 <br>금방 타들어가는 담배로 <br>속을 달래보고 <br>텅빈 공허함 속에서 <br>난 미끄러 지네 <br>내려올 계단이 없는 <br>작은 단상 위에 <br>한숨을 내쉬며 <br>오늘을 견디고 <br>눈뜨면 다시 <br>버텨야 된다고 <br>허튼 생각에 잠기는 순간 <br>헤어나오질 못하는 <br>한심한 놈이였지 <br>매번 나한테 감당못할 <br>일이 생기곤 했지 <br>막다른 길위에서 접했던 <br>swings의 믹스테잎 <br>듣고나서 가사를 <br>담기 시작해 <br>cuz i had to upgrade <br>이젠 남 눈치 볼 <br>여유 따윈 없어 결국엔 <br>남는건 하나 없었고 <br>피곤을 넘겼던 술잔과 새벽 <br>잘못된 선택 뒤엔 <br>핑계 나하나 좋자고 <br>의미 부여된 일에 <br>자아는 사라져가고 <br>시계를 보기엔 <br>크게 다가왔던 비애 <br>의미없는 시간만 <br>계속 흘러갔네 그렇게 <br>몇년을 보내보니 <br>쌓였어 나도 모르게 <br>꼬인것들을 이제와선 <br>가사속에 <br>풀어가면서 오직 <br>내 길을 걷는것 <br>굴곡이 많고 <br>험란했던 그길 위에서 <br>새롭게 내길로 <br>다시 포장해 가는 것 <br>]]></content><category term="YD (와이디)" label="YD (와이디)"/><category term="길" label="길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비프리_B-Free/Memories/</id><title>비프리_B-Free - Memories - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:21:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:21:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC_B-Free/Memories/" title="비프리_B-Free - Memories - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모두 기억하길 원해 난 <br>모두 기억하길 원해 날 <br>잊지마 너는 날 ay <br>잊지마 난 또 널 ay <br>내가 너무 많은 것을 <br>바라는 걸지도 몰라 <br>내가 너무 많은 것을 <br>바라는 걸지도 몰라 <br>모두 기억하길 원해 날 <br>모두 기억하길 원해 날 <br>아무도 몰라 저 하늘로 가는 날 <br>I seen the world and I want it now <br>제발 날 기억해 영혼히 <br>내 육체가 썩고 내 영혼이 <br>떠나도 노래로 역사에 <br>내 이름 적었지 <br>word to my 어머니 <br>middle finger to my enemies <br>I'm just trying to make memories <br>Out in L.a like L a reid <br>I need like 2 g for a beat <br>Told you that <br>you cannot fuck with me I <br>told you that <br>you cannot fuck with me <br>내 주머니 노리는 새끼들 <br>모두다 꺼져 다 저 멀리 <br>난 절대로 지지 않아 <br>난 절대로 잊지 않아 <br>아무리 길이 달라도 <br>만날 사람들은 다 결국엔 만나 <br>아무리 시간이 흐르고 <br>강산이 변해도 우린 남아 <br>모두다 기억해 <br>날 모두다 기억해 날 <br>모두 기억하길 원해 난 <br>모두 기억하길 원해 날 <br>잊지마 너는 날 ay <br>잊지마 난 또 널 ay <br>내가 너무 많은 것을 <br>바라는 걸지도 몰라 <br>내가 너무 많은 것을 <br>바라는 걸지도 몰라 <br>모두 기억하길 원해 난 <br>모두 기억하길 원해 날 <br>잊지마 너는 날 ay <br>잊지마 난 또 널 ay <br>내가 너무 많은 것을 <br>바라는 걸지도 몰라 <br>내가 너무 많은 것을 <br>바라는 걸지도 몰라 <br>U know what people say <br>let it be I'm making <br>a living off memories <br>then I just turn it to melodies <br>you live your life <br>and you rest in peace <br>돈보단 시간이 문제지 <br>on my tomb stone <br>hope it reads <br>everything I did I did it big <br>everything I did I did it big <br>모두다 기억해 날 <br>너무 부족한 인간 <br>산을 또 넘어서 산 <br>그래도 공기는 좋아 <br>trying to get mines <br>trying to get everything <br>that I deserve <br>until I run out of time <br>아버지 give me a sign lord <br>아버지 give me a sign lord <br>아무도 기억 못해 <br>they don't remember your name <br>whatever I just be in the back <br>doing my thing <br>just counting my change <br>너무나 외로워 <br>yeah it gets lonely <br>but better than hanging phonies <br>올라갈수록 더 늘어나 고민 <br>but I know where I'm going <br>모두 기억하길 원해 난 <br>모두 기억하길 원해 날 <br>잊지마 너는 날 ay <br>잊지마 난 또 널 ay <br>내가 너무 많은 것을 <br>바라는 걸지도 몰라 <br>내가 너무 많은 것을 <br>바라는 걸지도 몰라 <br>모두 기억하길 원해 난 <br>모두 기억하길 원해 날 <br>잊지마 너는 날 ay <br>잊지마 난 또 널 ay <br>내가 너무 많은 것을 <br>바라는 걸지도 몰라 <br>내가 너무 많은 것을 <br>바라는 걸지도 몰라 <br>]]></content><category term="비프리 (B-Free)" label="비프리 (B-Free)"/><category term="Memories" label="Memories"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비프리_B-Free/Bring_It_Back_Feat_Okasian/</id><title>비프리_B-Free - Bring It Back (Feat. Okasian) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:21:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:21:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC_B-Free/Bring_It_Back_Feat_Okasian/" title="비프리_B-Free - Bring It Back (Feat. Okasian) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bring it back bring it back <br>brick it back <br>I gotta go get it then bring it back <br>Bring it back bring it back <br>brick it back <br>I told you that Imma go <br>bring it back <br>Bring it back bring it back <br>bring it back <br>I Gotta go get it then bring it back <br>bring it to seoul <br>I'm bringing it home <br>Bring it back bring it back <br>bring it back <br>I'm puttin city on the map <br>I run the play like a quarterback <br>근데 아무도 나를 못 알아봐 <br>괜찮아 괜찮아 괜찮아 <br>난 그게 더 좋아 <br>walking the streets in peace <br>나와 내 그녀와 <br>l'm just living life <br>노래 좀 만들다 <br>하와이에 놀러 가서 <br>서핑 좀 하다가 배를 타 <br>공항에서 좀 급하게 <br>선물로 사온 이 귀걸이가 <br>마음에 들었으면 좋겠네 <br>안들게 뻔하지만 <br>Bring it back bring it back <br>brick it back <br>I gotta go get it then bring it back <br>Bring it back bring it back <br>brick it back <br>I told you that I'mma go <br>bring it back <br>Bring it back bring it back <br>bring it back <br>Gotta go get it then bring it back <br>bring it to seoul bringing it home <br>wish I could that bring you <br>the house on the hills <br>la 의 할리우드 위에 <br>우리의 가족의 미래를 위해 <br>thinking we gotta get outta korea <br>baby don't worry you know <br>you got nothing to fear <br>baby don't worry you know <br>you got nothing to fear <br>Imma go get it then bring it back <br>Imma go get you a bag of cash <br>현금다발을 가져다 줄게 <br>날 기다려 조금 더 참아 줄래 <br>did it for my dawgs <br>but my dawgs don't care for me <br>cause when I was down on my luck <br>you was the only one there for me <br>잠시만 다녀올게 <br>꼭 좋은걸 만들어 가져올게 <br>I promise you when I get back <br>they gonna be all on that wave <br>Imma come bring you the game <br>내가 본 것들을 <br>음악 통해 그려줄게 <br>paint you a picture so clear <br>year after year after year <br>Bring it back bring it back <br>brick it back <br>I gotta go get it then bring it back <br>Bring it back bring it back <br>brick it back <br>I told you that I'mma go <br>bring it back <br>Bring it back bring it back <br>bring it back <br>Gotta go get it then bring it back <br>bring it to seoul bringing it home <br>Bring it back bring it back <br>brick it back <br>I gotta go get it then bring it back <br>Bring it back bring it back <br>brick it back <br>I told you that I'mma go <br>bring it back <br>Bring it back bring it back <br>bring it back <br>Gotta go get it then bring it back <br>bring it to seoul bringing it home <br>]]></content><category term="비프리 (B-Free)" label="비프리 (B-Free)"/><category term="Bring It Back (Feat. Okasian)" label="Bring It Back (Feat. Okasian)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비프리_B-Free/Homies_Feat_cLAsicc/</id><title>비프리_B-Free - Homies (Feat. cLAsicc) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC_B-Free/Homies_Feat_cLAsicc/" title="비프리_B-Free - Homies (Feat. cLAsicc) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[North hollywood k town to oc <br>In the heat someone turn up the ac <br>You already know we be rolling <br>Low key better watch out <br>for the police <br>Long as there is money <br>there is no peace <br>We just rap now <br>blaZe dro and make beats <br>Light it up <br>Who you callin homie <br>Just get the money you owe me <br>Back at it again <br>with that LA to Seoul homie <br>Westcoast and you know homie <br>yah yah <br>We get throwed homie it feels good <br>when the sun on my dome homie <br>yah yah <br>I wanna live a life to live for <br>top down with a baddie <br>ridin six four yup <br>I know its so westcoast <br>but imma bless my coast <br>and imma bless my folks yup <br>Cali weather be like bomb bay <br>LA where the bomb stay <br>you know <br>I put it down I can chief all day <br>with a smile on my face can I parlay <br>I swear we can put this on wax <br>Free be my homie relax <br>puttin out bangers <br>every time we kick back <br>Welcome back to LA homie <br>can I recap yup <br>Back at it again <br>with that LA to Seoul homie <br>Westcoast and you know homie <br>We get throwed homie it feels good <br>when the sun on my dome homie <br>Back at it again <br>with that LA to Seoul homie <br>Westcoast and you know homie <br>We get throwed homie it feels good <br>when the sun on my dome homie <br>I'm riding with my bros out in LA <br>bumping ice cube <br>today was a good day <br>I'm feeling like yeah <br>it was a good day <br>we smoked laughed and made <br>plays on how to get paid <br>See my big ring I do my damn thang <br>hit my plug up I need to maintain <br>I've been rolling up all day <br>pouring up codeine <br>rollie and gold chains <br>I wake up in the morning <br>I can hear that money calling <br>You already know <br>I'm all in balmains <br>ysl and ralph laurens <br>I'm out on the westside <br>and I'm looking for the best high <br>yeah I live the fast life <br>let's make this night a great night <br>Back at it again <br>with that LA to Seoul homie <br>Westcoast and you know homie <br>We get throwed homie it feels good <br>when the sun on my dome homie <br>Back at it again <br>with that LA to Seoul homie <br>Westcoast and you know homie <br>We get throwed homie it feels good <br>when the sun on my dome homie <br>]]></content><category term="비프리 (B-Free)" label="비프리 (B-Free)"/><category term="Homies (Feat. cLAsicc)" label="Homies (Feat. cLAsicc)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비프리_B-Free/Water_II_Feat_Justhis/</id><title>비프리_B-Free - Water II (Feat. Justhis) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC_B-Free/Water_II_Feat_Justhis/" title="비프리_B-Free - Water II (Feat. Justhis) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let me flow yo <br>Let me flow yo <br>Let me flow yo <br>J-This <br>압구정물을 씻겨 <br>서울 전체에다 <br>make it rain <br>And I'm surffing <br>on that waves <br>With my beach <br>boys like U.S.A <br>유교의 산물 꼰대 <br>새끼들은 가르침 <br>But fuck ya <br>난 산수 못해도 <br>산수화 잘 팔리지 <br>사람은 속물인데 <br>감추는 아줌마 아저씨 <br>난 겉으로 드러내 <br>물 속에서 잠수하지 <br>난 신의 한 수보단 <br>닌자의 삼수 <br>진짜와 유치한 걸 <br>구분 못하는 미개한 <br>새끼들 feedback 안물 <br>혼자해도 길 잃지 않고 <br>노 젓는 중인 바닷물 <br>사공만 많은 놈팽이 <br>집단들은 갔지 산으루 <br>문화가 어쩌고 언더가 <br>저쩌고 지껄인 적두 없지만 <br>rapper들 창녀짓 덕분에 <br>이미지가 세탁 중 ah yeah <br>눈곱만큼 눈살 찌푸리고 <br>장점 보다는 단점 죽이는 <br>Batman 같은 JUSTHIS <br>and yall just robbin <br>글고 알지 그게 쿨 한 줄 <br>근까 너넨 내 조수 <br>노는 물이 다름 yeah <br>it's gonna flow yo <br>it's gonna flow yo <br>ayo i flow like water <br>나의 랩 내 걸음 <br>All real but whats realer <br>녹고 있는 얼음 <br>man killed for oil drills <br>점점 부족한 기름 <br>man vs mother earth <br>인간대 자연의 씨름 <br>And of course i love flossing <br>but what is it costing <br>i ready to die and might kill <br>for bigger portions <br>죽을때 까지 <br>i go hard till in a coffin <br>근데 여긴 내 시체를 <br>묻을 땅도 없지 <br>오직 나와 내 가족 <br>죽을때 까지 <br>with god on my side <br>누가 덤빌까 감히 <br>waikiki with my wife <br>where you can find me <br>with my raps like fukushima <br>i'm fucking toxic <br>식탐 교만으로 배가 <br>부른 악당들을 <br>찾아 내 보드 타고 <br>또 하늘을 날아 <br>진실 못듣는 새끼들은 <br>또 뱉어 나방 <br>온 사방 상상력과 <br>꿈이 없는 사막 <br>]]></content><category term="비프리 (B-Free)" label="비프리 (B-Free)"/><category term="Water II (Feat. Justhis)" label="Water II (Feat. Justhis)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비프리_B-Free/James_Bond/</id><title>비프리_B-Free - James Bond - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC_B-Free/James_Bond/" title="비프리_B-Free - James Bond - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[wearing saint laurent feel like <br>james bond <br>wearing saint laurent feel like <br>james bond <br>wearing saint laurent feel like <br>james bond <br>james bond <br>james bond <br>james bond <br>james bond <br>wearing saint laurent feel like <br>james bond <br>james bond <br>james bond <br>wearing saint laurent feel like <br>james bond <br>banging on my chest like <br>i'm king kong <br>got a big head vince vaughn <br>can't kill me better <br>bring your big guns <br>kushj from ethiopia we <br>light up africa like akon <br>camouflaged like viet congs <br>leather gloves gary payton <br>fresh off the boat like <br>eddie huang strip club <br>with a 100 ones <br>feeling like kobe <br>i'm bout to drop 81 <br>my wife her name lady luck <br>feeling like <br>james bond saving these <br>hoes you should have a cape on <br>i'm on the low getting <br>my dough but i'm bout to <br>blow like napalm <br>we stay lit like london <br>bridge so fly <br>make the haters sick <br>so sly we should be <br>mi-6 no matter <br>where i still first draft pick <br>you ain't even on no <br>List you ain't got no bitch <br>i'm swtichin up styles <br>new money new clothes <br>and kicks watch <br>how i jump out the whip <br>james bond <br>wearing saint laurent feel like <br>james bond <br>wearing saint laurent feel like <br>james bond <br>james bond <br>james bond <br>james bond <br>Im feeling so fresh <br>out of saint laurent <br>내 적들은 모두 다 들어와 <br>찌꺼기 랩퍼들 <br>모두 다 저리가고 <br>너네의 사장을 데려와 <br>time to break dance and break <br>necks pay me in cash or respect <br>you're obsolete like tape decks <br>i'm the new guy like daniel craig <br>oops did i mention i'm asian a <br>korean rapper that's aging <br>trying to escape from the <br>basement of the society that <br>never raised him <br>still rock a rolex i flex like <br>a bowflex dipped in the latest <br>you cannot stop all my agents <br>from breaking out of these cages <br>your stereo types not loud enough <br>your stereo type not loud enough <br>imma keep doing just what i want <br>i keep counting up a lot of wons <br>your stereo type not loud enough <br>your stereo type not loud enough <br>this message will self destruct in <br>3 2 1 <br>]]></content><category term="비프리 (B-Free)" label="비프리 (B-Free)"/><category term="James Bond" label="James Bond"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비프리_B-Free/Freedom/</id><title>비프리_B-Free - Freedom - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC_B-Free/Freedom/" title="비프리_B-Free - Freedom - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I need my medicine <br>it gives me freedom <br>I call her my mamacita <br>i'll never leave her <br>i really need her <br>i light another one <br>then i write another one <br>Feel like i made <br>another one <br>ran up a bag damn <br>i need another one <br>너네의 가격은 너무나 비싸 <br>don't make me <br>call up a another plug <br>Im good everywhere <br>like a visa <br>부재중 전화가 여러번 <br>Yall coyote's can't catch me <br>난 천재라 잡기가 어려워 <br>Guess they aint never seen <br>these saint laurents <br>they keep on askin me <br>what are those <br>i'm going straight <br>to the cash <br>i'm going straight <br>to the cash <br>나는 내 할일을 하면서 <br>잘먹고 잘살아 <br>i bout a new bag <br>Who you finessing <br>i dont believe it <br>거짓말 <br>you need to beat it <br>Hope that your case <br>you beat it <br>자유를 찾으러 떠나 <br>im leaving <br>i light another one and <br>then i write another one <br>Feel i made another one <br>이제는 자유만 찾기엔 <br>어깨가 무거워 <br>i bought my wifey a house <br>up in the mountains <br>its really old <br>but it is ours <br>winter it gets real cold im <br>thinking its tjme to move out <br>Cause i know that <br>i could do better <br>너네의 의견 <br>don't matter yeah <br>i'm a go getter <br>i gotta stack up <br>that chedder ate <br>me a edible now <br>i feel comfortable <br>너네는 똑같은 곳에서 <br>남들에 대해서 <br>이러고 저러고 어쩌고 <br>너네가 나에 대해 뭐라던 <br>내 귀는 꽉막힌 자유로 <br>이 세상 어디로 가도 <br>it's a war for survival <br>Father forgive <br>all my rivals <br>you gotta sleep <br>with one eye closed <br>used to think <br>that my people <br>were the only ones living <br>with blind folds <br>moment of silence <br>for the kids <br>people murdered by 5-0 <br>]]></content><category term="비프리 (B-Free)" label="비프리 (B-Free)"/><category term="Freedom" label="Freedom"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비프리_B-Free/Won_Feat_Cokejazz/</id><title>비프리_B-Free - Won (Feat. Cokejazz) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC_B-Free/Won_Feat_Cokejazz/" title="비프리_B-Free - Won (Feat. Cokejazz) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[To be free is all that i want <br>And If im free <br>then i've already won <br>I just wanna leave <br>this place that i'm from <br>I wanna be free <br>and feel like im loved <br>Yeah I've alreay won <br>i've already won <br>They call me free yeah <br>you know where i'm from <br>it gets cold i can <br>Feel my heart freezing <br>i said before but this <br>time im leaving <br>Im down on my luck <br>im down on luck <br>Im down on my luck yeah <br>but i gotta get up <br>i gotta get up <br>You told me i'd lose <br>but i think i won <br>I deserve everything <br>imma take it all <br>i gotta get up <br>i gotta get up <br>i gotta get up yeah <br>freezing <br>it's cold i'm alone here <br>i wanna be free <br>that's all that i want <br>freezing <br>it's cold i'm alone <br>i wanna be free <br>that's all that i want <br>freezing <br>it's cold i'm alone <br>i wanna be free <br>that's all that i want <br>freezing <br>it's cold i'm alone <br>i wanna be free <br>that's all that i want <br>]]></content><category term="비프리 (B-Free)" label="비프리 (B-Free)"/><category term="Won (Feat. Cokejazz)" label="Won (Feat. Cokejazz)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비프리_B-Free/Dollars_And_Yen_Feat_Okasian_Cokejazz/</id><title>비프리_B-Free - Dollars And Yen (Feat. Okasian, Cokejazz) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC_B-Free/Dollars_And_Yen_Feat_Okasian_Cokejazz/" title="비프리_B-Free - Dollars And Yen (Feat. Okasian, Cokejazz) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[dollars and yens counting up <br>dollars and yens <br>너네는 조금만 힘들어도 <br>배를 버리지 <br>you keep on switching up plans <br>riding round in a van <br>these are saint laurent's naw <br>these are not vans <br>i'm bout to pop me a xan <br>i'm bout to go to japan no luggage <br>imma go shop when i land <br>dollars and yen <br>환율이 올랐어 damn <br>i woke up in a sedan <br>with okasian counting up yens <br>counting it then count i again <br>counting it then count i again <br>counting it then count i again <br>why is you playing <br>spend it all credit card run it up <br>wake up it's time <br>to get money again <br>Dollars and yens <br>Thumbin thru dollars <br>and yens <br>엄마 서두르지마 <br>그리고 울지도 마 <br>난 안망해 말하지마 <br>지금은 들을때야 ay <br>Ur boy know wats <br>he doin ido <br>엄마가 티비로 보는 래퍼들 <br>대부분 빚 좋은 개살구 <br>they ran out of they <br>muhfuckin time <br>They so in denial <br>삽질에 허우적 <br>돈 팔아 인기 벌어 <br>거지 새끼 mindset <br>2년 못가 절대 <br>못 미더워도 나만 믿어 <br>Them basic ninjas got <br>nuthin on ur boy trust <br>dollars and yen <br>counting up dollars and yen <br>count it then count it then <br>count it again <br>it's all about dollars and yen <br>it's all about dollars and yen <br>count it then count it then <br>count it again <br>numbers don't lies it's the man <br>number's don't lie it's the man <br>Yea we be stackin it <br>audio dope flippin it <br>triple it <br>Bringing it bringing it <br>bring it back home <br>With some illegal <br>기념품 내 supreme brief안에 <br>니 여잔 냄새 맡아 <br>너는 이 기분 아냐 어이 <br>아무것도 안 느껴지는 에이 <br>Tunnel vision to the paperchase <br>but idont follow <br>or swallow i start a wave <br>Killerwhale underwater my way <br>Me and bfree been on our way <br>Draped in new Travis <br>cashing out yens <br>Trap 안하더라도 plugs in japan <br>feel like im ma dein Tokio Ubering <br>everywhere in tokio <br>필요하다면 난 다해 <br>너무나 원하면 음 필요했겠지 <br>Let em just hate you <br>and you get your money <br>배고파 보여 <br>man you looking hungry <br>들었어 안좋데 <br>경기 근데 난 <br>보러가 nba 경기 <br>Tokyo to la to denver가 써줄께 <br>편지 잠시만 떠날께 현실 <br>잠시만 눈감고 <br>then i'm back hustling <br>then i'm counting <br>and thumbing thumbing <br>stuck in that tokyo traffic <br>and on my mind money <br>and traviis thinking <br>i gotta just have it <br>thinking about tiffany carrots <br>for me and my wifey <br>but i'm still a savage <br>너네는 계속 또 장난쳐 <br>damn i gotta go catch a plane <br>i gotta go to the bank spent it <br>all time to get money <br>again time to get money again <br>]]></content><category term="비프리 (B-Free)" label="비프리 (B-Free)"/><category term="Dollars And Yen (Feat. Okasian, Cokejazz)" label="Dollars And Yen (Feat. Okasian, Cokejazz)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비프리_B-Free/Fly_Away_Remix_Feat_Loota_Kohh/</id><title>비프리_B-Free - Fly Away Remix (Feat. Loota, Kohh) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC_B-Free/Fly_Away_Remix_Feat_Loota_Kohh/" title="비프리_B-Free - Fly Away Remix (Feat. Loota, Kohh) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wanna spread <br>my wings fly away <br>Hundred and hundreds <br>of miles away <br>잠시만 여기를 떠날래 <br>갔다 올께 또다른 차원에 <br>Flexing and stutting <br>in shibuya <br>너네는 계속 삽질이야 <br>내가 가는 곳이 길이야 <br>i gotta go get it giddy up <br>Trying to flip <br>thousands to mllions <br>I gotta fly away <br>i got a hide away <br>I got that shit you can smell <br>like a mile away <br>I'm going hard <br>like hardaway <br>If you dont fuck with me <br>then go the otherway <br>Matane matane <br>모두 다 잘있길 바랄께 <br>모두 다 잘되길 바랄께 <br>근데 난 가야해 <br>지금 내 운명 만나야해 <br>더 넓은 세상을 봐야해 <br>원하면 그는 꼭 대답해 <br>원하면 그는 꼭 대답해 <br>내 미래가 보여 내 눈앞에 <br>de itai jiyuu 음악하는 이유 <br>3번째 눈뜨고 <br>다시 보고 싶어 <br>너무나 아름다운 지구 <br>that money go PHEW <br>주변 사람들도 PHEW <br>look at that view baby <br>just look at that view <br>skiiing in tokyo <br>with daeske hiro <br>flying with loota <br>and kohh knock out 2 songs <br>in a row <br>MOB you know the code <br>the world it's so cold <br>i need a saint laurent coat <br>i gotta go i gotta <br>]]></content><category term="비프리 (B-Free)" label="비프리 (B-Free)"/><category term="Fly Away Remix (Feat. Loota, Kohh)" label="Fly Away Remix (Feat. Loota, Kohh)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비프리_B-Free/거짓말_Lies_Feat_Justhis/</id><title>비프리_B-Free - 거짓말 (Lies) (Feat. Justhis) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC_B-Free/%EA%B1%B0%EC%A7%93%EB%A7%90_Lies_Feat_Justhis/" title="비프리_B-Free - 거짓말 (Lies) (Feat. Justhis) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여기를 봐도 저기를 봐도 <br>여기를 봐도 저기를 봐도 <br>이년도 저년도 <br>저년도 이년도 <br>거짓말 거짓말 거짓말 <br>이새끼 저새끼 <br>우리도 너네도 <br>너네가 하는말 거짓말 <br>기다려 내가 까먹기만 <br>너네는 느껴져 거리감 <br>너네가 하는말 <br>전부다 거짓말 <br>어디서 사기쳐 야임마 <br>너네는 너무나 티가나 <br>난 절대로 안속아 <br>모두다 꺼져 다 저리가 <br>복잡해 머리가 <br>남들을 속여서 <br>이득을 취하는 범죄자 <br>다시 말해 너는 사기꾼 <br>하는말 모두다 <br>거짓말 입에서 <br>나오는건 오로지 사기뿐 <br>애국심 팔아서 <br>국민의 돈 받는 <br>너네의 이름은 <br>왜 너네의 자식은 <br>안보내 꺼져 다 꺼져 <br>자 받아 내 sonic boom <br>밑 빠진 독에 물 붓기 <br>밑 빠진 독에 물 붓기 <br>시간이 멈춘것 처럼 <br>아무런 발전이나 <br>변화도 없지 <br>밑 빠진독에 물 붓기 <br>밑 빠진 독에 물 붓기 <br>수많은 사람들 죽어도 <br>너네는 죽어도 <br>책임이 없지 <br>여기를 봐도 저기를 봐도 <br>여기를 봐도 저기를 봐도 <br>이년도 저년도 <br>저년도 이년도 <br>거짓말 거짓말 거짓말 <br>이새끼 저새끼 <br>우리도 너네도 <br>거짓말 거짓말 거짓말 <br>너네는 계속 해 거짓말 <br>기다려 내가 까먹기만 <br>근데 난 넘 좋아 머리가 genius <br>용서는 모르고 멀리 봐 <br>나랑 한 방 안에 갇히면 <br>내 눈도 못 봐 <br>크면 뭐해 덩치만 <br>나한텐 조심해 <br>카톡 이모지 하나까지 <br>내 눈은 천진반 <br>거짓말은 걍 거짓말 <br>너 잘되라 그랬었어 지랄 <br>내가 잘되고 <br>안되고는 니 거짓말이 <br>정하는 게 아냐 <br>Y'all better quit playing with god <br>we only pray to god <br>And god show me the way <br>그 길은 비단 <br>난 거짓말 없이 <br>삶의 오류 없이 <br>천 리까지 왔지 <br>니네 식상함은 천리안 <br>니네가 먼저 시작했단 <br>말은 거짓말 biyatch <br>너네는 계속 해 거짓말 <br>기다려 내가 까먹기만 <br>근데 난 넘 좋아 머리가 genius <br>용서는 모르고 멀리 봐 <br>여기를 봐도 저기를 봐도 <br>여기를 봐도 저기를 봐도 <br>이년도 저년도 <br>저년도 이년도 <br>거짓말 거짓말 거짓말 <br>이새끼 저새끼 <br>우리도 너네도 <br>거짓말 거짓말 거짓말 <br>]]></content><category term="비프리 (B-Free)" label="비프리 (B-Free)"/><category term="거짓말 (Lies) (Feat. Justhis)" label="거짓말 (Lies) (Feat. Justhis)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비프리_B-Free/NEW_WAVE_Feat_Double_K_Paloalto/</id><title>비프리_B-Free - NEW WAVE (Feat. Double K, Paloalto) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC_B-Free/NEW_WAVE_Feat_Double_K_Paloalto/" title="비프리_B-Free - NEW WAVE (Feat. Double K, Paloalto) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[man i gotta stay cool <br>i'm trying to stay cool <br>i gotta make moves <br>Yeah i gotta get my beautiful wife <br>that brand new house <br>by the beach with <br>that beautiful view <br>man i gotta stay cool yeah <br>i'm trying to stay cool <br>cause i gotta make moves <br>Man i gotta pay bills <br>and couple past due <br>but they want me to lose <br>but i gotta stay cool man <br>i used to think <br>about running up <br>in the store yelling <br>give me the loot <br>man i had to go <br>and stop my self <br>and remind my self <br>that i have too much to lose <br>금방이나 털까를 <br>고민했던 그때 반지하에 <br>working on my mixtape ay <br>자유의 뮤직을 외치며 <br>출세를 꿈꿨지 <br>now i got on two chains <br>나는 old school <br>still making new waves <br>하와이로 가서 <br>catch a few waves <br>돈벌고 싶어 마치 유대인 <br>riding in my old whip <br>listening <br>to new slaves <br>서울시부터 all the way to uk <br>our crew deep lookin <br>like wutang <br>out in london yeah <br>i'm doing big things <br>why you heated lookin <br>like loul deng <br>하와이에 놀러가서 돈쓰자 <br>run a few checks hundreds <br>with the big face <br>우린 매일 마다 축제 <br>술은 안마셔도 <br>오늘만은 들었지 축배 <br>좋은 분위기에 꼰대들은 <br>또 술취해 일으키지 문제 <br>i'm the coolest like Lupe <br>but please don't kick <br>don't push man <br>you might get a chin check <br>trying to stay cool <br>but i'm stuck <br>in my old ways feel <br>like imma lose it on a bad day <br>trying to make moves <br>trying to get paid trying <br>to make it go up on a tuesday <br>used to hustle for some <br>cool grays now <br>i'm trying to hustle <br>for some wood grain <br>even if you fall down <br>if you make a mistake <br>its cool you can catch <br>the next wave <br>Fuck all ya negativity <br>All you downer들의 시기질 <br>오늘도 난 이기지 <br>While u bitching <br>and complaining bout little shit <br>Boi I'm chasing Mavericks <br>더 큰 물에서 난 놀꺼지 <br>Play hard but I Never cheat <br>깨진 파도에서 너나 <br>paddle 해 열심히 <br>작은것들에 집착하거나 <br>이미 지나간걸 쫒으며 <br>내 에너지안빼 <br>내가 잠시 duck down하면 <br>그건 아마 더 멀리 <br>나가기 위한 플랜 <br>빠질물은 빠져 <br>떨어져나갈것들은 <br>떨어져 알아서 <br>It's Just matter of time <br>사기꾼들마져 <br>얼마안가 들어내게 돼있어 <br>their true color <br>And when the sun shine <br>U ain't gonna be here <br>looking for no handout <br>생각 자체가 칙칙해 <br>맨날 날씨가 풀려도 <br>u gonna need your umbrella <br>I'll be chillin at the beach <br>wit my shades on <br>난 새 파도를 맞을 <br>준비가 돼있어 <br>라인업에서 And when <br>the right wave come <br>Ima catch it <br>Just Watch how I take off <br>New wave <br>매일밤 수많은 <br>고민을 해도 <br>마치 생일빵 <br>다시 태어나는기분 <br>진행해 일단 마음 <br>이끌리는 데로 <br>그게 내 입장 <br>fresh air 새 인간 <br>이해못하면 시간이 <br>좀 필요하겠지 <br>결국엔 따라오겠지만 <br>미행하겠지 <br>10대엔 준비를 했고 <br>20대엔 blow up <br>30대는 모험 종점 무릉도원 <br>작은 그릇에 자존심이 크면 <br>나머지 인생은 추해져 <br>내 일에 자긍심을 갖고 <br>아버지의 바톤받아 <br>웃을거야 삶의 끝에서 <br>positive energy가 <br>파도치는 내 느낌 <br>2002 붉은악마의 태극기 <br>나를 괴롭히는 <br>렉 없어 재부팅 <br>성산일출봉 해돋이 <br>나는 세계적이지 한글로 <br>내 마음속에 <br>새겨져있지 한국놈 <br>UN 사랑엔 <br>필요없어 번역기 <br>용기와 지혜 두개로 <br>굴려 두뇌 <br>좋을때 나쁠때 <br>언제나 나에게 <br>같은 모습보여줬던 <br>사람들과 나눌래 <br>돈이 세상굴려도 <br>사랑이 UNO <br>공유해 네비에 찍힌 주소 <br>]]></content><category term="비프리 (B-Free)" label="비프리 (B-Free)"/><category term="NEW WAVE (Feat. Double K, Paloalto)" label="NEW WAVE (Feat. Double K, Paloalto)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비프리_B-Free/Shadow_Feat_Cokejazz/</id><title>비프리_B-Free - Shadow (Feat. Cokejazz) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC_B-Free/Shadow_Feat_Cokejazz/" title="비프리_B-Free - Shadow (Feat. Cokejazz) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그림자가 보여 <br>니 미소에 나는 <br>또 돈벌고 놀라가 미국에 <br>너네는 집에가 질투해 <br>너네는 새로운 <br>작전이 필요해 <br>너네는 갇혔지 미로에 <br>cause ain't shit working <br>like either way <br>하와이에 가서 <br>난 수영해 <br>swim with the killer <br>whales finess <br>like a 돌고래 <br>사람은 변하지 <br>결국엔 떠나지 <br>하는건 좆도 <br>없으면서 항상 <br>사람들은 많은걸 원하지 <br>but it's okay <br>thats just the game <br>that we play you play <br>on or your the one <br>who gets played <br>속이 고 속이는 <br>바닥에 누가 내 친구고 <br>적인지 모르겠네 <br>like one day <br>they smile in your face <br>the next day <br>they wanna piss <br>on your grave <br>they wanna give up <br>your name <br>they wanna see you <br>in shakles and chains <br>떠나줘 혼자 있게 <br>좀 떠나줘 차라리 <br>혼자 있게 좀 떠나줘 <br>차라리 혼자 있게 <br>그림자가 보여 <br>니 미소에 난 <br>그림자가 보여 <br>니 미소에 <br>Snakes wanna smile <br>in yo face <br>dont even know <br>your damn name <br>think that you're <br>getting big fame <br>think that you're <br>getting big bank <br>well hold up <br>was in the shadow <br>so i took a gamble <br>came from the ghetto <br>my path was narrow <br>i heard the devil <br>so got me an angel <br>Now she cook for me tell me <br>do to better <br>Life is a battle but nothing <br>that i cannot handle <br>Im in that bape hiding <br>in camo ducking <br>the arrows feeling <br>like a veteran <br>got me a metal <br>My chain my ring 24k <br>made 3 beats 3 songs <br>in three days <br>put it out time <br>to get paid put it <br>out time to get paid <br>out of the shadow <br>i made it yeah <br>]]></content><category term="비프리 (B-Free)" label="비프리 (B-Free)"/><category term="Shadow (Feat. Cokejazz)" label="Shadow (Feat. Cokejazz)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/No_Smoke/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - No Smoke - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/No_Smoke/" title="Gucci_Mane - No Smoke - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br><br>Keep on taking these picture holding these straps but you a non smoker <br>You ain't no gun toter, pussy you ain't no real soldier <br>You ain't make your enemy buy black roses <br>Now the young nigga head smokin' <br>Nigga stop that pump fakin' who the fuck is you Tom Brady <br>My young niggas dumb crazy, might snatch your old lady <br>You ain't shot nobody nigga <br>Doin all that, we ain't scared of nobody nigga <br>Mac 90 with a telescope <br>Man I thought you were supposed to sell the dope <br>Then why the fuck is you filmin' it <br>Finger fuckin' my FandH <br>Baby lets get intimate <br>Just like a gangster nigga, just like a gentleman <br>Dressed like a gentleman <br><br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br><br>My shooters they don't pose for pictures <br>They ain't doin' no rappin nigga <br>You ain't hit no licks, you ain't sold no bricks <br>You ain't did no trappin' nigga no <br>These rappers <br>I'm headed my MandM <br>I don't need no niggas to like me, bitch I'm a grown man <br>Let me give you a lesson, Guwop I'm bouldercrestin' <br>You and all them non smokers go to the non smokin' section <br>We see them choppers blammin', fuck all that instagrammin' <br>You think you was killin' Cam Newton the way that nigga scramblin' <br>It's yo life you gambling <br>Bout to cause a stampedge <br>Hoe in the club tryna run away from me <br>Better have a plan B, you understand me <br>Gucci don't care bout no nigga living <br>Don't care if you nine feet <br><br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke <br>Why you flexin' boy you don't want no smoke]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="No Smoke" label="No Smoke"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Last_Time_Feat_Travis_Scott/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Last Time (Feat. Travis Scott) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Last_Time_Feat_Travis_Scott/" title="Gucci_Mane - Last Time (Feat. Travis Scott) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Haah, Wop, Trav, hah <br>Just took half of it, wooh <br>Just took half of <br>Wizzop, haah <br><br>I love when my bitch get drunk cause she talk greasy to me <br>Nigga with an attitude, this shit gettin' easy to me <br>The last time I drunk some lean I was out of my mind <br>Tried to give me 20 years and that's a whole lotta time <br>A married woman divorce her husband to spend the weekend with me <br>He think it nasty when she squirt but that shit sexy to me <br>The last time I took some molly, took a gram and a half <br>Niggas think they know 'bout Gucci but they don't know the half <br>See I'm an ex X popper and online shopper <br>Niggas thought I was a clone, they heard me speak proper <br>Convicted felon worth 10 million, I'm a well known robber <br>Like Shawty Lo I got 10 children, yeah, Lo my partner <br>Wop <br><br>Last time I took drugs I just took half of it hah <br>Cause last time I took pills I had to smash a bitch geek <br>And last time I smoked gas I almost crashed a whip skrt <br>Last time I took drugs I just took half of it half <br>Last time I took drugs I just took half of it hah wow <br>Last time I took drugs I just took half of it <br><br>Last time we took drugs you just took half of it it's lit <br>Stretchin' out my jeans just to make cash fit in yeah <br>Wake up every morning to some ass and grits <br>Raw dog all my birds, I'm tryna have some chicks <br>Fi fie fie fo yeah Zone 6 to the Mo <br>La Flame linked with La Flare, yeah, that's heat and snow <br>Goin' in all year, 300 plus days long straight up <br>Makin' money all year, talking 52 weeks strong <br>Better back up, give me space yeah <br>I want ice cream on your face <br>Goin' Pharrell Williams on the case oh my God <br>Ohhhh, then we skate skate skate away <br>720 with the grind, landed, landed all fine <br><br>Last time I took drugs I just took half of it <br>Cause last time I took pills I had to smash a bitch <br>And last time I smoked gas I almost crashed a whip <br>Last time I took drugs I just took half of it <br>Last time I took drugs I just took half of it hah <br>Last time I took drugs I just took half of it hah <br><br>The last time I went to Onyx man I ordered a dub <br>Tried to leave with every big booty bitch in the club <br>I bought a Rolls Royce and a Lambi' when I went to Miami vroom <br>The last time I seen little mama she wasn't wearin' no panties <br>Last time I went to Vegas, spent 200k gamblin' <br>I'm just an east Atlanta nigga servin' junkies in Chamblee <br>The last time I tricked out I brought 4 hoes to my place <br>They call me Gucci Mane Picasso cause I painted they face <br>Guwop <br><br>Last time I took drugs I just took half of it hah <br>Cause last time I took pills I had to smash a bitch geek <br>And last time I smoked gas I almost crashed a whip skrt <br>Last time I took drugs I just took half of it half <br>Last time I took drugs I just took half of it hah wow <br>Last time I took drugs I just took half of it <br><br>Burrr, Trav, blaow, it's Gucci <br>Straight up <br>Hah, burrr, wow, bling, burrr <br>Yeah, oh my God]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Last Time (Feat. Travis Scott)" label="Last Time (Feat. Travis Scott)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Nonchalant/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Nonchalant - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Nonchalant/" title="Gucci_Mane - Nonchalant - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Now my watch so fuckin' bright <br>It look like sunlight in the night <br>I shit on rappers, I shit on athletes <br>Me and Floyd should book a fight <br>I'm a sight to see for sho so your hoe should book a flight <br>Versace frames so call me Forbes <br>I done fucked every hoe I like <br>I'm so charming all these tinted chains <br>I didn't even wear a charm <br>She like Bentley bracelets what's that on your arm <br>You didn't have to speak offensive cause my watch is so expensive women get so damn defensive <br>They love me like kids love Christmas <br>I'm young active and attractive <br>Nonchalant but I'm persistent <br>I can get any bitch I want <br>But I'm so motherfuckin' picky <br>I'm a very picky person been like that since I was hurtin' <br>You can't tell me anything, you gotta be for certain <br><br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br><br>I'm a fed target, on the red carpet <br>In a whip so new valet scared to park it <br>Not a average artist, an elaborate artist <br>My collabs turn locals to established artists <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>Cause all these hoes bleed once a month huh <br>I give a chick a couple hundred just to leave me alone <br>A little hush money so she don't ask me none <br>I still get love from the EA six <br>But I got no love from the DA <br>I see the DJ run it back like a punt return <br>I guess I still get love from the DJs <br>But I got no love for you fuckboys <br>You still caught up in the he say she say <br>I send love to my niggas on lock down <br>A lot of them ain't got no release date <br>The J's love it how I whip it till my wrist ache <br>Bitch say that she in love with my mixtapes <br>Baby if you love me like you say that you do <br>Then you'll take these ten bricks to your ribcage <br>All the young niggas call me a OG <br>But I don't reminisce about the old days <br>I don't want nothin' old but a bankroll <br>I outgrew oldschools at a young age its Wop <br><br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant <br>In the strip club chillin' so nonchalant]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Nonchalant" label="Nonchalant"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Yet/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Yet - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Yet/" title="Gucci_Mane - Yet - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yet <br><br>My bitch ring cost 2 MandM's and I ain't been out a year yet <br>My wrist is sick, its terminally ill, it still ain't found a cure yet <br>You burning all your bridges nigga I'ma call you Bridgette <br>You acting like a bitch you mad cause you ain't made a hit yet <br>Someone come and stop GuWop ain't found a volunteer yet <br>This trap rap that influencing the world man Gucci pioneered it <br>I just vacuum sealed a couple mill, I know real niggas feel that <br>Gucci can't retire cause he ain't made a hundred mill yet <br>Keep on talkin' slick, I send my shooters where you live at <br>Pow pow pow, put that pistol where your grill at <br>Lil mama sucking it like she love me <br>I ain't even pay the bills yet <br>I was worth two hundred fifty thou, didn't even have a deal yet <br><br>dickin' down, we ain't even done it yet <br>He bought it 'fore I whipped the shit man I ain't even spun it yet <br>Water in it, water whippin', it ain't even dry yet <br>Quarter flippin, in the kitchen, workin' with the pyrex <br> dickin' down, we ain't even done it yet <br>He bought it 'fore I whipped the shit man I ain't even spun it yet <br>Water in it, water whippin', it ain't even dry yet <br>Quarter flippin, in the kitchen, workin' with the pyrex <br><br>They bring it to me <br>The work ain't even came yet <br>It's like they got umbrellas out it ain't even rain yet <br>Grr, that dog food and she can't find no vein at <br>Grr, mob rules might tie you to a train track <br>You leasing that don't even got the title jack <br>She peepin' that, that's why she didn't invite you back <br>You got midget arms, you swing, I don't even fight you back <br>I'm a tiger yous a lame, I get no stripes for that <br>Drop me in the jungle where the lions at grr <br>I come back with a lion jacket with the matching hat grr <br>I call you Raphael cause you hang with a sewer rat <br>I can't hang with no informer, I'm too hood for that <br><br>dickin' down, we ain't even done it yet <br>He bought it 'fore I whip the shit man I ain't even spun it yet <br>Water in it, water whippin', it ain't even dry yet <br>Quarter flippin, in the kitchen, workin' with the pyrex <br>Skrt <br> dickin' down, we ain't even done it yet <br>He bought it 'fore I whip the shit man I ain't even spun it yet <br>Water in it, water whippin', it ain't even dry yet <br>Quarter flippin, in the kitchen, workin' with the pyrex <br>Skrt <br><br>Yet, yet <br>Yet, yet]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Yet" label="Yet"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Crash/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Crash - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Crash/" title="Gucci_Mane - Crash - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Shutup <br>Gucci <br><br>I let my pockets do the talkin' <br>I ain't got nothin' to say <br>And if that bitch ain't pussy poppin' <br>Get the fuck out my face <br>And if you niggas ain't talkin 'bout profit <br>Then yall ass in the way <br>LIL' NIGGA <br>Talkin loud when he know he a lame <br>Claimin' blood <br>Hell naw, boy you know you's a dud <br>Fiendin cuz <br>Hell naw, boy we know you's a scrub <br>Where the love at <br>Naw, man you gets no love <br>Cuz you so lame <br>How the fuck you even get in the club <br>I got insane young niggas and they trained to go <br>I point my fingers like a cross, and god send em to ya door <br>Man y'all niggas ain't no killas, man yall niggas some hoes <br>Man y'all niggas ain't no dealers, man yall niggas some Js <br>I don't blame you, i blame yo daddy It was how you was raised <br>Should take this Tom Ford belt and beat you with it <br>Like back in the day <br>They say that Gucci Mane is crazy and I say I agree <br>But they stole so much sauce that I heard their record <br>And thought it was me <br>It's Gucci <br><br>LIL NIGGA <br>crash, we can crash nigga i just wanna crash <br>LIL NIGGA <br>crash, we can crash i just i just i just crash <br>LIL NIGGA <br>we can crash nigga i just wanna crash <br>LIL NIGGA <br>we can crash nigga i just wanna crash <br>LIL NIGGA <br>crash, we can crash nigga i just wanna crash <br>LIL NIGGA <br>crash, we can crash i just i just i just crash <br>LIL NIGGA <br>we can crash nigga i just wanna crash <br>LIL NIGGA <br>talkin trash nigga, but i just wanna crash <br><br>Think you ahead of me nigga <br>What you said to me nigga <br>Talkin' shit on the internet, you scared of me nigga <br>I got 10 million put away, you can belittle me nigga <br>LIL NIGGA, dig yo grave I'll bury yo ass with the figures <br>LIL NIGGA <br>I'm the one you wanted to grow up to be <br>LIL NIGGA <br>But you'll never ever, ever be me <br>LIL NIGGA <br>Ask yo bitch i bet she say I'm the truth <br>Matter of fact I'm day dreamin' about her right now in the booth <br>Ya Lil BITCH <br>Wanna crash We can crash on sight <br>200 rounds in my clip, we can blast all night <br>LIL BITCH <br>Speak softly and walk real light <br>I cut yo head off nigga, you know that plugs don't fight <br>It's Gucci <br><br>LIL NIGGA <br>crash, we can crash nigga i just wanna crash <br>LIL NIGGA <br>crash, we can crash i just i just i just crash <br>LIL NIGGA <br>we can crash nigga i just wanna crash <br>LIL NIGGA <br>we can crash nigga i just wanna crash <br>LIL NIGGA <br>crash, we can crash nigga i just wanna crash <br>LIL NIGGA <br>crash, we can crash i just i just i just crash <br>LIL NIGGA <br>we can crash nigga i just wanna crash <br>LIL NIGGA <br>talkin trash nigga, but i just wanna crash]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Crash" label="Crash"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Stutter/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Stutter - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Stutter/" title="Gucci_Mane - Stutter - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can't even lie, that bitch so bad, lil mama so thick <br>The way she throw it back it'll make you stutter when you hit <br><br>I'm just tryna fight it off, ain't tryna nut too quick <br>She make me wanna take her, she's another nigga bitch <br>A bitch that Gucci Mane can't get, man that bitch don't exist <br>This dick so good, I take it from her, she might slit her wrist <br>Bling blaww burr, I put diamonds on her clit <br>Fucked her in the air, yeah she ride me on the jet <br>His and her fur, yeah I bought my chick a fit <br>Like Edward Scissorhands, yeah she cut up on that dick <br>G g g good god, so why she standing back like a pic <br>Spaghetti straps in my Maybach, she showing off her tits <br>She ran off on the plug, so I'ma smash her at the Ritz <br>S skeeted in her mouth so now she talkin' with a lisp <br><br>I can't even lie, that bitch so bad lil mama so thick <br>The way she throw it back it'll make you stutter when you hit <br>I can't even lie, that bitch so bad lil mama so thick <br>The way she throw it back it'll make you stutter when you hit <br><br>I told her bring a friend with her but she just brought some twins <br>Three girls and one Gucci Mane god damn I'm goin' in <br>All these Franklins on me man I said my name was Ben <br>Magic City Monday night, I just threw up a ten <br>Nigga with a attitude I feel like Cube and Ren <br>These two ice cubes in my ear they cost a quarter M <br>That pussy hairy scarin' me god damn she need to trim <br>The way that bitch took care of me she might get her a Benz <br>She suck me til' it tickle me, slow down the neighbors listening <br>I got her like ten necklaces, you know my diamonds glistenin' <br>She fucked me then she shot me with her friends, I think she trickin' me <br>Her nigga know about me but god damn he can't get rid of me <br>She stutter step, sweet in lingerie <br>I beat it up like MMA she drank it up like Alize <br>Eight latin hoes in my room I feel like it's the fifth of May <br>Pull up on the kid, you dig <br>But bitch I ain't got time to play <br><br>I can't even lie, that bitch so bad lil mama so thick <br>The way she throw it back it'll make you stutter when you hit <br>I I can't even lie, that bitch so bad lil mama so thick <br>The way she throw it back it'll make you stutter when you hit <br>I I can't even lie, that bitch so bad lil mama so thick <br>The way she throw it back it'll make you stutter when you hit]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Stutter" label="Stutter"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Both_Feat_Drake/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Both (Feat. Drake) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Both_Feat_Drake/" title="Gucci_Mane - Both (Feat. Drake) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Southside <br>If Young Metro don't trust you <br>I'm gon' shoot you <br>I got so many felonies <br>I might can't never <br>go to Canada <br>But Drake said <br>he gon' pull some strings <br>So let me check my calendar <br>I just popped me one of them <br>one what you call its <br>And it boosted my stamina <br>Now I'm fucking her <br>on the banister <br>Guess I just East Atlanta'd her <br>I'm in an all red drop tarantula <br>Fuck a Challenger <br>Damn these hoes ain't <br>got no manners bruh <br>Where's the manager <br>I keep throwing rubber bandies up <br>Hoe pull your panties up <br>Cause you fuck <br>like a granny fuck <br>You're just an amateur <br>This Patek Philipe gon' <br>make this crooked judge <br>Try throw the book at me <br>I look like half <br>a million worth of heroin <br>When she look at me <br>But you ain't gotta <br>fuck with me my nig <br>But you're stuck with me <br>But how you called <br>the cops on me my nig <br>You grew up with me <br>I don't usually do this unless <br>I'm drunk or I'm high <br>But I'm both right now <br>got me talking about my life <br>I don't usually do this unless <br>I'm drunk or I'm high <br>But I'm both right now <br>I don't usually do this unless <br>I'm drunk or I'm high <br>But I'm both right now <br>and I need ya in my life <br>I don't usually do this unless <br>I'm drunk or I'm high <br>But I'm both right now <br>Yeah I'm both <br>Yeah I had a drink yeah <br>I smoked <br>Yeah you think I need you <br>but I don't <br>Just left out Dubai <br>with all my folk <br>Open water <br>my location is remote <br>Shout out Yachty <br>but this ain't a Lil Boat <br>This some shit I wrote <br>about when I was broke <br>See the power of <br>the mind is not a joke <br>Man I said <br>that I would do it <br>and I did <br>Used to get leftovers <br>out the fridge <br>Nobody was famous <br>where I lived <br>Till I got it jumping <br>at the crib <br>Took a lot to be able to give <br>I mean <br>I don't usually do this unless <br>I'm drunk or I'm high <br>But I'm both right now <br>got me talking about my life <br>I don't usually do this unless <br>I'm drunk or I'm high <br>But I'm both right now <br>I don't usually do this unless <br>I'm drunk or I'm high <br>But I'm both right now <br>and I need ya in my life <br>I don't usually do this unless <br>I'm drunk or I'm high <br>But I'm both right now <br>Southside <br>]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Both (Feat. Drake)" label="Both (Feat. Drake)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Walk_On_Water/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - Walk On Water - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/Walk_On_Water/" title="Gucci_Mane - Walk On Water - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ricky Racks <br>It's the return, East Atlanta, Santa <br><br>Off the wall, Off the chain <br>Off the top, I'm off the leash <br>So many freaks coming by the spot <br>Had to move, I broke the lease <br>I'm a dog, street gorilla <br>Going ape shit, I'm a beast <br>You feeling froggish, nigga jump <br>Got the pump on me capiche <br>I'm complete, can't compete <br>Pussy nigga check my physique <br>I'm a freak, made 3 albums in 6 months <br>I'm so unique, I'm elite <br>I'm prestigious, got two hoes in the same regions <br>And all day all I dream about is sex <br>That's why I got on Yeezys <br>The Trap god but I love Jesus <br>Jesus Jesus Goodness gracious <br>All these sauce it's getting contagious <br>Done in Vegas stays in Vegas <br>Punch <br>Put a brick down put it back together <br>Cash and dope go hand in hand <br>Hand you the yey, hand me the bags <br>It's Gucci <br><br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>Neck like water <br>Wrists like water <br>Ear rings, fingers and they look like water <br>Just bought a house and it's right by water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br><br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>Neck like water <br>Wrists like water <br>Fingers, ear rings man they look like water <br>Built me a house and it's right by water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br><br>G Gucci Mane I'm the water man <br>Make it rain, do the water dance <br>Water dripping like the faucet drip <br>Hit ten hoes on my Florida trip <br>Like 21 Savage I slaughter them <br>Thirty thousand dollars I ordered it <br>Like Dae Dae, I spend this shit <br>Like Lil Uzi Vert, I'm dripping it <br>You can walk on water too if have faith in me <br>I got high paid killers, you safe with me <br>Set me up on first date, Don't wait on me <br>I'm a human highlight, first take with me <br>If you got a Dawn, who needs a Wraith <br>If you got a bank, who needs a safe <br>Buy the restaurant, who needs a chef <br>My game's too official, who needs a ref <br>When the Wopter call, don't hold your breathe <br>I came to ball, until nothing left <br>Balenciaga sneakers, baby watch your step <br>All you rappers broke, But I came to help <br>I'm Ric Flair, I came to take your belt <br>East Atlanta Santa, you just an elf <br>When I do it, I do it, I do it to death <br>All this haters can go to hell <br><br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>Neck like water <br>Wrists like water <br>Ear rings, fingers and they look like water <br>Just bought a house and it's right by water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br><br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water <br>Neck like water <br>Wrists like water <br>Fingers, ear rings man they look like water <br>Built me a house and it's right by water <br>I'm the Trap God and I walk on water]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="Walk On Water" label="Walk On Water"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/I_Cant/</id><title>Gucci_Mane - I Can`t - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gucci_Mane/I_Cant/" title="Gucci_Mane - I Can`t - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Southside <br>If Young Metro don't trust you, I'm gon' shoot you <br><br>Let me just say this out the gate <br>I'm the nigga everybody love to hate <br>I'm the hustler every stripper wanna date <br>But I just wanna cut a check 'cus I can't wait <br>Most of these rappers groupies and I can't relate <br>Stay in line 'fore this chopper get you scraped <br>I got a problem, I'mma say it to your face <br>And fuck your bottom, I'mma shoot you in your face <br><br>They want me to apologize, but I can't <br>You can talk about homicides, but I can't <br>You pillow talking to these bitches, but I can't <br>You niggas snitchin' on your partners, but I can't <br>You let a nigga disrespect you, but I can't <br>You might get turned the other cheek, but I can't <br>You suckers rockin' fake jewelry, but I can't <br>I know they wait for me to fall, but I can't <br><br>Oh that's your girl That's your world, I'm with her tonight <br>A rich nigga smilin' at you It's so pearly white <br>It's the burr burr burr burr rockin' fur tonight <br>I'm Michael Kor's to the floor, call me sir tonight <br>Think what you wanna think, but you can't break a bank, fool <br>Can't let a nigga go, she know I keep her bank full <br>She wanna start a home with me, but I can't <br>She think that I'm her cup of tea, but I ain't <br>See, I'm the type to think her shit doesn't stink <br>The new ice cream has to compete without the tank <br>Fresh out the boat, but she's a freaky, not a saint <br>A stowaway, so I'mma make her walk the plank <br><br>They want me to apologize, but I can't <br>You can talk about homicides, but I can't <br>You pillow talking to these bitches, but I can't <br>You niggas snitchin' on your partners, but I can't <br>You let a nigga disrespect you, but I can't <br>You might get turned the other cheek, but I can't <br>You suckers rockin' fake jewelry, but I can't <br>I know they wait for me to fall, but I can't <br><br>I'm on that rich nigga shit, I drop some bread on that bitch <br>All these stones, man you'd think we're more than Fred in this bitch <br>I done shown this bitch so much, that I got scared of this bitch <br>She done seen so many mils I might go fed if she snitch <br>I need a mistress, the type to give me head 'til she sick <br>I told her, please stop sucking on me, I was begging the bitch <br>I was worth like half a million when I came in this shit <br>I'm a eight figure nigga now, I'm trained for this shit <br>Back to all these rocks on me, I look like Hov and Dame in this bitch <br>My life's a documentary, I feel like Game in this shit <br>So many of my partners turned I'm so ashamed of my clip <br>But I can't never be a snitch, I'm too attrained for this shit <br><br>They want me to apologize, but I can't <br>You can talk about homicides, but I can't <br>You pillow talking to these bitches, but I can't <br>You niggas snitchin' on your partners, but I can't <br>You let a nigga disrespect you, but I can't <br>You might get turned the other cheek, but I can't <br>You suckers rockin' fake jewelry, but I can't <br>I know they wait for me to fall, but I can't]]></content><category term="Gucci Mane" label="Gucci Mane"/><category term="I Can`t" label="I Can`t"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halestorm/I_Hate_Myself_For_Loving_You/</id><title>Halestorm - I Hate Myself For Loving You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:22:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:22:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Halestorm/I_Hate_Myself_For_Loving_You/" title="Halestorm - I Hate Myself For Loving You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight, gettin' uptight, where are you <br>You said you'd meet me, now it's quarter to two <br>I know I'm hangin' but I'm still wantin' you <br>Hey Jack, it's a fact they're talkin' in town <br>I turn my back and you're messin' around <br>I'm not really jealous, don't like lookin' like a clown <br><br>I think of you ev'ry night and day <br>You took my heart then you took my pride away <br><br>I hate myself for loving you <br>I can't break free from the things that you do <br>I wanna walk but I run back to you <br>That's why I hate myself for loving you <br>Yeah <br><br>Daylight, spent the night without you <br>But I've been dreamin' 'bout the lovin' you do <br>I'm over being angry 'bout the hell you put me through <br>Hey, man, bet you can treat me right <br>You just don't know what you was missin' last night <br>I wanna see you begging, say forget it just for spite <br><br>I think of you ev'ry night and day <br>You took my heart and you took my pride away <br><br>I hate myself for loving you <br>I can't break free from the the things that you do <br>I wanna walk but I run back to you <br>That's why I hate myself for loving you <br>Ow <br><br>I think of you ev'ry night and day <br>You took my heart and you took my pride away <br><br>I hate myself for loving you <br>I can't break free from the things that you do <br>I wanna walk but I run back to you <br>That's why I hate myself for loving you <br><br>I hate myself for loving you <br>I can't break free from the the things that you do <br>I wanna walk but I run back to you <br>That's why I hate myself for loving you <br><br>I hate myself <br>For loving you <br>I hate myself <br>For loving you <br>I hate myself <br>For loving you <br>I hate myself <br>I hate myself for loving you]]></content><category term="Halestorm" label="Halestorm"/><category term="I Hate Myself For Loving You" label="I Hate Myself For Loving You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yamazaki_Masayoshi/僕はここにいる___Bokuwa_Kokoni_Iru_나는_여기에_있다/</id><title>Yamazaki_Masayoshi - 僕はここにいる / Bokuwa Kokoni Iru (나는 여기에 있다) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:24:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:24:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yamazaki_Masayoshi/%E5%83%95%E3%81%AF%E3%81%93%E3%81%93%E3%81%AB%E3%81%84%E3%82%8B___Bokuwa_Kokoni_Iru_%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%97%AC%EA%B8%B0%EC%97%90_%EC%9E%88%EB%8B%A4/" title="Yamazaki_Masayoshi - 僕はここにいる / Bokuwa Kokoni Iru (나는 여기에 있다) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ため息だけが？寂に消えていった？り道 <br>타메이키다케가 시지마니 키에테이잇타 카에리미치 <br>한숨 만이 조용히 사라져가던 귀갓길 <br>遠い空　ゆれている街？ <br>토오이 소라 유레테이루 마치나미 <br>멀어보이는 하늘 흔들리고 있는 집들 <br><br>すべてに君のやさしい微笑みが離れない <br>스베테니 키미노 야사시이 호호에미가 하나레나이 <br>모든 것에서 너의 다정한 미소가 떨어지질 않아 <br>手をのばしても　？かない場所にいる <br>테오 노바시테모 토도카나이 바쇼니 이루 <br>손을 뻗어도 닿지 않는 장소에 있어 <br><br>もっと君のこと知りたいよ <br>모옷토 키미노 코토 시리타이요 <br>좀 더 너에 대해서 알고 싶어 <br>悲しみもささやきも全部見てみたい <br>카나시미모 사사야키모 제음부 미테미타이 <br>슬픔도 속삭임도 전부 보고 싶어 <br>苦しいよ　今度はいつ逢える <br>쿠루시이요 코은도와 이츠 아에루 <br>너무 힘들어 다음엔 언제 만날 수 있어? <br><br>？すぎた出？い　胸にかみしめている　痛いほど <br>오소스기타 데아이 무네니 카미시메테이루 이타이호도 <br>너무 늦은 만남을 가슴 속 깊이 곱씹고 있어 아플 정도로 <br>？付いたら夜は終りはじめてる <br>키츠이타라 요루와 오와리 하지메테루 <br>정신을 차리니 밤은 끝나기 시작하고 있었어 <br><br>うまく君の名を呼べないよ <br>우마쿠 키미노 나오 요베나이요 <br>제대로 네 이름을 부를 수가 없어 <br>せつなくて　むなしくて　つぶされそうさ <br>세츠나쿠테 무나시쿠테 츠부사레소오사 <br>가슴 아프고 허무해서 망가질 것 만 같아 <br>わかるかい　僕はここにいる <br>와카루카이 보쿠와 코코니 이루 <br>알고 있니? 나는 여기에 있어 <br><br>むくわれない束の間の夢ならば <br>무쿠와레나이 츠카노 마노 유메나라바 <br>보답받을 수 없는 한 순간의 꿈이라면 <br>せめて偶然の時だけでも <br>세메테 구우제은노 토키다케데모 <br>하다못해 우연한 순간 만이라도 <br>はかないうたかたの？ならば <br>하카나이 우타카타노 코이나라바 <br>허무한 물거품 같은 사랑이라면 <br>せめて今君の？だけでも <br>세메테 이마 키미노 코에다케데모 <br>하다못해 지금 너의 목소리 만이라도 <br><br>救われない痛みだけの？持ちでいい <br>스쿠와레나이 이타미다케노 키모치데이이 <br>희망 없는 아픔뿐인 마음이라도 좋아 <br>傷ついてもそれでかまわない <br>키즈츠이테모 소레데 카마와나이 <br>상처 입어도 그걸로 상관없어 <br>できるなら今すぐ抱きしめたい <br>데키루나라 이마 스구 다키시메타이 <br>할 수 있다면 지금 당장 껴안고 싶어 <br>二人だけの約束を交わしたい <br>후타리다케노 야쿠소쿠오 카와시타이 <br>두 사람 만의 약속을 나누고 싶어 <br><br>むくわれない束の間の夢ならば <br>무쿠와레나이 츠카노 마노 유메나라바 <br>보답받을 수 없는 한 순간의 꿈이라면 <br>せめて偶然の時だけでも <br>세메테 구우제은노 토키다케데모 <br>하다못해 우연한 순간 만이라도 <br>はかないうたかたの？ならば <br>하카나이 우타카타노 코이나라바 <br>허무한 물거품 같은 사랑이라면 <br>せめて今君の？だけでも <br>세메테 이마 키미노 코에다케데모 <br>하다못해 지금 너의 목소리 만이라도]]></content><category term="Yamazaki Masayoshi" label="Yamazaki Masayoshi"/><category term="僕はここにいる / Bokuwa Kokoni Iru (나는 여기에 있다)" label="僕はここにいる / Bokuwa Kokoni Iru (나는 여기에 있다)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yamazaki_Masayoshi/One_More_Time_One_More_Chance/</id><title>Yamazaki_Masayoshi - One More Time, One More Chance - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:24:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:24:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yamazaki_Masayoshi/One_More_Time_One_More_Chance/" title="Yamazaki_Masayoshi - One More Time, One More Chance - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[코레이조 나니오 우시나에바 코코로와 유루사레루노 <br>도레호도노 이타미나라바 모 이치도 키미니 아에루 <br>one more time 키세츠요 우츠로와나이데 <br>one more time 후자케앗타 지칸요 <br>쿠이치가우 토키와 이츠모 보쿠가 사키니 오레타네 <br>와가마마나 세카쿠가 나오사라 이토시쿠 사세타 <br>one more chance 키오쿠니 아시오 토라레테 <br>one more chance 츠기노 바쇼오 에라베나이 <br>이츠데모 사가시테이루요 돗카니 키미노 스가타오 <br>무카이노 호무 로지우라노 마도 <br>콘나 토코니 이루 하즈모 나이노니 <br>네가이가 모시모 카나우나라 이마 스구 키미노 모토에 <br>데키나이 코토와 모 나니모나이 <br>스베테 카케테 다키시메테 미세루요 <br>사비시사 마기라스 다케나라 다레데모 이이하즈 나노니 <br>호시가 오치소나 요루다카라 지분오 이츠와레나이 <br>one more time 키세츠요 우츠로와나이데 <br>one more time 후자케앗타 지칸요 <br>이츠데모 사가시테이루요 돗카니 키미노 스가타오 <br>코사텐데모 유메노 나카데모 <br>콘나 토코니 이루 하즈모 나이노니 <br>키세키가 모시모 오코루나라 이마스구 키미니 미세타이 <br>아타라시이 아사 코레카라노 보쿠 <br>이에나캇타 스키토유 코토바모 <br>나츠노 오모이데가 마와루 <br>후이니 키에타 코도 <br>이츠데모 사가시테이루요 돗카니 키미노 스가타오 <br>아케가타노 마치 사쿠라기쵸데 <br>콘나 토코니 쿠루하즈모 나이노니 <br>네가이가 모시모 카나우나라 이마 스구 키미노 모토에 <br>데키나이 코토와 모 나니모나이 <br>스베테 카케테 다키시메테 미세루요 <br>이츠데모 사가시테이루요 돗카니 키미노 스가타오 <br>타비사키노 미세 심분노 스미 <br>콘나 토코니 이루 하즈모 나이노니 <br>키세키가 모시모 오코루나라 이마스구 키미니 미세타이 <br>아타라시이 아사 코레카라노 보쿠 <br>이에나캇타 스키토유 코토바모 <br>이츠데모 사가시테 시마우 돗카니 키미노 에가오오 <br>큐코마치노 후미키리 아타리 <br>콘나 토코니 이루 하즈모 나이노니 <br>이노치가 쿠리카에스나라바 난도모 키미노 모토에 <br>호시 모노나도 모 나니모나이 <br>키미노 호카니 타이세츠나 모노 나노]]></content><category term="Yamazaki Masayoshi" label="Yamazaki Masayoshi"/><category term="One More Time, One More Chance" label="One More Time, One More Chance"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/잠비_Jambi/새벽세시_Vocal_Ver/</id><title>잠비_Jambi - 새벽세시 (Vocal Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:26:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:26:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A0%EB%B9%84_Jambi/%EC%83%88%EB%B2%BD%EC%84%B8%EC%8B%9C_Vocal_Ver/" title="잠비_Jambi - 새벽세시 (Vocal Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새하얗게 잘려진 초승달 <br>두 눈 가득 시리던 새벽세시 <br>유난히 초라한 내 두 손 <br>갈 길 잃은 무거운 발걸음 <br>두 손 모아 감싸 쥔 내 얼굴 <br>잿빛으로 물들던 그 시간 <br>아 보내야 하는데 <br>아 보낼 수 없는데 <br>새하얀 바람에 <br>두 눈을 감으니 <br>추억이 스쳐 지나가고 <br>새까만 그림자 <br>내 맘 속에 남아 <br>멍으로 살아 가는구나 <br>아 하늘도 우는데 <br>아 이제는 보내야지 <br>새하얗게 잘려진 초승달 <br>두 눈 가득 시리던 새벽세시 <br>]]></content><category term="잠비 (Jambi)" label="잠비 (Jambi)"/><category term="새벽세시 (Vocal Ver.)" label="새벽세시 (Vocal Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이세연/나무_Feat_이관제/</id><title>이세연 - 나무 (Feat. 이관제) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:27:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:27:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B8%EC%97%B0/%EB%82%98%EB%AC%B4_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%EA%B4%80%EC%A0%9C/" title="이세연 - 나무 (Feat. 이관제) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그댄 이제 막 싹튼 나무 <br>비록 열매는 없지만 <br>곧은 뿌리 내린 나무 <br>그댄 이제 막 싹튼 나무 <br>화사하고 눈부시게 <br>꽃들을 피울 나무 <br>캄캄한 밤 상처는 발목을 잡아 <br>한숨과 함께 내 안에 가두죠 <br>하지만 우린 알죠 <br>그 상처들이 날 강하게 해 <br>아름다워 <br>아름다워 <br>그댄 큰 나무가 될 거에요 <br>아름다워 <br>아름다워 <br>그댄 존재만으로 충분해요 <br>그댄 이제 막 싹튼 나무 <br>화사하고 눈부시게 <br>꽃들을 피울 나무 <br>캄캄한 밤 상처는 발목을 잡아 <br>한숨과 함께 내 안에 가두죠 <br>하지만 우린 알죠 <br>그 상처들이 날 강하게 해 <br>아름다워 <br>아름다워 <br>그댄 큰 나무가 될 거에요 <br>아름다워 <br>아름다워 <br>그댄 존재만으로 충분해요 <br>아름다워 <br>그댄 큰 나무가 될 거에요 <br>아름다워 <br>아름다워 <br>그댄 존재만으로 충분해요 <br>]]></content><category term="이세연" label="이세연"/><category term="나무 (Feat. 이관제)" label="나무 (Feat. 이관제)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이세연/그대나와_Feat_박성효/</id><title>이세연 - 그대나와 (Feat. 박성효) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:27:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:27:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B8%EC%97%B0/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%82%98%EC%99%80_Feat_%EB%B0%95%EC%84%B1%ED%9A%A8/" title="이세연 - 그대나와 (Feat. 박성효) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언제나 <br>난 그대의 손을 잡는 <br>순간을 기다렸죠 <br>나와 함께해요 그대 <br>언제나 늘 그래왔듯 <br>그대 옆에 있어요 <br>안아줘요 <br>오늘은 나와 있어요 <br>순간 스치는 니 생각에 <br>또 잠을 설치고 <br>상상의 나랠 펼치고 <br>멀어지는 그대의 그림자에 <br>다급해져와 네 이름을 불러 <br>그대 가지 말아요 <br>그대 영원을 약속해요 <br>그대 없이는 혼자 있지 못해요 <br>오늘밤 나와 있어줘요 <br>그대 상상 해봐요 <br>그대 행복하지 않나요 <br>우리 둘이서 손잡고 길을 걸을 때 <br>세상은 우리로 물들죠 그대 <br>사랑한다는 말은 사라지지 않죠 <br>언제나 우릴 맴돌죠 <br>서로에게 그 말을 전해요 <br>함께한 우리 기억 할 수 있게 <br>그대 가지 말아요 <br>그대 영원을 약속해요 <br>그대 없이는 혼자 있지 못해요 <br>오늘밤 나와 있어줘요 <br>그대 상상 해봐요 <br>그대 행복하지 않나요 <br>우리 둘이서 손잡고 길을 걸을 때 <br>세상은 우리로 물들죠 <br>그대 가지 말아요 <br>그대 영원을 약속해요 <br>그대 없이는 혼자 있지 못해요 <br>오늘밤 나와 있어줘요 <br>그대 상상 해봐요 <br>그대 행복하지 않나요 <br>우리 둘이서 손잡고 길을 걸을 때 <br>세상은 우리로 물들죠 그대 <br>]]></content><category term="이세연" label="이세연"/><category term="그대나와 (Feat. 박성효)" label="그대나와 (Feat. 박성효)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이세연/르누아르_Feat_최명서/</id><title>이세연 - 르누아르 (Feat. 최명서) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:27:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:27:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B8%EC%97%B0/%EB%A5%B4%EB%88%84%EC%95%84%EB%A5%B4_Feat_%EC%B5%9C%EB%AA%85%EC%84%9C/" title="이세연 - 르누아르 (Feat. 최명서) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우연히 액자 속 <br>당신을 봤어요 <br>그 안바다에 잠겨 <br>모든 것들이 꿈같고 <br>빛나는 세상을 봤어요 <br>당신은 행복을 <br>그리는 마술사래요 <br>따뜻한 빛들과 <br>소소하고 평화로운 풍경 <br>그 안에 사람들 <br>미소를 띠네요 <br>행복해 보여요 <br>내게도 그대가 본 <br>세상을 보여줘요 <br>언제나 미소를 <br>지을 수 있게 <br>우리 서로의 손을 <br>맞대고 함께 춤춰요 <br>그대 발위에 <br>내 두발을 탁탁 <br>Please let me know <br>행복이 뭘까요 <br>Please let me know <br>나도 그대와 같고 싶어 <br>Please let me know <br>행복이 뭘까요 <br>Please let me know <br>나도 그대와 같고 싶어 <br>따뜻한 빛들과 <br>소소하고 평화로운 풍경 <br>그 안에 사람들 <br>미소를 띠네요 <br>행복해 보여요 <br>내게도 그대가 본 <br>세상을 보여줘요 <br>언제나 미소를 <br>지을 수 있게 <br>우리 서로의 손을 <br>맞대고 함께 춤춰요 <br>그대 발위에 <br>내 두발을 탁탁 <br>Please let me know <br>행복이 뭘까요 <br>Please let me know <br>나도 그대와 같고 싶어 <br>Please let me know <br>행복이 뭘까요 <br>Please let me know <br>나도 그대와 같고 싶어 <br>Please let me know <br>행복이 뭘까요 <br>Please let me know <br>나도 그대와 같고 싶어 <br>Please let me know <br>행복이 뭘까요 <br>Please let me know <br>나도 그대와 같고 싶어 <br>]]></content><category term="이세연" label="이세연"/><category term="르누아르 (Feat. 최명서)" label="르누아르 (Feat. 최명서)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이세연/겨울에_안기어_Feat_남정현/</id><title>이세연 - 겨울에 안기어 (Feat. 남정현) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:27:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:27:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B8%EC%97%B0/%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8%EC%97%90_%EC%95%88%EA%B8%B0%EC%96%B4_Feat_%EB%82%A8%EC%A0%95%ED%98%84/" title="이세연 - 겨울에 안기어 (Feat. 남정현) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꿈이 아니니 <br>잠에서 깨어나 <br>겨울이 다가오는 <br>그 향기를 느껴봐 <br>높아진 하늘아래 <br>차분해진 공기와 <br>어릴 적 기억 떠오르는 <br>새하얀 겨울이 <br>내게도 온다 <br>겨울에 안기어 <br>후회의 지난날 떠올리니 <br>아팠던 여름 <br>감사했음을 <br>이제서야 알게 된다 <br>지쳤던 마음 가다듬고 <br>모든 것 내려 놓은 채 <br>설레는 마음 오직 <br>이 감정만을 <br>간직하며 끝을 맺는다 <br>겨울에 안기어 <br>새로운 시작을 준비하며 <br>흰 눈을 닮은 <br>겨울을 닮은 <br>편안한 <br>그런 사람 될래 <br>]]></content><category term="이세연" label="이세연"/><category term="겨울에 안기어 (Feat. 남정현)" label="겨울에 안기어 (Feat. 남정현)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/커피소년/내가_왜_이럴까_Inst/</id><title>커피소년 - 내가 왜 이럴까 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:27:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:27:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BB%A4%ED%94%BC%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84/%EB%82%B4%EA%B0%80_%EC%99%9C_%EC%9D%B4%EB%9F%B4%EA%B9%8C_Inst/" title="커피소년 - 내가 왜 이럴까 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 그녈 바라보고 있는 건지 <br>사랑인 걸까 <br>왜 그녈 보면 웃음이 나는지 <br>사랑인 걸까 <br>꿈일 거야 꿈일 거야 <br>있을 수 없는 일이야 <br>내가 왜 이럴까 대체 왜 이럴까 <br>왜 자꾸만 가슴이 떨려오는 걸까 <br>너의 그 눈빛과 <br>너의 목소리가 오 날 <br>왜 자꾸만 괴롭히는 걸까 <br>날 어떻게 한 거야 <br>왜 그녈 바라보고 있는 건지 <br>사랑인 걸까 <br>왜 그녈 보면 웃음이 나는지 <br>사랑인 걸까 <br>꿈일 거야 꿈일 거야 <br>있을 수 없는 일이야 <br>내가 왜 이럴까 대체 왜 이럴까 <br>왜 자꾸만 가슴이 떨려오는 걸까 <br>너의 그 눈빛과 <br>너의 목소리가 오 날 <br>왜 자꾸만 괴롭히는 걸까 <br>내가 왜 이럴까 대체 왜 이럴까 <br>왜 눈앞에 자꾸 어른거리는 건데 <br>나를 좀 놓아줘 <br>나를 좀 깨워줘 오 날 <br>내게 어떤 마법을 쓴 거야 <br>날 어떻게 한 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="커피소년" label="커피소년"/><category term="내가 왜 이럴까 (Inst.)" label="내가 왜 이럴까 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/데이지/내_우산을/</id><title>데이지 - 내 우산을 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:27:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:27:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80/%EB%82%B4_%EC%9A%B0%EC%82%B0%EC%9D%84/" title="데이지 - 내 우산을 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[맑은 날 우산을 들었지 <br>하늘은 또 내 맘 모르고 <br>세찬 바람이라도 불어주기를 <br>그렇게 또 그렇게 하룰 버틴다 <br>모두 행복해 보이는 <br>거릴 걸어 갈 때마다 <br>오늘은 비가 내려주길 <br>내가 작아만 보이는 <br>다들 행복해 보이는 세상을 <br>난 벗어나고파 <br>언제쯤 나는 다시 웃을까 <br>언제쯤 나는 바뀔 수 있을까 <br>오늘도 지겨운 맑은 하늘에 <br>내 우산을 펼치며 숨어본다 <br>모두 행복해 보이는 <br>거릴 걸어 갈 때마다 <br>오늘은 비가 내려주길 <br>내가 작아만 보이는 <br>다들 행복해 보이는 세상을 <br>난 벗어나고파 <br>언제쯤 나는 다시 웃을까 <br>언제쯤 나는 바뀔 수 있을까 <br>오늘도 지겨운 맑은 하늘에 <br>내 우산을 펼치며 숨어본다 <br>]]></content><category term="데이지" label="데이지"/><category term="내 우산을" label="내 우산을"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/애즈원/이별_같은_거_Inst/</id><title>애즈원 - 이별 같은 거 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:27:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:27:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%A0%EC%A6%88%EC%9B%90/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84_%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EA%B1%B0_Inst/" title="애즈원 - 이별 같은 거 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너무 밝게 웃는다거나 <br>그런 사진 보인다거나 하면 <br>떠난 니가 정말로 <br>내가 그런 줄 알까 봐 <br>그냥 아무 말도 없이 난 <br>또 아무 느낌 없는 표정만 짓고 <br>이렇게 난 아직도 <br>많이 아프다 티 내봐 <br>보내지도 붙잡지도 못한 <br>어쩜 난 아직 <br>혼자서 나 혼자서 <br>이별하는 중인가 봐 <br>짝사랑이라 하기엔 <br>설렘보단 아픔뿐이고 <br>이별했다 말하기엔 <br>여전히 넌 가까이 있고 <br>이도 저도 아닌 이별 같은 거 <br>그래 어쩜 이건 마치 이별 같은 거 <br>나 혼자서만 널 <br>보내지 못한 이별 같은 거 <br>날 것 같이 안 나는 눈물처럼 <br>답답한 지금 기분 <br>이런 답답한 아픔보다 <br>대놓고 아프고 싶어 <br>나 아픈 거 다 알면서 <br>미소 짓는 널 보면 <br>혼자만 나 혼자만 <br>이별하는 중인가 봐 <br>짝사랑이라 하기엔 <br>설렘보단 아픔뿐이고 <br>이별했다 말하기엔 <br>여전히 넌 가까이 있고 <br>이도 저도 아닌 이별 같은 거 <br>그래 어쩜 이건 마치 이별 같은 거 <br>나 혼자서만 널 <br>보내지 못한 이별 같은 <br>우리 사이에 흐린 날씨에 <br>우리 사이에 먹구름 땜에 <br>태양 같은 니가 웃어도 <br>나는 안 보여 <br>비 내리듯 니가 울어도 <br>나는 안 보여 <br>괜찮다고 말하기엔 <br>매일 너의 흔적을 찾고 <br>돌아오라 말하기엔 <br>내겐 그럴 자격이 없고 <br>이도 저도 아닌 이별 같은 거 <br>그래 어쩜 이건 마치 이별 같은 거 <br>나 혼자서만 널 <br>보내지 못한 이별 같은 거 <br>]]></content><category term="애즈원" label="애즈원"/><category term="이별 같은 거 (Inst.)" label="이별 같은 거 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/애즈원/이별_같은_거/</id><title>애즈원 - 이별 같은 거 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:27:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:27:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%A0%EC%A6%88%EC%9B%90/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84_%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EA%B1%B0/" title="애즈원 - 이별 같은 거 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너무 밝게 웃는다거나 <br>그런 사진 보인다거나 하면 <br>떠난 니가 정말로 <br>내가 그런 줄 알까 봐 <br>그냥 아무 말도 없이 난 <br>또 아무 느낌 없는 표정만 짓고 <br>이렇게 난 아직도 <br>많이 아프다 티 내봐 <br>보내지도 붙잡지도 못한 <br>어쩜 난 아직 <br>혼자서 나 혼자서 <br>이별하는 중인가 봐 <br>짝사랑이라 하기엔 <br>설렘보단 아픔뿐이고 <br>이별했다 말하기엔 <br>여전히 넌 가까이 있고 <br>이도 저도 아닌 이별 같은 거 <br>그래 어쩜 이건 마치 이별 같은 거 <br>나 혼자서만 널 <br>보내지 못한 이별 같은 거 <br>날 것 같이 안 나는 눈물처럼 <br>답답한 지금 기분 <br>이런 답답한 아픔보다 <br>대놓고 아프고 싶어 <br>나 아픈 거 다 알면서 <br>미소 짓는 널 보면 <br>혼자만 나 혼자만 <br>이별하는 중인가 봐 <br>짝사랑이라 하기엔 <br>설렘보단 아픔뿐이고 <br>이별했다 말하기엔 <br>여전히 넌 가까이 있고 <br>이도 저도 아닌 이별 같은 거 <br>그래 어쩜 이건 마치 이별 같은 거 <br>나 혼자서만 널 <br>보내지 못한 이별 같은 <br>우리 사이에 흐린 날씨에 <br>우리 사이에 먹구름 땜에 <br>태양 같은 니가 웃어도 <br>나는 안 보여 <br>비 내리듯 니가 울어도 <br>나는 안 보여 <br>괜찮다고 말하기엔 <br>매일 너의 흔적을 찾고 <br>돌아오라 말하기엔 <br>내겐 그럴 자격이 없고 <br>이도 저도 아닌 이별 같은 거 <br>그래 어쩜 이건 마치 이별 같은 거 <br>나 혼자서만 널 <br>보내지 못한 이별 같은 거 <br>]]></content><category term="애즈원" label="애즈원"/><category term="이별 같은 거" label="이별 같은 거"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트리가_Trigga/Goodbye_2013_Inst/</id><title>트리가_Trigga - Goodbye 2013 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:27:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:27:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AC%EA%B0%80_Trigga/Goodbye_2013_Inst/" title="트리가_Trigga - Goodbye 2013 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아직 난 그 꼬마애가 <br>생각이나 그때는 <br>아무것도 모르고 놀 때 <br>사실 난 그 꼬마인데 <br>많이 컸어 나는 <br>돌아가기엔 늦었지 baby <br>항상 말했어 <br>나는 될 놈이라고 <br>몇 번을 되새겨봐도 <br>꿈인 것만 같다고 <br>현실 그 앞에선 <br>그저 그림 밖에 안돼 <br>한땐 의사로 <br>어이 없이 바뀐 <br>나의 미래 <br>랩이 내 모든 <br>것을 바꿔놨네 <br>어떤 애들은 똑같이 <br>정해진 길을 걷네 <br>허나 이건 내가 <br>만들어가는 내 미래 <br>시작한 것 아빠의 말씀처럼 <br>멋지게 나는 것 <br>힘을 내 지금 너는 맞아 <br>ay 고민하지마 <br>주변에서 뭐라던 <br>갈 길을 가면 그게 맞아 <br>망설이지마 <br>지금 너는 맞아 <br>ay 그래 그게 <br>맞아 신경쓰지마 <br>뜻대로 해 그럼 <br>그게 맞아 hey boy <br>Goodbye my little young boy <br>19살의 마지막 <br>어제만 같았던 <br>서울에서의 첫 시작 <br>어느덧 훌쩍 커버린 <br>내 몸과 생각 <br>이젠 정리할 때가 왔어 <br>내 마지막을 <br>속으론 죄송했지 <br>내 부모님께 <br>남자다운 척 하며 <br>하루하루 힘든걸 숨겨 <br>그치만 가끔씩은 <br>못 견뎌 전화를 걸어 <br>부끄럽지만 내 쌓인 <br>먼지를 부모님께 털어 <br>잃은 것도 얻은 것도 <br>너무 많은 내 나이에 <br>시간과 세상은 <br>빠르게 지나가는데 <br>내 걸음은 여전히 <br>느려 안 어울리게 <br>지금 난 현실에 <br>부적응 적응을 못해 <br>남들은 너무 쉽게 <br>내 상황을 말해 <br>내 속도 모르고 <br>그런 말들에 나는 더 <br>성숙해짐을 느껴 <br>보장 없는 내 음악을 <br>미래에 걸어 <br>나와의 싸움을 벌여 <br>부모님이 주신 <br>사랑과 관심에 꼭 <br>보답하겠다란 <br>다짐을 올해에도 <br>변함없이 해 마치 <br>손톱을 뜯는 버릇처럼 <br>내년에도 같겠지 뭐 <br>조금 부끄럽기도 해 <br>이룬 것 하나 없이 <br>좋은 부모님께 <br>부끄럼 없이 자랐지만 <br>결과물들을 보여드리지는 <br>못한 난 <br>언제쯤 내 자신이 <br>자랑스러워 질까 <br>힘을 내 지금 너는 맞아 <br>ay 고민하지마 <br>주변에서 뭐라던 <br>갈 길을 가면 그게 맞아 <br>망설이지마 <br>지금 너는 맞아 <br>ay 그래 그게 맞아 <br>신경 쓰지마 <br>뜻대로 해 그럼 <br>그게 맞아 hey boy <br>힘을 내 지금 너는 맞아 <br>때가 되면 빛을 보겠지 <br>뭐 웃어넘겨 <br>속은 힘들지만 <br>티는 내지 말자고 <br>남자새끼가 눈물은 <br>보이지 말자고 <br>망설이지마 <br>지금 너는 맞아 <br>때가 되면 빛을 <br>보겠지 뭐 웃어넘겨 <br>속은 힘들지만 <br>티는 내지 말자고 <br>남자새끼가 눈물은 <br>보이지 말자고 <br>]]></content><category term="트리가 (Trigga)" label="트리가 (Trigga)"/><category term="Goodbye 2013 (Inst.)" label="Goodbye 2013 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트리가_Trigga/Goodbye_2013/</id><title>트리가_Trigga - Goodbye 2013 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:27:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:27:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AC%EA%B0%80_Trigga/Goodbye_2013/" title="트리가_Trigga - Goodbye 2013 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아직 난 그 꼬마애가 <br>생각이나 그때는 <br>아무것도 모르고 놀 때 <br>사실 난 그 꼬마인데 <br>많이 컸어 나는 <br>돌아가기엔 늦었지 baby <br>항상 말했어 <br>나는 될 놈이라고 <br>몇 번을 되새겨봐도 <br>꿈인 것만 같다고 <br>현실 그 앞에선 <br>그저 그림 밖에 안돼 <br>한땐 의사로 <br>어이 없이 바뀐 <br>나의 미래 <br>랩이 내 모든 <br>것을 바꿔놨네 <br>어떤 애들은 똑같이 <br>정해진 길을 걷네 <br>허나 이건 내가 <br>만들어가는 내 미래 <br>시작한 것 아빠의 말씀처럼 <br>멋지게 나는 것 <br>힘을 내 지금 너는 맞아 <br>ay 고민하지마 <br>주변에서 뭐라던 <br>갈 길을 가면 그게 맞아 <br>망설이지마 <br>지금 너는 맞아 <br>ay 그래 그게 <br>맞아 신경쓰지마 <br>뜻대로 해 그럼 <br>그게 맞아 hey boy <br>Goodbye my little young boy <br>19살의 마지막 <br>어제만 같았던 <br>서울에서의 첫 시작 <br>어느덧 훌쩍 커버린 <br>내 몸과 생각 <br>이젠 정리할 때가 왔어 <br>내 마지막을 <br>속으론 죄송했지 <br>내 부모님께 <br>남자다운 척 하며 <br>하루하루 힘든걸 숨겨 <br>그치만 가끔씩은 <br>못 견뎌 전화를 걸어 <br>부끄럽지만 내 쌓인 <br>먼지를 부모님께 털어 <br>잃은 것도 얻은 것도 <br>너무 많은 내 나이에 <br>시간과 세상은 <br>빠르게 지나가는데 <br>내 걸음은 여전히 <br>느려 안 어울리게 <br>지금 난 현실에 <br>부적응 적응을 못해 <br>남들은 너무 쉽게 <br>내 상황을 말해 <br>내 속도 모르고 <br>그런 말들에 나는 더 <br>성숙해짐을 느껴 <br>보장 없는 내 음악을 <br>미래에 걸어 <br>나와의 싸움을 벌여 <br>부모님이 주신 <br>사랑과 관심에 꼭 <br>보답하겠다란 <br>다짐을 올해에도 <br>변함없이 해 마치 <br>손톱을 뜯는 버릇처럼 <br>내년에도 같겠지 뭐 <br>조금 부끄럽기도 해 <br>이룬 것 하나 없이 <br>좋은 부모님께 <br>부끄럼 없이 자랐지만 <br>결과물들을 보여드리지는 <br>못한 난 <br>언제쯤 내 자신이 <br>자랑스러워 질까 <br>힘을 내 지금 너는 맞아 <br>ay 고민하지마 <br>주변에서 뭐라던 <br>갈 길을 가면 그게 맞아 <br>망설이지마 <br>지금 너는 맞아 <br>ay 그래 그게 맞아 <br>신경 쓰지마 <br>뜻대로 해 그럼 <br>그게 맞아 hey boy <br>힘을 내 지금 너는 맞아 <br>때가 되면 빛을 보겠지 <br>뭐 웃어넘겨 <br>속은 힘들지만 <br>티는 내지 말자고 <br>남자새끼가 눈물은 <br>보이지 말자고 <br>망설이지마 <br>지금 너는 맞아 <br>때가 되면 빛을 <br>보겠지 뭐 웃어넘겨 <br>속은 힘들지만 <br>티는 내지 말자고 <br>남자새끼가 눈물은 <br>보이지 말자고 <br>]]></content><category term="트리가 (Trigga)" label="트리가 (Trigga)"/><category term="Goodbye 2013" label="Goodbye 2013"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서울시립합창단/검은_베레모/</id><title>서울시립합창단 - 검은 베레모 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:28:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:28:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EC%9A%B8%EC%8B%9C%EB%A6%BD%ED%95%A9%EC%B0%BD%EB%8B%A8/%EA%B2%80%EC%9D%80_%EB%B2%A0%EB%A0%88%EB%AA%A8/" title="서울시립합창단 - 검은 베레모 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보아라 장한 모습 검은 베레모 <br>무쇠같은 우리와 누가 맞서랴 <br>하늘로 뛰어솟아 구름을 찬다 <br>검은 베레 가는 곳에 자유가 있다 <br>삼천리 금수강산 길이 지킨다 <br><br>안되면 되게 하라 특전부대 용사들 <br>아아 검은 베레 무적의 전사들 <br><br>명령에 죽고 사는 검은 베레모 <br>쏜살같은 우리를 누가 막으랴 <br>구름 위로 치솟아 하늘도 찬다 <br>검은 베레 가는 곳에 평화가 있다 <br>오천만 우리 겨레 길이 지킨다 <br><br>안되면 되게 하라 특전부대 용사들 <br>아아 검은 베레 무적의 전사들 <br><br>하늘을 오고 가는 검은 베레모 <br>바위같은 우리를 누가 막으랴 <br>산과 바다 누비며 어디든 간다 <br>검은 베레 가는 곳에 행복이 있다 <br>조국통일 그 날까지 싸워 이긴다 <br><br>안되면 되게 하라 특전부대 용사들 <br>아아 검은 베레 무적의 전사들 <br>무적의 전사들]]></content><category term="서울시립합창단" label="서울시립합창단"/><category term="검은 베레모" label="검은 베레모"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/9991/열꽃/</id><title>9991 - 열꽃 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:29:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:29:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/9991/%EC%97%B4%EA%BD%83/" title="9991 - 열꽃 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[참 바보 같은 나 <br>아직까지 기다리는 나 <br>네가 떠나간 길 <br>그 길에서 매일 <br>오지 않을 너를 기다리는 나 <br>내가 정말 하면 안 됐었던 일 <br>너를 사랑했던 일 <br>아직 사랑하는 일 <br>찬 바람에 또 네가 밀려와 <br>어김없이 찾아오는 감기처럼 <br>열이 나고 어지러운 게 <br>이맘때쯤 걸리는 <br>지독한 열병처럼 <br>또 기침이 나와 <br>이번엔 얼마나 아플까 <br>이만하면 이제 <br>된 것도 같은데 <br>어김없이 너는 내게 옮는다 <br>나을 수가 없는 병처럼 마치 <br>아프고 또 아프다가 <br>그러면 무뎌지긴 할까 <br>찬 바람에 또 네가 밀려와 <br>어김없이 찾아오는 감기처럼 <br>열이 나고 어지러운 게 <br>이맘때쯤 걸리는 <br>지독한 열병처럼 <br>또 네가 옮는다 <br>]]></content><category term="9991" label="9991"/><category term="열꽃" label="열꽃"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/슬리핑/울다_웃다_울다/</id><title>슬리핑 - 울다 웃다 울다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:30:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:30:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%AC%EB%A6%AC%ED%95%91/%EC%9A%B8%EB%8B%A4_%EC%9B%83%EB%8B%A4_%EC%9A%B8%EB%8B%A4/" title="슬리핑 - 울다 웃다 울다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루 종일 웃기만 해 <br>아니면 나 미칠 것 같아서 <br>눈을 감고 너의 얼굴 그리다 <br>울다 웃다 울다 <br>숨을 참으면 나을까 <br>입술을 깨물면 될까 <br>어떻게 해야 <br>네가 흐르지 않을까 <br>실컷 울어야 <br>비워낼 수 있을까 <br>너 아니면 난 안 되는데 <br>하루 종일 자기만 해 <br>눈을 감아야 네가 보이니까 <br>꿈속에서 너의 얼굴 그리다 <br>울다 웃다 울다 <br>숨을 참으면 나을까 <br>입술을 깨물면 될까 <br>어떻게 해야 <br>네가 흐르지 않을까 <br>맘껏 울어도 <br>널 밀어낼 수 있을까 <br>너 아니면 난 안 되는데 <br>]]></content><category term="슬리핑" label="슬리핑"/><category term="울다 웃다 울다" label="울다 웃다 울다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/끝없는잔향속에서우리는/푸른소매/</id><title>끝없는잔향속에서우리는 - 푸른소매 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:30:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:30:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%81%9D%EC%97%86%EB%8A%94%EC%9E%94%ED%96%A5%EC%86%8D%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94/%ED%91%B8%EB%A5%B8%EC%86%8C%EB%A7%A4/" title="끝없는잔향속에서우리는 - 푸른소매 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love is always ruthless to Me <br>Sometimes it hide it's shape <br>Then what can I do now <br>Love is always ruthless to Me <br>Sometimes it hide it's shape <br>Then what can I do now <br>And I know it's too much <br>cumbersome two both of Us <br>And I know it's too much <br>cumbersome two both of Us <br>Love Your greensleeves sleeves <br>Love Your greensleeves sleeves <br>Love Your greensleeves sleeves <br>Love Your greensleeves sleeves <br>Love is always ruthless to Me <br>Sometimes it hide it's shape <br>Then what can I do now <br>what can I do now <br>what can I do now <br>what can I do now <br>what can I do now <br>what can I do now <br>now <br>what can I do now <br>now now <br>what can I do now <br>now now now <br>what can I do now <br>now <br>what can I do now <br>now now <br>what can I do now <br>now <br>]]></content><category term="끝없는잔향속에서우리는" label="끝없는잔향속에서우리는"/><category term="푸른소매" label="푸른소매"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/끝없는잔향속에서우리는/5_41/</id><title>끝없는잔향속에서우리는 - 5:41 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:30:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:30:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%81%9D%EC%97%86%EB%8A%94%EC%9E%94%ED%96%A5%EC%86%8D%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94/5_41/" title="끝없는잔향속에서우리는 - 5:41 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sun came flying over head <br>Moon is walking over sky <br>Like it doesn't matter <br>cruelly but too simply <br>I can't let it die <br>and get out off my mind <br>I can't let it die <br>and get out off my mind <br>Sun came flying over head <br>Moon is walking over sky <br>Like it doesn't matter <br>cruelly but too simply <br>I can't let it die <br>and get out off my mind <br>I can't let it die <br>and get out off my mind <br>and get out off my mind <br>and get out off my mind <br>The pain grows inside me <br>The pain grows inside me <br>The pain kills Me completely <br>The pain kills Me completely <br>The pain grows inside me <br>The pain grows inside me <br>The pain kills Me completely <br>The pain kills Me completely <br>The pain grows inside me <br>The pain grows inside me <br>The pain kills Me completely <br>The pain kills Me completely <br>]]></content><category term="끝없는잔향속에서우리는" label="끝없는잔향속에서우리는"/><category term="5:41" label="5:41"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안현정/사랑인걸까/</id><title>안현정 - 사랑인걸까 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:30:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:30:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%ED%98%84%EC%A0%95/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B8%EA%B1%B8%EA%B9%8C/" title="안현정 - 사랑인걸까 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 손을 이렇게 <br>꼭 잡아준 건 <br>내 눈을 환하게 <br>웃게 해준 건 <br>그건 너야 낯설지만 <br>왠지 좋은 걸 <br>이런 마음 처음이었어 <br>함께한 시간들 <br>너와의 행복한 순간들 <br>문득문득 내 맘에 <br>떠올라 난 <br>사랑이 이런 걸까 <br>이런 느낌인 걸까 <br>어느새 나도 모르게 <br>네가 나를 점점 채워가 <br>사랑이 이런 걸까 <br>정말 사랑인 걸까 <br>저 끝까지 나와 <br>함께 해줄래 <br>내가 늘 웃을 수 있게 <br>너와의 순간들 <br>길고도 짧았던 시간들 <br>하루하루 내 맘은 <br>더 커져가 <br>사랑이 이런 걸까 <br>이런 느낌인 걸까 <br>어느새 나도 모르게 <br>네가 나를 점점 채워가 <br>사랑이 이런 걸까 <br>정말 사랑인 걸까 <br>저 끝까지 나와 <br>함께 해줄래 <br>내가 늘 웃을 수 있게 <br>매일 네 생각에 <br>가슴이 뛰는 걸 <br>오늘이 다 지나고 <br>내일이 다 지나도 <br>너뿐인 걸 <br>언제나 나의 곁을 <br>지켜준 너를 보며 <br>그 맘을 이제야 알게 됐어 <br>나도 몰랐던 내 맘 <br>조금씩 커져버린 <br>내 맘을 보여줄게 <br>저 끝까지 나와 <br>함께 해줄래 <br>너와 늘 웃을 수 있게 <br>]]></content><category term="안현정" label="안현정"/><category term="사랑인걸까" label="사랑인걸까"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하현곤_팩토리/별_지나고_태양/</id><title>하현곤_팩토리 - 별 지나고 태양 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:30:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:30:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%ED%98%84%EA%B3%A4_%ED%8C%A9%ED%86%A0%EB%A6%AC/%EB%B3%84_%EC%A7%80%EB%82%98%EA%B3%A0_%ED%83%9C%EC%96%91/" title="하현곤_팩토리 - 별 지나고 태양 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어디선가 힘 없이 <br>가녀린 소리 들려와 <br>어떤 표정도 느낄 수 없이 <br>조그마한 <br>멀어져 버린 별 빛에 <br>이제 그만 너를 놓아 <br>사라지는 거니 감추려는 듯이 <br>네 부서진 마음을 <br>내가 거둬 더는 <br>힘들지 않도록 할게 <br>너의 곁에 있을게 <br>애써왔던 널 위해 <br>쏟아지는 빛에 <br>또 눈물이 나는 게 <br>그만큼 아파서 <br>무너지는 마음을 <br>감출 수 없나 봐 <br>언제부터 어긋났었는지 <br>네 앞에 서있는 널 <br>되새기려 하지 않아도 돼 <br>똑바로 바라봐주길 <br>고통 없이 괴롭지 않게 이젠 <br>네 부서진 마음을 <br>내가 거둬 더는 <br>힘들지 않도록 <br>너의 곁을 떠나지 않을게 <br>빛 바랜 어제의 별은 그대로 <br>새로운 날의 태양이 비추면 <br>눈 부시게 또렷한 이곳에 <br>널 괴롭히던 별빛마저 <br>품에 안고 나와 빛낼 수 있게 <br>네 부서진 마음을 <br>내가 거둬 더는 <br>힘들지 않도록 <br>너의 곁에 서 있을게 <br>애써왔던 널 위해 <br>애써왔던 너에게 <br>다시 빛날 널 위해 <br>]]></content><category term="하현곤 팩토리" label="하현곤 팩토리"/><category term="별 지나고 태양" label="별 지나고 태양"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandun_Deshay/Summer_Getaway/</id><title>Brandun_Deshay - Summer Getaway - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:36:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:36:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandun_Deshay/Summer_Getaway/" title="Brandun_Deshay - Summer Getaway - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여보세요 <br>Ayyy, whaddown <br>자기야 <br>완전 보고싶어 <br>한국엔 언제와 <br>이번 자기 새로 나온곡 들었는데 완전 좋더라 <br>집 가서 문자해 <br><br>Got me a fix <br>Korean, she thick <br>Met on a trip <br>She's always wondering bout when <br>I'm bound to come in <br>She wanna commit <br>But she gon be missed <br>When I leave in fall <br>Pussy game, girl, it's A1 <br>You keep it cooler than naengmyeon <br>Treat you like one of my day ones <br>Didn't wanna have to say nothing <br>But youre probably the best <br>Looking at you like a God in the flesh <br>I be feigning, oh, I gotta confess <br>Plotted on you, now I got you undressed <br>Buck wild, then we do it again <br>Busan, maybe two of your friends <br>Too turnt when we at Itaewon <br>You know I love it, 너의 모든 점 <br>Why would you, why would you <br>Why would you front <br>No gas, girl, you bad as you want <br>You say, Ok, Ok <br>Is you ready <br>Yea, yea <br><br>You take my hand <br>We'll take a ride <br>Almost can taste those sherbet skies <br>I'll be looking forward to summer I'll be x4 <br>I'm on a wave <br>You wanna ride <br>Feels like I've waited all my life <br>I'll be looking forward to summer I'll be x4 <br><br>We gotta get away <br>We gotta get away <br>We got a getaway x4 <br><br>I just need one more dance <br>You show your feelings like On Demand <br>You wanting me to be your only man <br>Strolling through Seoul while we holding hands <br>'Know you're all mine, I don't wanna share <br>'Know you've got feelings you wanna share <br>Don't gotta wonder, I know it's there <br>Your love is rare like a Dragonair <br>Said, Are you ready for difficult times <br>Got all these differences and all this distance now <br>Miles and miles <br>Oh yea <br>But I'll hold you down <br>I feel it in my bones <br>I been waiting so long <br>'Got everything that I've been wanting so bad <br>Fuck what them people be talking bout <br>Girl, we just gon have to work it out <br>You know that I won't be here for too long <br>But you wait <br><br>You take my hand <br>We'll take a ride <br>Almost can taste those sherbet skies <br>I'll be looking forward to summer I'll be x4 <br>I'm on a wave <br>You wanna ride <br>Feels like I've waited all my life <br>I'll be looking forward to summer I'll be x4 <br><br>We gotta get away <br>We gotta get away <br>We got a getaway x4]]></content><category term="Brandun Deshay" label="Brandun Deshay"/><category term="Summer Getaway" label="Summer Getaway"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandun_Deshay/Celebrate/</id><title>Brandun_Deshay - Celebrate - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:36:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:36:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandun_Deshay/Celebrate/" title="Brandun_Deshay - Celebrate - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ha, ayyy whaddown <br>Good times man, good times <br>Let's get it <br><br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br><br>Uh, huh, here we go <br>Celebrate like you on a roll <br>Celebrate like the money comin' <br>Celebrate like you comin' home <br><br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br><br>Thoughts of failure leave me more than shook <br>Desperation, yeah I know the look <br>Searchin' my soul within' every nook <br>Talkin' faith, I coulda' wrote the book <br>In the kitchen like I know the cook <br>I swear it, but this is what arrogance is <br>Aware I'm a wiz <br>Stick to the shit til' I'm getting toupee'd like I'm wearin' a wig <br>Fuck is ya'll niggas fightin' for <br>Champion like the Final Four <br>These fans be actin' like they found the Lord <br>You fools, this ain't even my final form <br>Turnin' up on you on every song <br>You sleepin', my GLO game is very strong <br>Bringin' them hits like I'm Barry Bonds <br>I'm milkin' the game like a dairy farm <br><br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br><br>Uh, huh, here we go <br>Celebrate like you on a roll <br>Celebrate like the money comin' <br>Celebrate like you comin' home <br><br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a champ <br><br>Shh <br>Kindly get off of my nuts <br>You niggas annoying as fuck <br>Worrying about what I'm doing, about who I'm screwing <br>It's apparent your movement is not moving <br>On the day I collect all the Dragonballs <br>All I'mma wish is a nigga would <br>And drama ain't rare, we done had 'em all <br>So watch it, fore' get your dad involved <br>Takin' a flick and I'm taggin' your bitch on the rag <br>Oh, you mad cause you flaggin' my shit <br>In the the party, you know I be swaggin' my fit <br>You impressed well just try not to brag on my clique <br>All my brothers who I built the dynasty with <br>Your bullshit be makin' my sinuses itch <br>Each morning I'm up tryna' find me a lick <br>Been patient, I know <br>Man, this time, this is it <br><br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br><br>Uh, huh, here we go <br>Celebrate like you on a roll <br>Celebrate like the money comin' <br>Celebrate like you comin' home <br><br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br><br>Uh, got the crack to make the fiends wait <br>Started this year on a clean slate <br>So gimme a dinner with Kendall Jenner <br>I'm like God, I'm ready for my dream date <br>Fans fienin', I'mma let 'em wait <br>Doin' me, time to meditate <br>Been at the bottom, had to elevate <br>We all good, time to celebrate <br>I ain't fuck around like I'm celibate <br>Walk around feelin' hella' great <br>It's been 4 years since your last tape <br>Yeah I know nigga, I was hella' late <br>Be Deshay, be the man cause <br>He the real brand that the fans trust <br>So even if they try to ban us <br>They'll never ever slow my bands up <br>Let's celebrate <br><br>Even though niggas finna hate <br>Focus on your own dinner plate <br>Blessings coming not a minute late <br>I know I'm shinin' cause I see the shade <br>I'm just focusing on gettin' paid <br>Dreams of standin' on the center stage <br>Lord knows it done been a wait <br>Now it's time for me to celebrate <br><br>Celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a champion <br>We celebrate like a championship <br>Yeah, let's celebrate]]></content><category term="Brandun Deshay" label="Brandun Deshay"/><category term="Celebrate" label="Celebrate"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandun_Deshay/Its_GoldUn/</id><title>Brandun_Deshay - It`s GoldUn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:36:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:36:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandun_Deshay/Its_GoldUn/" title="Brandun_Deshay - It`s GoldUn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's golden, it's golden <br>It's golden, it's golden <br>It's goooldennn, nahh ahh <br>It's golden, it's golden <br><br>Playin' games at the park <br>Countin' stars after dark <br>Throwin' sand at the beach <br>Too much far from the streets <br>I'm gettin' high as a kite Nahh, na na na <br>Stayin' up all night Nahh, na na na <br>Spendin' time, havin' fun <br>You know what it is, just begun <br>It's golden <br><br>It's golden, it's golden <br>It's golden, it's golden <br>It's goooldennn, nahh ahh <br>It's golden, it's golden <br><br>Nahh, na na na <br>Nahh, na na na]]></content><category term="Brandun Deshay" label="Brandun Deshay"/><category term="It`s GoldUn" label="It`s GoldUn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandun_Deshay/Gomen_Nasai/</id><title>Brandun_Deshay - Gomen Nasai - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:36:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:36:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandun_Deshay/Gomen_Nasai/" title="Brandun_Deshay - Gomen Nasai - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was going postal <br>Dummy like a Slowbro <br>Cheating, that's a no no <br>Thinking I'd finesse her with the words though <br>Shawty hit me with the stunner like she fucking Stone Cold <br>Frequent flyer mileage, I had bitches out in Tokyo <br>She knew bout the hokey pokey at the karaoke though <br>Thought shit was sweet just like candy <br>Now you cannot stand <br>I played myself just like the rope a dope <br>You kept it real with me <br>How these hoes gon tempt me like this <br>I can't let you go <br>Girl, I'm sorry, I know I ain't shit <br>Fed up with me, the ending was sure to come <br>Now I'm stuck watching two turning into one <br>If there was problems, why you didn't mention em <br>Trees is your habit, now your ass crashing into one <br><br>Gomen nasai, oh <br>I didn't mean to make you cry, oh <br>I'm sorry 'bout the lies <br>Gomen nasai, oh <br>I didn't mean to make you cry, oh <br>I'm sorry 'bout the lies gomen ne <br><br>I'm feeling so sick, no NeYo, need a medic <br>Why all the good times we hold, oh, we forget it <br>I never ever was faithful, I let you tell it <br>You got me looking for love advising on reddit <br>And now I'm wishing we could reset it <br>You don't believe me now <br>You went from swimming in sheets to wanting to see me drown <br>I made mistakes once or twice, a hundred times <br>Even when I don't deserve it won't stop me from wanting mine <br>But ah <br>Is it too late now to say sorry <br>Cuz I don't wanna be another example of when love gets trampled on and end up on Maury <br>But everybody is sorry and everyone lies <br>And nobody miss it until the well runs dry <br>So Imma let you cheat, we'll call it even, yo <br>Though I hate the thought, I'd hate it even more to see ya go <br>Go <br><br>Gomen nasai, oh <br>I didn't mean to make you cry, oh <br>I'm sorry 'bout the lies <br>Gomen nasai, oh <br>I didn't mean to make you cry, oh <br>I'm sorry 'bout the lies gomen ne]]></content><category term="Brandun Deshay" label="Brandun Deshay"/><category term="Gomen Nasai" label="Gomen Nasai"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandun_Deshay/Truss_Mii/</id><title>Brandun_Deshay - Truss Mii - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:36:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:36:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandun_Deshay/Truss_Mii/" title="Brandun_Deshay - Truss Mii - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Aye <br>Trust me, cause' you know <br>Already know how I go <br>My team, getting green <br>You know <br>Woah, so many of us <br>Bad bitch from overseas <br>You know <br>Woah, so many of em' <br>Keep the shit lowkey because she know <br>She already know how I go <br>Young and hitting licks like the mob <br>Young and getting rich like the mob <br><br>Stacking up the sparka' on god <br>Young and hitting licks like the mob <br>Tell me what they're hitting, nobody <br>You know I can get it no problem <br>Young and hitting licks like the mob <br>Young and getting rich like the mob <br><br>Bottles on bottles, Aye <br>Pour it up, we finna ball <br>Stack it up, we spend it all <br>Blow some more, until its gone <br>Bottles on bottles, Aye <br>Pour it up, we finna ball <br>Stack it up, we spend it all <br>Blow some more, until its gone <br><br>Trust me, you know <br>Trust me, cause' you know <br>Trust me, cause' you know <br>Trust me, cause' you know <br><br>Young and hitting licks like the mob <br>Young and getting rich like the mob <br>Stacking up this money on god <br>Young and hitting licks like the mob <br>Tell me what they're hitting no problem <br>You know I can get it no problem <br>Young and hitting licks like the mob <br>Young and hitting licks like the mob <br><br>Aye, Trust me, cause you know <br>Already know how I go <br>My team getting green you know <br>Woah, so many of us <br>Bad bitch from overseas <br>Woah so many of em' <br>Keep the shit lowkey cause she know <br>She already know how I go <br>Woo]]></content><category term="Brandun Deshay" label="Brandun Deshay"/><category term="Truss Mii" label="Truss Mii"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandun_Deshay/Throwed/</id><title>Brandun_Deshay - Throwed - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:36:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:36:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brandun_Deshay/Throwed/" title="Brandun_Deshay - Throwed - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to goldUn Child 2 <br>Yeah, y'all make sure y'all turn this shit the fuck up <br>Know what I'm saying <br>All the way the fuck up <br><br>Back in Japan, I'm on track for them bands <br>And they in, passing hands like it's stacks in demand <br>Fuck a check, I need my cash in advance <br>Trying to stack a stack, I can't go back to my parents <br>Shake it fast, you make it clap but no hands <br>All this have me taking backers like, damn <br>But really in chance <br>Sitting there, wondering how the fuck she gon' fit all that ass in her pants <br>I got bleach in my hair, now I'm gon' Super Saiyan <br>And my hair match my chain <br>Don't do no Oscars, my niggs act insane <br>Blow up cartridge, game eject, the same effect as crack on the range <br>Take a look at my DMs <br>Hoes wanna fuck with me, bros wanna BM <br>Treat your wifey like a hoe <br>She out here with me, getting low and she told you she was playing Pokemon GO <br>Oh, these hoes out here tripping hard <br>Honestly, can't tell these chicks apart <br>Basic bitches think they fit the part <br>I only miss you when my dick is hard <br><br>Yeah, I moved to LA, making Cali classics <br>I done fucked a few hoes out in Calabasas <br>Got it sold, but I don't do no haberdashing <br>I pull up looking lit, but I'm glad you asked me <br><br>Yeah, I'm throwed we steady turning up <br>With my niggas we deep and we showing up <br>And this liquor, too we steady pouring up <br>And it's lit yeah, we get it going up <br>Yeah, I'm throwed we steady turning up <br>With my niggas we deep and we showing up <br>And this liquor, too we steady pouring up <br>And it's lit yeah, we get it going up <br>Yeah, I'm throwed we steady turning up <br>With my niggas we deep and we showing up <br>And this liquor, too we steady pouring up <br>And it's lit yeah, we get it going up <br>Yeah, I'm throwed we steady turning up <br>With my niggas we deep and we showing up <br>And this liquor, too we steady pouring up <br>And it's lit yeah, we get it going up]]></content><category term="Brandun Deshay" label="Brandun Deshay"/><category term="Throwed" label="Throwed"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/French_Montana/Lockjaw_Feat_Kodak_Black_Jeezy_Rick_Ross_DJ_Clue__DJ_Khaled_Remix/</id><title>French_Montana - Lockjaw (Feat. Kodak Black, Jeezy, Rick Ross, DJ Clue &amp; DJ Khaled) (Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:36:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:36:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/French_Montana/Lockjaw_Feat_Kodak_Black_Jeezy_Rick_Ross_DJ_Clue__DJ_Khaled_Remix/" title="French_Montana - Lockjaw (Feat. Kodak Black, Jeezy, Rick Ross, DJ Clue &amp; DJ Khaled) (Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My nigga on the road <br>You never told me, Montana <br><br>It be hard to watch the cash when the bands keep droppin' <br>Got the big 40 on me so my pants keep fallin' <br>It be hard to understand me cause my jaw keep lockin' <br>I ain't even tryna talk cause my jaw keep lockin' <br>She ain't tryna be a freak but them bands keep poppin' <br>Still caught up in the streets and the feds still knockin' <br>It be hard to understand me my jaw keep lockin' <br>It be hard to understand me cause my jaw keep lockin' <br>Bite down, bite down <br>It'd be hard to understand me cause my jaw keep lockin' <br>Bite down, bite down <br>It'd be hard to understand me cause my jaw keep lockin' <br><br>Slept on a bunk for 20 months for selling jacks to junk <br>Fuck in the trunk or the dunk, I'm in court playing Tunk <br>Troll blows and truck stops, bow loaded, bow walk <br>This the home of Coca Cola we call it the trap spot <br>I'm tryna stay sucker free, I ain't fuckin' with blow pops <br>I keep runnin' like South, fear the feds, not patrol cops <br>Had to shower in my boots, I had sleep in my shoes <br>I had a snitch in the trunk like he Rae Carruth <br>My ex chick drove a Acura, my plug drove a Maxima <br>Took the gold off my teeth and put the gold in my Axima <br>My blow white like my Audemar, Lamar got the super jar <br>And her jaws keep locking cause she only suck superstars <br>GUCCI <br><br>It be hard to watch the cash when the bands keep droppin' <br>Got the big 40 on me so my pants keep fallin' <br>It be hard to understand me cause my jaw keep lockin' <br>I ain't even tryna talk cause my jaw keep lockin' <br>She ain't tryna be a freak but them bands keep poppin' <br>Still caught up in the streets and the feds still knockin' <br>It be hard to understand me my jaw keep lockin' <br>It be hard to understand me cause my jaw keep lockin' <br>Bite down, bite down <br>It'd be hard to understand me cause my jaw keep lockin' <br>Bite down, bite down <br>It'd be hard to understand me cause my jaw keep lockin' <br><br>Slide in the Cutlass and you know I paint it candy <br>Then I pulled up in a bucket but I used to want to a Hemi <br>And I'm pouring up the round then I'm sippin on Remy <br>I ain't fuckin with that white shit, I'm throwed off Henny <br>Pull up to the back, black zac, chief rockin' <br>And the Feds keep lurkin' cause the boys keep talkin' <br>Ritz Carlton, ran off on the plug about forty times <br>Forty niggas strapped, we the 49ers <br>Bite downnnn, Karlton Hines <br>Got two twin bitches doing 69 <br>Jump off to the mula and you know that <br>50 chains on, diamonds flashing like Kodak <br>I remember toting 38, now I got a semi <br>Could've been had a baby K but I wasn't ready <br>Shawty say she like my Larry Pack, thought I went to Kelly <br>Nah baby I ain't want no Wap, I just want the Fetty <br><br>It be hard to watch the cash when the bands keep droppin' <br>Got the big 40 on me so my pants keep fallin' <br>It be hard to understand me cause my jaw keep lockin' <br>I ain't even tryna talk cause my jaw keep lockin' <br>She ain't tryna be a freak but them bands keep poppin' <br>Still caught up in the streets and the feds still knockin' <br>It be hard to understand me my jaw keep lockin' <br>It be hard to understand me cause my jaw keep lockin' <br>Bite down, bite down <br>It'd be hard to understand me cause my jaw keep lockin' <br>Bite down, bite down <br>It'd be hard to understand me cause my jaw keep lockin' <br><br>Ay, ay ay <br>Ay, ay ay ay <br>Skrr, ay, ay ay ay <br>Ay, ay ay <br>Bite down, bite down <br>It be hard to understand me cause my jaw keep lockin' <br>Bite down, bite down <br>It be hard to understand me cause my jaw keep lockin' <br>Ay, ay ay ay]]></content><category term="French Montana" label="French Montana"/><category term="Lockjaw (Feat. Kodak Black, Jeezy, Rick Ross, DJ Clue &amp; DJ Khaled) (Remix)" label="Lockjaw (Feat. Kodak Black, Jeezy, Rick Ross, DJ Clue &amp; DJ Khaled) (Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matthew__The_Atlas/Cant_You_See_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>Matthew__The_Atlas - Can`t You See (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:36:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:36:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matthew__The_Atlas/Cant_You_See_Acoustic_Ver/" title="Matthew__The_Atlas - Can`t You See (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[can't you see <br>that the light was always on you <br>and I won't let them put it out <br>and you should know <br>there's a lot to live for <br>and I won't let you do it alone <br><br>cause I'm on your side <br>if you need me there <br>and you're on my mind <br>all the time <br><br>can't you see <br>there's some weights you don't have to burden <br>even if you can't seem to lay them down <br><br>and you should know <br>there's a world that spins around you <br>and I won't let them run you down <br><br>cause I'm on your side <br>if you need me there <br>and you're on my mind <br>all the time <br><br>you should know <br>you should know <br>I was always by your side <br>and you're always on my mind <br>and I'm always by your side <br>if you need me there <br>if you need me there]]></content><category term="Matthew &amp; The Atlas" label="Matthew &amp; The Atlas"/><category term="Can`t You See (Acoustic Ver.)" label="Can`t You See (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Mvula/Ready_Or_Not_Feat_Jammz_Rude_Kid_Remix/</id><title>Laura_Mvula - Ready Or Not (Feat. Jammz) (Rude Kid Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:37:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:37:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Mvula/Ready_Or_Not_Feat_Jammz_Rude_Kid_Remix/" title="Laura_Mvula - Ready Or Not (Feat. Jammz) (Rude Kid Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ready or not, here I come <br>You can't hide, you can't hide <br>Ready or not, here I come <br>You can't hide, you can't hide <br><br>No warnings, ready or not <br>I'm coming to put a leg in your spot <br>I don't care if he said he's on top <br>I'm so far ahead that I'm two steps ahead of your boss <br>And when I land, it's better you're not <br>The one to try and ask me dead it or not <br>I won't let none of them talks run <br>I'm old school like needles with a penny on top <br>This one's one of them veteran songs <br>You know, the sick ones with the veterans on, cuh <br>I come like Tanitas with a dead battery <br>I don't care if you're heavy or not <br>Yeah, it's been a long time coming, I did send the memo <br>So, wait, have you read it or what <br>I'm the type to set it all off <br>Like Westwood's show when they're letting off bombs <br>So, pattern up quick <br>Think that you're man enough Back it up, kid <br>Man's had enough, yet I wasn't adding up quick <br>You're an amateur, better start packing up kit <br>When I bad 'em up, man have to wrap it up quick <br>Different caliber, man are not thick <br>You're a janitor and I'm a manager, prick <br>When it all falls down, I'll still keep my cool <br>Like an avalanche kick <br><br>Ready or not, here I come <br>You can't hide, you can't hide <br>Ready or not, here I come <br>You can't hide, you can't hide <br><br>No warnings, ready or not <br>I'm too far ahead in this game <br>I don't care if they say I'm insane, but <br>Just mind your business, tell your don stay in his lane <br>I don't care what you say in his name <br>He's just mad cause no one's saying his name <br>But it's cool, if he takes his eye off the ball <br>I'll be the next breh in his place <br>Today's one of them relevant days <br>When I pree and then start to make relevant plays <br>So keep talking like your ting's live <br>You'll soon be six feet where the skeletons lay <br>Man's hungry, I could have an elephant, mate <br>No joke ting, so it's kinda better you pray <br>Cause if I start killing MCs' dreams <br>It ain't one of them tings that medicine saves <br><br>Gonna find you <br>Ready or not <br>Gonna find you <br>Ready or not <br>Ready or not]]></content><category term="Laura Mvula" label="Laura Mvula"/><category term="Ready Or Not (Feat. Jammz) (Rude Kid Remix)" label="Ready Or Not (Feat. Jammz) (Rude Kid Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Fox_On_The_Run_Single_Ver/</id><title>Sweet - Fox On The Run (Single Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:37:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:37:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sweet/Fox_On_The_Run_Single_Ver/" title="Sweet - Fox On The Run (Single Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't wanna know your name <br>'Cause you don't look the same <br>The way you did before <br>Okay, you think you got a pretty face <br>But the rest of you is out of place <br>You looked alright before <br><br>Fox on the run <br>You scream and everybody comes a running <br>Take a run and hide yourself away <br>Foxy on the run <br>F foxy <br>Fox on the run <br>And hide away <br><br>You you talk about just every band <br>But the names you drop are second hand second hand <br>I've heard it all before <br>I don't wanna know your name <br>'Cause you don't look the same <br>The way you did before <br><br>Fox on the run <br>You scream and everybody comes a running <br>Take a run and hide yourself away <br>Foxy on the run <br>F foxy <br>Fox on the run <br>And hide away]]></content><category term="Sweet" label="Sweet"/><category term="Fox On The Run (Single Ver.)" label="Fox On The Run (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ricky_Martin/Vente_Pa_Ca_Feat_Delta_Goodrem/</id><title>Ricky_Martin - Vente Pa` Ca (Feat. Delta Goodrem) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:38:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:38:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ricky_Martin/Vente_Pa_Ca_Feat_Delta_Goodrem/" title="Ricky_Martin - Vente Pa` Ca (Feat. Delta Goodrem) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ricky Martin: <br>Vente cuento de una vez <br>Tu descanso esta en la cama de mis pies <br>Vente cuento un dos tres <br>Mis pasitos son descalzos sin estres <br><br>Dime si hay <br>Otro lugar para dejar <br>Mi corazon mi corazon <br>Hay tienes razon <br>¿Mejor, por que no <br>Nos vamos los dos <br><br>Si tu quieres nos ba?amos, si tu quieres nos soplamos, pa' secarnos lo mojado <br>Si tu boca quiere beso y tu cuerpo quiere de eso, arreglamos <br>Si tu quieres un atajo y lo quieres por abajo, yo te llevo bien callado <br>Vente pa'ca, vente pa'ca, vente pa'ca <br><br>Enamorados, que calor <br>Nos comimos boca a boca en el sillon <br>Fue por hambre, fue por sed <br>Me bebiste a fondo blanco con tu piel <br><br>Dime si hay <br>Otro lugar para dejar <br>Mi corazon mi corazon <br>Hay tienes razon <br>¿Mejor, por que no <br>Nos vamos los dos <br><br>Si tu quieres nos ba?amos, si tu quieres nos soplamos, pa' secarnos lo mojado <br>Si tu boca quiere beso y tu cuerpo quiere de eso, arreglamos <br>Si tu quieres un atajo y lo quieres por abajo, yo te llevo bien callado <br>Vente pa'ca, vente pa'ca, vente pa'ca <br><br>Maluma: <br>All right, too right baby <br>Pretty boy, dirty boy, baby <br>Cuando baila me seduce <br>Cuando le apagan las luces <br>Y asi luce yo se lo hago otra vez otra vez <br>Llevo tanto tiempo mirando reaccionar <br>Dime que estas esperando baby, no hay demora <br>Pegate a mi, que rico a mi, no dejes que pasen las horas <br>Tu amor me arrebata, tu sonrisa me atrapa <br>Quiero tenerte siempre y no dejarte sola <br>Esta historia no se acaba <br>Ven vamos pa' mi cama <br>Esta noche tu te enamoras <br>Dime de una vez <br>Si es que al lado tuyo yo estare <br>Todo lo que pidas te dare <br>Esta noche tu te enamoras <br><br>Ricky Martin: <br>Si tu quieres nos ba?amos, si tu quieres nos soplamos, pa' secarnos lo mojado <br>Si tu boca quiere beso y tu cuerpo quiere de eso, arreglamos <br>Si tu quieres un atajo y lo quieres por abajo yo te llevo bien callado <br>Vente pa'ca, vente pa'ca, vente pa'ca <br><br>Vente pa'ca, vente pa'ca, vente pa'ca]]></content><category term="Ricky Martin" label="Ricky Martin"/><category term="Vente Pa` Ca (Feat. Delta Goodrem)" label="Vente Pa` Ca (Feat. Delta Goodrem)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Regimen/Ramlar/</id><title>Regimen - Ramlar - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:38:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:38:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Regimen/Ramlar/" title="Regimen - Ramlar - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Det finns en gata dar alla kan mitt namn o jag ramlar daliga gatan fram <br>O ja va full o ja va dum o ja ramla pa allt <br>o ja foll for nan pa en fest nanstans <br><br>For det skulle ju va dans, dans, dans <br>det ar en lang vag ner <br>o ja skulle aldrig ramla mer <br>O det ar lang vag ner <br>och du skulle aldrig ramla mer <br>For manga ramlande flickor som ramla forbi <br>for manga ramlande sangar att ramla i <br>Ooh oh ooh <br>Manniskor ramlar runt pa stan <br>manniskor ramlar hart precis som du <br>ooh o jaaahhaaa <br>Det ar en lang vag ner <br>och jag skulle aldrig ramla mer <br>och det ar en lang vag ner <br>och du skulle aldrig ramla mer <br>O ja ramlade in pa nat diskotek <br>sen ramla ja ut sa vitt ja vet <br>o ja ramla omkull o tog mig upp osen <br>ramla jag omkull igen och <br>ja ramla in i en taxi mr visa den maximala hastigheten vart du vill safort du kan <br>vart du vill safort du kan <br>vart du vill safort du kan <br>Lang vag ner och jag skulle aldrig ramla mer <br>det ar en lang vag ner <br>och du skulle aldrig ramla mer <br>Jag vill vart du vill for ja ramlar aldrig hit igen <br>Ohhhoo, igen, aaah]]></content><category term="Regimen" label="Regimen"/><category term="Ramlar" label="Ramlar"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/다원/하얗게/</id><title>다원 - 하얗게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:38:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:38:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EC%9B%90/%ED%95%98%EC%96%97%EA%B2%8C/" title="다원 - 하얗게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지금 마주 잡은 두손 <br>하얀 눈꽃 속에 우리 <br>아직도 잊지 못하는 <br>내 겨울 이야기 <br>그대 사랑한단 <br>말을 못해 <br>바보처럼 그대 곁에 <br>맴돌다 영화속 <br>달콤한 첫키스와 <br>첫 눈이 내려요 <br>하얗게 내려 내 맘을 <br>덮은 흰 눈이 <br>때로는 쓰고 달콤한 <br>나만의 세상인데 <br>눈처럼 맑은 <br>천사와 같은 내사랑 <br>자존심 다 버릴게요 <br>오직 그대만 <br>그대 하나만 <br>사랑해 영원히 <br>하얀 눈꽃속에 연인 <br>거리엔 울려퍼진 선율 <br>우리의 사랑 축복해 <br>줄날이 오겠죠 <br>아직 사랑하기 서툴러도 <br>이젠 할 수 있을꺼라 생각해 <br>반전과 반전이 거듭되는 <br>겨울얘기니까요 <br>하얗게 내려 <br>내 맘을 덮은 흰 눈이 <br>때로는 쓰고 <br>달콤한 나만의 세상인데 <br>눈처럼 맑은 <br>천사와 같은 내사랑 <br>자존심 다 버릴게요 <br>오직 그대만 <br>그대 하나만 <br>사랑해 영원히 <br>때로는 그대얘길 <br>놓친다해도 <br>사랑한다고 사랑한다고 <br>날 깨워주세요 <br>하얗게 내려 <br>내 맘을 덮은 흰 눈이 <br>때로는 쓰고 <br>달콤한 나만의 세상인데 <br>눈처럼 맑은 천사와 <br>같은 내사랑 <br>자존심 다 버릴게요 <br>오직 그대만 <br>그대 하나만 <br>사랑해 영원히 <br>]]></content><category term="다원" label="다원"/><category term="하얗게" label="하얗게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Psychic_TV/Ov_Power/</id><title>Psychic_TV - Ov Power - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:39:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:39:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Psychic_TV/Ov_Power/" title="Psychic_TV - Ov Power - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ov power, Ov power <br>Ov power, Ov power <br>Dog power Dog power <br>Be relased <br>Seeds released <br>The secret in a cell <br>The freedom of its spell <br>Dog trainer <br>Ov rainer <br>Can you see the dog <br>Can you feed the fog <br>My son the dog <br>My sun the dog <br>Waiting to turn the pattern <br>Ov power, Ov power <br>In a cell <br>Cast your spell <br>Stops and turns <br>Red rope burns <br>No one hears <br>Is no fear <br>Let him in <br>They both begin <br>They cast their charms <br>A call to arms <br>Ov power Ov power <br><br>That very special power <br>That extra special power <br>The almighty power <br>The dog power <br>The ov power <br>My son the dog <br>My sun the dog <br>Ov power Ov power <br>Ov power Ov power]]></content><category term="Psychic TV" label="Psychic TV"/><category term="Ov Power" label="Ov Power"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Psychic_TV/Stolen_Kisses/</id><title>Psychic_TV - Stolen Kisses - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:39:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:39:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Psychic_TV/Stolen_Kisses/" title="Psychic_TV - Stolen Kisses - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Enter the tiny room, watched by scepters <br>Hope and happiness playing trumpets, dog swimming in heavy water <br>For the glory of gloom, dark songs on sunlight flower <br>Enclosed in your skin <br>All perfection spent in your arms <br><br>Stolen kisses fa fa fa fa fa <br><br>In retrospect this beauty is, What you see <br>The second part, the move, Is me <br>Onwards and upwards <br>The prize is the game to come <br>And there's nothing to miss <br>In the laughter and tears of love <br>There always are difficult mods <br>Yet sensual bonds of obsession]]></content><category term="Psychic TV" label="Psychic TV"/><category term="Stolen Kisses" label="Stolen Kisses"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Psychic_TV/Terminus/</id><title>Psychic_TV - Terminus - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:39:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:39:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Psychic_TV/Terminus/" title="Psychic_TV - Terminus - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Quiet and hooded, his eyes stared out, small hands <br>Make patterns on the window Body shifting on wood <br>Dog outside the door, flickering memories as trains <br>Maneuver in the old men's eyes Forever part of a sleep <br>Ing world, waiting for him to come Lost dreams of <br>Childhood forgotten like hope These lives are grey <br>Stones made for cemeteries, this time the victim is <br>Desired, like misery He stepped down from the train <br>Dust on road and clothes, across the way a boy was <br>Grinning, hard on obvious in torn grey trousers <br>Inherited from an earlier victim of the white horse <br>Filing past the flowers and signs full of dreams <br>Light of night filtering where woof tiles slipped <br>Into that darkness Each ritual makes demand, a hope <br>Less coil of expensive death affirming our exeistence <br>The direction never changes, never falters Along <br>Those derelict lines lines to journey's end Small hands <br>Smear juice on flesh squeezing tight crinkling of <br>Skin against worn eyes There is no need of light <br>Somewhere, in the secret cathedral, small movements <br>The whole area covered in sheets of snow, pitted by <br>Huts He had no expectations, there was no reason <br>Breathing short as the text on the wall Whenever the <br>Dog moved, the night trembled, shimmering like water <br>Moved by leaves in a forest Marks of cold spray in <br>The dust, as in the future faded by choice Our appetite <br>For miracles is not enough Here, only animals <br>Remain, immaculate, seduced by pain Ending fear into <br>Specters of welcome Floor stained with patients The <br>Moment of least action He moved like a rat in rubble <br>Toward the sheets of snow, awake and empty, like an <br>Old house, the place where all dreams meet He was <br>Grinning before he jumped <br><br>Las night the boy came Open arms Black hair <br>Strong Empty pale face A volunteer Unsure of why <br>He came Seduced by pain A faded painting Waiting <br>For release, he blinked, looked up at the ceiling <br>Let out a tiny gasp praying for oblivion <br><br>No engines anymoore The machine engine's stopped No <br>Ghosts of death playing in the grass Just simple, as <br>You would expect No physical core No smiles of love <br>From pitted carriages Just an empty town Derelict <br>No way to identify Sound playing across skin like <br>Fingers Just as ampty as flesh What do you want <br>Nothing in particular No reason at all Just a noise <br>Of dreams at the door Just as before Did you see <br>That <br><br>This is the place where all roads meet, the place <br>Where all is the secret The Place where time stands <br>Still in the comfort of night and love becomes will <br>In the presence of light I never want to leave I <br>Never want to leave I never want to leave]]></content><category term="Psychic TV" label="Psychic TV"/><category term="Terminus" label="Terminus"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Psychic_TV/Just_Drifting/</id><title>Psychic_TV - Just Drifting - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:39:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:39:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Psychic_TV/Just_Drifting/" title="Psychic_TV - Just Drifting - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, just drifting <br>In this simple world <br>Like a country stream <br>Asleep to discussion <br>the numbness of content <br>I see you smile drifting <br>Like a country stream <br>My little girl <br>Precious and pure <br>As I fall back <br>Into softness and sleep <br>You Caresse me with simple love <br>You possess me with <br>Simple love <br><br>A Caresse is just a touch <br>And you touched my heart, and now that we're together <br>You and I will never part <br><br>You Caresse me with simple love <br>You possess me with simple love <br>Place becomes time <br>Space becomes mine <br>And all ways <br>Like this robe <br>Green like a country dream <br>You surround me, and cover me <br>Protect me and Caresse me <br>With that special simple love <br><br>Sometimes, just drifting <br>Like a country stream <br>Precious and pure <br>I see you smile <br>Asleep to discussion <br>Of this simple word <br>The numbness of content <br>Drifting <br>Like a country scene <br>As I fall back <br>Into softness and sleep <br>You possess me with <br>Simple love <br>You Caresse me with simple love <br>You possess me with simple love <br>Space becomes time <br>Place becomes mind <br>And all ways <br>Like this rose <br>Seen like a country stream <br>You surround me <br>And comfort me <br>Protect me <br>And Caresse me <br>With that special simple love]]></content><category term="Psychic TV" label="Psychic TV"/><category term="Just Drifting" label="Just Drifting"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/Off_Da_Top_3am/</id><title>Yo_Gotti - Off Da Top (3am) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:39:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:39:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/Off_Da_Top_3am/" title="Yo_Gotti - Off Da Top (3am) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's 3am West Coast time nigga <br>We at Fat Burger <br>Hood nigga rich shit gourmet burgers <br>Know what I'm talkin' 'bout <br><br>She pussy poppin, pocket watchin', they call her a thot <br>Bad credit, cash it out, fresh up off the lot <br>No back and forth, yippin', yappin', niggas gettin' shot <br>10 million, 20 acres, that's the new spot <br>Flooded out my crib and told my dealer you the illest <br>Renegotiate my contract, told my label I ain'tt feel it <br>Fell out with my partner, he mixed friendship with our business <br>Broke up with my bitch 'cause she was too much in her feelings <br>I may fuck her friend, fuck it, I may fuck her friend <br>Between me and you, I always wanted to fuck her friend <br>If I kill a hater, Lord you gotta forgive my sins <br>That's one fuck nigga you ain't gotta worry about again <br>I'm forever thuggin', I ain't never changed <br>In plain colors but forever bangin' <br>Blowin' money but I'm maintainin' <br>Blowin' money but I'm maintainin' <br>I got a gamblin' problem but money can't really solve it <br>Tryna help all the real niggas, hate to see a nigga starvin' <br>Hate to see nigga robbin' they own people, shit, that's loyal <br>Bitch tryna give me the pussy for a Birkin bag, I can't afford you <br>I grew listenin' to 2pac and that Biggie, Jay Z and that Nas <br>No gimmick rappers, these niggas had bars <br>Back when record labels turnin' real niggas into stars <br>Sendin' niggas to Mars, nowadays the game done got hard <br>You get shot that make you hot <br>But where I'm from that make you start <br>Before I be a pussy, I'd rather rapper had the balls <br>I throw me some guns, get myself a charge <br>Never see me do that, I came too far to look back <br>I did too much to get help, 20 mil in one year <br>100 grand in one night, 50k on one flight <br>I've been trappin' my whole life <br>Ain't no secret, I be thuggin', ain't no secret, I be hustlin' <br>Pickin' loyalty over money, money orders to my homies <br>Groupie bitches be all on me, leave your phones at the door <br>You won't put me on no blog, once I fuck, you gotta go <br><br>3am ain't nothin' open but IHOP <br>And a bitch legs, and my trap spot <br>I said 3am, I'm trappin' at the IHOP <br>And I'm connected to the plug like a hotspot <br><br>I'm a grower, we don't do droughts <br>Birds in the sky, we call them iClouds <br>You know the birds fly down south <br>I took your bitch to eat at Mr Chow's <br>I met the plug at Benihanahs <br>On hibachi grills, eatin' rice and talkin' numbers <br>I don't do no middle men and I don't trust no runners <br>I'ma pay on time and I won't never take you under <br>I'm an OG dope boy <br>I ain't nothin' like these youngins <br>I don't take the dope I'm sellin' <br>I won't ever do no tellin' <br>Overnight my pack yeah, we call that FedEx <br>I ship in the 18 wheeler and I ain't talkin' UPS]]></content><category term="Yo Gotti" label="Yo Gotti"/><category term="Off Da Top (3am)" label="Off Da Top (3am)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/Free_Lunch_Feat_Blac_Youngsta/</id><title>Yo_Gotti - Free Lunch (Feat. Blac Youngsta) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:39:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:39:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/Free_Lunch_Feat_Blac_Youngsta/" title="Yo_Gotti - Free Lunch (Feat. Blac Youngsta) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I used to dream about a 9 when I had 4 in the spliff <br>When you fucked up, don't want no niggas around, is you and your bitch <br>Used to live in public housin', get free lunch at the school <br>Had to jump 'fore they came out, had them bring the strap to the school <br>I was trappin' in school, I was actin' a fool <br>I was a freshman and I was the freshest nigga in school, yeah yeah <br><br>Leavin' the school I was fuckin' the seniors <br>I got caught with the strap and sent to juvinial detention yeah yeah <br>Never liked police, shootin' dice under bleachers <br>Free period, get money, don't mind PE class <br>No books in the book bag, took math, I need to add <br>I was gon' get a bag <br>Came to school, filled the lot up <br>Play with me and get shot up <br>Five hundred for the Coogi sweater <br>Three fifty for the Prada's <br>Teacher told me I could be anythin' I wanna be <br>OG told me you gotta love yourself and don't love the streets <br><br>I used to dream about a 9 when I had 4 in the spliff <br>When you fucked up, don't want no niggas around, is you and your bitch <br>Used to live in public housin', get free lunch at the school <br>Had to jump 'fore they came out, had them bring the strap to the school <br>I was trappin' in school, I was actin' a fool <br>I was a freshman and I was the freshest nigga in school, yeah yeah <br>I was trappin' in school, I was actin' a fool <br>I was a freshman and I was the freshest nigga in school, yeah yeah <br><br>Last nigga played with me in school, gave him the street blues <br>Nigga tried to jump me in school so I went and got my tools <br>Yeah, I was fresh in school <br>I been broke all my life, I got somethin' to prove hoe <br>I shot my teacher hoe bitch, I took recess hoe bitch <br>You better Google me and do your research hoe <br>I fucked plenty bitches under the bleachers hoe <br>I cheat on my bitch 'cause I don't need you hoe <br>When I skip school, Grandma whoop my ass <br>I give my lil' brother my last <br>Made the best out of what we had <br>Tried my best to make it last <br>It was hard on me and my brothers <br>I ain't never ever see my dad <br>All my life I had to struggle <br>That's why I talk shit and show my ass <br><br>I used to dream about a 9 when I had 4 in the spliff <br>When you fucked up, don't want no niggas around, is you and your bitch <br>Used to live in public housin', get free lunch at the school <br>Had to jump 'fore they came out, had them bring the strap to the school <br>I was trappin' in school, I was actin' a fool <br>I was a freshman and I was the freshest nigga in school, yeah yeah]]></content><category term="Yo Gotti" label="Yo Gotti"/><category term="Free Lunch (Feat. Blac Youngsta)" label="Free Lunch (Feat. Blac Youngsta)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/Castro_Feat_Kanye_West_Big_Sean_Quavo__2_Chainz/</id><title>Yo_Gotti - Castro (Feat. Kanye West, Big Sean, Quavo &amp; 2 Chainz) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:39:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:39:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/Castro_Feat_Kanye_West_Big_Sean_Quavo__2_Chainz/" title="Yo_Gotti - Castro (Feat. Kanye West, Big Sean, Quavo &amp; 2 Chainz) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah Castro <br>Whoa whoa whoa yeah <br>Cubans on me <br>like I'm Castro yeah <br>Bitches like I'm Castro yah <br>Kickin' bitches <br>like I'm Castro whoa <br>Cuban cigar nigga <br>Spanish chick JLo <br>Dope money Pablo <br>The double cross <br>you up eyeball <br>Castro Castro Castro <br>Cubans on me <br>like I'm Castro <br>Hit your bitch <br>with a backstroke <br>Spanish bitch JLo <br>Dope money Pablo <br>Astronaut take off <br>John Travolta face off <br>In the kitchen <br>have a bake off <br>She gon' snort her <br>whole damn face off <br>Cubans on me <br>like I'm Castro <br>Hit your bitch <br>with a backstroke <br>Spanish bitch JLo <br>Dope money Pablo <br>Astronaut take off <br>John Travolta face off <br>In the kitchen <br>have a bake off <br>She gon' snort her <br>whole damn face off <br>EA Sports <br>I'm in the Playoffs <br>in the game <br>I'm in Saks goin' AWOL <br>I'm at Neimans goin' AWOL <br>Hit your bitch in the Aloft <br>Head cool <br>but the pussy wack <br>Wanna unfuck her <br>get her pussy back <br>Cuban on your boy <br>I'm Castro <br>Hit your bitch <br>with a backstroke <br>Medellin Pablo <br>Money bags Wells Fargo <br>Call my driver <br>where the car go <br>100 thousand in my cargo <br>I get dope by the cargo <br>I got whips no car note <br>I got whips no slave <br>All my cribs got maids <br>All my cribs like a maze <br>Shit so big they amazed <br>Still thuggin' they amazed <br>Put me on a track with 'Ye <br>In the kitchen rocking 'Ye's <br>In the trenches with the Js <br>Feds listenin' <br>we don't do the phone <br>They record everythin' we say <br>Cubans on me <br>like I'm Castro <br>Hit your bitch <br>with a backstroke <br>Spanish bitch JLo <br>Dope money Pablo <br>Astronaut take off <br>John Travolta face off <br>In the kitchen <br>have a bake off <br>She gon' snort her <br>whole damn face off <br>Cubans on me <br>like I'm Castro <br>Hit your bitch <br>with a backstroke <br>Spanish bitch JLo <br>Dope money Pablo <br>Astronaut take off <br>John Travolta face off <br>In the kitchen <br>have a bake off <br>She gon' snort her <br>whole damn face off <br>Quavo Huncho <br>My life like Pablo <br>Cuban hoes fall in love <br>with a nigga <br>They'll treat me like Fabio <br>Off white like shell toes <br>Stick to the money velcro <br>Standin' on the top ropes <br>Then I jump down <br>hit you with the elbow <br>Why do the birds <br>need a plane if they can fly <br>I be standin' in the field <br>with the fire <br>So many onions in the trap <br>make me cry <br>My styrofoam got more <br>oil than Dubai <br>Ridin' round with extendo <br>Ridin' round with extendo <br>Never never serve ya kinfolk <br>Never never serve ya kinfolk <br>Niggas shootin' out the window <br>Niggas shootin' at your window <br>Yeah you better <br>keep your head low <br>Feds watchin' <br>better lay low <br>Cubans on me <br>like I'm Castro <br>Hit your bitch <br>with a backstroke <br>Spanish bitch JLo <br>Dope money Pablo <br>Astronaut take off <br>John Travolta face off <br>In the kitchen <br>have a bake off <br>She gon' snort her <br>whole damn face off <br>Anti lame nigga <br>Take your girl like a pain killer <br>Just saw a picture of your <br>first baby mama <br>Look like a train hit her <br>Can't finesse me <br>I'm the finest <br>AKA it's your Highness <br>I don't know <br>if she got a snort habit <br>Or the bitch got sinus <br>Pyrex tried to sign us <br>Bakin' soda tryna sign us <br>Got a red stove and a gold fork <br>Shit lookin' like the 9ers <br>Told shawty you a minus <br>And I say it out of kindness <br>Cuban links change the climate <br>Dick tall <br>she can climb it <br>Sold so many damn bags <br>I coulda went diamond <br>Watch wristband diamond <br>On my neck look diamond <br>Simon says nigga <br>stop takin' my shit <br>Nigga start rhymin' <br>4 rings like an Audi <br>Hotel suite cloudy <br>Cubans on me <br>like I'm Castro <br>Hit your bitch <br>with a backstroke <br>Spanish bitch JLo <br>Dope money Pablo <br>Astronaut take off <br>John Travolta face off <br>In the kitchen <br>have a bake off <br>She gon' snort her <br>whole damn face off <br>]]></content><category term="Yo Gotti" label="Yo Gotti"/><category term="Castro (Feat. Kanye West, Big Sean, Quavo &amp; 2 Chainz)" label="Castro (Feat. Kanye West, Big Sean, Quavo &amp; 2 Chainz)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/I_Remember_Feat_DJ_Khaled/</id><title>Yo_Gotti - I Remember (Feat. DJ Khaled) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:40:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:40:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/I_Remember_Feat_DJ_Khaled/" title="Yo_Gotti - I Remember (Feat. DJ Khaled) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I remember, see I remember like yesterday <br>Vividly, everythin' I went through <br><br>I remember long nights, days <br>Been fucked up on steppin' my ice game <br>Openin' that door stages then the lights came <br>Went to Mexico, met a plug, then my life changed <br>And I was on vacation <br>Never was with waitin' <br>Always been impatient <br>Always 'bout the money <br>Never been with hatin' <br>Believe in loyalty, I had my niggas fight they cases <br>Don't believe in hope, I tell 'em hold they head <br>I tell 'em stack they bread <br>I tell 'em pipe it down <br>Before you get up in the feds, homie talkin' loud <br>Between you, I think you scared <br>'Cause if you really was the problem, he'll end up dead <br>And that's some real shit <br>I don't talk about niggas 'cause it's a waste of time <br>And when I talk to my young'ns, I tell 'em go and grind <br>And when I talk to the plug, I tell him double up <br>It's summer time, nigga tryna fuck the city up <br>I remember my first 9 like yesterday <br>Oil based, fucked up the kitchen lost an ounce of yay <br>Plug don't give a fuck, he like niggas still got to pay <br>My ounces 24 grams, not 28 <br>That's the make up and every day I wake up <br>Grab my strap and talk to God <br>Make sure that I'm prayin' <br>And once I leave the house I may bump into a hater <br>And imma shoot is ass in the face, straight up <br>Don't believe in hoe problems so I leave these hoes <br>You need that time by yourself so you don't need these hoes <br>I'm worth 20 mil nigga, but a 100 to go <br>It was 75 a half, it's 50 an O <br>I been a partner with LA Reid and Jay Z <br>I'm still hangin' with niggas who coppin' half a keys <br>Still runnin' with niggas gettin' pounds <br>And still game to let your ass down, nigga, for real <br><br>I'm your rappers favorite rapper, I'm a trap hero <br>My whips KKK white and my guns negro <br>Black, white, white, black, I'm color blind <br>Nigga if your life matter, well nigga so does mine <br>Yeah this shell 9, streets call for it <br>It was just amount of time <br>And the phone sell the record, fuck I still fine <br>I'ma still hold my head high and still shine, yeah <br>I drop without a single <br>Man I used to throw 10 thousand singles <br>Used to have my dope in a can of Pringles <br>I sell every pack of paper <br>Can 30, I done need some net <br>Street nigga at heart and I'm oldschool <br>My niggas used to smoke loud, now they on dog food <br>It's no average life, nigga this average life <br>Partner killed a partner, go to the funeral, go the burial <br>Talk to his mama, this shit can get scary <br>I'm known none of this is gon' worry us <br>The cars material, money deteriorate <br>Bitches gon' vanish and still illuminate <br>I got plaques on the wall, niggas in the jailhouse <br>Got my advance check, bail my niggas out <br>Played my role nigga, fishin' them birds out <br>When you the kingkin, there ain't shit you can tell 'bout <br>Look around nigga, who you see <br>We in streets, nigga chance is learnin' <br>Gettin' Lamorghini, 200 k advance <br>And that ain't label money, that was mine nigga <br>'Cause l my young'ns got the same dream as mine nigga <br>You tryna be a young millionaire, me too <br>Move your family out the hood, me too <br>We jump coupes <br>And we ain't makin' WorldStar, we makin' news <br>So don't get this shit conferred, nigga <br><br>I remember when they tried to play me, huh <br>Notice how I said 'try' <br>On everythin' I love, that will never happen <br>I remember when I made my first milli' <br>I remember, on everythin' I love, I remember <br>I remember when they tried to count me out <br>So I count it up <br>On my mama, I remember <br>I also remember those that showed love <br>I'm forever grateful <br>I swear to God, I remember <br>I remember, they wanted to see me broke <br>They wanted to finish me <br>They wanted me to be miserable <br>So I decided to make 25 million <br>In 11 months to be exact <br>I remember]]></content><category term="Yo Gotti" label="Yo Gotti"/><category term="I Remember (Feat. DJ Khaled)" label="I Remember (Feat. DJ Khaled)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/They_Like_Feat_YFN_Lucci/</id><title>Yo_Gotti - They Like (Feat. YFN Lucci) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:40:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:40:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/They_Like_Feat_YFN_Lucci/" title="Yo_Gotti - They Like (Feat. YFN Lucci) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ay you like in the check, don't it <br>VVS, don't it <br>She like when we say sex, don't it, yeah <br>She like, yeah yeah yeah <br>She like, yeah yeah yeah <br>We like in the check, don't it <br>Let me spend a check on it <br>I call VVS, don't it, yeah <br>They like, yeah yeah yeah <br>They like, yeah yeah yeah <br><br>Talkin' 'bout a nigga, ye ain't never gon' win <br>Told a bitch I like her and her girlfriend <br>Told that bitch I want her and her twin sister <br>Then I fucked her with my chains on and my pistol <br>I'm a dope boy, I be ballin' <br>I got dope money in my Balmains <br>Take a nigga bitch, I feel like Scarface <br>Damn her ass too big, I think they all fake <br>Never knew I't gon' be like that <br>Truck got the big B on that <br>Chain got the CMG on that <br>Price high, we can't eat like that <br>Niggas hatin', you can't eat like that <br>We ain't liked you, we never did <br>Can't knock her 'fore I get no bread <br>Shawty thick, I just want that head <br><br>Ay you like in the check, don't it <br>VVS, don't it <br>She like when we say sex, don't it, yeah <br>She like, yeah yeah yeah <br>She like, yeah yeah yeah <br>We like in the check, don't it <br>Let me spend a check on it <br>I call VVS, don't it, yeah <br>They like, yeah yeah yeah <br>They like, yeah yeah yeah <br><br>She like real niggas, she don't do lames <br>Son foreign, got pregnant it in that Mulsanne <br>She got gang babe, we call her Wu Tang <br>Her weave killer, call me 2 Chainz <br>Land on your dick, boy you too lame <br>I been bustin' outta like a shootin' rang' <br>She text me she ain't fuck, I'm thinkin' who ain't <br>Came through in that Lamb', mood changed <br>Purse on deck, Rollie on set <br>Him Upset, him Obsessed <br>We fuckin' No stress <br>We be fuckin' up checks <br>We ain't doin' nothin' 'less you <br><br>Ay you like in the check, don't it <br>VVS, don't it <br>She like when we sex, don't it, yeah <br>She like, yeah yeah yeah <br>She like, yeah yeah yeah <br>We like in the check, don't it <br>Let me spend a check on it <br>I call VVS, don't it, yeah <br>They like, yeah yeah yeah <br>They like, yeah yeah yeah]]></content><category term="Yo Gotti" label="Yo Gotti"/><category term="They Like (Feat. YFN Lucci)" label="They Like (Feat. YFN Lucci)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/Blah_Blah_Blah/</id><title>Yo_Gotti - Blah Blah Blah - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:40:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:40:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/Blah_Blah_Blah/" title="Yo_Gotti - Blah Blah Blah - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Blah blah blah blah blah <br><br>Put my bitch up out the house 'cause all she do is argue <br>Put that bitch up out the whip 'cause all she do is argue <br>All I heard is Blah blah blah blah blah, bitch, who are you <br>Made my side bitch my main bitch 'cause she don't argue <br>Blah, blah, blah, blah, she don't argue <br>Nah, nah, nah, nah, I don't argue <br>Blah, blah, blah, blah, she don't argue <br>Nah, nah, nah, nah, I don't argue <br><br>Put my bitch up out the house, told her leave <br>You no longer welcome here no, no, give me my keys <br>All you do is nag blah, blah, all you do is brag blah, blah <br>All you do is come play, play that shit, so sad <br>All that back and forth, being extra, cover scenes <br>I won't marry you so you won't never get no ring <br>All I hear is blah, blah, blah, blah, give me my keys to my car, car, car, car <br>And can go far, far, far, far, far <br>Here we are, after all, losin' focus, adderall <br>Fuss and fight, he said, she said, head hurt, Tylenol <br>Can't believe this hoe went through my phone and text my other broad <br>When she ask me 'bout the bitch, I just responded Blah, blah, blah <br><br>Put my bitch up out the house 'cause all she do is argue <br>Put that bitch up out the whip 'cause all she do is argue <br>All I heard is Blah blah blah blah blah, bitch, who are you <br>Made my side bitch my main bitch 'cause she don't argue <br>Blah, blah, blah, blah, she don't argue <br>Nah, nah, nah, nah, I don't argue <br>Blah, blah, blah, blah, she don't argue <br>Nah, nah, nah, nah, I don't argue <br><br>My hoes won't ask me 'bout another hoe <br>I'm not arguin' with no bitch, I don't even know that hoe <br>Try to go to sleep at night, you hit my ear and shit <br>Bitch I had a bad day, tryna hear that shit <br>Oh my plug just got just called up with my workin' shit <br>You like Blah blah blah blah blah all that perky shit <br>Besides, I'm tired of hearin' you hatin' on my lil perky bitch <br>And you way too excited 'bout this purse and shit <br>Head cool, pussy good but it ain't worth the shit <br>And ain't nothin' more annoyin' than a worse bitch <br>I want my purses back, my shoes when you leave <br>Bitches say I'm petty, hoe I even want the weave, I pay for it <br>Hoes they call my phone like 100 sometime <br>Hoe went through my phone, she had to lose her fuckin' mind <br>Hoe must think she run some, thought she the motherfuckin' man <br>All this back and forth, ain't got no motherfuckin' time <br><br>Put my bitch up out the house 'cause all she do is argue <br>Put that bitch up out the whip 'cause all she do is argue <br>All I heard is Blah blah blah blah blah, bitch, who are you <br>Made my side bitch my main bitch 'cause she don't argue <br>Blah, blah, blah, blah, she don't argue <br>Nah, nah, nah, nah, I don't argue <br>Blah, blah, blah, blah, she don't argue <br>Nah, nah, nah, nah, I don't argue]]></content><category term="Yo Gotti" label="Yo Gotti"/><category term="Blah Blah Blah" label="Blah Blah Blah"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/Weatherman_Feat_Kodak_Black/</id><title>Yo_Gotti - Weatherman (Feat. Kodak Black) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:40:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:40:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/Weatherman_Feat_Kodak_Black/" title="Yo_Gotti - Weatherman (Feat. Kodak Black) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So much cheese no not government <br>We just hit a lick for 10 bands <br>But now I need 100 grand <br>Got cookies like the gingerbread man <br>All these 100's pop my rubberband <br>Shut up, your irrelevant ass <br>Make it rain call me thunderman <br>Dammit where the weatherman at <br><br>Trap money, Neiman Marcus <br>250 in my pocket, I can buy a 'rari <br>I'm young, black and rich, I know I'm a target <br>If I put my hands up, they gon' shoot regardless <br>I just bought my sister that new Benz <br>This money turn your enemies to friends <br>Lil bitch tryna chop me for the pussy <br>So I would never fuck that hoe again <br>Audemaur, nig, been a star, just bought another car <br>I been sellin' bricks, so white sour diesel out the jar <br>Cocaine had a nigga far, all my dogs know who they are <br>All my plugs gon' bring they pack, all my hoes gon' play they part <br>I'm the weather man, whatever man <br>Make it rain, make it snow, tell a hoe <br>I'ma change her <br>Like fuck her then tell her she gotta go <br>They like Gotti, where the forecast at <br>I predict a lot of snow coming in, with a little Kodak <br><br>So much cheese no not government <br>We just hit a lick for 10 bands <br>But now I need 100 grand <br>Got cookies like the gingerbread man <br>All these 100's pop my rubberband <br>Shut up, your irrelevant ass <br>Make it rain call me thunderman <br>Dammit where the weatherman at <br><br>You run up, I'm gon' bust you then ask <br>That Kodak, he got so much damn swag <br>You always out your lane, your pants sag <br>Lil boy, you need to go to damn class <br>I just bought my mom a Louis handbag <br>I just run a target for 10 bands <br>Lil niggas gettin' all the damn cash <br>So that why all you niggas gettin' mad <br>No government a nigga can't cheat <br>I was in the trap since elementary <br>20 caps, can call me Ali <br>Might take another trip to Larry <br>Filthy bitch, look at your damn feet <br>He come behind me on the banshee <br>Did I tell you what I hit for 10 G <br>Me and Jackboy like Ed and Eddy <br><br>So much cheese no not government <br>We just hit a lick for 10 bands <br>But now I need 100 grand <br>Got cookies like the gingerbread man <br>All these 100's pop my rubberband <br>Shut up, your irrelevant ass <br>Make it rain call me thunderman <br>Dammit where the weatherman at]]></content><category term="Yo Gotti" label="Yo Gotti"/><category term="Weatherman (Feat. Kodak Black)" label="Weatherman (Feat. Kodak Black)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/Lifestyle_Feat_LunchMoney_Lewis/</id><title>Yo_Gotti - Lifestyle (Feat. LunchMoney Lewis) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:40:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:40:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/Lifestyle_Feat_LunchMoney_Lewis/" title="Yo_Gotti - Lifestyle (Feat. LunchMoney Lewis) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jesus from the ghetto, nigga, so am I <br>I'm like God to you niggas <br>I said Jesus from the ghetto, nigga, so am I <br>I'm like God to you niggas <br>That's my lifestyle <br>Lifestyle, nigga white <br>Girl, white power, white cloud , iced out <br>That's my lifestyle, lifestyle, lifestyle <br>That's my lifestyle <br>I'm like god to you niggas <br><br>We go bricks, all white bricks <br>Cocaine music man, I'm on that same shit <br>Just put a hunnit fifty on my same wrist <br>I used to whip whip whip whip whip with Tip <br>Fuck around got residue on my Patek <br>Fucked around and got pulled over, tail light out in the Vip <br>Ridin' dirty and if they search, I know I'm headed to the feds <br>Once they ask me for license and registration, know I flip <br>Nigga talkin' 'bout front 'em something, me outta here <br>Next nigga try owe my somethin' just hear me loud and clear <br>Don't do credit or finances, strip clubs, I don't do dances <br>Just throw my money up and watch it come down on the dancers <br>Put my money up so I can double up with Hector <br>If he ain't no hustler, he ain't get no money, I don't respect it <br>All that tough shit gon' get you killed nigga <br>And that ra ra talkin' how I'm built nigga <br><br>Jesus from the ghetto, nigga, so am I <br>I'm like God to you niggas <br>I said Jesus from the ghetto, nigga, so am I <br>I'm like God to you niggas <br>That's my lifestyle <br>Lifestyle, nigga white <br>Girl, white power, white cloud , iced out <br>That's my lifestyle, lifestyle, lifestyle <br>That's my lifestyle <br>I'm like god to you niggas <br><br>Dough boy of the century, I'm God to the hood <br>I just parked a half a million dollar car in the hood <br>I sell crack to my community, try get on <br>Sometimes I think about that shit like was I wrong <br>God bless the trap and hallelujah to the kitchen <br>Bless the chef that came before me and fuck the ones who owe me <br>This my gift from God and it my talent <br>Now I'm talkin' dope on Jimmy Fallon <br>Man I live the life these niggas kill for <br>Trill nigga on the billboard <br>I just robbed the AM more <br>I just killed the Louis store <br>I'm like God to these niggas <br>So gangster, I get money, still gon' ra on thes niggas <br>Fuck it, ski mask, ski mask, ski mask <br>The kitchen like a slope, I'm bakin' up a ski batch <br>Gave the wrong nigga money, I'ma make these streets mad <br>I'm a walkin' blessing, I get everybody bags nigga <br><br>Jesus from the ghetto, nigga, so am I <br>I'm like God to you niggas <br>I said Jesus from the ghetto, nigga, so am I <br>I'm like God to you niggas <br>That's my lifestyle <br>Lifestyle, nigga white <br>Girl, white power, white cloud , iced out <br>That's my lifestyle, lifestyle, lifestyle <br>That's my lifestyle <br>I'm like god to you niggas]]></content><category term="Yo Gotti" label="Yo Gotti"/><category term="Lifestyle (Feat. LunchMoney Lewis)" label="Lifestyle (Feat. LunchMoney Lewis)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/Power_Of_Money/</id><title>Yo_Gotti - Power Of Money - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:40:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:40:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/Power_Of_Money/" title="Yo_Gotti - Power Of Money - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[9 <br><br>I want the money nigga, yeah yeah me too <br>I want the power nigga, yeah yeah me too <br>Hustle every hour nigga, yeah yeah I am <br>Do you see 'em doing it like this nigga, no no <br>I want the money nigga, yeah yeah me too <br>I want the power nigga, yeah yeah I do <br>Hustle every hour nigga, yeah yeah I am <br>Do you see 'em doing it like this nigga, no no <br><br>I heard it's over trap niggas, word to the rap niggas <br>Word to the internet, I've never been into that <br>I know niggas doing life sentences, some of 'em innocent for real <br>But they'll never tell on they man, what them niggas hatin' <br>Who came through in the drophead before the deal Me <br>Who bought himself out of his contract for half a mil Me <br>Who kept the streets alive Me, who put his niggas on Me <br>Who rode with you right or wrong <br>Me, and repped the streets in every song <br>I know Young when Meech was free, talk to Meek before DC <br>I dodged a life sentence, niggas so can't shit discourage me <br>Get me a big ol bag of money if you trying to encourage me <br>They say it cost to be the boss well you say I paid the fee, nigga <br><br>I want the money nigga, yeah yeah I do <br>I want the power nigga, yeah yeah Do <br>Hustle every hour nigga, yeah yeah I am <br>Do you see 'em doing it like this nigga no no <br>I want the money nigga, yeah yeah <br>I want the power nigga, yeah yeah I do <br>Hustle every hour nigga, yeah yeah I do <br>Do you see 'em doing it like this nigga no no <br><br>Walk in the studio and into the booth <br>talk to the microphone mic shit <br>Tell 'em about your life and about the shit you be standin' on I am <br>How you put your niggas up I did <br>how you fucked a thousand bitches true <br>But you never leave your home I can't do it <br>Bitches is bitches and family is family, for real <br>Rappin' was cool but dope boy was payin' the bills <br>Friends they hate, they frenemies, they're not your enemies <br>They really do like you, they hate, just envious energy <br>You know the power of money, the power of fame <br>Bitches fuck on a nigga for real, knowin' he lame <br>Damn to say it ain't personal for the shoes and the purses <br>It's like we said in the verse, the money ain't worth it, I can't do it <br><br>I want the money nigga, yeah yeah I can do it <br>I want the power nigga, yeah yeah Fo' real <br>Hustle every hour nigga, yeah yeah I am <br>Do you see 'em doing it like this nigga, no no <br>I want the money nigga, yeah yeah I do <br>I want the power nigga, yeah yeah I do <br>Hustle every hour nigga, yeah yeah I am <br>Do you see 'em doing it like this nigga no no <br><br>See it was like, when we first started with Cocaine Music 1 <br>we was puttin' the CDs in sandwich bags and shit and like <br>pullin' up in niggas trap like right there like <br>I won't hire no more fuckin' street team <br>like the Street Team was me and my guys <br>you know what I'm sayin' <br>I'm jumping out giving niggas my shit, hand for hand <br>and I knew they had to repec' it <br>You know' what I'm sayin' <br>Then we went Cocaine Music 2, 3, 4, 4 and a half <br>Then we went CM 5, CM 6, CM 7 <br>Then I said i was gon quit at CM 8 <br>Then I came back, fuck it <br><br>I want the money nigga, yeah yeah <br>I want the power nigga, yeah yeah <br>Hustle every hour nigga, yeah yeah <br>Do you see 'em doing it like this nigga, no no <br>I want the money nigga, yeah yeah <br>I want the power nigga, yeah yeah <br>Hustle every hour nigga, yeah yeah <br>Do you see 'em doing it like this nigga, no no <br><br>Ay, this CM 9 nigga let's go Yo <br>252 grams nigga <br>This shit may be over ya head or under ya head <br>They know what I'm talkin' 'bout <br>Weight it up, it's all there Put the residue on that We here Beep]]></content><category term="Yo Gotti" label="Yo Gotti"/><category term="Power Of Money" label="Power Of Money"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/81/</id><title>Yo_Gotti - 81 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:40:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:40:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yo_Gotti/81/" title="Yo_Gotti - 81 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Only if a nigga knew like <br>It's amazin' what 365 days can do for you <br>This time last year niggas was like <br>Talkin' 'bout uttin' budgets and shit <br>I dropped the biggest record of my career, yeah <br>Nigga business partner with JAY Z <br>Shout out to Ty Ty, wassup nigga <br>Emory, what it do <br>You see 'em <br><br>Gotta pick 'em wisely <br>Gotta choose 'em carefully <br>Got niggas I know that weren't there for me <br>Got bitches I know that don't care for me <br>Could of went on tour with your favorite rapper and declined <br>Why I'm tryna break CMG <br>So fuck that, I'm doin' mine <br>They see I'm mad, see they call in the streets, call me back <br>Say they miss the old Gotti, old Jeezy, old Boosie, that was real rap <br>In New York with 3 bangers <br>Did Jimmy Fallon with Meaghan Trainor <br>I guess the sets won't taint him <br>Guess the money won't change him <br>Decisions <br>Homie on probation <br>Took him up to Roc Nation <br>Let him meet Jay, told him be patient <br>Decisions, and lil homie really got it <br>Trying to tell him wait his turn <br>He ain't learn, lil homie caught a body <br><br>9 times 9 is 81 <br>I'm an 80's baby born in '81 <br>From a family full of hustlers, youngest son <br>They say get that money, show 'em him how it done <br>9 times 9 is 81 <br>I'm an 80's baby born in '81 <br>From a family full of hustlers, youngest son <br>They say get that money, show 'em him how it done <br>How it's done, got it, got it how it's done <br>You would make that shit look easy, how it's done <br>Gotti you make that shit look easy, how it's done <br>Gotti you make that shit look easy, how it's done <br><br>Biggest deal of my career <br>I feel the pressure, gotta follow up <br>Same time I can feel the feds <br>Gettin' closer, lockin' niggas up <br>Decisions <br>Closer partners, they in prison <br>Never want to be the biggest <br>I just want to be the realest <br>I pay 6 figures a year for a hitter <br>Knockers, see your goon, he my nigga <br>He got the city divided <br>Bring it together, I tried it <br>Fuck them lil niggas, I tried it <br>Fuck them lil niggas, I tried it <br>I am the king, your highness <br>You want a problem, well find it <br>I was too busy gettin' too many million <br>Like now the perfect timin' <br>Let them lil niggas in <br>They what they do to bitch <br>I don't be trippin' at all <br>Whatever come with it, I'm with it <br>Lil nigga, I swear I'm good for it all <br><br>9 times 9 is 81 <br>I'm an 80's baby born in '81 <br>From a family full of hustlers, youngest son <br>They say get that money, show 'em him how it done <br>9 times 9 is 81 <br>I'm an 80's baby born in '81 <br>From a family full of hustlers, youngest son <br>They say get that money, show 'em him how it done <br>How it's done, got it, got it how it's done <br>You would make that shit look easy, how it's done <br>Gotti you make that shit look easy, how it's done <br>Gotti you make that shit look easy, how it's done <br><br>1 million, 2 million, 3 <br>CM9 strictly for the streets <br>I'm tryna get a twin piece <br>First class nigga, I'm a millionaire <br>First class nigga, I'm a millionaire <br>I'm tryna be the first trap billionaire <br>I'm tryna be the first trap billionaire]]></content><category term="Yo Gotti" label="Yo Gotti"/><category term="81" label="81"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Don_Q/Bag_On_Me/</id><title>Don_Q - Bag On Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:45:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:45:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Don_Q/Bag_On_Me/" title="Don_Q - Bag On Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I got that bag on me, I I got that bag on me now <br>I got that bag on me, I I keep that bag on me now <br>I got that bag on me, I I got that bag on me now <br>I got that bag on me, I I keep that bag on me now <br><br>They want to run down on me <br>When they see me them niggas is mad at me <br>So I walk around with it <br>Cause they plottin' and I keep that bag on me <br>I was a clown to them hatin' niggas <br>Yeah they used to laugh at me <br>Now I got to hold it down <br>Case a nigga feel like he want to come after me <br><br>Cause I got that bag on me, yeah I got that bag on me <br>I got that bag on me, yeah I keep that bag on me <br>They want to run down on me <br>When they see me them niggas is mad at me <br>So I walk around with it <br>Cause they plottin' and I keep that bag on me <br><br>Double R's what we ridin' <br>Highbridge spelt in diamonds <br>Fell in love with designer <br>Then I fell in love with Rihanna <br>All I hang around is shottas <br>They'll never ever tell your honor <br>Nina have em singin', Na Na Na Nuh <br>We can meet up anywhere you want to <br>Run it up, I run it up again <br>She was frontin' so I fucked her friend <br>Bitches callin' me a dog because <br>I dont wanna fall in love with them <br>You could call it what you wanted cause <br>She gon' still let me fuck again <br>I'ma keep on countin' hundreds so <br>We don't fuck with you Washingtons <br>They just want to see me starve again <br>Reason why I'm goin' hard again <br>Missed my target so I shot again <br>Missed my ex so I shot again <br>You a dub, you is not a ten <br>Just the money, I don't got a friend <br>Told my hitter shoot, he shot at them <br>Left a nigga in the garbage bin <br>Now I got that bag fuck that shit I never had <br>Cause I'm going in for that shit <br>And I never laugh at a nigga if he doing bad <br>Cause nigga I been through that shit <br>But I'm in my bag, yeah my nigga, I'm in my bag <br>But I think you been knew that shit <br>How I make a track, and I'm making niggas mad <br>And I know they ain't doin shit <br><br>They want to run down on me <br>When they see me them niggas is mad at me <br>So I walk around with it <br>Cause they plottin' and I keep that bag on me <br>I was a clown to them hatin' niggas <br>Yeah they used to laugh at me <br>Now I got to hold it down <br>Case a nigga feel like he want to come after me <br><br>Cause I got that bag on me, yeah I got that bag on me <br>I got that bag on me, yeah I keep that bag on me <br>They want to run down on me <br>When they see me them niggas is mad at me <br>So I walk around with it <br>Cause they plottin' and I keep that bag on me <br><br>Dreamt about it, then we went and did it <br>Double R's, we was really in it <br>Pullin' up and they be in they feelings <br>It was all good when we was in the Civic <br>Sick jewels make your bitch choose <br>They all stare when the wrist move <br>And it all came from that raw cane <br>In the kitchen with the wrist moves <br>Give a fuck about your rap deal <br>I could show you how the cash feel <br>Run it up until the bags fill <br>Safe spot, keep stash sealed <br>Money money, I don't sleep without it <br>Couple hundreds, I don't leave without it <br>All my niggas got to keep it solid <br>Then if not then I don't want to be around it <br>Now my bitch bad, got a C around it <br>I just took my neck and put a key around it <br>Money piling, I can't see around it <br>So the pocket rockets, got to keep around it <br>We couldn't just settle, my foot on the pedal <br>I come in Hell's Kitchen and cook with the devil <br>I'm good in the ghetto, for real nigga <br>I be in the trenches with the night riders <br>And the pack pushers and the white buyers <br>I'm like Mike Myers with a knife by him <br>I could bring it to you but the price higher <br>Bust down, make the ice brighter <br>We ain't really on sight typers <br>We the serve you on sight type of <br>Give it to you in a white Viper <br><br>They want to run down on me <br>When they see me them niggas is mad at me <br>So I walk around with it <br>Cause they plottin' and I keep that bag on me <br>I was a clown to them hatin' niggas <br>Yeah they used to laugh at me <br>Now I got to hold it down <br>Case a nigga feel like he want to come after me <br><br>Cause I got that bag on me, yeah I got that bag on me <br>I got that bag on me, yeah I keep that bag on me <br>They want to run down on me <br>When they see me them niggas is mad at me <br>So I walk around with it <br>Cause they plottin' and I keep that bag on me]]></content><category term="Don Q" label="Don Q"/><category term="Bag On Me" label="Bag On Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Perzonal_War/Mother_Darkness/</id><title>Perzonal_War - Mother Darkness - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:45:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:45:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Perzonal_War/Mother_Darkness/" title="Perzonal_War - Mother Darkness - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Senses sharp as ice darkness my paradise <br>what does it matter it is all the same to me <br>Too fast for human eyes my presence paralyzes <br>a silhouette that is one with time and space <br>Born between life and death a hybrid more or less <br>but I don't care I'm the walker on two sides <br>The daylight bears an offer <br>but I'm condemned to suffer until the day when my misssion is <br>Fulfilled <br>My shadow you can feel your life is all <br>I steel your end will be my kiss <br>Ius sanguinis]]></content><category term="Perzonal War" label="Perzonal War"/><category term="Mother Darkness" label="Mother Darkness"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Perzonal_War/Voices/</id><title>Perzonal_War - Voices - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:45:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:45:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Perzonal_War/Voices/" title="Perzonal_War - Voices - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Can you hear the voices <br>They are calling from inside <br>Wanna whisper little secrets <br>That you try so hard to hide <br>Can't jump over your shadow <br>An inner distance keeps you back <br>The honest man inside still dreaming <br>And some pain starts streaming <br>An open book with empty sites mean nothing <br>Eyes that 're staying blind see nothing <br>Of ourselves the secrets of our lifes <br>Some angels from the past <br>Reminding us of days that last <br>Times that made us what we are <br>Some future devils's hate <br>The cause for fear of our own fate <br>There is a bar preventing the unburdened way <br>An open book with empty sites mean nothing <br>Eyes that 're staying blind see nothing <br>Of ourselves the secrets that we keep <br>Wanna close my eyes <br>Drowning in an endless sleep <br>Glittering mouldy stains <br>Turning into stars so deep <br>Faces, pale white skin drained of vital energy <br>Turn into the ones beloved in my memory <br>A simulated compromise means nothing <br>A speech with empty words is nothing <br>Nothing but a waste of our time]]></content><category term="Perzonal War" label="Perzonal War"/><category term="Voices" label="Voices"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Perzonal_War/Nothing_Remains_At_All/</id><title>Perzonal_War - Nothing Remains At All - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:45:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:45:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Perzonal_War/Nothing_Remains_At_All/" title="Perzonal_War - Nothing Remains At All - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh my friend I'll tell you what I'm feeling now, my deepest secrets <br>Come into my world and you'll be part of myself <br>Can you feel the confusion that leads me where it wants <br>Oh I'm just a puppet on a string but I enjoy <br>A new day awakes but I don't know which path it takes to leave its mark on me <br>Fate has grabbed the strings tight in its hands so find the strength to change it <br>I know time is an immemorial state and I will never compromise <br>Although I'm weak I still stand by me and I will never compromise <br>And still all these moments last for years but I will try to hold back my tears <br>I won't deny myself otherwise my deepest sense would drown in lies]]></content><category term="Perzonal War" label="Perzonal War"/><category term="Nothing Remains At All" label="Nothing Remains At All"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/The_Lipstick_On_His_Collar_Acoustic/</id><title>Caro_Emerald - The Lipstick On His Collar (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:46:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:46:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/The_Lipstick_On_His_Collar_Acoustic/" title="Caro_Emerald - The Lipstick On His Collar (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The clock has ticked eleven and the place is clear <br>Reality is kicking in and so is my beer <br>I don't make excuses when it's all my fault <br>If a heart is made of money he's cleaned out my vault <br><br>I feel a little wounded and it isn't fair <br>To sit inside a parlor and see him standing over there <br>As smug as a robber that a cop can't catch <br>The lipstick on his collar doesn't seem to match mine <br><br>Mine, doesn't seem to match mine, mine <br><br>Now Joe behind the bar is offering advice <br>Cause I'm a broken record and he has to tell me twice <br>Why don't I understand that he just can't change <br>I wanna be his woman not his weekend dame <br><br>Now Joe has eyes a'rollin' says it's just too bad <br>And he'll be back tomorrow for my heartbeat crash <br>I'd like to say goodbye, but hello is the match <br>Though the lipstick on his collar never seems to match mine <br><br>Never seem to match, mine ooh, never seem to match <br><br>This line is disconnected <br><br>Mine, oohohohooh, match mine, yeah hey yeah]]></content><category term="Caro Emerald" label="Caro Emerald"/><category term="The Lipstick On His Collar (Acoustic)" label="The Lipstick On His Collar (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/Back_It_Up_Acoustic/</id><title>Caro_Emerald - Back It Up (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:46:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:46:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/Back_It_Up_Acoustic/" title="Caro_Emerald - Back It Up (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can't stop shaking <br>The room has a groove in the floor <br>It's almost earthquaking <br>Uhuh <br><br>Look what we're making <br>History out on the floor <br>And it's just awaking <br>Uhuh <br><br>So get that needle in the core <br>Scratch that back and gimme more <br>You know exactly what I came here for <br>Back it up and do it again <br><br>From the middle to the top to the end <br>Ba dlun dla dla doday <br>Ba dlun dla dla doday <br>Back to the middle to the front to the end <br>Za dlun dla dla doday <br>Everybody ba dlun doday <br>I don't care if he's a friend <br>From the front to the middle to the back to the end <br><br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh <br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh <br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh <br>Back it up and do it again <br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh <br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh, uhuh <br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh, uhuh <br><br>Gimme some of that funky <br>The kind that the Duke used to play <br>And make it more swingy <br>Heyey <br><br>And then give me some horny <br>You know the bub pu pa bub pu pa bay <br>Come on, give it to me <br>Hmm hmm <br><br>Slam that bass and make it sing <br>Give those strings that rip 'n zing <br>You know exactly what I came here for <br>Back it up and do it again <br><br>From the middle to the top to the end <br>Ba dlun dla dla doday <br>Ba dlun dla dla doday <br>Back to the middle to the front to the end <br>Za dlun dla dla doday <br>Everybody ba dlun doday <br>I don't care if he's a friend <br>From the front to the middle to the back to the end <br><br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh <br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh <br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh, mmm <br>Back it up and do it again <br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh <br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh, uhuh <br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh, uhuh <br><br>Take me to the second break <br><br>Uhummm <br>Uh uh uhuhumm <br><br>You, you can do it again <br>Do do do do eh do do it again <br>A again a a gain a again <br>You can do it again <br><br>Get that needle in the core <br>Scratch that back and gimme more <br>You know exactly what I came here for <br>Back it up and do it again <br><br>From the middle to the top to the end mmm <br>Ba dlun dla dla doday <br>Ba dlun dla dla doday <br>Back to the middle to the front to the end <br>Za dlun dla dla doday <br>Everybody ba dlun doday <br>I don't care if he's a friend <br>From the front to the middle to the back to the end <br><br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh <br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh <br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh <br>Back it up and do it again <br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh <br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh, uhuh <br>Back, back, back, back it up I wanna, uhuh, uhuh <br>Back it up and do it again <br><br>Uhummm <br>Uh uh uhuhumm]]></content><category term="Caro Emerald" label="Caro Emerald"/><category term="Back It Up (Acoustic)" label="Back It Up (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/You_Dont_Love_Me_Acoustic/</id><title>Caro_Emerald - You Don`t Love Me (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:46:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:46:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/You_Dont_Love_Me_Acoustic/" title="Caro_Emerald - You Don`t Love Me (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Another day, another night got me thinkin' <br>What is it with him, he's naturally moving slow <br>I see him at the corner bar, am I dreamin' <br>Surrounded by friends, it's got to end, I need to know <br><br>Am I just a night of lust, a lost temptation <br>Is someone like me his destiny he'll never know <br>I gotta find a way to show my expectations <br>He ends it where it begins but I won't let go <br><br>I know you don't love me <br>But still I burn for you <br>I know you don't love me <br>This flame will die, it's true <br>My soul barred completely <br>Don't seem enough for you <br>I know you don't love me <br>But the message can't get through <br><br>Any man can see that I'm worth the talkin' <br>Love can be bittersweet when a girl hears no <br>Opportunity knocks, but your doors don't open <br>But I feel a fire inside that's about to blow <br><br>So, sweep me off my feet and show me something different <br>You know all the tricks, come get your kicks, you know I'm game <br>You gotta understand a girl needs more than romance <br>How many chances lost 'till you just run away <br><br>I know you don't love me <br>But still I burn for you <br>I know you don't love me <br>This flame will die, it's true <br>My soul barred completely <br>Don't seem enough for you <br>I know you don't love me <br>But the message can't get through <br><br>Maybe I'm missing the telepathy <br>There's a disconnection, you don't think of me <br>I don't really care because I disagree <br>'Cause I'm the only part of you that you don't see <br>Maybe I'm missing the telepathy <br>There's a disconnection, you don't think of me <br>I don't really care because I disagree <br>'Cause I'm the only part of you that you don't see <br><br>I know you don't love me <br>But still I burn for you <br>I know you don't love me <br>This flame will die, it's true <br>My soul barred completely <br>Don't seem enough for you <br>I know you don't love me <br>But the message can't get through <br><br>I know you don't love me I know you don't love me <br>But still I burn for you But still I burn for you <br>I know you don't love me <br>This flame will die, it's true This flame will die, it's true <br>My soul barred completely <br>Don't seem enough for you <br>I know you don't love me]]></content><category term="Caro Emerald" label="Caro Emerald"/><category term="You Don`t Love Me (Acoustic)" label="You Don`t Love Me (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/I_Know_That_Hes_Mine_Acoustic/</id><title>Caro_Emerald - I Know That He`s Mine (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:46:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:46:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/I_Know_That_Hes_Mine_Acoustic/" title="Caro_Emerald - I Know That He`s Mine (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Three o'clock on a late Sunday morning <br>The candles have burned to their end <br>Found the pictures we've taken <br>And now I'm awaken and <br>Sleep's my invisible friend <br><br>So I'm staring the hands off my wall clock <br>Seems both of us just hang around <br>Got no one to warm me <br>And nothing to hold <br>My body needs what it don't have <br><br>Without him <br>I really don't mind <br>A little bit lonely <br>He'll make up in time <br>As long as he loves me <br>He'll answer his crime <br>The door stays wide open <br>I know that he's mine <br><br>The tracks of my tears keep on freezin' <br>I'm melting the cold in the halls <br>I feel like I'm drownin' <br>There's no one around <br>And now I'm just climbing the walls <br><br>Perhaps if I played the seductress <br>A passionate woman of guile <br>He'd be there in a minute <br>The heat won't diminish <br>He'd wear nothing more than a smile <br><br>Without him <br>I really don't mind <br>A little bit lonely <br>He'll make up in time <br>As long as he loves me <br>He'll answer his crime <br>The door stays wide open <br>I know that he's mine <br><br>Charlie keep singin' that chanson <br>Your words always make so much sense <br>And though they're in French <br>I've got no defense <br>I know that I'm reaching the end <br><br>So, rumors, keep flying around me <br>It's you I refuse to believe <br>He's right 'round the corner <br>He knows that I'm home now <br>And nobody calls me naive <br><br>Without him <br>I really don't mind <br>A little bit lonely <br>He'll make up in time <br>As long as he loves me <br>He'll answer his crime <br>The door stays wide open <br>I know that he's mine]]></content><category term="Caro Emerald" label="Caro Emerald"/><category term="I Know That He`s Mine (Acoustic)" label="I Know That He`s Mine (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/Just_One_Dance_Acoustic/</id><title>Caro_Emerald - Just One Dance (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:46:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:46:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/Just_One_Dance_Acoustic/" title="Caro_Emerald - Just One Dance (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey handsome have you got the time <br>I've been watching you since the moment you arrived <br>A white suit from London, and shoes from Paris <br>Don't you wanna spend about an hour with me <br><br>The scent and the aroma refuses to breathe <br>It's more like a haze that's trying to succeed <br>It's drawing me in and pulling me to you <br>And every thought I have turns the language blue <br><br>All it cost is just a minute now <br>For one dollar you can show me how <br>I'll take your hand and then your worries too <br>In just one dance I'll make your dreams come true <br><br>Your dreams come true, mmm <br><br>Don't know why you play hard to get <br>I'm here to kiss away any thoughts of regret <br>A silk tie from Siam shows elegance and class <br>Handsome as the heavens that a film would never cast <br><br>But underneath the mask I see the skin of a man <br>Smooth and seductive who's really got a plan <br>It's drawing me in, magnetically to you <br>You haven't got forever, but I got that too <br><br>All it cost is just a minute now <br>For one dollar you can show me how <br>I'll take your hand and then your worries too <br>In just one dance I'll make your dreams come true <br><br>Your dreams come true <br>I'll make your dreams come <br>I'll make your dreams come <br>I'll make your dreams come true <br><br>I'm like the smoke on your fire <br>Smoldering endless desire <br>How long will your flame burn <br><br>All it cost is just a minute now <br>For one dollar you can show me how <br>I'll take your hand and then your worries too <br>In just one dance I'll make your dreams come true <br><br>All it cost is just a minute now <br>For one dollar you can show me how <br>I'll take your hand and then your worries too <br>In just one dance I'll make your dreams come true]]></content><category term="Caro Emerald" label="Caro Emerald"/><category term="Just One Dance (Acoustic)" label="Just One Dance (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/A_Night_Like_This_Acoustic/</id><title>Caro_Emerald - A Night Like This (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:46:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:46:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/A_Night_Like_This_Acoustic/" title="Caro_Emerald - A Night Like This (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[From where you are <br>You see the smoke start to arise where they play cards <br>And you walk over, softly moving passed the guards <br>The stakes are getting higher, you can feel it in your heart <br><br>He calls you bluff <br>He is the ace you never thought he played that much <br>And now it's more than all this cards you want to touch <br>You never know if winning this could really be enough <br><br>Take a look beyond the moon <br>You'll see the stars mmm <br>And when you look around <br>You know the room by heart <br><br>I have never dreamed it <br>Have you ever dreamed a night like this <br>I cannot believe it <br>I may never see a night like this <br>When everything you think is incomplete <br>Starts happening when you are cheek to cheek <br>Could you ever dream it <br>I have never dreamed, dreamed a night like this <br><br>How many times <br>Have I been waiting by the door to hear these chimes <br>To hear that someone debonair has just arrived <br>And opened up to see my world before my eyes <br><br>That silhouette <br>creates an image and a night I can't forget <br>It has the scent of something special, I can't rest <br>If I resist temptation, oh I know for sure that I will lose the bet <br><br>I walk away and suddenly it seems <br>I'm not alone mmm <br>In front of me he stands <br>I stop before he goes <br><br>I have never dreamed it <br>Have you ever dreamed a night like this <br>I cannot believe it <br>I may never see a night like this <br>When everything you think is incomplete <br>Starts happening when you are cheek to cheek <br>Could you ever dream it <br>I have never dreamed, dreamed a night like this <br><br>Mmm <br>Mmm <br><br>I have never dreamed it <br>Have you ever dreamed a night like this <br>I cannot believe it <br>I may never see a night like this <br>When everything you think is incomplete <br>Starts happening when you are cheek to cheek <br>Could you ever dream it <br>I have never dreamed, dreamed a night like this]]></content><category term="Caro Emerald" label="Caro Emerald"/><category term="A Night Like This (Acoustic)" label="A Night Like This (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/Dr_Wanna_Do_Acoustic/</id><title>Caro_Emerald - Dr. Wanna Do (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:46:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:46:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/Dr_Wanna_Do_Acoustic/" title="Caro_Emerald - Dr. Wanna Do (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I just made an appointment <br>For a special rendez vous <br>To see a man of miracles <br>And all that he can do <br><br>I checked in at reception <br>Put my hat onto my lap <br>And when he walked in dressed in white <br>I had a heart attack <br><br>My eyes went ooh <br>My voice just cooed <br>My mind let loose <br>I'll stay forever, it's up to you <br><br>Dabedebedibedabedudohdoh <br><br>Doctor I want you <br>Mmm, my Doctor Wanna Do <br>I can't get over you <br>Dr Do anything that ya Wanna Do <br>Doctor I want you <br>Mmm, my Doctor Wanna Do <br>I can't get over you <br>Dr Do anything that ya Wanna Do <br><br>I sat down and I waited <br>'Til I heard my name get called <br>It's like I'm at the races <br>And I think I won them all <br><br>He asked me to step forward <br>First I caught my breath, and ran <br>For endless observation <br>In the hands of Superman <br><br>My eyes went ooh <br>My voice just cooed <br>My mind let loose <br>I'll stay forever, it's up to you <br><br>Dabedebedibedabedudohdoh <br><br>Doctor I want you <br>Mmm, my Doctor Wanna Do <br>I can't get over you <br>Dr Do anything that ya Wanna Do <br>Doctor I want you <br>Mmm, my Doctor Wanna Do <br>I can't get over you <br>Dr Do anything that ya Wanna Do <br><br>Come over here and give me some medicine <br>Move a little closer so my head can spin <br>A little bit of potion makes my fever go <br>Get it out of me me like a volcano <br><br>My eyes went ooh uhuh uhuh <br>My voice just cooed you know it <br>My mind let loose <br>Mmm, Dr Love <br><br>Dabedebedibedabedudohdoh <br><br>Doctor I want you <br>Mmm, my Doctor Wanna Do <br>I can't get over you <br>Dr Do anything that ya Wanna Do <br>Doctor I want you <br>Mmm, my Doctor Wanna Do <br>I can't get over you <br>Dr Do anything that ya Wanna Do]]></content><category term="Caro Emerald" label="Caro Emerald"/><category term="Dr. Wanna Do (Acoustic)" label="Dr. Wanna Do (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/Riviera_Life_Acoustic/</id><title>Caro_Emerald - Riviera Life (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:46:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:46:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caro_Emerald/Riviera_Life_Acoustic/" title="Caro_Emerald - Riviera Life (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Eh, Yeah, yeah, hit'm, ye yeah <br><br>I'm really tired of my concrete jungle <br>Six days a week is way too much <br>I'm gonna make the great escape <br>Go on a little getaway <br><br>I'll go get my beat up motor <br>Start it up and head for the green <br>Of endless countrysides <br>And go somewhere I've never been <br><br>I'll stop, kiss my blues goodbye <br>Breathe until I soar outside my crazy nights <br>And live the Riviera life <br>I'll stop, thank you for today <br>I'm sure that by candlelight, I'll be alright <br>And live a Riviera life <br><br>Mmm <br>I'll live a Riviera life <br><br>The road can wind like my hidden hair bow <br>You clear my face so I can feel the breeze <br>And down below it's Monaco <br>And Mister, I don't know a soul <br><br>I'll drop off the keys at valet <br>Look out my window bay <br>One afternoon martini <br>Wouldn't want it any other way <br><br>I'll stop, kiss my blues goodbye <br>Breathe until I soar outside my crazy nights <br>And live the Riviera life <br>I'll stop, thank you for today <br>I'm sure that by candlelight, I'll be alright <br>And live a Riviera life <br><br>So whenever <br>My eyes get weary <br>I'm not fearing what life brings <br>Forever <br>When times make me teary <br>I'll know what I was meant to do <br>I've nothing at all to lose <br><br>I'll stop, kiss my blues goodbye <br>Breathe until I soar outside my crazy nights <br>And live the Riviera life <br>I'll stop, thank you for today <br>I'm sure that by candlelight, I'll be alright <br>And live a Riviera life <br><br>Mmm <br>Dududa ta ta ta ta ta <br>Mmm <br>I'll live a Riviera life]]></content><category term="Caro Emerald" label="Caro Emerald"/><category term="Riviera Life (Acoustic)" label="Riviera Life (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bandit_Gang_Marco/Same_Road/</id><title>Bandit_Gang_Marco - Same Road - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:46:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:46:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bandit_Gang_Marco/Same_Road/" title="Bandit_Gang_Marco - Same Road - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm off of you <br>You off of me <br>But truthfully we've never been <br>Cause we going down the same road <br>Cause we going down the same road <br>Going down the same road <br>I know like you know <br>We'll be back at it tomorrow <br><br>Baby I can't complain <br>So many things have changed <br>Baby I gave you this ring <br>Now I'm feeling pain <br>I know you feel it too <br>You need to tell me what you wanna do <br>Cause I want your love <br>You use to cry about my touch <br>Imma be here as long as you living <br>Imma deal with my feelings <br>Baby won't you need me <br>I'm tired of waiting by the phone <br>You always telling me you leaving me alone <br>And I'm like damn why <br><br>I'm off of you <br>You off of me <br>But truthfully we've never been <br>Cause we going down the same road <br>Cause we going down the same road <br>Going down the same road <br>I know like you know <br>We'll be back at it tomorrow <br><br>He said You the princess of the south but you my Queen <br>He said Ain't no Jay and B we do our own thing <br>Like they can't parallel park <br>They can't get in between us <br>Like the Tin Man you need love, You heartless <br>And I'm gone be the one that turn you up <br>Show you out <br>Check you out <br>Look at you showing out <br>Acting like you moving on <br>You always in and out <br>What happened now <br>Don't throw in the towel <br>Now matter how much you up <br>You need me to hold you down <br>You need me to hold you down <br>You need me to hold you down <br>Down <br>Down <br>You need me to hold you down <br><br>I'm off of you <br>You off of me <br>But truthfully we've never been <br>Cause we going down the same road <br>Cause we going down the same road <br>Going down the same road <br>I know like you know <br>We'll be back at it tomorrow]]></content><category term="Bandit Gang Marco" label="Bandit Gang Marco"/><category term="Same Road" label="Same Road"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mark_Carpio/Hiling_Live/</id><title>Mark_Carpio - Hiling (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:46:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:46:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mark_Carpio/Hiling_Live/" title="Mark_Carpio - Hiling (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ito ay isang dalangin <br>Huwag sanang ipagkait <br>Matagpuan na ang hanap <br>Na pangarap <br>Na pangarap <br><br>Kasalanan nga bang umibig <br>Parusang lungkot ang hatid <br>Lamig ng hangin ang yakap <br>Tuwing gabi <br>Tuwing gabi <br><br>Pilit mang itago <br>Hindi kayang maglaho <br>Ang mga katanungang tulad ng <br><br>Bakit parang sa'kin lamang may galit <br>Ang madayang tadhanang 'di namamansin <br>Wala na bang karapatan <br>Na pagbigyan ang hiling <br><br>Lumilipad ang aking isip <br>Bigla na lang napapailing <br>Wala na ngang mapagtuunan <br>Ng pansin <br>Ng pansin <br><br>Pilit mang itago <br>Hindi kayang maglaho <br>Ang mga katanungang tulad ng <br>Tulad ng <br><br>Bakit parang sa'kin lamang may galit <br>Ang madayang tadhanang 'di namamansin <br>Wala na bang karapatan <br>Na pagbigyan ang hiling <br><br>Nakahanda ang puso <br>Kahit pa ako ay maskatan <br><br>Kung sino man para sa'kin <br>Hindi ko sasayangin <br>Madayang tadhana iyong pansinin <br>Wala na bang karapatan <br>Na pagbigyan ang hiling <br><br>Kung sino man para sa'kin kahit magalit <br>Oh madayang tadhana iyong pansinin <br>Wala na bang karapatan <br>Na pagbigyan ang hiling]]></content><category term="Mark Carpio" label="Mark Carpio"/><category term="Hiling (Live)" label="Hiling (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mark_Carpio/Kay_Tagal_Live/</id><title>Mark_Carpio - Kay Tagal (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:46:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:46:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mark_Carpio/Kay_Tagal_Live/" title="Mark_Carpio - Kay Tagal (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Akala ko'y di pa handang <br>Muling tumibok ang damdamin <br>Ngunit bigla kang <br>dumating sa buhay ko <br>Hindi kailangang umimik <br>Nagdadaldalan lang sa tingin <br>Saan ka ba nanggaling <br>bakit ngayong lang <br>Oh kay tagal kitang hinanap <br>Oh kay tagal ko ring nangarap <br>Na makapiling ka <br>Oh aking mahal <br>Pangakong hindi ka iiwanan <br>At hindi pababayaan <br>Oh anong saya ang nadarama <br>'di kailangang magpanggap <br>Walang kailangang baguhin <br>Sadyang ginawa para sa isa't isa <br>'di kailangang magmadali <br>Buti na lang 'di pinilit <br>Alam ko naman na <br>ikaw ay darating <br>Oh kay tagal kitang hinanap <br>Oh kay tagal ko ring nangarap <br>Na makapiling ka <br>Oh aking mahal <br>Pangakong hindi ka iiwanan <br>At hindi pababayaan <br>Oh anong saya ang nadarama <br>Oh heto ako ngayo'y iyong iyo <br>Bago mag alala nais <br>kong malaman mo <br>Ooh <br>Oh kay tagal kitang hinanap <br>Oh kay tagal ko ring nangarap <br>Na makapiling ka <br>Oh aking mahal <br>Pangakong hindi ka iiwanan <br>At hindi pababayaan <br>Oh anong saya ang nadarama <br>Oh anong saya ang nadarama <br>Akala ko ay 'di pa handang <br>Muling tumibok ang damdamin <br>Ngunit bigla kang <br>dumating sa buhay ko <br>]]></content><category term="Mark Carpio" label="Mark Carpio"/><category term="Kay Tagal (Live)" label="Kay Tagal (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Reynolds_Girls/Id_Rather_Jack_Extended_Ver/</id><title>The_Reynolds_Girls - I`d Rather Jack (Extended Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:49:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:49:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Reynolds_Girls/Id_Rather_Jack_Extended_Ver/" title="The_Reynolds_Girls - I`d Rather Jack (Extended Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All we wanna do is have a good time <br>Then you went and took our house away <br>No one ever asked for our opinion <br>No, no, we don't get a say <br><br>AM, FM, all that jazz <br>We'd rather sing along with Yazz <br>What happened to the radio <br>They never play the songs we know <br><br>Golden oldies, Rolling Stones, we don't want them back <br>I'd rather jack than Fleetwood Mac <br>No heavy metal, rock'n'roll, music from the past <br>I'd rather jack than Fleetwood Mac <br><br>I'd rather jack <br><br>Can't they see that every generation <br>Has music for its own identity <br>But why the DJ on the radio station <br>Is always more than twice the age of me <br><br>Who needs Pink Floyd, Dire Straits <br>That's not our music, it's out of date <br>Demographic stereo <br>They never play the songs we know <br><br>Golden oldies, Rolling Stones, we don't want them back <br>I'd rather jack than Fleetwood Mac <br>No heavy metal, rock'n'roll, music from the past <br>I'd rather jack than Fleetwood Mac <br><br>I'd rather jack, I'd rather jack <br><br>AM, FM, all that jazz <br>We'd rather sing along with Yazz <br>What happened to the radio <br>They never play the songs we know <br><br>Golden oldies, Rolling Stones, we don't want them back <br>I'd rather jack than Fleetwood Mac <br>No heavy metal, rock'n'roll, music from the past <br>I'd rather jack than Fleetwood Mac <br><br>Golden oldies, Rolling Stones, we don't want them back <br>I'd rather jack than Fleetwood Mac <br>No heavy metal, rock'n'roll, music from the past <br>I'd rather jack than Fleetwood Mac <br><br>Golden oldies, Rolling Stones, we don't want them back <br>I'd rather jack than Fleetwood Mac <br>No heavy metal, rock'n'roll, music from the past <br>I'd rather jack than Fleetwood Mac]]></content><category term="The Reynolds Girls" label="The Reynolds Girls"/><category term="I`d Rather Jack (Extended Ver.)" label="I`d Rather Jack (Extended Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/베이식_Basick/그래서_그런가_Feat_비오/</id><title>베이식_Basick - 그래서 그런가 (Feat. 비오) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:50:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:50:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B2%A0%EC%9D%B4%EC%8B%9D_Basick/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%98%EC%84%9C_%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%B0%EA%B0%80_Feat_%EB%B9%84%EC%98%A4/" title="베이식_Basick - 그래서 그런가 (Feat. 비오) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[네 생각 나서 <br>쌀쌀한 건지 <br>쌀쌀해지니까 <br>네 생각이 나는 건지 <br>갑자기 쓸쓸하게 <br>느껴지는 건 <br>그저 단순히 추워진 <br>날씨 때문일까 <br>그렇게 사랑하다 <br>우리가 남이 된 건 <br>내가 널 대했던 <br>방식 때문일까 <br>네가 생각나는 건 <br>바람이 불기 때문일까 <br>널 잊었다 생각함 <br>내가 울기 때문일까 <br>그래서 네 생각을 <br>난 절대 놓지 못해 <br>우는 게 쪽팔려 <br>그러는 건 아닌데 <br>쪽팔린 거는 아냐 절대 <br>너 때문에 찌질해지는 건 <br>괜찮다에 내 모든걸 걸게 <br>취해서 전화를 걸 때 <br>또 어떤 영화를 볼 때 <br>너만 생각나 <br>넌 느껴져 한걸음 멀게 <br>이젠 돌아서 설게 OK <br>그래야만 할 이유는 <br>적어도 열 개 OK <br>그땐 네 수많은 <br>물음표들에 지쳤었지만 <br>지금 난 날 향한 <br>질문들만 외롭게 찾고 있네 <br>홀로 길을 걷다 <br>문득문득 생각나는 건 <br>겨울이라서 그런가 <br>새벽이라서 그런가 <br>찬바람이 불어오면 <br>내가 달려가 <br>꼭 안아주었던 <br>그 겨울처럼 <br>네가 다시 찾아올까 <br>네 생각 나서 <br>쌀쌀한 건지 <br>그래서 그런가 <br>쌀쌀해지니까 <br>네 생각이 나는 건지 <br>그래서 그런가 <br>새벽이라 네 생각 난 건지 <br>그래서 그런가 <br>네 생각 하다 보니 <br>그래서 그런가 <br>새벽이 된 건지 <br>Baby I just wanna go back <br>우리가 하나였던 그때로 <br>그럼 다 네 뜻대로 <br>뭐든 해줄게 다 <br>매일매일이 축제로 <br>비행기도 때마다 <br>태워줄게 국제로 <br>하긴 이게 이제 와서 <br>무슨 의미가 있겠어 <br>너 없이 든 네 생각 <br>죄다 짐이야 <br>네가 했던 말 다 <br>일리가 있던 말 <br>But 내 사랑이 <br>거짓 일리가 없잖아 <br>이별의 기미가 <br>보인걸 몰랐던 건 <br>아니지만 <br>내가 뭔갈 하면 <br>할수록 넌 멀어졌지 <br>내가 생각했던 <br>아픔은 잠깐이지만 <br>나도 거부할 수 <br>없었던 이별의 법칙 <br>네 생각나서 술 마신 건지 <br>술 마시다 보니 <br>네 생각이 나는 건지 <br>널 못 잊어 네 생각 한 건지 <br>네 생각만 하다 보니 <br>널 못 잊는 건지 <br>홀로 길을 걷다 <br>문득문득 생각나는 건 <br>겨울이라서 그런가 <br>새벽이라서 그런가 <br>찬바람이 불어오면 <br>내가 달려가 <br>꼭 안아주었던 <br>그 겨울처럼 <br>네가 다시 찾아올까 <br>계속 I'm okay okay <br>괜찮다고 말해 뭣해 <br>맘속으론 no way no way <br>Cuz you're about fade away <br>다짐은 항상 매일 꼭 해 <br>주문같이 외워 행복해 <br>But 네가 생각이나 재수없게 <br>하지만 더 이상은 못해 <br>I just wanna go back <br>매일같이 네가 <br>생각이나 재수없게 <br>하지만 더 이상은 못해 <br>I just wanna go back <br>To the good old days we had <br>홀로 길을 걷다 <br>문득문득 생각나는 건 <br>너였기 때문에 그랬어 <br>잊지 못해서 그랬어 <br>찬바람이 널 데려와 <br>그 겨울처럼 <br>꼭 안고 싶지만 <br>우리 그때처럼 <br>다시 볼 수는 없을까 <br>네 생각 나서 <br>쌀쌀한 건지 <br>그래서 그런가 <br>쌀쌀해지니까 <br>네 생각이 나는 건지 <br>그래서 그런가 <br>새벽이라 네 생각난 건지 <br>그래서 그런가 <br>네 생각 하다 보니 <br>그래서 그런가 <br>새벽이 된 건지 <br>]]></content><category term="베이식 (Basick)" label="베이식 (Basick)"/><category term="그래서 그런가 (Feat. 비오)" label="그래서 그런가 (Feat. 비오)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이동윤/틈_Inst/</id><title>이동윤 - 틈 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:50:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:50:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%EC%9C%A4/%ED%8B%88_Inst/" title="이동윤 - 틈 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[알고 있었죠 <br>우리 두 사람 사이 <br>언제부턴가 <br>작은 틈이 생겼죠 <br>차가운 바람이 <br>자꾸 스며와 <br>우릴 갈라 놓았죠 <br>조심스럽게 <br>그댈 지켜보면서 <br>내 마음에도 <br>작은 틈이 생겼죠 <br>견딜 수 없이 <br>조여오는 생각이 <br>우릴 멀게만 했죠 <br>누구나 아픈 <br>그런 사랑은 <br>하기 싫어요 <br>멀어진 그 맘 <br>되돌릴 수는 <br>없나요 이젠 <br>사랑할수록 <br>지쳐가는 날 <br>붙잡아줘요 <br>그대만이 나를 <br>살게 하니까 <br>사랑은 항상 <br>나만의 몫이었죠 <br>내가 그대를 <br>더 많이 사랑해서 <br>아프다 너무 <br>버틸 수 없어 <br>눈물로 하룰 보내죠 <br>누구나 아픈 <br>그런 사랑은 <br>하기 싫어요 <br>멀어진 그 맘 <br>되돌릴 수는 <br>없나요 이젠 <br>사랑할수록 <br>지쳐가는 날 <br>붙잡아줘요 <br>그대만이 나를 <br>살게 하니까 <br>왜 나만 아픈건가요 <br>그대란 사람 <br>너무 나빠요 <br>사랑했다는 <br>그런 말은 나 <br>듣기 싫어요 <br>더 좋은 사람 <br>찾아가란 말 <br>하지 말아요 <br>어차피 아픈 <br>그런 사랑을 <br>해야한다면 <br>그대 뒤에서 <br>나 사랑할래요 <br>]]></content><category term="이동윤" label="이동윤"/><category term="틈 (Inst.)" label="틈 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이동윤/틈/</id><title>이동윤 - 틈 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T15:50:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T15:50:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%EC%9C%A4/%ED%8B%88/" title="이동윤 - 틈 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[알고 있었죠 <br>우리 두 사람 사이 <br>언제부턴가 <br>작은 틈이 생겼죠 <br>차가운 바람이 <br>자꾸 스며와 <br>우릴 갈라 놓았죠 <br>조심스럽게 <br>그댈 지켜보면서 <br>내 마음에도 <br>작은 틈이 생겼죠 <br>견딜 수 없이 <br>조여오는 생각이 <br>우릴 멀게만 했죠 <br>누구나 아픈 <br>그런 사랑은 <br>하기 싫어요 <br>멀어진 그 맘 <br>되돌릴 수는 <br>없나요 이젠 <br>사랑할수록 <br>지쳐가는 날 <br>붙잡아줘요 <br>그대만이 나를 <br>살게 하니까 <br>사랑은 항상 <br>나만의 몫이었죠 <br>내가 그대를 <br>더 많이 사랑해서 <br>아프다 너무 <br>버틸 수 없어 <br>눈물로 하룰 보내죠 <br>누구나 아픈 <br>그런 사랑은 <br>하기 싫어요 <br>멀어진 그 맘 <br>되돌릴 수는 <br>없나요 이젠 <br>사랑할수록 <br>지쳐가는 날 <br>붙잡아줘요 <br>그대만이 나를 <br>살게 하니까 <br>왜 나만 아픈건가요 <br>그대란 사람 <br>너무 나빠요 <br>사랑했다는 <br>그런 말은 나 <br>듣기 싫어요 <br>더 좋은 사람 <br>찾아가란 말 <br>하지 말아요 <br>어차피 아픈 <br>그런 사랑을 <br>해야한다면 <br>그대 뒤에서 <br>나 사랑할래요 <br>]]></content><category term="이동윤" label="이동윤"/><category term="틈" label="틈"/></entry></feed>