<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:45:47+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/차라준/별을_쏜다/</id><title>차라준 - 별을 쏜다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:45:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:45:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B0%A8%EB%9D%BC%EC%A4%80/%EB%B3%84%EC%9D%84_%EC%8F%9C%EB%8B%A4/" title="차라준 - 별을 쏜다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 온길 돌아보니 <br>쉼표가 없네 <br>헐떡이며 앞만 보고 <br>달려온 세월 <br>마른날도 궂은 날도 <br>오르막도 내리막도 <br>멈추지 않고 달려 온 거야 <br>성난 파도 몰아칠 땐 <br>두렵기도 했었지만 <br>이왕에 할 것 보란 듯이 <br>파도타기 즐겼고 <br>거센 비바람 불어 올 땐 <br>옷깃을 여몄지만 <br>뺨 위에 눈물 부끄러워 <br>우산 없이 걸었네 <br>후회 없는 지난날들 <br>미련도 없다 <br>세월 한 자락 깔고 누워 <br>나는 또 별을 쏜다 <br>차차 차차 <br>별을 쏜다 <br>내가 온길 돌아보니 <br>쉼표가 없네 <br>헐떡이며 앞만 보고 <br>달려온 세월 <br>마른날도 궂은 날도 <br>오르막도 내리막도 <br>멈추지 않고 달려 온 거야 <br>성난 파도 몰아칠 땐 <br>두렵기도 했었지만 <br>이왕에 할 것 보란 듯이 <br>파도타기 즐겼고 <br>거센 비바람 불어 올 땐 <br>옷깃을 여몄지만 <br>뺨 위에 눈물 부끄러워 <br>우산 없이 걸었네 <br>후회 없는 지난날들 <br>미련도 없다 <br>세월 한 자락 깔고 누워 <br>나는 또 별을 쏜다 <br>별을 쏜다 <br>]]></content><category term="차라준" label="차라준"/><category term="별을 쏜다" label="별을 쏜다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이홍/참사랑/</id><title>이홍 - 참사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:51:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:51:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%99%8D/%EC%B0%B8%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="이홍 - 참사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[풀잎에 서리꽃처럼 <br>하얗게 물들이고 <br>백발이 된 그 모습이 <br>어머님의 일생인가요 <br>이제야 느껴보는 <br>자식이 되니 <br>세상살이 고달픈 날 <br>인고의 세월 같은데 <br>어머님의 참사랑은 <br>높고 높은 하늘 같아라 <br>어여쁜 서리꽃처럼 <br>하얗게 물들이고 <br>백발이 된 그 모습이 <br>어머님의 일생인가요 <br>이제야 느껴보는 <br>자식이 되니 <br>인생살이 고달픈 날 <br>인고의 세월 같은데 <br>어머님의 참사랑은 <br>넓고 넓은 바다 같아라 <br>]]></content><category term="이홍" label="이홍"/><category term="참사랑" label="참사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이홍/어머님의_세월/</id><title>이홍 - 어머님의 세월 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:51:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:51:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%99%8D/%EC%96%B4%EB%A8%B8%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%84%B8%EC%9B%94/" title="이홍 - 어머님의 세월 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꽃처럼 아름다운 <br>청춘도 세월에 지고 <br>바람 같은 우리인생 <br>정처 없는 이 내 발길을 <br>굽이굽이 고비마다 <br>눈물 눈물로 <br>모진세월 견디시고 <br>뒤돌아 보니 <br>청춘은 간 곳이 없네 <br>주름진 얼굴 <br>흰 머리카락 <br>어머님의 세월 인가요 <br>구름에 달 가듯이 <br>젊음도 세월에 가고 <br>강물 같은 우리인생 <br>정처 없는 나그네길을 <br>굽이굽이 고비마다 <br>눈물 눈물로 <br>모진세월 견디시고 <br>뒤돌아 보니 <br>청춘은 간 곳이 없네 <br>주름진 얼굴 <br>흰 머리카락 <br>어머님의 세월 인가요 <br>]]></content><category term="이홍" label="이홍"/><category term="어머님의 세월" label="어머님의 세월"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이홍/당신은_왕비/</id><title>이홍 - 당신은 왕비 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:51:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:51:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%99%8D/%EB%8B%B9%EC%8B%A0%EC%9D%80_%EC%99%95%EB%B9%84/" title="이홍 - 당신은 왕비 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여자는 꽃이니까 <br>이름표만 달아도 <br>한점수 이미 딴 거야 <br>여자는 왕비니까 <br>바람불면 추울까 <br>비가오면 젖을까 <br>내사랑 당신은 왕비 <br>하늘아래 단 한 사람 <br>당신은 내 여자 <br>내사랑 당신은 왕비 <br>이 생명 다 바쳐서 <br>내 인생 모두 걸고 <br>내가 당신 지켜 줄 거야 <br>여자는 꽃이니까 <br>이름표만 달아도 <br>한점수 이미 딴 거야 <br>여자는 왕비니까 <br>바람불면 추울까 <br>비가오면 젖을까 <br>내사랑 당신은 왕비 <br>하늘아래 단 한 사람 <br>당신은 내 여자 <br>내사랑 당신은 왕비 <br>이 생명 다 바쳐서 <br>내 인생 모두 걸고 <br>내가 당신 지켜 줄 거야 <br>이 생명 다 바쳐서 <br>내 인생 모두 걸고 <br>내가 당신 지켜 줄 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="이홍" label="이홍"/><category term="당신은 왕비" label="당신은 왕비"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이홍/백년을_산다해도/</id><title>이홍 - 백년을 산다해도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:51:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:51:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%99%8D/%EB%B0%B1%EB%85%84%EC%9D%84_%EC%82%B0%EB%8B%A4%ED%95%B4%EB%8F%84/" title="이홍 - 백년을 산다해도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세상을 다 준대도 <br>바꿀 수는 없습니다 <br>그 누가 뭐라해도 <br>내 사랑은 당신입니다 <br>백년을 산다해도 <br>몇 천년을 산다해도 <br>나에겐 당신밖에 <br>그 누구도 없습니다 <br>행복해요 난 좋아요 <br>당신이 내곁에 있기에 <br>봄날처럼 화사한 <br>당신의 미소에 <br>내 마음은 녹아 내려요 <br>백년을 산다해도 <br>몇 천년을 산다해도 <br>나에겐 당신밖에 <br>그 누구도 없습니다 <br>행복해요 난 좋아요 <br>당신이 내곁에 있기에 <br>봄날처럼 화사한 <br>당신의 미소에 <br>내 마음은 녹아 내려요 <br>백년을 산다해도 <br>몇 천년을 산다해도 <br>나에겐 당신밖에 <br>그 누구도 없습니다 <br>그 누구도 없습니다 <br>]]></content><category term="이홍" label="이홍"/><category term="백년을 산다해도" label="백년을 산다해도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이홍/사랑이_최고야/</id><title>이홍 - 사랑이 최고야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:51:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:51:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%99%8D/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4_%EC%B5%9C%EA%B3%A0%EC%95%BC/" title="이홍 - 사랑이 최고야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세상살이 인생살이 <br>가는길이 멀고 험해도 <br>사랑 하나만 있으면 되잖아 <br>더 이상은 욕심인거야 <br>쩐은 있다가도 없고 <br>없다가도 있는거 <br>강아지도 안먹는 요물 같은거 <br>욕심 내지마 건강에 해로워 <br>우리 인생 사랑이 최고야 <br>세상살이 인생살이 <br>사랑말고 무얼 더바래 <br>사랑 하나로 살면은 되잖아 <br>그게 바로 행복인거야 <br>쩐은 있다가도 없고 <br>없다가도 있는거 <br>강아지도 안먹는 요물 같은거 <br>욕심 내지마 건강에 해로워 <br>우리 인생 사랑이 최고야 <br>쩐은 있다가도 없고 <br>없다가도 있는거 <br>강아지도 안먹는 요물 같은거 <br>욕심 내지마 건강에 해로워 <br>우리 인생 사랑이 최고야 <br>]]></content><category term="이홍" label="이홍"/><category term="사랑이 최고야" label="사랑이 최고야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/꽤_괜찮은_지도/작은_도시락_With_최윤아/</id><title>꽤 괜찮은 지도 - 작은 도시락 (With 최윤아) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:51:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:51:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%BD%A4_%EA%B4%9C%EC%B0%AE%EC%9D%80_%EC%A7%80%EB%8F%84/%EC%9E%91%EC%9D%80_%EB%8F%84%EC%8B%9C%EB%9D%BD_With_%EC%B5%9C%EC%9C%A4%EC%95%84/" title="꽤 괜찮은 지도 - 작은 도시락 (With 최윤아) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여기 한 아이가 있어 <br>보리떡 다섯 개와 <br>물고기 두 마리를 <br>가지고 있나이다 <br>그러나 그것이 <br>이 많은 사람에게 <br>얼마나 되겠사옵 나이까 <br>요한복음 6절 9절 <br>말씀입니다 <br>그것은 정말 <br>놀라운 일이었습니다 <br>지금껏 들어본 적 없는 <br>눈으로 보고도 믿기 힘든 <br>기적과 같았습니다 <br>아픈 몸을 이끌고 <br>찾아온 사람들은 <br>언제 그랬냐는 듯이 <br>병이 나았습니다 <br>한 마디 말 <br>한 번의 손짓으로 <br>어떤 병이든지 <br>낫게 하는 능력자가 <br>눈앞에 나타났기 때문입니다 <br>더 가까이에서 <br>그 모습을 보고 싶은 마음에 <br>나도 모르게 <br>그 분을 따라 <br>걷기 시작했습니다 <br>어디서든 스스럼없이 <br>사람들을 대하는 모습은 <br>너무도 따듯했고 <br>그분을 둘러싼 주변의 공기는 <br>사랑으로 가득한 것 <br>같았습니다 <br>무언가에 홀린 듯 <br>수많은 사람들이 <br>그분의 뒤를 쫓기 <br>시작했습니다 <br>갈릴리 바다를 건넌 후에도 <br>그 분의 주변은 <br>몰려드는 사람들로 <br>북적 였습니다 <br>날이 저물어 갈 무렵 <br>아무런 준비 없이 <br>그 분을 따라나선 사람들에겐 <br>먹을 것이 전혀 없었습니다 <br>이 많은 사람들의 허기짐을 <br>어떻게 해결할 수 있을지 <br>궁금해 하던 찰나 <br>제자인 빌립 아저씨에게 <br>말씀하시는 <br>그분의 음성이 들려왔습니다 <br>빌립 우리가 <br>이 사람들을 먹일 수 있겠니 <br>그분의 물음에 <br>고심하는 듯한 목소리의 <br>빌립 아저씨가 <br>조심스레 대답했습니다 <br>주님 지금 이곳엔 <br>5천 명도 넘는 <br>사람들이 있습니다 <br>이 사람들을 모두 먹이려면 <br>아무리 조금씩 <br>나누어 준다 해도 <br>이백 데나리온이 넘는 <br>떡이 필요합니다 <br>하지만 이곳엔 <br>아무것도 없어서 <br>어떻게 해야 할지 <br>모르겠습니다 <br>그렇게 많은 양의 떡을 <br>지금 당장 구할 수 없는 건 <br>너무도 당연했습니다 <br>순간 <br>나의 가방 안에 들어 있는 <br>도시락이 생각났습니다 <br>보리떡 다섯 개와 <br>물고기 두 마리 <br>내 작은 도시락에 담긴 음식은 <br>그게 전부였습니다 <br>혼자 먹을 수 있을 정도의 <br>정말 적은 양이었지만 <br>놀라운 일을 행하시는 그분 앞에 <br>내어드리고 싶었습니다 <br>내게도 배고픔이 몰려왔지만 <br>우선은 그분께 <br>모두 드리고 싶었습니다 <br>또 다른 제자인 <br>안드레 아저씨에게 <br>내 마음을 전하며 <br>살며시 도시락을 <br>내밀었습니다 <br>안드레 아저씨는 <br>나의 보리떡 다섯 개와 <br>물고기 두 마리를 <br>예수님께 전해드렸습니다 <br>이후 <br>상상도 못할 일이 <br>벌어졌습니다 <br>삼삼오오 <br>자리에 모여 앉은 <br>사람들 모두가 <br>보리떡과 물고기를 <br>먹게 된 것입니다 <br>내가 드린 <br>보리떡과 물고기를 <br>손에 든 그분이 <br>하나님을 향해 기도하신 이후 <br>순식간에 일어난 일이었습니다 <br>사람들은 <br>자신이 원하는 만큼 <br>배가 부르다고 느껴질 때까지 <br>마음껏 음식을 먹었고 <br>나 역시 <br>보리떡 6개와 <br>물고기 3마리를 먹었습니다 <br>처음 내가 <br>가졌던 것보다 <br>훨씬 더 배부르게 <br>먹을 수 있었습니다 <br>그런데도 <br>음식이 남았고 <br>열 두 바구니에 <br>가득 채워졌습니다 <br>사람들의 얼굴마다 <br>행복한 포만감이 <br>가득했습니다 <br>내게 있던 작은 도시락으로 <br>수많은 사람들이 <br>함께 행복해질 수 있었습니다 <br>그분이 그렇게 <br>놀라운 일을 행하셨기 <br>때문입니다 <br>도대체 <br>그분의 능력은 <br>어디까지인 걸까요 <br>때론 <br>가진 것이 <br>너무 적다고 느껴질 때가 <br>있습니다 <br>그것이 물질이든 <br>시간이든 <br>재능이든 <br>인간관계든 <br>다른 사람과 비교하면 <br>볼품없게 느껴져서 <br>마음까지 작아지는 때가 <br>있습니다 <br>그런데 한편으론 <br>아주 잘 알고 있습니다 <br>하나님께서 내게 주신 건 <br>아주 사소한 것이라도 <br>아주 소중하게 사용될 수 있는 <br>충분한 재료가 된다는 <br>사실입니다 <br>알면서도 불평하고 <br>알면서도 망설였던 마음을 <br>하나님의 은혜로 <br>다시 한 번 다독여봅니다 <br>한 끼의 도시락에 담긴 <br>물고기 두 마리와 <br>보리떡 다섯 개처럼 <br>주어진 하루를 <br>소중하게 <br>받은 은사를 <br>값지게 올려드리길 원합니다 <br>오늘 주님 앞에 내어드리는 <br>나의 작은 헌신과 섬김이 <br>오병이어처럼 드려져서 <br>하나님 나라를 아름답게 하고 <br>하나님을 기쁘시게 하는 일에 <br>쓰임 받게 되기를 <br>수많은 사람들이 <br>배불리 먹을 수 있는 <br>영혼의 양식이 되고 <br>사랑의 통로가 되기를 <br>간절히 소망해봅니다 <br>]]></content><category term="꽤 괜찮은 지도" label="꽤 괜찮은 지도"/><category term="작은 도시락 (With 최윤아)" label="작은 도시락 (With 최윤아)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동요세상/북극곰송/</id><title>동요세상 - 북극곰송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:51:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:51:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81/%EB%B6%81%EA%B7%B9%EA%B3%B0%EC%86%A1/" title="동요세상 - 북극곰송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[북극에서 살고 있는 <br>북극곰은 참 귀여워 <br>무서운 동물이지만 <br>겉모습은 참 예뻐요 <br><br>하얀색의 백곰이 <br>북극에서 놀고 있죠 <br>물고기 잡아 먹어요 <br>물범도 잡아 먹어요 <br><br>북극곰은 추운 날씨에도 안 춥나봐 <br>두꺼운 털이 있어서 <br>하나도 춥지 않대요]]></content><category term="동요세상" label="동요세상"/><category term="북극곰송" label="북극곰송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엘페라/바램_하나/</id><title>엘페라 - 바램 하나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:51:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:51:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%98%ED%8E%98%EB%9D%BC/%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%A8_%ED%95%98%EB%82%98/" title="엘페라 - 바램 하나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[또 그렇게 찾아온 낙엽 <br>소리없이 물들은 추억 <br>수줍게도 두 볼을 <br>붉혀와 파란하늘 <br>너와 함께 안아본다 <br>바램하나 들어보겠소 <br>혼자만의 꿈일진 몰라도 <br>그대에게 기대고 싶구나 <br>기다렸던 선물처럼 <br>유난히도 햇살 밝은 <br>청명한 오늘날 <br>옅은 지저귐도 들려 <br>고요한 마음에 <br>찬란한 태양이 <br>우리의 세상이 <br>태어난 건 즐겨 하는 <br>같은 마음 사람들 <br>참 그늘에 붉은 빛 <br>나무와 함께 가자 <br>우리 가을아 <br>바램 하나 들어보겠소 <br>혼자 만에 꿈일진 몰라도 <br>그대에게 기대고 싶구나 <br>기다렸던 선물처럼 <br>유난히도 햇살 밝은 <br>청명한 오늘날 <br>옅은 지저귐도 들려 <br>고요한 마음에 <br>찬란한 태양이 <br>우리의 세상이 <br>태어난 건 즐겨 하는 <br>같은 마음 사람들 <br>참 그늘에 붉은 빛 <br>나무와 함께 가자 <br>우리 가을아 <br>찬란한 태양이 <br>우리의 세상이 <br>태어난 건 즐겨 하는 <br>같은 마음 사람들 <br>참 그늘에 붉은 빛 <br>나무와 함께 가자 <br>우리 가을아 <br>]]></content><category term="엘페라" label="엘페라"/><category term="바램 하나" label="바램 하나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PLUTO/Record/</id><title>PLUTO - Record - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:51:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:51:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PLUTO/Record/" title="PLUTO - Record - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너로 채우고싶어 <br>하나도 놓치지 않을거야 <br>내 머릿속에 메모리 <br>내 일상이 망가진대도 <br>너와 함께 한다면 <br>어디를 가든 새롭지 <br>하나도 놓치기 싫어 어떻게 <br>그런 표정을 지을 수 있어 넌 <br>걸어가고 있을 뿐인데도 <br>Always be best cut <br>항상 나의 옆에 있어줘 <br>널 담아두고 싶어 <br>넌 내 두눈이 찍은 <br>가장 아름다운 장면 <br>Oh girl i wanna know you <br>내 곁에 두고 너를 <br>알아보고 싶어 baby <br>Yeah all i have is you <br>내게서 널 빼면 아무것도 없어 <br>i need you <br>stand by my side <br>i can't get you out of my mind <br>of my mind <br>i need you <br>stand by my side <br>i can't get you out of my mind <br>of my mind <br>너와 눈을 맞춘다는건 <br>마치 멜로영활 보는것 <br>하루종일 나를 설레게해 <br>너와 눈이 마주칠때 <br>그 눈빛마저 담아두고 <br>계속 떠올리고 싶어 <br>떠올리고 싶어 <br>다음에 또 너를 보기까지 <br>시간이 너무 길어 <br>마음 같아선 지금 <br>미리 꺼내보고 싶어 <br>어제 만난 너가 <br>아직 내눈에는 <br>선명해 so <br>밤새 눈 떠 있어 <br>널 더 보고 싶어서 <br>Oh girl i wanna know you <br>내 곁에 두고 너를 <br>알아보고 싶어 baby <br>Yeah all i have is you <br>내게서 널 빼면 아무것도 없어 <br>i need you <br>stand by my side <br>i can't get you out of my mind <br>of my mind <br>i need you <br>stand by my side <br>i can't get you out of my mind <br>Oh girl i wanna know you <br>내 곁에 두고 너를 <br>알아보고 싶어 <br>Yeah all i have is you <br>내게서 널 빼면 아무것도 <br>]]></content><category term="PLUTO" label="PLUTO"/><category term="Record" label="Record"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이재이/사랑그게_뭐라고/</id><title>이재이 - 사랑..그게 뭐라고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:52:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:52:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%9E%AC%EC%9D%B4/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EA%B7%B8%EA%B2%8C_%EB%AD%90%EB%9D%BC%EA%B3%A0/" title="이재이 - 사랑..그게 뭐라고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그냥 옆에 있어줬잖아 <br>너도 사랑하는 것처럼 <br>내 말다 들어줬잖아 <br>너도 같은 맘인 것처럼 <br>사랑한다 니가 없다 <br>거짓말처럼 사라져 <br>이제 나를 보지 않는다 <br>내가 생각했던 것보다 깊어 <br>니가 없는 매일매일을 울어 <br>내 옆에 니가 없어서 <br>니가 내가 아니라서 <br>철저히 혼자라서 <br>한 번이라도 <br>괜찮냐고 물어주면 <br>이제 그만 돌아와 달라고 <br>부탁이라도 해볼 텐데 <br>너무 멀리 왔나 봐 <br>기억이 없어진 사람처럼 <br>까맣게 다 지워 버린 거니 <br>그냥 좋았다고 했잖아 <br>이젠 그냥 싫어진 거야 <br>매일 같은 날처럼 <br>따뜻하게 안아줬잖아 <br>사랑한다 니가 없다 <br>거짓말처럼 사라져 <br>이제 나를 보지 않는다 <br>내가 생각했던 것보다 깊어 <br>니가 없는 매일매일을 울어 <br>내 옆에 니가 없어서 <br>니가 내가 아니라서 <br>철저히 혼자라서 <br>한 번이라도 <br>괜찮냐고 물어주면 <br>이제 그만 돌아와 달라고 <br>부탁이라도 해볼 텐데 <br>너무 멀리 왔나 봐 <br>기억이 없어진 사람처럼 <br>까맣게 다 지워 버린 거니 <br>내 집을 걸어오는 <br>니 걸음소리 <br>어떻게 어떻게 <br>널 가진데도 다 순간이야 <br>한번이라도 <br>아니라고 말해주면 <br>이제라도 사랑해달라고 <br>부탁이라도 해볼 텐데 <br>너무 멀리 왔나 봐 <br>사랑 그게 그게 다 뭐라고 <br>이렇게 일어나질 못하나 <br>]]></content><category term="이재이" label="이재이"/><category term="사랑..그게 뭐라고" label="사랑..그게 뭐라고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NovaCaine/달_月/</id><title>NovaCaine - 달 (月) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:52:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:52:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NovaCaine/%EB%8B%AC_%E6%9C%88/" title="NovaCaine - 달 (月) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나의 태양은 졌다 <br>나의 빛도 떠났다 <br>이제 나는 어디로 <br>무너진 내 마음은 <br>아직 달을 보는데 <br>이제 나는 어디로 <br>이 고통은 언제까지 날 감싸나 <br>이제 그만 <br>날 떠나가길 <br>부서진 내 마음은 바람에 실려 <br>흘러가네 <br>저 꿈 속으로 <br>나의 태양은 졌다 <br>나의 빛도 떠났다 <br>이제 나는 어디로 <br>무너진 내 마음은 <br>아직 달을 보는데 <br>이제 나는 어디로 <br>이 고통은 언제까지 날 감싸나 <br>이제 그만 <br>날 떠나가길 <br>부서진 내 마음은 바람에 실려 <br>흘러가네 <br>저 꿈 속으로 <br>]]></content><category term="NovaCaine" label="NovaCaine"/><category term="달 (月)" label="달 (月)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/EZEN/미로MAZE/</id><title>EZEN - 미로(MAZE) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:52:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:52:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/EZEN/%EB%AF%B8%EB%A1%9CMAZE/" title="EZEN - 미로(MAZE) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[돌아보면 이 길 위에 <br>나는 없어 <br>남겨왔다 생각했던 <br>흔적도 없어 <br>기다리면 누군가 찾아와 <br>줄 거라 믿었던 날이 <br>의미 없이 버려져 <br>흩어져간걸 알았을 때 <br>눈을 감아보아도 <br>귀를 막아보아도 <br>머릿속에 가득 찬 생각들이 <br>입을 막아 보아도 <br>새어 나올 한숨은 <br>나를 숨 막히게 해 <br>다시 또 제자리에 서있어 <br>다른 길로 가다보면 <br>찾을 거야 <br>Nobody Knows <br>아무도 본적 없는 <br>이 길의 끝을 <br>눈을 감아보아도 <br>귀를 막아보아도 <br>머릿속에 가득 찬 생각들이 <br>입을 막아 보아도 <br>새어 나올 한숨은 <br>나를 숨 막히게 해 <br>다시 또 제자리에 <br>막다른 길에 서서 <br>나를 마주 하네 <br>눈을 감아보아도 <br>귀를 막아보아도 <br>머릿속에 가득 찬 생각들이 <br>입을 막아 보아도 <br>새어 나올 한숨은 <br>나를 숨 막히게 해 <br>다시 또 제자리에 <br>감은 눈을 떠 봐도 <br>막은 귀를 열어도 <br>풀리지 않는 똑같은 질문이 <br>입을 열어 외쳐도 <br>소리 내어 울어도 <br>결국 길을 잃은 난 <br>다시 또 제자리에 서있어 <br>]]></content><category term="EZEN" label="EZEN"/><category term="미로(MAZE)" label="미로(MAZE)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucas__Steve/Calling_On_You_Feat_Jake_Reese/</id><title>Lucas &amp; Steve - Calling On You (Feat. Jake Reese) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:52:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:52:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucas__Steve/Calling_On_You_Feat_Jake_Reese/" title="Lucas &amp; Steve - Calling On You (Feat. Jake Reese) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll have a good, good time when I need ya <br>Because I know you need me too <br>And everybody's looking for something <br>But when I'm lost I'm calling on you <br><br>Calling on you, you, you, you, you, you <br>Calling on you <br>Calling on you <br>Calling on you <br>But when I'm lost I'm calling <br>I'm lost I'm calling on you <br>You, you <br><br>I'll have a good, good time when I need ya <br>Because I know you need me too <br>And everybody's looking for something <br>But when I'm lost I'm calling on you <br>I'll have a good, good time when I need ya <br>Because I know you need me too <br>And everybody's looking for something <br>But when I'm lost I'm calling on you <br><br>Calling on you, you, you, you, you, you <br>But when I'm lost I'm calling <br>I'm lost I'm calling on you <br>Calling on you <br>Calling on you <br>But when I'm lost I'm calling <br>I'm lost I'm calling on you <br>You, you <br>Calling on you, you, you <br>Calling on you, you <br>But when I'm lost I'm calling <br>I'm lost I'm calling on you]]></content><category term="Lucas &amp; Steve" label="Lucas &amp; Steve"/><category term="Calling On You (Feat. Jake Reese)" label="Calling On You (Feat. Jake Reese)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/허가람/겨울_빛/</id><title>허가람 - 겨울 빛 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:52:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:52:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%88%EA%B0%80%EB%9E%8C/%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8_%EB%B9%9B/" title="허가람 - 겨울 빛 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[겨울이 다가오네 <br>아픔도 같이오네 <br>마음이 시려오네 <br>겨울만 앞서가네 <br>사랑은 뒤쳐지네 <br>기억이 떠나가네 <br>나 혼자 되지 않기를 <br>나 홀로 남지 않기를 <br>저 하늘 너머로부터 <br>내 길을 비추는 <br>희망의 빛 있어 <br>저 바다 끝에서부터 <br>내 맘을 비추는 <br>희망의 빛있어 <br>한 발짝 다가가네 <br>그러다 물러서네 <br>보이지 않는 앞이 <br>무서워서 <br>손을 내밀어보네 <br>머릴 흔들어보네 <br>내가 서 있는 길이 <br>아닐까봐 <br>나 혼자 되지 않기를 <br>나 홀로 남지 않기를 <br>저 하늘 너머로부터 <br>내 길을 비추는 <br>희망의 빛있어 <br>저 바다 끝에서부터 <br>내 맘을 비추는 <br>희망의 빛있어 <br>저 하늘 너머로부터 <br>내 길을 비추는 <br>희망의 빛있어 <br>저 바다 끝에서부터 <br>내 맘을 비추는 <br>희망의 빛있어 <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>ah ah ah ah ah <br>저 하늘 너머로부터 <br>내 길을 비추는 <br>희망의 빛있어 <br>저 바다 끝에서부터 <br>내 맘을 비추는 <br>희망의 빛있어 <br>저 하늘 너머로부터 <br>내 길을 비추는 <br>희망의 빛있어 <br>저 바다 끝에서부터 <br>내 맘을 비추는 <br>희망의 빛있어 <br>]]></content><category term="허가람" label="허가람"/><category term="겨울 빛" label="겨울 빛"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/4ROSE/블랙리스트/</id><title>4ROSE - 블랙리스트 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:52:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:52:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/4ROSE/%EB%B8%94%EB%9E%99%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/" title="4ROSE - 블랙리스트 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[양아치들 <br>그렇게 아니라더니 어쩌니 <br>블랙리스트는 안 만들었고 <br>적군리스트를 만들었어 <br>대박 소름 <br>전쟁 나가냐 <br>염병 발병의 종류도 <br>다양해 진짜 창조적이네ㅎ <br>적군이 뭐냐 적군이 <br>얼씨구 지금이 <br>독재시대도 아니고 <br>모르쇠로 가믄 <br>다 덮혀질 줄 알았지 <br>진짜 왕 뻔뻔 <br>한대 맞자 <br>최악질 <br>저 쓰레기 두 개를 <br>빨리 구치소에 버려라 <br>말세다 말세 나라 꼬라지가 <br>과연 국정원과 <br>문체부만 있을까나 <br>]]></content><category term="4ROSE" label="4ROSE"/><category term="블랙리스트" label="블랙리스트"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/영차/유기/</id><title>영차 - 유기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:53:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:53:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%81%EC%B0%A8/%EC%9C%A0%EA%B8%B0/" title="영차 - 유기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[정해줘 내 안에 널 바꿀 시간을 <br>멍해져 화조차 못 내고 <br>기다렸던 너 <br>정해줘 내 안에 널 바꿀 시간을 <br>멍해져 화조차 못 내고 <br>기다렸던 너 <br>그늘이 지는 오후 시간은 <br>더디 가고 <br>술래 없는 숨바꼭질은 지쳐가죠 <br>매일 다르게 생기는 그림자도 <br>누워있기만 해 너무 피곤하죠 <br>습관이 되어버린 공간에 <br>설렘이 없다 해도 행복하네 <br>되 내이는 건 오직 너 하나 때문 <br>유혹이 괴롭혀도 난 지독하게 <br>흐르는 듯 하지만 <br>정해진 것은 방향뿐 <br>차례가 없어서 <br>포화돼버린 마음은 <br>털어놓을 곳 없는 <br>휴지통의 운명처럼 <br>넘치는 감정을 비우지 <br>못하고 썩혀버려 <br>쉬지 못하는 심장을 <br>욕할 수도 없고 <br>쉴 수 밖에 없는 숨은 <br>참을 수가 없어 <br>그래도 웃을 수만 있다면 <br>인내해볼게 네가 <br>변할 수만 있다면 <br>정해줘 내 안에 널 바꿀 시간을 <br>멍해져 화조차 못 내고 <br>기다렸던 너 <br>정해줘 내 안에 널 바꿀 시간을 <br>멍해져 화조차 못 내고 <br>기다렸던 너 <br>많이 다르다는 걸 알고 있다는 건 <br>양보해야 하는 상황이 많다는 것 <br>나를 포기하지만 널 위하니까 <br>다투다가도 그래 그러니까 미안 <br>먼저 다가가기만 수백 번이지 <br>그래 봤자 멀어지고 <br>있기 때문인지 <br>관계의 줄이 단단히 당겨져 있어 <br>끌려가는 느낌은 착각일 뿐 인지 <br>입과 눈이 대칭을 이루고 <br>알 수 없는 사과하는 <br>네가 나를 본다 <br>그게 여기까지 나를 <br>데려온 이유고 <br>떨어질까 무서웠던 <br>따뜻해진 손 놓아 <br>모르겠어 <br>뭔가 들킨 듯이 도망치는 듯이 <br>돌아선 잔상이 멈춰 <br>마지막인 듯이 <br>내가 눈치 없어서 <br>이해 못하겠는데 <br>여기서 기다리라고 <br>한 것만 같은데 <br>정해줘 내 안에 널 바꿀 시간을 <br>멍해져 화조차 못 내고 <br>기다렸던 너 <br>정해줘 내 안에 널 바꿀 시간을 <br>멍해져 화조차 못 내고 <br>기다렸던 너 <br>이럴 거면 왜 그랬어 <br>새끼손가락 왜 걸었어 <br>처음처럼 왜 웃었어 <br>내 모든걸 왜 가졌어 <br>진짜 너를 왜 보였어 <br>이름은 또 왜 써놨어 <br>내 입에 미소 왜 그렸어 <br>심장에 널 왜 새겼어 <br>설명할 수 없잖아 <br>딱 하나 아니라면 <br>알고 싶지도 않아 <br>진실이 그거라면 <br>왜 내가 잡을 때 멈추는 척 했니 <br>왜 내가 잡을 때 멈추지 않았니 <br>정해줘 내 안에 널 바꿀 시간을 <br>멍해져 화조차 못 내고 <br>기다렸던 너 <br>정해줘 내 안에 널 바꿀 시간을 <br>멍해져 화조차 못 내고 <br>기다렸던 너 <br>]]></content><category term="영차" label="영차"/><category term="유기" label="유기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/새터데이/바람_겨울/</id><title>새터데이 - 바람, 겨울 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:53:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:53:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%83%88%ED%84%B0%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4/%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C_%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8/" title="새터데이 - 바람, 겨울 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대는 기억할까 우리 만나 <br>처음 인사 나눈 그때가 난 생각나 <br>그냥 스쳐가는 사람 중에 하나 <br>그냥 스쳐가는 바람 같은 만남 <br>그렇게 끝났으면 좋았을걸 <br>그게 다였으면 <br>그걸로 끝이었으면 <br>촌스러운 말이라 <br>욕할지 모르겠다만 <br>시간이 지날수록 <br>내 안의 그대는 커져갔어 <br>오랜 시간 동안 <br>함께 한 건 아니고 <br>그렇게 많은 얘길 <br>나눈 것도 아니지만 <br>그대를 보내야만 <br>하는 게 날 멍하게 해 <br>이리 큰 자리를 <br>차지하면 난 어떻게 해 <br>곁에 있는 걸로 만족했어 <br>그대의 얼굴 손 눈동잘 <br>바라볼 때 마다 언젠가 <br>내게 오길 꿈꿨어 <br>하지만 그대 대신 내겐 <br>이별이 왔어 <br>그대를 너무나 아끼고 싶지만 <br>곁에 머물고 싶었지만 <br>그대와 나는 겨울바람처럼 <br>아프지만 지나쳐 가는 거야 <br>그대를 너무나 원하고 있지만 <br>우린 절대로 안 되는 거야 <br>그대와 나는 슬픈 영화처럼 <br>괴롭지만 외면해야 해 <br>혼자만의 사랑이란 걸 <br>나도 잘 알아 <br>하지만 그댄 내게 <br>행복을 가져다 준 사람이니까 <br>나도 그대에게 <br>의미 있는 사람이기를 <br>기억이 아닌 <br>추억으로 남겨지기를 <br>바라기만 할 뿐야 내 욕심이야 <br>난 그대에게 아무것도 <br>아니었을 거란 걸 <br>나도 알아 살을 베는 <br>이 계절의 바람 그 끝은 <br>우리가 스쳐가는 <br>인연일 뿐이라고 <br>그래야만 하는데 <br>마음 같지가 않네 <br>사람들이 내게 궁상맞다 해 <br>30분만에 먹은 밥도 <br>뱃 속에 3시간은 있는데 <br>이리 오래 담아둔 <br>사람을 어떻게 쉽게 버리래 <br>그래 그러고 보니 <br>그래서 보내는 건데 <br>그대도 맘에 담아둔 <br>사람이 있는 건데 <br>그 사람이 이미 곁에 있는데 <br>그래 내가 궁상 맞은 것 맞네 <br>좋은 데서 같이 <br>밥을 먹고 싶었어 <br>좋은 선물을 안겨줄 <br>기념일을 원했어 <br>하지만 이 모든 걸 <br>네게 해줄 사람이 이미 있어 <br>너의 곁에 내 자리는 없어 <br>좋은 데서 같이 <br>밥을 먹고 싶었어 <br>좋은 선물을 안겨줄 <br>기념일을 원했어 <br>하지만 이 모든 걸 <br>네게 해줄 사람이 이미 있어 <br>너의 곁에 내 자리는 없어 <br>그대를 너무나 아끼고 싶지만 <br>곁에 머물고 싶었지만 <br>그대와 나는 겨울바람처럼 <br>아프지만 지나쳐 가는 거야 <br>그대를 너무나 원하고 있지만 <br>우린 절대로 안 되는 거야 <br>그대와 나는 슬픈 영화처럼 <br>괴롭지만 외면해야 해 <br>죽을 만큼 싫지만 <br>이제 끝을 맺으려 해 <br>나는 아프겠지만 <br>넌 몰랐으면 해 <br>너의 행복이 내 행복이니까 <br>나는 이제 너를 지울게 <br>죽을 만큼 싫지만 <br>이제 끝을 맺으려 해 <br>혼자 이러는 것도 <br>넌 싫어할 게 뻔해 <br>난 없으니까 <br>우린 없던 사랑이니까 <br>그저 이렇게 스쳐갈게 <br>죽을 만큼 싫지만 <br>이제 끝을 맺으려 해 <br>나는 아프겠지만 넌 몰랐으면 해 <br>너의 행복이 내 행복이니까 <br>나는 이제 너를 지울게 <br>죽을 만큼 싫지만 <br>이제 끝을 맺으려 해 <br>혼자 이러는 것도 <br>넌 싫어할 게 뻔해 <br>난 없으니까 <br>우린 없던 사랑이니까 <br>그저 이렇게 스쳐갈게 <br>]]></content><category term="새터데이" label="새터데이"/><category term="바람, 겨울" label="바람, 겨울"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김아름/솔로맨스/</id><title>김아름 - 솔로맨스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:53:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:53:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%95%84%EB%A6%84/%EC%86%94%EB%A1%9C%EB%A7%A8%EC%8A%A4/" title="김아름 - 솔로맨스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[누가 돌 던졌니 내 가슴에 <br>잔잔하던 마음이 <br>소용돌이 같아 <br>네가 내 인생에 들어와 <br>엉망이 돼버렸어 이렇게 <br>더 이상은 나도 몰라 <br>참을 수가 없는 걸 <br>니가 없는 건 <br>도대체 왜 너는 뭐야 <br>이렇게 나를 <br>들었다 놨다 하는 넌 뭐니 <br>하루가 시작되면 햇살은 다시 <br>반짝이고 있어 내 맘을 흔들어 <br>바람이 불어오면 생각나듯이 <br>오늘은 뭐하니 무슨 약속 있니 <br>썼다가 지웠다가 또 쓰고 <br>하루에도 몇 번씩이나 고백해 <br>이런 내 맘을 너도 알고 있는지 <br>아니면 나 혼자만의 착각이니 <br>네 앞에만 서면 내 가슴이 <br>작아지는 것 같아 <br>가뜩이나 작은데 <br>Oh no no no <br>쳐다보지마 <br>가슴 뛰는 내 맘 <br>들킬까 조마조마해 <br>더 이상은 나도 몰라 <br>참을 수가 없는 걸 <br>니가 없는 건 <br>도대체 왜 너는 뭐야 <br>이렇게 나를 <br>들었다 놨다 하는 넌 뭐니 <br>하루가 시작되면 햇살은 다시 <br>반짝이고 있어 내 맘을 흔들어 <br>바람이 불어오면 생각나듯이 <br>오늘은 뭐하니 무슨 약속 있니 <br>오 어지러워 널 볼 때 마다 <br>가슴이 터질 것 같아 <br>이런 좋은 느낌 사랑인가 봐 <br>하루가 시작되면 햇살은 다시 <br>반짝이고 있어 내 맘을 흔들어 <br>바람이 불어오면 생각나듯이 <br>오늘은 뭐하니 무슨 약속 있니 <br>썼다가 지웠다가 또 쓰고 <br>하루에도 몇 번씩이나 고백해 <br>이런 내 맘을 너도 알고 있는지 <br>아니면 나 혼자만의 착각이니 <br>고백해줄래 <br>썼다가 지웠다가 또 쓰고 <br>하루에도 몇 번씩이나 고백해 <br>이런 내 맘을 너도 알고 있는지 <br>아니면 나 혼자만의 착각이니 <br>]]></content><category term="김아름" label="김아름"/><category term="솔로맨스" label="솔로맨스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Palson_팔선/내이름_김순영_Feat_김민경/</id><title>Palson (팔선) - 내이름 김순영 (Feat. 김민경) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:53:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:53:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Palson_%ED%8C%94%EC%84%A0/%EB%82%B4%EC%9D%B4%EB%A6%84_%EA%B9%80%EC%88%9C%EC%98%81_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EB%AF%BC%EA%B2%BD/" title="Palson (팔선) - 내이름 김순영 (Feat. 김민경) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여자로 여자로 태어나 <br>누군가의 여자로 살다가 <br>빛나던 젊음주고 <br>엄마가 되었네 <br>후회없이 세월에 날 묶었네 <br>누구의 엄마로 살다가 <br>누군가의 여자로 살다가 <br>낯설은 이름하나 <br>써보게 되었네 <br>빛나게 예쁘던 내 이름 <br>오늘은 내생에 <br>가장 어리고 예쁜날 <br>왼쪽 가슴에 이름표 달고 <br>가버린 세월아 <br>넌 그냥 가거라 <br>나는 오늘 좀 예뻐야겠다 <br>예전에 빛나던 내이름 <br>오늘 더 빛나게 불러본다 <br>긴세월 꾹꾹꾹 눌러쓴 <br>빛나는 내이름 <br>김순영입니다 <br>여자로 사랑을 받았나 <br>자식들도 바르게 자랐나 <br>살면서 넘의 인생 <br>부러워 했었나 <br>흔들리며 세월속에 있었나 <br>감출수 없었던 세월이 <br>내 얼굴에 깊숙이 사무쳐 <br>변한건 얼굴하나 <br>그리고 또하나 <br>빛나게 예뻐진 내 이름 <br>오늘은 내생에 <br>가장 어리고 예쁜날 <br>왼쪽 가슴에 이름표 달고 <br>가버린 세월아 <br>넌 그냥 가거라 <br>나는 오늘 좀 예뻐야겠다 <br>예전에 빛나던 내이름 <br>오늘 더 빛나게 불러본다 <br>긴세월 꾹꾹꾹 <br>눌러쓴 빛나는 <br>내이름 김순영입니다 <br>빛나는 내이름 <br>김순영입니다 <br>]]></content><category term="Palson (팔선)" label="Palson (팔선)"/><category term="내이름 김순영 (Feat. 김민경)" label="내이름 김순영 (Feat. 김민경)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bandana/Bombon_Feat_Wisin/</id><title>Bandana - Bombon (Feat. Wisin) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:55:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:55:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bandana/Bombon_Feat_Wisin/" title="Bandana - Bombon (Feat. Wisin) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yo quiero tu amor bombon tu amor <br>Yo quiero tu amor bombon tu amor <br>Yo quiero tu amor yo quiero tu amor <br>Ah ah ah ah <br>Yo quiero tu amor bombon tu amor <br>Yo quiero tu amor bombon tu amor <br>Yo quiero tu amor yo quiero tu amor <br>Ah ah ah ah <br>Muestrame suelta tu cuerpo <br>Y mueve tus pies <br>Solo sigueme y sabras como es <br>Y si me bailas me rindo a tu encanto <br>Te miro y no aguanto <br>Y esta vez <br>Deja que tu cuerpo piense <br>con los pies <br>Y esta vez <br>Baila hasta con la luna ya ves <br>Y esta vez <br>Algo entre los dos se va a encender <br>Y esta vez <br>Ah ah ah ah <br>Yo quiero tu amor bombon tu amor <br>Yo quiero tu amor bombon tu amor <br>Yo quiero tu amor yo quiero tu amor <br>Ah ah ah ah <br>Yo quiero tu amor bombon tu amor <br>Yo quiero tu amor bombon tu amor <br>Yo quiero tu amor yo quiero tu amor <br>Ah ah ah ah <br>Muestrame suelta tu cuerpo <br>Y mueve tus pies <br>Solo sigueme y sabras como es <br>Y si me bailas me rindo a tu encanto <br>Te miro y no aguanto <br>Y esta vez <br>Deja que tu cuerpo piense <br>con los pies <br>Y esta vez <br>Baila hasta con la luna ya ves <br>Y esta vez <br>Algo entre los dos se va a encender <br>Y esta vez <br>Argentina y Puerto Rico <br>W Bandana <br>Este ritmo corre por toda <br>tu piel bandolera <br>Ella sabe que conmigo <br>puede hacer lo que quiera <br>Baby yo soy tuyo dime que tu esperas <br>W <br>Ella me baila otra vez <br>Y se formo el sal pa' fuera <br>Ando con Bandana partysiando <br>Toda la semana <br>Tres capitanas vestidas de gala <br>Tienen el truco <br>una sorpresa preparada <br>Hoy el party nadie se va <br>Hasta por la madrugada <br>Todo el mundo bailando <br>esta calentando <br>El ritmo le envuelve <br>se sigue pegando <br>La copa en la mano <br>mi mami sigue matando <br>Dale guayando <br>conmigo perreando <br>Dale no pares baby <br>Dale no pares baby <br>Yo soy el tuyo <br>tu eres la mia <br>Mi fantasia bailar hasta el otro dia <br>Bandana <br>Porque yo quiero que lo bailes <br>Porque yo quiero que lo bailes <br>Porque la noche ya esta comenzando <br>Y tu ritmo sensual me esta matando <br>Y esta vez <br>deja que tu cuerpo <br>Piense con los pies <br>Uhhhhhhh <br>Baila hasta con la luna ya ves <br>Porque yo quiero que lo Bailes <br>Porque yo quiero que lo Bailes <br>Y esta vez <br>Au au au oh <br>Yo quiero tu amor bombon tu amor <br>Yo quiero tu amor bombon tu amor <br>Yo quiero tu amor yo quiero tu amor <br>Ah ah ah ah <br>Yo quiero tu amor bombon tu amor <br>Yo quiero tu amor bombon tu amor <br>Yo quiero tu amor yo quiero tu amor <br>Ah ah ah ah <br>Yo quiero tu amor <br>Yo quiero tu amor bombon tu amor <br>]]></content><category term="Bandana" label="Bandana"/><category term="Bombon (Feat. Wisin)" label="Bombon (Feat. Wisin)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LA/Wind/</id><title>L.A. - Wind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:55:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:55:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LA/Wind/" title="L.A. - Wind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If the wind don't blow or the wind is blowing <br>If the lights go out or the lights are shinning <br>If the clocks are stopped or the clocks are ticking <br><br>Are we moving fast Are we moving forward <br><br>Even if the lights go out <br>And the clocks just stop <br>Even if the wind don't blow <br>I'm coming <br><br>Saw the people crying other people running <br>There is so much pain outside it's burning <br>Please don't be afraid I will be always with you <br>Please don't be afraid I will be always with you <br><br>Even if the lights go out <br>And the clocks just stop <br>Even if the wind don't blow <br>I'm coming <br><br>Are we moving fast <br>Are we moving slow <br>Keep your eyes wide shut <br>I'm coming home <br><br>Even if the lights go out <br>And the clocks just stop <br>Even if the wind don't blow <br>I'm coming <br><br>Are we moving fast <br>Are we moving slow <br>Keep your eyes wide shut <br>I'm coming home]]></content><category term="L.A." label="L.A."/><category term="Wind" label="Wind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/dePresno/See_You_Soon/</id><title>dePresno - See You Soon - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:55:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:55:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/dePresno/See_You_Soon/" title="dePresno - See You Soon - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fall knocked on our door <br>We'd been counting days for months <br>And now you're close to gone <br>I hope you packed some sun <br>She was heading east <br>Beyond the safe <br>and sound surroundings <br>we call home <br>Into the unknown <br>Treat me like you'll see me soon <br>Treat me like you'll see me soon <br>'Cause if you don't <br>I swear <br>I'll even miss you now <br>when you are here <br>'Cause if you don't <br>I swear <br>I'll even miss you now <br>when you are here <br>Don't waste your precious tears <br>Save them for a time you miss me <br>more than words can tell <br>And not on this farewell <br>Dont you worry now <br>'Cause when you're back <br>it'll be as if you never left <br>You know I won't forget <br>Treat me like you'll see me soon <br>Treat me like you'll see me soon <br>'Cause if you don't <br>I swear <br>I'll even miss you now <br>when you are here <br>'Cause if you don't <br>I swear <br>I'll even miss you now <br>when you are here <br>I'll be I'll be <br>Counting down to you <br>I want months to feel like days <br>I'll be I'll be <br>Counting down to you <br>I want months to feel like days <br>If we both met our troubles halfway <br>Wouldn't we cry in the middle <br>I'd rather see you smile <br>I'd rather say goodbye <br>And treat you like I'll see you soon <br>And treat you like I'll see you soon <br>'Cause if I don't <br>I swear <br>I'll even miss you now <br>when you are here <br>'Cause if I don't <br>I swear <br>I'll even miss you now <br>when you are here <br>I'll be I'll be <br>Counting down to you <br>I want months to feel like days <br>I'll be I'll be <br>Counting down to you <br>I want months to feel like days <br>Counting down to you <br>Counting down to you <br>]]></content><category term="dePresno" label="dePresno"/><category term="See You Soon" label="See You Soon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Life_Of_Dillon/Sex_For_Breakfast/</id><title>Life Of Dillon - Sex For Breakfast - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:55:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:55:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Life_Of_Dillon/Sex_For_Breakfast/" title="Life Of Dillon - Sex For Breakfast - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I ordered sex for breakfast <br>Texting all my exes <br>On some Kanye West shit <br>Good morning <br>I don't worry 'bout tomorrow <br>Still drinking from the bottle <br>I know my time is borrowed <br>I spend it all right now hey <br>I don't have a lot of feelings <br>I ain't living for the weekend <br>No I ain't waiting <br>for the evening <br>I want it all right now <br>I ordered sex for breakfast <br>Texting all my exes <br>On some Kanye West shit <br>Good morning <br>Me Myself and Molly <br>Surfing on that body <br>Roll one for the Marley no worry <br>I get so high <br>I'm friends with Jesus <br>So you don't you drag me <br>down to hell <br>When I wake up I can't believe it <br>Life's far as good as I can tell <br>You say I got a problem <br>Baby I ain't trying to solve them <br>I started from the bottom <br>And I'm up right now yeah <br>I like to go where they know me <br>Where I ain't never feeling lonely <br>Forget about the old me <br>'Cause I'm on right now <br>I ordered sex for breakfast <br>Texting all my exes <br>On some Kanye West shit <br>Good morning <br>Me Myself and Molly <br>Surfing on that body <br>Roll one for the Marley no worry <br>I get so high I'm friends with Jesus <br>So you don't you drag me down to hell <br>When I wake up I can't believe it <br>Life's far as good as I can tell <br>If you want it you got it <br>You wake me up like coffee <br>Swear it feels just like college <br>So be on your way <br>If you want it you got it <br>You wake me up like coffee <br>Swear it feels just like college <br>So be on your way <br>I ordered sex for breakfast <br>Texting all my exes <br>On some Kanye West shit <br>Good morning <br>I get so high I'm friends with Jesus <br>So you don't you drag me down to hell <br>When I wake up I can't believe it <br>Life's far as good as I can tell <br>]]></content><category term="Life Of Dillon" label="Life Of Dillon"/><category term="Sex For Breakfast" label="Sex For Breakfast"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/2_Chainz/Good_Drank_Feat_Gucci_Mane__Quavo/</id><title>2 Chainz - Good Drank (Feat. Gucci Mane &amp; Quavo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:55:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:55:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/2_Chainz/Good_Drank_Feat_Gucci_Mane__Quavo/" title="2 Chainz - Good Drank (Feat. Gucci Mane &amp; Quavo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Uhh, alright <br>I did it, hahah, yeah <br><br>Used to treat my mattress like the ATM, yeah <br>Bond number 9 that's my favorite scent, yeah <br>Can't forget the kush, I'm talking OG, yeah <br>Rest in peace to pop, he was an OG, oh yeah <br>285 I had that pack on me, uh <br>I cannot forget I had that strap on me, yeah <br>Rest in peace to my nigga Doe TRU <br>All we ever want to do is ball <br>That was the easy part, we playing that Weezy hard <br>We sit in the kitchen late, we tryna to make an escape <br>Trying to make me a mil, so I'mma keep me a plate <br>I told 'em shawty can leave, so I'mma keep me a rake <br>So I'mma keep me a Wraith, my jewelry look like a lake <br>Today I'm in the Maybach <br>And that car came with some drapes <br>You know I look like a safe, I put you back in your place <br>I look you right in your face, sing to your bitch like I'm Drake <br>Yeah <br><br>Good drank, big knots <br>Good drugs, I put a four on the rocks lean <br>Drop top, no hot box <br>12 tried to pull me over, pink slips to the cops <br>She said the molly give her thizz face <br>Put the dick in her rib cage <br>Whips out, Kunta Kinte <br>Diamonds clear like Bombay <br>Take your babies, no Harambe <br>Play with keys like Doc Dre <br>3K like Andre <br>And your girl, call her come face <br><br>It's Gucci <br>Your trunk in the front <br>Well check this out my top in the trunk <br>You play with my money <br>Then check this out your pop in the trunk <br>Three mil in a month <br>But I just did three years on a bunk <br>Oh, you in a slump <br>I'm headed to Oakland like Kevin Da Runt <br>What is your point <br>Square with the stamp, fuck Kevin Durant <br>Lay on on my trap <br>Play with my cap and I'll knock off your hat <br>I'm taking the cheese and killing the rats <br>Gucci Mane, call me the cat with the racks <br>I'm swervin', but I'm in back of the 'Bach <br>I'm Persian, man I got hoes from Iraq <br>I'm servin' I pay a bird for that <br>He nervous, I ain't got no word for that <br>He hurt and want all of his purses back <br>He mixing the syrup with the Percocets <br>She perfect and she got perky breasts <br>I just want some of that turkey neck <br>Trapper of the year, I'm from Bouldercrest <br>You snitch of the year cause you told the best <br><br>Good drank, big knots <br>Good drugs, I put a four on the rocks <br>Drop top, no hot box <br>12 tried to pull me over, pink slips to the cops <br>She said the molly give her thizz face <br>Put the dick in her rib cage <br>Whips out Kunta Kinte <br>Diamonds clear like Bombay <br>Take your babies, no Harambe <br>Play with keys like Doc Dre <br>3K like Andre <br>And your girl, call her cum face <br><br>Aye, Mike Dean <br>This shit hard as fuck, bruh <br>You a living legend, I appreciate that <br>Aye, Guwop, I'm glad you home, cuz <br>Quavo, you already know man <br>You got next on these niggas double salute man <br>True shit, 2 Chainz <br>Hair Weave Killer <br>Daniel Son, the Necklace Don <br>Chapo Jr <br>I mean, I can go on for days]]></content><category term="2 Chainz" label="2 Chainz"/><category term="Good Drank (Feat. Gucci Mane &amp; Quavo)" label="Good Drank (Feat. Gucci Mane &amp; Quavo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alaa/Black__Gold_Feat_Kodie/</id><title>Alaa - Black &amp; Gold (Feat. Kodie) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:55:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:55:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alaa/Black__Gold_Feat_Kodie/" title="Alaa - Black &amp; Gold (Feat. Kodie) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[my black and gold Tee <br>so fitting with my black and gold sneaks <br>my black and gold jeans <br>good lookin' in my black and gold sleeves <br>Im a top dawg <br>roll up in the club turnt up, get it in like a rockstar <br>dressed to kill, sex appeal <br>filled with thrill, top of the hill, fo real <br>men in black and gold <br>suited up so fly, yeah that's the code <br>red carpet swagger, strike a pose <br>that's right lights, camera, action, go <br>it's all about the good vibes <br>me and my squad <br>be having good times <br>rockin the black and gold, yeah we fly <br>put it on instagram and lets shine <br>let the beat ride <br><br>I got it on my mind <br>on my mind <br>filling my head <br>got it with me all the time <br>all the time <br>wear it <br>'cause the world is looking up on me <br>yeah ah ay, yeah ah ay <br>my black and gold is what they see <br>yeah ah ey, yeah ah ey <br><br>my black and gold chain <br>my hat, my black and gold shades <br>my black and gold ring <br>I love my black and gold things <br>I wont deny it, Im an all nighter <br>everybody party with me <br>Stockholm, Miami, let's go overseas <br>then to to Ibiza, follow my lead let's go <br>Women in black n gold <br>so fly we own the fashion show <br>my crew, we international <br>on top of the world, Im at the throne <br>it's all about the good vibes <br>me and my squad <br>be having good times <br>rockin the black and gold, yeah we fly <br>put it on instagram and lets shine <br>let the beat ride <br><br>I got it on my mind, filling my head <br>got it with me all the time <br>the world is looking up on me <br>my black and gold, my black and gold]]></content><category term="Alaa" label="Alaa"/><category term="Black &amp; Gold (Feat. Kodie)" label="Black &amp; Gold (Feat. Kodie)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Circa_Waves/Wake_Up_Acoustic/</id><title>Circa Waves - Wake Up (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:55:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:55:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Circa_Waves/Wake_Up_Acoustic/" title="Circa Waves - Wake Up (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So, coming, tryna break my fall <br>Leaving, spitting sticks and stones <br>And I lay awake I don't know <br>This room will lead me to an open door <br><br>But it's alright, cause I can't wait to see the trouble here tonight <br><br>And so wake up, it's just a little too late for conversations <br>It's just a bit too much doubt for me to make up <br>But you'll give it all that you got now, give it all that you got now, give it all <br><br>Slow, I feel ya, wrapping round my bones, I call ya but you're never home <br>And am I a fool I don't know And see me see the way the silver talks <br><br>But it's alright, cause I can't wait to see the trouble here tonight <br><br>And so wake up, it's just a little too late for conversations <br>It's just a bit too much doubt for me to make up <br>But you'll give it all that you got now, give it all that you got now, give it all that you got now <br>You should give it all <br><br>And so wake up, it's just a little too late for conversations <br>It's just a bit too much doubt for me to make up <br>But you'll give it all that you got now, give it all that you got now, give it all]]></content><category term="Circa Waves" label="Circa Waves"/><category term="Wake Up (Acoustic)" label="Wake Up (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Muna/Crying_On_The_Bathroom_Floor/</id><title>Muna - Crying On The Bathroom Floor - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:56:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:56:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Muna/Crying_On_The_Bathroom_Floor/" title="Muna - Crying On The Bathroom Floor - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Give me that diamond ring <br>Give me that love <br>on the movie screen <br>And I won't feel a thing <br>Promise I won't feel a thing <br>Give me that kiss goodnight <br>Give me that gold tell me <br>it's alright <br>And I won't feel a thing <br>Promise I won't feel a thing <br>And I guess that I got rewired <br>'Cause you're cold as ice <br>but it feels like fire fire fire fire <br>And the drugs don't work <br>and I don't know why <br>But when you hurt me I go higher <br>higher higher higher <br>But when I'm crying <br>on the bathroom floor <br>Tearing off the dress I wore I wonder <br>If I could never ask for more <br>If I'm never gonna <br>ask for more from a lover <br>Crying on the bathroom floor <br>Tearing off the dress I wore I wonder <br>If I could never ask for more <br>If I'm never gonna <br>ask for more from a lover <br>Give me your disrespect <br>Give me your pain and loneliness <br>And I'll love you the best <br>Promise I'll love you the best <br>Give me no peace of mind <br>Give me distress give me <br>all your lies <br>And I'll love you for life <br>Promise I'll love you 'til I die <br>But I'm crying <br>on the bathroom floor <br>Give me some more <br>Tearing off the dress I wore I wonder <br>If I could ever ask for more <br>Would you give me some more <br>If I'm never gonna <br>ask for more from a lover <br>Crying on the bathroom floor <br>Give me some more <br>Tearing off the dress I wore I wonder <br>If I could never ask for more <br>Would you give me some more <br>If I'm never gonna <br>ask for more from a lover <br>It's asking a lot of myself <br>I'm asking a lot of myself <br>It's taking a lot out of me <br>loving you <br>It's taking a lot out of me <br>loving you <br>Asking a lot of myself <br>I'm asking a lot of myself <br>It's taking a lot out of me <br>loving you <br>There isn't a lot that <br>I think I can do <br>I'm crying on the bathroom floor <br>Tearing off the dress I wore I wonder <br>If I could ever ask for more <br>Would you give me some more <br>If I'm never gonna <br>ask for more from a lover <br>Crying on the bathroom floor <br>Give me some more <br>Tearing off the dress I wore I wonder <br>If I could never ask for more <br>Would you give me some more <br>If I'm never gonna <br>ask for more from a lover <br>]]></content><category term="Muna" label="Muna"/><category term="Crying On The Bathroom Floor" label="Crying On The Bathroom Floor"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sofi_Tukker/Johny/</id><title>Sofi Tukker - Johny - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:56:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:56:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sofi_Tukker/Johny/" title="Sofi Tukker - Johny - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Johny esta me ouvindo <br>Sim, sim, claro <br>tua mae e eu perdoamos <br>ja perdoamos <br>eu disse perdoamos <br>isso acontece <br>claro acontece a qualquer um <br>eu disse qualquer um e to anyone <br>e claro tudo perdoado <br>Johny do you do you do you <br>Johny can you hear me <br>Johny]]></content><category term="Sofi Tukker" label="Sofi Tukker"/><category term="Johny" label="Johny"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tom_Chaplin/Still_Waiting_Acoustic/</id><title>Tom Chaplin - Still Waiting (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:56:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:56:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tom_Chaplin/Still_Waiting_Acoustic/" title="Tom Chaplin - Still Waiting (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Buried in the rubble <br>There's a boy in trouble <br>Reaching for a piece of the sky <br>Clawing at the wreckage <br>Sending out a message <br>Dying to get back to the light <br><br>Lost in time <br>Long forgotten, hung forever <br>On the line <br>Still waiting behind <br><br>Still waiting <br>Forever left to wonder why <br>Still waiting <br>In truth I know that really I'm <br>Still out there <br>Still waiting <br>A wandering ghost forevermore <br>Still out there <br>Still waiting <br>I feel like I've been here before <br><br>I had never reckoned <br>Ever coming second <br>Stretching to get over the line <br>But I'm all in pieces <br>Sick as all my secrets <br>Still know how they weigh on my mind <br><br>Lost in time <br>Long forgotten, hung forever <br>On the line <br>Still waiting behind <br><br>Still waiting <br>Forever left to wonder why <br>Still waiting <br>In truth I know that really I'm <br>Still out there <br>Still waiting <br>A wandering ghost forevermore <br>Still out there <br>Still waiting <br>I feel like I've been here before <br><br>Phantoms in the shadows howl <br>To devils on the edge of town <br>Passing through the city walls <br>Dancing down the hollow halls <br>Vultures in the inky haze <br>Circle where my body lays <br>I've got to get a message out <br>Pull me from the wreckage now <br><br>Still waiting <br>Forever left to wonder why <br>Still waiting <br>In truth I know that really I'm <br>Still out there <br>Still waiting <br>A wandering ghost forevermore <br>Still out there <br>Still waiting <br>I feel like I've been here before]]></content><category term="Tom Chaplin" label="Tom Chaplin"/><category term="Still Waiting (Acoustic)" label="Still Waiting (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Ink/No_Slack/</id><title>Kid Ink - No Slack - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:57:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:57:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Ink/No_Slack/" title="Kid Ink - No Slack - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I made history <br>you told that <br>Realest shit I wrote <br>in my notepad <br>Ain't left 'bout the game <br>nigga no stats <br>Cut the cheque <br>no I don't cut 'em no slack <br>Put that shit on wax <br>you know 'bout the grind <br>I put in work in that overtime <br>Pocketin' that 9 <br>clock that Audi 9 <br>Cut the motherfuckin' cheque <br>get to shoppin' now <br>Here we go again <br>smoke up 'til the sunny sky <br>I ain't been to sleep <br>since the other night <br>My baby know I'm always <br>late to supper times <br>So she leave it in the stove <br>with the oven light on <br>Keep it warm for a nigga <br>'til I'm back home <br>Put it to my mouth <br>like a saxophone <br>Black phone <br>text on the Samsung <br>And the realest shit <br>I wrote was a ransom <br>Young <br>handsome nigga <br>with a hand full of money <br>I blow it baby <br>if you bust a dance move <br>Drive my tyre in Miami Vice <br>on a boat <br>Blazin' no tyres <br>no buttons <br>just my tattoos <br>How I'm feelin' <br>play like I invented <br>I brought the old me <br>back for new beginnings <br>Where we from now <br>make it to my lifespan <br>And you could blame <br>my daddy <br>if I'm actin' light skinned <br>I made history <br>you told that <br>Realest shit I wrote <br>in my notepad <br>Ain't left 'bout the game <br>nigga no stats <br>Cut the cheque <br>no I don't cut 'em no slack <br>My ambitions in designer <br>Dolce and Gabanna <br>All this courtesy champagne <br>while I'm shoppin' <br>Got a nigga thrown <br>I'm 'bout buy the whole store <br>In the dressin' room <br>bitch keep peakin' <br>through the door <br>Bathroom break <br>prolly' sneakin' <br>geekin' on the low <br>Skiin' through the slopes <br>one thing is for sure <br>You ain't gotta say yes <br>if I offer you the drugs <br>I'm a bad influence <br>but I'm better than I was <br>baby <br>Used to hit the dirty money <br>with the slugs <br>Now I walk over the road <br>big show in the club <br>baby <br>My mama tell me <br>never fear no one <br>Grab the blunt by the neck <br>and I chokeslam <br>Might show up to the beach <br>with my own sand <br>I brought the whole thing <br>and these hoes in <br>Kurt Cobain <br>you know where the shot go <br>I just need a refill <br>I'm tryna reload <br>I made history <br>you told that <br>Realest shit I wrote <br>in my notepad <br>Ain't left 'bout the game <br>nigga no stats <br>Cut the cheque <br>no I don't cut 'em no slack <br>Realest shit I wrote <br>in my notepad <br>]]></content><category term="Kid Ink" label="Kid Ink"/><category term="No Slack" label="No Slack"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/uberLAB/Aisha/</id><title>uberLAB - Aisha - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:57:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:57:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/uberLAB/Aisha/" title="uberLAB - Aisha - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I saw you <br>Again <br>I knew just where you'd be <br>I'll stop this real soon <br>when you're back safe with me <br>In pictures <br>I'd see it <br>you weren't really there <br>In truth <br>I still feel it hanging in the air <br>When you come home <br>I'll stop this <br>When you come home <br>I'll hide it good <br>I'll never cry again <br>When you come home to me <br>In pictures <br>I'd see it <br>you weren't really there <br>In truth <br>I still feel it hanging in the air <br>When you come home <br>I'll stop this <br>When you come home <br>I'll hide it good <br>I'll never cry again <br>When you come home to me <br>to me <br>to me <br>to me <br>]]></content><category term="uberLAB" label="uberLAB"/><category term="Aisha" label="Aisha"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Firewind/Back_On_The_Throne/</id><title>Firewind - Back On The Throne - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:57:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:57:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Firewind/Back_On_The_Throne/" title="Firewind - Back On The Throne - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[He has always been defiant <br>And he's gotta take control <br>No sympathy or kindness <br>In hos blackened empty soul <br><br>His legions set the pace <br>Marching onward to the west <br>So he looms behind the silence <br>Let all his minions do their best <br><br>They're shooting straight for the heart <br>And wanna tear us apart <br>They're gonna cut to the bone <br>It's gonna take some time to put you back on the throne <br>On the throne <br>Back on the throne <br>On the throne <br><br>Sailing right into destruction <br>Then defeated by his foe <br>Gotta find a way to fall back <br>But there's nowhere left to go <br><br>The trumpets sound retreat <br>But it just too late for some <br>And the man behind the failure <br>Soon will greet his kingdom come <br><br>They're shooting straight for the heart <br>And wanna tear us apart <br>They're gonna cut to the bone <br>It's gonna take some time to put you back on the throne <br>On the throne <br>On the throne <br>On the throne <br><br>Back on the throne <br>On the throne <br><br>Straight for the heart <br>They tear us apart <br>They cut to the bone <br>It's gonna take some time to put you back on the throne]]></content><category term="Firewind" label="Firewind"/><category term="Back On The Throne" label="Back On The Throne"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Firewind/Hands_Of_Time/</id><title>Firewind - Hands Of Time - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:57:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:57:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Firewind/Hands_Of_Time/" title="Firewind - Hands Of Time - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Rage and fire in me <br>Turns a boy into a soldier <br>There's no wrong or right in the fight <br>For we do as we are told <br><br>Years went by and and I became <br>A king to lead this land to fame <br>Deep inside I feel the power <br>When it's over, it's over <br><br>And the fear inside us <br>Will never divide us all <br>For united we'll never fall <br>We will never know the future <br>We will only know the past <br>For an instant there'll be sorrow in their eyes <br><br>There'll be no one to surrender <br>And our numbers are fading fast <br>Victory will not rewind the hands of time <br><br>In the southern sea <br>Vicious strikes on the water <br>No bridge left to cross <br>We'll destroy everything you leave behind <br><br>All in my head and out of my mind <br>I'm keeping the faith with forces allied <br>If there's a chance I'll make someone pay the price <br>But the war's not over <br><br>And the fear inside us <br>Will never divide us all <br>For united well never fall <br><br>We will never know the future <br>We will only know the past <br>For an instant there'll be sorrow in their eyes <br><br>There'll be no one to surrender <br>And our numbers are fading fast <br>Victory will not rewind the hands of time <br><br>We will never know the future <br>We will only know the past <br>For an instant there'll be sorrow in their eyes <br><br>There'll be no one to surrender <br>And our numbers are fading fast <br>Victory will not rewind the hands of time <br><br>Hands of time <br>Victory]]></content><category term="Firewind" label="Firewind"/><category term="Hands Of Time" label="Hands Of Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastille/Blame_Bunker_Sessions/</id><title>Bastille - Blame (Bunker Sessions) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:57:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:57:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastille/Blame_Bunker_Sessions/" title="Bastille - Blame (Bunker Sessions) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You go sleep with the fishes <br>There's no room for you here <br>There's no room for you here <br>Wrap your teeth around the pavement <br>Cause your body's a message <br>Send my regards to hell <br>Fall upon your knees <br>Sing This is my body and soul here <br>Crawl and beg and plead <br>Sing You've got the <br>power and control <br>Don't pin it all on me <br>Don't pin it all on me <br>You've been granted three wishes <br>Say goodbye to your mother <br>your father your son <br>I can hear your pulse <br>racing from here <br>Sitting next to this gun <br>beats your heart in your mouth <br>Fall upon your knees <br>Sing This is my body and soul here <br>Crawl and beg and plead <br>Sing You've got the <br>power and control <br>Don't pin it all on me <br>Don't pin it all on me <br>Oh blame blame blame <br>Oh blame blame blame <br>Oh blame blame blame <br>I got you I got you <br>Oh blame blame blame <br>Fall upon your knees <br>Sing This is my body and soul here <br>Crawl and beg and plead <br>Sing You've got the <br>power and control here <br>This is my body this is my soul <br>Fall upon your knees <br>Sing This is my body and soul <br>Don't pin it all on me <br>Don't pin it all on me <br>]]></content><category term="Bastille" label="Bastille"/><category term="Blame (Bunker Sessions)" label="Blame (Bunker Sessions)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Luxury_Vintage_Rap/</id><title>Nick Grant - Luxury Vintage Rap - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:57:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:57:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Luxury_Vintage_Rap/" title="Nick Grant - Luxury Vintage Rap - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All you rap niggas running in place <br>Nothing to say you such a disgrace <br>I don't want it easy baby, it's the love of the chase <br>Life's a wet dream niggas a kill you and come to your wake <br>My demeanor fly Benny Medina high as Chris Tucker's eyes <br>When watching Al Greene but the game changed they cross dress <br>Rim offset I'm a dog marrying me Miss Lady is farfetched <br>Run Simmons leathers the MC never lost <br>I'm cut from Biggie's Coogi sweater cloth <br>X marks the spot I pray we never cross <br>Drug dealer thoughts inspired by Raw Report <br>Unruly Italian Cut suits I'm such a mulli <br>Ferrari with the bubble booty never hug a groupie <br>Francis Ford dope enough I'm a seduction movie <br>Quick to bust like when a baby clutch an uzi <br><br>I don't believe the devil came as a snake <br>Why would he come as something you naturally hate <br>I got fine taste Get it <br>Why wait Shooter keep the 30 like a 9 5 break <br>Shit get ugly as Strange <br>Diamonds shine on my Bitch call it a blind date <br>Everything is high stakes <br>Can't wait to get the Rollie with the wide face <br>I'ma call it Moesha <br>I ain't doing features nigga <br>Triple beam dream these dope fiends get lit <br>I never compromise my integrity for a hit <br>My story rag and rich <br>But funny how when I got the money I never fell off <br>Give my ring a kiss <br>Don Shit Keyante sip basking in the ambiance <br>Listen and get insomnia <br>Her top left me hanging like a top of palm tree slop me up <br>In and out her like a robbery bruh <br><br>High fashion <br>I'm the newest king of all these rappers <br>Go head and make a list of who's the wackest <br>You ran rapid, little one hit wonders were average <br>That hoe called fame shit you can have her <br>Pure nigga vernacular <br>Benz backing up ball player swagger huh <br>Got to stay in tune I'm looney it's just my character <br>I go deep in Japanese denim with a freak <br>English don't speak any <br>I made It by the skin if my teeth celebration call it off <br>nah Not tonight no good words for me <br>I ain't even got a vice <br>Rob the game we got paper to blow <br>Niggas hate who they relate to the most <br>I don't get it <br>I'm a star you'll need forever to reach Nick <br>Grimm Reaper flirting I can feel death in each kiss <br>John Lennon vintage no cheap shit you weak shit <br>Sugar on the kit that's a sweet lick <br><br>Fuck 'em All]]></content><category term="Nick Grant" label="Nick Grant"/><category term="Luxury Vintage Rap" label="Luxury Vintage Rap"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Return_of_the_Cool_Feat_B_Hess/</id><title>Nick Grant - Return of the Cool (Feat. B. Hess) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:57:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:57:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Return_of_the_Cool_Feat_B_Hess/" title="Nick Grant - Return of the Cool (Feat. B. Hess) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>Uh <br>Here's to the competition, I'm killing you <br>Here to save the game, it's a miracle <br>Moet Chandon Imperial <br>The nigga who had nothin', now they screamin', I'm feelin' you <br>She wanna be everywhere that the life's at <br>Ballers, Nicholson's, spikes at <br>Never ran train, but I'm on the right track <br>Kick game like Tina fighting the nigga Ike back <br>Wow, a night on the town <br>Money talk, bullshit can hike you a mile <br>Confidence is dripping, somebody wipe up the isle <br>I bet a hotel, like the whitest of towels <br>What was life as a child <br>Even then I was premature with the pen, then niggas bited the style <br>Tom Ford linen, sinning, she's grinning <br>Shoe game like my rap lines, they don't get em <br>Lipstick staining the glass, pure finish <br>Flow like a thing of the past, so vintage <br>Baby don't fight it, you just gotta go with it <br>Ain't nothing for sale, I just put my soul in it <br>You gotta love it, I'm moving too fast you need to speed up <br>Girl, your body the dopest, I'm tryna re up <br>Yeah we came from the bottom, but nigga we up <br>The cool niggas is back to turn the heat up <br><br>Cuff links, strong drinks <br>You see I'm fly through the tint, babe <br>Chauffeur, backseat <br>I hope I don't spill the champagne <br>Roll up, not me <br>I get high off the life, babe <br>Once lost, but its back again, baby <br>It's the return of the cool, baby <br>The return of the cool baby, baby <br>It's the return of the cool, baby yeah <br>The return of the cool oh yeah, oh yeah yeah <br><br>Uh, cool nigga, I'm here to break the monotony <br>It ain't the real shit if its not me <br>Her painted on jeans like a Basquiat piece <br>I'm slick, Gordon Gekko meets artiste <br>At the top, you niggas should never doubt him <br>The young knight still sipping out the Youth Fountain <br>Ain't no bad days, but the Bentley grill poutin' <br>I own shit, my cologne switch every outing <br>Ten fold, give po po no info <br>Clean up nice, get fresh like Mento's <br>Bet them hoe go wherever the wind blow <br>Them wrongdoing come back true, ten fold <br>Karma is a must, suit fitting like a mob boss <br>See the tux, broads in a rush <br>To get a nigga home, she just caught up in the lust <br>Send a bottle over compliments of us, back to catch wreck <br>All respect to those who break they neck to keep they hoes in check <br>Cause oh they Sweat a nigga like Keith first LP <br>Ain't shit that a broke nigga tell me <br>Heaven on Earth, I can make Hell cease <br>My line up be sharp 'nuff to cut keys <br>Nigga please, square feet, kick my feet up <br>Oh yeah, the cool niggas is back to turn the heat up <br><br>Cuff links, strong drinks <br>You see I'm fly through the tint, babe <br>Chauffeur, backseat <br>I hope I don't spill the champagne <br>Roll up, not me <br>I get high off the life, babe <br>Once lost, but its back again, baby <br>It's the return of the cool, baby <br>The return of the cool baby, baby <br>It's the return of the cool, baby yeah <br>The return of the cool oh yeah, oh yeah yeah]]></content><category term="Nick Grant" label="Nick Grant"/><category term="Return of the Cool (Feat. B. Hess)" label="Return of the Cool (Feat. B. Hess)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Get_Down_Poonana/</id><title>Nick Grant - Get Down (Poonana) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:57:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:57:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Get_Down_Poonana/" title="Nick Grant - Get Down (Poonana) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I'm in the spot man they know who I be <br>Do it cause I love it not for notoriety <br>Never was a fad shit I'm super sonic <br>All my bitches bad gotta go exotic <br>Hard in the paint man I been the wildest <br>All about the green like I'm on a diet <br>Nothing funny know the money thicker than Maliah <br>Man I'm like a stick of dyna mite baby hype baby never was a liar <br>I can see the future everything designer <br>Let me hit the poonana a premadonna <br>Gotta keep it real with you its a thing of honor <br>bounce <br><br>You gone get searched <br>Shake that shit, DAMN <br><br>Something they could never be <br>Hot enough to fill the devil up with jealousy <br>Little model lady you gone be the death of me <br>Beautiful, personality on Della Reese <br>You mean to me, but you love me, love me heavily <br>Got a nigga out here tryna cuff you like a felony <br>That divine timing, bring the fine china <br>Cause eating cat is a delicacy <br>Seeing through you like when girls use to rock the jellies on their feet <br>You'll never wanna leave, atomic dog but I am never on a leash <br>The flow Mona Lisa go hard my nigga you hear the things she telling me <br>DAMN <br><br>You gone get searched <br>Shake that shit, DAMN <br><br>Niggas mad cause they ain't hot as befo' <br>Sleeping on a clown nigga I'm so tired of the jokes <br>Your lady running to the wood like a knock at the door <br>Girl you making up your story did you powder your nose <br>She get dick on the run and I get vagina to go <br>You can keep the cry from the baby monitor though <br>I don't need it, freak if he don't fuck ya then ya leaving <br>Believe it, guess the nigga slacking like a deacon <br>Jumping off the deep end, tell em I'm anemic <br>Its a cold world when the iron ain't on you can't reach it <br>Life decent, her pussy ripe, tighter than lime squeezes she freaky church <br><br>You gone get searched <br>Shake that shit, DAMN]]></content><category term="Nick Grant" label="Nick Grant"/><category term="Get Down (Poonana)" label="Get Down (Poonana)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Get_Up_Feat_WatchTheDuck/</id><title>Nick Grant - Get Up (Feat. WatchTheDuck) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:57:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:57:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Get_Up_Feat_WatchTheDuck/" title="Nick Grant - Get Up (Feat. WatchTheDuck) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I come to get down <br>Everybody get up <br>Yea, don't fight the vibe when it hit you <br>Do it 'til ya get you enough <br>I said get up, why you sitting get up <br>Yea, don't fight the vibe when it hit you <br>Do it 'til ya get you enough <br><br>Uh, yeah, shakin' what your momma gave ya <br>You got the act right, I should nominate ya <br>You know you a star, keep shining baby <br>Girl I put the house on you and accommodate ya <br>Tell em I'm a dance machine <br>I only pay attention you should dance for free <br>I could show you things that you can't believe <br>We should play together come and join the band with me <br>Hot damn, going Tina Turner on em <br>Got the place lit, you the furnace on her <br>Girl you drive me crazy, keep the swervin' on em <br>Blood on the dance floor need an organ donor <br>Put your left foot in take your right foot out <br>Money making money making what it's all about <br>If you're giving me the number should I call you now <br>Fly brother but I need the gravity cause I come to get down <br><br>I come to get down <br>Everybody get up <br>Yea, don't fight the vibe when it hit you <br>Do it 'til ya get you enough <br>I said get up, why you sitting get up <br>Yea, don't fight the vibe when it hit you <br>Do it 'til ya get you enough <br><br>Uh yea, shake it like Beyonce <br>Girl you know you're thicker than some pound cake <br>Love it when you mo move it all around babe <br>Up and down up and down like a sound wave <br>Uh preach, church on the move <br>Two step till ya feet hurt in them shoes <br>Dance away the pain it ain't hurtin' ya groove <br>He a baller but he ain't James worthy of you <br>I ain't judging baby you know Ima love ya <br>Daddy say ya good for me and my momma love ya <br>Yea they hatin' on ya <br>That's so common of em <br>Make it hot for me, fresh up out the oven <br>But uh, you turn me into uh, newer me <br>I know you wish you had two of me <br>Lowkey baby you a beast <br>Whoopty whoop super freak <br><br>I come to get down <br>Everybody get up <br>Yea, don't fight the vibe when it hit you <br>Do it 'til ya get you enough <br>I said get up, why you sitting get up <br>Yea, don't fight the vibe when it hit you <br>Do it 'til ya get you enough <br><br>Uh, either love em or leave em <br>Let loose, I don't think I believe you <br>Make it hot you got me running a fever <br>Kick game like I'm a product of FIFA <br>Play on playa <br>Spray on Cologne baby I'm on the way up <br>Girl you got that good loving its hard to break up <br>But you want me 'cause I'm in when you call we lay up <br>I'm on my way up to get down <br><br>I come to get down <br>Everybody get up <br>Yea, don't fight the vibe when it hit you <br>Do it 'til ya get you enough <br>I said get up, why you sitting get up <br>Yea, don't fight the vibe when it hit you <br>Do it 'til ya get you enough <br>I come to get down <br>Everybody get up <br>Yea, don't fight the vibe when it hit you <br>Do it 'til ya get you enough <br>I said get up, why you sitting get up <br>Yea, don't fight the vibe when it hit you <br>Do it 'til ya get you enough]]></content><category term="Nick Grant" label="Nick Grant"/><category term="Get Up (Feat. WatchTheDuck)" label="Get Up (Feat. WatchTheDuck)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/PPIPP_Feat_Miloh_Smith/</id><title>Nick Grant - PPIPP (Feat. Miloh Smith) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:58:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:58:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/PPIPP_Feat_Miloh_Smith/" title="Nick Grant - PPIPP (Feat. Miloh Smith) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>Uh, let's get it <br>Classy, but nasty <br>Thumb all in her ass cheeks <br>Move fastly <br>Sinning while we listening to this Al Green <br>So glad we, touchin' <br>I fuck you like you had bad week <br>80's baby, wavy <br>You'll think I'm hailing a taxi <br>Correction, I'm so wavy <br>This should be sponsored by Max B <br>The black Leo DiCaprio, tuxedo, Great Gatsby, exactly <br><br>I'm coming home again <br>Baby don't forget the rose and gin <br>You gon' have to play this song again <br>Oooh 'cause it's on again, it's on <br>Oh, I'm coming home again <br>Baby don't forget the rose and gin <br>You gon' have to play this song again <br>Oooh 'cause it's on again, it's on on <br>It's on on <br>It's on on <br><br>We'll alright <br>The wonderful sounds that you are listening to <br>Are being brought to you by the beautiful people of Culture Republic <br>Where dreams come true, ya' dig that <br>It's 'bout time we bring the real back <br>One of a kind, so soulful <br>I have the ever so talented Miloh Smith with me ladies and gentlemen <br>You know it only gets better <br>I understand you got a little devil in you baby but <br>To not agree with us would be a sin <br>Sit back and enjoy the show <br>Don't forget the rose and gin <br>This is The Return of the Cool <br>Let me hear that back]]></content><category term="Nick Grant" label="Nick Grant"/><category term="PPIPP (Feat. Miloh Smith)" label="PPIPP (Feat. Miloh Smith)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Gotta_Be_More_Feat_BJ_The_Chicago_Kid/</id><title>Nick Grant - Gotta Be More (Feat. BJ The Chicago Kid) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:58:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:58:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Gotta_Be_More_Feat_BJ_The_Chicago_Kid/" title="Nick Grant - Gotta Be More (Feat. BJ The Chicago Kid) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Niggas ain't been rapping lately, guess I'm trapped in the 80s <br>Ain't fly enough if the fashion statements don't make you hate me <br>Looking up to drug czars, same ones who sold my mother raw <br>Die quick as the culture if we don't evolve <br>Could never hide the scars I'm from where pistols bark like a pit of dogs, nigga shit gets hard <br>Thirsty bitches even wanna sips the tears from dons <br>Rich rap skin black as Norman Lear sitcoms <br>Diamonds looking pissed on, picking bitches like I'm Frankie Lemon nigga which one <br>Pray my niggas live long, no time for silly rappers and they too lame cliques <br>For the record we deeper than a Wu Tang hit <br>My drive took me out the ghetto found a new lane quick <br>At any moment they gone hit me with that you changed shit uh <br>More honesty than Richard Pryor comedy, I don't know where I'ma be when Obama leave <br>gotta be more, more, more <br><br>Said theres gotta be more yeah baby <br>Said theres gotta be more, more than what we see <br>More is what we gotta be yeah <br><br>I'm Gil Scott Heron, here to give America a dose of their own medicine <br>Who I ain't better than, you should watch who bet against <br>Expose hearts of jealous men, predator felon mama's bestie molested them <br>Killers vanish cause feds tamper with evidence, long as the souls wealthy we cool cause we were never rich <br>Sweat me like fed pressure, was left for dead, sorry I'm misleading miss lady all I wanted was head <br>Sipping wine imported, my rhyme style is gorgeous, bout my money this is worst than Sally Mae extortion <br>Don't know whats real its like I'm looking through the eyes of orphans <br>The newest Benz turning like some disappointed corpses <br>Old head stories of how they was the shit in their day <br>The world bleeds menstral shows get tickets today <br>Two hundred on a car dash with a trunkful of Ye' <br>Life's good no more reruns of minimum wage <br>Gotta Be More <br><br>Said theres gotta be more yeah baby <br>Said theres gotta be more, more than what we see <br>More is what we gotta be yeah <br><br>Still could pull a model with no dollar to my name <br>A nation in debt and here we are begging for change <br>All for nothing another brother slained <br>Death is a tough exchange, Trump even running game <br>All aboard the coon train clown samba painted faces you frontin' <br>So embarrassing tap dancin' for whitey gets you nothing <br>But a penny for your thoughts, if all times are good do you know who you really are <br>I need the bad times adversity gets you far, this verse is a ki of raw <br>Babies die young remember you via the project walls <br>My generation needs a Redd Foxx a Lena Horne <br>Feel like I'm the one to put us on top where we belong uhh <br>Walking Fred Hampton agenda I'm too attentive, my shit is poison to these rap pretenders <br>Who swear they trap but never seen a pack this epidemic of twisting facts <br>Still we celebrate your backwards image, it gotta be more]]></content><category term="Nick Grant" label="Nick Grant"/><category term="Gotta Be More (Feat. BJ The Chicago Kid)" label="Gotta Be More (Feat. BJ The Chicago Kid)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/The_Sing_Along_Feat_Ricco_Barrino/</id><title>Nick Grant - The Sing Along (Feat. Ricco Barrino) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:58:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:58:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/The_Sing_Along_Feat_Ricco_Barrino/" title="Nick Grant - The Sing Along (Feat. Ricco Barrino) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Got me moving slow as a love ballad <br>All up in the club she like all her thugs tatted <br>As the radio plays return of the drug addict <br>Mama youngin was raised they taught me that love matters <br>I can see all your flaws, hiding them not at all <br>Niggas reaching new heights then shortly they fallin off <br>Michael I'm off the wall, typical art of war <br>Everybody's the plug but none you niggas in charge <br>Criminal still at large, fatal just kill em off <br>Niggas is closed minded the label should get involved <br>Bitches cheating on you, ain't no lovin' on the menu <br>Now she with the other nigga like you with the hotter single <br>Mama got another favorite, daddy disappointed in you <br>And they came to get the caddy, how you gettin to the venue <br>Need of revenue, please never let em Jerry Heller you <br>As the regret screams, I pray that the weed settles you <br>Nothing is worse than having it and then losing it <br>The hunger starts fading and then you become cool with it <br>Overnight pjs to coach class stewardess <br>Nothing change I can smell vh1 moving in <br>I'm the one you should ask for <br>It's all the same song what you spinning it back for <br>I swear your last record should've been your last choice <br>Shit is looking like radio made the trap star <br>The sing along <br><br>Niggas talk about keys and we sing along <br>Preach <br>Niggas talk about bitches and we sing along <br>Ohh Preach <br>Everything codeine, and ya bankroll mean <br>Nigga I'm sleep <br>You didn't even sell your soul it was free <br>It's like you got the same shit on repeat <br>Niggas talk about keys and we sing along <br>Preach <br>Niggas talk about bitches and we sing along <br>Ohh Preach <br>Everything codeine, and ya bankroll mean <br>Nigga I'm sleep <br>You didn't even sell your soul it was free <br>It's like you got the same shit on repeat <br><br>Ima sight for blind eyes, ribbon in sky <br>Vision 20 20 nobody gifted as I <br>Gotta take care your people my nigga sit and divide <br>Gotta be bout the love and only spit when inspired <br>Lyrical genocide, forever immortalized <br>Numb to the fame, never succumb to the corporate ties <br>Rappers are borderline, stuck in a normal mind <br>I kill em all and lay em in front as the organ cries <br>I'm alive pay your tax never let a comma slide <br>Crazy like lookin In damas eyes <br>If I say it all they plotting on my demise <br>Phenomenon, I'm a god <br>I arrived in all black nigga cause they don't follow the format <br>Of raw rap, tell me what the fuck do you call that <br>Quiet nigga better believe I'm bout all that <br>They all whack <br>It gets worse cause the niggas that we love gave you niggas a hall pass <br>Same song and we all dance <br>Why you dropping the ball uhh, another dark cloud on a poor black <br>Brother trying to make it so I gotta support the sing along <br><br>Niggas talk about keys and we sing along <br>Preach <br>Niggas talk about bitches and we sing along <br>Ohh Preach <br>Everything codeine, and ya bankroll mean <br>Nigga I'm sleep <br>You didn't even sell your soul it was free <br>It's like you got the same shit on repeat <br>Niggas talk about keys and we sing along <br>Preach <br>Niggas talk about bitches and we sing along <br>Ohh Preach <br>Everything codeine, and ya bankroll mean <br>Nigga I'm sleep <br>You didn't even sell your soul it was free <br>It's like you got the same shit on repeat]]></content><category term="Nick Grant" label="Nick Grant"/><category term="The Sing Along (Feat. Ricco Barrino)" label="The Sing Along (Feat. Ricco Barrino)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/All_of_You_Feat_B_Hess/</id><title>Nick Grant - All of You (Feat. B. Hess) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:58:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:58:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/All_of_You_Feat_B_Hess/" title="Nick Grant - All of You (Feat. B. Hess) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Girl you gon think I'm from Jersey <br>I want your name and number <br>I hit you from behind <br>Like niggas tryna jump ya <br>Ask you no to judge me <br>I guess that's my guilty conscience <br>You love me then you hate me <br>That's organized destruction <br>Girl open wide and bust it <br>You talking to me nasty <br>God said keep it classy <br>But heaven marked you absent <br>You make my heart beat faster <br>I pray the bras are strapless <br>I put my whiskers down under <br>Thank God I ain't get cat fished <br>Beauty and the Bastard my movie needs an actress <br>Your nigga play you over <br>How he abuse a classic <br>The irony in that shit <br>You finding me attractive <br>He finna make you do it emotional entrapment <br>Ok my mind is dancing the girl is mine I'm asking <br>You gotta watch my movements <br>I'll sway to find the answers <br>She something like the money <br>Gotta keep her safe <br>In order to be strong lets gather weeks to pray <br>Life is a piece of cake <br>Icing proceeds the taste <br>Don't go against the grain <br>I keep my Caesar straight <br>I got you screaming God <br>That's right just keep the faith <br>Yeah I'm gone lead the <br>La Petite Morte Wait <br><br>Hey girl let's keep a million <br>I'm your account <br>Them curves crazy I need some consoling <br>Trying to write on the walls of you virgina <br>Baby come be my rock and less move some mountains <br>You the dopest and you know this <br>Outta sight but we get closer as microscopes can get <br>I'm reloaded hard for him to notice this <br>Keep back stroking in oceans hopelessness <br>Love is blind <br>Scent is clear Synclaire <br>Shit I'm Overton <br>Living single girl they faker then a Rollie tick <br>Bout time you got in them jeans <br>Party was over with <br>Who's Robe is this <br>Girl I promise I can be everything you need and more <br>Unexpected I guess <br>Tell me who's at the door <br>I'm Steph at long range <br>Shoot my shot and its pure <br>I step over my feelings like people sleep on the floor <br>But I want ya]]></content><category term="Nick Grant" label="Nick Grant"/><category term="All of You (Feat. B. Hess)" label="All of You (Feat. B. Hess)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Bouncin/</id><title>Nick Grant - Bouncin` - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:58:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:58:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Bouncin/" title="Nick Grant - Bouncin` - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Uh <br>Somebody tell them niggas that I'm legendary <br>We gon' check 'em first, like the secretary <br>Leap the competition <br>Twenty ninth of February <br>This double M is all I need <br>I think I'm Meth and Mary <br>Bouncin' <br>I peel off like a dead nigga' <br>Shooter do it himself <br>Boy he Blair Witchin' <br>Blood spillin' over beef <br>I'm a rare nigga <br>And we don't know from nothin' <br>'less the feds with ya' <br>How you want it <br>This that '96 Pac <br>Never met a nah notha nigga this hot <br>Pen game dope, scribble 'til my wrist lock <br>Niggas ballin' thinkin' shit is sweet <br>Chris Bosh <br>Boy, bouncin' <br>You gotta catch those lines <br>Tell a broke nigga <br>Hold up that depressed hoe sign <br>She want dick and I'ma nail it <br>Not the press on kind <br>Baby girl throw it back <br>Like it's West Coast time <br>And get it <br><br>Hot damn <br>It ain't 'bout the money <br>Boy, the shit ain't in the plans <br>Girl I got a bag on me <br>Money dancin' <br>And when you real nigga <br>Everybody understand <br>Hot damn nigga <br>I can make the money nigga <br>I can make the money nigga <br>With the top down <br>Tell them other niggas <br>They can't do what I can <br><br>Food for the soul <br>Real nigga' ingredient <br>Never was a hater <br>Nigga' that shit look too tedious haha <br>Come through wavy and they gon' do you the greasiest <br>Kids slide up on you <br>Like pajamas with the feet in 'em <br>Strong minded, she ain't messin' with no weak nigga <br>My biggest fear is that you treatin' me like theeese niggas' <br>Got a PHD, and she like the weed lit up <br>Ass fat, she don't waste much <br>Like a cheap nigga' <br>Bouncin' <br>My outfit scream murderer whoo <br>Yeah I'm showing out, roll the curtains up <br>Baby blue Jordan 9 <br>Think I should hit Gerber up <br>Going harder than Laura lettin' Urkle fuck <br>I thought I told you that it's all about the moola <br>Know I keep that thing <br>Like when Lauryn dropped Doo Wop <br>Tell them niggas' cool out <br>'Fore they hear that booyah <br>Party animal It's like when Meech brought the zoo out <br>Bouncin' <br><br>Hot damn <br>It ain't 'bout the money <br>Boy, the shit ain't in the plans <br>Girl I got a bag on me <br>Money dancin' <br>And when you real nigga <br>Everybody understand <br>Hot damn nigga <br>I can make the money nigga <br>I can make the money nigga <br>With the top down <br>Tell them other niggas <br>They can't do what I can <br>Hot damn <br>It ain't 'bout the money <br>Boy, the shit ain't in the plans <br>Girl I got a bag on me <br>Money dancin' <br>And when you real nigga <br>Everybody understand <br>Hot damn nigga <br>I can make the money nigga <br>I can make the money nigga <br>With the top down <br>Tell them other niggas <br>They can't do what I can]]></content><category term="Nick Grant" label="Nick Grant"/><category term="Bouncin`" label="Bouncin`"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Drug_Lord_Couture/</id><title>Nick Grant - Drug Lord Couture - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:58:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:58:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Drug_Lord_Couture/" title="Nick Grant - Drug Lord Couture - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The new king now watch a nigga spazz <br>The school of hard knocks, you niggas skipping class <br>You fake, bumping Trae the only time your trigger blast <br>Talking you through the present time I got the gift of gab <br>Jewelry swinging like a freak couple I got a hoe fetish <br>Wide body Ferrari look bowlegged, we go getters <br>Niggas that you admire acknowledge me, its prophecy <br>No shame cocaine white as the dress on the bride to be <br>Pimpin', promote the pussy like she signed to me <br>Nicole Scherzinger nigga, nina on my lap <br>Here's my squirt finger, bloaw how you like me now <br>Niggas telling' on the crowd, where the fuck is the morale wow <br><br>I do it all for the love <br>I do it all for the love <br>I do it all for the love <br>I do it all for the love <br>This is for the hustler in you <br><br>Damn it feels good to see people up on it <br>First rap deal, gave it back didn't want it <br>Your style is haunted, with ghostwriters in your corner <br>I'm disappointed, how silent killers turn informant <br>At your door like the Mormans, peep how bitches adore him <br>I make em freeze like when a nigga scared of performing <br>Understand it, fuck with me and up your standards <br>You tryna freak Nick, baby, I'm out in Atlanta uhh <br>Lift as you climb my nigga they couldn't carry us <br>Said we wouldn't make it 'til we broke down the barriers <br>These niggas name dropping pussy who u marrying <br>Alienate us, send 51 niggas to your area blaow <br><br>I do it all for the love <br>I do it all for the love <br>I do it all for the love <br>I do it all for the love <br>This is for the hustler in you <br><br>Fuck the drama man I'm so beyond it <br>All I do is move around, I don't know confinement <br>Never had a high but know my bitches roll the finest <br>I'm just so honest, get behind her like I'm photobombing <br>This the life I'm posed' to live, tell a hoe don't comment <br>Yellow gold like a wine o's eye rolls of jaundice <br>Slick, you'll never catch it flows are ultrasonic <br>They over grinding, selling blow like a nose with sinus <br>Where I'm from, they pull out quick, here i come <br>Like the wool out, they wasn't 'bout static <br>But never run <br>Blast out, hit gas than mash out <br>Seeing through your favorite rapper like he riding glass house blaow <br><br>I do it all for the love <br>I do it all for the love <br>I do it all for the love <br>I do it all for the love <br>This is for the hustler in you]]></content><category term="Nick Grant" label="Nick Grant"/><category term="Drug Lord Couture" label="Drug Lord Couture"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Sometimes_Feat_Dominic_Gordon/</id><title>Nick Grant - Sometimes (Feat. Dominic Gordon) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:58:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:58:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nick_Grant/Sometimes_Feat_Dominic_Gordon/" title="Nick Grant - Sometimes (Feat. Dominic Gordon) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You know, most of these niggas ain't shit <br>But, when you find you a smooth brother <br>You know what I mean, like, but real good brother <br>You better keep that nigga <br>Because things do change you know <br>Sometimes <br><br>Sometimes I wonder would you show love if I'm average uhh <br>Such a good heart my surroundings just make me savage uhh <br>Sometimes they wonder will I deliver a classic baby <br>Now I'm strong arming the game, Angela Bassett <br>T T Tell em' I'm a don, coke seats Nicky Barnes <br>Movin' up, all my bitches clean up nice, think they Florence <br>From where the feds got the phone tapped, Gregory Hines <br>What goes up must come down nigga, thats a 69 oww <br>Sometimes they think that I changed for what its worth <br>Young nigga cool as a fan, go buy the merch uhh <br>Even if this life wasn't sweet, never dessert me <br>We gone stay forever like black people in church preach church <br>Sometimes niggas don't hate you, women want trust <br>Sometimes I pray that my people believe in us <br>Sometimes she try to be good, can't make it up <br>Funny how a mack moving this powder could make you blush sometimes <br><br>Lately, the world done gone so crazy <br>I seen things that I can't believe <br>Man it's getting too hard to breathe <br>That's how it feel sometime <br>yeah, ohh, ohh, ohh, ohh, ohh <br>Sometimes <br><br>Sometimes they love you, sometimes I feel the neglect <br>Yes I'm, young Berry Gordy temptations are of the flesh <br>Yessir, demons are TLC'n, they creep up the best <br>This is a Weekend At Bernies these niggas dancin' with death uhh <br>Kill of the phony friends, can't let the cancers breathe <br>Please girl don't steal my heart, this is the land of thieves <br>I'm Dr King on the balcony, what a cancelled dream <br>Money's the root of evil that destroyed the family trees <br>Sometimes my futures bright, sometimes its dark around me <br>I'm living through these bars, can't get the law from round me <br>Life was so awful, we made it, now she so awkward round <br>Still bending corners like I overheard you talk about me oww <br>Told you this is peacoat galore, p i m p, d o p e they told me ki's open doors <br>They must be down with opp how JB coming for y'all <br>Sometimes you gotta let it go and let shit go run its course sometimes <br><br>Lately, the world done gone so crazy <br>I seen things that I can't believe <br>Man it's getting too hard to breathe <br>That's how it feel sometime <br>yeah, ohh, ohh, ohh, ohh, ohh <br>Sometimes <br><br>Yeah <br>That brother is ice cold <br>Sometimes, occasionally rather than all the time <br>From time to time, every so often <br>Sometimes only shows you my inconcistency <br>It also shows you that I'm human <br>Sometimes I dig you baby, sometimes I don't <br>True player for real <br>Sometimes we slip, sometimes we trip out <br>But will there be a time you niggas'll be able to fuck with me <br>Know what I'm talking bout <br>Not even on my gloomy days <br>Culture Republic]]></content><category term="Nick Grant" label="Nick Grant"/><category term="Sometimes (Feat. Dominic Gordon)" label="Sometimes (Feat. Dominic Gordon)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Armand_Van_Helden/Wings/</id><title>Armand Van Helden - Wings - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:58:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:58:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Armand_Van_Helden/Wings/" title="Armand Van Helden - Wings - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again <br>I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again <br>I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again <br>I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again <br><br>I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again <br>I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again <br>I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again <br>I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again <br><br>I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again <br>I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again <br>I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again <br>I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again <br><br>I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again <br>I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again <br>I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again <br>I won't let you down <br>Won't let you down again]]></content><category term="Armand Van Helden" label="Armand Van Helden"/><category term="Wings" label="Wings"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Armand_Van_Helden/Know_Thyself/</id><title>Armand Van Helden - Know Thyself - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T10:58:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T10:58:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Armand_Van_Helden/Know_Thyself/" title="Armand Van Helden - Know Thyself - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The people with the funny hats and the noisemakers <br>They've gone home, Goldie <br>The party's over, baby <br>It's dawn, it's reality <br><br>'Cause I can love nobody <br>Till I can love myself <br>You can love nobody <br>Till you can love yourself <br>'Cause I can love nobody <br>Till I can love myself <br>You can love nobody <br>Till you can love yourself <br>'Cause I can love nobody <br>Till I can love myself <br>You can love nobody <br>Till you can love yourself <br>'Cause I can love nobody <br>Till I can love myself <br>You can love nobody <br>Till you can love yourself <br><br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br><br>My brother <br>My sister <br>My brother <br>My sister <br><br>'Cause I can love nobody <br>Till I can love myself <br>You can love nobody <br>Till you can love yourself <br><br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br><br>Wave your hands 'Cause I <br>Wave your hands Can love nobody <br>Wave your hands Till I <br>Wave your hands Can love myself <br>Wave your hands You can <br>Wave your hands Love nobody <br>Wave your hands Till you <br>Wave your hands Can love yourself <br><br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br>Wave your hands <br><br>My brother <br>My sister <br>My brother <br>My sister]]></content><category term="Armand Van Helden" label="Armand Van Helden"/><category term="Know Thyself" label="Know Thyself"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Elsa__Emilie/Kill_Your_Darlings/</id><title>Elsa &amp; Emilie - Kill Your Darlings - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:05:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:05:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Elsa__Emilie/Kill_Your_Darlings/" title="Elsa &amp; Emilie - Kill Your Darlings - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If you leave me now, you'll be comin' back <br>You'll be here for the morning, come take me darlin' <br>Steal me now, I won't hold you back <br>Stole my heart with no warning, still it's left no darlin' <br><br>Now, ooh oh <br>Ooh eh <br>Ooh eh <br>Now, ooh yeah <br>Ooh eh <br>Ooh eh <br><br>But if you kill me now, I won't be coming back <br>If you do it 'fore the morning, just kill me darlin' <br>Do it slowly now, so I won't come back <br>Don't give me no warning, just do it darlin' <br><br>Now, ooh oh <br>Ooh eh <br>Ooh eh <br>Now, ooh hey hey <br>Ooh eh <br>Ooh eh <br><br>Ooh eh <br>Ooh eh <br>Now]]></content><category term="Elsa &amp; Emilie" label="Elsa &amp; Emilie"/><category term="Kill Your Darlings" label="Kill Your Darlings"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LANY/ILYSB/</id><title>LANY - ILYSB - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:06:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:06:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LANY/ILYSB/" title="LANY - ILYSB - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ain't never felt this way <br>Can't get enough so stay <br>with me <br>It's not like we got big plans <br>Let's drive around town <br>holding hands <br>And you need to know <br>You're the only one <br>alright alright <br>And you need to know <br>That you keep me up <br>all night all night <br>Oh my heart hurts so good <br>I love you baby <br>so bad so bad <br>Oh oh my heart hurts so good <br>I love you baby <br>so bad so bad <br>Mad cool in all my clothes <br>Mad warm when you get close <br>to me <br>Slow dance these summer nights <br>Our disco ball's my kitchen <br>light <br>And you need to know <br>That nobody could take <br>your place your place <br>And you need to know <br>That I'm hella obsessed with <br>your face your face <br>Oh my heart hurts so good <br>I love you baby <br>so bad so bad <br>Oh oh my heart hurts so good <br>I love you baby <br>so bad so bad <br>Oh oh my heart hurts so good <br>I love you baby <br>so bad so bad oh <br>And you need to know <br>You're the only one <br>alright alright <br>And you need to know <br>That you keep me up <br>all night all night <br>Oh my heart hurts so good <br>I love you baby <br>so bad so bad <br>Oh oh my heart hurts so good <br>I love you baby <br>so bad so bad oh <br>So bad oh <br>Oh my heart hurt <br>Oh my heart hurt <br>Oh my heart hurt <br>So bad oh <br>]]></content><category term="LANY" label="LANY"/><category term="ILYSB" label="ILYSB"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/American_Authors/Im_Born_To_Run_Acoustic/</id><title>American Authors - I`m Born To Run (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:06:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:06:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/American_Authors/Im_Born_To_Run_Acoustic/" title="American Authors - I`m Born To Run (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm born to run down rocky cliffs <br>Give me grace, bury my sins <br>Shattered glass and black holes <br>Can't hold me back from where I need to go <br>Oh <br><br>Yellow hills and valleys deep <br>I watch them move under my feet <br>Stranger things have come and gone <br>To see the world and take the throne <br><br>Don't hold back <br>Oh, I won't hold back <br><br>I'm gonna live my life like I'm gonna die young <br>Like it's never enough, like I'm born to run <br>I'm gonna spend my time like tomorrow won't come <br>Do whatever I want like I'm born to run <br><br>I wanna see Paris, I wanna see Tokyo <br>I wanna be careless even if I break my bones <br>I'm gonna live my life like I'm gonna die young <br>Like it's never enough, like I'm born to run <br><br>A winding road where strangers meet <br>To feel the love of a warm drink <br>My body moves, it's speaking loud <br>Don't have to say what I'm thinking now <br><br>Don't hold back <br>Oh, I won't hold back <br><br>I'm gonna live my life like I'm gonna die young <br>Like it's never enough, like I'm born to run <br>I'm gonna spend my time like tomorrow won't come <br>Do whatever I want like I'm born to run <br><br>I wanna see Paris, I wanna see Tokyo <br>I wanna be careless even if I break my bones <br>I'm gonna live my life like I'm gonna die young <br>Like it's never enough, like I'm born to run <br><br>All these things I've seen and done <br>I live my life like I'm born to run <br>All these things I've seen and done <br>I live my life like I'm born to run <br>I was born, born, born, born, born to run <br>I was born, born, born, born, born to run <br>All these things I've seen and done <br>I live my life like I'm born to run <br><br>I'm gonna live my life like I'm gonna die young <br>Like it's never enough, like I'm born to run <br>I'm gonna spend my time like tomorrow won't come <br>Do whatever I want like I'm born to run <br><br>I wanna see Paris, I wanna see Tokyo <br>I wanna be careless even if I break my bones <br>I'm gonna live my life like I'm gonna die young <br>Like it's never enough, like I'm born to run]]></content><category term="American Authors" label="American Authors"/><category term="I`m Born To Run (Acoustic)" label="I`m Born To Run (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Call_It_Off/Emily/</id><title>Call It Off - Emily - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:07:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:07:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Call_It_Off/Emily/" title="Call It Off - Emily - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Where to start <br>It has been so long since it all fell apart <br>Yes I look the same as when I broke your heart and <br>Left you crying <br>And I admit <br>I'm not proud of the moronic things I did <br>Cannot bear to face the truth that you're not with me <br>So please forgive me <br>I'd take every single thing back if you'd <br>Take my hand and not let go again <br><br>Emily <br>Remember how I lost your heart for good <br>Or I felt misunderstood <br>Emily <br>I'd be a different person if I could <br>Emily I would <br><br>Once again <br>Infatuation led me to a dying end <br>It'd be better if it's put out of it's misery <br>So don't forget me <br>Even though I'd give the world to keep you with me <br>Emily I know, that I should let you go <br><br>Emily <br>Remember how I lost your heart for good <br>Or I felt misunderstood <br>Emily <br>I'd be a different person if I could <br>Emily I would <br><br>With all the memories fading <br>We're all eliminating <br>Everything that give me hope again <br>I'd be a different person and take it all back if I could <br>Oh Emily you know I would <br>Oh Emily you know I would <br>I'd take every single thing back <br><br>Emily <br>Remember how I lost your heart for good <br>Or I felt misunderstood <br>Emily <br>I'd be a different person if I could <br>Emily, Emily you know I would <br>Emily I would]]></content><category term="Call It Off" label="Call It Off"/><category term="Emily" label="Emily"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Call_It_Off/Abandoned/</id><title>Call It Off - Abandoned - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:07:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:07:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Call_It_Off/Abandoned/" title="Call It Off - Abandoned - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Had enough Had enough <br>Gave it all that I got <br>Give it up Give it up <br>Give me one single reason why <br>I should not leave today <br>But you can't No, you can't No, you can't <br>Bring yourself to pretend To pretend To pretend <br>That there's something to fight for here <br>Don't pull your punches at me <br>Down for the count <br>Over and out <br>I'm gone <br>Forget what I said and leave it at that <br>I'm moving on <br>I'm never ever gonna go back Gonna go back <br>Never ever gonna go back to you <br>Never look back, never look back <br>Emily I wish you well cause' I'm abandoning you <br>If only you knew, if you knew, if you knew <br>When you're bending the tuth <br>Like you do, like you do <br>It will never get easier <br>You'll bend till you break completely <br>Down for the count <br>Over and out <br>I'm gone <br>Forget what I said and leave it at that <br>I'm moving on <br>I'm never ever gonna go back Gonna go back <br>Never ever gonna go back to you <br>Never look back, never look back <br>Emily I wish you well cause' I'm abandoning you <br>Tell me again, tell me a lie <br>Tell me that everything's alright <br>Tell me that I was wrong before <br>Tell me it's still worth fighting for, worth fighting for <br>I'm never ever gonna go back Gonna go back <br>Never ever gonna go back to you <br>Never look back, never look back <br>Emily I wish you well cause' I'm abandoning you <br>I will abandoning <br>I will abandoning you <br>Emily I wish you well cause' I'm abandoning you]]></content><category term="Call It Off" label="Call It Off"/><category term="Abandoned" label="Abandoned"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Beach/Bite_My_Tongue_Acoustic/</id><title>The Beach - Bite My Tongue (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:08:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:08:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Beach/Bite_My_Tongue_Acoustic/" title="The Beach - Bite My Tongue (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She says I need you now <br>But I don't know why <br>She's got this fairytale <br>But that's just not mine <br><br>And I drink and smoke too much <br>She doesn't mind <br>But I know it's best for her <br>If I said goodbye <br><br>And I think I've said it <br>I know that I did <br><br>Wish I could bite my tounge <br>without tasting the blood <br>Of your broken heart my love <br>Wish I could <br>Wish I could bite my tounge without tasting the blood <br>Of your broken heart my love <br>Wish I could <br>Ohhhh <br>But it's too late, too late, too late <br>But it's too late, too late, too late <br><br>I call you every night <br>Cause I know that's what you want <br>But I got this poision touch <br>And this won't last long <br><br>And I think that I've said it <br>I know that I did <br><br>Wish I could bite my tounge <br>Without tasting the blood <br>Of your broken heart my love <br><br>Wish I could <br>Wish I could bite my tounge <br>Without tasting the blood <br>Of your broken heart my love <br><br>Wish I could <br><br>But it's too late, too late, too late <br>But it's too late, too late, too late <br><br>She says I need you now <br>But I don't know why <br>She's got this fairytale <br>But that's just not mine <br><br>And I think I've said it <br>I know that I did <br><br>Wish I could bite my tounge <br>Without tasting the blood <br>Of your broken heart my love <br><br>Wish I could <br>Wish I could bite my tounge <br>Without tasting the blood <br>Of your broken heart my love <br><br>Wish I could <br><br>But it's too late, too late, too late <br>But it's too late, too late, too late]]></content><category term="The Beach" label="The Beach"/><category term="Bite My Tongue (Acoustic)" label="Bite My Tongue (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanic/Too_Soon_Feat_Maty_Noyes/</id><title>Vanic - Too Soon (Feat. Maty Noyes) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:09:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:09:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanic/Too_Soon_Feat_Maty_Noyes/" title="Vanic - Too Soon (Feat. Maty Noyes) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Gotta get myself out of this town <br>Cause we got a lotta history <br>And if I don't get away, I might drown <br>In a sea of haunting memories <br>Everybody wants to know what happened <br>Cause they thought that we were meant to be <br>And I'm sorry I don't have an answer <br>But people always asking me <br><br>Yeah people always asking <br>People always asking <br>People always asking me <br><br>I tell them <br>If you don't want me to keep feeling this pain <br>Don't say his name <br>Don't say his name <br>Cause he's not something that I wanna explain <br>Don't say his name <br>Don't say his name <br>It's too soon <br>It's too soon <br>It's too soon <br>Don't say his name <br>Don't say his name <br><br>Don't say his name <br>Don't say his name <br>Don't say his name <br>Don't say his name <br><br>And I wonder where you're sleeping <br>Cause I know it isn't next to me <br>Gotta find that silver lining <br>And think of it as being free <br><br>And people always asking <br>People always asking <br>People always asking me <br><br>I tell them <br>If you don't want me to keep feeling this pain <br>Don't say his name <br>Don't say his name <br>Cause he's not something that I wanna explain <br>Don't say his name <br>Don't say his name <br><br>Don't say his name <br>Don't say his name <br><br>Got me worked up, all I'm sayin' <br>I just can't talk about it yet <br>Cause you know I'm not okay <br>I just don't know what's left to say <br>Got me worked up, all I'm sayin' <br>I just can't talk about it yet <br>Cause you know I'm not okay <br>I just don't know what's left to say <br><br>I tell them <br>If you don't want me to keep feeling this way <br>Don't say his name <br>Don't say his name <br>Cause I don't think that I should have to explain <br>Don't say his name <br>Don't say his name <br><br>Don't say his name <br>Don't say his name <br>It's too soon <br>It's too soon <br>It's too soon <br>Don't say his name <br>Don't say his name]]></content><category term="Vanic" label="Vanic"/><category term="Too Soon (Feat. Maty Noyes)" label="Too Soon (Feat. Maty Noyes)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_New_Christy_Minstrels/The_Girl_From_Ipanema/</id><title>The New Christy Minstrels - The Girl From Ipanema - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:09:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:09:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_New_Christy_Minstrels/The_Girl_From_Ipanema/" title="The New Christy Minstrels - The Girl From Ipanema - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tall and tan and young and lovely <br>The girl from Ipanema goes walking <br>And when she passes, each one she passes goes ah <br><br>When she walks, she's like a samba <br>That swings so cool and sways so gentle <br>That when she passes, each one she passes goes ah <br><br>Ooh But he watch her so sadly <br>How can he tell her he loves her <br>Yes I would give my heart gladly <br>But each day, that she walks to the sea <br>She looks straight ahead, not at he <br><br>Tall, and tan, and young, and lovely <br>The girl from Ipanema goes walking <br>And when she passes, he smile but she doesn't see <br>Doesn't see <br>She just doesn't see, she never sees him]]></content><category term="The New Christy Minstrels" label="The New Christy Minstrels"/><category term="The Girl From Ipanema" label="The Girl From Ipanema"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_New_Christy_Minstrels/Chim_Chim_Cher-ee/</id><title>The New Christy Minstrels - Chim Chim Cher-ee - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:09:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:09:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_New_Christy_Minstrels/Chim_Chim_Cher-ee/" title="The New Christy Minstrels - Chim Chim Cher-ee - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Chim chiminey, chim chiminey <br>Chim chim cher ee <br>A chimney sweep is as lucky <br>As lucky can be <br><br>Chim chiminey, chim chiminey <br>Chim chim cher oo <br>Good luck will rub off <br>When I shake hands with you <br><br>Now as the ladder of life <br>Has been strung <br>A chimney sweep hung <br>The bottom most rung <br><br>Though I spend my time <br>In the ashes and smoke <br>In this whole wide world <br>There's no happier bloke <br><br>Chim chiminey, chim chiminey <br>Chim chim cher ee <br>A chimney sweep is as lucky <br>As lucky can be <br><br>Chim chiminey, chim chiminey <br>Chim chim cher oo <br>Good luck will rub off <br>When I shake hands with you <br><br>Now in my profession <br>There's many a time <br>When I embark <br>On a perilous climb <br><br>Chim chiminey, chim chiminey <br>Chim chim cher ee <br>A chimney sweep is as lucky <br>As lucky can be <br><br>Chim chiminey, chim chiminey <br>Chim chim cher oo <br>Good luck will rub off <br>When I shake hands with you <br><br>Gables and rooftops <br>Become Taj Mahal <br>Then climbing the chimney's <br>A great Chinese wall <br><br>Chim chiminey <br>Chim chiminey <br><br>Chim chiminey, chim chiminey <br>Chim chim cher ee <br>A chimney sweep is as lucky <br>As lucky can be <br><br>Chim chiminey, chim chiminey <br>Chim chim cher oo <br>Good luck will rub off <br>When I shake hands with you <br><br>And that's lucky too]]></content><category term="The New Christy Minstrels" label="The New Christy Minstrels"/><category term="Chim Chim Cher-ee" label="Chim Chim Cher-ee"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_New_Christy_Minstrels/Today/</id><title>The New Christy Minstrels - Today - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:10:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:10:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_New_Christy_Minstrels/Today/" title="The New Christy Minstrels - Today - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Today while the blossoms still cling to the vine <br>I'll taste your strawberries, I'll drink your sweet wine <br><br>A million tomorrows shall all pass away <br>Ere I forget all the joy that is mine today <br><br>I'll be a dandy and I'll be a rover <br>You'll know who I am by the song that I sing <br>I'll feast at your table, I'll sleep in your clover <br><br>Who cares what the morrow shall bring <br><br>Today while the blossoms still cling to the vine <br>I'll taste your strawberries, I'll drink your sweet wine <br><br>I can't be contented with yesterday's glory <br>I can't live on promises winter to spring winter to spring <br><br>Today is my moment and now is my story <br><br>I'll laugh and I'll cry and I'll sing <br><br>Today while the blossoms still cling to the vine <br>I'll taste your strawberries, I'll drink your sweet wine <br>A million tomorrows shall all pass away <br>Ere I forget all the joy that is mine today]]></content><category term="The New Christy Minstrels" label="The New Christy Minstrels"/><category term="Today" label="Today"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_New_Christy_Minstrels/Saturday_Night_Single_Ver/</id><title>The New Christy Minstrels - Saturday Night (Single Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:10:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:10:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_New_Christy_Minstrels/Saturday_Night_Single_Ver/" title="The New Christy Minstrels - Saturday Night (Single Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Saturday Night Saturday Night We all get together on Saturday Night <br>Put on your shoes, go downtown Do nothing but walk around On a Sunday <br>Or a Monday you can't do it right, Ain't ya glad we got Saturday Night <br><br>Early in the evening all week long, sit on your stoop and sing your little <br>Song Cry on yer pillow when things go wrong and wait for Saturday Night <br><br>Saturday Night Saturday Night We all get together on Saturday Night <br>Vocal oo On a Sunday or a Monday you can't do it <br>Right Ain't ya glad we got Saturday Night Ain't ya glad we got Saturday <br>Night Green Green on a Saturday Night Ain't ya glad we got Saturday <br>Night]]></content><category term="The New Christy Minstrels" label="The New Christy Minstrels"/><category term="Saturday Night (Single Ver.)" label="Saturday Night (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_New_Christy_Minstrels/Last_Farewell/</id><title>The New Christy Minstrels - Last Farewell - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:10:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:10:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_New_Christy_Minstrels/Last_Farewell/" title="The New Christy Minstrels - Last Farewell - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm going away at eventide <br>Across the wild and the rolling sea <br>I bid you stay, stay here by my side <br>And share a last farewell with me <br><br>Through snow clad mountains, proud and tall <br>Or a thousand miles 'cross the burning sand <br>Our last farewell, then will I recall <br>When I'm alone in a far off land <br><br>A wandering song is all I know <br>Yet I love you more, more than words can tell <br>I hear that call, and I'm bound to roam <br>I leave you now, with a last farewell <br>I leave you now, with a last farewell]]></content><category term="The New Christy Minstrels" label="The New Christy Minstrels"/><category term="Last Farewell" label="Last Farewell"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_New_Christy_Minstrels/Green_Green/</id><title>The New Christy Minstrels - Green, Green - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:10:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:10:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_New_Christy_Minstrels/Green_Green/" title="The New Christy Minstrels - Green, Green - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Green, green <br>It's green they say <br>On the far side of the hill <br>Green, green <br>I'm going away to where <br>The grass is greener still <br><br>A well, I told my mama <br>On the day I was born <br>Don't you cry <br>When you see I'm gone <br><br>You know there ain't no woman <br>Gonna settle me down <br>I just gotta be traveling on <br>A singing <br><br>Green, green <br>It's green they say <br>On the far side of the hill <br>Green, green <br>I'm going away to where <br>The grass is greener still <br><br>Nah, there ain't nobody <br>In this whole wide world <br>Gonna tell me how to spend my time <br>I'm just a good loving rambling man <br>Say, buddy, can you spare me a dime <br>Hear me crying, it's a <br><br>Green, green <br>It's green they say <br>On the far side of the hill <br>Green, green <br>I'm going away to where <br>The grass is greener still <br><br>Yeah, I don't care <br>When the sun goes down <br>Where I lay my weary head <br>Green, green valley or rocky road <br>It's there I'm gonna make my bed <br>Easy, now <br><br>Green, green <br>It's green they say <br>On the far side of the hill <br>Green, green <br>I'm going away to where <br>The grass is greener still <br><br>Everybody, I wanna hear it now <br><br>Green, green <br>It's green they say <br>On the far side of the hill <br>Green, green <br>I'm going away to where <br>The grass is greener still]]></content><category term="The New Christy Minstrels" label="The New Christy Minstrels"/><category term="Green, Green" label="Green, Green"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_New_Christy_Minstrels/This_Land_Is_Your_Land/</id><title>The New Christy Minstrels - This Land Is Your Land - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:10:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:10:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_New_Christy_Minstrels/This_Land_Is_Your_Land/" title="The New Christy Minstrels - This Land Is Your Land - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This land is your land, this land is my land <br><br>From bonna vista, to vancouver island <br><br>From the arctic circle to the great lake waters <br><br>This land was made for you and me <br><br>As I was walking that ribbon of highway <br>I saw above me, that endless skyway <br>I saw below that golden valley <br>This land was made for you and me <br><br>I roamed and rambled and followed my footsteps <br>To the firclad forests of her mighty mountains <br>And all around me a voice was calling <br>This land was made for you and me <br><br>As the sun came shining and I was strolling <br>And the wheat fields waving and the dust clouds rolling <br>As the fog was lifting a voice was sounding <br>This land was made for you and me]]></content><category term="The New Christy Minstrels" label="The New Christy Minstrels"/><category term="This Land Is Your Land" label="This Land Is Your Land"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Hey_Jacque/</id><title>Eartha Kitt - Hey Jacque - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:11:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:11:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Hey_Jacque/" title="Eartha Kitt - Hey Jacque - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, Jacques <br>Have you seen Louis <br>Is he still in Paris <br>I wait, day after day <br>in that cafe <br>by the river <br><br>Please, Jacques <br>if you see Louis <br>tell him to come to me <br>I've tried, I can't forget <br>I love him yet <br>Please, Jacques <br>tell Louis, for me <br><br>Hola, Jacques Have you seen Louis <br>He's not come to see me in <br>I've waited, and waited, in that cafe <br>down by the river No, Jacques <br><br>Please, Jacques <br>if you see Louis <br>tell him to come to me <br>I've tried, I can't forget <br>I love him yet <br>Please, Jacques <br>tell Louis, for me]]></content><category term="Eartha Kitt" label="Eartha Kitt"/><category term="Hey Jacque" label="Hey Jacque"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/My_Hearts_Delight/</id><title>Eartha Kitt - My Heart`s Delight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:11:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:11:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/My_Hearts_Delight/" title="Eartha Kitt - My Heart`s Delight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Why the first thing I want in the morning <br>And the last thing I want at night <br>Is you baby, just you baby <br>Cause you're my heart's delight <br><br>The first time that you ever kissed me <br>And you squeezed me with all of your might <br>I knew baby, that you baby <br>Would be my heart's delight <br><br>But it ain't what you say it's the way how you say it <br>You say love me baby and I have to obey <br>Your sweet talk puts me at your command <br>And you rule me with the wave of your hand <br><br>That's why the first thing I want in the morning <br>And the last thing I want at night <br>Is you baby, just you baby <br>Cause you're my heart's delight <br><br>But it ain't what you say it's the way how you say it <br>You say love me baby and I have to obey <br>Your sweet talk puts me at your command <br>And you rule me with the wave of your hand <br><br>That's why the first thing I want in the morning <br>And the last thing I want at night <br>Is you baby, just you baby <br>Cause you're my heart's delight]]></content><category term="Eartha Kitt" label="Eartha Kitt"/><category term="My Heart`s Delight" label="My Heart`s Delight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Mambo_De_Paree/</id><title>Eartha Kitt - Mambo De Paree - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:11:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:11:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Mambo_De_Paree/" title="Eartha Kitt - Mambo De Paree - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[oui <br>oui <br>when they do the mambo in Paree <br>ca c' est quelque chose <br>when they do the mambo tres jolie <br>c'est la vie en rose <br>oui <br><br>how they love to mambo in Paris <br>ca c'est magnifique <br>when they do the mambo in Paree <br>ca c'est tres tres chique <br><br>madame Dupont mambos <br>monsieur Dupont mambos <br>mademoiselle Dupont <br>they love to ooo <br><br>le marechal mambos <br>la femme fatale mambos <br>La Rue Pigalle mambos <br>they love to ooo <br>oui <br><br>when they do the mambo in Paree <br>chaque un a son gout <br>now they never need psychiatry <br>toute le monde est fou <br>oui <br><br>everybody mamboos in Paree <br>meme le vieux marie <br>he goes out alone and so does she <br>vive la Liberte <br><br>la tete du veaux mambos <br>la saucisson mamboos <br>meme l'escargot mamboos <br>it is just that ooo <br><br>just like a jank mamboos <br>sometimes a frank <br>le georges cinq mamboos <br>it is just that ooo <br>oui <br><br>how they love to mambo in Paree <br>ca c'est magnifique <br>how they love to mambo in Paree <br>ca c'est tres tres chique <br><br>la tete du veaux mambos <br>la saucisson mamboos <br>meme l'escargot mamboos <br>it is just that ooo <br><br>just like a jank mamboos <br>sometimes a Frank mamboos <br>le Georges Cinq mamboos <br>it is just that ooo <br>oui <br><br>ooo la laa <br>c'est le mambo de Paree <br>ooo la laa <br>c'est la derniere cris <br><br>oui]]></content><category term="Eartha Kitt" label="Eartha Kitt"/><category term="Mambo De Paree" label="Mambo De Paree"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/The_Heel/</id><title>Eartha Kitt - The Heel - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:11:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:11:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/The_Heel/" title="Eartha Kitt - The Heel - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The one who has me for his own <br>Is on the town and I'm alone <br>In his blue suit and his new tie <br>He slams the door without goodbye <br>Tonight my eyes are jealous green <br>Tonight I'm melancholy mean <br>He meets in secret rendezvous <br>Some dame to tell his troubles to <br>The heel <br><br>He'll promise her most anything <br>A sable coat, a diamond ring <br>She'll find him out when its too late <br>And all she'll get will be the date <br>But while the dawn's a distant thing <br>In his embrace her heart will sing <br>A dizzy head will spin with lies <br>And all too soon a woman cries <br>The heel <br><br>The neon lights that flash below <br>Ignite my room with double glow <br>And in the gloom I hear a laugh <br>Its coming from his photograph <br>I wring my hands and mop the floor <br>And swear to even up the score <br>But where a kitten cried tonight <br>A panther waits to claw and bite <br>The heel <br><br>I dare not play my radio <br>One more complaint and out I go <br>I'm sick of playing solitaire <br>The ace of spades is everywhere <br>They'll be no sleep for me tonight <br>The sheep I count are never white <br>They all turn out to be jet black <br>And who's the leader of the pack <br>The heel <br><br>At dawn I know he'll stagger in <br>Demanding coffee black as sin <br>And as I take it from the tin <br>I'll slip a little powder in <br>He'll look at me and start to cry <br>And cross his heart and hope to die <br>And mumble I know how you feel <br>But I've been on a business deal <br>The heel <br><br>Then as the pot begins to perc <br>I know my plan will never work <br>When he starts to drink it up <br>I grab his hand and break the cup <br>Its only jealousy I know <br>That brought my thinking down so low <br>Why must I wait for him and grieve <br>Why don't I just pack up and leave <br>The heel <br><br>But now he's reeling on the stair <br>I'll try to act like I don't care <br>For in my heart's arithmetic <br>I find it takes two heels to click <br>We're in a web of love and hate <br>Where it will end is up to fate <br>I'll let him have his little flings <br>I'll be the chewing gum that clings <br>To the heel]]></content><category term="Eartha Kitt" label="Eartha Kitt"/><category term="The Heel" label="The Heel"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Apres_Moi/</id><title>Eartha Kitt - Apres Moi - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:11:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:11:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Apres_Moi/" title="Eartha Kitt - Apres Moi - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We've been friends for a long long time <br>We've shared again and again <br>We like the same clothes and we like the same wine <br>And we have similar taste in men <br>Now we've found one man, and we can share him too <br>For I will love him first and what is left I give to you <br><br>Apres moi you can tell 'em <br>That his eyes are the colour of the sea <br>Only apres moi means you tell 'em <br>After me, after me, after me <br><br>Apres moi you can hold 'em <br>Till he melts like the sugar in your tea <br>Only apres moi means you'll hold 'em <br>After me, after me, after me <br><br>Apres moi I learned in France <br>When I learn the meaning of the word romance <br>If you wish to learn this too <br>I suggest you watch me closely while I woo woo woo woo <br><br>Mmm mm mm, I have kissed him <br>Do you hear how he whispered ooh la la <br>Do you really think he will kiss you <br>Apres moi, apres moi, apres moi <br><br>Apres moi I learned in France <br>When I learn the meaning of the word romance <br>If you wish to learn this too <br>I suggest you watch me closely while I woo woo woo woo <br><br>Mmm mm mm, I have kissed him <br>Do you hear how he whispered ooh la la <br>Do you really think he will kiss you <br>Apres moi, apres <br>Oh well, I really didn't like him anyway]]></content><category term="Eartha Kitt" label="Eartha Kitt"/><category term="Apres Moi" label="Apres Moi"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/The_Day_That_The_Circus_Left_Town_Remastered_2001/</id><title>Eartha Kitt - The Day That The Circus Left Town (Remastered 2001) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:11:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:11:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/The_Day_That_The_Circus_Left_Town_Remastered_2001/" title="Eartha Kitt - The Day That The Circus Left Town (Remastered 2001) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I waved to the man with the golden baton <br>And I waved through the rain falling down <br>And I waved till the last of the music was gone <br>The day that the circus left town <br><br>My heart still recalls when it seems to my mind <br>That my heart only knows how to frown <br>How my heart almost broke when they left me behind <br>The day that the circus left town <br><br>I asked for a job doing anything <br>Feed the elephants, carry water, anything <br>But the man said they didn't have anything <br>And turned me away, turned me away <br><br>And away went the lions and the tigers so wild <br>And away went my beautiful clown <br>And away went my very last day as a child <br>The day that the circus left town <br><br>I asked for a job doing anything <br>Feed the elephants, carry water, anything <br>But the man said they didn't have anything <br>And turned me away, turned me away <br><br>And away went the lions and the tigers so wild <br>And away went my beautiful clown <br>And away went my very last day as a child <br>The day that the circus left town]]></content><category term="Eartha Kitt" label="Eartha Kitt"/><category term="The Day That The Circus Left Town (Remastered 2001)" label="The Day That The Circus Left Town (Remastered 2001)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Strangers_In_The_Starlight/</id><title>Eartha Kitt - Strangers In The Starlight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:11:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:11:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Strangers_In_The_Starlight/" title="Eartha Kitt - Strangers In The Starlight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We were strangers in the starlight <br>Two hearts passing in the night <br>Then you whispered please don't leave me <br>And I whispered hold me tight <br><br>When I kissed you, how you thrilled me <br>In a moment, love was born <br>We were strangers in the starlight <br>Now we're lovers in the dawn <br><br>We were strangers in the starlight <br>Two hearts passing in the night <br>Then you whispered please don't leave me <br>And I whispered hold me tight <br><br>When I kissed you, how you thrilled me <br>In a moment, love was born <br>We were strangers in the starlight <br>Now we're lovers in the dawn]]></content><category term="Eartha Kitt" label="Eartha Kitt"/><category term="Strangers In The Starlight" label="Strangers In The Starlight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Oh_John/</id><title>Eartha Kitt - Oh John - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:11:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:11:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Oh_John/" title="Eartha Kitt - Oh John - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh John, please don't kiss me <br>Oh John, please don't kiss <br>Oh John, please don't <br>Oh John, please <br>Oh John <br>Oooh <br><br>Oh John, please don't hold me <br>Oh John, please don't <br>Oh John, please don't <br>Oh John, please <br>Oh John <br>Oooh <br><br>I keep thinking we only met an hour or two ago <br>Though I like you, I mustn't let you <br>No, no, no, no, no <br><br>Oh John, please go home now <br>Oh John, please go home <br>Oh John, please go <br>Oh John, please <br>Oh John <br>Oooh <br><br>Oh John, please go home now <br>Oh John, please go home <br>Oh John, please go <br>Oh John, please <br>Oh John <br>Oooooh]]></content><category term="Eartha Kitt" label="Eartha Kitt"/><category term="Oh John" label="Oh John"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Ive_Got_That_Lovin_Bug_Itch/</id><title>Eartha Kitt - I`ve Got That Lovin` Bug Itch - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:11:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:11:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Ive_Got_That_Lovin_Bug_Itch/" title="Eartha Kitt - I`ve Got That Lovin` Bug Itch - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've got that lovin' bug itch <br>But no one to scratch it <br>Got a good ball to pitch <br>But no one to catch it <br>Here's the key to my heart <br>Won't somebody unlatch it <br>Got that lovin' bug itch <br><br>And I've got two lovin' arms <br>They're not made of plastic <br>Got a wonderful urge <br>To do somethin' drastic <br>I'm just dyin' to splurge <br>In a way that's fantastic <br>Got that lovin' bug itch I got that lovin' bug itch <br><br>There was a time that nothing ever bothered me <br>And I was pretty certain I would never be hooked <br>But I've been bitten by the love bug and it's plain to see <br>That my goose oh me is cooked oh my <br><br>I've got that lovin' bug itch <br>I'm a gal who's been yearning <br>And my heart's within reach <br>A fire is burning <br>If you're willing to teach <br>Then I'm ready for the learning <br>Got that lovin' bug itch <br><br>I've got that lovin' bug itch <br>But no one to scratch it <br>Got a good ball to pitch <br>But no one to catch it <br>Here's the key to my heart <br>Won't somebody unlatch it <br>Got that lovin' bug itch I got that lovin' bug itch <br><br>There was a time that nothing ever bothered me <br>And I was pretty certain I would never be hooked <br>But I've been bitten by the love bug and it's plain to see <br>That my goose oh me is cooked oh my <br><br>I pray to heaven above <br>To stop me from shakin' <br>Got a heart full of love <br>It's just about breakin' <br>All I need is a shove <br>And I'm yours for the takin' <br>Got that lovin' bug itch got that lovin' bug itch <br>Got that lovin' bug itch got that lovin' bug itch <br>Got that lovin' bug itch got that lovin' bug itch]]></content><category term="Eartha Kitt" label="Eartha Kitt"/><category term="I`ve Got That Lovin` Bug Itch" label="I`ve Got That Lovin` Bug Itch"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Looking_For_A_Boy/</id><title>Eartha Kitt - Looking For A Boy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:11:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:11:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Looking_For_A_Boy/" title="Eartha Kitt - Looking For A Boy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I am just a little girl <br>Who's looking for a little boy <br>Who's looking for a girl to love <br>Tell me please, where can he be <br>The loving he who'll bring to me <br>The harmony I'm dreamin' of <br><br>It'll be goodbye, I know <br>To my tale of woe <br>When he says hello, so <br>I am just a little girl <br>Who's looking for a little boy <br>Who's looking for a girl to love <br><br>If it's true that love affairs are all arranged in heaven <br>My guardian angel's holding out on me <br>So I'm looking for a boy 'bout five foot six or seven <br>And won't be happy till I'm on his knee <br>I'll be blue until he comes my way <br>Hope he takes the cue when I am sayin' <br><br>Tell me please, where can he be <br>The loving he who'll bring to me <br>The harmony I'm dreamin' of <br><br>It'll be goodbye, I know <br>To my tale of woe <br>When he says hello, so <br>I am just a little girl <br>Who's looking for a little boy <br>Who's looking for a girl to love <br>Won't you find that boy <br>Help me find a boy <br>Who's lookin' for a girl to love]]></content><category term="Eartha Kitt" label="Eartha Kitt"/><category term="Looking For A Boy" label="Looking For A Boy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Do_You_Remember/</id><title>Eartha Kitt - Do You Remember - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:11:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:11:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/Do_You_Remember/" title="Eartha Kitt - Do You Remember - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can hear you sighin' <br>Sayin' you'll stay beside me <br>Why must it be <br>That you always creep <br>Into my dreams <br><br>On the beach we're sitting <br>Huggin', squeezin', kissin' <br>Why must it be <br>That you always creep <br>Into my dreams <br>In my dreams <br><br>When I'm sleep at night babaa <br>I feel those moments of ecstasy <br>When you sleep at night babaa <br>I wonder do I creep into your dreams <br>Or could it be I sleep alone in my fantasy <br><br>Oh, love is so amazing <br>Oh, oh, oh, ah, ah <br>Guess you will be stayin' <br>So let it be <br>That you always creep <br>Into my dreams <br>In my dreams <br><br>When I'm sleep at night babaa <br>I feel those moments of ecstasy <br>When you sleep at night babaa <br>I wonder do I creep into your dreams <br>Or could it be I sleep alone in my fantasy <br><br>Oh, love is so amazing <br>Oh, oh, oh, ah, ah <br>Guess you will be stayin' <br>So let it be <br>That you always creep <br>Into my dreams <br>In my dreams]]></content><category term="Eartha Kitt" label="Eartha Kitt"/><category term="Do You Remember" label="Do You Remember"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/I_Wantcha_Around/</id><title>Eartha Kitt - I Wantcha Around - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:11:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:11:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eartha_Kitt/I_Wantcha_Around/" title="Eartha Kitt - I Wantcha Around - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pause at the crossings, wait for the light <br>Go to bed early, early at night <br>Darling keep healthy, don't lose a pound <br><br>Cause if I love ya <br>than I need ya <br>if I need ya <br>than I want ya around <br><br>If you love matches, you can get burned <br>Never kiss strangers, nasty old germs <br>Exercise daily, jump up and down <br><br>Cause if I love ya <br>than I need ya <br>if I need ya <br>than I want ya around <br><br>Take vitamins A, B, C, D, E, F, G for lunch lunch <br>Sweetheart dont run yourself down <br>by hanging around with the bunch <br><br>You can have fun dear, life is a kick <br>Baby's got kisses, they'll make you tick <br>Even at ninety, you'll still be sound <br><br>Cause if I love ya <br>than I need ya <br>if I need ya <br>than I want ya around <br><br>Take vitamins A,B,C,D,E,F,G for lunchlunch <br>Sweetheart don't run yourself down <br>by hanging around with the bunch <br><br>You can have fun dear, life is a kick <br>Baby's got kisses, they'll make you tick <br>Even at ninety, you'll still be sound <br><br>Cause if I love ya <br>than I need ya <br>if I need ya <br>than I want ya around x3]]></content><category term="Eartha Kitt" label="Eartha Kitt"/><category term="I Wantcha Around" label="I Wantcha Around"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aaron_Carter/Sooner_Or_Later/</id><title>Aaron Carter - Sooner Or Later - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:11:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:11:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aaron_Carter/Sooner_Or_Later/" title="Aaron Carter - Sooner Or Later - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[These past days and past nights <br>Walks under streetlights <br>Something don't feel right <br>Sooner or later she'll be <br>Trips to Chicago <br>Don't call me crazy <br>this time tomorrow <br>You lead me I'll follow <br>I got the tables <br>I bought the bottles <br>Sooner or later she'll <br>Be walking away <br>I got something to say to her <br>Sooner or later she'll <br>See what's inside <br>I've put something away for her <br>Man I'd do anything for her <br>Sooner or later she'll be <br>She'll be <br>She'll be <br>She'll be <br>Sooner or later she'll be <br>She'll be <br>She'll be <br>She'll be <br>Sooner or later she'll be <br>I ain't pulling you back <br>When you feeling like that <br>I ain't tripping getting mad <br>Sooner or later she'll be <br>Coming right back <br>When you feeling like that <br>I ain't tripping getting mad <br>'Cause sooner or later she'll be <br>Sooner or later yeah <br>Sooner or later yeah <br>Don't tell me I'm not sure <br>Don't tell me I'm not yours <br>I stop moving backwards <br>And sooner or later we'll be <br>Just over oceans <br>I need your body <br>on me like lotion <br>Cause a commotion <br>Worship your body <br>call that devotion <br>Sooner or later she'll <br>Call me and tell me <br>she's feeling alone tonight <br>Sooner or later she'll <br>Text me and tell me <br>that she's leaving on the light <br>Guess I'm not going home tonight <br>Sooner or later she'll be <br>She'll be <br>She'll be <br>She'll be <br>Sooner or later she'll be <br>She'll be <br>She'll be <br>She'll be <br>Sooner or later she'll be <br>I ain't calling you back <br>When you feeling like that <br>I ain't tripping getting mad <br>Sooner or later she'll be <br>Coming right back <br>When you feeling like that <br>I ain't tripping getting mad <br>'Cause sooner or later she'll be <br>Sooner or later yeah <br>Sooner or later yeah <br>]]></content><category term="Aaron Carter" label="Aaron Carter"/><category term="Sooner Or Later" label="Sooner Or Later"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Black_Mamba/I_Wanna_Be_With_You/</id><title>The Black Mamba - I Wanna Be With You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:11:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:11:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Black_Mamba/I_Wanna_Be_With_You/" title="The Black Mamba - I Wanna Be With You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Existe uma rapariga que eu quero conhecer <br>Passa por mim todos os dias <br>e que me faz sonhar <br>faz me sentir um nervoso agradavel tipo borboletas na barriga <br><br>Ela e a unica coisa em que eu penso <br>Invade os meus pensamentos quando eu saio <br>E esta noite e apenas mais uma noite <br>Em que vou ficar sozinho <br><br>Eu quero estar contigo <br>Todas as vezes que passas por mim leva me ctg <br>beija me e faz o meu dia <br><br>Quando ela sorri eu sinto me muito bem <br>Todas as vezes que ela sorri para mim parece que estou a cair do ceu <br>e e por isso que quero estar com ela <br><br>Ela nao e nada igual ao que ja vi ate hoje <br>Faz me desejar por mais]]></content><category term="The Black Mamba" label="The Black Mamba"/><category term="I Wanna Be With You" label="I Wanna Be With You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Emilie_Nicolas/Sky/</id><title>Emilie Nicolas - Sky - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:11:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:11:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Emilie_Nicolas/Sky/" title="Emilie Nicolas - Sky - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What they tell us about this <br><br>It's only feelings, don't listen <br>It's only in your head ah <br>Don't fear them <br>It's only in your head ah <br>Don't beat 'em <br><br>But they will not tell us how to sail in our seas <br>This weather is tearing us down <br>But one of these days it will come down <br><br>Oh oh oh, this time will soon be over <br>Oh oh oh, and we would all stand taller <br>over a calm sea <br>I lean on you, now you lean on me <br>Oh oh oh, I think this time it's over <br><br>Hold it in, don't fall apart now <br>The world hasn't got down for figuring you out <br>It's like you on the outside looking in <br>Looking at what could've been <br>And they're miles apart, they're miles apart <br><br>But they will not tell us how to sail in our seas <br>This weather is tearing us down <br>But one of these days it will come down <br><br>Oh oh oh, this time will soon be over <br>Oh oh oh, and we would all stand taller <br>over a calm sea <br>I lean on you, now you lean on me <br>Oh oh oh, I think this time it's over <br><br>We are only boats floating under the same sky <br>Drifting into one another once in a while <br>We are only boats floating under the same sky <br>Drifting into one another once in a while <br><br>Oh oh oh, this time will soon be over <br>Oh oh oh, and we would all stand taller <br>over a calm sea <br>I lean on you, now you lean on me <br>Oh oh oh, I think this time it's over <br><br>We are only boats floating under the same sky]]></content><category term="Emilie Nicolas" label="Emilie Nicolas"/><category term="Sky" label="Sky"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Modern_Baseball/This_Song_Is_Gonna_Buy_Brendan_Lukens_A_New_Pair_Of_Socks/</id><title>Modern Baseball - This Song Is Gonna Buy Brendan Lukens A New Pair Of Socks - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:13:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:13:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Modern_Baseball/This_Song_Is_Gonna_Buy_Brendan_Lukens_A_New_Pair_Of_Socks/" title="Modern Baseball - This Song Is Gonna Buy Brendan Lukens A New Pair Of Socks - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't like you <br>And I don't have to <br>If I said it once I only said it once <br>Play my records <br>And read my stories <br>And I won't see you unless I have to <br><br>Get out of Philly <br>And lose my mind a little bit <br>Nicky and Jackson saved my smile and I feel home <br>Joseph's running <br>To tell me something <br>I feel older but I am so sure it's a lie <br><br>When I was eighteen <br>I could not love her <br>I was always thinking of the one she left behind <br>I retraced her picture <br>To fit inside of mine <br>But she was naked and misshapen and confined <br><br>Now I don't see her <br>She loves another <br>And in my bright I thought I had it figured out <br>But I'm still tracing <br>And I'm erasing <br>And somewhere sleeping I read words that have my doubts <br><br>I don't like you <br>And I don't have to <br>And I won't see you unless I have to <br>I don't like you <br>And I don't have to <br>And I won't see you unless I have to]]></content><category term="Modern Baseball" label="Modern Baseball"/><category term="This Song Is Gonna Buy Brendan Lukens A New Pair Of Socks" label="This Song Is Gonna Buy Brendan Lukens A New Pair Of Socks"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kesi/God_Dag/</id><title>Kesi - God Dag - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:13:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:13:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kesi/God_Dag/" title="Kesi - God Dag - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sikken dejlig dag det er i dag <br><br>Jeg ka' maerke, det bli'r en god dag <br>Sa jeg rammer min dans la' mig dans', uh la la la <br>Plejede at sidde i 2A <br>Nu 'jeg en af dem, der ikk' er to af, uh la la la <br>Har du det ligesom mig Jeg kan aldrig lave en fejl <br>Jeg' en vinder la' mig vise vej <br>Har det rart, det' et godt sted at start' <br>Og vi' fuldt fart, til vi' ude herfra <br><br>For vi' ovenpa, bare en tar til <br>Og det gar ned, ja, det gar <br>Ingen af os star stille vi forstar at spil' <br>Sa det gar ned, ja, det gar <br><br>Drikker min drink, se mig lave min dans <br>Uh la la la <br>Fre frem og tilbage, for det' en af de der dage <br>Uh la la la <br>For jeg har det sadan, uh la la la la, la la la la <br>Uh la la la la, uh uh, sikken dejlig dag det er i dag <br>Uh la la la la, la la la la <br>Uh la la la la, uh uh <br><br>Jeg ka' maerke, det bli'r en god nat <br>Sa jeg rammer min drink la' mig drik', uh la la la <br>Plejede at sidde pa sofaen <br>Nu 'det hovedet ud af soltaget, uh la la la <br>Har vi tog det ens Jeg har nok til, vi ka' del' <br>De her naetter bli'r alt for sen' <br>Ingen ro, vi har alt, hvad vi skal bruge <br>Pa det helt gode, til vi' inde i zonen <br><br>For vi' ovenpa, bare en tar til <br>Og det gar ned, ja, det gar <br>Ing ingen forspil vi gar hardt ind <br>Til det gar ned, ja, det gar <br><br>Drikker min drink, se mig lave min dans <br>Uh la la la <br>Frem frem og tilbage, for det' en af de der dage <br>Uh la la la <br>For jeg har det sadan, uh la la la la, la la la la <br>Uh la la la la, uh uh, sikken dejlig dag det er i dag <br>Uh la la la la, la la la la <br>Uh la la la la, uh uh <br><br>Jeg ka' maerke, det bli'r en god dag <br>Jeg ka' maerke, det bli'r en god dag <br>Sikken dejlig dag det er i dag <br>Jeg' en af dem, der ikk' er to af <br>Jeg ka' maerke, det bli'r en god dag <br>Sikken dejlig dag det er i dag <br>Jaja <br><br>Drikker min drink, se mig lave min dans <br>Uh la la la <br>Fre frem og tilbage, for det' en af de der dage <br>Uh la la la <br>For jeg har det sadan, uh la la la la, la la la la <br>Uh la la la la, uh uh, sikken dejlig dag det er i dag <br>Uh la la la la, la la la la <br>Uh la la la la, uh uh, sikken dejlig dag det er i dag]]></content><category term="Kesi" label="Kesi"/><category term="God Dag" label="God Dag"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엄마의_자장가/잘자라_우리아가/</id><title>엄마의 자장가 - 잘자라 우리아가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:22:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:22:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%84%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%98_%EC%9E%90%EC%9E%A5%EA%B0%80/%EC%9E%98%EC%9E%90%EB%9D%BC_%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EC%95%84%EA%B0%80/" title="엄마의 자장가 - 잘자라 우리아가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잘자라 우리아가 <br>앞뜰과 뒷동산에 <br>새들도 아가양도 <br>다들 자는데 <br><br>달님은 영창으로 <br>은구슬 금구슬을 <br>보내는 이 한밤 <br>잘자라 우리아가 <br><br>잘자라 우리아가 <br>앞뜰과 뒷동산에 <br>새들도 아가양도 <br>다들 자는데 <br><br>달님은 영창으로 <br>은구슬 금구슬을 <br>보내는 이 한밤 <br>잘자라 우리아가 <br><br>잘자라 우리아가]]></content><category term="엄마의 자장가" label="엄마의 자장가"/><category term="잘자라 우리아가" label="잘자라 우리아가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Do_U_Dirty/</id><title>Kehlani - Do U Dirty - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:30:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:30:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kehlani/Do_U_Dirty/" title="Kehlani - Do U Dirty - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Next nigga to fuck with me, gon' be stuck with me with his stuck ass <br>Bitch Watch, look Hold up, l l look, no time Okay <br><br>I, I <br><br>Up for hours drinking <br>Posted up, just reflecting on it <br>And I know you won't believe me <br>But babe, I'm cold and yeah, this life is cold <br>I say swear you won't come near me <br>Keep your heart 'cause I could fuck you up <br>Or have you never thinking clearly <br>Never thinking clearly <br>Have you all up in your feelings <br>Experienced, I did it times before <br>And I can see you from a distance <br>I could fuck you now and years later on <br>You gon' be stuck, just reminiscing <br>It's the way I ride you, let you stay inside <br>Yeah, I'ma fuck you like a vixen <br>There's something 'bout me <br><br>Swear you see the good in me <br>But that don't beat the hood in me <br>And I got my intentions and use <br>Guess I'm make believe 'cause baby, I know, baby, I know <br><br>I, I'ma do you dirty <br>Say you love me now, but baby, it's too early <br>I, I'ma do you dirty <br>You think you love me now, I think you should be worried <br><br>Up for days, been rolling <br>Sweating them bullets, don't regret the choices <br>That I made 'cause I'm still growing <br>Sign the deal and then they cut the check <br>And ever since, my color's showing <br>Change the scene, the things are better now <br>And you know the wave is never slowing <br>The wave is never slowing <br>I know that you will miss me <br>You liked it when I used to leave a wound <br>And promise I would come and kiss it <br>I fed you lies and you just ate 'em up <br>And I don't care to do the dishes <br>I ain't no wifey, ain't gon' hold you down <br>It's way more fun to be the mistress <br>I know I'm not like other bitches <br><br>Swear you see the good in me <br>But that don't beat the hood in me <br>And I got my intentions and use <br>Guess I'm make believe 'cause baby, I know, baby, I know <br><br>I, I'ma do you dirty <br>Say you love me now, but baby, it's too early <br>I, I'ma do you dirty <br>You think you love me now, I think you should be worried <br><br>You want all my time but I don't got enough <br>Baby, I can put it down but I can't put it up <br>I got too much time to live, well I'm still way too young <br>I'm still way too young, yeah <br><br>I'ma do you dirty, I, I'ma do you dirty <br>Say you love me now, but baby, it's too early <br>I, I'ma do you dirty <br>You think you love me now, I think you should be worried]]></content><category term="Kehlani" label="Kehlani"/><category term="Do U Dirty" label="Do U Dirty"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/고속도로_로맨스/</id><title>윤종신 - 고속도로 로맨스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:31:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:31:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%EA%B3%A0%EC%86%8D%EB%8F%84%EB%A1%9C_%EB%A1%9C%EB%A7%A8%EC%8A%A4/" title="윤종신 - 고속도로 로맨스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[멈추지 않고 달려 갈 거야 Baby <br>그곳의 파란 하늘 <br>보여주고 싶어 Baby <br>내 손 한번 꼭 잡아 주겠니 Baby <br>우리 오늘을 얼마나 <br>손꼽아 기다렸나 <br>찌는 더위도 나는 좋아 <br>타는 태양도 좋아 <br>이렇게 너와 달리고 있는데 <br>어디쯤 왔나 우리 사랑 <br>후끈 달아 오를 곳 <br>조금만 조금만 더 빠르게 <br>창을 열어 소리쳐봐 <br>우리는 바다로 가요 <br>답답한 도시는 버린 지 오래 <br>까맣게 타서 돌아올 거예요 <br>창을 열어 소리쳐 봐 <br>우린 너무 사랑해요 <br>그래 우리는 미쳐버렸어 <br>떠난 게 좋아서 <br>The summer dream <br>찌는 더위도 나는 좋아 <br>타는 태양도 좋아 <br>이렇게 너와 달리고 있는데 <br>어디쯤 왔나 우리 사랑 <br>후끈 달아 오를 곳 <br>조금만 조금만 더 빠르게 <br>창을 열어 소리쳐봐 <br>우리는 바다로 가요 <br>답답한 도시는 버린 지 오래 <br>까맣게 타서 돌아올 거예요 <br>창을 열어 소리쳐 봐 <br>우린 너무 사랑해요 <br>그래 우리는 미쳐버렸어 <br>떠난 게 좋아서 <br>창을 열어 소리쳐봐 <br>우리는 바다로 가요 <br>답답한 도시는 버린 지 오래 <br>까맣게 타서 돌아올 거예요 <br>창을 열어 소리쳐 봐 <br>우린 너무 사랑해요 <br>그래 우리는 미쳐버렸어 <br>떠난 게 좋아서 <br>The summer dream <br>창을 열어 <br>창을 열어 <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="고속도로 로맨스" label="고속도로 로맨스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/해변_Mood_Song/</id><title>윤종신 - 해변 Mood Song - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:31:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:31:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%ED%95%B4%EB%B3%80_Mood_Song/" title="윤종신 - 해변 Mood Song - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[부드러워 모래밭 <br>잔잔히 부서지는 <br>파도 소리 앞에서 <br>너와 나 단둘이 <br>이게 바로 천국 아니겠니 <br>안겨 볼래 내 품에 <br>그렇게 넓고 <br>우람하지는 않겠지만 <br>좋잖아 이럴 땐 <br>그냥 와락 안겨 보는 거야 <br>우리 여기에서 <br>그냥 확 살아버릴까 <br>난 부족할 게 없어 <br>내가 필요한 건 너뿐인데 <br>너 하나만 있어 준다면 <br>내 인생 바랄 게 없어 <br>I love you <br>바라 볼래 나의 눈 <br>무언가 이글거리는 게 <br>보이지 않니 <br>불타는 내 사랑 <br>걷잡을 수 없이 번진 거야 <br>우리 여기에서 <br>그냥 확 살아버릴까 <br>난 부족할 게 없어 <br>내가 필요한 건 너뿐인데 <br>너 하나만 있어 준다면 <br>내 인생 바랄 게 없어 <br>I love you <br>내 인생 바랄 게 없어 <br>I love you <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="해변 Mood Song" label="해변 Mood Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/미행/</id><title>윤종신 - 미행 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:31:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:31:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%EB%AF%B8%ED%96%89/" title="윤종신 - 미행 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[붐비는 사람들 속 한가운데 <br>서두르게 뒤돌아본다 <br>분명히 너였기에 <br>그리운 너였기에 <br>애타게 다가간다 <br>그토록 보고 싶던 한 사람이 <br>지금 내 앞을 걸어간다 <br>부를까 너의 이름 <br>어깨를 두드릴까 <br>점점 가까워진다 <br>잊기엔 너무 사랑했어 <br>이별한 그 날부터 깨달았던 <br>결국 추억은 짐이 될 거란 걸 <br>지샌 밤이 하루하루 가르쳐주고 <br>차마 부르지 못해 걷기만 해 <br>니가 가는 그 길 따라서 <br>붐비는 사람들 속 <br>그 안에 뒤섞인 나 <br>이젠 못 알아보네 <br>잊기엔 너무 사랑했어 <br>이별한 그 날부터 깨달았던 <br>결국 추억은 짐이 될 거란 걸 <br>지샌 밤이 하루하루 가르쳐주고 <br>이젠 너를 부르고 싶어 <br>너무 부르고 싶던 사람 <br>나를 바라보는 너의 눈빛 <br>그게 그리웠던 거야 <br>기억 속의 너로 버텨 온 <br>지쳐버린 이별 견디기는 <br>이제 더 이상 힘을 잃어가고 <br>잊기엔 너무 사랑했어 <br>이별한 그 날부터 깨달았던 <br>결국 추억은 짐이 될 거란 걸 <br>지샌 밤이 하루하루 가르쳐주고 <br>조금씩 빨라지는 니 발걸음 <br>이젠 널 부르려 한 순간 <br>기다리던 그 사람 <br>너를 품에 안는다 <br>난 얼른 돌아섰네 <br>그래 그랬었구나 <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="미행" label="미행"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/오랜만에/</id><title>윤종신 - 오랜만에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:31:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:31:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%EC%98%A4%EB%9E%9C%EB%A7%8C%EC%97%90/" title="윤종신 - 오랜만에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[묻지 말아요 잘 있었냐고 <br>그렇다며 고개 끄덕이기엔 <br>너무 힘들게 보낸 시간이었죠 <br>지친 내 모습 보이지 않나요 <br>우연히 그대 내 소식 듣고 <br>너무 반가웠다구요 <br>하지만 내게 그대 소식은 <br>며칠 밤을 헤매게 하죠 <br>나 이제 그대에게는 <br>그저 오랜만에 만난 <br>친구인가요 추억인가요 <br>그대에겐 너무 쉬운 걸 <br>나 지금 그댈 보아요 <br>마냥 웃고만 있는 모습을 <br>어떤 아픔도 견딜 수 있는 <br>모진 그대를 배울 수 있게 <br>기억 하나요 우리가 했던 <br>꽤나 많은 약속들 <br>단 하나 그대 지켜주었죠 <br>지금 우리 서로 잊자던 <br>나 이제 그대에게는 <br>그저 오랜만에 만난 <br>친구인가요 추억인가요 <br>그대에겐 너무 쉬운 걸 <br>나 지금 그댈 보아요 <br>마냥 웃고만 있는 모습을 <br>어떤 아픔도 견딜 수 있는 <br>모진 그대를 배울 수 있게 <br>그대처럼 웃을 순 없어도 <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="오랜만에" label="오랜만에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/그리움_축제/</id><title>윤종신 - 그리움 축제 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:31:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:31:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9B%80_%EC%B6%95%EC%A0%9C/" title="윤종신 - 그리움 축제 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한밤 뒤척인 뒤 물 한잔 <br>내 가슴 스며들면 <br>그 밤 포기하듯 <br>그 음악을 튼다 <br>점점 검은 밤이 다 보여 <br>돌아가고 싶은 그때가 보여 <br>그리운 사람아 <br>볼륨을 높여줘 <br>가끔씩 찾아오는 그때 그대 <br>내 자그만 방엔 축제가 열리고 <br>모두가 찾아와 <br>옛 친구 옛 추억 그 향기 <br>꾹꾹 눌러왔던 그리움 축제 <br>혼자 부딪히는 건배에 <br>보고픈 그대 미소 <br>어디서 뭘 하든 <br>그 미소 잃지 마 <br>가끔씩 찾아오는 그때 그대 <br>내 자그만 방엔 축제가 열리고 <br>모두가 찾아와 <br>옛 친구 옛 추억 그 향기 <br>꾹꾹 눌러왔던 그리움 축제 <br>다시는 다신 오지 않겠지 <br>마냥 좋았던 날 <br>잘 몰라서 좋은 날 <br>세상 이렇게 어려운 걸 <br>그때는 서로 몰라서 좋았던 날 <br>다시는 다신 오지 않겠지 <br>그 영원함을 꿈꾸던 그 소년 하나 <br>그리워 그리워하다 <br>축제의 밤은 아무 일 없던 것처럼 <br>내일을 살겠지 <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="그리움 축제" label="그리움 축제"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/전역하던_날/</id><title>윤종신 - 전역하던 날 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:31:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:31:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%EC%A0%84%EC%97%AD%ED%95%98%EB%8D%98_%EB%82%A0/" title="윤종신 - 전역하던 날 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오지 않을 것 같던 날이 <br>내게도 찾아와주었죠 <br>보고픈 사람들 맞으며 <br>나의 오늘은 흐르고 있는데 <br>하루 종일 웃던 얼굴이 <br>이젠 제 모습을 찾아요 <br>그리움에 찌든 눈가에 취해 <br>숨겨 버리려 하는 눈물 <br>아무도 그대 얘기 않으려 해도 <br>이 자린 떠올리게 하네 <br>단 한 사람 빠져버린 내 옆자릴 <br>모두 모를 리가 있나요 <br>오히려 그리워 <br>하루하루를 지우며 <br>그대를 만나려 기다린 날들이 <br>아무도 모르게 발길 돌려보는 곳 <br>서럽게 닫혀진 그 낯익은 집 앞 <br>그냥 실컷 울고 싶은데 <br>이젠 눈물이 쑥스러워 <br>내내 웃어대기만 하는 <br>내가 지겹도록 원망스러워 <br>다들 부딪히는 술잔들 속엔 <br>날 보는 안쓰러움 담겨 <br>거뜬히 견딜 거라던 <br>그대의 기다림은 너무 길었나요 <br>오히려 그리워 <br>하루하루를 지우며 <br>그대를 만나려 기다린 날들이 <br>아무도 모르게 발길 돌려보는 곳 <br>서럽게 닫혀진 그 낯익은 집 앞 <br>오히려 그리워 <br>하루하루를 지우며 <br>그대를 만나려 기다린 날들이 <br>아무도 모르게 발길 돌려보는 곳 <br>서럽게 닫혀진 그 낯익은 집 앞 <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="전역하던 날" label="전역하던 날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/모처럼/</id><title>윤종신 - 모처럼 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:31:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:31:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%EB%AA%A8%EC%B2%98%EB%9F%BC/" title="윤종신 - 모처럼 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모처럼 나와 보았네 <br>아직도 익숙한 거리 <br>그렇게 잊기 위해서 피해 다닌 <br>골목골목 낯익은 가게들 <br>모처럼 마셔 보았네 <br>그때와 똑같은 잔에 <br>하나도 바뀌지 않은 <br>그 의자와 <br>그 향기와 날 알아보는 <br>주인까지 <br>시간이 멈춘 걸까 <br>여긴 모든 게 그대로인데 <br>창가에 비친 내 얼굴과 <br>맞은편 자리는 <br>이제 초라하게 변해 <br>이곳은 어울리지 않아 <br>마침 흘러나온 <br>그 때 그 노래를 <br>다시 따라 해 봐도 <br>그저 내 목소리만이 <br>무안하게 들려오네 <br>비어있는 내 맞은편과 <br>더 이상은 할 말 없어서 <br>모처럼 나온 내 발길 돌리네 <br>시간이 멈춘 걸까 <br>여긴 모든 게 그대로인데 <br>창가에 비친 내 얼굴과 <br>맞은편 자리는 <br>이젠 초라하게 변해 <br>이곳은 어울리지 않아 <br>마침 흘러나온 <br>그 때 그 노래를 <br>다시 따라 해 봐도 <br>그저 내 목소리만이 <br>무안하게 들려오네 <br>비어있는 내 맞은편과 <br>더 이상은 할 말 없어서 <br>모처럼 나온 내 발길 돌리네 <br>또 언제 나오게 될런지 <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="모처럼" label="모처럼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/나의_안부/</id><title>윤종신 - 나의 안부 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:32:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:32:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%95%88%EB%B6%80/" title="윤종신 - 나의 안부 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여전히 담배 나 끊지 못했어 <br>너 싫어했던 술 더 는 것 같은데 <br>니가 떠나갔어도 <br>날 고치지 못했어 <br>나의 친구들 혹시 궁금하니 <br>아빠가 된 녀석 부자가 된 녀석 <br>다들 너무 잘 있어 <br>널 모른 척해주며 <br>이사도 했어 추억 없는 <br>낯선 이름의 마을로 <br>더디 가던 시간은 어느 샌가 <br>날 어른으로 만들었지만 <br>널 볼 수 있었던 다투기도 했던 <br>그 어린 날이 부럽기도 한 걸 <br>부질없이 내 소식 말하는 걸 <br>처량한 후횐 줄 오해 말아 <br>누구나 한 번쯤 돌아보는 세월 <br>그 중에 너를 빼놓을 수 없어서 <br>너의 친구와 마주친 적 있지 <br>살짝 띤 미소에 난 알 수 있었지 <br>너의 좋은 안부를 <br>그래 그래야 하지 <br>여행도 했어 추억 없는 <br>바다는 너무 파랬어 <br>더디 가던 시간은 어느 샌가 <br>날 어른으로 만들었지만 <br>널 볼 수 있었던 다투기도 했던 <br>그 어린 날이 부럽기도 한 걸 <br>부질없이 내 소식 말하는 걸 <br>처량한 후횐 줄 오해 말아 <br>누구나 한 번쯤 돌아보는 세월 <br>그 중에 너를 빼놓을 수 없어서 <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="나의 안부" label="나의 안부"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/잘했어요/</id><title>윤종신 - 잘했어요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:32:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:32:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%EC%9E%98%ED%96%88%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="윤종신 - 잘했어요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대 잘산다고 <br>소식 들었죠 <br>그때의 그 사람과 <br>그토록 원망했던 <br>그대 선택 <br>잘했어요 <br>나 역시 좋아요 <br>그대 덕분에 <br>나를 알았죠 <br>너무나 쉽게 <br>무너져 버리는 <br>나를 알게 해 주었고 <br>어쩌면 돌아오지 않을까 <br>날 잊긴 힘들 거야 <br>그대의 잘못된 <br>선택이길 비는 <br>비겁한 날 알았죠 <br>떠올리지 마요 <br>그대 옛 사랑은 <br>너무나 못난 사람이죠 <br>추억이라 하면서 <br>가끔이라도 <br>내 생각은 <br>정말 안 돼요 <br>이제 만들어가요 <br>그대들의 추억을 <br>내 탓에 늦게 만났지만 <br>나도 잘 살 거예요 <br>또 아파하기엔 <br>내 가슴에게 <br>너무 미안해 <br>떠올리지 마요 <br>그대 옛 사랑은 <br>너무나 못난 사람이죠 <br>추억이라 하면서 <br>가끔이라도 <br>내 생각은 <br>정말 안 돼요 <br>이제 만들어가요 <br>그대들의 추억을 <br>내 탓에 늦게 만났지만 <br>나도 잘 살 거예요 <br>또 아파하기엔 <br>내 가슴에게 <br>너무 미안해 <br>건강해요 <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="잘했어요" label="잘했어요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/치과에서/</id><title>윤종신 - 치과에서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:32:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:32:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%EC%B9%98%EA%B3%BC%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C/" title="윤종신 - 치과에서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[선생님의 하늘색 <br>마스크 한심해하네 <br>그동안 이 아픈 걸 <br>어떻게 참아왔냐고 <br>제가 너무 미련하죠 <br>하고 말하려 해도 <br>이미 마취제로 <br>굳어버린 혀 <br>구멍 뚫린 하늘색 <br>헝겊이 나를 덮는다 <br>그 하늘 위로 그려지는 <br>아직 선명한 얼굴 <br>이 와중에 떠오르는 <br>너는 도대체 뭐니 <br>그라인더 윙하고 <br>나를 향하네 <br>진작 찾아와야 했어 <br>진작 잊어버려야 <br>했는데 두려워서 <br>가끔 한 번씩 <br>몸서리치는 그 순간 <br>의자엔 나 혼잔게 두려워 <br>깊숙이도 파고 <br>들어가는 그라인더야 <br>좀 더 가면 니가 <br>처음 보는 상처가 있어 <br>안 아프게 그것도 <br>좀 갈아 없애주겠니 <br>치통의 몇 배로 <br>나를 괴롭혀 <br>진작 찾아와야 했어 <br>진작 잊어버려야 <br>했는데 두려워서 <br>가끔 한 번씩 <br>몸서리치는 그 순간 <br>의자엔 나 혼잔게 두려워 <br>하늘은 걷히고 <br>마스크는 내게 말하네 <br>오늘 밤에 무지 붓고 <br>아플지도 몰라요 <br>괜찮아요 오늘 <br>하루 만에 끝나준다면 <br>힘들었던 그 밤 <br>끝나준다면 <br>마취 안 풀린 채 <br>안녕히 계세요 <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="치과에서" label="치과에서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/말꼬리/</id><title>윤종신 - 말꼬리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:32:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:32:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%EB%A7%90%EA%BC%AC%EB%A6%AC/" title="윤종신 - 말꼬리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비는 오고 너는 가려 하고 <br>내 마음 눅눅하게 잠기고 <br>낡은 흑백영화 한 장면처럼 <br>내 말은 자꾸 끊기고 <br>사랑한 만큼 힘들었다고 <br>사랑하기에 날 보낸다고 <br>말도 안 되는 <br>그 이별 핑계에 <br>나의 대답을 원하니 <br>너만큼 사랑하지 <br>않았었나 봐 <br>나는 좀 덜 사랑해서 <br>널 못 보내 <br>가슴이 너무 좁아 <br>떠나간 너의 <br>행복 빌어줄 <br>그런 드라마 같은 <br>그런 속 깊은 사랑 <br>내겐 없으니 <br>사랑하면 내게 <br>머물러줘 <br>사랑하면 이별은 <br>없는 거야 <br>너만큼 사랑하지 <br>않았었나 봐 <br>나는 좀 덜 사랑해서 <br>널 못 보내 <br>가슴이 너무 좁아 <br>떠나간 너의 <br>행복 빌어줄 <br>그런 드라마 같은 <br>그런 속 깊은 사랑 <br>내겐 없으니 <br>우리의 사랑 <br>바닥 보일 때까지 <br>우리의 사랑 <br>메말라 갈라질 때까지 <br>다 쓰고 가 <br>남은 사랑처럼 <br>쓸모 없는 건 <br>만들지 마요 <br>손톱만큼의 작은 사랑도 <br>내게 다 주고 가요 <br>그러니까 이별은 <br>없는 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="말꼬리" label="말꼬리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/You_Are_So_Beautiful/</id><title>윤종신 - You Are So Beautiful - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:32:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:32:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/You_Are_So_Beautiful/" title="윤종신 - You Are So Beautiful - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 어떻게 <br>표현할 수 있을까 <br>내게 있어 <br>왜 그토록 <br>나를 떨리게 하지 <br>그 생각 속에 살다 <br>내가 빠져든 사람 <br>그 모든 것들에 <br>검은 눈과 여린 듯 <br>목소리와 작은 입술 <br>웃음을 가리는 <br>가녀린 손과 <br>머릴 넘기는 또 한 손 <br>혼자 걸을 땐 <br>조금 무표정한 걸 아니 <br>너의 모든 건 <br>내게 기억되어 <br>다가가게 하지 <br>가까이 바라본 <br>너의 모습은 <br>또 새로운 널 알게 해 <br>내가 사랑에 빠진 이유는 <br>너무 쉬운 것이었어 <br>운 좋게 너와 <br>마주칠 수 있었고 <br>그날 이후 내겐 <br>You are so beautiful <br>Hey I need your love <br>Everytime <br>You are so beautiful <br>I feel your heart <br>Everytime <br>You are so <br>널 어떻게 <br>표현할 수 있을까 <br>내게 있어 <br>왜 그토록 <br>나를 떨리게 하지 <br>그 생각 속에 살다 <br>내가 빠져든 사람 <br>그 모든 것들에 <br>검은 눈과 여린 듯 <br>목소리와 작은 입술 <br>웃음을 가리는 <br>가녀린 손과 <br>머릴 넘기는 또 한 손 <br>혼자 걸을 땐 <br>조금 무표정한 걸 아니 <br>너의 모든 건 <br>내게 기억되어 <br>다가가게 하지 <br>가까이 바라본 <br>너의 모습은 <br>또 새로운 널 알게 해 <br>내가 사랑에 빠진 이유는 <br>너무 쉬운 것이었어 <br>운 좋게 너와 <br>마주칠 수 있었고 <br>그날 이후 내겐 <br>You are so beautiful <br>널 더 알아야겠지만 <br>나는 조급한 사람인 걸 <br>충분히 너에게 <br>빠질 만큼 빠져버렸지 <br>세상에서 널 제일 <br>아름다워하는 사람 <br>어느 날 널 찾아갈 거야 <br>Hey I need your love <br>Everytime <br>You are so beautiful <br>I feel your heart <br>Everytime <br>You are so <br>You are so beautiful <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="You Are So Beautiful" label="You Are So Beautiful"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/그래도_크리스마스/</id><title>윤종신 - 그래도 크리스마스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:32:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:32:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%98%EB%8F%84_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%A4%EB%A7%88%EC%8A%A4/" title="윤종신 - 그래도 크리스마스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[참 힘들었죠 <br>올해 돌아보면 <br>어쩜 그렇게도 <br>그럴 수가 있는 건가요 <br>잘했어요 <br>참아 내기 힘든 그 <br>용서할 수 없는 걸 <br>다 함께 외쳤던 그 날들 <br>정말 젠틀했던 강렬했던 <br>뭘 바라는지 또 뭘 잃었는지 <br>우린 모두 알고 있죠 <br>하나하나 다시 해요 <br>지금 내 옆 거짓말 못 하는 <br>작은 꿈들로 사는 사람들 <br>그들과 건배해 <br>오늘은 그래도 크리스마스 <br>믿고 믿고 싶어 <br>고개 끄덕일 수 있는 <br>내일 이제는 <br>그게 그렇게도 <br>어려운 일인 건지 <br>나 어른 되는 동안 <br>사랑하기도 모자란 <br>세월 속에서 <br>내리는 하얀 눈 <br>진실만큼은 덮지 말아줘 <br>그래도 크리스마스 <br>그래도 <br>I Love You <br>My Love <br>그래도 내 사랑 <br>내 사람 행복해 줘 <br>뚜루루루 나아질 거야 <br>내일은 <br>길을 걷다 누구라도 <br>마주치면 같은 맘일걸 <br>Merry Merry Christmas <br>오 그래도 크리스마스 <br>곧 해피 뉴이어 <br>더 어른 되면 좀 더 <br>괜찮은 얘길 해요 <br>가슴이 따듯해지는 <br>미소가 떠나지 않는 날들 <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="그래도 크리스마스" label="그래도 크리스마스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/널_사랑한_너_With_민서/</id><title>윤종신 - 널 사랑한 너 (With 민서) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:32:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:32:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%EB%84%90_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%9C_%EB%84%88_With_%EB%AF%BC%EC%84%9C/" title="윤종신 - 널 사랑한 너 (With 민서) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 나에게 왜 그러니 <br>어쩜 그래 <br>나를 뻔히 알면서 <br>너를 위했던 날 알면서 <br>내가 좋아서 한 <br>배려일지라도 <br>그래도 그럴 수는 없는 거야 <br>나쁜 나쁜 <br>구속하지 말자고 <br>서로 자유롭자고 <br>그게 무슨 사랑이야 <br>편리한 사랑 못하는 <br>내게 단 한 번이라도 <br>배려할 순 없겠니 <br>이젠 니 차례야 <br>무례한 그 연애의 결론을 <br>해피하게 끝내긴 <br>바닥난 배려 <br>부디 너도 빠지길 바래 <br>니가 훨씬 더 사랑해 <br>가슴이 찢어지다가 <br>부서지다 가루되어 <br>뻥 뚫린 너의 다음 사랑 <br>너의 삶이 궁금해 <br>어쩜 그래 <br>너만이 너무나 중요한 너 <br>한때는 너보다 너를 <br>더 사랑하나 했지만 <br>너보단 아닌 듯해 <br>이젠 니 차례야 <br>무례한 그 연애의 결론을 <br>해피하게 끝내긴 <br>바닥난 배려 <br>부디 너도 빠지길 바래 <br>니가 훨씬 더 사랑해 <br>가슴이 찢어지다가 <br>부서지다 가루되어 <br>뻥 뚫린 너의 다음 사랑 <br>꼭 그런 사랑 하길 바래 <br>그걸 느끼길 바래 <br>얼마나 아픈 건지 <br>눈물 마르면 <br>스치듯 한 번만 떠올려 <br>널 죽도록 사랑했던 <br>조금도 배려 못 받은 <br>널 고이 떠나 보내준 <br>이 예쁜 노래 주인공을 <br>결국 넌 사랑 받을 걸 <br>넌 원래 그런 사람이야 <br>다시 다시는 그러지 마 <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="널 사랑한 너 (With 민서)" label="널 사랑한 너 (With 민서)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/처음_With_민서/</id><title>윤종신 - 처음 (With 민서) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:32:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:32:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%EC%B2%98%EC%9D%8C_With_%EB%AF%BC%EC%84%9C/" title="윤종신 - 처음 (With 민서) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모든 게 다 처음이라서 <br>많이 어색하고 별로였겠지 <br>마지막 그 인사말조차도 <br>넌 나보다 훨씬 빛나 보여서 <br>괜히 움츠러든 내가 미웠어 <br>그게 더 바보 같았었겠지 <br>늘 꿈인 것만 같아서 <br>그게 불안했었어 <br>내 사람 아닌 것만 같아서 <br>내 마지막이 되고 싶다던 <br>너를 믿지 못한 <br>나의 잘못이겠지 뭐 <br>그래도 난 처음이었어 <br>밤을 새며 누굴 꿈꿔본 것도 <br>이렇게 마구 아픈 마음도 <br>어른스러워야 할 것 같아서 <br>맘이랑은 조금 다른 말 했어 <br>난 혼자여도 자신 있다고 <br>늘 내가 더 사랑해서 <br>지는 것만 같았어 <br>그게 난 제일 바보 같았어 <br>널 믿는다면 영원할 거라던 말 <br>믿지 못한 내가 전부 망친 거야 <br>나 그래도 너의 곁에서 <br>너무 눈부셨던 날들 <br>그게 다 거짓말일 린 없잖아 <br>내 손을 보석보다 더 소중히 <br>쥐고 말했던 그 멋진 말들도 <br>모든 게 다 처음이었어 <br>소리 들릴 만큼 가슴 뛴 것도 <br>소리 내 울며 잠든 그 밤도 <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="처음 (With 민서)" label="처음 (With 민서)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/가을옷/</id><title>윤종신 - 가을옷 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:32:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:32:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%EA%B0%80%EC%9D%84%EC%98%B7/" title="윤종신 - 가을옷 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 가을옷 하나씩 꺼내 <br>좀만 지나면 못 입을 옷 <br>성격 급한 겨울이 두툼하게 <br>덮어버리는 바람에 <br>그때 추억은 스치듯 <br>시작했어 이 가을날에 <br>연 브라운이 짙어질 쯤 <br>무르익던 두 입술 뺨을 지나 <br>너의 니트에 얼굴 묻던 <br>우리의 가을밤이여 <br>제법 쌀쌀해지면 손을 감싸던 <br>그 길 위 우리의 투 톤 <br>다가올 계절의 준비를 하던 <br>영원할 것 같던 <br>깊었던 믿었던 그 계절 <br>타버린 낙엽 냄새만 그대로 <br>뚜루루루 뚜루루루루 뚜루루루 <br>주머니 속 종잇 조각 <br>그 언젠지 몰라도 <br>그때 흔적일 것 같은 <br>괜시리 계절 타려 해 <br>계절 다시 타려 해 <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="가을옷" label="가을옷"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/age/</id><title>윤종신 - age - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:32:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:32:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/age/" title="윤종신 - age - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그땐 그대 어디쯤에 있을까 <br>한없이 약속 장소에 기다렸었지 <br>오지 않을 것도 알지 못한 채 <br>마냥 또 마냥 기다려 <br>터벅 터벅 터벅 걷다가 <br>공중전화 앞에서 <br>대신 전화 걸어 달라고 <br>지나치는 여인에게 부탁해 <br>Let’s go back <br>Go back 절실했던 고백 <br>그대 하나에 내 모든 걸 <br>옴팡 걸었던 <br>Let’s go back <br>Go go back 나 고백하던 날 <br>92 or 93 or 그 맘 그때쯤 <br>봄비 보봄비 촉촉이 오던 날 <br>춘천 가는 기차 탔던 <br>수업 없던 날 <br>뭥미 뭐뭥미 웬 이별 통보니 <br>오 결국 이별 여행 됐어 <br>터벅 터벅 터벅 걷다가 <br>레코드방 앞에서 <br>빛과 소금 테잎 사다가 <br>그대 떠난 뒤만 <br>늘어지게 들었어 <br>Let’s go back <br>Go back 절실했던 고백 <br>그대 하나에 내 모든 걸 <br>옴팡 걸었던 <br>Let’s go back <br>Go go back 나 고백하던 날 <br>92 or 93 or 그 맘 그때쯤 <br>On my way <br>On my life 고마워 <br>Oh good bye <br>Oh my love 또다시 <br>세월에 길이 다 넓어져 <br>아마 우린 마주치긴 <br>어려울 거야 <br>Let’s go back <br>Go back 절실했던 고백 <br>그대 하나에 내 모든 걸 <br>옴팡 걸었던 <br>Let’s go back <br>Go go back 나 고백하던 날 <br>92 or 93 or 그 맘 그때쯤 <br>Oh come back <br>Come back <br>내 현재로 Come back <br>익숙해진 나의 루틴 <br>살아남자던 <br>Come back <br>Come come back <br>괜찮은 아재로 <br>2016 할일 많은 <br>One more night <br>추억보다 걱정 많은 <br>Before the dawn <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="age" label="age"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/Empty_City_With_개코/</id><title>윤종신 - Empty City (With 개코) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:32:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:32:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/Empty_City_With_%EA%B0%9C%EC%BD%94/" title="윤종신 - Empty City (With 개코) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[텅 빈 거릴 걸어가네 <br>푹푹푹 찌는 보도블록 속 <br>어쩜 이리 비어 보일까 <br>죄다 휴가 떠난 걸까 <br>올해 내 이별은 Summer <br>작년 너와 짜릿했던 Summer <br>또 어디 놀러 갔니 Summer <br>텅텅텅 비어버린 Hot city <br>All right All right 땀 찬 겨드랑이 <br>I got the Deodorant <br>Good luck Good luck 넌 부디 <br>Hot city 떠나 확실히 잡아 <br>New love new face face <br>나도 곧 가리다 가리다 <br>가리다 가리다 with my new face <br>프리다 프리다 프리다 <br>프리다 프리다 from you <br>가리다 가리다 가리다 <br>가리다 with my new face <br>프리다 프리다 프리다 <br>프리다 프리다 from you <br>너 하나 없는 거리가 <br>이리 상쾌할 줄 알았다면 <br>진작에 정리했지 <br>너와의 관계는 <br>미세먼지보다 숨이 막혀 <br>비 한번 왈칵 쏟아질 때 됐지 <br>가뭄의 끝 우산 꽃이 피네 <br>난 이 도시 구석구석 <br>막 쑤시고 다닐래 <br>식사 후 이쑤시개처럼 <br>발정 난 개처럼 <br>내 차례로 계 탄 것처럼 <br>술 한잔 부었다 담배 한 대 물었다 <br>친구들아 미안 그간 <br>쪼잔하게 굴었다 <br>10bands 50bands 아 몰라 <br>나 지금 돈뭉치 끈 몇 개 풀었다 <br>일이 술술 풀려 향수 안 뿌려도 <br>쿨내가 풀풀 풍겨 풀풀 풍겨 <br>좀 치열했지 너와 난 <br>디에고와 프리다 <br>난 이제 리베로 <br>다른 말로 Free맨이다 <br>Spend my money tonight <br>With my new honey tonight <br>다 죽었어 이 텅 빈 도시를 <br>다 태워버릴 거야 <br>Burn the city tonight <br>Burn the city tonight <br>너 하나 떠나간 게 뭐라고 <br>광란의 heart &amp; city is empty <br>Empty city 저 길 구석에 <br>죄다 버려버리겠어 <br>All dry All dry 내 맘 다 말라 <br>금이 쭉쭉 가 <br>I'll try I'll try 이 empty city를 <br>나하고 떠나갈 사람아 <br>Where where where are you <br>나도 곧 가리다 가리다 <br>가리다 가리다 with my new face <br>프리다 프리다 프리다 <br>프리다 프리다 from you <br>가리다 가리다 가리다 <br>가리다 with my new face <br>프리다 프리다 프리다 <br>프리다 프리다 from you <br>쓸쓸하지 않아 이 텅 빈 거리가 <br>Hell no hell no <br>내 마음속에 미니멀리즘을 <br>실천하는 중이야 <br>Hell yeah hell yeah <br>내일 난 떠날 거야 무작정 <br>벙커로 숨을 거니까 나 찾지 마 <br>벌써 티켓 done 미련 none <br>잃었던 나의 남성성 돌아와 줘 <br>양손을 파리처럼 <br>빌어도 날 볼 수 없어 <br>아마 난 근사한 식사 in Paris <br>행운을 빌어 날 찾는 길은 <br>고되고 힘들 거야 <br>마치 설국열차 에드해리스 <br>Spend my money tomorrow <br>With my new honey not alone <br>다 버리고 이 텅 빈 도시를 <br>떠나 버릴 거야 <br>나의 은신처로 <br>가리다 가리다 가리다 <br>나의 은신처로 <br>프리다 프리다 프리다 <br>지금 난 근심 제로 완전 자유다 <br>가리다 가리다 가리다 <br>너로부터 옆에 딱 붙어 <br>허니허니 옆에 딱 붙어 <br>프리다 프리다 프리다 <br>몇 시 비행 tres bien <br>I’m free 다 from you <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="Empty City (With 개코)" label="Empty City (With 개코)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/의미_없다_With_한해_키디비/</id><title>윤종신 - 의미 없다 (With 한해, 키디비) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T11:32:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T11:32:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/%EC%9D%98%EB%AF%B8_%EC%97%86%EB%8B%A4_With_%ED%95%9C%ED%95%B4_%ED%82%A4%EB%94%94%EB%B9%84/" title="윤종신 - 의미 없다 (With 한해, 키디비) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[더럽게 힘 빠지는 초여름 <br>Saturday Night <br>온난화 때문인가 <br>쟤 얼굴은 빨간 색깔 <br>맥주 한잔 걸친 <br>James Brown 보여줘 발재간 <br>황혼에서 새벽까지 Fiesta <br>수많은 girl들은 놀러 올래 <br>Saturday Night <br>내가 랩을 하길 원한다면 <br>Give me the mic <br>이거 뻔한 가사 아니니까 <br>오늘 밤새 한번 놀아제껴 보자고 <br>Till the die <br>Set you on Saturday night <br>Uptown uptown Saturday night <br>특히 Insane Saturday night <br>What the <br>이게 다 뭔 말일까 <br>아이고 의미 없다 <br>기껏 짜다리 말 멋있게 막 늘어놔도 <br>아이고 의미 없다 <br>Oh just rhythm 박자감 Baby <br>몸이 먼저 Baby <br>되도록 뇌는 쉬어 Baby <br>디립다 지껄이다 끼 부리다 아님 말다 <br>가타부타 족족 따지지 맘마 <br>논리 버려 Baby <br>우리말 그루비리 Baby <br>디립다 지껄이다 끼 부리다 아님 말다 <br>가타부타 족족 따지지 뱅뱅 <br>지금 내 가사는 의미 없어 휘뚜루마뚜루 <br>8마디 대충 채우고 나서 기분을 맛보는 중 <br>월간 윤종신이라고 달라지나 <br>갈겨써도 저작권료 따박따박 나올 테니까 <br>난 쉽게 벌어먹고 벌어먹는 래퍼니까 <br>공연장에서는 냅다 물만 뿌리면 되니까 <br>아싸라비야 아주 신나는 인생이야 <br>누가 대신 살아봤으면 해 <br>너네한텐 미안 <br>I’ll catch you on Saturday night <br>Downtown downtown Saturday night <br>특히 Insane Saturday night <br>What the <br>이게 다 뭔 말일까 <br>아이고 의미 없다 <br>기껏 짜다리 말 멋있게 막 늘어놔도 <br>아이고 의미 없다 <br>Oh Just Just Just Just Baby <br>몸이 먼저 Baby <br>몸이 먼저 Baby <br>되도록 뇌는 쉬어 Baby <br>되도록 뇌는 쉬어 Baby <br>디립다 지껄이다 <br>끼 부리다 아님 말다 <br>가타부타 족족 따지지 작작 <br>논리 버려 Baby <br>논리 버려 Baby <br>우리말 그루비리 Baby <br>우리말 그루비리 Baby <br>디립다 지껄이다 <br>끼 부리다 아님 말다 <br>가타부타 족족 따지지 맘마 <br>안 되는 머리를 굴리고 굴려 <br>가사를 막 쥐어짜 봤자 <br>회초릴 내미는 사람들 말해 <br>대 손 발바닥 <br>참 뭔 상관이야 <br>또 설상가상 난 문제아 <br>넌 너대로 지적질 해 <br>난 그냥 흔들어랄라라 <br>오 생각 스위친 Off 이 비트 위로 <br>흩뿌려지는 네 막 춤사위는 이뻐 <br>Oh shit 숨 좀 쉬어 아저씨 <br>Your 그루비리 I feel it <br>스트레슨 잘 가 안녕히 <br>아이고 의미 없다 <br>이렇게 지껄여도 아무 의미 없다 <br>아이고 의미 없다 <br>좀 지쳐 그럼 숨어 띠리리 영구 없다 <br>Oh Just Rhythm 박자감 Baby <br>Yo 다 같이 그루비리 Like this <br>뚜 뚜루두루두루 Baby <br>엉덩이 부비부비 Like this <br>몸이 먼저 Baby <br>몸이 먼저 baby <br>우리말 그루비리 Baby <br>우리말 그루비리 Baby <br>디립다 지껄이다 <br>끼 부리다 아님 말다 <br>가타부타 족족 따지지 작작 <br>논리 버려 Baby <br>논리 버려 Baby <br>되도록 뇌는 쉬어 Baby <br>되도록 뇌는 쉬어 Baby <br>디립다 지껄이다 <br>끼 부리다 아님 말다 <br>가타부타 족족 따지지 맘마 <br>이렇게 하는 거 맞아요 <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="의미 없다 (With 한해, 키디비)" label="의미 없다 (With 한해, 키디비)"/></entry></feed>