<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:56:37+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/매드킨/화장/</id><title>매드킨 - 화장 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:56:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:56:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%A4%EB%93%9C%ED%82%A8/%ED%99%94%EC%9E%A5/" title="매드킨 - 화장 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[검은 세상 숨 막힌 공기 <br>나는 왜 여기에 누워있나 <br>조여 오는 이 고통은 다 <br>누가 주는 선물상자인가 <br>시간이 없어 빛도 없어 <br>여긴 땅 속 깊은 터널인가 <br>불태워진 내 몸을 살려 <br>빛나는 색을 하나하나 채워줘 <br>wake up wake up wake up <br>잠자는 내 영혼 <br>make up make up make up <br>붉게 쳐 발라줘 <br>give up give up give up <br>색바랜 내 영혼 <br>welcome welcome welcome <br>welcome to a fake face <br>조명 아래 거울 속에 <br>그려진 무표정한 얼굴에 <br>빛을 잃고 표정도 잃은 <br>의미 없이 살아난 내 영혼 <br>숨겨줘 날 빛이 없던 <br>내가 왔던 그 지하 세계로 <br>불태워줘 날 색이 없던 <br>예전의 나로 제발 돌려줘 <br>wake up wake up wake up <br>Don't wake me up tonight <br>burn up burn up burn up <br>깨어난 내 영혼 <br>give up give up give up <br>살아난 내 욕망 <br>welcome welcome welcome <br>welcome to a zombie's face <br>wake up wake up wake up <br>잠자는 내 영혼 <br>make up make up make up <br>붉게 쳐 발라줘 <br>give up give up give up <br>색바랜 내 영혼 <br>welcome welcome welcome <br>welcome to a fake face <br>wake up wake up wake up <br>Don't wake me up tonight <br>burn up burn up burn up <br>깨어난 내 영혼 <br>give up give up give up <br>살아난 내 욕망 <br>welcome welcome welcome <br>welcome to a zombie's face <br>]]></content><category term="매드킨" label="매드킨"/><category term="화장" label="화장"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Werther/Diamonds_Feat_Noa_Original_Mix/</id><title>Werther - Diamonds (Feat. Noa) (Original Mix.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:56:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:56:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Werther/Diamonds_Feat_Noa_Original_Mix/" title="Werther - Diamonds (Feat. Noa) (Original Mix.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lights <br>Lights <br>다이아몬드같이 비췄어 <br>네 눈에서 umm <br>You're voluptuous <br>손가락엔 없는 diamond rings <br>다행인 걸 woo <br>Lights <br>다이아몬드같이 비췄어 <br>네 눈에서 <br>She has jewels O A <br>Her eyes are like diamonds <br>우리의 눈이 마주쳤을 때 <br>Cant take my eyes off you woo <br>Her eyes are like diamonds <br>woo yeah <br>diamonds diamonds diamonds <br>우리의 눈이 마주쳤을 때 <br>Cant take my eyes off you woo <br>Lights <br>다이아몬드같이 비췄어 <br>네 눈에서 <br>you’re melody <br>머릿속을 계속 맴돌지 <br>떠나지않아 <br>Lights <br>다이아몬드같이 비췄어 <br>네 눈에서 <br>She has jewels O A <br>Her eyes are like diamonds <br>우리의 눈이 마주쳤을 때 <br>Cant take my eyes off you woo <br>Her eyes are like diamonds <br>woo yeah <br>diamonds diamonds diamonds <br>우리의 눈이 마주쳤을 때 <br>Cant take my eyes off you woo <br>She has jewels <br>She has jewels <br>She has jewels O A <br>Her eyes are like diamonds <br>She has jewels O A <br>Her eyes are like diamonds <br>우리의 눈이 마주쳤을 때 <br>Cant take my eyes off you woo <br>Her eyes are like diamonds <br>woo yeah <br>diamonds diamonds diamonds <br>우리의 눈이 마주쳤을 때 <br>Cant take my eyes off you woo <br>Lights <br>다이아몬드같이 비췄어 <br>네 눈에서 <br>]]></content><category term="Werther" label="Werther"/><category term="Diamonds (Feat. Noa) (Original Mix.)" label="Diamonds (Feat. Noa) (Original Mix.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Werther/Diamonds_Feat_Noa/</id><title>Werther - Diamonds (Feat. Noa) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:56:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:56:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Werther/Diamonds_Feat_Noa/" title="Werther - Diamonds (Feat. Noa) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lights <br>다이아몬드같이 비췄어 <br>네 눈에서 umm <br>You're voluptuous <br>손가락엔 없는 diamond rings <br>다행인 걸 woo <br>처음봤어 진짜 <br>너같은 여자 <br>시선이 자꾸 가 <br>아까부터 계속 쭉 지켜봤어 <br>왜 몰라 <br>Lights <br>다이아몬드같이 비췄어 <br>네 눈에서 <br>She has jewels O A <br>Her eyes are <br>like diamonds <br>우리의 눈이 마주쳤을 때 <br>Cant take my eyes off you woo <br>Her eyes are like diamonds <br>woo yeah <br>diamonds diamonds <br>우리의 눈이 마주쳤을 때 <br>Cant take my eyes off you woo <br>Lights <br>다이아몬드같이 비췄어 <br>네 눈에서 <br>you’re melody <br>머릿속을 계속 맴돌지 <br>떠나지않아 <br>네게 다가가 말을 걸어볼까 <br>멀어질까 겁이 나 <br>그대로 있어줘 girl <br>you’re my mind <br>Lights <br>다이아몬드같이 비췄어 <br>네 눈에서 <br>diamonds diamonds <br>She has jewels O A <br>Her eyes are <br>like diamonds <br>우리의 눈이 마주쳤을 때 <br>Cant take my eyes off you woo <br>Her eyes are like diamonds <br>woo yeah <br>diamonds diamonds <br>우리의 눈이 마주쳤을 때 <br>Cant take my eyes off you woo <br>Lights <br>다이아몬드같이 비췄어 <br>네 눈에서 <br>]]></content><category term="Werther" label="Werther"/><category term="Diamonds (Feat. Noa)" label="Diamonds (Feat. Noa)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/편한메아리/과거형/</id><title>편한메아리 - 과거형 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:56:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:56:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8E%B8%ED%95%9C%EB%A9%94%EC%95%84%EB%A6%AC/%EA%B3%BC%EA%B1%B0%ED%98%95/" title="편한메아리 - 과거형 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[고요한 하늘과 <br>조용한 거리 <br>깜빡이는 가로등 <br>그대 어디 있나요 <br>희미한 추억들이 <br>바람에 실려와 <br>오늘 같은 밤이면 <br>나 이곳에 서있죠 <br>싸늘한 말투와 <br>그 표정까지 <br>그리운 건 왜일까요 <br>당연한 줄 알았던 <br>우리 사이 결국엔 이렇게 <br>지난 날의 추억이여 <br>우리였던 그 날 이여 <br>아무도 없는 밤 <br>귀뚜라미 소리 <br>깜빡이는 신호등 <br>그 때 그대의 뒷모습 <br>싸늘한 말투와 <br>그 표정까지 <br>그리운 건 왜일까요 <br>당연한 줄 알았던 <br>우리 사이 결국엔 이렇게 <br>지난 날의 추억이여 <br>우리였던 그날이여 <br>철없던 시절에 눈물의 흔적 <br>오늘 같은 밤이면 <br>나 그대를 그리죠 <br>]]></content><category term="편한메아리" label="편한메아리"/><category term="과거형" label="과거형"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/No_Dodge_Brothers_노다지_브라더스/Way/</id><title>No Dodge Brothers (노다지 브라더스) - Way - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:56:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:56:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/No_Dodge_Brothers_%EB%85%B8%EB%8B%A4%EC%A7%80_%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EB%8D%94%EC%8A%A4/Way/" title="No Dodge Brothers (노다지 브라더스) - Way - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[점점 더 나를 소개하기 힘들어져 <br>쓸데없이 말이 자꾸 길어져 <br>좋게 말하면 많은 색깔의 바쁜 사람 <br>나쁜 말로는 과부하 걸린 <br>숨가쁜 사람 <br>그래서 때론 지치지 <br>이젠 맘대로 부리지 못할 치기 <br>내 능력 안에서 이쪽에서 <br>저쪽으로 뛰고는 <br>다시 기어서 원위치 <br>무리한 욕심이었을까 <br>좋은 아들과 친구 남자 <br>그리고 음악 <br>이 최고의 타이틀들을 얻기에는 <br>생각보단 부실한 빌어먹을 내 어깨 <br>할 수 있다고 골백번이고 <br>맘에 새긴 문신 <br>하지만 아직도 아무것도 <br>오늘도 왔다 갔다 바람만 부네 <br>이젠 겨울인 듯 제법 춥네 <br>난 그냥 길을 따라 걷다 <br>막다른 골목을 만났어 <br>걱정하지마 난 멈추지않아 <br>잠깐 쉬고 또 걸어 <br>하늘까지 솟아버린 벽 <br>알려주지않는 살아남는 법 <br>달콤한 거짓 도사리는 덫 <br>나지막이 읊조려봐 good luck <br>하늘까지 솟아버린 벽 <br>알려주지않는 살아남는 법 <br>달콤한 거짓 도사리는 덫 <br>나지막이 읊조려봐 good luck <br>매일매일 도망가 이 Game <br>술래는 없는데 <br>다시 내 안에 숨어 <br>밝았던 날은 저물어 가는 중 <br>툭툭 털어내려고 <br>good good 나를 위로하고 <br>한숨 속에 걸음을 던지네 <br>발길을 옮기네 지쳐 있었지만 <br>늘 하루의 끝은 항상 <br>니 손끝이 생각 나는 밤 <br>계속 날 옮기네 모르는 길 따라 <br>난 계속 걸어가 마음 그냥 가는 대로 <br>가루처럼 부스러진 하루 <br>바람에 흩날려버린 날들 <br>내가 품은 한줌 꿈은 <br>비를 머금은 회색 빛 구름 <br>그렇게 말하곤 이제 가라고 <br>이게 다라고 그게 나라고 <br>아무렇지 않게 내뱉곤 <br>흐릿한 발자국만 찾아 헤매 <br>세상은 너무 급해 내 걸음도 조급해 <br>길을 걷다 보니 뉘엿뉘엿 해지네 <br>내 방은 너무 습해 숨쉬는 걸 연습해 <br>침대에 나의 몸을 뉘여 나른 해지네 <br>내 머릿속을 한참이나 걸었지만 <br>보이는 건 몇 글자의 발자국 뿐 <br>나 자신에게 물어 <br>지금 어디까지 왔는지 <br>돌아오는 답은 그냥 메아리 뿐 <br>신발은 한 쪽으로 닳아서 내 걸음은 <br>내 마음처럼 안쪽으로 기울어져가네 <br>가끔은 멈춰서 숨을 내쉬네 <br>푸념 섞인 말을 대신해 <br>아무런 생각없이 걸어도 <br>제자린 아니겠지 <br>멈춰있는 모든 것이 풍경이 되겠지 <br>그냥 이렇게 난 지금처럼 걸어가 <br>뒤돌아 보며 걸어도 제자린 아니겠지 <br>난 그냥 길을 따라 걷다 <br>막다른 골목을 만났어 <br>걱정하지마 난 멈추지않아 <br>잠깐 쉬고 또 걸어 <br>하늘까지 솟아버린 벽 <br>알려주지않는 살아남는 법 <br>달콤한 거짓 도사리는 덫 <br>나지막이 읊조려봐 good luck <br>하늘까지 솟아버린 벽 <br>알려주지않는 살아남는 법 <br>달콤한 거짓 도사리는 덫 <br>나지막이 읊조려봐 good luck <br>]]></content><category term="No Dodge Brothers (노다지 브라더스)" label="No Dodge Brothers (노다지 브라더스)"/><category term="Way" label="Way"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/숨셔/너무_좋아/</id><title>숨셔 - 너무 좋아 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:56:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:56:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%88%A8%EC%85%94/%EB%84%88%EB%AC%B4_%EC%A2%8B%EC%95%84/" title="숨셔 - 너무 좋아 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 학교 앞에서 팔던 <br>솜사탕으로 빚어서 <br>만든 사람 같아 <br>어딜 만져도 너무 부드러워 <br>어딜 핥아도 너무너무 달아 <br>너랑 있으면 말야 <br>안 써지던 가사도 말야 <br>떠올라 떠올라 <br>너의 보라 보라색 이불 <br>그 안이 너무 좋아 <br>서로를 오르락 내리락 거리다 <br>우린 늘 배가 고파지면 <br>가잖아 집 앞 CU <br>제일 좋아하는 과자도 사고 <br>처음처럼 한두 병 사다 <br>좀 더 뜨거워진 <br>너의 바다에서 <br>밤새 수영하는 게 난 <br>너무 좋아 너무 좋아 <br>난 너가 너무 좋아 <br>너무 좋아 너가 너무 너무 좋아 <br>너무 좋아 너무 좋아 <br>난 너가 너무 좋아 <br>너무 좋아 너가 너무 너무 좋아 <br>언제나 너랑 있고 싶어 <br>화가 나거나 우울한 날에도 <br>꽉 끌어안으면 <br>모든 게 스르륵 <br>녹아 내리니깐 너무 좋아 <br>너의 모든 장면이 완벽하지 <br>가끔씩은 슬로우 모션 <br>너가 긴 머릴 쓸어 올릴 때는 <br>정말 취해버려 난 아이고 <br>엘리베이터 안 우린 올라가네 <br>RAMADA 12층 <br>나만 아는 널 보여주네 <br>그래 그런 그 표정 <br>내 위에 올라와서 넌 말하잖아 <br>너무 좋아 너무 좋아 <br>난 너가 너무 좋아 <br>너무 좋아 너가 너무 너무 좋아 <br>너무 좋아 너무 좋아 <br>난 너가 너무 좋아 <br>너무 좋아 너가 너무 너무 좋아 <br>가지 말고 더 있어 줘 <br>커튼으로 전부 다 가리고 <br>낮인지 밤인지 너가 모르게 <br>낮에도 밤에도 너랑 <br>새빨간 얼굴이 채 식기도 전에 <br>한 번 더 입 맞출게 <br>너의 여기저기 다 <br>말해줘 얼마나 좋은지 <br>너무 좋아 너무 좋아 <br>난 너가 너무 좋아 <br>너무 좋아 너가 너무 너무 좋아 <br>너무 좋아 너무 좋아 <br>난 너가 너무 좋아 <br>너무 좋아 너가 너무 너무 좋아 <br>]]></content><category term="숨셔" label="숨셔"/><category term="너무 좋아" label="너무 좋아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PENGUIN_RESEARCH/ボタン___Button/</id><title>PENGUIN RESEARCH - ボタン / Button - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:57:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:57:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PENGUIN_RESEARCH/%E3%83%9C%E3%82%BF%E3%83%B3___Button/" title="PENGUIN RESEARCH - ボタン / Button - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ねぇ、あんなに遠いと感じた <br>네- 안나니 토오이토 칸지타 <br>저기, 그렇게 멀다고 느꼈던 <br><br>細い上り坂も 夏休みも <br>호소이 노보리자카모 나츠야스미모 <br>좁은 오르막길도 여름방학도 <br><br>僅かと思うんだろうが <br>와즈카토 오모운다로우가 <br>금방이라고 생각하겠지만 <br><br>大人になってしまったら <br>오토나니 낫테 시맛타라 <br>어른이 되어버리면 <br><br>もう？うこともないだろうと <br>모우 아우 코토모 나이다로우토 <br>"이제 만날 일도 없겠지"라며 <br><br>今、一生分の言葉を探す <br>이마 잇쇼-뷴노 코토바오 사가스 <br>지금 일생 분의 말을 찾았어 <br><br>おかしいな 語彙はそんなに <br>오카시이나 고이와 손나니 <br>이상하네, 어휘는 그렇게 <br><br>乏しいはずじゃないのに <br>토보시이 하즈쟈 나이노니 <br>부족하지 않았을 텐데 <br><br>明日にはもう誰もいなくなって <br>아시타니와 모우 다레모 이나쿠 낫테 <br>내일이면 이제 아무도 없게 되어서 <br><br>孤？とも違う震えを知る朝が？る <br>코도쿠토모 치가우 후루에오 시루 아사가 쿠루 <br>고독과도 다른 떨림을 아는 아침이 와 <br><br>ただ愛しい別れの日に <br>타다 이토시이 와카레노 히니 <br>그저 사랑스러운 이별의 날에 <br><br>振り向かないで 行かなくちゃ！ <br>후리무카나이데 이카나쿠챠! <br>돌아보지 마, 가지 않으면 안돼! <br><br>またいつか なんて無くても <br>마타 이츠카 난테 나쿠테모 <br>언젠가 다시 라는 말따위 없어도 <br><br>僕らは？えている？？の暗？も <br>보쿠라와 오보에테 이루 라이쇼노 안고모 <br>우리들은 기억하고 있는 비밀 암호도 <br><br>放課後にしか無い？の空も <br>호우카고니시카 나이 아카네노 소라모 <br>방과 후밖에 없는 붉게 물든 하늘도 <br><br>さよならなんて似合わない <br>사요나라난테 니아와나이 <br>작별인사 따위 어울리지 않아 <br><br>運命が遠く掛け違えても <br>운메이가 토오쿠 카케치가에테모 <br>운명이 크게 엇갈려도 <br><br>最初の一つだけ お？いだから良い <br>사이쇼노 히토츠다케 오소로이다카라 이이 <br>처음 하나 뿐인 모임이니까 좋아 <br><br>全部消えても ただそれだけは解れない <br>젠부 키에테모 타다 소레다케와 호츠레나이 <br>전부 사라져도 그저 그것만은 흐트러지지 않아 <br><br>今、思えばあの異世界も <br>이마 오모에바 아노 이세카이모 <br>지금 생각하면 저 이세계도 <br><br>秘密の近道も 綺麗な日？も <br>히미츠노 치카미치모 키레이나 히비모 <br>비밀의 지름길도 멋진 나날도 <br><br>別？に終わった？春も <br>베츠베츠니 오왓타 세이슌모 <br>따로따로 끝난 청춘도 <br><br>全部優しい日？だった <br>젠부 야사시이 히비닷타 <br>전부 상냥한 나날이었어 <br><br>？わらないのは記憶だけでも <br>카와라나이 노와 키오쿠다케데모 <br>변하지 않는 건 기억뿐이지만 <br><br>行き過ぎてしまう僕らを <br>이키스기테시마우 보쿠라오 <br>지나쳐 버리고 마는 우리들을 <br><br>照らす？りがただ一つ… <br>테라스 아카리가 타다 히토츠... <br>비추는 등불이 단 하나... <br><br>一つあれば良い！ <br>히토츠 아레바 이이! <br>하나만 있으면 돼! <br><br>振り向かないで もうそこに <br>후리무카나이데 모우 소코니 <br>돌아보지 마, 이제 거기에 <br><br>少年の永遠はないから <br>쇼우넨노 에이엔와 나이카라 <br>소년의 영원은 없으니까 <br><br>汚れのないでも 擦り切れるほど <br>요고레노 나이데모 스리키레루호도 <br>더러운 건 없지만 닳아버릴 정도로 <br><br>幾度と無くこれから探すんだ <br>이쿠도토 나쿠 코레카라 사가슨다 <br>셀 수 없을 만큼 지금부터 찾는 거야 <br><br>さよならなんて似合わない <br>사요나라난테 니아와나이 <br>작별인사 따위 어울리지 않아 <br><br>運命が遠く掛け違えても <br>운메이가 토오쿠 카케치가에테모 <br>운명이 크게 엇갈려도 <br><br>僕らを？ぐ最後の夕？け <br>보쿠라오 츠나구 사이고노 유우야케 <br>우리들을 잇는 마지막 노을 <br><br>きっと忘れない… <br>킷토 와스레나이... <br>분명 잊지 않아... <br><br>全部消えても ただそれだけは解れない <br>젠부 키에테모 타다 소레다케와 호츠레나이 <br>전부 사라져도 그저 그것만은 흐트러지지 않아]]></content><category term="PENGUIN RESEARCH" label="PENGUIN RESEARCH"/><category term="ボタン / Button" label="ボタン / Button"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오버헤드/Ill_Be_Fine/</id><title>오버헤드 - I`ll Be Fine - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:57:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:57:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%B2%84%ED%97%A4%EB%93%9C/Ill_Be_Fine/" title="오버헤드 - I`ll Be Fine - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 기억속에 버려진 이곳에 <br>아침하늘 아래 그림자를 따라 <br>어둠속을 걷던 너는 어느순간 <br>노을이 되어서 가려져버렸네 <br><br>희미해진 내 기억속 <br>난 언제까지 멈춰있을까 <br>지금 딛는 한걸음 너에게로 <br><br>If you fall down <br>내가 너의 빛이 될께 (빛이 될게 <br>If you feel down <br>멈춰있지 말아줘. (시간이) <br>얼마나 걸리든 반드시 따라갈테니 <br><br>we know life will always be a journey]]></content><category term="오버헤드" label="오버헤드"/><category term="I`ll Be Fine" label="I`ll Be Fine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/해주/어여쁜_꽃/</id><title>해주 - 어여쁜 꽃 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:57:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:57:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%B4%EC%A3%BC/%EC%96%B4%EC%97%AC%EC%81%9C_%EA%BD%83/" title="해주 - 어여쁜 꽃 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밤이슬 맞으며 외롭게 핀 꽃 <br>벌 나비 찾아와 사뿐히 앉네 <br>꽃은 피어도 소식이 없네 <br>못 본체 말고 찾아오세요 <br>꿀 냄새 취해버려 <br>날아가지도 못하게 꼭 잡고 싶어 <br>꽃잎으로 감싸 줄래 <br>아 외면을 하지 말아줘요 <br>나에게는 오직 당신뿐 <br>어여쁜 꽃이랍니다 <br>밤이슬 맞으며 외롭게 핀 꽃 <br>벌 나비 찾아와 사뿐히 앉네 <br>꽃은 피어도 소식이 없네 <br>못 본체 말고 찾아오세요 <br>꿀 냄새 취해버려 <br>날아가지도 못하게 꼭 잡고 싶어 <br>꽃잎으로 감싸 줄래 <br>아 외면을 하지 말아줘요 <br>나에게는 오직 당신뿐 <br>어여쁜 꽃이랍니다 <br>어여쁜 꽃이랍니다 <br>]]></content><category term="해주" label="해주"/><category term="어여쁜 꽃" label="어여쁜 꽃"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더_바스타즈_the_Vastards/sugar_free/</id><title>더 바스타즈 (the Vastards) - sugar free - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:57:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:57:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94_%EB%B0%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80%EC%A6%88_the_Vastards/sugar_free/" title="더 바스타즈 (the Vastards) - sugar free - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not happy in the clouds <br>너는 웃는 얼굴로 <br>나를 쳐다보지만 <br>그런 널 보는 내 맘은 <br>한없이 차갑고 또 슬프기만 해 <br>갈라진 길에서 고개 숙여 울며 <br>너를 생각했었어 <br>우리는 무설탕 솜사탕 위를 <br>걷는 기분이야 <br>I’m not happy in the clouds <br>It seems to be rain falls <br>I’m not happy in the clouds <br>It seems to be rain falls <br>I’m not happy in the clouds <br>It seems to be rain falls <br>I’m not happy in the clouds <br>I’m not happy in the clouds <br>처음 만났을 때를 넌 기억할까 <br>그 어떤 이야기로도 <br>우리 지난 날들을 말할 수 없어 <br>갈라진 길에서 고개 숙여 울며 <br>너를 생각했었어 <br>우리는 무설탕 솜사탕 위를 <br>걷는 기분이야 <br>I’m not happy in the clouds <br>It seems to be rain falls <br>I’m not happy in the clouds <br>It seems to be rain falls <br>I’m not happy in the clouds <br>It seems to be rain falls <br>I’m not happy in the shining <br>brilliant rainbow <br>]]></content><category term="더 바스타즈 (the Vastards)" label="더 바스타즈 (the Vastards)"/><category term="sugar free" label="sugar free"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더_바스타즈_the_Vastards/1m30s/</id><title>더 바스타즈 (the Vastards) - 1m30s - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:57:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:57:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94_%EB%B0%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80%EC%A6%88_the_Vastards/1m30s/" title="더 바스타즈 (the Vastards) - 1m30s - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무도 너를 모르지만 <br>나는 잘 알고 있지 <br>새까만 타이즈와 <br>Tight한 너의 outfit <br>사랑이 필요한 타이밍 <br>나는 잘 알고 있지 <br>날 바라보는 순간 <br>I got ya under my skin <br>I don’t care what you say <br>We just need <br>only 1 minute 30 seconds baby <br>I don’t care what you say <br>We just need <br>only 1 minute 30 seconds baby <br>숨이 꽉 막혀버릴 <br>공간에 갇힌 <br>네게 위로가 되어줄게 <br>니는 내꺼니까 <br>난 이미 네 안에 들어와있어 <br>이젠 날아와 <br>내 꽃길을 즈려밟고 <br>헤어날 수 없는 <br>1 kiss 30 high <br>I don’t care what you say <br>We just need <br>only 1 minute 30 seconds baby <br>I don’t care what you say <br>We just need <br>only 1 minute 30 seconds baby <br>]]></content><category term="더 바스타즈 (the Vastards)" label="더 바스타즈 (the Vastards)"/><category term="1m30s" label="1m30s"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NIZKYMUN/WSI_Feat_Young_Froze_Prod_By_Larkin/</id><title>NIZKYMUN - WSI (Feat. Young Froze) (Prod. By Larkin) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:57:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:57:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NIZKYMUN/WSI_Feat_Young_Froze_Prod_By_Larkin/" title="NIZKYMUN - WSI (Feat. Young Froze) (Prod. By Larkin) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우린 팔꺼야 힙합 LE에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 길거리에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 스트리밍에다가 <br>팔아서 벤틀리 타고 시장갈꺼야 <br>우린 팔꺼야 힙합 LE에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 길거리에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 스트리밍에다가 <br>팔아서 벤틀리 타고 시장갈꺼야 <br>\e $ell it celebrate our $uccess <br>아 어머나 오늘 내일 내 birthday <br>Wacth me now fucker 너의 절제 <br>money는 나의 휴지 i gotta waste it <br>yes 내 통장에 공이 여러개 <br>달리면 난 바로 집평수를 넓게 <br>032431 나의 형제 <br>PERAQUAT = G-SQUAD 나와 평생 <br>난 정체기 없어 그런 느낌이 들어 <br>내가 나와 넌 바로 붕솔 들이 부어 <br>불러 니 친구들 전부 <br>얘네들 페이에는 필요없는 염분 <br>넌 티끌모아 한방을 노리지 <br>빵야빵야 여기 니이름을 오리지 <br>난 파워워킹 넌 뒤뚱 넌 오리지 <br>넌 스탈원하지마 별별 꼴이지 <br>다비켜 난 팔꺼야 많이 <br>다비켜 우리 피울꺼야 난리 <br>내 페이 공 하나 더 붙여 <br>곧있음 거기에 공 하나 더 붙어 <br>백배 천배 어쩌겠어 unfair uh <br>우린 팔꺼야 힙합 LE에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 길거리에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 스트리밍에다가 <br>팔아서 벤틀리 타고 시장갈꺼야 <br>우린 팔꺼야 힙합 LE에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 길거리에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 스트리밍에다가 <br>팔아서 벤틀리 타고 시장갈꺼야 <br>야 돈 얘기하는데 나 왜 이제 불러 <br>나만큼 돈독이 오른 놈은 <br>이세상에 없다고 <br>무공으로치면 만독불침 <br>같은 이미지를 굳히고 나서도 <br>돈을 당연하게 버는 인간들도 있던데 <br>나는 왜 아직도 이러고 있는지 몰라 <br>그래도 난 좌판을 <br>깔기 위해서 똥을 눟지 <br>언젠가 목디스크 걸려 <br>걸려있는 cool chain <br>나는 팔거야 내 노래 \orld\ide <br>나도 몰랐는데 이미 <br>중국에서도 $ervice 돼 <br>나는 팔거야 내 간지 <br>무대 위 랩하는 거 <br>사람들 보면 길거리 정체돼 <br>Versace givancy <br>channel louis vuiton <br>다 내꺼로 만들어 <br>내 시체는 신세계 백화점 <br>1층 명품관에 묻어줘 <br>평화속 잠들어 froze <br>우린 팔꺼야 힙합 LE에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 길거리에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 스트리밍에다가 <br>팔아서 벤틀리 타고 시장갈꺼야 <br>우린 팔꺼야 힙합 LE에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 길거리에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 스트리밍에다가 <br>팔아서 벤틀리 타고 시장갈꺼야 <br>ferrari ferrari 아무렇지않게 <br>we sippin sippin <br>돔페리뇽같은 샴페인 <br>주의해 주의해 올라가려 할 때 <br>i don't need 개새끼들의 빨대 <br>ferrari ferrari 아무렇지 않게 <br>we sippin sippin <br>돔페리뇽같은 샴페인 <br>주의해 주의해 올라가려 할 때 <br>i don't need 개새끼들의 빨대 <br>우린 팔꺼야 힙합 LE에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 길거리에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 스트리밍에다가 <br>팔아서 벤틀리 타고 시장갈꺼야 <br>우린 팔꺼야 힙합 LE에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 길거리에다가 <br>우린 팔꺼야 스트리밍에다가 <br>팔아서 벤틀리 타고 시장갈꺼야 <br>]]></content><category term="NIZKYMUN" label="NIZKYMUN"/><category term="WSI (Feat. Young Froze) (Prod. By Larkin)" label="WSI (Feat. Young Froze) (Prod. By Larkin)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/러브엑스테레오/Rage_Is_Not_Enough_Danja_Mix_Remastered/</id><title>러브엑스테레오 - Rage Is Not Enough (Danja Mix) (Remastered) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:59:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:59:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9F%AC%EB%B8%8C%EC%97%91%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A4/Rage_Is_Not_Enough_Danja_Mix_Remastered/" title="러브엑스테레오 - Rage Is Not Enough (Danja Mix) (Remastered) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wake up <br>It's time to freshen up your makeup <br>Their money really doesn't add up <br>It's like a never ending game to you <br>Warm kiss <br>You start a war against the nervous <br>You deal your fears but <br>don't forget this <br>No matter what they tell you <br>They'll soon forget about you <br>Unless you do something cause <br>Rage is not enough <br>Rage is not enough <br>Enslavement <br>You're way too young to hit <br>the pavement <br>You thought that this was your moment <br>That moment when you start to fly away <br>Make it <br>I got your back cause you deserve it <br>Let's bring the devil down to break it <br>No matter what you've been through <br>I'm here to stand beside you <br>We're gonna break some rules cause <br>Rage is not enough <br>Rage is not enough <br>Rage is not enough <br>Rage is not enough <br>is not enough <br>Rage is not enough <br>Rage is not enough <br>Rage is not enough <br>Rage is not enough <br>is not enough <br>]]></content><category term="러브엑스테레오" label="러브엑스테레오"/><category term="Rage Is Not Enough (Danja Mix) (Remastered)" label="Rage Is Not Enough (Danja Mix) (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/러브엑스테레오/Like_A_Waterfall_In_The_Sky/</id><title>러브엑스테레오 - Like A Waterfall In The Sky - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:59:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:59:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9F%AC%EB%B8%8C%EC%97%91%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A4/Like_A_Waterfall_In_The_Sky/" title="러브엑스테레오 - Like A Waterfall In The Sky - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Free your emotions <br>Time to close your eyes <br>Lose your focus <br>As you fall asleep tonight <br>저 하늘에 떨어지는 폭포처럼 <br>저 하늘에 불타는 구름처럼 <br>Sleepless ocean <br>Waving through your eyes <br>Splash down your senses <br>Like a waterfall in the sky <br>Good bye <br>Good night <br>Good bye <br>Good night <br>저 하늘에 떨어지는 폭포처럼 <br>저 하늘에 불타는 구름처럼 <br>Good bye <br>Good night <br>Good bye <br>Good night <br>Good bye <br>Good night <br>Good bye <br>Good night <br>Good bye <br>Good night <br>Good bye <br>Good night <br>Good bye <br>Good night <br>Good bye <br>Good night <br>Like a waterfall in the sky <br>]]></content><category term="러브엑스테레오" label="러브엑스테레오"/><category term="Like A Waterfall In The Sky" label="Like A Waterfall In The Sky"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/러브엑스테레오/Parallel_Universe/</id><title>러브엑스테레오 - Parallel Universe - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:59:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:59:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9F%AC%EB%B8%8C%EC%97%91%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A4/Parallel_Universe/" title="러브엑스테레오 - Parallel Universe - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Beautiful <br>What world is that you're looking for <br>Beautiful <br>My world does not exist anymore <br>Beautiful <br>How'd you run away so far <br>Beautiful <br>Time and space became unnatural <br>Did I let you down <br>Well I'm not a saviour <br>What makes you think that <br>we live in parallel <br>You and I <br>We're full of possiblities <br>You and I <br>We're full of broken memories <br>Did I let you down <br>Well I'm not a saviour <br>What makes you think that <br>we live in parallel <br>Did I lift you up <br>Cause I don't remember <br>What makes you think that <br>I am your other half <br>You and I <br>We're full of possiblities <br>You and I <br>We're full of broken memories <br>You and I <br>We're full of possiblities <br>You and I <br>We're full of broken memories <br>]]></content><category term="러브엑스테레오" label="러브엑스테레오"/><category term="Parallel Universe" label="Parallel Universe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/러브엑스테레오/Paradise_Lost/</id><title>러브엑스테레오 - Paradise Lost - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:59:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:59:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9F%AC%EB%B8%8C%EC%97%91%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A4/Paradise_Lost/" title="러브엑스테레오 - Paradise Lost - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hide me up on the celiling <br>나를 숨겨줘 제발 <br>Take my hand never let go <br>나를 어디든 데려가 <br>아무도 널 보지 않아 <br>아무도 널 듣지 않아 <br>아무도 널 보지 않아 <br>아무도 널 듣지 않아 <br>Save my sorrow <br>Do you need a reason <br>Save my sorrow <br>Do you need a reason <br>Hide me under the moonlight <br>나를 가려줘 제발 <br>Take my hand don't you let go <br>나는 어디든 따라가 <br>나를 숨겨줘 <br>나를 가려줘 <br>나를 안아줘 제발 <br>아무도 널 보지 않아 <br>아무도 널 듣지 않아 <br>아무도 널 보지 않아 <br>아무도 널 듣지 않아 <br>아무도 널 듣지 않아 <br>Save my sorrow <br>Do you need a reason <br>Save my sorrow <br>Do you need a reason <br>Save my sorrow <br>Do you need a reason <br>Save my sorrow <br>Do you need a reason <br>Save my sorrow <br>Do you need a reason <br>Save my sorrow <br>Do you need a reason <br>Save my sorrow <br>Do you need a reason <br>Save my sorrow <br>Do you need a reason <br>]]></content><category term="러브엑스테레오" label="러브엑스테레오"/><category term="Paradise Lost" label="Paradise Lost"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/러브엑스테레오/백색소음_White_Noise/</id><title>러브엑스테레오 - 백색소음 White Noise - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:59:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:59:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9F%AC%EB%B8%8C%EC%97%91%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A4/%EB%B0%B1%EC%83%89%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%8C_White_Noise/" title="러브엑스테레오 - 백색소음 White Noise - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Listen 내 심장을 <br>Listen 내 숨결을 <br>거짓된 진실을 말하고 <br>잊혀진 미래를 꿈꾸는 <br>Still I fall for you <br>나는 바람처럼 스쳐도 <br>너는 나를 붙들었고 <br>나는 노래처럼 흘러도 <br>너는 나를 믿었었어 <br>서로 다른 시공간에서 <br>우린 밀고 당기며 <br>깊은 밤이 다 지새도록 <br>We realize <br>Listen 내 기억을 <br>Listen 내 비밀을 <br>버려진 마음을 채우고 <br>꺼지는 불빛을 지키는 <br>Still I fall for you <br>나는 바람처럼 스쳐도 <br>너는 나를 붙들었고 <br>나는 노래처럼 흘러도 <br>너는 나를 믿었었어 <br>서로 다른 시공간에서 <br>우린 밀고 당기며 <br>깊은 밤이 다 지새도록 <br>We realize <br>나는 바람처럼 스쳐도 <br>너는 나를 붙들었고 <br>나는 노래처럼 흘러도 <br>너는 나를 믿었었어 <br>서로 다른 시공간에서 <br>우린 밀고 당기며 <br>깊은 밤이 다 지새도록 <br>We realize <br>]]></content><category term="러브엑스테레오" label="러브엑스테레오"/><category term="백색소음 White Noise" label="백색소음 White Noise"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/러브엑스테레오/Battle_Wings/</id><title>러브엑스테레오 - Battle Wings - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:59:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:59:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9F%AC%EB%B8%8C%EC%97%91%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A4/Battle_Wings/" title="러브엑스테레오 - Battle Wings - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Kind enough to hide my secrets <br>underneath your skin <br>You and I both took bullets <br>in our hearts deep within <br>Time goes by fast <br>Quicker than you dare imagine <br>I know you'll find the path <br>We're escaping <br>from this world we live in <br>Diamonds clubs hearts spades <br>Tanks planes bullets blades <br>Here there heaven or hell <br>You there You there <br>I wish you well <br>Battle wings <br>Fly me home tonight <br>Battle wings <br>Fly me home tonight <br>Battle wings <br>Fly me home tonight <br>Battle wings <br>Fly me home tonight <br>I wanna go home tonight <br>]]></content><category term="러브엑스테레오" label="러브엑스테레오"/><category term="Battle Wings" label="Battle Wings"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/러브엑스테레오/Bring_Me_Back_To_You/</id><title>러브엑스테레오 - Bring Me Back To You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:59:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:59:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9F%AC%EB%B8%8C%EC%97%91%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A4/Bring_Me_Back_To_You/" title="러브엑스테레오 - Bring Me Back To You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm gonna miss you after all <br>Crashing waves <br>and never ending shores <br>I just want to let you know <br>You're in my heart <br>I'll never let you go <br>Chin up stand up <br>you got the cools to make up <br>Keep your head up <br>I'll come running back to you <br>Bring me back to you <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Will you bring me back to you <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Don't let go <br>I'm gonna miss you after all <br>Pink blue skies <br>and city streets of gold <br>I just want to let you know <br>You're in my soul <br>I'll never let you go <br>Chin up stand up <br>you got the cools to make up <br>Keep your head up <br>I'll come running back to you <br>Bring me back to you <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Will you bring me back to you <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Don't let go <br>I started dipping my face <br>into the sun <br>I must be dreaming <br>I'm not the only one <br>I started dipping my face <br>into the sun <br>I must be dreaming <br>I'm not the only one <br>I started dipping my face <br>into the sun <br>I must be dreaming <br>I'm not the only one <br>Bring me back to you <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Will you bring me back to you <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Don't let go <br>Bring me back to you <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Will you bring me back to you <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Cause it feels more natural <br>Don't let go <br>Don't let go <br>Don't let go <br>]]></content><category term="러브엑스테레오" label="러브엑스테레오"/><category term="Bring Me Back To You" label="Bring Me Back To You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/러브엑스테레오/Lemon_Spark/</id><title>러브엑스테레오 - Lemon Spark - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:59:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:59:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9F%AC%EB%B8%8C%EC%97%91%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A4/Lemon_Spark/" title="러브엑스테레오 - Lemon Spark - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning around <br>I'm drinking way <br>too much lemon soda <br>Spinning around <br>Can't think of a way <br>to get out of this sofa <br>You got me spinning around <br>Come shake me up <br>I'm paralyzed <br>You got me spinning around <br>Go set me free <br>or we stay all night <br>Lemon spark <br>Spinning into the dark <br>Lemon spark <br>Spinning into the dark <br>Lemon spark for you and me <br>Won't stop until it's over over <br>Lemon spark for you and me <br>Won't stop until it's over over <br>Spinning around <br>Please help me <br>before I hit my head <br>on the ground <br>Spinning around <br>Please help me <br>before I hit my head <br>on the ground <br>Lemon spark <br>Spinning into the dark <br>Lemon spark <br>Spinning into the dark <br>Lemon spark for you and me <br>Won't stop until it's over over <br>Lemon spark for you and me <br>Won't stop until it's over over <br>Spinning around <br>Lemon spark for you and me <br>Won't stop until it's over over <br>Spinning around <br>Lemon spark for you and me <br>Won't stop until it's over over <br>Spinning around <br>Lemon spark for you and me <br>Won't stop until it's over over <br>Spinning around <br>Lemon spark for you and me <br>Won't stop until it's over over <br>Spinning around <br>Lemon spark for you and me <br>Won't stop until it's over over <br>Spinning around <br>Lemon spark for you and me <br>Won't stop until it's over over <br>Spinning around <br>]]></content><category term="러브엑스테레오" label="러브엑스테레오"/><category term="Lemon Spark" label="Lemon Spark"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/러브엑스테레오/Dark_And_Light/</id><title>러브엑스테레오 - Dark And Light - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:59:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:59:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9F%AC%EB%B8%8C%EC%97%91%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A4/Dark_And_Light/" title="러브엑스테레오 - Dark And Light - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Have you been in love <br>been in love been in love <br>There must be more <br>You gotta rethink <br>about what is true love after all <br>What they say what they say <br>what they say <br>doesn't mean a thing at all <br>Only thing that matters is <br>what we think of each other cause <br>Everyday I <br>And everyday we <br>We stay in the dark together <br>in the dark together <br>Everyday I <br>And everyday we <br>We stay in the light together <br>in the light together <br>Have you been in love <br>been in love been in love <br>There must be more <br>What you gotta understand is <br>that love ain't about less or more <br>What they say what they say <br>what they say doesn't mean <br>a thing at all <br>Only thing that matters is <br>how we feel for each other cause <br>Everyday I <br>And everyday we <br>We stay in the dark together <br>in the dark together <br>Everyday I <br>And everyday we <br>We stay in the light together <br>in the light together <br>Everyday I <br>And everyday we <br>We stay in the dark together <br>in the dark together <br>Everyday I <br>And everyday we <br>We stay in the light together <br>in the light together <br>Everyday I <br>And everyday we <br>We stay in the dark together <br>in the dark together <br>Everyday I <br>we <br>light together <br>together <br>]]></content><category term="러브엑스테레오" label="러브엑스테레오"/><category term="Dark And Light" label="Dark And Light"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/러브엑스테레오/Maybe_I/</id><title>러브엑스테레오 - Maybe I - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:59:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:59:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9F%AC%EB%B8%8C%EC%97%91%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A4/Maybe_I/" title="러브엑스테레오 - Maybe I - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe I <br>Maybe I <br>Maybe I just want to say <br>that I'm sorry <br>Maybe I just want to say <br>that I'm sorry <br>Maybe I just want to say <br>that I worry <br>Maybe I just want to say <br>that I ruined it <br>You said you'll be long gone <br>We can't live forever <br>You said you'll be long gone <br>We can't live forever <br>Maybe I <br>Maybe I <br>Maybe I was supposed to say <br>that I'm sorry <br>Maybe I was supposed to say <br>that I'm sorry <br>Maybe I was supposed to say <br>that I worry <br>Maybe I was supposed to say <br>that I ruined it <br>You said you'll be long gone <br>We can't live forever <br>You said you'll be long gone <br>We can't live forever <br>]]></content><category term="러브엑스테레오" label="러브엑스테레오"/><category term="Maybe I" label="Maybe I"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aimer/Stars_in_the_Rain/</id><title>Aimer - Stars in the Rain - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:59:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:59:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aimer/Stars_in_the_Rain/" title="Aimer - Stars in the Rain - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So close so far <br>Kitto me o tojitandarou <br>Rainbows or stars <br>Zutto mitsukerarenakute <br><br>Machi o ima kasa mo sazu ni ate mo nakute <br><br>Soshite kogoesouna ame ni mata nakisouna yume o <br>Tada nakusanai youni katayose atta futari <br><br>Tonight maybe, we'll see the stars in the rain... <br>Tonight maybe, we'll see the stars in the rain... <br><br>So close so far <br>Miles away, right past what I know <br>Rainbows of stars <br>How could I ever be afraid... <br><br>Out of my window <br>I found a reason to breathe <br>Beyond the bright lights <br>It shows <br><br>When it's all over I see <br>I just want to hold onto this dream <br>We're going in circles again <br>I wouldn't trade it for anything <br><br><br>Tonight maybe, we'll see the stars in the rain... <br>Tonight maybe, we'll see the stars in the rain... <br><br>Rainbows or stars <br>Zutto mitsukerarenakute <br><br>Soshite kogoesouna ame ni mata nakisouna yume o <br>Tada nakusanai youni katayose atta futari <br><br>Tonight maybe, we'll see the stars in the rain... <br>Tonight maybe, we'll see the stars in the rain...]]></content><category term="Aimer" label="Aimer"/><category term="Stars in the Rain" label="Stars in the Rain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aimer/Hz/</id><title>Aimer - Hz - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T12:59:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T12:59:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aimer/Hz/" title="Aimer - Hz - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[曖昧なヘルツに合わせたならNo Good <br><br>아이마이나 헤르츠니 아와세타나라 No Good <br><br>애매한 헤르츠에 맞추었다면 No Good <br><br>？ <br><br>もうパスワ？ドのようにダイヤルをアジャスト <br><br>모오 파스와-도노요오니 다이야루오 아쟈스토 <br><br>이젠 비밀번호 처럼 ？다이얼을 adjust <br><br>？ <br><br>見えない波長が？を音を？けて <br><br>미에나이 하쵸오가 코에오 오토오 토도케테 <br><br>？보이지 않는 파장이 목소리를 소리를 전달하고 <br><br><br><br>名前のない時間、リライトする <br><br>나마에노나이 지캉, 리라이토스루 <br><br>이름이 없는 시간, 재도전을 해 <br><br>？ <br><br>空と空を架けて想いと想いを？げて <br><br>소라토 소라오 카케테 오모이토 오모이오 츠나게테 <br><br>하늘과 하늘을 걸고서 마음과 마음을 연결해서 <br><br>？ <br><br>僕たちを輝かせる？むジングル <br><br>보쿠타치오 카가야카세루 하즈무 징그루 <br><br>？우리를 빛내주는 통통 튀는 Jingle <br><br>？ <br><br>さぁ Radio　響けク？ルな音で　憂鬱なノイズすらイレ？ス <br><br>사아 Radio 히비케 쿠-루나 오토데 유우우츠나 노이즈스라 이레-스 <br><br>？자, Radio 울려퍼져라 Cool 한 소리로 우울한 노이즈 조차 erase <br><br><br><br>うまくいかない苛立ちも泡んなって消える <br><br>우마쿠 이카나이 이라다치모 아완낫테 키에루 <br><br>잘 풀리지 않는 짜증도 거품이 되어 사라져 <br><br>？ <br><br>So great day　？快な鼻歌で　？色な日？をメイクアップ <br><br>So great day 켓카이나 하나우타데 탄쇼쿠나 히비오 메이크압푸 <br><br>So great day 경쾌한 콧노래로 단색뿐인 날들을 메이크업 <br><br>？ <br><br>ハイになるサウンド　明日へのエネルギ？　yes！ <br><br>하이니 나루 사운도 아스에노 에네루기- yes！ <br><br>high가 되는 사운드 내일로 이어지는 에너지 yes! <br><br><br><br>？れ幅でもって？えてAmplitude <br><br>유레 하바데못테 츠타에테 Amplitude <br><br>흔들리는 폭만큼 전해줘 Amplitude <br><br><br><br>そんな遠くに行っちゃ？かんよFrequency <br><br>손나 토오쿠니 잇챠 토도칸요Frequency <br><br>그렇게 멀리 가면 닿지 않아 Frequency <br><br><br><br>鼓膜を震わす心地よい言葉 <br><br>코마쿠오 후루와스 코코치요이 코토바 <br><br>고막을 울리는 기분좋은 말들？ <br><br><br><br>身？を？け巡っていく <br><br>카라다오 카케메굿테쿠 <br><br>온 몸을 돌아 <br><br><br><br>Pops Rock Fusion Jazz R&amp;BにCountry <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>流れ出すその瞬間に心躍る <br><br>나가레다스 소노 슌칸니 코코로 오도루 <br><br>흘러 들어오는 그 순간에 마음이 들떠 <br><br><br><br>Oh DJ！　バッチリなナイスなチョイスで　誰かの孤？すらイレ？ス <br><br>Oh DJ！　밧치리나 나이스나 쵸이스데 다레카노 코도쿠스라 이레-스 <br><br>Oh DJ！　딱 맞는 나이스한 선택으로 누군가의 고독마저 erase <br><br><br><br>溜め？んじゃってるストレスも煙になって消える <br><br>타메콘쟛테루 스토레스모 케무리니 낫테 키에루 <br><br>쌓여있는 스트레스도 연기가 되어 사라져 <br><br>？ <br><br>So great day　キャッチ？なイントロで　？調な日？をグレ？ドアップ <br><br>So great day　캿치-나 인토로데 단쵸오나 히비오 그레-도 압푸 <br><br>So great day 　catchy한 Intro로 단조로운 날들을 업그레이드 <br><br><br><br>どんな背景も彩ってくれるんだ　yes！ <br><br>돈나 하이케이모 이로돗테 쿠레룬다　yes！ <br><br>？어떠한 풍경도 색으로 물들여줘　yes！ <br><br><br><br>さぁ Radio　響けク？ルな音で　邪魔するノイズはオ？ルイレ？ス <br><br>사아 Radio　히비케 쿠-루나 오토데 쟈마스루 노이즈와 오-루이레-스 <br><br>자, Radio 울려라 Cool 한 소리로 방해하는 노이즈를 All erase <br><br><br><br>口をつくようなヨワネなんかボリュ？ム絞ってしまえ！ <br><br>쿠치오 츠쿠요오나 요와네난카 보류-무 시봇테 시마에! <br><br>무심코 내뱉은 투덜따윈 볼륨을 줄여! <br><br><br><br>そんくらいで feel so good！自分だけの　チュ？ニング見つけてワンアップ <br><br>손쿠라이데 feel so good ! 지분다케노 츄-닝구 미츠케테 완압푸 <br><br>그 정도면feel so good！나만의 튜닝을 발견해서 One up <br><br><br><br>拳をギュッと固く握って　yes！！ <br><br>코부시오 귯토 카타쿠 니깃테 yes！！ <br><br>주먹을 세게 쥐고서　yes！！]]></content><category term="Aimer" label="Aimer"/><category term="Hz" label="Hz"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aimer/Kataomoi/</id><title>Aimer - Kataomoi - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:00:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:00:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aimer/Kataomoi/" title="Aimer - Kataomoi - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tatoteba kimi no no kao ni <br>Mukashi yori SHIWA ga fuete mo <br>Sore demo ii nda <br>Boku ga GITAA wo omou youni <br>Kikenakunatte mo <br>Kokoro no uta wa <br>Kimi de afureteiru yo <br>Takai koe mo dasezu ni <br>Omoidoori utaenai <br>Sore demo unazuki nagara <br>Issho ni utatte kureru kana <br>Waren bakari no hakushuu mo <br>Hibiki wataru kansei mo <br>Iranai <br>Kimi dake <br>Wakatte yo <br>Wakatte yo <br><br>Darlin' <br>Yume ga kanatta no <br>Oniai no kotoba ga <br>Mitsukaranai yo <br>Darlin' <br>Yume ga kanatta no <br>"Aishiteru" <br><br>Tatta ichido no <br>Tatta hitori no <br>Umarete kita shiawase <br>Ajiwatteru nda yo <br>*Kyou ga MEIN DISSHU de <br>Owari no hi ni wa <br>Amasuppai DEZAATO wo taberu no <br>Yama mo tani mo <br>Zenbu FURU KOOSU de* <br>Ki ga kiku youna kotoba wa iranai <br>Subarashii tokubetsu mo iranai <br>Tada zutto zutto soba ni <br>Oite ite yo <br>Boku no omoi wa <br>Toshi wo toru to <br>Fueteku bakka da <br>Suki da yo <br>Wakatte yo <br>Wakatte yo <br><br>Nee, Darlin' <br>Yume ga kanatta no <br>Oniai no kotoba ga <br>Mitsukaranai yo <br>Darlin' <br>Yume ga kanatta no <br>Ai ga afurete yuku]]></content><category term="Aimer" label="Aimer"/><category term="Kataomoi" label="Kataomoi"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aimer/Ninelie/</id><title>Aimer - Ninelie - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:00:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:00:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aimer/Ninelie/" title="Aimer - Ninelie - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[君を？ぐ空の星が1つ音を立てても <br>키미오 츠나구 소라노 호시가 히토츠 오토오 타테테모 <br>그대를 이어주는 하늘의 별 하나가 소리를 내도 <br><br>どれも同じ雨に濡れた夢ばかり 乾くだけの光こう <br>도레모 오나지 아메니 누레타 유메바카리 카와쿠 다케노 코- <br>죄다 같은 비에 젖은 꿈뿐, 메말라만 가는 빛 <br><br>相手をなぞる 0答えに疲れた <br>아이테오 나조루 코타에니 츠카레타 <br>상대방을 따르는 해답에는 지쳤어 <br><br>繰り返す陽の無い夜明けに 崩れた朝 <br>쿠리카에스 히노 나이 요아케니 쿠즈레타 아사 <br>반복되는 태양 없는 새벽에 무너진 아침 <br><br>捕まえたdaydream 出？れたスト？リ？と？光が <br>츠카마에타 daydream 테오쿠레타 스토-리-토 에이코오가 <br>붙잡은 daydream 때를 놓친 스토리와 영광이 <br><br>どこへ叫び唱えても <br>도코에 사케비 토나에테모 <br>어딜 향해 목청껏 외친들 <br><br>荒れたトンネル ？もくぐれない <br>아레타 톤네루 코에모 쿠구레나이 <br>거칠어진 터널, 목소리도 빠져나가지 못하네 <br><br>だからサイレンス ？すためと <br>다카라 사이렌스 토모스 타메토 <br>그러니 silence 밝히기 위해 <br><br>外とパズルのようにハマるピ？スが必要としても <br>소토토 파즈르노 요오니 하마루 피-스가 히츠요오토 시테모 <br>외부와 퍼즐처럼 들어맞는 조각이 필요할지라도 <br><br>影えいもない？いつわりと同じだ 捨て去られ？ぶだけの賞しょう <br>에이모 나이 이츠와리토 오나지다 스테사라레 나라부 다케노 쇼오 <br>그림자조차 없는 거짓이랑 똑같아, 버려져서 늘어놓이기만 하는 상 <br><br>箱の中に？えた苛立いらだち <br>하코노 나카니 소로에타 이라다치 <br>상자 속에 채워진 초조함 <br><br>順番待ちさらし 誤魔化しのゴ？ル <br>쥼방마치 사라시 고마카시노 고-루 <br>대기열을 드러냄은 눈속임의 종착점 <br><br>Don't be above your daydream 角かどが取れたvision <br>Don't be above your daydream 카도카 토레타 vision <br>Don't be above your daydream 모퉁이가 잘려나간 vision <br><br>君の夢が？で外れても <br>키미노 유메가 요코데 하즈레테모 <br>그대의 꿈이 옆에서 떨어져 나가도 <br><br>僕は歌い 橋をかけよう <br>보쿠와 우타이 하시오 카케요오 <br>나는 노래하며 다리를 걸치리 <br><br>だからサイレンス 鳴らすためと <br>다카라 사이렌스 나라스 타메토 <br>그러니 silence 울리기 위해 <br><br>どこまでも片側に沿ったリズム <br>도코마데모 카타가와니 솟타 리즈무 <br>한없이 한쪽으로 기운 리듬, <br><br>過ぎた街？は終の愛と遠くへ <br>스기타 마치나미와 오와리노 아이토 토오쿠에 <br>지나간 길거리는 종말의 사랑과 저 멀리 <br><br>？えれない歪ひずみかけのイメ？ジに <br>츠타에레나이 히즈미 카케노 이메-지니 <br>전할 수 없는 일그러지다 만 이미지에 <br><br>目が？めた抵抗 型落ちの衝動 <br>메가 사메타 테이코오 카타오치노 쇼오도오 <br>눈이 뜨인 저항, 균형을 잃은 충동 <br><br>？けたcrying dream 扉だけの理想 <br>쿠다케타 crying dream 토비라 다케노 리소오 <br>부서진 crying dream 문에서 끝나는 이상 <br><br>街が？音に溺れはしゃいでも <br>마치가 자츠온니 오보레 하샤이데모 <br>시내가 잡음에 빠져 시끄러워도 <br><br>僕は歌い 舵を捨てよう <br>보쿠와 우타이 카지오 스테요오 <br>나는 노래하며 키를 버리리 <br><br>だからサイレンス 響くためと <br>다카라 사이렌스 히비쿠 타메토 <br>그러니 silence 퍼트리기 위해 <br><br>Don't be afraid Daybreak has come <br><br>Don't be afraid Daybreak has come <br><br>Don't be afraid Daybreak has come <br><br>Don't be afraid Daybreak has come]]></content><category term="Aimer" label="Aimer"/><category term="Ninelie" label="Ninelie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TGER_티거/Good_Time/</id><title>TGER (티거) - Good Time - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:00:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:00:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TGER_%ED%8B%B0%EA%B1%B0/Good_Time/" title="TGER (티거) - Good Time - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Have a good time <br>good time <br>오늘 그대와 <br>우리 둘이서 함께 <br>good time <br>good time <br>여기 내 손을 잡아 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>오늘따라 기분이 좋아 <br>바람마저 상큼해 <br>뭘 해도 즐거울 것 같아 <br>너와 나 둘이 손을 잡고서 <br>어디든 걸어 다녀도 <br>난 좋을 것만 같아 <br>어디 갈래 <br>너와 함께라면 It's alright <br>Have a good time <br>good time <br>오늘 그대와 <br>우리 둘이서 함께 <br>good time <br>good time <br>여기 내 손을 잡아 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>Good time good time <br>Good time good time <br>Doo roo doo doo doo <br>Doo roo doo doo doo <br>Good time good time <br>Good time good time <br>Doo roo doo doo doo <br>눈이 마주치면 웃음 나는 걸 <br>너와 있는 곳은 <br>어디든지 천국일거야 <br>지금 이 시간이 멈췄으면 해 <br>넌 예쁜 미소를 짓고 <br>내게 손짓해 <br>이런 내 마음을 다 아는 것 같아 <br>넌 행복하다 내게 말해 <br>Have a good time <br>good time <br>오늘 그대와 <br>우리 둘이서 함께 <br>good time <br>good time <br>여기 내 손을 잡아 <br>내 곁에 있어줘 <br>Good time good time <br>Good time good time <br>Doo roo doo doo doo <br>Doo roo doo doo doo <br>Good time good time <br>Good time good time <br>Doo roo doo doo doo <br>good time <br>우리 둘이 함께하는 시간 <br>good time <br>good time <br>Doo roo doo doo doo roo doo <br>da ra da ra da ra da ra da <br>]]></content><category term="TGER (티거)" label="TGER (티거)"/><category term="Good Time" label="Good Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SOOM/인정_Inst/</id><title>SOOM - 인정 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:00:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:00:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SOOM/%EC%9D%B8%EC%A0%95_Inst/" title="SOOM - 인정 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 웃을때 입꼬리가 이뻐 <br>가지런히 가득담긴 치열 <br>표정없는 니가 웃어보일때 <br>나도 모르게 따라 미소를 짓네 <br>지금 나한테 넌 유일한 Muse <br>너말고 딴소린 다 안들려 Mute 쉿 <br>같이 걸을땐 다 Nice view <br>Woo I can't stop think about you <br>일이 손에 안잡힌단말 <br>빈말인거 같지만 <br>집중력에 한계가 와 매일밤 <br>일부러 안보려 폰을 뒤집어 놔도 <br>십분도 못넘기는거 알어 나도 <br>모든게 달라 어쩜 순정만화 <br>머리부터 발끝까지 너무 멋져 <br>너도 바로 인정 <br>너무 좋은 것 같애 <br>좋은 것 같애 <br>너를 처음 봤을때 <br>부터 쭉 이런 상태 뻔한 Story잖아 <br>정말 미칠것 같애 <br>미칠 것 같애 <br>너랑 같이 있을땐 <br>머리와 반대 내 맘대로 안돼 <br>그래 인정 해 <br>Baby <br>Yeah <br>너를 ㅇㅈ 가볍게 ㅇㅈ <br>내가 널 인정해 <br>인정 해 <br>Baby <br>Yeah <br>너를 ㅇㅈ 가볍게 ㅇㅈ <br>보고 싶어져 <br>매일 매일 매일 매일 매일 <br>입구는 있고 출구는 없나봐 <br>입고있는 츄리닝도 넌 멋져보여 <br>그눈으로 날 쳐다보며 말하면 <br>무슨대화를 했는지 기억 나질 않어 <br>Oh god 제발 날 살려줘 <br>벅차 생각만으로도 <br>넌 편하게 돈까스나 먹고있을때 <br>난 니 생각에 숨막히네 All day <br>너무 좋은 것 같애 <br>좋은 것 같애 <br>너를 처음 봤을때 <br>부터 쭉 이런 상태 뻔한 story잖아 <br>정말 미칠것 같애 <br>미칠 것 같애 <br>너랑 같이 있을땐 <br>머리와 반대 내 맘대로 안돼 <br>그래 인정해 <br>Hey <br>난 이미 너를 거부 못해 <br>Hey <br>친구들은 날 바보같댔지만 어때 <br>취향 Attack 딱 제대로야 <br>Can I do that <br>그래 인정 해 <br>Baby <br>Yeah <br>너를 ㅇㅈ 가볍게 ㅇㅈ <br>보고 싶어져 <br>매일 매일 매일 매일 매일 <br>너무 좋은 것 같애 <br>좋은 것 같애 <br>너를 처음 봤을때 <br>부터 쭉 이런 상태 뻔한 story잖아 <br>정말 미칠것 같애 <br>미칠 것 같애 <br>너랑 같이 있을땐 <br>머리와 반대 내 맘대로 안돼 <br>그래 인정 해 <br>Baby <br>Yeah <br>너를 ㅇㅈ 가볍게 ㅇㅈ <br>내가 널 인정해 <br>인정 해 <br>Baby <br>Yeah <br>너를 ㅇㅈ 가볍게 ㅇㅈ <br>보고 싶어져 <br>매일 매일 매일 매일 매일 <br>]]></content><category term="SOOM" label="SOOM"/><category term="인정 (Inst.)" label="인정 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SOOM/인정_Feat_산체스/</id><title>SOOM - 인정 (Feat. 산체스) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:00:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:00:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SOOM/%EC%9D%B8%EC%A0%95_Feat_%EC%82%B0%EC%B2%B4%EC%8A%A4/" title="SOOM - 인정 (Feat. 산체스) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 웃을때 입꼬리가 이뻐 <br>가지런히 가득담긴 치열 <br>표정없는 니가 웃어보일때 <br>나도 모르게 따라 미소를 짓네 <br>지금 나한테 넌 유일한 Muse <br>너말고 딴소린 다 안들려 Mute 쉿 <br>같이 걸을땐 다 Nice view <br>Woo I can't stop think about you <br>일이 손에 안잡힌단말 <br>빈말인거 같지만 <br>집중력에 한계가 와 매일밤 <br>일부러 안보려 폰을 뒤집어 놔도 <br>십분도 못넘기는거 알어 나도 <br>모든게 달라 어쩜 순정만화 <br>머리부터 발끝까지 너무 멋져 <br>너도 바로 인정 <br>너무 좋은 것 같애 <br>좋은 것 같애 <br>너를 처음 봤을때 <br>부터 쭉 이런 상태 뻔한 Story잖아 <br>정말 미칠것 같애 <br>미칠 것 같애 <br>너랑 같이 있을땐 <br>머리와 반대 내 맘대로 안돼 <br>그래 인정 해 <br>Baby <br>Yeah <br>너를 ㅇㅈ 가볍게 ㅇㅈ <br>내가 널 인정해 <br>인정 해 <br>Baby <br>Yeah <br>너를 ㅇㅈ 가볍게 ㅇㅈ <br>보고 싶어져 <br>매일 매일 매일 매일 매일 <br>입구는 있고 출구는 없나봐 <br>입고있는 츄리닝도 넌 멋져보여 <br>그눈으로 날 쳐다보며 말하면 <br>무슨대화를 했는지 기억 나질 않어 <br>Oh god 제발 날 살려줘 <br>벅차 생각만으로도 <br>넌 편하게 돈까스나 먹고있을때 <br>난 니 생각에 숨막히네 All day <br>너무 좋은 것 같애 <br>좋은 것 같애 <br>너를 처음 봤을때 <br>부터 쭉 이런 상태 뻔한 story잖아 <br>정말 미칠것 같애 <br>미칠 것 같애 <br>너랑 같이 있을땐 <br>머리와 반대 내 맘대로 안돼 <br>그래 인정해 <br>Hey <br>난 이미 너를 거부 못해 <br>Hey <br>친구들은 날 바보같댔지만 어때 <br>취향 Attack 딱 제대로야 <br>Can I do that <br>그래 인정 해 <br>Baby <br>Yeah <br>너를 ㅇㅈ 가볍게 ㅇㅈ <br>보고 싶어져 <br>매일 매일 매일 매일 매일 <br>너무 좋은 것 같애 <br>좋은 것 같애 <br>너를 처음 봤을때 <br>부터 쭉 이런 상태 뻔한 story잖아 <br>정말 미칠것 같애 <br>미칠 것 같애 <br>너랑 같이 있을땐 <br>머리와 반대 내 맘대로 안돼 <br>그래 인정 해 <br>Baby <br>Yeah <br>너를 ㅇㅈ 가볍게 ㅇㅈ <br>내가 널 인정해 <br>인정 해 <br>Baby <br>Yeah <br>너를 ㅇㅈ 가볍게 ㅇㅈ <br>보고 싶어져 <br>매일 매일 매일 매일 매일 <br>]]></content><category term="SOOM" label="SOOM"/><category term="인정 (Feat. 산체스)" label="인정 (Feat. 산체스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정화/지나가다/</id><title>정화 - 지나가다 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:01:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:01:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%ED%99%94/%EC%A7%80%EB%82%98%EA%B0%80%EB%8B%A4/" title="정화 - 지나가다 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[불현듯이 찾아오는 공허함 <br>누군가가 날 찾아줬으면 <br>오래된 기억들 하나 둘 <br>잊어버린 그 시절 그 시간 <br>I lose my way 다시 찾고 싶은 <br>I can’t go back 잘 알면서도 <br>What if I could go back <br>What if I could go back <br>그때의 날 다시 만날 수만 있다면 <br>What if I could go back <br>What if I could go back <br>그때의 날 다시 만날 수만 있다면 <br>있다면 <br>예전의 내 모습은 달랐을까 <br>누군가에 비춰진 내 모습은 <br>I lose my way 다시 찾고 싶은 <br>I can’t go back 잘 알면서도 <br>What if I could go back <br>What if I could go back <br>그때의 날 다시 만날 수만 있다면 <br>What if I could go back <br>What if I could go back <br>그때의 날 다시 만날 수만 있다면 <br>있다면 <br>What if I could go back <br>What if I could go back <br>그때의 날 다시 만날 수만 있다면 <br>있다면 <br>What if I could go back <br>What if I could go back <br>그때의 날 다시 만날 수만 있다면 <br>있다면 <br>]]></content><category term="정화" label="정화"/><category term="지나가다" label="지나가다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CHiCO_with_HoneyWorks/Wolf/</id><title>CHiCO with HoneyWorks - Wolf - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:01:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:01:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CHiCO_with_HoneyWorks/Wolf/" title="CHiCO with HoneyWorks - Wolf - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모-아이타쿠나이요 <br>신지테모신지테모 <br>키미닷테소-다로? <br>우라기라레룬다 <br>미세카케노토모다치 <br>무리시테룻테와카루요 <br>혼토-노코토쿠치니시테미나요 <br>카즈아와세하미다시테 <br>소레데모마다신지테 <br>바카미타이다네호라다마사레테 <br>아와노요-나키오쿠 <br>스레치가우보쿠타치 <br>코노키즈아토와케세나인다로? <br>키라이다 <br>맛스구니신지탓테 <br>코코로후사이데미탓테 <br>보쿠라와키즈츠케아운다 <br>손나후-니데키테루 <br>키미와카오이로카에즈니 <br>다레카노타메츠마즈이테루 <br>보쿠라와키즈츠케아운다 <br>손나후-니이키테루 <br>"코카이난테사세나이" <br>후루에테타키미노코에 <br>카키미다사레루... 키미가니가테다 <br>"나니사마노츠모리다" <br>도-요-카쿠스세리후 <br>바카미타이다네 호라다마사레테 <br>이츠모노요-니키미와 <br>아타리마에노카오데도나리오아루쿠 <br>모-운자리다 <br>키라이다 <br>즛토마모루카라난테 <br>코코로카키미다시탓테 <br>보쿠라와키즈츠케아운다 <br>손나후-니데키테루 <br>키미와야사시스기루카라 <br>나카나이카라 니게나이카라 <br>보쿠라와키즈츠케아운다 <br>손나후-니이키테루 <br>미세카케노키즈나니난도모다마사레테 <br>키미와히토리데카타오오토시타 <br>마케루나 <br>신지테루토사켄다 <br>코에가무네니토도이탓테 <br>보쿠라와키즈츠케아운다 <br>손나후-니데키테루 <br>키미와야사시스기루카라 <br>나카나이카라니게나이카라 <br>보쿠라와키즈츠케아운다 <br>손나후-니이키테루 <br>쿄-모카오이로카에즈니 <br>다레카노타메츠마즈이테루 <br>보쿠라와키즈츠케아운다 <br>손나후-니이키테루 <br>ah ah ah ah]]></content><category term="CHiCO with HoneyWorks" label="CHiCO with HoneyWorks"/><category term="Wolf" label="Wolf"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CHiCO_with_HoneyWorks/Canele/</id><title>CHiCO with HoneyWorks - Canele - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:01:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:01:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CHiCO_with_HoneyWorks/Canele/" title="CHiCO with HoneyWorks - Canele - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[토쿠이노 레시피 아피루시테 한노- 나이케도네 <br>호라네 카레노 타이도와 이츠모 도코카 츠메타이노 <br>하데메노 메이쿠 나레테키테 <br>세노비 시타 구루푸데 <br>쿄-모 에가오 츠쿳테 난토카 얏테마스 <br>코이오 돈돈돈 가소쿠사세테 <br>도아오 톤톤톤 놋쿠스루노 <br>와타시 신지테루요 다레모 시라나이 카레오 싯테루노 <br>와타시 다케노 히미츠 스코시 아게루 다키시메테 <br>후타리다케노 히미츠니 시챠오? <br>시로이 메렝게노 아와 키에나이 요-니 <br>후타리 다케노 히미츠 츠쿠로- <br>마카롱 쇼코라 카누레 타르토렛 마슈마로 가토쇼코라 <br>네- 타베테요네 <br>신지테루요 <br>우타가우 코토모 아루케도네 <br>코와쿠 나인데스요 <br>호라네 소바니 이루카라 키즈닷테 와케아이타이요 <br>쿠치가 와루쿠테 부아이소-데 <br>「다레모 타요라나이노?」 <br>쿄-모 에가오 사가시테 토나리오 아루키마스 <br>쿄리가 노 노 노 와칸나쿠낫테 <br>히토리봇치 이츠노 마니카 <br>와타시 신지타카라? 바카 미타이다네 호라 마타 츠마즈이테 <br>와타시 다케노 히미츠 카쿠시타이 코토모 아루노 <br>히토리다케노 히미츠니 시챠에… <br>시로이 메렝게노 아와 키에나이 요-니 <br>츠쿠리 와라이와 토쿠이난데스 <br>마카롱 쇼코라 카누레 타르토렛 마슈마로 가토쇼코라 <br>네- 노코사 나이데 <br>톤톤톤 놋쿠스루요 <br>키미니 우소와 츠키타쿠나이 <br>와타시 신지테루요 나미다와 니아와나이노 <br>와타시 다케노 히미츠 스코시 아게루 다키시메테 <br>「키미가 스키다요」 <br>츠부야쿠 <br>시로이 메렝게노 아와 키에나이 요-니 <br>후타리 다케노 히미츠 츠쿠로- <br>마카롱 쇼코라 카누레 타르토렛 마슈마로 가토쇼코라 <br>네- 타베테요네 <br>스키×10 세-노! 상큐♪ <br>신지테루요 <br>아이시테루요 <br>신지테루요]]></content><category term="CHiCO with HoneyWorks" label="CHiCO with HoneyWorks"/><category term="Canele" label="Canele"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TK_from_Ling_tosite_sigure/Unravel_Acoustic_Version/</id><title>TK from Ling tosite sigure - Unravel (Acoustic Version) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:02:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:02:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TK_from_Ling_tosite_sigure/Unravel_Acoustic_Version/" title="TK from Ling tosite sigure - Unravel (Acoustic Version) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[？えて ？えてよ その仕組みを <br>오시에테 오시에테요 소노 시쿠미오 <br>알려줘 알려줘 그 구조를 <br><br>僕の中に誰がいるの? <br>보쿠노 나카니 다레가 이루노 <br>내 안에 누가 있는거야? <br><br>？れた ？れたよ この世界で <br>코와레타 코와레타요 코노 세카이데 <br>부서졌어 부서져버렸어 이 세계에서 <br><br>君が笑う 何も見えずに <br>키미가 와라우 나니모 미에즈니 <br>네가 웃고있어 아무것도 보이지 않은 채 <br><br>？れた僕なんてさ 息を止めて <br>코와레타 보쿠난테사 이키오 토메테 <br>부서진 나같은 건 말이야 숨을 멈춰줘 <br><br>ほどけない もう ほどけないよ <br>호도케나이 모우 호도케나이요 <br>풀 수 없어 이젠 풀 수 없어 <br><br>？？さえ Freeze <br>시인지츠사에 Freeze <br>진실조차도 Freeze <br><br>？せる <br>코와세루 <br>부술 수 있어 <br><br>？せない <br>코와세나이 <br>부술 수 없어 <br><br>狂える <br>쿠루에루 <br>미칠 수 있어 <br><br>狂えない <br>쿠루에나이 <br>미칠 수 없어 <br><br>あなたを見つけて <br>아나타오 미츠케테 <br>너를 찾아서 <br><br>？れて 歪んだ世界にだんだん僕は <br>유레테 유간다 세카이니 단단 보쿠와 <br>흔들리고 일그러진 세계에 점점 나는 <br><br>透き通って見えなくなって <br>스키토옷테 미에나쿠낫테 <br>투명해져서 보이지 않게 되서 <br><br>見つけないで 僕のことを <br>미츠케 나이데 보쿠노 코토오 <br>찾지 말아줘 나를 <br><br>見つめないで <br>미츠메나이데 <br>보지 말아줘 <br><br>誰かが描いた世界の中で <br>다레카가 에가이타 세카이노 나카데 <br>누군가가 그린 세계 속에서 <br><br>あなたを傷つけたくはないよ <br>아나타오 키즈츠케 타쿠와 나이요 <br>널 상처입히고 싶진 않아 <br><br>？えてて 僕のことを <br>오보에테테 보쿠노 코토오 <br>기억해줘 나에 대해서 <br><br>鮮やかなまま <br>아자야카나 마마 <br>선명한 채로 <br><br>無限に？がる孤？が絡まる <br>무게엔니 히로가루 코도쿠가 카라마루 <br>무한히 펼쳐지는 고독감이 얽혀 <br><br>無邪？に笑った記憶が刺さって <br>무쟈키니 와랏타 키오쿠가 사삿테 <br>천진난만하게 웃었던 기억이 박혀서 <br><br>動けない <br>우고케나이 <br>움직일 수 없어 <br><br>動けない <br>우고케나이 <br>움직일 수 없어 <br><br>動けない <br>우고케나이 <br>움직일 수 없어 <br><br>動けない <br>우고케나이 <br>움직일 수 없어 <br><br>動けない <br>우고케나이 <br>움직일 수 없어 <br><br>動けないよ <br>우고케나이요 <br>움직일 수 없다고 <br><br>Unraveling ghoul <br><br>？わってしまった ？えられなかった <br>카왓테시맛타 카에라레나캇타 <br>변해버렸어 변할 수 없었어 <br><br>二つが絡まる 二人が滅びる <br>후타츠가 카라마루 후타리가 호로비루 <br>두가지가 얽힌 두 사람이 죽어가 <br><br>？せる <br>코와세루 <br>부술 수 있어 <br><br>？せない <br>코와세나이 <br>부술 수 없어 <br><br>狂える <br>쿠루에루 <br>미칠 수 있어 <br><br>狂えない <br>쿠루에나이 <br>미칠 수 없어 <br><br>あなたを汚せないよ <br>아나타오 케가세 나이요 <br>당신을 더럽히지 않아 <br><br>？れて 歪んだ世界にだんだん僕は <br>유레테 유간다 세카이니 단단 보쿠와 <br>흔들리고 일그러진 세계에 점점 나는 <br><br>透き通って見えなくなって <br>스키토옷테 미에나쿠낫테 <br>투명해져서 보이지 않게 되서 <br><br>見つけないで 僕のことを <br>미츠케 나이데 보쿠노 코토오 <br>찾지 말아줘 나를 <br><br>見つめないで <br>미츠메나이데 <br>보지 말아줘 <br><br>誰かが仕組んだ孤？な？に <br>다레카가 시쿤다 코도쿠나 와나니 <br>누군가가 만든 고독한 함정에 <br><br>未？がほどけてしまう前に <br>미라이가 호도케테시마우 마에니 <br>미래가 녹아버리기 전에 <br><br>思い出して 僕のことを <br>오모이다시테 보쿠노 코토오 <br>떠올려줘 나에 대해서 <br><br>鮮やかなまま <br>아자야카나 마마 <br>선명한 채로 <br><br>忘れないで <br>와스레 나이데 <br>잊지 말아줘 <br><br>忘れないで <br>와스레 나이데 <br>잊지 말아줘 <br><br>忘れないで <br>와스레 나이데 <br>잊지 말아줘 <br><br>忘れないで <br>와스레 나이데 <br>잊지 말아줘 <br><br>？わってしまったことに Paralyze <br>카왓테시맛타코토니 Paralyze <br>변해버린 것에 Paralyze <br><br>？えられないことだらけ Paradise <br>카에라레나이코토다라케 Paradise <br>바꿀 수 없는 것뿐인 Paradise <br><br>？えてて 僕のことを <br>오보에테테 보쿠노 코토오 <br>기억해줘 나에 대해서 <br><br>？えて ？えて <br>오시에테 오시에테 <br>알려줘 알려줘 <br><br>僕の中に誰がいるの? <br>보쿠노 나카니 다레가 이루노? <br>내 안에 누가 있는거야?]]></content><category term="TK from Ling tosite sigure" label="TK from Ling tosite sigure"/><category term="Unravel (Acoustic Version)" label="Unravel (Acoustic Version)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TK_from_Ling_tosite_sigure/Signal/</id><title>TK from Ling tosite sigure - Signal - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:02:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:02:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TK_from_Ling_tosite_sigure/Signal/" title="TK from Ling tosite sigure - Signal - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[카은죠우니츠케루 <br>나마에와지유우다네 <br>호라 카와리하테타 <br>케세나이보쿠노 <br>츠미노히키가네가 <br>토케테시마이소우데 <br>치다라케니나앗타 <br>아노히노이미와 <br>나쿠나루하즈모나이요네 <br>니쿠시미가키에테시마앗타라 <br>키미오코로세나이카라 <br>카코오미타시테이루 <br>츠미가츠쿠웃타 <br>보쿠데아루타메니 <br>에이에은세이노나이푸데 <br>키오쿠노 Signal <br>키자마레테루노니 <br>이타미사에케시사앗테시마우 <br>키즈나노 Spiral <br>마요이코은다 <br>보쿠와보쿠니 <br>키에카쿠레테이쿠 <br>보쿠와코도쿠사 <br>도우카소노마마데 <br>키미가와라우타비니 <br>나쿠나루하즈모나이노니 <br>키즈카라메오소라사나이요우니 <br>니쿠시미요소바니이테 <br>키미오코로시타이카라 <br>카코오미타시테이루 <br>츠미가츠쿠웃타 <br>보쿠데아루타메니 <br>에이에은세이노나이푸데 <br>키오쿠노 Signal <br>키자마레티루노니 <br>이타미사에케시사앗테시마우 <br>키즈나노 Spiral <br>마요이코은다보쿠와보쿠니 <br>키에카쿠레테이쿠 <br>레이가무게은 레이가무게은 <br>레이가무게은 레이가무게은 <br>]]></content><category term="TK from Ling tosite sigure" label="TK from Ling tosite sigure"/><category term="Signal" label="Signal"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aimer/セプテンバーさん___September_San/</id><title>Aimer - セプテンバーさん / September San - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:02:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:02:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aimer/%E3%82%BB%E3%83%97%E3%83%86%E3%83%B3%E3%83%90%E3%83%BC%E3%81%95%E3%82%93___September_San/" title="Aimer - セプテンバーさん / September San - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[히토리노타메니에가이타유메오 다레카니츠카이마와시타 <br>손나코토모아루사토 와라에루보쿠모킷토세프템바 <br>「나츠」테다케데키라키라시테타 아노키모치가스키나노 <br>「모오스코시다케코코니이사세테」손나카오데보쿠미루노 <br>데모키미가와라에루리유-나라 보쿠가미츠케테키테아게루 <br>콘나후타리오츠나구노와 킷토난데모나이세프템바 <br>혼모노요리모리아루니미에타 아노마호-와모오토케타 <br>케도귯토스레바큔토나루아레와 나츠노오카게난카쟈나이 <br>시메루소라가카와쿠이로오 킷토파파와사가시테이타노 <br>손나토키니히토리포츤토우즈쿠맛테타세프템바 <br>OH September- OH September- <br>OH September- OH September- <br><br>유메가카타리츠쿠시타키보-오 보쿠와히로우요 키미와미테루노? <br>사아이마나라바 코노코에나라바토도쿠키가시탄다 <br>나츠가치라카시텟타코코로오 보쿠와츠무구요 사아이자유코 <br>소오이마다카라 코노코에다카라 히비쿠세프템바 <br>코에가히비키다스 소코니이미와나쿠토모 <br>키미가와라이다스 소코니나츠와이나쿠토모 <br>OH September- OH September- <br>OH September- OH September- <br><br>보쿠가와라에루리유-나라 이마마사니메노마에니이루요 <br>콘나보쿠라오츠나구노와 소오사이츠모 <br>아이가카타리츠쿠시타오모이오 보쿠와우타우요 히토와와라우요 <br>데모이마나라바 코노코에나라바토도쿠키가시탄다 <br>테토테오토레바유레루코코로가 카카에타후시기 소레와테레파시 <br>사아이마다카라 코노코에다카라 사아이마나라바 코노코에나라바 <br>콘나보쿠다케도 소오키미토나라 나니모나이케레도 소오이마나라바 <br>코노코에나라바 소오키미토나라 히비쿠키가시탄다 <br>아아 코노토키가 카타루모노 <br>아아 코노토키가 츠나구모노]]></content><category term="Aimer" label="Aimer"/><category term="セプテンバーさん / September San" label="セプテンバーさん / September San"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aimer/蝶々結び___Choucho_Musubi_나비_매듭/</id><title>Aimer - 蝶々結び / Choucho Musubi (나비 매듭) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:02:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:02:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aimer/%E8%9D%B6%E3%80%85%E7%B5%90%E3%81%B3___Choucho_Musubi_%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84_%EB%A7%A4%EB%93%AD/" title="Aimer - 蝶々結び / Choucho Musubi (나비 매듭) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[片っぽで丸を作って <br>카탓포데 마루오 츠쿳테 <br>한쪽 끝으로 원을 만들어서 <br><br>しっかり持ってて <br>싯카리 못테테 <br>꽉 잡고 있어 <br><br>もう片っぽでその丸の後ろを <br>모우 카탓포데 소노 마루노 우시로오 <br>다른쪽 끝을 원 뒤쪽으로 <br><br>ぐるっと回って <br>구룻토 마왓테 <br>한바퀴 휙 돌려서 <br><br>間にできたポッケに入って <br>아이다니 데키타 폿케니 하잇테 <br>사이에 생긴 구멍에 넣어 <br><br>出て？るのを待ってて <br>데테쿠루노오 맛테테 <br>끝이 나오길 기다려 <br><br>出てきたところを迎えにきて <br>데테키타토코로오 무카에니키테 <br>나오면 마중가서 <br><br>「せの？」で引っぱって <br>「세노-」데 힛팟테 <br>"하나 둘 셋"을 세고 잡아당겨 <br><br>はじめはなんとも <br>하지메와 난토모 <br>처음에는 굉장히 <br><br>情けない形だとしても <br>나사케나이 카타치다토 시테모 <br>예쁘지 못한 형태라 할지라도 <br><br>同じだけ力を？めて <br>오나지다케 치카라오 코메테 <br>균일하게 힘을 줘봐 <br><br><br>羽根は大きく 結び目は固く <br>하네와 오오키쿠 무스비메와 카타쿠 <br>날개(고리)는 커다랗게 매듭은 단단히 <br><br>なるようにきつく <br>나루요우니 키츠쿠 <br>풀리지 않게 꽈악 <br><br>結んでいてほしいの <br>무슨데 이테 호시이노 <br>묶어주면 좋겠어 <br><br>腕はここに 想い出は遠くに <br>우데와 코코니 오모이데와 토오쿠니 <br>끈은 여기에 추억은 저 멀리 <br><br>置いておいてほしい ほしいの <br>오이테 오이테 호시이 호시이노 <br>두었으면 좋겠어 <br><br><br>片っぽでも引っ張っちゃえば <br>카탓포데모 힛팟챠에바 <br>한쪽을 잡아당겨버리면 <br><br>ほどけちゃうけど <br>호도케챠우케도 <br>풀려버리지만, <br><br>作ったもの？すのは <br>츠쿳타모노 코와스노와 <br>만든 걸 망가뜨리는 건 <br><br>？かに簡？だけど <br>하루카니 칸탄다케도 <br>너무나 간단한 일이지만, <br><br>だけどほどく時も <br>다케도 호도쿠 토키모 <br>그럼에도 풀 때도 <br><br>そう、ちゃんと 同じようにね <br>소우, 챤토 오나지 요우니네 <br>그래, 제대로 아까와 같이 <br><br>分かってるよ でもできたらね <br>와캇테루요 데모 데키타라네 <br>알고 있어 그래도 가능하다면 <br><br>「せの？」で引っ張って <br>「세노-」데 힛팟테 <br>"하나 둘 셋"에 맞춰 잡아당겨 <br><br>ほどけやしないように <br>호도케 야시나이 요우니 <br>풀려버리지 않기를 <br><br>と願って力？めては <br>토 네갓테 치카라 코메테와 <br>바라며 힘을 주면 <br><br>？げすぎた羽根に？惑う <br>히로게스기타 하네니 토마도우 <br>너무 활짝 펴진 날개에 깜짝 놀라 <br><br><br>羽根は大きく 結び目は固く <br>하네와 오오키쿠 무스비메와 카타쿠 <br>날개는 커다랗게 매듭은 단단히 <br><br>なるようにきつく <br>나루요우니 키츠쿠 <br>풀리지 않게 꽈악 <br><br>結んでいてほしいの <br>무슨데 이테 호시이노 <br>묶어주면 좋겠어 <br><br>夢はここに 想い出は遠くに <br>유메와 코코니 오모이데와 토오쿠니 <br>꿈은 여기에 추억은 저 멀리 <br><br>？付けばそこにあるくらいがいい <br>키즈케바 소코니 아루 쿠라이가 이이 <br>어느새 눈 앞에 있다는 걸 눈치챌 정도가 좋아 <br><br><br>？って引っ張ったりしないでよ <br>다맛테 힛팟타리 시나이데요 <br>말도 없이 당기지 마 <br><br>不恰好な蝶にしないでよ <br>부캇코나 쵸우니 시나이데요 <br>이상한 나비모양으로 하지 마 <br><br>結んだつもりがほどいていたり <br>무슨다 츠모리가 호도이테 이타리 <br>묶었다고 생각했는데 풀리기도 하고 <br><br>緩めたつもりが締めていたり <br>유루메타 츠모리가 시메테 이타리 <br>느슨히 하려고 했더니 더 꽉 조여지기도 하고 <br><br><br>この蒼くて？い世界に <br>코노 아오쿠테 히로이 세카이니 <br>이 푸르고 넓은 세상에 <br><br>無？に散らばった中から <br>무스우니 치라밧타 나카카라 <br>무수하게 흐트러진 그 속에서 <br><br>別？に二人選んだ？を <br>베츠베츠니 후타리 에란다 이토오 <br>우리가 각자 고른 끈을 <br><br>お互いたぐり寄せ合ったんだ <br>오타가이 타구리 요세앗탄다 <br>실은 서로가 당기고 있었던 거야 <br><br>結ばれたんじゃなく結んだんだ <br>무스바레탄 쟈나쿠 무슨단다 <br>묶여진 게 아니라 우리가 묶은 거야 <br><br>二人で「せの？」で引っ張ったんだ <br>후타리데 「세노-」데 힛팟탄다 <br>둘이서 "하나 둘 셋"에 맞춰 잡아당긴거야 <br><br>大きくも　小さくも なりすぎないように <br>오오키쿠모 치이사쿠모 나리스기나이 요우니 <br>과하게 크지도 작지도 않도록 <br><br>力を？めたんだ <br>치카라오 코메탄다 <br>힘을 준거야]]></content><category term="Aimer" label="Aimer"/><category term="蝶々結び / Choucho Musubi (나비 매듭)" label="蝶々結び / Choucho Musubi (나비 매듭)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blush/Electric/</id><title>Blush - Electric - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:02:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:02:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blush/Electric/" title="Blush - Electric - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ooh Woah <br>A sensitivity In every part of me <br>Like a shock On my skin <br><br>Every time you walk in <br>It's Electricity <br>Like A beat <br>In my heart <br>And now I'm thinking bout you <br>And now I'm thinking bout you <br>And now I'm thinking bout you <br>Ohh, Yeah <br><br>Boy I don't really know Nothing about you <br>But I'm excited just to be around you <br>I'm taken by the Aura that surrounds you <br>I feel Electric <br>I feel Electric <br>You give me Butterflies <br>You give me Butterflies <br>You give me Butterflies <br>You give me Butterflies <br><br>You've got me wired to Every part of you <br>You came, Hit the switch <br>Oooh, You made me Electric <br>I'm connected to you <br>Like a beat In my heart <br>And now I'm thinking bout you <br>And now I'm thinking bout you <br>And now I'm thinking bout you <br>You got me thinking bout you <br><br>Boy I don't really know Nothing about you <br>But I'm excited just to be around you <br>I'm taken by the Aura that surrounds you <br>I feel Electric <br>I feel Electric <br>You give me Butterflies <br>You give me Butterflies <br>You give me Butterflies <br>You give me Butterflies <br><br>Boy I don't really know Nothing about you <br>But I'm excited just to be around you <br>I'm taken by the Aura that surrounds you <br>I feel Electric <br>I feel Electric <br>You give me Butterflies <br>You give me Butterflies <br>You give me Butterflies <br>You give me Butterflies <br><br>Boy I don't really know Nothing about you <br>But I'm excited just to be around you <br>I'm taken by the Aura that surrounds you <br>I feel Electric <br>I feel Electric <br><br>You give me Butterflies <br><br>You give me Butterflies]]></content><category term="Blush" label="Blush"/><category term="Electric" label="Electric"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/새벽세시/작은_별_Little_Star/</id><title>새벽세시 - 작은 별 (Little Star) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:02:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:02:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%83%88%EB%B2%BD%EC%84%B8%EC%8B%9C/%EC%9E%91%EC%9D%80_%EB%B3%84_Little_Star/" title="새벽세시 - 작은 별 (Little Star) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[푸른 꿈을 꾸고 있을 <br>작고 어린 너에게 <br>누구도 <br>헛되다 말할 수 없어 <br>꿈을 꾼다는 건 <br>희망이 있다는 거 <br>그 희망이 결국 <br>널 웃게할꺼야 <br>손 닿지 않는 별을 보며 <br>허공에 손을 뻗어 보며 <br>오늘은 그렇게 네 옅은 <br>한숨속에 눈물짓겠지만 <br>닿지 않는 꿈에 <br>짊어진 한숨보다 <br>그런 꿈마저 꾸지 않는 건 <br>많이 울고 많이 웃을 <br>나날들 속에서 <br>너마저 네 곁에 없다면 <br>빛난 별들 사이 <br>작은 별 하나 <br>쉽게 움츠려들곤 해 <br>오늘도 그렇게 <br>지친 맘 달래보며 <br>잠이 들겠지만 <br>푸른 꿈을 꾸고 있을 <br>작고 어린 너에게 <br>누구도 <br>헛되다 말 할 수 없어 <br>꿈을 꾼다는 건 <br>희망이 있다는 거 <br>그 희망이 결국 <br>널 웃게할꺼야 <br>꺄르르 터뜨리는 <br>너의 웃음 반짝이는 눈망울 <br>야무지게 다문 빨간 입술 <br>널 감싸는 따스한 공기 <br>그 꿈을 꾸는 것만으로 <br>넌 내게 이미 작은 별 <br>]]></content><category term="새벽세시" label="새벽세시"/><category term="작은 별 (Little Star)" label="작은 별 (Little Star)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Carbon_Warfare/</id><title>Dan Bull - Carbon Warfare - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:09:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:09:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/Carbon_Warfare/" title="Dan Bull - Carbon Warfare - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm the most heartless of businessmen, I'm on a mission <br>Harming the climate with carbon emission <br>Falsify facts to calm opposition <br>Despite the obvious harsher condition we live in <br>The thermometer's splitting <br>Can't take the heat <br>Then depart from the kitchen <br>Just stop all the bitching, I'm trynna' do business <br>Acquiring riches is like a religion <br>Melt the last ice caps, just like that <br>Deploy propaganda to gaslight stats <br>Then cry 'fake news' when I dislike facts <br>That's my strategy, that's my act <br>Slash and burn and amass my cash <br>Salt the scorched Earth, just for a laugh <br>Don't get caught in the global warming hoax <br>All the warnings are totally boring <br><br>I, just want to watch the world burn <br>Earn what's mine <br>'Til we arrive at the point of no return <br>I, just want to watch the world burn <br>Burn <br>We'll never learn, we'll never learn, we'll never learn <br><br>Aim <br>Create massive pain <br>Spray acid rain <br>Assassinate Mother Nature, that's the game <br>Natural disaster, that's what we're after <br>Tapping that ass like I'm fracking for gas <br>Look <br>Gas guzzler <br>Mass muzzler <br>Fact shuffler <br>Crap shoveller <br>Blast muffler <br>The whole planet's last hustler <br>Dat autocratic fat cat sat smug on a pandaskin rug <br>That I had smuggled in from the jungle I'm cutting up <br>My cash stocks and the temperature's looking up <br>No inspectors'll get through me <br>You'll regret if you reckon that I'll let you see <br>I'll affect every breath you breathe <br>Chainsmoke cigarettes in my SUV <br>I'll choke the sheriff and the deputy <br>Turn everyone on Earth to a refugee <br>I revel in seeing the sea level reach a new piece of the beach 'til the piers beneath it <br>The Devil and the deep blue sea you're between <br>It's too late to cease when you've already seen it <br>Rip right through reefs like a riptide <br>Look right to the sky, see hypocrites ride <br>Private planes while describing the ways we should fight the invasion of climate change <br>Stop their childish ways off the climbing frames <br>I say put 'em on the firing range <br>I'm a tyrant, violent to my environment <br>Crimes against nature, acquiring a pile of 'em <br>Innit ironic, that I run it, when I couldn't give a flying fog if anyone'll survive from it <br>I'm not even being hyperbolic, I'm diabolic <br>Never do I wanna' see a dial with a smile on it <br><br>I, just want to watch the world burn <br>Earn what's mine <br>'Til we arrive at the point of no return <br>I, just want to watch the world burn <br>Burn <br>We'll never learn, we'll never learn, we'll never learn]]></content><category term="Dan Bull" label="Dan Bull"/><category term="Carbon Warfare" label="Carbon Warfare"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김효영/그땐/</id><title>김효영 - 그땐 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:15:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:15:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%9A%A8%EC%98%81/%EA%B7%B8%EB%95%90/" title="김효영 - 그땐 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그땐 <br>몰랐었지 그땐 <br>함께일 거라 했었지 <br>믿었었지 그땐 <br>이렇게도 쉽게 <br>모든 것이 사라질거라 <br>믿을 수가 없었지 <br>정말 몰랐었지 그땐 <br>그때 우리 좀 더 사랑했다면 <br>덜 아팠을까 우린 <br>따뜻했을까 <br>내가 사랑한다 말을 했다면 <br>지금도 함께일까 우린 <br>행복하게 웃고 있을까 <br>이렇게도 쉽게 <br>모든 것이 사라질거라 <br>믿을 수가 없었지 <br>정말 몰랐었지 그땐 <br>그때 우리 좀 더 사랑했다면 <br>덜 아팠을까 우린 <br>따뜻했을까 <br>내가 사랑한다 말을 했다면 <br>지금도 함께일까 우린 <br>행복하게 웃고 있을까 <br>엉켜버린 실을 <br>나 풀 줄 몰라서 <br>그때는 그냥 <br>피해야 할 것 같았어 <br>어렸었던 나의 방법에 <br>니가 얼마나 아플 줄 몰랐어 <br>그때 우리 좀 더 아꼈더라면 <br>덜 아팠을까 우린 <br>행복했을까 <br>내가 미안하다 말을 했다면 <br>니가 날 안았을까 우린 <br>서로 손을 잡아줬을까 <br>]]></content><category term="김효영" label="김효영"/><category term="그땐" label="그땐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/미셸_킴/416_Waltz/</id><title>미셸 킴 - 416 Waltz - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:15:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:15:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AF%B8%EC%85%B8_%ED%82%B4/416_Waltz/" title="미셸 킴 - 416 Waltz - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이리 와 이리 와 나와 함께 가자 <br>이리 와 이리 와 나와 함께 가자 <br>엄마랑 아빠랑 나와 함께 가자 <br>친구랑 쌤이랑 나와 함께 가자 <br>우 우 우 우 <br>우 우 우 우 우 <br>이리 와 이리 와 나와 함께 가자 <br>이리 와 이리 와 나와 함께 가자 <br>]]></content><category term="미셸 킴" label="미셸 킴"/><category term="416 Waltz" label="416 Waltz"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍영구/내게_돌아와_Come_Back_To_Me/</id><title>홍영구 - 내게 돌아와 (Come Back To Me) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:15:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:15:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%98%81%EA%B5%AC/%EB%82%B4%EA%B2%8C_%EB%8F%8C%EC%95%84%EC%99%80_Come_Back_To_Me/" title="홍영구 - 내게 돌아와 (Come Back To Me) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잊었다는 말 못하겠어 <br>너 돌아오려 할 때쯤 <br>그런 나를 보고 너 <br>차마 단념할지 모르니 <br>그날 그때의 모습으로 <br>나 기다리고 있을 테니 <br>준비될 때 오면 돼 <br>많은 건 묻지 않을 테니까 <br>내게 돌아와 널 사랑하는 나에게 <br>그 미소 다시 보여 줄 순 없니 <br>우리의 짧은 만남은 헛된 것이 아니야 <br>나 다시 웃을 수 있게 <br>도와줘 <br>다른 누군갈 사랑할 거라면 <br>그래 그래도 난 괜찮아 <br>준비될 때 오면 돼 <br>많은 건 묻지 않을 테니까 <br>내게 돌아와 널 사랑하는 나에게 <br>그 미소 다시 보여 줄 순 없니 <br>우리의 짧은 만남은 헛된 것이 아니야 <br>나 다시 웃을 수 있게 <br>내게 돌아와 널 사랑하는 나에게 <br>그 미소 보여줄 순 없니 <br>우리의 짧은 만남은 헛된 것이 아니야 <br>나 다시 웃을 수 있게 <br>도와줘 <br>]]></content><category term="홍영구" label="홍영구"/><category term="내게 돌아와 (Come Back To Me)" label="내게 돌아와 (Come Back To Me)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오빗/30/</id><title>오빗 - 30 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:16:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:16:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%97/30/" title="오빗 - 30 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[인생역전할거라고 음악으로 <br>답이 없어 좆망하고 난 학교로 <br>다 끝내니 실려가 응급실로 <br>중환자실에서 <br>갱생하고 나니 나이 서른 <br>당뇨판정 받고 나니 몸이 병신 <br>대가리는 원래부터 병신이었고 <br>그럼 나는 둘 다 병신 근데 <br>여자들은 병신보단 <br>차라리 짐승을 더 좋아한대 <br>답은 출세가 아닌 용기란 걸 <br>삼류영화보고 나는 알았는걸 <br>순간의 짙은 감정조차 숨겼었던 <br>내가 진짜 너무 바보 같아 <br>노래하는 모습에 반했었던 <br>학교에서 몇 번 봤던 예쁜 그녀 <br>바라만 봐도 너무 설레었어 <br>이제 와서 나 혼자서 짓껄여 <br>화려한 밤의 유혹들 다 지나가고 <br>밝은 햇살은 그림자만 키워가고 <br>다가갈까 하다가도 내가 못나 보여 <br>날 이상하게 볼까 봐서 <br>화려한 밤의 유혹들 다 지나가고 <br>밝은 햇살은 그림자만 키워가고 <br>다가갈까 하다가도 내가 못나 보여 <br>내 마음만은 진심인데 <br>배때기에 인슐린을 <br>꽂고 나서 생각을 해 <br>뭐를 해서 돈을 벌까 나를 위해 <br>우리 엄만 투잡을 해 돈을 벌기 위해 <br>그래 여긴 씨발 자본주의 사회 <br>학교에서 배운 건 다 필요 없어 <br>돈을 버는 그런 기술이 아니었어 <br>음악만이 내가 살 길인데 <br>음악이 나의 목을 조여오네 <br>담배 피는 그런 기분 <br>사람들은 내 음악이 이상하대 <br>난 그렇게 나쁜 놈 아닌데 <br>검은 색을 카메라에 담은 건데 <br>하얀색도 붉은색도 다 있는데 <br>친구들은 하나 둘씩 자릴 잡고 <br>첫사랑은 결혼해서 아일 낳고 <br>그마저도 짝사랑이라 아무 말도 <br>이제 와서 나 혼자서 짓껄여 <br>화려한 밤의 유혹들 다 지나가고 <br>밝은 햇살은 그림자만 키워가고 <br>다가갈까 하다가도 내가 못나 보여 <br>날 이상하게 볼까 봐서 <br>화려한 밤의 유혹들 다 지나가고 <br>밝은 햇살은 그림자만 키워가고 <br>다가갈까 하다가도 내가 못나 보여 <br>내 마음만은 진심인데 <br>알 수 없는 불안함에 방황하다가 <br>생각에 생각이 꼬릴 잡고 따라가다가 <br>원초적인 증오심에 사로잡혀 난 <br>온갖 못된 걸 다 해버리고 자기합리화 <br>씨발 개발 거리면서 <br>병신들을 욕하더니 <br>나도 병신이 되어있네 <br>아니었던 적 있었는지 <br>누굴 위해 뭘 한 적이 있었는지 <br>해보려고 했었는지 <br>거짓 뿐인 세상 속에 <br>하나 둘씩 모여들어 <br>진실을 외치라고 사람들은 외쳐 <br>세상이 거짓인데 진실이 있긴 있어 <br>사람들은 얼마만큼 진실했어 <br>거짓뿐인 사람들을 욕하면서 <br>스스로의 감정에는 계속 구라 쳤어 <br>아니라고 아니라고 말하면서 <br>나도 그저 그런 놈이 되어 있어 <br>화려한 밤의 유혹들 다 지나가고 <br>밝은 햇살은 그림자만 키워가고 <br>다가갈까 하다가도 내가 못나 보여 <br>날 이상하게 볼까 봐서 <br>화려한 밤의 유혹들 다 지나가고 <br>밝은 햇살은 그림자만 키워가고 <br>다가갈까 하다가도 내가 못나 보여 <br>내 마음만은 진심인데 <br>]]></content><category term="오빗" label="오빗"/><category term="30" label="30"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오빗/존나_멋진_악당/</id><title>오빗 - 존나 멋진 악당 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:16:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:16:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%97/%EC%A1%B4%EB%82%98_%EB%A9%8B%EC%A7%84_%EC%95%85%EB%8B%B9/" title="오빗 - 존나 멋진 악당 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[못되고 나쁜 새끼들은 교활한 <br>대가리 굴리면서 빠구리도 <br>존나 잘치면서 개똥폼 처 잡으면서 <br>가슴 큰 여자 젖 만지면서 <br>존나 잘 살어 <br>나처럼 힘 없는 병신 찐따들은 <br>그런 놈들 욕을 하며 <br>마녀사냥 다구리지 <br>그래 너넨 평생 병신 찐따 <br>아다 나는 될거야 yo <br>존나 멋진 악당 <br>중학생 때 찐따 엄마가 공부도 <br>못하니까 음악 같은 거라도 해보라 <br>보낸 기타 학원에서 베이스를 <br>배워 기다랗고 큰 귀두처럼 생겼어 <br>두둥 뛰는 심장처럼 두둥 울리는 <br>베이스 소리 두둥 세상을 <br>울릴 것만 같았었던 <br>우리 팀은 파죽지세 <br>우린 기세등등 그 때 난 이미 <br>rockstar <br>현실은 락찔이 방구석 딸잡이가 <br>무대에 서니 인생 바뀐 줄 알지 <br>바뀐 건 없지 바뀐 거 같지 <br>뭐라도 된 줄 알았지 <br>될 줄 알았지 비뚤어진 세상보다 <br>더 비뚤어지고 싶어 공부 못해도 <br>성공한단 걸 보여주고서 비웃으면서 <br>존나 멋진 악당이 되고 싶었지 <br>못되고 나쁜 새끼들은 교활한 <br>대가리 굴리면서 빠구리도 <br>존나 잘치면서 개똥폼 처 잡으면서 <br>가슴 큰 여자 젖 만지면서 <br>존나 잘 살어 <br>나처럼 힘 없는 병신 찐따들은 <br>그런 놈들 욕을 하며 <br>마녀사냥 다구리지 <br>그래 너넨 평생 병신 찐따 <br>아다 나는 될거야 yo <br>존나 멋진 악당 <br>천호동 bobos9 에서 <br>dj hiphop 부터 e.d.m 섹스를 <br>매일 하는 형들이 부러워 <br>나도 섹스하고 싶어ㅋ <br>근데 잘 안돼 그러다 온 기회 <br>그녀가 오늘 같이 있어달래 <br>오예 밤새 대한민국 만세 <br>나도 간다 모텔 <br>아 근데 씨발 엄마한테 전화 왔네 <br>오늘도 그냥 집에 가서 딸딸이 <br>1년 2년 3년 4년 음악 하다 <br>보니까 나는 누군가 여긴 어딘가 <br>고졸에 백수 소리도 없이 <br>사라질 나의 소리 <br>에이 씨발 음악 안해 하고 <br>대학 갔네 그래놓고 1년 후엔 <br>다시 건반을 애무하네 <br>쪽팔려서 음악한단 말도 못하면서 <br>랩으로 해 존나 <br>멋진 악당이 되고 싶어 <br>못되고 나쁜 새끼들은 교활한 <br>대가리 굴리면서 빠구리도 <br>존나 잘치면서 개똥폼 처 잡으면서 <br>가슴 큰 여자 젖 만지면서 <br>존나 잘 살어 <br>나처럼 힘 없는 병신 찐따들은 <br>그런 놈들 욕을 하며 <br>마녀사냥 다구리지 <br>그래 너넨 평생 병신 찐따 <br>아다 나는 될거야 yo <br>존나 멋진 악당 <br>]]></content><category term="오빗" label="오빗"/><category term="존나 멋진 악당" label="존나 멋진 악당"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오빗/오빗이가_추천하는_av배우/</id><title>오빗 - 오빗이가 추천하는 av배우 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:16:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:16:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%97/%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%97%EC%9D%B4%EA%B0%80_%EC%B6%94%EC%B2%9C%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_av%EB%B0%B0%EC%9A%B0/" title="오빗 - 오빗이가 추천하는 av배우 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아 나 존잘 키만 컸어도 배우 <br>정우성의 뒤를 이을 뜨는 남배우 <br>허나 현실은 우울 방구석에서 <br>비트 찍구 랩을 하구 딸만 <br>잡구 린내 나는 놈들 씹구 <br>걸그룹에 곡 주는 꿈꾸구 <br>뻘짓 하구 나이만 처먹구 <br>야동 켜구 <br>aisaki reira <br>akiho yoshizawa <br>anna anjyo <br>iori kogawa <br>keiko koguchida <br>megumi shino <br>meguri <br>mikami aya <br>miki sunohara <br>momotani erika <br>nami aino <br>nana ninomiya <br>nao wakana <br>nozomi aso <br>ogura nana <br>satomi suzuki <br>sayuki kanno <br>tsukasa minami <br>yua mikami <br>지금 이 상태로 상승선 타면 <br>홍만이 형 보다 더 클 거 같아 <br>도끼보다 돈 더 벌 거 거 같아 <br>시미켄도 부럽지 않을 거 같아 <br>일류 뮤지션 될 거 같아 <br>아 나 존나 쌀 거 같아 <br>yo 2절은 전설이 되어 버린 클라스 <br>2절은 전설이 되어 버린 클라스 <br>akane hotaru <br>azusa nagasawa <br>io asuka <br>maki hojo <br>maria ozawa <br>nao oikawa <br>natsume nana <br>rio <br>sakura sakurada <br>tsubomi <br>yuma asami <br>sora aoi <br>보다 더 올라가면 <br>miai kobato <br>minori aoi <br>miyuki saori <br>missy <br>akari asagiri <br>ayana rei <br>ayano murasaki <br>ayumi isawa <br>kawakami yu <br>rei kitajima <br>reiko sawamura <br>yuki tsukamoto <br>yo <br>서양쪽 아시안도 있어 <br>evelyn lin <br>alina lee <br>meiko askara <br>meiko askara <br>그녀들께 감사를 표해 <br>엄마 몰래 우리들만의 세계 축제 <br>소년 청년들을 위한 신세계 <br>오빗이가 추천하는 av탑배우 <br>그 외에도 많아 대한민국 <br>딸잡이를 위한 힙합 <br>즐거운 딸문화를 위한 힙합 yo <br>현자 따윈 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="오빗" label="오빗"/><category term="오빗이가 추천하는 av배우" label="오빗이가 추천하는 av배우"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오빗/whats_up_yo_thats_no_no/</id><title>오빗 - what`s up yo that`s no no - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:16:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:16:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%97/whats_up_yo_thats_no_no/" title="오빗 - what`s up yo that`s no no - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[야이 xx놈년들아 <br>존나 x같이들 굴어 <br>x 같은 새끼들이 많어 <br>착한 나를 x나 긁어 <br>듣기만 해 싸우면 내가 지니까 <br>듣기만해 yo <br>yo yo a yo yo <br>verse 1 <br>요놈 새끼 오빗새끼 4년제 대학교 <br>갔네 비꼬아대던 친구새끼들 <br>순수 록커로 살기에 난 배짱이 좀 <br>부족했지 그 정도로 족하지 못했지 <br>싹 다 x깠지 반은 강제로 <br>학교 갔지 gg치고 짜졌지 <br>이젠 아냐 x같은 거 몇 개만 <br>말할게 이 xxxx들아 <br>행정처리하는 땡보들 <br>뭣들 하는 건지 먹고 놀자 공무원 <br>일처리들 x같고 돈 받고 <br>한다는 게 그 모양 <br>난 뭐 사실 잡종에 xx이라 <br>크게 상관 안해 근데 x도 <br>손가락만 놀려대는 꼬라지들 보고 <br>있노라면 나랑 다를 것도 없는 <br>존나 잘난 학우 여러분 <br>xx 이모들도 일 처리를 <br>그 따위론 하지 않아 <br>이 xxxx들아 <br>내가 수준 낮다고 x까지마 <br>니네 엄마보다 수준 높아 <br>괜한 노파심에 오지랖 떨지나 마 <br>컨닝 하다 x됐는데 x같은 <br>손가락 놀려대서 <br>두 번 조지니까 좋냐 xxx아 <br>괜찮아 너보다 잘 살거야 <br>나 이번에 졸업해 <br>what's up yo that's no no <br>프리톡으로 끌던 어그로 <br>현실에선 주둥이 여물어 <br>냄새나니 싸물어 시궁창내 개쩔어 <br>장담하지 보나마나 면상은 xxx이지 <br>벌어지는 xx 근데 아무도 안 꽂지 <br>내 말 맞지 아니라고 말 못하지 <br>맞다 해도 개구라지 xxxx 3대가 xxxx <br>나쁜 놈 아니오 <br>난 그렇게 xxx 아니오 <br>xxx을 xxx이라 부를 뿐이오 <br>이 xxx아 네 다음은 xxx <br>장난이고 지금 내가 말하는 거 xxxx <br>얼굴도 모르는 년이 <br>x같이 나를 찔러 <br>내가 너 평생 저주한다 <br>이 xxx아 <br>yo yo a yo verse 2 <br>요놈 새끼 오빗새끼 4년제 대학교 <br>갔네 비꼬아대던 친구새끼 <br>너같은 새끼가 뭐 배워갖고 <br>큰소리칠 거 생각하니까 어휴래 <br>괜찮아 그래봤자 노답이야 <br>여긴 헬조선이야 <br>배운 거 써먹을 때도 없어 <br>쓸 수 있는 건 노래와 <br>가사 그리고 xx뿐 <br>하 xx xx나 하고 싶다 <br>하나 더 있어 누구라고 말은 안해 <br>이 xx놈아 너 같은 xx 방송하면 안돼 <br>xxx가 존나 코스프레 xxx에 <br>정치질에 xx처럼 미묘하게 선동질 해 <br>우리민족끼리 들어가서 xxx해 그게 <br>너랑 잘 어울려 이 xxx야 <br>xx xx 족발에 xx찍어 뚝딱하던가 <br>xx xx 내 인생 따라다녀 <br>뭐 xx 내 음악이 x같다고 <br>x같은 건 내 음악 아냐 <br>니 얼굴이지 <br>빈 말 아냐 진심이야 xxx에 <br>왜 xx 안 꼈냐고 물어볼 뻔했잖아 <br>아 xx였지 xx크기 3mm 너네 아빤 <br>4mm 어머니는 1000mm 하핫 <br>한다는 건 televise 아니 <br>내가 하지 말랬지 이 xxxx <br>what's up yo that's no no <br>지가 근무하는 학교가 지잡대라던 <br>모 교수 교수형 당해도 모자랄 판에 <br>싹싹 빌어도 모자랄 판에 판만 x나 <br>키워놓고 휴가를 가네 <br>다시 학교 다니네 먹고는 살아야 <br>하네 대한민국은 학연 지연 <br>이게 문제야 xx <br>기타 <br>나의 랩은 일본야동 비웃어 <br>그러면서 알아서들 찾아 <br>한계 따윈 없어 외설로 <br>치부해도 진정 예술 <br>고도의 technic 카메라 예술 <br>술수 아닌 real xx는 필수 <br>횟수는 무한 청취 그 이상의 값어치 <br>흥분의 극치 끝이 없는 <br>xxx 목표는 xxx <br>부러워서 미치지 <br>뿌리 깊은 역사 항상 <br>존재했던 소비자 <br>그래서 또 생산 톱 배우의 탄생과 <br>김본좌 가라사대 <br>막지 못해 나 역시 그럼에도 부정 <br>억압과 탄압하면서 <br>듣지 보지 야동처럼 <br>빠져들수록 지옥계 <br>파고들수록 신세계 <br>실질적으로 xx를 <br>어디서 배웠나 생각해 <br>이 xxx들아 <br>]]></content><category term="오빗" label="오빗"/><category term="what`s up yo that`s no no" label="what`s up yo that`s no no"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오빗/달/</id><title>오빗 - 달 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:16:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:16:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%97/%EB%8B%AC/" title="오빗 - 달 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[얼마나 힘들었니 얼마나 괴로웠니 <br>매서운 바람보다도 <br>차가운 세상 앞에서 <br>얼마나 울고 싶었니 <br>얼마나 아파야 했니 <br>참고 참고 또 참아 <br>혼자 속 앓이 하고 <br>말 못할 아픔들을 가슴에 품고 <br>흘러야 할 눈물들을 흘리지 않고 <br>차가운 시선들을 체념한 채로 <br>모든 걸 감춘 채로 <br>왜 웃고 있었니 <br>사랑보다 더 아픈 건 <br>어둠보다 어두운 어둠이라고 <br>그보다도 어두운 어둠 속에서 <br>어지러이 흔들리며 <br>빛을 찾고 있던 그대 모습을 봤어 <br>울지 마라 울지 마라 되새기면서 <br>속으로는 대성통곡한 그 소릴 들었어 <br>떨어지는 별보다 더 멀리 <br>떨어지는 그 별을 보았어 <br>밝은 세상은 나를 <br>욕 할거야 모욕할 거야 <br>비가 와서 모든 게 <br>다 씻겨진다 한들 <br>검게 물든 내 마음도 씼겨질까 <br>밝은 척 한 이 어두움이 밝아질까 <br>눈 앞에서 사라지는 <br>담배 연기를 보면 <br>아무도 없는 가로수 불빛을 보면 <br>혼자 뜬 달을 나 혼자 <br>계속 보고 있으면 <br>네 생각이 나 어떻게 웃고 있었니 <br>이별보다 더 슬픈 건 <br>그리움 사무치는 그리움이라고 <br>그 보다 더 그리운 그때 <br>웃어야지 웃어야지 되새기면서 <br>속으로는 울고 있는 그 표정을 봤어 <br>밝게 뜬 달의 뒤 표면은 <br>어둡다던데 몹시도 춥다 하던데 <br>]]></content><category term="오빗" label="오빗"/><category term="달" label="달"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오빗/한_소녀의_이야기/</id><title>오빗 - 한 소녀의 이야기 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:16:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:16:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%97/%ED%95%9C_%EC%86%8C%EB%85%80%EC%9D%98_%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC%EA%B8%B0/" title="오빗 - 한 소녀의 이야기 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[버티고 나아가도 슬프기만 <br>어둡기만 한 소녀의 이야기 <br>시련이 시련인줄도 모른 채 <br>살았었던 한 소녀의 이야기 <br>아버지의 폭력 속에서 <br>열 다섯 살에 어머니를 <br>여의고 몸과 마음에 <br>멍이 든 채 살다가 <br>하루가 하루가 두려워 <br>학교를 나와 집에서 도망쳐 <br>추위의 거리를 떠돌고 떠돌다 <br>아무도 없는 상가 안에서 <br>어느 남자가 다가와 <br>갈 곳이 없냐며 쉴 곳을 대준대 <br>차가운 방에서 순결을 빼앗겨 <br>한없이 울다가 <br>그렇게 그렇게 살아가 <br>어느새 소녀는 열 일곱 살 <br>아니야 스무살이라고 <br>거짓말을 하고 <br>화장을 하고 염색을 하고 <br>짧은 치마를 입고 <br>향수를 뿌리고 동화 속 신데렐라 <br>술을 따라 노래를 불러 술에 취해 <br>처음 본 남자에 기대어 웃음을 팔아 <br>그렇게 그렇게 살아가 힘든 게 <br>힘든 건지도 모른 채 그렇게 <br>그렇게 흘러가 <br>버티고 나아가도 슬프기만 <br>어둡기만 한 소녀의 이야기 <br>시련이 시련인줄도 모른 채 <br>살았었던 한 소녀의 이야기 <br>버티고 나아가도 슬프기만 <br>어둡기만 한 소녀의 이야기 <br>시련이 시련인줄도 모른 채 <br>살았었던 한 소녀의 이야기 <br>열 여덟 살이 된 소녀에게도 <br>사랑이 찾아와 첫사랑의 시작 <br>꼬마신랑 아니 꼬마건달 <br>서로의 보호관찰 세상의 장난 <br>위험한 사랑 <br>소녀 입의 담배에 불이 붙듯 모든 <br>걸 태워 그만큼 모든 게 <br>서툴고 뒤틀려 <br>다 타버리고 이뤄지지 못한 채 <br>상처 만 가득히 끝난 사랑 <br>너무도 거센 파도 드센 운명 <br>매일이 술에 취해 소녀는 고달파 <br>정신도 못 차릴 만큼 걸어온 길을 <br>돌아봐 돌아갈 곳도 없어 <br>어김없이 아침이 오고 차들은 달려 <br>소녀는 취해 비틀거려 <br>좀 전까지 함께 있던 남잔 없어 <br>소녀가 살던 세상도 없어 <br>하늘에선 비가 오고 빗물들은 피에 <br>젖어 소녀는 붉게 물들어 <br>이제 더는 아프지 않아도 돼 <br>기대지 않아도 돼 울지 않아도 돼 <br>하늘에선 비가 오고 빗물들은 피에 <br>젖어 소녀는 붉게 물들어 <br>이제 더는 아프지 않아도 돼 <br>기대지 않아도 돼 울지 않아도 돼 <br>버티고 나아가도 슬프기만 <br>어둡기만 한 소녀의 이야기 <br>시련이 시련인줄도 모른 채 <br>살았었던 한 소녀의 이야기 <br>버티고 나아가도 슬프기만 <br>어둡기만 한 소녀의 이야기 <br>시련이 시련인줄도 모른 채 <br>살았었던 한 소녀의 이야기 <br>]]></content><category term="오빗" label="오빗"/><category term="한 소녀의 이야기" label="한 소녀의 이야기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오빗/씹새끼/</id><title>오빗 - 씹새끼 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:16:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:16:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%97/%EC%94%B9%EC%83%88%EB%81%BC/" title="오빗 - 씹새끼 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 얼마나 <br>양아치가 될 수 있는지 <br>알게 해준 씹새끼 <br>랩으로 존나 팬다 <br>진짜 패면 안돼 <br>좆돼 내가 져 <br>이러쿵 저러쿵 말 많아 <br>불만만 요란한 빈 깡통 <br>여기저기 들쑤셔 <br>물 흐리기 물타기 <br>분탕질 씹새끼 <br>뭐 그런 새끼가 다 있나 <br>입 털다 걸리면 아가리 닥치고 <br>수행에 들어가 정치인 납셨다 <br>욕구불만 고추가 작아서 그런가 <br>청렴한 척 놀아나던 씹새끼 <br>돈 가지고 장난치던 씹새끼 <br>뒤통수나 갈겨대던 씹새끼 <br>뒤에서는 교수 씹던 씹새끼 <br>실 없는 소리 여기 저기 <br>진실은 저기 멀리 <br>박쥐 같은 무리 <br>속은 항상 구리 <br>mother fuckin <br>속이 썩힌 시궁창 버러지 <br>사실 속엔 진실 그 속에선 가식 <br>개념머리 상실 아닌 순실 <br>명실상부 씹새끼 <br>손바닥으로 하늘을 가려 <br>변명도 아닌 그냥 말을 바꿔 <br>어디서 배워 쳐먹은 정치놀이 <br>sextep 3절에 나온 그 씹새끼 <br>좆같은 건 개 같은 건 <br>빵셔틀 면상하고 <br>정일이를 따라하네 <br>뭐라도 되는 마냥 <br>김양이건 이양이건 <br>되는대로 보빨하다 <br>아니다 싶으면 나가리냐 <br>그런 싸가지는 어디서 배웠더냐 <br>아버지 안 계시냐 <br>올바른 척은 다 하고서 <br>지 돈도 아닌 걸로 장난질 <br>누가 뭐 좀 한다 싶음 방해질 <br>정보랍시고 퍼나르는 찌라시 <br>그런 걸로 선동질 <br>대통령 욕하면서 <br>대통령 따라하던 <br>씹새끼 개새끼 호로새끼 <br>실 없는 소리 여기 저기 <br>진실은 저기 멀리 <br>박쥐 같은 무리 <br>속은 항상 구리 <br>mother fuckin <br>속이 썩힌 시궁창 버러지 <br>사실 속엔 진실 그 속에선 가식 <br>개념머리 상실 아닌 순실 <br>명실상부 씹새끼 <br>]]></content><category term="오빗" label="오빗"/><category term="씹새끼" label="씹새끼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오빗/연산군/</id><title>오빗 - 연산군 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:16:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:16:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%97/%EC%97%B0%EC%82%B0%EA%B5%B0/" title="오빗 - 연산군 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너넨 날 못 이겨 <br>운명은 정해져 <br>태어날 때부터 확실히 말해둬 <br>잘난 척 있는 척 해 봤자 <br>두뇌는 원정녀 <br>일상이 가식적 <br>다 알어 왜 찔려 <br>요새는 야동도 중국산이 판을 쳐 <br>문제는 국산이라 속여 팔어 <br>때론 에로도 노모라고 속여 팔어 <br>어떤 새낀 짜집기로 묶어 팔어 <br>솎으고 솎아도 <br>그런 새낀 늘 있어 yo <br>늘 항상 가십질 앞에선 <br>쪼개고 뒤에선 까대고 <br>생각 없는 손가락 <br>라면에 손가락 짤라 넣고 <br>같이 먹어 허잇 같이 먹어 <br>먹다 뒤져도 이간질이 재밌어 <br>썩은 내장이랑 아가리가 다 보여 <br>어떻게 아무렇지가 않어 <br>그럴 수가 있어 <br>그래서 또 그렇게 <br>삽질하고 있는 거 <br>계산기 좀 바꿔 <br>yo <br>배경이 바껴도 <br>천성은 잘 안 바껴 <br>올드보이급의 고통 없이는 <br>대다수가 돈 가지고 장난질 <br>계급 달고 꼰대질 <br>인력거급 택시질 <br>평생 그냥 양아치 <br>하면 생각나는 폰팔이 <br>쌍년들은 죠리퐁 <br>테트리스 xxx <br>그러고들 사는 거지 <br>그래 난 적이 많어 <br>덕분에 늘 뒤가 구려 <br>뒷구멍 빨아대던 <br>임숭재들 어디 갔어 <br>난 연산군이 되어 있어 <br>그럼 이제 판 넓혀서 칭기즈칸 <br>뒤집어도 시라소니 <br>어쩌면 이 씬이 더 순수하지 <br>무식하게 music 밖에 모르는 <br>병신들만 모였으니 <br>그리 생각하던 나도 병신이지 <br>어딜 가도 사짜들은 숨어있지 <br>여기 저기 위아래로 <br>날 좋아하던 형아는 <br>날 동생 아닌 동네 잡배취급 <br>판 돌리는 바닥도 뭐 양아치굴 <br>최소 은수저라 학교에서 <br>꿀 빨면서 예술 하던 학도들은 <br>창작 아닌 과제 노예마냥 <br>상대 평가를 당연하게 받들이고 <br>플러스를 받기 위해 <br>교수님께 싸바 싸바 <br>중졸 고졸 새끼들이 <br>실력이 더 뛰어나도 <br>이사회는 A플러스 성적표를 <br>더 쳐주지랄 같네 <br>바꿔야 해 말들 해도 말뿐이지 <br>책을 많이 보는 <br>김박사는 장님이지 <br>내가 개 병신인 거 인정한다 <br>키도 작고 거지에다 찌질하다 <br>그래서 뭐 <br>돈 주고도 했다 <br>연예인만 불쌍하다 <br>깔 테면 다 까라지들 <br>근데 음악으론 아무도 날 못 까 <br>연기로 치면 이병헌 급 <br>좆으로 보나 보지로 보나 <br>너넨 날 못 이겨 <br>]]></content><category term="오빗" label="오빗"/><category term="연산군" label="연산군"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오빗/한_恨/</id><title>오빗 - 한 (恨) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:16:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:16:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%97/%ED%95%9C_%E6%81%A8/" title="오빗 - 한 (恨) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[빛이 없는 어둠 속에서 <br>두려움 속에서 혼자서 싸워 <br>형체가 없는 상대 <br>그래 내 상대는 없어 <br>아무도 없어 <br>내 안에서 일어났던 <br>전쟁과 테러 <br>그 속에서 승리를 하고 나니 <br>왼쪽 가슴과 어깨 <br>허리의 부상은 <br>정신과를 가보라는 <br>의사의 말이 됐네 <br>아무런 의미 없네 <br>아무렇지 않다네 <br>그냥 내 길을 가네 <br>내 mental은 원래부터 <br>칼침으로 들쑤셔져 있었다네 <br>피해를 원해 <br>피해를 준 그들에게 <br>용서를 구한다는 <br>얕은 말도 할 수 없음에 <br>또 용서를 구해 <br>파괴를 파괴하고 <br>파괴 받고 나서야 <br>비로소 나를 찾네 <br>그 속에서 꽃이 폈네 <br>살랑 살랑 불어오던 봄바람에도 <br>심한 흔들림에 <br>비틀대던 내 감정은 <br>폭풍에도 끄떡 없는 <br>뿌리 깊은 나무가 돼 날아가네 <br>민들레 꽃씨처럼 사라지네 <br>겸손 앞에선 더 겸손하네 <br>교만 앞에선 더 교만하네 <br>그동안에 만난 적들과 아군 <br>모두에게 감사하네 <br>미치지 않고선 미침을 모르니 <br>365일 미쳐있네 <br>지치고 지쳐 <br>흘리지 못한 눈물조차 증발되고 <br>비가 되어 다시 또 쏟아지듯 <br>혼이 없는 누군가에 말을 하듯 <br>나의 한을 계속해서 풀어가네 <br>지나간 것들을 잡으려 <br>발버둥 쳤네 <br>절대 손에 잡히지 않네 <br>흩날리네 이젠 없네 <br>그런 나는 없네 <br>형체가 없는 시체가 돼 <br>지금의 내가 있네 <br>yo <br>혼자 악과 독에 빠져 허우적 <br>그건 이미 오래 전 <br>너무나도 철학적 형태의 선율은 <br>학문적 탐구가 아닌 <br>그 이상의 목적 진화의 흔적 <br>그리고 나를 표적으로 한 <br>사방이 적 <br>시간을 거스른 위험한 여행은 <br>현실과 동떨어진 이상을 만들어 <br>날 벼랑 끝으로 몰아 <br>utopia를 찾으려 <br>애초에 없던 걸 <br>대체 왜 찾으려 <br>모든 걸 짓밟고 <br>이기는 법을 알려주신 <br>당신을 세상에서 <br>제일 원망하고 미워해 <br>동시에 존경심과 <br>경외함을 느끼네 <br>극과 극으로 치닫는 감정은 <br>늘 혼란에 빠지네 <br>집을 나간 어머니를 <br>이해함과 동시에 <br>사무치게 그리워 한 아이는 <br>몸과 마음이 자라지 못한 채 <br>기괴해진 영혼을 안고 <br>엄마 품에 안겨있네 <br>거짓으로 웃고 있네 <br>나를 감춰 모든 걸 감춰 <br>비트 위에서 춤을 췄던 <br>그녀들과 미친 세상을 등져 <br>모두가 스쳐가고 <br>끝이 없는 타락 속에서도 <br>never die 이젠 웃는다 <br>this is the 첫 번째 mixtape <br>major를 지향하는 minor type <br>scene의 두뇌 진입 개입한 사람 die <br>only my music scene에 가입 <br>순간을 전부다 기입 <br>좌익 우익 할 거 없이 <br>흡수통일 <br>언어유희의 한계를 넘어선 <br>언어유희 <br>시간이 갈수록 엇갈리는 <br>너와 나의 희비 <br>괴리를 느껴도 어쩔 수 없는 <br>너와 나의 차이 <br>겸손 앞에선 더 겸손하네 <br>교만 앞에선 더 교만하네 <br>그동안에 만난 적들과 아군 <br>모두에게 감사하네 <br>미치지 않고선 미침을 모르니 <br>365일 미쳐있네 <br>지치고 지쳐 흘리지 못한 <br>눈물조차 증발되고 <br>비가 되어 다시 또 쏟아지듯 <br>혼이 없는 누군가에 말을 하듯 <br>나의 한을 계속해서 풀어가네 <br>]]></content><category term="오빗" label="오빗"/><category term="한 (恨)" label="한 (恨)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오빗/0/</id><title>오빗 - 0 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:16:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:16:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%97/0/" title="오빗 - 0 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오래 전 이미 장인의 경지 <br>멈춰있지 말고 던져 주사위 <br>부수지 못한 인지부조화 <br>또 다른 세계.. <br><br>hybrid is classic <br>피우지 못한 비운의 명작 <br>허튼 수작 아닌 수작 <br>절대 사라지지 않는 소멸된 듯 해도 평생 살아나는 성기의 성욕과도 같지 <br>노가다를 해도 난 안해 삽질 <br>뒤에서 펼쳐진 공작질 <br>커튼 쳐도 보이는 경치 <br>잘 나봐야 후진 건 unchanged <br><br>고통도 없고 쾌락도 없이 <br>さすが 안전빵 전부 쌤쌤 <br>싹 다 모자이크 답답 뒤에선 칼 꽂기 <br>고작 한다는 게? 피식 유치 정치질 <br>혀로 난도질 나의 등은 이미 낡아빠진 (다트판) <br>절로 맞춰지는 퍼즐 <br>어릴 적 두 번 봤던 살인 직전 <br>그럼에도 절대 쓰러지지 않고 <br>자 버티잖아 <br>dirty 속에서 beauty하잖아 <br>무너지지 않아 <br>redline 따윈 zero zero zero zero <br>동네 짜바리정도 조작은 easy <br>원래 없던 것처럼 수 없이 많이 사라진 <br>자본주의 앞에 무릎 꿇린 <br>자본주의 욕해도 난 돈이 좋아 <br>자연스레 생겨난 건 사라지지 않아 <br><br>뭐 이 씨발 말들만 존나 잘해 <br>죄다 정치질 토나와 병신들 <br>똥구멍에 혀 처박고 다 보는데 しゃくはち <br>좆들 까세요 니미씹 <br>개나 소나 하는 거 같지 그래 맞지 <br>허접들도 뭐 좀 한다 까불지 깝치지 말지어다 <br>쉽게 보지 말지어다 친다 그럼 넌 다친다 <br>그러니 닥치거라 <br><br>私は韓?人です 섰어 <br>下半身は pro-Japanese <br>이 판 다 뒤집어 uppercut을 날려 <br>あの 랩으로 나의 랩으로 <br>비트 없이도 かんじ いちろう <br>모두 제 위치로 때가 되면 여기로 <br>これは どろの なかの しんじゅ <br>それは にせの なかに 本物 <br>本?に すばらしい <br><br>ありがとう할 거 없어 <br>やめて는 개구라 <br>전부다가 きもち <br>나랏 말 바꿔해도 <br>남잔 다 알아듣지 <br>진짠 알아보겠지 <br>겨울에도 꽃은 피겠지 <br><br>10빼기 10은 zero <br>히로시마 원자폭탄 <br>한반도의 핵미사일 <br>scene의 super virus <br>이미 초토화 <br>zero zero zero zero <br><br>뭐 이 씨발 말들만 존나 잘해 <br>죄다 정치질 토나와 병신들 <br>똥구멍에 혀 처박고 다 보는데 しゃくはち <br>좆들 까세요 니미씹 <br>개나 소나 하는 거 같지 그래 맞지 <br>허접들도 뭐 좀 한다 까불지 깝치지 말지어다 <br>쉽게 보지 말지어다 친다 그럼 넌 다친다 <br>그러니 닥치거라 <br>? ほんとう]]></content><category term="오빗" label="오빗"/><category term="0" label="0"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/꼬마견/넌_거기_있어/</id><title>꼬마견 - 넌 거기 있어 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:16:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:16:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%BC%AC%EB%A7%88%EA%B2%AC/%EB%84%8C_%EA%B1%B0%EA%B8%B0_%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4/" title="꼬마견 - 넌 거기 있어 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너무 마음 쓰지도마 <br>주지 않아도 돼 사랑 <br>내가 더더 많이 줄게 <br>나 때문에 아파하지도 마 <br>나 때문에 눈물 흘리지도 마 <br>그냥 내가 더 사랑할게 <br>바람필 걱정하지도 마 <br>너 아닌 여잔 내 눈엔 그냥 사람 <br>생일 기념일 모두 챙기지도 마 <br>내가 다 챙겨줄게 <br>난 안받아도 돼 <br>너만 행복하게 해줄게 <br>연락 오지 않는다고 <br>신경 쓸 필요 없어 <br>1분 1초 다 너만 생각하니까 <br>식사 시간엔 밥은 제때 먹고 있나 <br>지나가다 꽃이 보여도 너가 생각나 <br>좋은 노래 소리 들리면 함께 듣고파 <br>잠자리 들 때면 옆에 너가 있고파 <br>나에게 하루밖에 없다면 <br>그 하루를 너에게 쓰고 싶어 <br>빛을 밝힐 필요 없어 <br>너로 인해 내 삶은 밝게 빛나니까 <br>성숙하지 못한 나를 더 <br>성숙하게 만드는 너 <br>내 삶의 모든 건 <br>다 너를 위한 삶 <br>그 자리에 너는 그냥 있어줘 <br>내가 너의 곁으로 갈 테니 <br>넌 거기 있어 <br>내가 갈 테니 <br>하나 둘 나이 먹어가니까 <br>사랑이란 걸 이제야 느껴 <br>그게 너라서 다행이야 <br>너 you <br>너의 웃는 모습에 <br>내 마음은 배불러 <br>피곤하다며 옆에 기대어 <br>눈감은 너의 꿈속에 <br>들어가 24시간 함께 하고파 <br>있고파 너의 맘속에 <br>너의 거짓말도 난 <br>진실로 믿어 <br>부드러운 살결 <br>부터 너의 촉촉한 입술까지 <br>하나하나 소중해 <br>너를 위한 난 정신이상자 <br>꽂혔어 너란 존재에 <br>너가 행복했으면 좋겠어 <br>너의 웃음소리 <br>듣고파 <br>나로 인해 아파하는 날들 없게 <br>내가 더 잘 할게 <br>넌 그냥 받기만 해 <br>내 모든걸 다 <br>신경 쓰지마 <br>내가 다 해결해줄게 <br>웃을 일만 남아 <br>아픔 따윈 없게 <br>노력할게 <br>앞으로 더더 사랑 가득 <br>웃음 가득 행복 가득 <br>가득가득 갖고 너에게로 갈게 <br>식사 시간엔 밥은 제때 먹고 있나 <br>지나가다 꽃이 보여도 너가 생각나 <br>좋은 노래 소리 들리면 함께 듣고파 <br>잠자리 들 때면 옆에 너가 있고파 <br>그 자리에 너는 그냥 있어줘 <br>내가 너의 곁으로 갈 테니 <br>넌 거기 있어 <br>내가 갈 테니 <br>]]></content><category term="꼬마견" label="꼬마견"/><category term="넌 거기 있어" label="넌 거기 있어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hey_Rosetta/New_Year_Song/</id><title>Hey Rosetta! - New Year Song - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:20:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:20:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hey_Rosetta/New_Year_Song/" title="Hey Rosetta! - New Year Song - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lend me your walking stick <br>And I lean on it <br>And I walk on out through the snow bound yard <br>Past the neighbours on the lawn <br>Drinking last year out <br>I leave this town, cut the year off clear <br>Cauterized by leaving <br>Sick and tired of living last year <br>Roll out the tarmac and baptize the air craft <br>Escaping loss and push me off <br><br>The cold can bleach us out <br>And freeze our doubt <br>And all that you knew becomes muffled and mute <br>But I'm done with it <br>All this standing stiff <br>When I move my mouth only snow comes out <br>Euthanized by whiteness <br>But I'll arise despite this last year <br>So roll out the tarmac and baptize the aircraft <br>Escaping loss and push me off <br><br>Should old acquaintance be forgot <br>And never brought to mind <br>Should acquaintance be forgot <br>And auld lang syne <br>For auld lang syne, my dear <br>For auld lang syne <br>We'll take a cup of kindness yet <br>For auld lang syne <br><br>For auld lang syne, my dear <br>For auld lang syne <br>We'll take a cup of kindness yet <br>For auld lang syne <br>x2]]></content><category term="Hey Rosetta!" label="Hey Rosetta!"/><category term="New Year Song" label="New Year Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hey_Rosetta/The_First_Snow/</id><title>Hey Rosetta! - The First Snow - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:20:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:20:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hey_Rosetta/The_First_Snow/" title="Hey Rosetta! - The First Snow - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Things are dying <br>The summer's gone <br>You spend half your night off <br>On the phone <br>Pacing around <br>You're gonna wear a rut <br>Trying to make her understand <br>What you do not <br>Then you hang up <br>So quiet <br>And you look out <br>Into the cold night <br><br>You're getting older <br>But you still never learn <br>It's like you're frozen <br>In a frozen world <br>But then you feel it <br>The stillness moves <br>It's like a tiny voice <br>In a silent room <br><br>The first snow <br>The first snow <br>So slow <br>The first snow <br><br>Then you know it <br>The thing you've never known <br>That you won't outgrow it <br>But she'll move along <br>Into your bed <br>You lie alone <br>But you'll be fine dreaming <br>Of the first snow <br><br>The first snow <br>The first snow <br>Feel it flow <br>Like the first snow]]></content><category term="Hey Rosetta!" label="Hey Rosetta!"/><category term="The First Snow" label="The First Snow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hey_Rosetta/O_Come_O_Come_Emmanuel/</id><title>Hey Rosetta! - O Come O Come Emmanuel - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:20:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:20:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hey_Rosetta/O_Come_O_Come_Emmanuel/" title="Hey Rosetta! - O Come O Come Emmanuel - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[o come o come emmanuel <br>and ransom captive israel <br>that mourns in lowly exile here <br><br>until the sun of god appear <br><br>rejoice rejoice <br>emmanuel shall come to thee <br>o israel <br><br>o come thou rod of jesse, free <br>thine own from satan's tyranny <br>from the depths of hell thy people save <br>and give them victory o'er the grave <br><br>rejoice rejoice <br><br>o come thou dayspring, come and cheer <br>our spirits by thine advent here <br>and drive away the shades of night <br>pierce the clouds and bring us light <br><br>rejoice rejoice]]></content><category term="Hey Rosetta!" label="Hey Rosetta!"/><category term="O Come O Come Emmanuel" label="O Come O Come Emmanuel"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hey_Rosetta/Carry_Me_Home/</id><title>Hey Rosetta! - Carry Me Home - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:20:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:20:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hey_Rosetta/Carry_Me_Home/" title="Hey Rosetta! - Carry Me Home - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This hotel is cheap <br>And the pillows stink <br>And there's not a single thing <br>To say it's Christmas Eve <br>Oh Saint Nicholas <br>I know I ain't in your list <br>But if you're listening <br>I need a bus ticket <br>I came through Montreal <br>I lost a lot of dough <br>Could find no honest job <br>So I did some other ones <br>Got into trouble and <br>I had to run or suffer <br>And then a long road <br>Into a long December <br><br>Over the water and <br>Over the border and <br>Over the open land <br>To this Ramada Inn <br>No overbooking here <br>No sort of holy birth <br>No miracles occurring <br>No not a creature stirring <br>Oh Saint Stephen <br>Where is your feast when I <br>When I so sorely need it <br>When I haven't hardly eaten <br>But I'd give my food and drink <br>To see my home again <br>To see my mother's hand <br>Against her apron edge <br><br>Oh <br>Oh <br>Oh x2 <br><br>Oh Saint Christopher <br>Send me a Christian word <br>Send me a southern wind <br>Oh send me up to my kin <br>Hear the boys singing <br>Through their drunken grinning <br>Of Jesus, Joseph, Mary <br>I hear their voices carry <br><br>Carry me home <br>Home <br>Home x2 <br><br>Can any saints hear me <br>Is there any angel near me <br>If you won't lift me up <br>Then would you send my love <br>Back to my home <br>Back to my only shelter <br>Where in the awful weather <br>I will be warm and welcome <br><br>Back to my home <br>Home <br>Home]]></content><category term="Hey Rosetta!" label="Hey Rosetta!"/><category term="Carry Me Home" label="Carry Me Home"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Motorleague/We_Are_Chemical/</id><title>The Motorleague - We Are Chemical - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:21:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:21:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Motorleague/We_Are_Chemical/" title="The Motorleague - We Are Chemical - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been searching for clarity <br>Why is it so hard to find <br>It's the words I can't say <br>It's the price I will pay but <br>Maybe it's all in my mind <br><br>Now it's time to set you free <br>I can never let go <br>It's the choice I can't make <br>It's the vice I can't break but <br>I guess I'll never know <br><br>We are chemical <br>Cancelling each other out <br>We are variables <br>We are lost within ourselves <br>We are chemical <br>Cancelling each other out <br>We are chemical <br><br>I've been digging a shallow grave <br>It's so hard to cut through <br>It's the sounds of the weak that we don't like to speak but <br>They mean something to you <br><br>And I've been trying to cut you off <br>I can't see through the pain <br>Suffice it to say it won't be today 'cause <br>I'll do it again <br><br>We are chemical <br>Cancelling each other out <br>We are variables <br>We are lost within ourselves <br>We are chemical <br>Cancelling each other out <br>We are chemical <br><br>And I've got substance in my veins <br>I won't let anything go <br><br>And I've got substance in my veins <br>I can't let anything escape <br>And I've got substance in my veins <br>I can't let anything go <br><br>And I've got substance in my veins <br>I can't let anything escape <br>And I've got substance in my veins <br>I can't let anything go <br><br>We are chemical <br>Cancelling each other out <br>We are variables <br>We are lost within ourselves <br>We are chemical <br>Cancelling each other out <br>We are variables <br>We are lost within ourselves <br><br>We are chemical <br>We are chemical <br>We are chemical <br>We are chemical]]></content><category term="The Motorleague" label="The Motorleague"/><category term="We Are Chemical" label="We Are Chemical"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김태민/묻지마라/</id><title>김태민 - 묻지마라 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:23:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:23:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%83%9C%EB%AF%BC/%EB%AC%BB%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88%EB%9D%BC/" title="김태민 - 묻지마라 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 사느냐고 묻지 마라 <br>묻지 마라 묻지를 마라 <br>살다가 보면 좋은 날도 <br>웃는 날도 오지 않겠소 <br>사는 게 모두가 그렇지 <br>그렇고 그런 거지 <br>그리우면 그리운 대로 <br>서러우면 서러운 대로 <br>한번 가면 다시는 없을 <br>우리 삶은 축복인 거야 <br>가끔은 삶의 무게가 <br>무거워 힘이 들어도 <br>인생이란 다 그런 거야 <br>인생이란 다 그런 거야 <br>왜 사느냐고 묻지 마라 <br>묻지 마라 묻지를 마라 <br>살다가 보면 좋은 날도 <br>웃는 날도 오지 않겠소 <br>사는 게 모두가 그렇지 <br>그렇고 그런 거지 <br>그리우면 그리운 대로 <br>서러우면 서러운 대로 <br>한번 가면 다시는 없을 <br>우리 삶은 축복인 거야 <br>가끔은 삶의 무게가 <br>무거워 힘이 들어도 <br>인생이란 다 그런 거야 <br>인생이란 다 그런 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="김태민" label="김태민"/><category term="묻지마라" label="묻지마라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아이동요/바닷속에는/</id><title>아이동요 - 바닷속에는 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:23:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:23:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%B7%EC%86%8D%EC%97%90%EB%8A%94/" title="아이동요 - 바닷속에는 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바닷속에는 무엇이 있을까 <br>정말로 궁금해 <br>무서운 상어 덩치 큰 고래 <br>수많은 물고기 <br><br>물개도 있고 펭귄도 있고 <br>물고기 정말 많아요 <br>산호도 있고 말미잘 있고 <br>거북이도 있죠 <br><br>바닷속에는 무엇이 있을까 <br>정말로 신기해 <br>다 봤으면 좋겠다 <br>꿈에 나타나라]]></content><category term="아이동요" label="아이동요"/><category term="바닷속에는" label="바닷속에는"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DID/I_Meant_To_Hurt_You/</id><title>D.I.D - I Meant To Hurt You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:23:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:23:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DID/I_Meant_To_Hurt_You/" title="D.I.D - I Meant To Hurt You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You head straight for the drug you love <br>Now I can barely breathe, I really need you <br><br>I guess all we had were trips and way <br>And birthday celebration barbeques <br><br>You can't condemn the town you're from <br>The life you're born into, your neighbourhood <br><br>'Cause somewhere there's a beating heart <br>That needs to prove it's just misunderstood <br><br>And you breathe in, and you breathe out <br>Theres an off white little lie I made about you <br>That I meant to hurt you, I meant to hurt you <br><br>I gotta call time, guess it's better to dive in the deep end sometimes <br>Oh I gotta let you go, oh I gotta let you go now <br><br>Call time, yes its easier to hide in the darkness sometimes <br>Oh I gotta take control, oh I gotta let you go now <br><br>I know it's bad to open yourself up this much to girls from posh schools <br>Still, somehow I convince myself the time is better spent alone with you <br><br>And you breathe in, and you breathe out <br>There's an off white little lie I made about you <br>That I meant to hurt you, I meant to hurt you <br><br>I gotta call time, guess it's better to dive in the deep end sometimes <br>Oh I gotta let you go, oh I gotta let you go now <br><br>Call time, yeah its easier to hide in the darkness sometimes <br>Oh I gotta take control, oh I gotta let you go now <br><br>I wouldn't waste a breath on you <br>'Cause I meant <br>I meant to hurt you <br><br>I wouldn't waste a breath on you <br>Even if you asked me to <br>I meant to hurt you <br><br>I wouldn't waste a breath on you <br>'Cause I meant <br>I meant to hurt you <br><br>I wouldn't waste a breath on you <br>Even if you asked me to <br>I meant to hurt you <br><br>Cold time, guess it's better to dive in the deep end sometimes <br>I wouldn't waste a breath on you <br>'Cause I meant <br>'Cause I meant to hurt you <br><br>Cold time, yeah its easier to hide in the darkness sometimes <br>I wouldn't waste a breath on you <br>Even if you asked me to <br>'Cause I meant to hurt you]]></content><category term="D.I.D" label="D.I.D"/><category term="I Meant To Hurt You" label="I Meant To Hurt You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DID/Gameplan/</id><title>D.I.D - Gameplan - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:23:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:23:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DID/Gameplan/" title="D.I.D - Gameplan - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You caught me on my own again <br>Like I'd never been so lonely <br>I never want to be that man <br><br>Did I ask you for the compliments <br>Or even for the room key <br>I find that hard to comprehend <br>We can make another phone call home <br>We can make another time <br>And on <br>And on <br>Love me at your wildest <br>Cut me out the picture <br>Like you never felt so stylish <br>By the time it takes to write this <br>I'll be like a stranger <br>Love me at your wildest <br>What's the gameplan hun <br>What's your gameplan <br>And you can take my photograph <br>But it isn't <br>You find that hard to understand <br>I've given you your oxygen <br>But now I need the closure <br>I think we need a concrete plan <br>And I take more than the long walk home <br>To get you off my mind <br>And on <br>And on <br>Love me at your wildest <br>Cut me out the picture <br>Like you never felt so stylish <br>By the time it takes to write this <br>I'll be like a stranger <br>Love me at your wildest <br>I know this isn't crazy <br>I'm never giving up the game <br>What's the gameplan hun <br>What's the gameplan hun <br>What's your gameplan hun <br>What's the gameplan hun <br>What's your gameplan hun <br>What's your gameplan hun]]></content><category term="D.I.D" label="D.I.D"/><category term="Gameplan" label="Gameplan"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DID/Flush/</id><title>D.I.D - Flush - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:23:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:23:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DID/Flush/" title="D.I.D - Flush - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Honey there's an exit sign, flickerin', oceans apart <br>We're as far as it gets from a breathrough <br>And I'll be hittin' bars while you're learning lines, hoping you'll save me from somebody else I can get to <br>They say that, another fracture, go ahead and plaster up, this is heavywieght, this is heavyweight <br>They say that, love is raptured, someone goes and pulls the plug, this is heavywieght any way you look at it <br><br>How you keeping <br>How you keeping <br>'Cause I can flush you out of my head <br>How's your week been <br>I can shake it <br>And I can flush you out of my head <br><br>Honey there were warning signs <br>I still feel like its away from the boy that you met when we first moved <br>A polyester neon moon, shinin' through, I wish you'd stay for a while, wish you'd stay for a while <br>After you, hold me for ransom and intend to rip me up, I'm as heavyweight, as heavyweight <br><br>How you keeping <br>How you keeping <br>'Cause I can flush you out of my head <br>How's your week been <br>I can shake it <br>And I can flush you out of my head <br><br>And I can flush you out <br>Oooh Oooh <br>I can flush you out <br>Oooh Oooh x5 <br><br>How you keeping <br>How you keeping <br>'Cause I can flush you out of my head <br>How's your week been <br>I can shake it <br>And I can flush you out of my head <br>And I can flush you out <br>Oooh Oooh <br>I can flush you out <br>Oooh Oooh x3]]></content><category term="D.I.D" label="D.I.D"/><category term="Flush" label="Flush"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DID/Hotel/</id><title>D.I.D - Hotel - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:23:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:23:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DID/Hotel/" title="D.I.D - Hotel - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh my look at yourself <br>You know you're ruined from the bottom and up <br>No hard feelings at all <br>We only loved you for your loose change <br>We're just <br>Skin, bones and regular clothes <br>But I suggest you keep your distance <br>Eighteen <br>The devil and me <br>It's just a pipe dream but a temptress <br>Her face is a mirror <br>And doing what we know and love <br>Never fails to let us down <br>Solitude arrives like a guest in a hotel <br>When she ups and leaves for the devil in the detail <br>Run, child <br>Move it along <br>And be eager to get up and ahead <br>One class <br>See it here in stone <br>I'd say I'm nothing to look up to <br>Black tie <br>City at night <br>I need the money then I'm out of your hair <br>Drunk fight <br>Left of the line <br>And I can run if I get desperate <br>Her face is a mirror <br>And doing what we know and love <br>Never fails to let us down <br>Solitude arrives like a guest in a hotel <br>When she ups and leaves for the devil in the detail <br>The trouble arrives <br>Stronger than a root <br>I'm running like I did from the world <br>Solitude arrives like a guest in a hotel <br>Solitude arrives like a guest in a hotel <br>When she ups and leaves for the devil in the detail <br>The trouble arrives <br>Stronger than a root <br>I'm running like I did from the world <br>Solitude arrives like a guest in a hotel <br>Solitude arrives like a guest in a hotel <br>When she ups and leaves for the devil in the detail]]></content><category term="D.I.D" label="D.I.D"/><category term="Hotel" label="Hotel"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DID/Heavy_Cloud/</id><title>D.I.D - Heavy Cloud - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:23:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:23:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DID/Heavy_Cloud/" title="D.I.D - Heavy Cloud - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Heavy cloud, heavy cloud above my head <br>Well I learned something I didn't know <br>About someone I love <br><br>Am I ready now, ready now to move along <br>I'm done with all the cigarettes <br>And long distance calls <br>Is this a good time to let you know that <br>Theres a fallen angel running wild under your eyelid <br>So save it for a rainy day <br><br>And what a view, what a view from out the car <br>And the moon is like a river boat <br>Sailing on the stars <br>And heavy cloud, heavy cloud above my head <br>Sometimes it take a little while <br>To crawl out of the bed <br>Is this a good time to say goodnight <br>Say your prayer and heaven holds a gate for you and I dear <br>We're waiting on a rainy day <br><br>Am I ready now, heavy cloud above my head]]></content><category term="D.I.D" label="D.I.D"/><category term="Heavy Cloud" label="Heavy Cloud"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DID/Funnybone/</id><title>D.I.D - Funnybone - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:23:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:23:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DID/Funnybone/" title="D.I.D - Funnybone - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Make a face then punch me out of bed <br>Tonight I feel like you'd sell me to the highest bidder now <br>The TV's on, we're drunk and we're ahead in life <br><br>At least in my eyes, I read you like an open book <br><br>It's like that H O joke, will I stay broke will I stay sober <br>Told the light in the mirror <br>And if a part of you accepts that we'll still fit when we get older, would it catch your funnybone <br><br>But I'll keep fighting on, keep fighting on, keep fighting on <br>From here on out it's me and you, girl <br><br>Catch your breath then push me down the stairs and into real life <br>I really thought said you loved this time <br>I'm like that H O joke, I'm like old chip on your shoulder <br>You'll be glad to see it go <br>And if a part of you remembers days like this as being golden, would it catch your funny bone <br><br>And I'll keep fighting on, keep fighting on, keep fighting on <br>From here on out it's me and you girl <br>And I'll keep fighting on, keep fighting on, keep fighting on <br>From here on out it's me and you girl <br>From here on out it's me and you girl <br>From here on out it's me and girl <br><br>On the accident that left you where you are now <br>Made you unaware and you lost your trust and confidence <br>At first, I felt sure <br>That I'll keep fighting on keep fighting on keep fighting on <br>From on out it's me and you girl <br>And I'll keep fighting on keep fighting on keep fighting on <br>From on out it's me and you girl <br>From on out it's me and you girl <br>From on out it's me and you girl <br>From on out it's me and you girl <br>From on out it's me and you girl <br>From on out it's me and you girl]]></content><category term="D.I.D" label="D.I.D"/><category term="Funnybone" label="Funnybone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DID/Fast_Food/</id><title>D.I.D - Fast Food - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:23:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:23:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DID/Fast_Food/" title="D.I.D - Fast Food - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The beginners look you never knew you had <br>Well you got something right for once in your life <br>And time races on when the old spark is gone <br>You waste each other for a brief moment in the light <br><br>Now all we do is eat fast food <br>All we do is fool around <br>All we do means nothing nothing nothing <br>All we do is either come to blows <br>Or dream into the suburb <br>All we do means nothing nothing nothing now <br>And i can keep my head up <br>And if i lay you down <br>I can keep my head up <br><br>The tragic cliche you never knew you were <br>Til you jumped right in and swam for your life <br>We both needed space <br>Someone else's pillow case <br>To rest our necks on and be alone for a little while <br><br>Now all we do is eat fast food <br>All we do is fool around <br>All we do means nothing nothing nothing <br>All we do is either come to blows <br>Or dream into the suburb <br>All we do means nothing nothing nothing now <br>And i can keep my head up <br>And if i lay you down <br>I can keep my head up <br><br>So fade me out <br>I'll fade you out <br>How very english of us <br>So maybe now we'll fade each other out <br>So fade me out <br>I'll fade you out <br>How very english of us <br>So maybe now we'll fade each other out <br><br>Now all we do is eat fast food <br>All we do is fool around <br>All we do means nothing nothing nothing <br>All we do is either come to blows <br>Or dream into the suburb <br>All we do means nothing nothing nothing now <br>And i can keep my head up <br>And if i lay you down <br>I can keep my head up]]></content><category term="D.I.D" label="D.I.D"/><category term="Fast Food" label="Fast Food"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/려/달빛하늘_Feat_태사비애/</id><title>려 - 달빛하늘 (Feat. 태사비애) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:23:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:23:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%A4/%EB%8B%AC%EB%B9%9B%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98_Feat_%ED%83%9C%EC%82%AC%EB%B9%84%EC%95%A0/" title="려 - 달빛하늘 (Feat. 태사비애) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람처럼 또 먼지처럼 <br>사라지는 기억이 <br>그대라는 추억 속에 사랑 <br>왜 아직도 날 스치는 걸까 <br>하루 이틀 지나고 일년이 가도 <br>그대란 사람 사랑이 추억이 돼서 <br>지금 행복한데 나는 왜 눈물이 날까 <br>또 이렇게 그대가 가 <br>그 기억이 어두운 날엔 <br>눈을 감고 가만히 <br>그대라는 기억 속에 사랑 <br>왜 아직도 날 스치는 걸까 <br>달빛 하늘 아래서 두 손을 모아 <br>내 소원 빌면 혹시나 들어줄까 봐 <br>달님 별님 들리나요 나의 기도가 <br>소녀의 작은 기도가 <br>다 살아 가는 이유 그렇고 그런 건데 <br>왜 갑자기 눈물이 날까 <br>하루 이틀 지나고 일년이 가고 <br>뒤돌아 보면 어느덧 십 년이 지나 <br>지금 행복하다는데 왜 눈물이 날까 <br>또 이렇게 사랑이 가 <br>또 이렇게 그대가 가 <br>]]></content><category term="려" label="려"/><category term="달빛하늘 (Feat. 태사비애)" label="달빛하늘 (Feat. 태사비애)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VAS_LEON/Trust_Nobody/</id><title>VAS LEON - Trust Nobody - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:24:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:24:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VAS_LEON/Trust_Nobody/" title="VAS LEON - Trust Nobody - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't you <br>Hate it when they smile and think that <br>Everything's okay, and they <br>Swear they tell the truth but they're just <br>Lying to your face <br><br>Are you crazy, are you crazy crazy <br>You ain't fooling me <br>All this time I knew about you and 'bout <br>All your silly games <br><br>Nah I ain't even listenin' <br>Yeah I'm sick of all your gibberish <br>You thought I would never find out, but you <br>Don't know who you're dealing with <br><br>All I hear is sorry sorry <br>But I ain't got a worry worry <br>'Cause you know very well that <br>I don't trust no body <br><br>See I heard it before <br>So you're one to ignore <br>I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody but me <br><br>You see I heard it before <br>So you're one to ignore <br>I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody <br><br>I got pictures I got proof <br>Go on tell me your excuse <br>Ain't a thing you said add up <br>'Cause one add one ain't three it's two, yeah <br><br>Yes I knew <br>What's the point in stopping you <br>When you're out in the club <br>You're freaking them I'm freaking too <br><br>I don't need none of it <br>I don't care what you're offering <br>You thought I would never find out <br>But you're one hell of an optimist <br><br>All I hear is sorry sorry <br>But I ain't got a worry worry <br>'Cause you know very well <br>I don't trust no body <br><br>See I heard it before <br>So you're one to ignore <br>I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody but me <br><br>You see I heard it before <br>So you're one to ignore <br>I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody <br><br>See I heard it before <br>So you're one to ignore <br>I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody but me <br><br>You see I heard it before <br>So you're one to ignore <br>I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody <br><br>I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody but me <br>I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody <br>Vas Leon <br><br>You say you're my best friend <br>But you're lying once again <br>I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody, I don't trust nobody]]></content><category term="VAS LEON" label="VAS LEON"/><category term="Trust Nobody" label="Trust Nobody"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chuuwee/Posse_Up_Feat_Roctedy/</id><title>Chuuwee - Posse Up (Feat. Roc$tedy) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:24:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:24:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chuuwee/Posse_Up_Feat_Roctedy/" title="Chuuwee - Posse Up (Feat. Roc$tedy) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What you may see before your eyes is a thing called emcees that rhyme <br>Bitch ass niggas is blind, to the real, and here's where you'll find <br><br>You dudes froze up, heard the cannon blow up <br>Sniper with his sights in a scope, perfect for close ups <br>But when I'm close up, nicer with a knife <br>Slice him down to size, murder beats turning beef into cold cuts <br>Go head, it's your guts Turn into a hostage <br>Talk slick I'll point a hollow tip to where your thoughts is <br>This is putting ammunition on an animal <br>Split your cantaloupe, envision a dinner with Hannibal <br>Thor shit let the hammer go Invading your base to spit in the face of your admiral <br>You dudes sick I spew shit called the antidote <br>Overrated twits I'll take a piss in your talent pool watch this <br>Kick the door in, run inside your home with <br>Underworld superiors clearing you out your own shit <br>Start diminishing all the competition and hit em with the vision that you should be watching the throne with <br><br>Blood on my left shoe <br>Left him with his chin in his hand <br>Wheels spin on the van, peelin got him spillin his lip <br>Flipped his new era, fuck with the crew cheddar <br>Get shredded pumpin premium shells in your tank no unleaded <br>Bet it nigga, you better than my bread drain then lose it all <br>A crew of sharks swarm on you if you move at all <br>Talkin cheap stack on his head if he choose to stall <br>Let off a round big enough to fuckin move em all <br>Chillin like a buddha lightin buddah <br>Writin like my prime is right now but im the future <br>Heavy on the beats but my rhymes are tryna shoot ya <br>While you high like supra's im disguised as a user <br>Try shit make ya mom vomit on her lawn, while she in her long johns <br>Ill be searchin through your closet <br>Shotgun past on my arm out the socket <br>End zone touchdown, TUS, got this <br><br>Fuck it im full of hormones <br>Poppin at a drunk bitch chuggin a four loko <br>Skin color coco <br>Cabana my banana clip will lay ya like banana hammock <br>Dammit I hand cock it back and rock ya mans planet <br>Bandanna bandit Sneakin over while her mans absent <br>A damn savage you damn right I let him have it <br>Havocing prodigy <br>We mobbing deep <br>Cause a scene <br>Law enforcing callin me, cuz I got a squad with me <br>The diabolical im aiming at your folicals <br>Ill flow a pot of gold <br>Bitch the white just like an audible <br>Hail mary, hell ya them scary niggas run away <br>And coward when we scouring the building yelling da da doe <br>Look like they gotta go, before I let my rolly smoke <br>I bust a wally runnin down the block <br>Because the trolly broke <br>The lally smoke <br>Chiefing on a pound of la di da di <br>Nigga click clack shotty blast <br>Who shot the party folk]]></content><category term="Chuuwee" label="Chuuwee"/><category term="Posse Up (Feat. Roc$tedy)" label="Posse Up (Feat. Roc$tedy)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chuuwee/Friday_Night_Feat_Roctedy/</id><title>Chuuwee - Friday Night (Feat. Roc$tedy) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:24:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:24:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chuuwee/Friday_Night_Feat_Roctedy/" title="Chuuwee - Friday Night (Feat. Roc$tedy) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's a Friday night <br>Promoter playing games so we prolly gon fight <br>Pull up and hop off a bike cuz I ran outta gas when I stopped at a light <br>Niggas don't know what it's like, to be hounted by fans when I get off the mic <br>Niggas don't know what it's like to be hounted by ex's who hate outta spite <br><br>They mad cuz I'm tight Get this money to write <br>Express how I feel and promote what I like <br>You dick ride niggas for comments and likes <br>Fronting for bitches and live for the hype <br>Faded I'm mixing my vodka with Sprite <br>High as a bitch when I jump on a flight <br>I land in LA with a freak to my right, finna lyft to my house nigga shit is the life <br><br>It's a Friday night <br>Yup And we prolly gon fight <br>Promoters don't want us to trip but we might <br>If niggas want beef we can do it on sight <br>Aye It's a Friday night <br>Niggas might die on the night of your life <br>Yup it's a Friday night, we gon get it cracking on a Friday night <br><br>Aye You don't know what's it like to be 6 pills in tongue fighting a dike <br>It's a Friday night Living the life Never expected we'd get in a fight <br>Fresh from the sip bout to get off a flight <br>Posted with my nigga he gone get off this rice <br>Hop in the lyft we gone meet up with Trizz <br>I know a shortcut get off the right <br>Tucked in my sock we'll get lit off tonight <br>Higher than whatever got lift off ignite <br>Got a 5th in my sprite or and 4 in my ice <br>Stop all that talking just get off or slide <br>If it ain't beef Ima go get some fries <br>5 guys it was just me I'm outside <br>Tee haha ha I be laughing inside <br>BBP Crew got the spot going live <br><br>It's a Friday night <br>Yup And we prolly gon fight <br>Promoters don't want us to trip but we might <br>If niggas want beef we can do it on sight <br>Aye It's a Friday night <br>Niggas might die on the night of your life <br>Yup it's a Friday night, we gon get it cracking on a Friday night <br><br>Land of the hopeless Caskets and roses <br>we active in motion, in back with a back get it cracking and smoke it <br>Get back or I'll roast em <br>Rocky the stoner just rolled up the roaches <br>Niggas just ran outta bud through the mud with the rodents <br>No love in the streets, if you see it it's bogus <br>Climb up the totem <br>Look back at the times that we told em <br>Eyes never lie, man we knew we was golden <br>Bitch I'm reloaded And so is the gun <br>One shot and it's over <br>This double o seven we still sixty four it <br>Bounce with a player, watch how I control it <br>Mario party I had to come join in <br>Just parked me the kart <br>Bout to pick me my poison <br>She wanna come play, let her ride on the joystick <br>Bust a nut then I'm snoring Gone <br><br>It's a Friday night <br>Yup And we prolly gon fight <br>Promoters don't want us to trip but we might <br>If niggas want beef we can do it on sight <br>Aye It's a Friday night <br>Niggas might die on the night of your life <br>Yup it's a Friday night, we gon get it cracking on a Friday night]]></content><category term="Chuuwee" label="Chuuwee"/><category term="Friday Night (Feat. Roc$tedy)" label="Friday Night (Feat. Roc$tedy)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chuuwee/Rotation/</id><title>Chuuwee - Rotation - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:24:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:24:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chuuwee/Rotation/" title="Chuuwee - Rotation - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Now as the name grow big and game the rotate <br>All I wanna do is blow really loud dank <br>If it ain't no pay then we ain't gone play <br>All I'm tryna do is save little more bank <br>Oh oh let's do it like Wakka Flocka Flame <br>All I ever do is go hard in the paint <br>How you flex so hard you don't even got a chain <br>I been on planes doing real big thangs <br><br>Now as the game rotate and my name grow big <br>I been staying down and I ain't gone switch <br>Had a grade a 9 that I traded for a 6 <br>And now I want her back like baby back ribs <br>But it's back to the matter Break Bread what it is <br>BBP Crew getting blitted off spliffs <br>All them sideline problems they gone cease to exist <br>I'm in a down spiral eating seeds with your bitch <br>I C E Cold THCs with no seed we smoke <br>PayPal loaded but to she he's broke <br>Pisso fire but all I need is deepthroat in her fendi peacoat <br>Make two G's stee twice to 3 fold <br>And he keeps loud gas he likes the breathe smoke <br>Stupid shit I don't like to be told <br>I'll mute niggas just like life had a remote <br><br>Now as the name grow big and game the rotate <br>All I wanna do is blow really loud dank <br>If it ain't no pay then we ain't gone play <br>All I'm tryna do is save little more bank <br>Oh oh let's do it like Wakka Flocka Flame <br>All I ever do is go hard in the paint <br>How you flex so hard you don't even got a chain <br>I been on planes doing real big thangs <br><br>That's what I muthafuckin said <br>Smoke till I'm sleep, eyes muthafuckin red <br>If we don't fuck I'm getting muthafuckin head <br>or she bringing me some breakfast to this muthafuckin bed <br>What is you saying, my nigga I'm what is they playing <br>Bitch we all around, the album is in Japan <br>Shout out to Chez that's my muthafuckin fam <br>If he tripping then I'm tripping ask questions when we scram <br>That's how I am, I'm loyal even to fans <br>I won't eat if they don't jam so I'm doing what I can <br>I post and smoke grams, with the homies from the land <br>and I post it on the gram cuz that's really who I am <br>Y'all just be talking I'm really insane <br>the doctor prescribed me some Percs for the pain <br>Papers legit, bitch I'm covered and paid <br>was never a problem for Trizz to get laid <br><br>Now as the name grow big and game the rotate <br>All I wanna do is blow really loud dank <br>If it ain't no pay then we ain't gone play <br>All I'm tryna do is save little more bank <br>Oh oh let's do it like Wakka Flocka Flame <br>All I ever do is go hard in the paint <br>How you flex so hard you don't even got a chain <br>I been on planes doing real big thangs]]></content><category term="Chuuwee" label="Chuuwee"/><category term="Rotation" label="Rotation"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chuuwee/By_Myself/</id><title>Chuuwee - By Myself - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:24:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:24:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chuuwee/By_Myself/" title="Chuuwee - By Myself - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can get it by myself <br>I been drinking I been thinking I been sinking in depression 2nd guessing I don't need nobody help <br>Determination is impressive, wake up bright and early like the bill collector I just came here for a check <br>Early morning rolling stoning in the zone I gotta make it out the doe I'm tryna prove it to myself <br>I'm gone take whatever's given save it up and make a living take it all come back and take whatever's left <br><br>Just let me smoke this gas by my lonely I'm fine <br>A whole zip of master kush roshi and I'm high <br>My mane grew and can't nobody notice me a lion <br>I changed my insight and all that gun talk expired <br>Been doing what I'm posed to and saving up my bread <br>Refortified my mind good thoughts within my head <br>I been getting high as Zion ever since I got my dreads <br>I can't do anything before I take my daily meds <br>Cuz everytime I turn my neck I catch the smell of someone's breath <br>Everybody hates Chris and don't nobody like Greg <br>Everybody loves Raymond but they wanna kill Chez <br>At night I dream of Beamer with the heater in my bed <br>Replay my legacy and you can hear the tears shed <br>How everything I did was everything I ever said <br>How niggas used to ride my coat tails till they would shred <br>Found a dinner table took my jacket off we breaking bread <br><br>I can get it by myself <br>I been drinking I been thinking I been sinking in depression 2nd guessing I don't need nobody help <br>Determination is impressive, wake up bright and early like the bill collector I just came here for a check <br>Early morning rolling stoning in the zone I gotta make it out the doe I'm tryna prove it to myself <br>I'm gone take whatever's given save it up and make a living take it all come back and take whatever's left <br><br>You know my get down, I'm hopping out the Hyundai <br>And pull up tripping like Joy did on Friday <br>Nigga it's a fried day, a smoke and get high day, like Usher do it my way Faded leaning sideways <br>We ain't clubbing, we be thugging in the drive way <br>Bending corners, nigga fuck taking a high way <br>So Cal, my lo cal If you didn't then you know now <br>I was broke as you niggas But hey I'm getting doe now <br>Kicking in the door now, if you ain't got that dough now <br>Couple hundred people when you pull up to my show now <br>They getting mad cuz we charging for the flow now <br>If niggas keep on tripping we gone have to do'em low down <br>Mosh pits and fist fights bitch we go wild <br>It's all love, it don't ever really go down <br>Niggas know the la familia move and ain't gone slow down <br>I ain't never going broke again cuz I don't know how]]></content><category term="Chuuwee" label="Chuuwee"/><category term="By Myself" label="By Myself"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chuuwee/Above_It_All_Too/</id><title>Chuuwee - Above It All Too - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:24:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:24:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chuuwee/Above_It_All_Too/" title="Chuuwee - Above It All Too - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[These niggas be saying my name <br>I think they be needing a fade <br>He say he ain't mean what he saying, talking circles you niggas be playing <br>Tell me then what is you saying <br>You niggas be thinkin I'm playing, you gossip and talk about niggas like women that's why you a bitch and get treated like fans <br>He wanna be treated like fam <br>He tell me his gun will go blam, but shit that don't make you a man, that make you a mark like a nigga who ran <br>We gone come up with a plan <br>We on our way in a van <br>22 hours away from my city, nigga just me and my band <br>Talk like I'm white with a tan <br>Only show up if they paying <br>I need it all in my hand, I ain't gone take nothing less than a grand <br>Niggas fronting on a cam <br>BBP is in demand BBP is in Japan This ain't no clique it's a brand <br>Don't get caught up in the jam <br>They don't fucking understand <br>I be doing what I can <br>I be thugging in the land <br>I be thugging in some vans <br>Broken promises and scams <br>Fuck it I don't give a damn Attention I don't give a nan <br><br>They don't love us just want us to slave <br>Fuck it I'm never gone change <br>I go through the misunderstandings and pain they only see money and fame <br>It's funny they think it's a game Till they notice it's really a shame <br>These niggas'll turn on you quick as a bitch cuz they really be needing a name <br><br>Ac3 Beats med pills Trizz verse all gas 3 peat <br>We the tag dream team Nigga pass me the weed <br>I been having bad dreams lately I don't really wanna go to sleep <br>I been taking pain killers 7 days of the week <br>Life is all about perception Tell me how you look at me <br>From a whole different world I am not a human being <br>I can mash on the gas pedal while I'm on passenger seat skrt <br>Ima slide on you with a skirt steak since you really beef <br>Peep Conversation ain't cheap I gotta charge a $100 fee <br>I gotta break her heart for her trust, I think there's something really wrong with me <br>4 of us like Adele in a jeep <br>Go hit the show rolling in the deep <br>They talking wreckless on a small screen I know to never sweat small things <br>I know that life is really what you make it <br>You can be anything you wanna be <br>I'm on the conquest of the century I gotta lot of shit I gotta see <br>I'm talking common sense ingenuity I'm talking commas and I speak it fluently <br>In economics never had a truancy I got momentum now I'm steady moving <br><br>They don't love us just want us to slave <br>Fuck it I'm never gone change <br>I go through the misunderstandings and pain they only see money and fame <br>It's funny they think it's a game Till they notice it's really a shame <br>These niggas'll turn on you quick as a bitch cuz they really be needing a name]]></content><category term="Chuuwee" label="Chuuwee"/><category term="Above It All Too" label="Above It All Too"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chuuwee/Bout_Mine/</id><title>Chuuwee - Bout Mine - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:24:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:24:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chuuwee/Bout_Mine/" title="Chuuwee - Bout Mine - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We gone ride before we die Nigga we high <br>I need all of mines before we slide In the g ride <br>If your mouth wide, then I'm outside Cuz I'm bout mine <br>Bitch I'm bout mine, bitch I'm bout mine Bitch I'm bout mine <br><br>Who is that with a pound of broccoli <br>Stayed down came around monopoly <br>Got some OGs off the block with me <br>And real niggas gone share the top with me <br>Twitch stream how the game keep watching me <br>Level up and maintain sub consciously <br>Fan boys how they email awkwardly <br>Tell them lame niggas back up off of me approach me cautiously <br>Smoking gas in the Nissan chunk the peace sign with my feet high yea <br>Now I got it going 3 times and they offer help cuz they need mines yea <br>I been on this doing me time on my own moves under street lights bet <br>I been riding like wheelchair and I'm still here for the real players yea <br><br>We gone ride before we die Nigga we high <br>I need all of mines before we slide In the g ride <br>If your mouth wide, then I'm outside Cuz I'm bout mine <br>Bitch I'm bout mine, bitch I'm bout mine Bitch I'm bout mine <br><br>Lost mind but my I found mine <br>Insane but I sound fine <br>Break Bread with some foul guys, counting so much money is the downside <br>Smoke weed on my down time, stay low key and don't allow eyes <br>Outta site nigga outta mind <br>Niggas tried but who stopping mine Disrespectful niggas outta line <br>Show some love when you around mine <br>We provide the sounds and get down live <br>Spends lots of cheese and walk around fly <br>Lost friends but fuck it <br>Slap slumps out the bucket <br>They don't want no funk with us just mad as fuck cuz we stunting <br>Have my bread and stop fronting <br>If you ask for shit have a budget <br>Niggas broke and they can't be fixed so fuck a bitch and get duckets <br>Pull up first or start ducking <br>Throw them things or start bussin <br>We don't hide we ain't hard to find you can catch us live at our function <br><br>We gone ride before we die Nigga we high <br>I need all of mines before we slide In the g ride <br>If your mouth wide, then I'm outside Cuz I'm bout mine <br>Bitch I'm bout mine, bitch I'm bout mine Bitch I'm bout mine]]></content><category term="Chuuwee" label="Chuuwee"/><category term="Bout Mine" label="Bout Mine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sons_Of_Butcher/Nsane_Dream/</id><title>Sons Of Butcher - Nsane Dream - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:30:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:30:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sons_Of_Butcher/Nsane_Dream/" title="Sons Of Butcher - Nsane Dream - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Girl <br>Oh girl <br>I won't play games <br><br>See my face <br>Don't tell me the dream has gone insane <br>I won't play games <br>I'm praying that you would feel the same <br>Just a taste <br>I'm only a single hearted man <br>If you give chase <br>I'll get the life that I once had <br><br>Oh girl <br>Oh girl <br>Oh girl <br>Oh girl <br>Oh girl <br>Girl, I won't play games <br><br>See my face <br>Don't tell me the dream has gone insane <br>I won't play games <br>I'm praying that you would take that plane <br>Just a taste <br>I'm only a single hearted man a single hearted man <br>If you give chase <br>I'll get the life that I once had I love you]]></content><category term="Sons Of Butcher" label="Sons Of Butcher"/><category term="Nsane Dream" label="Nsane Dream"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sons_Of_Butcher/Tapeworm/</id><title>Sons Of Butcher - Tapeworm - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:30:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:30:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sons_Of_Butcher/Tapeworm/" title="Sons Of Butcher - Tapeworm - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[God bless you tapeworm <br>Gonna eat my ass off <br>Foods I don't dream of <br>Even stuff that's not food, ya <br><br>With a tapeworm <br>Calories burn <br>With all the food you eat <br>So eat <br><br>I love you tapeworm <br>Makin' me all skinny, and shit <br>Even stuff that's not food, like a blender <br><br>With a tapeworm <br>Calories burn <br>With all the food you eat <br>So eat]]></content><category term="Sons Of Butcher" label="Sons Of Butcher"/><category term="Tapeworm" label="Tapeworm"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sons_Of_Butcher/Go_Vegan/</id><title>Sons Of Butcher - Go Vegan - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:32:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:32:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sons_Of_Butcher/Go_Vegan/" title="Sons Of Butcher - Go Vegan - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Gettin' healthy but I don't feel good <br>Eatin' only what they tell me I should <br>'Cause meat is cruel and bad for your bod <br>Of course Vegans are all smarter than God <br><br>Go Vegan <br>Livin' clean and goin' strong <br>Go Vegan <br>Even though my body tells me it's wrong <br>Go Vegan <br>No beef, pork, dairy or fish <br>Go Vegan <br>And you can all be healthy just like this]]></content><category term="Sons Of Butcher" label="Sons Of Butcher"/><category term="Go Vegan" label="Go Vegan"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matt_Andersen/Broken_Man/</id><title>Matt Andersen - Broken Man - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:33:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:33:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matt_Andersen/Broken_Man/" title="Matt Andersen - Broken Man - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[you can't take the home from a homeless man <br>you can't take away his streets <br>you can't threaten a man, with nothing to lose <br><br>or bruise him when he's beat <br>you can't take money from a poor man <br>or scare a man with no fear <br>you can't shame a man with no pride <br>or force a stone to tears <br>what can you do to a broken man <br>what can you do to a broken man <br>you can't cut a man who's bleeding <br>you can't push a man who's down <br>you can't starve a man who's hungry <br>or loose him when he's found <br>you can't break a man who's broken <br>or cheat a man who knows <br>or kill a dream that's dead <br>and curse it when it goes <br>what can you do to a broken man <br>what can you do to a broken man <br>you can't strip a man who's naked <br>you can't defend a man who's lied <br>you can't believe a man who's lost <br>you can't envy a man that's cried <br>you can't lift a man who's risen <br>or teach a man that knows <br>you can't fight a man who's won <br>or heat a fire that burns <br>what can you do to a broken man <br>what can you do to a broken man]]></content><category term="Matt Andersen" label="Matt Andersen"/><category term="Broken Man" label="Broken Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matt_Andersen/Better_Man_Blues/</id><title>Matt Andersen - Better Man Blues - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:33:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:33:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matt_Andersen/Better_Man_Blues/" title="Matt Andersen - Better Man Blues - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My girl, My girl <br>Where have you gone <br>My girl, my girl <br><br>where have you gone <br>well you took all my love <br>left me here alone <br><br>i know, i was cruel <br>wont you please be kind <br>yes i know i was cruel to you <br>wont you please be kind <br>i didnt want to bring you down, i never meant to make you cry <br>when you walk by <br>i hold my head in my hands <br>knowing such a good woman <br>deserves a better man]]></content><category term="Matt Andersen" label="Matt Andersen"/><category term="Better Man Blues" label="Better Man Blues"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matt_Andersen/So_Gone_Now/</id><title>Matt Andersen - So Gone Now - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:33:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:33:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Matt_Andersen/So_Gone_Now/" title="Matt Andersen - So Gone Now - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If I gave you a wish, babe <br>Would I be the thing that you'd change <br>Would you wish you never smiled, babe <br>Would you wish you never asked for my name <br>When you pour all your heart <br>On that last falling star <br>Will that be the wish that you make <br><br>Do you ever think about, babe <br>How right it felt when it was good <br>I'd shoot at the moon, babe <br>Just to hold you in the dark, if I could <br>How we'd stay up all night <br>just to feel the sun rise <br>Do you ever think about it, babe <br><br>'Cause it's been so long now <br>Since I let you down <br>And I don't, I don't know how <br>You are so gone now <br><br>Lately I've been talking, babe <br>Talking to myself about you <br>Trying to figure out <br>All of those things I wouldn't do for you <br>How I didn't even try when we said our last goodbye <br>And lately I've been talking to me, babe <br><br>'Cause it's been so long now <br>Since I let you down <br>And I don't know how <br>You are so gone now <br><br>Now I'm out on the road, babe <br>With nothing to do but pass the time <br>I pull away from the town, babe <br>Just like I've done to you <br>and I leave them all behind <br>When I see you again <br>It'll be just as your friend <br>I know it's hard <br>but that's just how it's gonna be, babe <br><br>'Cause it's been so long now <br>Since I let you down <br>And I don't know how <br>You are so gone now <br><br>Yeah, it's been so long now <br>Since I let you down <br>and I don't know how <br>You are so gone now]]></content><category term="Matt Andersen" label="Matt Andersen"/><category term="So Gone Now" label="So Gone Now"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조민/엘리사벳과_마리아/</id><title>조민 - 엘리사벳과 마리아 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:38:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:38:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EB%AF%BC/%EC%97%98%EB%A6%AC%EC%82%AC%EB%B2%B3%EA%B3%BC_%EB%A7%88%EB%A6%AC%EC%95%84/" title="조민 - 엘리사벳과 마리아 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마리아여 <br>당신과 나의 태중에 <br>아이도 복이 있습니다 <br>내 주의 모친이 <br>나에게 나아오니 <br>이 어찐 일입니까 <br>내 영혼이 주를 찬양하며 <br>내 마음이 하나님 <br>내 구주를 기뻐합니다 <br>마리아 목소리 <br>내 귀에 들릴 때 <br>나의 아이가 기뻐 뛰노네 <br>내 영혼이 주를 찬양하며 <br>내 마음이 하나님 <br>내 구주를 기뻐합니다 <br>믿은 그대에게 <br>복을 복을 복을 <br>주의 계집종의 <br>비천함을 돌아보셨으니 <br>이제 후로는 만세에 <br>당신께 복이 있다 하리요 <br>주께서 당신에게 하신 <br>말씀이 반드시 이루리라 <br>내 영혼이 주를 찬양하며 <br>내 마음이 하나님 <br>내 구주 기뻐합니다 <br>찬양합니다 나의 구주 <br>]]></content><category term="조민" label="조민"/><category term="엘리사벳과 마리아" label="엘리사벳과 마리아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/크러쉬_피버/꺼져_Inst/</id><title>크러쉬 피버 - 꺼져 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:40:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:40:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%81%AC%EB%9F%AC%EC%89%AC_%ED%94%BC%EB%B2%84/%EA%BA%BC%EC%A0%B8_Inst/" title="크러쉬 피버 - 꺼져 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그런 말 하지 말고 이제 그만 내게서 <br>말 같잖은 핑계대지 말고 그만 <br>억울하단 표정 짓지 말고 그만 <br>가식적인 표정 내 앞에서 그만 <br>치워줘 <br>이제 니가 뭐라 하든 <br>내 귀에 하나 들리지 않아 <br>내게 그런 강요하지마 <br>계속 그러면 <br>내게 남아있는 정마저 떨어져버려 <br>내가 왜 지금 와서 그 애길 <br>하고 있는 건지 <br>도대체 내가 내가 이해할 수가 <br>없자나 <br>지껄이지 말고 시끄럽게 말고 <br>더 이상 내게서 <br>그런 말 하지 말고 이제 그만 내게서 <br>말 같잖은 핑계대지 말고 그만 <br>억울하단 표정 짓지 말고 그만 <br>가식적인 표정 내 앞에서 <br>그런 말 하지 말고 이제 그만 내게서 <br>말 같잖은 핑계대지 말고 그만 <br>억울하단 표정 짓지 말고 그만 <br>가식적인 표정 내 앞에서 그만 <br>지워줘 <br>원 스탭 투 스텝 <br>멀어지는 우리 사이 돈스탑 <br>이 스타일 저 스타일 <br>말하지마 넌 그냥 <br>not my style <br>이제 니가 뭐라 하든 <br>내 귀에 하나 들리지 않아 <br>내게 그런 강요하지마 <br>계속 그러면 그러면 <br>내게 남아있는 <br>정마저 떨어져버려 <br>내가 왜 지금 와서 그 애길 <br>하고 있는 건지 <br>도대체 내가 내가 이해할 수가 <br>없자나 <br>지껄이지 말고 시끄럽게 말고 <br>더 이상 내게서 <br>그런 말 하지 말고 이제 그만 내게서 <br>말 같잖은 핑계대지 말고 그만 <br>억울하단 표정 짓지 말고 그만 <br>가식적인 표정 내 앞에서 <br>그런 말 하지 말고 이제 그만 내게서 <br>말 같잖은 핑계대지 말고 그만 <br>억울하단 표정 짓지 말고 그만 <br>가식적인 표정 내 앞에서 <br>그런 말 하지 말고 이제 그만 내게서 <br>말 같잖은 핑계대지 말고 그만 <br>억울하단 표정 짓지 말고 그만 <br>가식적인 표정 내 앞에서 <br>그런 말 하지 말고 이제 그만 내게서 <br>말 같잖은 핑계대지 말고 그만 <br>억울하단 표정 짓지 말고 그만 <br>가식적인 표정 내 앞에서 <br>치워줘 <br>]]></content><category term="크러쉬 피버" label="크러쉬 피버"/><category term="꺼져 (Inst.)" label="꺼져 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/크러쉬_피버/꺼져/</id><title>크러쉬 피버 - 꺼져 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:40:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:40:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%81%AC%EB%9F%AC%EC%89%AC_%ED%94%BC%EB%B2%84/%EA%BA%BC%EC%A0%B8/" title="크러쉬 피버 - 꺼져 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그런 말 하지 말고 이제 그만 내게서 <br>말 같잖은 핑계대지 말고 그만 <br>억울하단 표정 짓지 말고 그만 <br>가식적인 표정 내 앞에서 그만 <br>치워줘 <br>이제 니가 뭐라 하든 <br>내 귀에 하나 들리지 않아 <br>내게 그런 강요하지마 <br>계속 그러면 <br>내게 남아있는 정마저 떨어져버려 <br>내가 왜 지금 와서 그 애길 <br>하고 있는 건지 <br>도대체 내가 내가 이해할 수가 <br>없자나 <br>지껄이지 말고 시끄럽게 말고 <br>더 이상 내게서 <br>그런 말 하지 말고 이제 그만 내게서 <br>말 같잖은 핑계대지 말고 그만 <br>억울하단 표정 짓지 말고 그만 <br>가식적인 표정 내 앞에서 <br>그런 말 하지 말고 이제 그만 내게서 <br>말 같잖은 핑계대지 말고 그만 <br>억울하단 표정 짓지 말고 그만 <br>가식적인 표정 내 앞에서 그만 <br>지워줘 <br>원 스탭 투 스텝 <br>멀어지는 우리 사이 돈스탑 <br>이 스타일 저 스타일 <br>말하지마 넌 그냥 <br>not my style <br>이제 니가 뭐라 하든 <br>내 귀에 하나 들리지 않아 <br>내게 그런 강요하지마 <br>계속 그러면 그러면 <br>내게 남아있는 <br>정마저 떨어져버려 <br>내가 왜 지금 와서 그 애길 <br>하고 있는 건지 <br>도대체 내가 내가 이해할 수가 <br>없자나 <br>지껄이지 말고 시끄럽게 말고 <br>더 이상 내게서 <br>그런 말 하지 말고 이제 그만 내게서 <br>말 같잖은 핑계대지 말고 그만 <br>억울하단 표정 짓지 말고 그만 <br>가식적인 표정 내 앞에서 <br>그런 말 하지 말고 이제 그만 내게서 <br>말 같잖은 핑계대지 말고 그만 <br>억울하단 표정 짓지 말고 그만 <br>가식적인 표정 내 앞에서 <br>그런 말 하지 말고 이제 그만 내게서 <br>말 같잖은 핑계대지 말고 그만 <br>억울하단 표정 짓지 말고 그만 <br>가식적인 표정 내 앞에서 <br>그런 말 하지 말고 이제 그만 내게서 <br>말 같잖은 핑계대지 말고 그만 <br>억울하단 표정 짓지 말고 그만 <br>가식적인 표정 내 앞에서 <br>치워줘 <br>]]></content><category term="크러쉬 피버" label="크러쉬 피버"/><category term="꺼져" label="꺼져"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강산여울_With_두강/Hey_Girl/</id><title>강산여울 With 두강 - Hey Girl - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:41:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:41:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%82%B0%EC%97%AC%EC%9A%B8_With_%EB%91%90%EA%B0%95/Hey_Girl/" title="강산여울 With 두강 - Hey Girl - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[길을 걷다 너를 봤어 <br>우연인듯 운명인듯 <br>오래전에 헤어졌던 <br>네가 저 멀리 서 있어 <br>다가가서 말을 걸까 <br>모른 척 지나갈까 <br>고민하던 순간 네가 내 앞에 서있네 <br>아이 잠깐 덜컹거린 상황 <br>hi 인사는 커녕 눈을 감아 <br>아무렇지 않은 척 <br>담담하게 있지만 꽤나 당황했나봐 <br>oh 많은 사람중 왜 하필 네가 또 <br>oh 많은 하루중 왜 지금일까 no <br>고민하는 순간이 왜 이리도 긴거야 <br>시간이 멈춘 상황 실없이 미소만 <br>hey girl 네가 눈치 채지 않게 <br>애써 태연한척 웃어 <br>hey girl 왠지 나 촌스럽게 <br>자꾸 맘이 떨려와 <br>부르르 불어오는 바람에서 향기가 <br>알고있는 향기라서 흔한말로 심쿵해 <br>좋은 냄새 좋은 기억 좋은 <br>너무 익숙해서 가슴 언저리가 시큰해 <br>예전 서로의 대한 믿음이란 시험에 <br>우리가 피워낸 꽃들이 <br>서서히 시들 때를 <br>다 잊은 일들을 기억해내고 있어 <br>그래서 내가 지금 조금 많이 위험해 <br>수많은 인파속에서도 <br>이 향기가 스쳐지 나가면 <br>고개를 돌린 날들 <br>지금은 고개를 돌리지 않아도 <br>느낄수 있으니 그래 맞아 <br>왠지 많이 불편해 <br>혼자 불평하네 고개 떨군체 말야 <br>모든 일들 오해 가득한 나야 <br>말 안해도 알고 있지 그래서 우린 <br>멀어진거 일테니까 <br>이젠 상관없는 너와 나 <br>hey girl 네가 눈치 채지 않게 <br>애써 태연한척 웃어 <br>hey girl 왠지 나 촌스럽게 <br>자꾸 맘이 떨려와 <br>너와 나 잊은 건 하나 <br>나와 너 잃은 건 하나 <br>I &amp; U U &amp; I <br>우리란 단어인가봐 <br>너와 나 잊은 건 많아 <br>나와 너 잃은 건 하나 <br>I &amp; U U &amp; I <br>우리란 단어인가봐 <br>길을 걷다 너를 봤어 <br>우연인듯 운명인듯 <br>오래전에 헤어졌던 <br>네가 저 멀리 서 있어 <br>다가가서 말을 걸까 <br>모른 척 지나갈까 <br>고민할 필요없이 네가 내 앞을 <br>스쳐가네 <br>]]></content><category term="강산여울 With 두강" label="강산여울 With 두강"/><category term="Hey Girl" label="Hey Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마리슈/별총총_Feat_소영이/</id><title>마리슈 - 별총총 (Feat. 소영이) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:41:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:41:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%88/%EB%B3%84%EC%B4%9D%EC%B4%9D_Feat_%EC%86%8C%EC%98%81%EC%9D%B4/" title="마리슈 - 별총총 (Feat. 소영이) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이어폰을 나눠 끼고 걸었어 <br>손을 꼭 잡고서 <br>난 너를 보고 하늘을 봤어 <br>매번 바래다주는 길인데 오늘은 <br>유난히 예뻐서 <br>한 번 더 너를 바라봤어 <br>별이 총총 빛나는 밤에 <br>너를 꼭꼭 품에 안고서 <br>우린 영영 잊지 못할 날이 <br>물들어가네 <br>별이 총총 빛나는 밤에 <br>발을 동동 구르며 <br>아쉬워 헤어지기 아쉬워 <br>별이 총총 <br>너를 꼭꼭 <br>우린 영영 <br>너의 걸음에 맞춰서 걸었어 <br>손을 꼭 잡고서 <br>난 그 노래를 흥얼거렸어 <br>내게 익숙한 멜로디지만 오늘은 <br>유난히 예뻐서 <br>한 번 더 너를 불러봤어 <br>별이 총총 빛나는 밤에 <br>너를 꼭꼭 품에 안고서 <br>우린 영영 잊지 못할 날이 <br>물들어가네 <br>별이 총총 빛나는 밤에 <br>발을 동동 구르며 <br>아쉬워 헤어지기 아쉬워 <br>행복하냐고 묻는 너의 표정이 <br>밝게 빛나고 <br>저 밤하늘에 비친 <br>그림자가 예뻤어 <br>너를 한껏 끌어안고 <br>우린 별빛이 되었네 <br>몇 번이고 사랑이 되었네 <br>별이 총총 빛나는 밤에 <br>너를 꼭꼭 품에 안고서 <br>우린 영영 잊지 못할 날이 <br>물들어가네 <br>별이 총총 빛나는 밤에 <br>발을 동동 구르며 <br>아쉬워 헤어지기 아쉬워 <br>별이 총총 <br>너를 꼭꼭 <br>우린 영영 <br>별이 총총 <br>너를 꼭꼭 <br>]]></content><category term="마리슈" label="마리슈"/><category term="별총총 (Feat. 소영이)" label="별총총 (Feat. 소영이)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/몽니/나를_잊지_말아요_Inst/</id><title>몽니 - 나를 잊지 말아요 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:45:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:45:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AA%BD%EB%8B%88/%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9E%8A%EC%A7%80_%EB%A7%90%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94_Inst/" title="몽니 - 나를 잊지 말아요 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대여 당신은 무슨 이유로 <br>나를 바라봤나요 <br>너무나 특별한 <br>당신은 내게 노래였지 <br>그대여 나를 잊지 말아요 <br>나의 소리를 잊지 말아요 <br>우리 너무나 소중했기에 <br>꿈을 꾸기로 해요 <br>그대여 당신은 무슨 이유로 <br>나를 찾아왔나요 <br>너무나 특별한 <br>당신은 내게 노래였지 <br>그대여 나를 잊지 말아요 <br>나의 소리를 잊지 말아요 <br>우리 너무나 소중했기에 <br>꿈을 꾸기로 해요 <br>그대여 나를 잊지 말아요 <br>나의 소리를 잊지 말아요 <br>우리 너무나 힘들었기에 <br>꿈을 꾸기로 <br>그대여 우리 잊지 말아요 <br>나의 손길을 잊지 말아요 <br>우리 너무나 사랑했기에 <br>꿈을 꾸기로 해요 <br>그대여 나를 잊지 말아요 <br>]]></content><category term="몽니" label="몽니"/><category term="나를 잊지 말아요 (Inst.)" label="나를 잊지 말아요 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/몽니/나를_잊지_말아요/</id><title>몽니 - 나를 잊지 말아요 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:45:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:45:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AA%BD%EB%8B%88/%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9E%8A%EC%A7%80_%EB%A7%90%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94/" title="몽니 - 나를 잊지 말아요 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대여 당신은 무슨 이유로 <br>나를 바라봤나요 <br>너무나 특별한 <br>당신은 내게 노래였지 <br>그대여 나를 잊지 말아요 <br>나의 소리를 잊지 말아요 <br>우리 너무나 소중했기에 <br>꿈을 꾸기로 해요 <br>그대여 당신은 무슨 이유로 <br>나를 찾아왔나요 <br>너무나 특별한 <br>당신은 내게 노래였지 <br>그대여 나를 잊지 말아요 <br>나의 소리를 잊지 말아요 <br>우리 너무나 소중했기에 <br>꿈을 꾸기로 해요 <br>그대여 나를 잊지 말아요 <br>나의 소리를 잊지 말아요 <br>우리 너무나 힘들었기에 <br>꿈을 꾸기로 <br>그대여 우리 잊지 말아요 <br>나의 손길을 잊지 말아요 <br>우리 너무나 사랑했기에 <br>꿈을 꾸기로 해요 <br>그대여 나를 잊지 말아요 <br>]]></content><category term="몽니" label="몽니"/><category term="나를 잊지 말아요" label="나를 잊지 말아요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucas__Steve/Up_Till_Dawn_On_The_Move/</id><title>Lucas &amp; Steve - Up Till Dawn (On The Move) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:45:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:45:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lucas__Steve/Up_Till_Dawn_On_The_Move/" title="Lucas &amp; Steve - Up Till Dawn (On The Move) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes when love is calling <br>I just try to take it slow oh <br>It’s gone the other morning <br>Like those angels in the snow oh <br>On our way <br>To the bay <br>Dazzled by the way <br>the sun shines <br>on your face O oh <br>If you say <br>You will stay <br>We could feel the love <br>and dance the night away <br>’Cause <br>Oh the night is young <br>We're drinking cocktails <br>in the sun <br>DJ plays that song <br>You and I go on and on <br>We’re just having fun <br>Feels so right it must be wrong <br>We’ll be up till dawn <br>Sometimes without warning <br>I go and give someone my soul <br>you know <br>You leave and leave me longing <br>For that special night once more <br>I’m up for more <br>On our way <br>To the bay <br>Dazzled by the way <br>the sun shines <br>on your face O oh <br>If you say <br>You will stay <br>We could feel the love <br>and dance the night away <br>’Cause <br>Oh the night is young <br>We're drinking cocktails <br>in the sun <br>DJ plays that song <br>You and I go on and on <br>We’re just having fun <br>Feels so right it must be wrong <br>We’ll be up till dawn <br>Heartbeat away <br>All it takes for love is <br>Just your heartbeat <br>And we can turn this thing <br>to something great <br>’Cause <br>Oh the night is young <br>We're drinking cocktails <br>in the sun <br>DJ plays that song <br>You and I go on and on <br>We’re just having fun <br>Feels so right it must be wrong <br>We’ll be up till dawn <br>We’ll be up till dawn <br>]]></content><category term="Lucas &amp; Steve" label="Lucas &amp; Steve"/><category term="Up Till Dawn (On The Move)" label="Up Till Dawn (On The Move)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CHiCO_with_HoneyWorks/プライド革命___Pride_Kakumei_프라이드_혁명_-_TV_애니_은혼_OP_테마곡/</id><title>CHiCO with HoneyWorks - プライド革命 / Pride Kakumei (프라이드 혁명) - TV 애니 `은혼` OP 테마곡 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:46:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:46:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CHiCO_with_HoneyWorks/%E3%83%97%E3%83%A9%E3%82%A4%E3%83%89%E9%9D%A9%E5%91%BD___Pride_Kakumei_%ED%94%84%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EB%93%9C_%ED%98%81%EB%AA%85_-_TV_%EC%95%A0%EB%8B%88_%EC%9D%80%ED%98%BC_OP_%ED%85%8C%EB%A7%88%EA%B3%A1/" title="CHiCO with HoneyWorks - プライド革命 / Pride Kakumei (프라이드 혁명) - TV 애니 `은혼` OP 테마곡 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[리소- 다케오 쿠치니시테타 카코 <br> 카베와 도코니닷테 타치 후사이데 <br> 테사구리데 이키테쿠 <br>아카이 소라가 카게오 노바스 <br> 마다 소레와 타요리 나쿠테 지분 캇테 <br>타메이키오 코보스 <br> 치가우 호하바 아와나이 코큐데모 <br> 키미와 맛스구니 부츠캇테 <br>소바니 이테 쿠레루 <br> 스레치가이 미와타세바 소- 토리노코 사레테이타 <br>아스와 미에테 마스카 <br>쿠라야미 카키케스 키미노 코에가 키코에탄다 <br>요와쿠탓테 타치 무카운다 <br>리유-나라 키미니 모랏타 <br>와캇테루 타카라 이쿤다요 <br>이마모 쿠루시쿳테 무네가 이타이요 <br>치카라나라 키미니 모라사 <br> 마모리누쿠 타메니 이쿤다요 <br>마케테 바카리 마모루 모노모 나이 <br> 손나 지신 나쿠테 시아이 호-키 <br>이이와케오 코보스 <br>도코카라 토나쿠 미미오 사시타 코에 <br>키미와 맛스구니 부츠카레 읏테 <br>쿠야시 소-니 나게쿠 <br> 후레아에바 무네노 오쿠니 도소쿠데 후미콘데 <br>아스와 키미가 키메로 <br>쿠라야미 카케케스 키미노 코에와 나이테 이타 <br>나미다난테 후리하라운다 <br>리유-나라 보쿠가 츠쿳타 <br> 와캇테루 다카라 이쿤다요 <br>이마모 코와쿠낫테 아시가 스쿤데 <br> 혼토-와 후루에테룬다 <br>토리 모도스 타메니 타타카우요 <br>타치 무카우 <br>코와쿠 나이 <br>키미가이루 <br>코코니이루 <br>맛테이테 <br>다이죠-부 <br> 마케나이요 <br> 미토메테루 <br>사아 후미콘데 스스문다 <br>토도쿠마데 와라에 <br>코에니 나라나이 사케비 코에가 <br>무네노 나카 후루에테룬다 <br>와캇테루 다카라 타타카우요 <br>이미와 히토리쟈나이 <br>무네가 아츠이요 <br>치카라나라 키미니 모랏타 <br>마모리 누쿠 타메니 타타카우요 <br>키미토 마타 와랏테루]]></content><category term="CHiCO with HoneyWorks" label="CHiCO with HoneyWorks"/><category term="プライド革命 / Pride Kakumei (프라이드 혁명) - TV 애니 `은혼` OP 테마곡" label="プライド革命 / Pride Kakumei (프라이드 혁명) - TV 애니 `은혼` OP 테마곡"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CHiCO_with_HoneyWorks/世界は恋に落ちている___Sekai_Wa_Koi_Ni_Ochiteiru_세상은_사랑에_빠져있어_-_TV_애니_아오하라이드_OP_테마곡/</id><title>CHiCO with HoneyWorks - 世界は恋に落ちている / Sekai Wa Koi Ni Ochiteiru (세상은 사랑에 빠져있어) - TV 애니 `아오하라이드` OP 테마곡 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:46:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:46:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CHiCO_with_HoneyWorks/%E4%B8%96%E7%95%8C%E3%81%AF%E6%81%8B%E3%81%AB%E8%90%BD%E3%81%A1%E3%81%A6%E3%81%84%E3%82%8B___Sekai_Wa_Koi_Ni_Ochiteiru_%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81%EC%9D%80_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%97%90_%EB%B9%A0%EC%A0%B8%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4_-_TV_%EC%95%A0%EB%8B%88_%EC%95%84%EC%98%A4%ED%95%98%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EB%93%9C_OP_%ED%85%8C%EB%A7%88%EA%B3%A1/" title="CHiCO with HoneyWorks - 世界は恋に落ちている / Sekai Wa Koi Ni Ochiteiru (세상은 사랑에 빠져있어) - TV 애니 `아오하라이드` OP 테마곡 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세카이와 코이니 오치테이루 <br>히카리노야 무네오 사스 <br>키미오 와카리타인다요 <br>네에 오시에테 <br>스레치가우 코토바니 <br>춋토다케노 코-카이 <br>나미다 코보레테 <br>이소가시이 칸죠오 <br>코도-니 링쿠스루 <br>츄-닝구 <br>타시카메타인다 <br>모쿠테키밧카니 토라와레테 <br>다이지나 모노가 카슨데 니게테 <br>쿄-모 리스타-토 <br>세카이와 코이니 오치테이루 <br>히카리노야 무네오 사스 <br>젠부 와카리타인다요 <br>네에 키카세테 <br>탓타 이치미리가 토-쿠테 <br>카케누케타 히비니 <br>와스레나이 와스레라레나이 <br>카가야쿠 이치 페-지 <br>오니아이노 후타리니 <br>난다카 후쿠자츠나 <br>키모치가 이루요 <br>하지메테노 칸죠오 <br>코도-니 링쿠스루 <br>타이온케 <br>코와레챳타카나 <br>지분노 코토 와카라나이 마마 <br>아노 코니 아도바이스마데 시챳테 <br>무네가 이타이야 <br>세카이와 코이니 오치테이루 <br>히카리노야 무네오 사스 <br>키즈이타 코노 오모이와 <br>모우 오소이노 <br>아노 코노 호-가 카와이이노 <br>싯테루요 다케도 <br>우마쿠 이카나이데 난테네 <br>니게다시타 쿠세니 <br>바카 <br>키미노 코토 젠부 <br>와카리타잇테 오못챠우 <br>코레가 코이닷테 <br>하지메테 키즈이타노 <br>젯타이 후리무이테 호시이 <br>오소캇타케도 아키라메타쿠나이 <br>닷테 <br>스키다카라 <br>하루니 사이타 하나가 코이오 시타 <br>하나와 힛시니 <br>우에오 무이테 와랏타 <br>아오이 나츠노 <br>츠보미모 코이오 시타 <br>사카나이 하나토 카야쿠노 니오이 <br>혼토노 키모치 코토바니시테 <br>다이지나 코토 하나세타라 <br>쿄-모 리스타-토 <br>돈칸나 키미다카라 <br>쿠치니 다시테 이와나캬 <br>이마 키미니 츠타에루요 <br>네에 스키데스 <br>세카이와 코이니 오치테이루 <br>히카리노야 무네오 사스 <br>젠부 와카리타인다요 <br>네에 키카세테 <br>타구리 요세테 모- 제로센치 <br>카케누케타 히비니 <br>와스레나이 와스레라레나이 <br>카가야쿠 이치 페-지 <br>]]></content><category term="CHiCO with HoneyWorks" label="CHiCO with HoneyWorks"/><category term="世界は恋に落ちている / Sekai Wa Koi Ni Ochiteiru (세상은 사랑에 빠져있어) - TV 애니 `아오하라이드` OP 테마곡" label="世界は恋に落ちている / Sekai Wa Koi Ni Ochiteiru (세상은 사랑에 빠져있어) - TV 애니 `아오하라이드` OP 테마곡"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christopher/Naked_Unplugged/</id><title>Christopher - Naked (Unplugged) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:47:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:47:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christopher/Naked_Unplugged/" title="Christopher - Naked (Unplugged) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Body talk body lock <br>Daylight dreaming <br>You and I late at night <br>TV screaming <br>We don't have to say a word <br>We don't have to say a word about it <br>Pink noise white lie's and <br>Heavy breathing <br>Silhouettes in the dark <br>Got me feeling <br>Like we don't have to save the world <br>We don't have to <br>cause you know what we can do <br>In this hotel room <br>We're in slow motion <br>Waves in this ocean <br>Crashing over us under us <br><br>I like us better when we're naked <br>We dress up only to take it off <br>And there's no easy way to say this <br>I like us better when we're naked <br><br>Take it off dry lips <br>Lipstick on my pillow <br>You know there's a storm <br>Raging outside our window <br>And we're in here <br>And we're in here <br>But it's so bitter sweet <br>That love's so hard to cheat <br>We're the perfect disaster ashes to ashes <br>We're alone but you should know <br><br>I like us better when we're naked <br>We dress up only to take it off <br>And there's no easy way to say this <br>I like us better when we're naked <br>So take it off <br>Take it off <br>Take it off <br>We're naked <br><br>But it's to bitter sweet <br>That love's so hard to cheat <br>We're the perfect disaster ashes to ashes <br>We're alone but you should know <br><br>I like us better when we're naked <br>We dress up only to take it off <br>And there's no easy way to say this <br>I like us better when we're naked naked <br>I like us better when we're naked <br>We dress up only to take it off <br>No easy way to say this <br>I like us better when we're naked <br>So take it off]]></content><category term="Christopher" label="Christopher"/><category term="Naked (Unplugged)" label="Naked (Unplugged)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nishino_Kana/Story/</id><title>Nishino Kana - Story - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:47:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:47:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nishino_Kana/Story/" title="Nishino Kana - Story - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[소레데모 킷토 <br>마치갓테 이나이요네 <br>와타시타치노 Story <br>이마마데모 코레카라모 <br>마요이나가라 <br>Just let it go <br>아노 히니 모도리타잇테 <br>모우 난넨 마에닷케 <br>키즈케바 토오이 <br>무카시노 하나시데 <br>Uh 아이소 와라이오 미가이테 <br>Uh 바카나 코토와 아키라메테 <br>오토나니 나라나캬 <br>이케나이노카나 <br>오타가이 히토노 유메나라 <br>오우엔 데키루노니네 <br>Oh Yeah <br>I just don't know why <br>소레데모 킷토 <br>마치갓테이나이요네 <br>와타시타치노 Story <br>미라이노 혼노 <br>이치부가 미에나쿠테 <br>Give up Never Give up <br>쿠리카에시테 Try <br>미가카레루 Style <br>이츠카 혼토우노 유메오 <br>미츠케루 소노 히마데 <br>Trying Trying <br>난도데모 So just let it go <br>시아와세니 나리타잇테 <br>모우 난카이메닷케 <br>키즈케바 오나지 싯파이바나시데 <br>Uh 아이타이 키모치 가쿠시테 <br>Uh 와가마마난테 이와나이데 <br>오토나니 나라나캬 <br>이케나이노카나 <br>오타가이 히토노 코이나라 <br>레이세이니 나레루노니네 <br>Oh Yeah <br>I just don't know why <br>소레데모 킷토 <br>마치갓테 이나이요네 <br>와타시타치노 Story <br>코코로노 혼노 <br>이치부가 이타이다케 <br>Hello Goodbye Hello <br>쿠리카에시테 Cry <br>츠요쿠나루 Heart <br>이츠카 혼토우노 코이오 <br>미츠케루 소노 히마데 <br>Crying Crying <br>난도데모 So just let it go <br>I don't know what should I do <br>I don't know what I want to do <br>도코에 무카우노 코노 사키와 <br>Nobody knows the way it's gonna be <br>Everything depends on me <br>코노 테데 스베테오 <br>에가이테쿠 Story <br>에가오모 나미다모 <br>키레이나 오모이데모 <br>와타시타치노 Story <br>마다마다 츠즈키가 <br>아루카라 카나시미니 <br>Goodbye All right All right <br>Just let it go <br>소레데모 킷토 <br>마치갓테 이나이요네 <br>와타시타치노 Story <br>미라이노 혼노 <br>이치부가 미에나쿠테 <br>Give up Never Give up <br>쿠리카에시테 Try <br>미가카레루 Style <br>이츠카 혼토우노 와타시오 <br>미츠케루 소노 히마데 <br>Trying Trying <br>난도데모 So just let it go <br>Just let it go <br>Just let it go <br>]]></content><category term="Nishino Kana" label="Nishino Kana"/><category term="Story" label="Story"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/렉스디/좋은_방법/</id><title>렉스디 - 좋은 방법 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:48:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:48:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%89%EC%8A%A4%EB%94%94/%EC%A2%8B%EC%9D%80_%EB%B0%A9%EB%B2%95/" title="렉스디 - 좋은 방법 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[hey 잘 지내 <br>여전히 아침 겸 점심 해결엔 <br>또 베이글로 대충 때우고 그래 <br>나는 네 덕에 일찍 일어나 <br>밥 먹고 산책해 <br>hey 일은 어때 <br>개강도 했으니까 바쁘지 <br>미팅은 언제 해 <br>하루빨리 좋은 작품이나 <br>공연하면 좋은데 <br>네가 싫을 수 있으니 <br>한 번만 몰래 보러 갈게 <br>살살해 줘 이제 시간도 <br>많이 갔으니까 막말로 <br>그때 죽을 죄를 지었던 건 <br>아니니까 물론 잘못한 내가 <br>할 소린 아니지 참 미안해 <br>그때나 지금이나 <br>존나 멍청하게 그저 맨날 미안 <br>한 나도 내가 한심해 열심히 작업이나 <br>하는 중 이게 내가 택한 좋은 방법이야 <br>널 잊을 방법 기다리는 법이 같아 <br>멀리서 봐도 네가 아직 좋은 건 맞아 <br>변하지 않아 내가 힘들어해 봤자 <br>차라리 너도 그때의 날 잊고 살아 <br>이 모든 게 너와 날 위한 <br>가장 좋은 방법 <br>널 잊을 좋은 방법 <br>기다릴 좋은 방법 <br>어떤 시작이 와도 <br>가장 좋은 방법 <br>다시 돌아와도 <br>오지 않아도 <br>가장 좋은 방법 <br>나 원래 찡찡대는 거 알고 있지 넌 <br>네 예상대로 너와 헤어진 그 뒤로 <br>죄 없는 내 친구들은 고생이고 <br>평생 이렇게 하다간 친구들마저도 <br>잃어버릴까 봐 요즘에 <br>혼자 걷기도 하고 <br>혼자서 커피도 마셔 <br>혼자 영화를 보기도 하고 <br>또 무관심했던 <br>날씨에 영향도 많이 받고 네 덕에 <br>이기적인 날 돌아보며 <br>사람 공부 많이 해 <br>넌 어때 아직 술은 좋아하니 걱정돼 <br>잔뜩 취하면 귀가 본능 여전해 <br>이제 이런 걱정해주는 <br>누군가는 어떤 애일까 <br>다 여전해 <br>혜수 지영이 현진이는 어떻게 <br>여전히 밝게 지내는지 <br>괜히 궁금해하는 중 <br>넌 안 궁금하겠지만 <br>난 곡에 널 소중히 기록하는 중 <br>널 잊을 방법 기다리는 법이 같아 <br>멀리서 봐도 네가 아직 좋은 건 맞아 <br>변하지 않아 내가 힘들어해 봤자 <br>차라리 너도 그때의 날 잊고 살아 <br>이 모든 게 너와 날 위한 <br>가장 좋은 방법 <br>널 잊을 좋은 방법 <br>기다릴 좋은 방법 <br>어떤 시작이 와도 <br>가장 좋은 방법 <br>다시 돌아와도 <br>오지 않아도 <br>가장 좋은 방법 <br>베이글 떡볶이 혜화 <br>가비아노 묵전 중대 앞 <br>봉피양 을지면옥 보라메나 <br>파스꾸찌 탐탐 삐삐네나 <br>제주일기 형 웨딩판타지 <br>도토리 삼천포 노래방 <br>이태원 경리단 또 신대방 <br>이수 논현동 또 그밖에 많은 <br>곳에 다 묻어있지만 지우진 않을게 <br>혹 다른 사람 만나도 그냥 말할게 <br>뭐 앨범으로 남은 이런 마당에 <br>너한텐 했지만 나도 이상한 게 <br>너도 알지만 난 노래로는 거짓말 안 해 <br>그리고 이제 살면서 거짓말 안 해 <br>거짓말 안 하는 김에 이건 말할게 <br>내 모자 가져와 아끼는 거니까 <br>농담 아님 <br>널 잊을 방법 기다리는 법이 같아 <br>멀리서 봐도 네가 아직 좋은 건 맞아 <br>변하지 않아 내가 힘들어해 봤자 <br>차라리 너도 그때의 날 잊고 살아 <br>이 모든 게 너와 날 위한 <br>가장 좋은 방법 <br>널 잊을 좋은 방법 <br>기다릴 좋은 방법 <br>어떤 시작이 와도 <br>가장 좋은 방법 <br>다시 돌아와도 <br>오지 않아도 <br>가장 좋은 방법 <br>]]></content><category term="렉스디" label="렉스디"/><category term="좋은 방법" label="좋은 방법"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/렉스디/170220/</id><title>렉스디 - 170220 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:48:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:48:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%89%EC%8A%A4%EB%94%94/170220/" title="렉스디 - 170220 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[happy birthday to you <br>큰 선물과 cake 앞에 두고 <br>happy birthday to you <br>네가 없어도 <br>happy birthday to you <br>결국 이 가사를 쓰게 됐네 <br>죽기보다 싫었던 걸 <br>이젠 인정해야 돼 <br>난 너에게 해준 게 많다 생각했어 <br>그래서 이렇게 쉽게 떠난 걸 <br>부정하려 애썼어 근데 <br>너도 첫 만남부터 내게 <br>준 게 많아 많은 돈과 시간 <br>이런 걸 말하는 게 아냐 <br>이제야 알았어 널 위할 <br>자격이나 연애할 자격이 <br>없던 놈이었단 걸 3자로서 내가 날 <br>냉철하게 보게 해준 네게 <br>진짜 고맙단 말 <br>우연히 마주치면 꼭 하고 싶어 <br>언제가 됐던 간 <br>평생 기억에 남을 <br>내 29번째 생일날을 <br>선사해준 것도 감사하지 <br>절대 비꼬는 말 아냐 <br>왜 그랬을까 후회는 항상 늦고 <br>쏟은 물은 순식간 <br>네가 싫어할 게 싫어 <br>네가 싫어하는 거짓말 <br>했던 나보다 알아챈 널 <br>원망해 편해질까 <br>happy birthday to you <br>큰 선물과 cake 앞에 두고 <br>happy birthday to you <br>니가 없어도 <br>happy birthday to you <br>솔직한 서로의 모습 <br>인정하는 게 <br>오래가는 연애란 말 <br>진짜로 맞긴 맞는데 <br>난 너랑 싸우면 친구들끼리 <br>니 뒷담 까는 앤데 <br>이런 모습들까지 솔직할 <br>깡은 없지 감히 넌데 <br>유독 거짓말을 싫어하던 네게 난 <br>꾸밈없기엔 무서웠나 봐 <br>늦은 자책해봐 도 <br>이젠 너무 멀리 왔나 봐 <br>아무리 생각해봐도 <br>니 맘을 다시 돌릴 <br>방법은 없어 책에 봐도 <br>종종 생각하곤 해 첫 번째 <br>이별 이전에 우리 연애를 <br>진짜 짧긴 짧았어도 매번 <br>붙어있을 만큼 잘 통했던 <br>우리였지만 이제 난 너한테 <br>대죄인이 됐어 <br>넌 화가 나면 <br>많은 시간이 필요하고 <br>사과조차 필요 없단 걸 알아서 <br>부디 홧김에 떠났다고 믿고 <br>별 수 없이 기다리고 있어 <br>다른 여잔 많아도 네가 아니여서 <br>happy birthday to you <br>큰 선물과 cake 앞에 두고 <br>happy birthday to you <br>네가 없어도 <br>happy birthday to you <br>앨범이 나온 후 <br>누군가의 옆의 널 <br>발견하게 되더라도 분명히 <br>어쩔 수 없을 거야 <br>넌 내 인생으로 와서 <br>이젠 내 career가 되어 <br>평생 지우지 못할 <br>좋은 추억에 남길 거야 <br>네가 두고 간 건 달랑 <br>생일 케이크 하나가 아냐 <br>내가 얼마나 찌질이인지 <br>알게 됐고 이젠 아냐 <br>이건 네가 준 가장 큰 선물이고 <br>그날 남아 있던 케이크엔 <br>곰팡이 폈지만 <br>널 기다릴 난 남아 있어 <br>happy birthday to you <br>큰 선물과 cake 앞에 두고 <br>happy birthday to you <br>네가 없어도 <br>happy birthday to you <br>]]></content><category term="렉스디" label="렉스디"/><category term="170220" label="170220"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/렉스디/하고_있어/</id><title>렉스디 - 하고 있어 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:48:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:48:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%89%EC%8A%A4%EB%94%94/%ED%95%98%EA%B3%A0_%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4/" title="렉스디 - 하고 있어 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[연애를 하고 있어 <br>좋은 남자이길 <br>그냥 네게 묻고 싶어 <br>좋은 남자인지 <br>넌 존재 자체가 예뻐 <br>좋은 여자인지 <br>중요치 않아 뭘 해도 널 원하지 <br>랩을 하고 있어 네 남자로 <br>그래 랩을 하고 있어 <br>그냥 나로서도 <br>랩을 하고 있어 네 친구로 <br>쇼미 나가 스타가 되면 <br>좋은 아들로 <br>약을 먹고 있어 술 담배도 <br>건강 걱정하고 있어 네가 매번 <br>건강 걱정하고 있어 내 친구들도 <br>요즘 나랑 잘 안 마셔 <br>내 걱정 땜에 <br>혼자 살고 있어 개 한 마리와 <br>밥 좀 제때 챙겨 먹어 <br>다 잔소리야 <br>정훈이 산책 시켜 <br>또 잔소리야 <br>밤에 작업 좀 해 작업 <br>걱정하고 있어 <br>내 통장 잔고를 <br>돈 좀 아껴서 써 <br>빌려 써 버릇 말고 <br>너도 나와 있고 싶어 <br>내일도 모래도 <br>너도 나와 먹고 싶어 <br>맛집에 가서 <br>밤엔 술도 먹고 싶어 <br>그래 나도 그러고 싶어 <br>버는 돈이 모자라도 <br>너에겐 대책 없이 미쳐 <br>쓰고 싶어 <br>노력하고 있어 <br>나도 노력하고 있어 <br>그냥 위로 받고 싶어 <br>위로 받고 싶어 <br>궁금해하고 있어 <br>좋은 남자인지 <br>또 궁금해하고 있어 <br>좋은 친구인지 <br>궁금해하고 싶어 <br>좋은 아들일지 <br>내가 어디가 좋아서 <br>모두 남아있지 <br>사과하고 있어 <br>화난 너에게 <br>네가 화가 나면 필요해 시간이 <br>so 기다리고 있어 <br>불안해하며 <br>기다리고 있어 <br>이별을 겪고 있어 <br>내 실수로 <br>시간을 돌려놓고 싶어 <br>죽고 싶도록 <br>변명하고 싶어 <br>너 있는 곳 어디든 <br>당장 달려가서 <br>넌 내게 화가 나서 <br>날 차버렸고 <br>넌 화가 많이 나면 <br>미안하단 말도 <br>듣기 싫어해 알아 <br>so 잡지 못해 <br>내가 반성하면 <br>돌아와 줄래 <br>내가 힘들어하면 <br>모두들 그래 <br>그 감정에 작업하면서 <br>널 기다리면 <br>남자답게 아무렇지 않은 듯 <br>열심히 살고 있다 보면 <br>돌아올 수도 <br>]]></content><category term="렉스디" label="렉스디"/><category term="하고 있어" label="하고 있어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/렉스디/편한_대로/</id><title>렉스디 - 편한 대로 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:48:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:48:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%89%EC%8A%A4%EB%94%94/%ED%8E%B8%ED%95%9C_%EB%8C%80%EB%A1%9C/" title="렉스디 - 편한 대로 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 자꾸 편한 대로 하라고 해 <br>그냥 너무 보고 싶다고 <br>하면 나가잖아 <br>아무 때나 불러도 갈게 <br>내가 더 보고 싶은 거 <br>네가 잘 알잖아 <br>어제 너와 마신 <br>술이 다 깰 때쯤엔 <br>바로 네가 보고 싶어서 <br>또 연락을 해 <br>안 그래도 <br>우리 너무 쭉 붙어있어서 <br>요즘 소홀했던 <br>작업은 해야겠지만 <br>아무래도 <br>요즘 내 일상의 100이 넌데 <br>다른 가사는 재미없네 <br>그래서 널 위한 노래를 적으려 <br>메모장을 폈네 근데 <br>그때쯤 울린 폰 바로 너 <br>너는 오늘 밤 친구들과 <br>술자릴 가질 테니 <br>나보고 올라면 오래 <br>그래 편한 대로 하래 <br>그럼 내가 지금은 <br>불편하냐 왜 이래 <br>야야 그냥 보고 싶다고 <br>하면 될 거 아냐 <br>그럼 내가 뭐 부담스럽다라고 <br>안 나갈 것 같냐 <br>난 네 친구 아니고 애인 <br>그래 넌 불러 날 soulmate <br>이라지만 더 나를 원해 <br>보이게 불러줬음 해 <br>난 네가 보고 싶을 땐 <br>네 사정도 안 궁금해 <br>조커가 할리를 원할 때처럼 <br>나쁜 마음도 품네 <br>왜 자꾸 편한 대로 하라고 해 <br>그냥 너무 보고 싶다고 <br>하면 나가잖아 <br>아무 때나 불러도 갈게 <br>내가 더 보고 싶은 거 <br>네가 잘 알잖아 <br>난 항상 wait for you <br>그래 매일 보는 <br>너라도 친구 대신 널 만날 거야 난 <br>네가 책을 보든 또 영화를 보든 <br>널 방해하지 않고 너만 볼 거야 <br>나이 서른 먹도록 <br>내가 가장 많이 한 건 <br>연애라 생각했어서 <br>널 다 안다고 착각했나 봐 <br>네가 날 편한 대로 <br>하라고 할 때면 그게 참 <br>유치하게도 싫지만 <br>cool한 척 꾹 참네 <br>네가 그럴 때마다 <br>묘한 거리감이 느껴져 <br>너의 주변엔 아주 가까운 <br>남사친들이 있어서 <br>난 질투하는 마음 피곤하니 <br>숨기곤 하지만 이건 알지 <br>그 친구들과 내 차이가 <br>뭔지 더 확실하길 욕심이 나지 <br>넌 말할 거야 분명 그게 배려라고 <br>이럴 땐 누나 같네 아주 최고라고 <br>편한 대로 그래 편한 대로 해 <br>새벽에라도 보고 싶다 하면 <br>talk만 하면 돼 <br>난 네 친구 아니고 애인 <br>그래 넌 불러 날 soulmate <br>이라지만 더 나를 원해 <br>보이게 불러줬음 해 <br>난 네가 보고 싶을 땐 <br>네 사정도 안 궁금해 <br>조커가 할리를 원할 때처럼 <br>나쁜 마음도 품네 <br>왜 자꾸 편한 대로 하라고 해 <br>그냥 너무 보고 싶다고 <br>하면 나가잖아 <br>아무 때나 불러도 갈게 <br>내가 더 보고 싶은 거 <br>네가 잘 알잖아 <br>난 항상 wait for you <br>그래 매일 보는 <br>너라도 친구 대신 널 만날 거야 난 <br>니가 책을 보든 또 영화를 보든 <br>널 방해하지 않고 너만 볼 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="렉스디" label="렉스디"/><category term="편한 대로" label="편한 대로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/렉스디/파스꾸찌_PASCUCCI/</id><title>렉스디 - 파스꾸찌 (PASCUCCI) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:48:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:48:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%89%EC%8A%A4%EB%94%94/%ED%8C%8C%EC%8A%A4%EA%BE%B8%EC%B0%8C_PASCUCCI/" title="렉스디 - 파스꾸찌 (PASCUCCI) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어느샌가 네가 많이 <br>묻어있는 내 방안엔 <br>하나둘 널 위한 물건이 <br>이를테면 저기 화장대 <br>네 옷에 밴 담배 냄새를 <br>항상 걱정했잖아 <br>집 가서 혼난대서 <br>내가 향도 사놨잖아 <br>집에서 걱정하는 거 알아 다만 <br>너무 서둘러 가지 말아줘 <br>또 혼자 남잖아 <br>넌 다녀가지만 <br>네 베개와 이 방 <br>우리 이야기가 잔뜩 담긴 이 방에 <br>또 혼자 남아서 <br>정리하다 보면 <br>어제 우리 이야긴 <br>혼자 나눠야 하잖아 <br>그냥 데려다줄게 집 근처까지만 <br>혹시나 많이 안 혼나면 또 나와줄래 <br>몇 시간이든 늘 널 기다리던 <br>거기서 기다릴게 <br>좋게 생각해줘 자꾸 이래서 미안해 <br>금방 나와줘 고마워 <br>오늘은 일찍 갈게 <br>]]></content><category term="렉스디" label="렉스디"/><category term="파스꾸찌 (PASCUCCI)" label="파스꾸찌 (PASCUCCI)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/렉스디/발냄새/</id><title>렉스디 - 발냄새 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:48:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:48:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%89%EC%8A%A4%EB%94%94/%EB%B0%9C%EB%83%84%EC%83%88/" title="렉스디 - 발냄새 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 위해 무슨 노래를 <br>만들까 고민했어 <br>과장 않고 100번은 한 내 연애에서 <br>누군가를 얻기 위한 <br>노래나 아님 차이고 <br>나서 만든 노래만 있는 거 알지 <br>그래 넌 예뻐 아주 불안할 정도로 <br>그래 왜겠어 넌 배우 지망생이니까 <br>너의 데뷔작이 나의 MV면 해서 <br>그 안의 네 모습이 눈부시게 예뻐 <br>랑데뷰 뮤비에서 나온 걔보다 예뻐 <br>네가 성공하는 큰 꿈을 꾸기도 했어 <br>근데 아직도 모르겠어 <br>너의 어떤 모습을 담아 <br>노래로 잘 다듬어 <br>인스타그램의 6000여 명이 아닌 <br>바로 온 세상이 아는 <br>노래의 주제가 아직도 <br>그러다 문득 떠오른 너의 발에 <br>냄새가 안 났다는 게 신기하네 <br>넌 발냄새가 왜 안 나니 <br>내 방에 놓인 네 양말에 <br>섬유 냄새만 은은하네 <br>너 가고 나면 뭐가 남지 <br>넌 발냄새가 왜 안 나니 <br>금방 들어온 내 방안엔 <br>내 발냄새만 은은하네 <br>너 가고 나면 뭐가 남지 <br>소름 끼치게 네가 너무 좋아 <br>내 모든 연애의 여자친구들 다 <br>전부 발냄새가 나서 <br>자주 놀리고 놀았어 <br>근데 넌 이것조차도 <br>전혀 놀릴 게 없잖아 <br>네 몸에서 내 입은 피할 곳이 없어 <br>네게 키스하면 발끝에 벌써 <br>내 입술이 와있고 이건 참을 수 없어 <br>다시 올라가 널 보면 <br>그땐 잠들 수 없어 <br>아침이 오면 네가 벗어놓은 <br>양말을 신고 집에 가지 <br>어제 그 양말은 <br>오늘도 뽀송하고 네가 <br>가고 나면 아무 냄새도 남지 않지 <br>너무 아쉬운 마음에 침대를 정리하다 <br>긴 너의 머리카락 발견하고는 <br>미소를 짓기도 해 <br>넌 미안해하지만 난 이것들을 모아 <br>인형을 만들어버리고 잘 때 <br>안고 싶을 정도 <br>아니 그 이상 그 정도로 <br>네가 너무 좋아 <br>이런 사랑 노래는 <br>아마 세상에 없을 거고 <br>난 네 발에 관한 추억을 <br>다 자랑할 거야 <br>넌 발냄새가 왜 안 나니 <br>금방 들어온 내 방안엔 <br>내 발냄새만 은은하네 <br>너 가고 나면 뭐가 남지 <br>]]></content><category term="렉스디" label="렉스디"/><category term="발냄새" label="발냄새"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/렉스디/음악_들으러_갈래/</id><title>렉스디 - 음악 들으러 갈래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-08T13:48:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-08T13:48:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%89%EC%8A%A4%EB%94%94/%EC%9D%8C%EC%95%85_%EB%93%A4%EC%9C%BC%EB%9F%AC_%EA%B0%88%EB%9E%98/" title="렉스디 - 음악 들으러 갈래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 집에 음악 들으러 갈래 <br>아님 귀여운 강아지 보러 갈래 <br>다른 뜻은 없어 단지 너와 함께 <br>지금은 아직 떨어지지 않고 싶을 뿐 <br>네가 더 이상은 술이 무리라는 말에 <br>난 조금 당황해서 <br>바로 천천히 마시라고 바로 말해 <br>만난 지 두 시간도 안돼서 <br>네가 집에 가야 할 것 같다는 말에 <br>난 생각 없이 말했어 <br>한 다섯 잔만 쉬었다 <br>마시는 건 어때 <br>너 원래 술이 약해 <br>이제부터 이야기가 재밌지 <br>넌 괜한 술 자존심이 강했어 <br>갑자기 돌변한 채로 더 마실 수 <br>있다고 했고 우린 2차로 향했어 <br>그래 짠해 짠해 짠해 <br>네가 예뻐 불안해하네 나는 <br>눈웃음이 말해 아주 많은 <br>오빠들이 talk 할 것 같네 주말에 <br>우리 집에 음악 들으러 갈래 <br>아님 귀여운 강아지 보러 갈래 <br>다른 뜻은 없어 단지 너와 함께 <br>지금은 아직 떨어지지 않고 싶을 뿐 <br>안 건드려 그저 술이 더 마시고파 <br>곧 나올 노래들이 잔뜩 있어 오빠네 <br>취해 보여도 원래 잘 마셔 걱정 마 <br>난 이 상태로 오래가 <br>아이폰 1프로같이 <br>우리가 2차로 어딜 갔든 <br>그건 중요하지 않아 근데 가끔 <br>우연히 압구정 포차를 지나갈 땐 <br>네가 생각나는 건 <br>어쩔 수 없지 Goddam <br>제일 기억에 남는 건 니가 <br>술이 깰 정도로 예뻤다던 기억 <br>연애에 대해서 서로 이야기할 때 <br>소름 끼치도록 잘 통해서 <br>널 놓치기 싫어서 <br>곧바로 말했지 <br>너도 날 마음에 들어 하겠지 싶어 <br>망설임 없이 말했어 <br>우리 집에서 음악 들으러 갈래 <br>무안하게도 넌 거절을 했고 <br>대신 노래방에서라도 내 노랠 <br>들어보고 싶단 네 말에 Thank God <br>세상은 아직 살만해 <br>우리 집에 음악 들으러 갈래 <br>아님 귀여운 강아지 보러 갈래 <br>다른 뜻은 없어 단지 너와 함께 <br>지금은 아직 떨어지지 않고 싶을 뿐 <br>안 건드려 그저 술이 더 마시고파 <br>곧 나올 노래들이 잔뜩 있어 오빠네 <br>취해 보여도 원래 잘 마셔 걱정 마 <br>난 이 상태로 오래가 <br>아이폰 1프로같이 <br>노래방에서의 수줍은 나를 봐 <br>그날 뭘 부른지도 기억이 잘 <br>나지 않아도 날 보던 네 얼굴이 <br>지겹게 말하지만 <br>넌 참 눈웃음이 very good <br>1절만 부르고 끄던 내가 <br>귀여웠단 네 말이 생각나 <br>너는 노래를 하지는 않았지만 <br>나를 바라보던 <br>네 얼굴이 계속 생각나 <br>우리 집에 음악 들으러 갈래 <br>아님 귀여운 강아지 보러 갈래 <br>다른 뜻은 없어 단지 너와 함께 <br>지금은 아직 떨어지지 않고 싶을 뿐 <br>우리 집에 음악 들으러 갈래 <br>아님 귀여운 강아지 보러 갈래 <br>다른 뜻은 없어 단지 너와 함께 <br>지금은 아직 떨어지지 않고 싶을 뿐 <br>안 건드려 그저 술이 더 마시고파 <br>곧 나올 노래들이 잔뜩 있어 오빠네 <br>취해 보여도 원래 잘 마셔 걱정 마 <br>난 이 상태로 오래가 <br>아이폰 1프로같이 <br>]]></content><category term="렉스디" label="렉스디"/><category term="음악 들으러 갈래" label="음악 들으러 갈래"/></entry></feed>