<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:49:49+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마블제이_MarvelJ/뭐없녜_Feat_베이식_빅트레이_Bonus_track/</id><title>마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 뭐없녜 (Feat. 베이식, 빅트레이) (Bonus track) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:49:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:49:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%B8%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4_MarvelJ/%EB%AD%90%EC%97%86%EB%85%9C_Feat_%EB%B2%A0%EC%9D%B4%EC%8B%9D_%EB%B9%85%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_Bonus_track/" title="마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 뭐없녜 (Feat. 베이식, 빅트레이) (Bonus track) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[얼마 전에 강남 클럽을 갔네 <br>많은 남녀들이 매력을 뽐내 <br>그리고 나는 걔네 보다 우월해 <br>라고 생각했던 것도 <br>잠시 잠시뿐 이였지 <br>그런데 그 때 들어오던 <br>키 작은 추남 랩퍼 <br>그는 여자들을 전부 죽여놨지 <br>다들 그를 빨어 <br>그래 사실은 쇼미 <br>아니면 클럽 사파리서 <br>나가리 또 그리고 <br>잠시도 눈길조차도 안갈 놈 같다구 <br>더러운 내 열등감 더러운 내 열등감 <br>쇼미 2년 연속 1차 탈락 <br>gave me <br>좆같은 여러 가지 <br>더 말하기엔 치졸해 <br>보여서 입 닫았더니 <br>누군가는 오해하지 <br>내가 부족한 게 <br>실력으로 아가리가리 <br>부탁하지 다시 말하자면 <br>나는 절대 절대 부족하지 않아 <br>내가 부족한 건 오직 돈과 명성 <br>그리고 내게 군침 <br>흘릴 여자 ooh <br>저 좆밥이던 자식 셀피 <br>여자 댓글이 수백 개 <br>수많은 행사 억단위 money <br>이제부터 우리 꺼여야 해 <br>동진이형 물어봐 오늘 뭐 없녜 <br>비오형도 물어봐 요즘 뭐 없녜 <br>베이식형 물어봐 정말 뭐 없녜 <br>우리 형들 물어보네 오늘 밤 뭐 없녜 <br>뭐 없녜 뭐 없녜 뭐없녜 <br>allday allday allday <br>뭐 없녜 뭐 없녜 뭐 없녜 <br>뭐 있는 삶이 가득 차길 원해 <br>야 임마 뭐 없다 임마 <br>넌 라임만 생각할 짬이야 <br>쇼미 우승하고도 <br>끌어올리지 못하는 니 형 좀 봐 임마 <br>been there done <br>that muthafuckas used to go crazy <br>when i hit the club <br>방송인기 <br>fuck that hype 다 빌어먹어 <br>so im back on the mic <br>우승까지 하고 지레 겁먹고 냈던 <br>대중적인 곡들 <br>떠났다 컴백하자마자 <br>받은 스팟라잇 <br>그 후엔 다 욕들 <br>이제 와서 후회해봤자지 <br>poof there goes the mirage <br>인생 수업했다 치자기엔 <br>배 아픈 이윤 <br>행사가 다 쟤네 차지 <br>팔로워 수는 그대론데 <br>댓글은 좆도 없네 <br>언제부터 내가 이런 거 <br>신경 썼다고 그래 <br>다 fuck that <br>라고 자위나 해야지 <br>야 시발 뭐 없냐고 물은 건 <br>랩 할 비트 없냔 거다 <br>물론 침은 이빠이로 발랐지 <br>그 랩퍼가 잘나가는 건 <br>너보다 이룬 게 많아서야 <br>bro face facts <br>니가 나간 오디션 쟨 더 올라간 거야 <br>키 말고 랩으로 게임 셋 <br>시발 완전 꼰대 같은 개소리로 <br>동생 기나 죽이고 있네 <br>fuck it <br>가서 쟤 옆에 있는애 니가 다시 꼬셔 <br>꽤 찌질한 payback <br>동진이형 물어봐 오늘 뭐 없녜 <br>비오형도 물어봐 요즘 뭐 없녜 <br>베이식형 물어봐 정말 뭐 없녜 <br>우리형들 물어보네 오늘 밤 뭐 없녜 <br>뭐 없녜 뭐 없녜 뭐 없녜 <br>allday allday allday <br>뭐 없녜 뭐 없녜 뭐 없녜 <br>뭐 있는 삶이 가득 차길 원해 <br>Ay Ay 내동생 마블이 마블이 <br>별거 아닌 거 갖고 신경을 써 <br>걔네가 아무리 아무리 <br>날고 기어봐야 겨우 일년 <br>그 후엔 추운 겨울인걸 <br>봤잖아 벌써 어딨는지 <br>보이지도 않는 놈들이 태반인걸 <br>니 강아지들한테 물어봐 <br>걔네 랩 무대 개판이래 같이 풀어놔 <br>Money Fame <br>Fuck Bitches Everyday <br>쥐새끼들은 <br>잘 숨어라 곧 Break <br>Break Ya Fuckin’ Neck Uh <br>드러운 그 열등감이 <br>Rhyme을 토해내게 하지 <br>그게 다 돈으로 바뀌고 <br>콧대는 하늘에 닿지 <br>손목엔 Rollie 보단 AP <br>내 여자는 깔별로 Birkin <br>여행은 어디로 갈지 <br>고민 안 해 다 갈 거야 어디든 멀리 <br>니 미랜 내 머리처럼 빛나 <br>걱정 말고 하던 랩 계속해 <br>넌 특별하니까 <br>저 좆밥들은 내버려둬 <br>We Keep It Rollin' <br>아직 이룬 게 없어도 돼 <br>앞으로 이룰꺼니까 <br>동진이형 물어봐 오늘 뭐 없녜 <br>비오형도 물어봐 요즘 뭐 없녜 <br>베이식형 물어봐 정말 뭐 없녜 <br>우리형들 물어보네 오늘 밤 뭐 없녜 <br>뭐 없녜 뭐 없녜 뭐 없녜 <br>allday allday allday <br>뭐 없녜 뭐 없녜 뭐 없녜 <br>뭐 있는 삶이 가득 차길 원해 <br>]]></content><category term="마블제이 (Marvel.J)" label="마블제이 (Marvel.J)"/><category term="뭐없녜 (Feat. 베이식, 빅트레이) (Bonus track)" label="뭐없녜 (Feat. 베이식, 빅트레이) (Bonus track)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마블제이_MarvelJ/걸어/</id><title>마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 걸어 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:49:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:49:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%B8%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4_MarvelJ/%EA%B1%B8%EC%96%B4/" title="마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 걸어 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 밤도 나는 걸어 yeah <br>아무도 없는 도로 그 위에 난 <br>walkin' allday <br>목적지는 멀어 yeah <br>난 정처 없이 걸어 <br>이젠 어딘지도 모르겠네 <br>I said Im gon be allright <br>now fuck that <br>절로 숙여지는 고개 <br>오늘 밤도 나는 걸어 yeah <br>아무도 없는 도로 그 위에 난 <br>walkin' allday <br>너무 어두운 것 같어 <br>내 삶을 비추기엔 <br>빛을 발하기엔 <br>갈 길이 너무 멀어 <br>그런 생각을 했어 <br>24이 모두 이루기엔 <br>너무 어려 이러고 모든걸 미뤘기에 <br>Now Im still fuckin' here <br>고작 해 여기까지 <br>여기가 어딘지 가늠조차도 안 가지 <br>느껴지는 건 <br>소름 돋는 나의 자위행위 <br>니들 하는 말은 여전해 <br>저 새낀 안되지 <br>yeah get the fuck outta here <br>니네 다 x까라 그래 <br>너나 똑바로 해 <br>근데 또 인정할 수 밖에 <br>나도 확신할 수 없기에 <br>이대로 길을 가는 게 맞는지 <br>I do not fuckin' know <br>20대 뜨거운 청춘의 회고 <br>이 질문의 답을 위해서 <br>나는 계속 뱉어 <br>Imma rapper 지금 내겐 <br>잠시의 틈조차 사치기에 <br>끊임없이 발꿈칠 들어 <br>오늘 밤도 나는 걸어 yeah <br>아무도 없는 도로 그 위에 난 <br>walkin' allday <br>목적지는 멀어 yeah <br>난 정처 없이 걸어 <br>이젠 어딘지도 모르겠네 <br>I said Im gon be allright <br>now fuck that <br>절로 숙여지는 고개 <br>오늘 밤도 나는 걸어 yeah <br>아무도 없는 도로 그 위에 난 <br>walkin' allday <br>YEAH 끌어당김의 법칙 <br>그런게 사실이면 <br>난 이미 끌어당겼어 <br>YEAH 난 이미 됐어야 해 <br>졸부재벌이 그니까 <br>니네 다 전부 닥쳐 어서 <br>YEAH YEAH <br>긍정적인 생각 좋아 <br>나도 믿는다고 자기최면 <br>또 그런 각오와 <br>그런 mind <br>근데 이쯤 되면 신빙성은 없어 <br>눈을 봐 반쯤 풀려있는 <br>내 혼탁한 동공 <br>ooh X빠지게 만든 <br>앨범 여태까지 <br>X빠지게 뱉은 내 야망과 포부 <br>XX 다 물거품이라고 <br>이 한 트랙으로 내 평소 일상도 <br>이 앨범구성과 같다고 <br>열심히 노력하지 난 이뤄낼 거야 <br>몰라 이젠 그런 거 <br>I don't give a shit yeah <br>난 그냥 내 할 일을 해 묵묵히 <br>앞에 놓인 길이나 걷는 거지 <br>오늘 밤도 나는 걸어 yeah <br>아무도 없는 도로 그 위에 난 <br>walkin' allday <br>목적지는 멀어 yeah <br>난 정처 없이 걸어 <br>이젠 어딘지도 모르겠네 <br>I said Im gon be allright <br>now fuck that <br>절로 숙여지는 고개 <br>오늘 밤도 나는 걸어 yeah <br>아무도 없는 도로 그 위에 난 <br>walkin' allday <br>]]></content><category term="마블제이 (Marvel.J)" label="마블제이 (Marvel.J)"/><category term="걸어" label="걸어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마블제이_MarvelJ/Swimmin/</id><title>마블제이 (Marvel.J) - Swimmin` - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:49:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:49:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%B8%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4_MarvelJ/Swimmin/" title="마블제이 (Marvel.J) - Swimmin` - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[hey We'll be on the boat <br>I gotta get that paper <br>지중해 한 가운데에서 <br>I'm Swimmin Swimmin Swimmin <br>I've been Dreamin of my broads <br>I gotta get that paper <br>내 꿈을 살기 위해서 <br>I'm Dreamin dreamin dreamin <br>When Im swimmin' <br>Im swimmin' in ma dream <br>When Im dreamin' <br>Im dreamin' when I swim <br>When Im swimmin' <br>Im swimmin' in ma dream <br>When Im dreamin' <br>Im dreamin' when I swim <br>Yeah 나는 필요해 <br>꿈을 세는 기계가 <br>Yeah 왜냐면 나는 하고 있어 <br>im doin it right <br>Yeah 청춘은 빨리 떠나가지 <br>난 스물 네살 <br>어느덧 시간은 흘러버렸지 <br>그리고 나는 여기까지 <br>오기까지 많은 사람들은 말을 했지 <br>때론 내가 못한다고 <br>때론 구리다고 정치 질을 했지 <br>근데 이걸 어째 어디 말해봐 <br>그 잘난 입으로 <br>내가 안 했다고도 <br>그렇겐 말 못해 왜냐면 <br>지금 난 doin it right <br>꿈을 하고 있는 중이라고 <br>난 나의 꿈을 선택했어 <br>I be on my dream <br>I be on my dream <br>now I be on my dream <br>난 가고 싶어 vacay <br>Im swimmin' in ma dream <br>Im swimmin' in ma dream <br>Im swimmin' in ma dream <br>사람들은 참 유치하지 <br>특히 온라인 상에선 그게 심해 <br>편협된 시각 일방적 정보 <br>나는 두 손 두 팔을 다 드네 <br>mothafucka들은 사실 따윈 <br>중요하지 않아 <br>보고 싶은 것만 본 후에 <br>그 다음은 알지 사람 뒤질 때까지 <br>뭐 물어뜯는 거지 안 그래 <br>everytime I dab <br>이런 거 해 놓으면 <br>또 가사가 유치하대 <br>그래서 내 스타일대로 해 놨더니 <br>그건 또 구식이래 <br>hater hater hater 이 씨발놈아 <br>너네 맘대로 해라 메롱메롱메롱 <br>난 누가 뭐라든 내 갈길 가련다 <br>지금 이대로 계속 계속 계속 <br>real recognize real <br>난 이 말의 주어가 되고싶어 <br>94년도엔 태어났지 <br>많은 랩 천재들 사이에서 <br>근데 나는 <br>그 중에서 원탑이라고 불려 <br>지고 싶어 남고 싶어 레전드로 <br>난 뻗어나갈 거야 저 세계 속으로 <br>내 야망이 멈추는 것은 <br>곧 내게 죽음 워 <br>창모 슈보 랩몬 겸이 <br>삼순 kronic flow and 쩌리 <br>얘네말고 난 다 멀리 했지 <br>중삼때 부터 내 뿌린 여기였지 <br>나는 꿈을 꾸지 <br>이젠 너네들이 나와 <br>저기 grammy <br>무대까지 같이 삼킬 <br>상상뿐 이여도 참 기쁘지 <br>mothafucka들아 <br>실현시켜 나의 야망 <br>graduation <br>앨범에서 날 봐라 <br>내가 발전이 없단 새끼들은 봐라 <br>분명 걔네들은 들었겠지 타이틀 하나 <br>this asian doin' bigger <br>지금 나는 또 큰일을 하나 치뤄 <br>병신들아 너네들이 <br>할 수 있는 힘껏 날 깎아내려 <br>어쨌든 나는 이뤄 <br>그래 내 가사는 <br>그냥 중2병 shit <br>그런 너네들은 알고 있냐 <br>힙합이 뭔지 <br>난 내 힙합을 할게 넌 니 할일 할래 <br>그리고선 후에 누가 남나 볼래 <br>어차피 결관 뻔해 걍 이대로 너넨 <br>키보드나 쳐라 난 빨리러 갈게 <br>hey We'll be on the boat <br>I gotta get that paper <br>지중해 한 가운데에서 <br>I'm Swimmin Swimmin Swimmin <br>I've been Dreamin of my broads <br>I gotta get that paper <br>내 꿈을 살기 위해서 <br>I'm Dreamin dreamin dreamin <br>When Im swimmin' <br>Im swimmin' in ma dream <br>When Im dreamin' <br>Im dreamin' when I swim <br>When Im swimmin' <br>Im swimmin' in ma dream <br>When Im dreamin' <br>Im dreamin' when I swim <br>]]></content><category term="마블제이 (Marvel.J)" label="마블제이 (Marvel.J)"/><category term="Swimmin`" label="Swimmin`"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마블제이_MarvelJ/Netflix_and_chill/</id><title>마블제이 (Marvel.J) - Netflix and chill - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:49:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:49:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%B8%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4_MarvelJ/Netflix_and_chill/" title="마블제이 (Marvel.J) - Netflix and chill - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘밤은 길어 너를 꽉 껴 안을래 <br>yeah 아니 사실 짧어 <br>우리가 사랑하기엔 <br>yeah 네 눈은 너무 깊어 <br>밤새 쳐다보기에 <br>yeah 나는 너무 깊어 <br>밤새 감당하기엔 <br>yeah 우리 그 때 좋았잖아 <br>왜 자꾸 날 밀어내려 해 <br>ooh 나는 네가 부름 <br>언제든 네게 달려갈 준비해 <br>yeah 나도 내가 바보 같아 <br>내가 이럴 줄은 몰랐지 <br>ooh 네 눈 은 <br>내 이성을 멎게 만들고 <br>그대로 굳었지 <br>ooh 할래 말래 <br>이런 곡은 네게 안 어울려 babe <br>나는 진지할 땐 또 진지하지 <br>나는 네게 진실만을 말해 babe <br>친구들은 뭐래 내가 어떻대 <br>물론 걔네 말에 신빙성은 없어 <br>그냥 흘려 들어 <br>내 과거는 중요하지 않어 <br>지금 내 눈빛을 볼래 그래 <br>난 되어 볼게 너의 피터팬 <br>Fuck her Im not her gentleman <br>너를 괴롭게 하는 일들 내게 맡겨 <br>Im only ya superman <br>I said Im only ya superman <br>너가 원한다면 언제든 불러내 <br>난 되어 볼게 너의 피터팬 <br>Fuck her Im not her gentleman <br>오늘밤은 길어 너를 꽉 껴 안을래 <br>아니 사실 짧어 우리가 사랑하기엔 <br>네 눈은 너무 깊어 밤새 쳐다보기에 <br>나는 너무 깊어 밤새 감당하기엔 <br>How bout netflix and chillin' <br>How bout netflix and chillin' <br>How bout netflix and chillin' <br>오늘 같이 가자 <br>netflix and chillin' <br>우리가 그때 만났었던 그날 <br>onenight <br>나도 원래 너 같은 여자 안 만나 <br>왜냐면 다 똑같다 생각해서 말이야 <br>하지만 나는 네게 또 <br>원하고 있어 tonight <br>너도 날 원한다면 그날 밤처럼만 <br>I be like I be like <br>그 무엇도 안 부러울 거야 <br>너도 날 원한다면 그날 밤처럼만 <br>I be like I be like <br>그 무엇도 안 부러울 거야 <br>널 데리고 let's get it <br>술 마신다면 나는 분마다 사진을 <br>네게 남길 거야 <br>그리고 나서 니가 <br>술 먹을 땐 집에서 입 닥치고 <br>기다리지 나는 오직 너의 연락을 <br>너의 그 어떤 면도 나는 준비완료 <br>그래 그니까 다시 내게 와 <br>뜨겁게 타올랐던 <br>그 날 밤의 우리처럼만 <br>난 네게 팔 베게 해주다가 <br>피가 안 통해 <br>쥐가 나고 싶어 <br>또 네 집 앞에 데려다 준 후에 <br>오는 길에 <br>인신매매 그래 너 땜에 <br>나의 장기가 그냥 막 헐값에 <br>매매 되도 I don' care <br>난 널 원해 너를 보내 버릴 거야 <br>저 먼 곳에 <br>오늘밤은 길어 너를 꽉 껴 안을래 <br>아니 사실 짧어 우리가 사랑하기엔 <br>네 눈은 너무 깊어 밤새 쳐다보기에 <br>나는 너무 깊어 밤새 감당하기엔 <br>How bout netflix and chillin' <br>How bout netflix and chillin' <br>How bout netflix and chillin' <br>오늘 같이 가자 <br>netflix and chillin' <br>]]></content><category term="마블제이 (Marvel.J)" label="마블제이 (Marvel.J)"/><category term="Netflix and chill" label="Netflix and chill"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마블제이_MarvelJ/오늘밤을_원해_Feat_비오/</id><title>마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 오늘밤을 원해 (Feat. 비오) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:49:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:49:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%B8%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4_MarvelJ/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98%EB%B0%A4%EC%9D%84_%EC%9B%90%ED%95%B4_Feat_%EB%B9%84%EC%98%A4/" title="마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 오늘밤을 원해 (Feat. 비오) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 밤을 원해 너에게 <br>don't wanna be your boyfriend <br>물론 나도 그리 <br>착한 녀석은 아냐 man <br>I just wanna fuck with you <br>I just wanna fuck with you <br>왜 자꾸 내숭을 떨어 나도 알어 <br>너 남자친구 있는거 말이야 <br>자꾸 순진한 척 하지 말어 <br>넌 그런 컨셉 전혀 안 어울려 <br>난 지금 솔직히 말해 <br>딱 보자마자 첫 눈에 반했지 <br>아 그렇다고 오핸 하지마 제발 <br>몸이 그냥 반응한거니까 뭐 <br>I'll do it like <br>내일 죽을 것처럼 <br>손 끝부터 발이 닿는 곳까지 <br>I'll give you anything you want girl <br>오늘 밤을 원해 너에게 <br>쟤들은 너무 뻔해 <br>물론 나도 그리 <br>착한 녀석은 아냐 man <br>I don't wanna be boyfriend <br>I don't wanna be <br>I don't wanna be be be <br>오늘 밤을 원해 너에게 <br>쟤들은 너무 뻔해 <br>물론 나도 그리 <br>착한 녀석은 아냐 man <br>I don't wanna be boyfriend <br>I don't wanna be <br>I don't wanna be be be <br>Versace versace my bitchs <br>hoes on me but 이건 다 거짓 <br>This is Marvel J <br>당장 내 옆으로 와 한잔 따를래 <br>난 진도같은 건 섬밖에 몰라 <br>쭉 뻗은 팔과 다리 <br>일단 벌려 일단 벌려 <br>니 허릴 꽉 감아 안을래 <br>난 네 앞에선 마치 개같아 <br>주위 눈에 흥분해 <br>네 몸매는 유모차도 아닌데 <br>왜 자꾸만 계속 내 애를 태우네 <br>mofucka들은 많어 but <br>걔넨 마치 그냥 싸구려 <br>행사 사은품 같어 <br>왜냐면 걔넨 모두 다 무료할 걸 <br>난 니 마음 게다가 또 spot 도 알어 <br>I'll do it like <br>내일 죽을 것처럼 <br>손 끝부터 발이 닿는 곳까지 <br>I'll give you anything you want girl <br>오늘 밤을 원해 너에게 <br>쟤들은 너무 뻔해 <br>물론 나도 그리 <br>착한 녀석은 아냐 man <br>I don't wanna be boyfriend <br>I don't wanna be <br>I don't wanna be be be <br>오늘 밤을 원해 너에게 <br>쟤들은 너무 뻔해 <br>물론 나도 그리 <br>착한 녀석은 아냐 man <br>I don't wanna be boyfriend <br>I don't wanna be <br>I don't wanna be be be <br>어떤 옷을 입어도 감출 수 없어 <br>네 몸매 <br>yeah yeah I need you girl <br>baby you know that I'm always you <br>I wanna surf in your body <br>I wanna dive in <br>너의 가장 깊은 곳으로 <br>오늘 밤을 원해 너에게 <br>쟤들은 너무 뻔해 <br>물론 나도 그리 <br>착한 녀석은 아냐 man <br>I don't wanna be boyfriend <br>I don't wanna be <br>I don't wanna be be be <br>오늘 밤을 원해 너에게 <br>쟤들은 너무 뻔해 <br>물론 나도 그리 <br>착한 녀석은 아냐 man <br>I don't wanna be boyfriend <br>I don't wanna be <br>I don't wanna be be be <br>]]></content><category term="마블제이 (Marvel.J)" label="마블제이 (Marvel.J)"/><category term="오늘밤을 원해 (Feat. 비오)" label="오늘밤을 원해 (Feat. 비오)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마블제이_MarvelJ/Valhalla_Feat_슬리피/</id><title>마블제이 (Marvel.J) - Valhalla (Feat. 슬리피) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:50:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:50:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%B8%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4_MarvelJ/Valhalla_Feat_%EC%8A%AC%EB%A6%AC%ED%94%BC/" title="마블제이 (Marvel.J) - Valhalla (Feat. 슬리피) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Turn up reverb in valhalla <br>bitch gotta <br>know that It's timeout <br>mf you dead valhalla <br>you dead you dead <br>you dead hol up <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>Bitch got the <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>Turn up reverb in valhalla <br>bitch gotta <br>know that It's timeout <br>mf you dead valhalla <br>you dead you dead <br>you dead hol up <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>Bitch got the <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>ooh Marvel ooh J yeah <br>let's go get it get it ooh <br>이런 이런 이런 이런 yeah <br>flow flow 죽여 죽여 ooh <br>내가 만든것은 아냐 물론 ooh <br>그래서 지금 내가 존나 구려 ooh <br>그럼 한국 랩퍼들중 누가 ooh <br>좋냐 이 돌대가리 빠순아 yeah <br>나이먹고 망한 랩퍼들 <br>지금도 어딘가서 <br>술쳐먹고 하지 꼰대질을 <br>ooh 작업 좆도 안해 <br>아니 어떻게 보면 <br>대한민국 넘버원 다른의미로 <br>ooh 클럽서 친구 테이블 <br>잡음 나가 지하철로 <br>물론 나이는 곧 불혹 <br>ooh 누군 말해 그런 <br>애들 보다 나를 보면 <br>나는 정말 대단하대 <br>fuck you fuck you <br>that's a fuckin' bullshit bull shit <br>난 이 곳이 곳이 절대 <br>내 목표에 끝 종착지 착지 <br>라 생각치 각치 않아 I be like <br>kendrick wutang tupac bigge 같이 <br>새역사를 써야지 이 곳에 남겨 <br>내 이름과 또 명성을 같이 ooh <br>Turn up reverb in valhalla <br>bitch gotta <br>know that It's timeout <br>mf you dead valhalla <br>you dead you dead <br>you dead hol up <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>Bitch got the <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>Turn up reverb in valhalla <br>bitch gotta <br>know that It's timeout <br>mf you dead valhalla <br>you dead you dead <br>you dead hol up <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>Bitch got the <br>Magic in me like the Doctor <br>슬리피 그새끼 꼴보기 싫은데 <br>티비만 틀면은 존나게 나오지 우 야 <br>물타기 서핑을 해야지 <br>너네들 댓글을 타고서 우 야 <br>몇번을 말하니 젤쓸데 없는게 <br>연예인 걱정이구 야 <br>씨잼이 말했다구 랩이나 잘하라구 <br>대한민국 힙합 꼬마 랩퍼들 <br>날 씹기 제일 좋겠지 바빠서 랩들을 <br>들어보기도 힘들어 지워 <br>싸클은 니가 누가 잘된대 <br>성공은 개뿔이 whoo <br>니가 누굴 인정 하든 니가 누구 한테 <br>랩을 배우던 말던 누굴 파던 <br>어차피 넌 확률 없어 아무도 <br>안듣는 랩들은 결국엔 휴지통에 <br>버릴 랩 친구가 죽 인다고 해주면 <br>앞으로 쭉 이길을 간다고 지랄을 우 야 <br>휴지통에 버릴 랩 친구가 <br>죽 인다고 해주면 앞으로 <br>쭉 이길을 간다고 지랄을 우 야 <br>]]></content><category term="마블제이 (Marvel.J)" label="마블제이 (Marvel.J)"/><category term="Valhalla (Feat. 슬리피)" label="Valhalla (Feat. 슬리피)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마블제이_MarvelJ/위기_Feat_Huckleberry_P_베이식/</id><title>마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 위기 (Feat. Huckleberry P, 베이식) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:50:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:50:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%B8%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4_MarvelJ/%EC%9C%84%EA%B8%B0_Feat_Huckleberry_P_%EB%B2%A0%EC%9D%B4%EC%8B%9D/" title="마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 위기 (Feat. Huckleberry P, 베이식) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ooh 위기 위기 위기 위기 <br>ooh 위기 위기 위기 위기 <br>yeah 랩퍼들은 위기위기 <br>yeah 마블제이는 돈을 get it <br>ooh 나를 모를 수도 있네 <br>그렇다면 니들 딱 입 닫어 닫어 <br>ooh 아 못 닫을 수도 있어 왜냠 <br>지금 우리 랩이 너무 쩔어 <br>ooh turn up turn up M F F <br>내가 또 저질렀어 <br>쩔어 쩔어 질 내 커리어들 <br>나는 앞만 보지 또 <br>내 반려견들 보다 못한 <br>허접랩퍼들은 또 신께 기도 <br>물론 나도 기도하지 허나 <br>근거가 돼 나의 노력 <br>I GOT THE SKILLS 아빤 말했지 <br>태균아 넌 1등 할 수 있지 <br>그 땐 중1 그리고 난 말했지 <br>아빠 내가 어떻게 자식들은 <br>모두 제치고 <br>1등을해 아빤 개 좆까래 <br>걔네 다 내 밑이래 <br>난 최선을 다했고 그 다음 시험에서 <br>또 그 말을 실천을 했지 <br>Oh god 이런 멋진 나란 새끼 <br>real real I get it <br>1년 전에 나를 씹던 <br>그 년은 지금 뭐해 <br>아마도 같겠지 딱 그때처럼 <br>뭐 남들 뒤나 또 까며 자위하고 <br>어디서 알바중 <br>그리고선 내 음악이 구리다며 <br>친구들과 XX 사냥중 <br>ooh 어려서부터 난 원하는 건 <br>모든지 이뤄내고야 말았지 <br>그게 뭐든지 I got it got it got it <br>그리고선 이치를 깨닳았지 <br>내가 해내지 못할 일은 없어 <br>난 대가리가 컸어 그래서 사람들이 <br>나를 싫어 할 수 있지 <br>또 미워 할 수 있지 하지만 난 <br>그런것 따위 I dont give a shit <br>MF Imma be rapstar like kendrick <br>매일 밤 난 깨있지 <br>준비가 난 돼있지 한다면 난 해내지 <br>이런 놈이라고 난 뭘 상상 하든간 <br>I rap like kanye and jay z <br>랩만 잘하는 줄 알았더니 <br>이젠 비트까지 해쳐먹어 <br>this track aint fake shit <br>YEAH 여기 랩퍼들은 내가 볼때 <br>전부 위기위기위기 <br>YEAH 그래서지 내 앨범이 나옴 <br>니네 위기위기위기 <br>YEAH 난 기침하며 랩을 해도 <br>귀에 착 감 기지기지기지 <br>YEAH 여기 랩퍼들은 내가 볼때 <br>전부 위기위기위기 <br>bring it muthafucka i go rambo <br>토쏠리게 하는 너의 행동 <br>필요한건 마이크 든 내 왼손 <br>그냥 제발 닥치고 가만히있어 <br>better go airplane mode <br>눈만 떠 넌 airplane mode <br>할수있는게 없지 airplane mode <br>넌 그냥 서있는 과녁이 되있고 <br>두두두두 fucka i go rambo <br>bring it muthafucka <br>i go rambo again <br>붙자마자 니탄약은 앵꼬났네 <br>얼어버렸지 니상태는 냉동 <br>어디한번 계속해봐 센척 <br>오 한번에 딱나와버린 갠또 <br>니랩은 묵음 just like d in django <br>when it goes down in the tempo <br>when the muthafuckin' <br>track's getting killed by 내 펜촉 <br>i go rambo 결과는 KO <br>굳이 모두 말하지 않아도 <br>they know <br>니 존재자체 횡포 <br>귀를 없애고 싶게 해 <br>tryna make us van gogh <br>lay low muthafuckas <br>better stay raw <br>안그래서 니상태는 위기 <br>난 B지 모든 시기 <br>한꺼번에 받는 1위 <br>나는 이기기 위해 <br>숨겨둔 비기 실력이지 <br>all you bitches <br>새겨들어 지금이 니 위기 <br>유행만 쫓다 니 활약상 확실히 미비 <br>니네들 워너비 <br>bitches ain't killin shit <br>다른 랩퍼 뒷꽁무니만 쫓는건 <br>어떤 느낌이니 <br>muthafuckas better pay attention <br>니가위기에처한건 <br>that ain't random <br>나도 가끔은 부러워 fandom <br>결국엔 내가 더 열심히 해야지 <br>니 위기가 내 위기 시발 <br>사실 내 앞가림이 더 시급해서 <br>오늘도 어제도 내일도 <br>랩하고 랩하고 랩하고 음 <br>하지만 질생각은 없어 나도 <br>음 bitch i'm a rider yeah <br>YEAH 여기 랩퍼들은 내가 볼때 <br>전부 위기위기위기 <br>YEAH 그래서지 내 앨범이 나옴 <br>니네 위기위기위기 <br>YEAH 난 기침하며 랩을 해도 <br>귀에 착 감 기지기지기지 <br>YEAH 여기 랩퍼들은 내가 볼때 <br>전부 위기위기위기 <br>한 글자만 뱉어도 달라지는 <br>분위기 위기 위기 <br>다 뱉고나면 너거 랩퍼들의 <br>표정에는 위기 위기 위기 <br>그 위기를 느낀 이들을 위해 <br>비밀게시판이 있지 <br>거긴 Nagativity 피비비랜내로 <br>가득한 DCT secret <br>자신의 재능없음에 대해 고민해본 적 <br>없이 SNS 혹은 게시판에서 <br>래퍼들에게 땡깡부리는 <br>자칭 MC 들을 다 후려까는 <br>rhyme 한 번 들어봐 <br>함부로 나를 판가름 하지를 마 <br>계속 까불어봐 그러다 들어나면 <br>다 자긴 안그랬다 말하고 다닐 거 알아 <br>그런 새끼들이 나의 주변에도 <br>분명히 존재하는걸 알아 <br>그런 새끼들이 어디가서는 <br>나를 무슨 꼰대라 말하잖아 <br>한국힙합에 좆도 관심없는 <br>좆밥새끼들이 말야 <br>여자 아이돌 관련 게시물에다가만 <br>계속 리플을 달아 <br>걔네 다 그래봤자 반백수들이잖아 <br>알고보면 <br>그런 새끼들에게는 되게 <br>배아플꺼야 내 단독공연 <br>니들이 아무리 마이크 잡아도 <br>아무도 안 보러 와 what <br>난 마이크 안 들어 알아서 막 불러 <br>아무도 안 부러워 what <br>YEAH 여기 랩퍼들은 내가 볼때 <br>전부 위기위기위기 <br>YEAH 그래서지 내 앨범이 나옴 <br>니네 위기위기위기 <br>YEAH 난 기침하며 랩을 해도 <br>귀에 착 감 기지기지기지 <br>YEAH 여기 랩퍼들은 내가 볼때 <br>전부 위기위기위기 <br>]]></content><category term="마블제이 (Marvel.J)" label="마블제이 (Marvel.J)"/><category term="위기 (Feat. Huckleberry P, 베이식)" label="위기 (Feat. Huckleberry P, 베이식)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마블제이_MarvelJ/반성해/</id><title>마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 반성해 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:50:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:50:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%B8%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4_MarvelJ/%EB%B0%98%EC%84%B1%ED%95%B4/" title="마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 반성해 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bounce with me Bounce with me <br>랩퍼들은 모두 반성해 <br>Bounce with me Bounce with me <br>랩퍼들은 모두 반성해 <br>안된댔지 안된댔지 <br>마블제이는 돈 못 번댔지 <br>근데 어쩌니 근데 어쩌니 <br>난 이제 벌기 시작했지 <br>Bounce with me Bounce with me <br>랩퍼들은 모두 반성해 <br>Bounce with me Bounce with me <br>랩퍼들은 모두 반성해 <br>넌 좆됐지 넌 좆됐지 <br>마블제이는 돈을 벌겠지 <br>representing representing <br>부정하면 나는 침뱉지 <br>yeah 랩퍼들은 나를 너무 좆밥 취급 <br>babe babe babe <br>yeah 랩퍼들아 일년뒤엔 니들 똥차 <br>빼래 빼래 빼래 <br>yeah 클럽년들 나를 너무 좆밥 취급 <br>babe babe babe <br>ooh 근데 사실 너네 거들 떠도 안봄 <br>babe babe babe <br>ooh 얼마전엔 가로수길 가서 <br>50만원 쇼핑했지 <br>우 야 그리고선 의자사러 <br>강남 시디즈로 40만원 바로 swish <br>우 야 컴퓨터 바꾸고 싶어 <br>다나와서 조립컴을 120 더 swish <br>우 야 물론 노트북은 중고 40만에 <br>다시 되팔았지 바로 ㅎ <br>우 야 마잌스웨거 시즌 3 <br>죽여놨지 Rap skill <br>그랬더니 중고나라 판매자가 <br>마블제이녜 Oh shit <br>지금도 좋은데 좀 더 뜨면 <br>어케 되는거냐 <br>aomg illi 존나 짱 부럽다 <br>진짜 왕 부럽다 진심 oh god ooh <br>내 반려견은 마블이와 제이 <br>먹였었지 fuckin' 프로플랜 <br>이젠 먹어 네츄럴 코어 <br>나중엔 먹여야지 Organic 으로 <br>나는 존나 계속 잘나갈거고 <br>I be like 신사임당 오만안에 <br>hater hater hater 끼리 뭉쳐 <br>어디 한번해봐 븅신 단합대회 <br>Bounce with me Bounce with me <br>랩퍼들은 모두 반성해 <br>Bounce with me Bounce with me <br>랩퍼들은 모두 반성해 <br>안된댔지 안된댔지 <br>마블제이는 돈 못 번댔지 <br>근데 어쩌니 근데 어쩌니 <br>난 이제 벌기 시작했지 <br>Bounce with me Bounce with me <br>랩퍼들은 모두 반성해 <br>Bounce with me Bounce with me <br>랩퍼들은 모두 반성해 <br>넌 좆됐지 넌 좆됐지 <br>마블제이는 돈을 벌겠지 <br>representing representing <br>부정하면 나는 침뱉지 <br>그래 내게 친구들은 물어보지 <br>취업 어떻게 <br>할거녜 fuck that shit 좆까고 <br>너네집 이나 걱정해 MFMF <br>나는 다짐했다고 다신 절대 <br>안한다고 돈벌러왔어의 삶 <br>그게 뭐냐면 인생에서 을로 <br>살아가는 거지 고갤 늘 숙이는 삶 <br>내 친구새낀 내게 전공걱정하대 <br>취업률이 어떻녜 <br>그래 축하한다 전라북도 공대 <br>학생회장 200 해쳐먹었다매 <br>야이 모자란 새끼야 <br>그게 자랑이냐 참 좋겠다 <br>굶는 한이 있더라도 네놈처럼 <br>나는 안해 먹어 이 청렴한 새끼야 <br>난 인생의 맛을 알어 ooh <br>고진 감랠 안다고 <br>yeah 열매나 쫓아가봐 <br>그럼 혹시나 알어 미안해 <br>넌 그럴 자격 없어 MUFUCKA <br>그런 놈이라고 넌 FUCKA <br>check ya wallet 술값 뿜빠이 <br>할때 천원 손해보면 <br>You said oh god <br>mofucka 야이 멋없는 친구야 <br>허구헌날 입으로는 친구친구 <br>또는 의리 의리 또는 우리 <br>우리 애들 끼리 난 관심없단다 <br>야이 대단한 친구야 OOH <br>평생 그렇게 살어 <br>나는 평생 떳떳하게 벌어 <br>그리고 을의 삶을 벗어 <br>Bounce with me Bounce with me <br>랩퍼들은 모두 반성해 <br>Bounce with me Bounce with me <br>랩퍼들은 모두 반성해 <br>안된댔지 안된댔지 <br>마블제이는 돈 못 번댔지 <br>근데 어쩌니 근데 어쩌니 <br>난 이제 벌기 시작했지 <br>Bounce with me Bounce with me <br>랩퍼들은 모두 반성해 <br>Bounce with me Bounce with me <br>랩퍼들은 모두 반성해 <br>넌 좆됐지 넌 좆됐지 <br>마블제이는 돈을 벌겠지 <br>representing representing <br>부정하면 나는 침뱉지 <br>]]></content><category term="마블제이 (Marvel.J)" label="마블제이 (Marvel.J)"/><category term="반성해" label="반성해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마블제이_MarvelJ/Really_Feat_뉴챔프_올티/</id><title>마블제이 (Marvel.J) - Really (Feat. 뉴챔프, 올티) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:50:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:50:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%B8%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4_MarvelJ/Really_Feat_%EB%89%B4%EC%B1%94%ED%94%84_%EC%98%AC%ED%8B%B0/" title="마블제이 (Marvel.J) - Really (Feat. 뉴챔프, 올티) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[걔가 랩을 잘해 <br>really really really woo <br>내가 볼 때 걔넨 비리비리비리 woo <br>누가 제일 잘해 <br>really really really woo <br>어디한번 대보자고 <br>get it get it get it boy <br>나는 지리 지리 지리고 <br>너네 랩은 미니미니마니모 <br>낄때 끼지 허접새끼 끼리 놀때 <br>놀아 찌질이 질이 빙신병신들 <br>나는 됐어 됐어 느그 장난질 <br>나는 랩은 절대로가라 안침 <br>그래 나는 느그들을 다 가라앉힘 <br>니 여친은 오늘 바람핌 Okay <br>난 영어 못 써 왜냠 했어 수능 공부 <br>나인 스물넷 이마엔 <br>fuckin' 주름 세줄 <br>나는 받았지 우리 집 정씨 핏줄 <br>그걸 알았다면 빨리들 튀어 <br>난 꽤 다혈 질이라구 <br>mffff yeah 돈 벌어 woo <br>랩 쩔어 yeah F yeah <br>랩퍼들은 모두 떨어 YA <br>그 사이 홍해 바달 걸어 WOO <br>이제 눈치 챘냐 이 새끼들아 <br>이런 곡에 가산 따윈 없어 WOO <br>걔가 랩을 잘해 <br>really really really woo <br>내가 볼 때 걔넨 비리비리비리 woo <br>누가 제일 잘해 <br>really really really woo <br>어디한번 대보자고 <br>get it get it woo <br>really really really woo <br>really really really woo <br>really really really woo <br>누가 제일 잘해 <br>really really really woo <br>이 멋이 멋이 전혀 안나는 <br>머시마들 show me show me <br>왜 굳어있어 <br>여기저기 떠리떠리 들이 쩌리 처럼 <br>dirty dirty 붙어있어 <br>이건 legendary 아카펠라 <br>Like j hova roca fella <br>다 take over 내 입이 <br>shot ya shot ya <br>Brrrr brrrr I kill'em <br>지긋지긋하게 찢어찢어 발갠다고 <br>걔가 지은 별명 비글 <br>나의 리듬 미끈미끈 기름칠을 <br>석유 재벌 feel을 아살라말리꿈 <br>아살라말리꿈 나의 꿈 uh <br>두바이와 아부다비를 uh <br>와리가리하며 아침에 머리를 말리며 <br>마시는 malibu uh <br>그녀가 내 옆에 있겠지 uh <br>입고 싶은거 다 입겠지 uh <br>우린 이른 아침부터 xx <br>석양이 질 쯤에 다시 음쫘 <br>로 시작해서 저 끝까지 가 uh <br>밑에서 또 시작하지 와 uh <br>꿈은 달콤하게 녹아내릴테니 <br>마블제이와의 작업 후 ah <br>걔가 랩을 잘해 <br>really really really woo <br>내가 볼 때 걔넨 비리비리비리 woo <br>누가 제일 잘해 <br>really really really woo <br>어디한번 대보자고 <br>get it get it woo <br>really really really woo <br>really really really woo <br>really really really woo <br>누가 제일 잘해 <br>really really really woo <br>굳이 말 안해도 i'm really dope <br>콧대 세우며 다녀 no 실리콘 <br>덤볐다 응급실에 실릴걸 <br>요즘 취미거든요 인실좆 phhh <br>무릎 꿇을 준비나 해 <br>mofos 차피 닿지 못할 리치 <br>내가 니네 목표야 <br>young &amp; wild bitch i'm rich <br>음원 성적 준수하지 <br>안경 쓴 모범생 간지 <br>트랙은 뉴스쿨 올드스쿨 <br>전학 밥 먹듯이 하는 양아치 <br>now i'm talking bout dough <br>now i'm talking bout gold <br>방송 끝났어도 냄비는 끓어 펄펄 <br>내 인성이 뭐 또 <br>트집 잡으려 별 지랄 똥을 싸도 <br>니 여친 전화보다 <br>많이 오는 러브콜 <br>하러 가야해 또 앵콜 떼써 <br>that's all i got it <br>내겐 없어 무료 공개곡 <br>cuz my verse's for cash <br>가친 무려 억대고 <br>이사님이 또 행사 다 밀려있대도 <br>이깟 16마디쯤 <br>전혀 무리가 없대도 ya <br>걔가 랩을 잘해 <br>really really really woo <br>내가 볼 때 걔넨 비리비리비리 woo <br>누가 제일 잘해 <br>really really really woo <br>어디한번 대보자고 <br>get it get it woo <br>really really really woo <br>really really really woo <br>really really really woo <br>누가 제일 잘해 <br>really really really woo <br>]]></content><category term="마블제이 (Marvel.J)" label="마블제이 (Marvel.J)"/><category term="Really (Feat. 뉴챔프, 올티)" label="Really (Feat. 뉴챔프, 올티)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마블제이_MarvelJ/띵_Feat_김효은_San_E/</id><title>마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 띵 (Feat. 김효은, San E) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:50:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:50:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%B8%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4_MarvelJ/%EB%9D%B5_Feat_%EA%B9%80%ED%9A%A8%EC%9D%80_San_E/" title="마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 띵 (Feat. 김효은, San E) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[허접 랩퍼들에게 <br>내 랩은 띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 yeah <br>니 랩은 네 부모님들도 <br>낄 낄 낄 낄 낄 yeah <br>내 음악 내 트랙 <br>그리고 랩 띵 띵 띵 띵 yeah <br>허접 랩퍼들에게 <br>내 랩은 띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 yeah <br>요즘엔 이렇게 오토튠을 걸어야해 <br>발음 주의 절대 구리게 부정확해야해 <br>왜냠 thug scott형 들이 존나 짱짱맨 <br>이기에 우린 그걸 본받아서 <br>내껄 존나게 잘 만들어야 해 <br>ooh 내 꿈은 졸부재벌 <br>ooh 내 꿈은 졸부재벌 <br>Im on a new level 돈을 그냥 <br>씨발 존나게 개막써 <br>쇼미더머니 개 좋지만 일년 <br>행사바짝하고 굶을 생각 없어 <br>난 임마 스물네살에 꿈꾼다고 <br>재벌을 너는 삼성 면접 꿈 꿔 <br>yeah 원래 힙합은 하고 싶은 <br>말을 하는데 그 본질이 있다고 <br>나는 그래서 너네들이 <br>내 인성을 논하기 전에 <br>힙합을 한다고 mf 알아 들었냐 <br>나를 거들떠도 안보겠지 지금의 <br>인간들 그게 남자든 여자든 mf <br>yeah 니 여친이 이별을 말하고 <br>니들이 울 때 나는 지구를 생각해 <br>이게 나다 mf <br>허접 랩퍼들에게 <br>내 랩은 띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 yeah <br>니 랩은 네 부모님들도 <br>낄 낄 낄 낄 낄 yeah <br>내 음악 내 트랙 <br>그리고 랩 띵 띵 띵 띵 yeah <br>허접 랩퍼들에게 <br>내 랩은 띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 yeah <br>띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 내 음악 내 트랙 <br>내 랩 모두 <br>띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 니네 기집애 같은 <br>랩퍼 친구들 모두 <br>낄 낄 낄 낄 낄 내 음악 <br>내 트랙 내 랩 모두 <br>띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 <br>You got it let's get it <br>띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 속으로 <br>나 실실 비웃고 있어 <br>너네들 불평하는 소리 <br>빙빙 돌려 말 안할게 너넨 안 되니 <br>끽 끽 해야 쇼미 나가도 <br>걔넨 너한테 관심 없어 <br>의미 없이 미워하지 말고 <br>내가 부럽다고 말해봐 <br>눈을 떠라 새꺄 니 맘대로 <br>니가 원한 세상 <br>야 내가 이렇게 보여주고 있잖아 <br>바래 다 돈 여자 유명세 <br>믿음으로 구원해 <br>구걸이라면 자존심이 <br>허락하지 못 하는 니들을 구경해 <br>굳이 나를 닮지 못 할 거라면 <br>내 시간을 물어내 <br>시간은 돈이고 쌓아 올리고 <br>몰리고 파리들이 요기조기 <br>피를 빠는 모기도 <br>너가 봤듯이 나는 내 엄마 손목에 <br>비싼 팔찌 사주는 것 밖엔 관심없어 <br>보릿고개 시절이 생각 나네 <br>내가 말했잖아 될 거 라고 배 <br>아파해 근데 만약에 내가 망해도 <br>너네 보다는 잘 살고 행복해 장담해 <br>내 가사엔 적어도 거짓은 없어 mf <br>나는 졸라 쩔어 mf 기지배들 나를 <br>연예인 만들고 싶어하는 거라면 <br>필요 없어 다 꺼져 <br>허접 랩퍼들에게 <br>내 랩은 띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 yeah <br>니 랩은 네 부모님들도 <br>낄 낄 낄 낄 낄 yeah <br>내 음악 내 트랙 <br>그리고 랩 띵 띵 띵 띵 yeah <br>허접 랩퍼들에게 <br>내 랩은 띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 yeah <br>띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 내 음악 내 트랙 <br>내 랩 모두 <br>띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 니네 기집애 같은 <br>랩퍼 친구들 모두 <br>낄 낄 낄 낄 낄 내 음악 <br>내 트랙 내 랩 모두 <br>띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 <br>You got it let's get it <br>존나 오랜만에 하네 피쳐링 <br>예전엔 거의 걸레 수준이 였는데 <br>언젠가부터 별로 찾지 않더라고 <br>나 그리 어려운 사람 아냐 <br>함께하고 싶다면 마운틴 언더바 <br>보이 골뱅이 다음 닷넷 후 <br>요새 트렌드 <br>이렇게 뒤에끝 부분에 yeah <br>이런거 하나씩 붙이대 ay <br>그러다 한번씩 flow like woo <br>어쩌다 중간쯤 skir skir <br>Oh 그리고 my favorite brrr <br>존나 꽂혀 중독적이야 <br>I fucking love this goddamn <br>있지 나 랩이 다시 재밌네 like 갓겜 <br>사실 마블제이 잘 몰라 <br>근데 들어보니 he got game <br>김효은 역시 wow <br>they motivate me like hell <br>but one thang that don't change <br>변하지 않는 진리 <br>허접랩퍼들은 예나제나 띨띨띨띨띨 <br>im sorry <br>팩트폭행해서 미안 근데 <br>다 사실실실 true true <br>마음 아파하지 말고 <br>take pain kill kill kill kill <br>지금까지 산 이이이이이 였습니다 <br>허접 랩퍼들에게 <br>내 랩은 띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 yeah <br>니 랩은 네 부모님들도 <br>낄 낄 낄 낄 낄 yeah <br>내 음악 내 트랙 <br>그리고 랩 띵 띵 띵 띵 yeah <br>허접 랩퍼들에게 <br>내 랩은 띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 yeah <br>띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 내 음악 내 트랙 <br>내 랩 모두 <br>띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 니네 기집애 같은 <br>랩퍼 친구들 모두 <br>낄 낄 낄 낄 낄 내 음악 <br>내 트랙 내 랩 모두 <br>띵 띵 띵 띵 띵 <br>You got it let's get it <br>]]></content><category term="마블제이 (Marvel.J)" label="마블제이 (Marvel.J)"/><category term="띵 (Feat. 김효은, San E)" label="띵 (Feat. 김효은, San E)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마블제이_MarvelJ/행복하기_위해/</id><title>마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 행복하기 위해 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:50:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:50:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%B8%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4_MarvelJ/%ED%96%89%EB%B3%B5%ED%95%98%EA%B8%B0_%EC%9C%84%ED%95%B4/" title="마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 행복하기 위해 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[살아있다는 느낌을 받아 <br>나를 음악으로 만들 때 YEAH <br>그 무엇보다 좋아 의견을 묻고 <br>서로 이야기를 나눌 때 YEAH <br>잘 나가는 랩퍼들이 <br>너무 많아 나도 많아 <br>그들이 부러울 때 YEAH <br>하지만 나는 지금 너무 즐겁다고 <br>내 삶이 너무 행복해 YEAH <br>YEAH Im happy all day <br>학굔 휴학 이제 <br>드디어 날 찾았어 man <br>ooh Im happy nowadays <br>랩퍼들은 정말 <br>축복을 받았어 man <br>yeah 사랑한다면 그 순간을 즐겨 <br>그녀를 바라봐 어서 <br>그리고 그걸 적어 너의 수첩안에 <br>그리고 그건 이제 <br>네 앨범안에 전부 담어 <br>yeah 이제 나는 여기까지 <br>난 부천에서부터 어느새 강남 까지 <br>와버렸지 중3부터 스물넷 까지 <br>물론 아직 되진 못했어 내 목표까진 <br>now Im better better 내 삶에 <br>괴로워 괴로워 <br>하던 내 지난 날이 되려 <br>내게 힘이 되어줘 <br>Imma bigger bigger bigger <br>난 즐겨 즐겨 즐겨 <br>누군가의 선택에 <br>내 삶이 좌우되긴 싫어 <br>자유롭고 싶어 딱 지금처럼만 <br>적고 싶은게 있다면 적어 임마 <br>먹고 싶은게 있다면 <br>먹어 임마 그리고 <br>벌고 싶은게 있다면 벌어 임마 <br>자유롭고 싶어 딱 지금처럼만 <br>적고 싶은게 있다면 적어 임마 <br>먹고 싶은게 있다면 <br>먹어 임마 그리고 <br>벌고 싶은게 있다면 벌어 임마 <br>Yeah Yeah 내 기분 너무 좋아 <br>가고 싶은대로 향해가 <br>Yeah Yeah 그래 거친 파돌 뚫고 가지 <br>삶이라는 항해가 <br>Yeah Yeah 게임 난이도를 조절하지 <br>너희들이 방해가 <br>Yeah Yeah 남자라면 뛰어들어 임마 <br>Im Divin' Im Divin' <br>Im Divin' Im Divin' <br>난 행복하기 위해 오늘도 <br>난 행복하기 위해 오늘도 <br>난 행복하기 위해 오늘 적고 <br>또 먹고 또 벌고 또 얻어 <br>난 행복하기 위해 오늘도 <br>난 행복하기 위해 오늘도 <br>난 행복하기 위해 오늘 적고 <br>또 먹고 또 벌고 또 얻어 <br>물론 삶이 항상 아름답다고만 <br>절대 말을 못해 <br>그 동안 많이 힘들었네 <br>나도 꽤 아직도 있는것 같애 <br>그 과정안에 <br>그리고 나는 그 과정이 좋아 <br>물론 자위일 수 있지 <br>아직 뜨지 못한 <br>한 랩퍼의 회한 아무렴 어때 <br>난 지금 좋아 그렇다고 <br>모든 사람들이 이렇게 전부 다 <br>긍정적일 수는 없지 화 날 수도 있지 <br>빡칠수도 있지 다 패고 싶을 수 있지 <br>그렇기엔 우린 가살쓰고 <br>랩을 할 수 있지 <br>게 우리가 축복받은 이유이자 빛이지 <br>now we better better <br>그게 난 즐겁다고 <br>하루종일 가살 쓰다 <br>머리 아픔 산책 GO <br>내 옆엔 마블이와 제이 <br>그리고 여자친구 <br>내 뒤엔 부모님 뿐 만이 아냐 주님도 <br>이렇게 하다보면 <br>언젠가 오게되겠지 나의 날 <br>내 음악이 세상에서 빛을 발할 날 <br>내 야망을 성취하고 또 인정 받을 날 <br>그래 이 선순환적인 구조 <br>난 나를 믿지 <br>그리고 난 즐기지 <br>또 노력하지 매일이 <br>내 땀방울로 차있기에 아 근데 사실 <br>지금 내겐 그런건 전혀 안 중요하지 <br>Now Im happy 우리는 왜 살지 <br>그것에 대한 답을 원한다면 <br>당장 빨리 <br>널 존재하게 하는 것을 찾어 <br>난 이미 찾아 행하고 있다고 <br>그래 뭐야 말해봐 어서 <br>그리고 그걸로 딱 지금처럼만 <br>적고 싶은게 있다면 적어 임마 <br>먹고 싶은게 있다면 <br>먹어 임마 그리고 <br>벌고 싶은게 있다면 벌어 임마 <br>Yeah Yeah 내 기분 너무 좋아 <br>가고 싶은대로 향해가 <br>Yeah Yeah 그래 거친 파돌 뚫고 가지 <br>삶이라는 항해가 <br>Yeah Yeah 게임 난이도를 조절하지 <br>너희들이 방해가 <br>Yeah Yeah 남자라면 뛰어들어 임마 <br>Im Divin' Im Divin' <br>Im Divin' Im Divin' <br>난 행복하기 위해 오늘도 <br>난 행복하기 위해 오늘도 <br>난 행복하기 위해 오늘 적고 <br>또 먹고 또 벌고 또 얻어 <br>난 행복하기 위해 오늘도 <br>난 행복하기 위해 오늘도 <br>난 행복하기 위해 오늘 적고 <br>또 먹고 또 벌고 또 얻어 <br>]]></content><category term="마블제이 (Marvel.J)" label="마블제이 (Marvel.J)"/><category term="행복하기 위해" label="행복하기 위해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마블제이_MarvelJ/말해봐/</id><title>마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 말해봐 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:50:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:50:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%B8%94%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4_MarvelJ/%EB%A7%90%ED%95%B4%EB%B4%90/" title="마블제이 (Marvel.J) - 말해봐 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아직도 기억나 일곱살 그 때였지 <br>나의 안에 뜨거운 게 깨어난 <br>그 날의 무대는 유치원 재롱잔치 <br>극은 아마 최진삿댁 셋째 딸 <br>uh 그 때 내 역할은 최진사였지 <br>나에겐 있었어 세명의 딸 <br>지금은 그거 말고 하나도 기억 안나 <br>but 그 날의 감정은 아직 선명하지 <br>날 찍는 큰 비디오 카메라들 <br>관객석에서 날 응원하는 엄마 아빠 <br>또 그리고 친구들 <br>내 몸은 그 때 두배 만하지만 <br>그 감정은 아직 날 둘러싸고 있어 <br>나이는 세배가 됐는데 그건 아직 <br>내 원동력 <br>존재 하고있어 <br>uh 무대가 끝난 후 <br>일곱살 내가 한말은 <br>아 또 공연 하고 싶다 였지 <br>그게 아마 내 첫 시작 <br>우리 엄마 아빤 그 때 알았겠지 <br>도저히 주체 못하는 나의 끼를 <br>uh 너네도 이제 알겠지 <br>내게서 흐르는 예술가의 피를 <br>네 진짜 꿈을 말해봐 <br>너의 삶을 말해봐 <br>어떤 걸 원하고 살아 <br>그걸 절대 숨기진 마 <br>난 그 기분 너무 잘 알아 <br>현실의 벽 마주치면 <br>넌 그걸 부술 능력이 있어 <br>그러니 넌 꿈이 뭐야 <br>말해봐 말해봐 말해봐 <br>숨기지마 기지마 기지마 <br>말해봐 말해봐 말해봐 <br>네 진짜 꿈을 말해봐 <br>너의 삶을 말해봐 말해봐 <br>그렇게 시작됐지 나의 삶의 꿈이 <br>그 꿈을 난 여태 잊어본 적 없지 <br>중3 때부터 난 대남협과 함께 <br>21 땐 목표한 악스홀에 섰지 <br>근데 나도 부딪혔어 현실의 벽 <br>스무살이 되자마자 진 <br>등록금 빚과 한 끼 식사의 벽 <br>당시엔 모든 것을 원망했고 <br>돈이란 게 두려웠어 <br>but 나의 motto <br>connectin' the dots <br>경험들이 날 만들었어 <br>그건 내 가사가 됐고 앨범이 됐어 <br>그 track은 돈 벌러왔어 <br>그 명곡은 real recognize real <br>그래서 난 지금 with rbw mofucka <br>uh 내 삶은 재밌어 <br>물론 그건 나의 꿈이 <br>함께 하기 때문이지 <br>uh 삶은 재밌어 <br>그건 꿈이 함께 하기 때문이지 <br>네 진짜 꿈을 말해봐 <br>너의 삶을 말해봐 <br>어떤 걸 원하고 살아 <br>그걸 절대 숨기진 마 <br>난 그 기분 너무 잘 알아 <br>현실의 벽 마주치면 <br>넌 그걸 부술 능력이 있어 <br>그러니 넌 꿈이 뭐야 <br>말해봐 말해봐 말해봐 <br>숨기지마 기지마 기지마 <br>말해봐 말해봐 말해봐 <br>네 진짜 꿈을 말해봐 <br>너의 삶을 말해봐 말해봐 <br>네 진짜 꿈을 말해봐 <br>너의 삶을 말해봐 <br>어떤 걸 원하고 살아 <br>그걸 절대 숨기진 마 <br>난 그 기분 너무 잘 알아 <br>현실의 벽 마주치면 <br>넌 그걸 부술 능력이 있어 <br>그러니 넌 꿈이 뭐야 <br>말해봐 말해봐 말해봐 <br>숨기지마 기지마 기지마 <br>말해봐 말해봐 말해봐 <br>네 진짜 꿈을 말해봐 <br>너의 삶을 말해봐 말해봐 <br>말해봐 <br>말해봐 <br>네 진짜 꿈을 말해봐 <br>너의 삶을 말해봐 말해봐 <br>]]></content><category term="마블제이 (Marvel.J)" label="마블제이 (Marvel.J)"/><category term="말해봐" label="말해봐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/류세라/필/</id><title>류세라 - 필 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:50:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:50:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%98%EC%84%B8%EB%9D%BC/%ED%95%84/" title="류세라 - 필 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[혼자가 더 나을거라 믿었죠 <br>아무말도 못하는건 아마도 <br>어설픈 내 표현땜에 우리 <br>멀어지면 어쩌나 음 <br>비가 온다면 나 피어날까요 <br>그대 내려와 이 비에 내맘 <br>녹아내려요 <br>그대 이 비가 내게 <br>내려앉아 반짝이죠 <br>익숙하게 들려오는 목소리 <br>변함없이 기다려준 그대가 <br>부드럽게 두드리는 소리 <br>떨어지는 빗방울 우 <br>비가 온다면 나 피어날까요 <br>그대 내려와 이 비에 내 맘 <br>녹아내려요 <br>그대 이 비가 내게 <br>내려와 <br>너무 추운 바람에 <br>나를 닫아버렸죠 <br>따뜻한 그대에 품 <br>다시 꿈을 꾸죠 <br>그대 내려와 이 비에 내 맘 <br>녹아내려요 <br>그대 이 비가 내게 <br>내려 앉아 반짝이죠 <br>]]></content><category term="류세라" label="류세라"/><category term="필" label="필"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/류세라/나와_걸어줘/</id><title>류세라 - 나와 걸어줘 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:50:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:50:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%98%EC%84%B8%EB%9D%BC/%EB%82%98%EC%99%80_%EA%B1%B8%EC%96%B4%EC%A4%98/" title="류세라 - 나와 걸어줘 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아름답잖아 저 하늘에 별빛이 <br>근데 있잖아 너 센치해 유난히 <br>여기 있잖아 나 니곁에 <br>여전히 귀기울여 <br>잠깐 우리 걸을까 <br>느린 걸음걸음 하나하나 <br>이제 괜찮아 <br>터벅터벅터벅터벅터벅터벅터벅 <br>나는 걸음걸음 하나하나 <br>너무 행복해 <br>이 길에서 우리 늘 함께일테니 <br>Slow <br>take it slow take it slow <br>Slow <br>take it slow take it slow <br>너도 알잖아 모든게 다 변해도 <br>나의 목소리 널 위해 노래하고 <br>지금 이 가사처럼 <br>곁에 붙어서 손을 잡고 <br>잠깐 우리 걸을까 <br>느린 걸음걸음 하나하나 <br>이제 괜찮아 <br>터벅터벅터벅터벅터벅터벅터벅 <br>나는 걸음걸음 하나하나 <br>너무 행복해 <br>이 길에 끝에서도 함께일테니 <br>I will remain <br>here and all the way <br>till the very end <br>I will remain <br>here and all the way <br>till the very end <br>Slow <br>Take it slow Take it slow <br>Slow <br>Take it slow Take it slow <br>Slow <br>Take it slow <br>Slow <br>Take it slow Take it slow <br>]]></content><category term="류세라" label="류세라"/><category term="나와 걸어줘" label="나와 걸어줘"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/Minor/</id><title>Gimmiky - Minor - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:51:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:51:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/Minor/" title="Gimmiky - Minor - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[yuh 그래 나는 철저히 Fuckin` Minor <br>피어싱 드레드 헤어 성적 취향마저 <br>자칭 힙스터 따위 흉내 관심없어 <br>지향할 건 major 아래급이 <br>아닌 독자 영역 <br>yuh 누군 예술병이라 지랄하지만 <br>남과 비슷하게 혹은 주류에 <br>의존하기엔 <br>일개 일원이 되는 것에 <br>위안을 갖지 않지 <br>같이 하기보단 홀로가 편하지 <br>빵셔틀보단 왕따로 산다 했잖아 <br>어차피 혼자니 내가 우두머리고 <br>반면 저들은 한 자리를 위해 <br>옷을 벗잖아 기꺼이 몸을 줬잖아 <br>랩퍼가 호빠랑 다름없잖아 <br>적자를 두려워해 재능이 썩잖아 <br>결국엔 레슨따위로 푼돈을 벌잖아 <br>그 돈을 모아다 유흥에 털잖아 <br>내가 갇혀있던가 <br>그래 그래 그럴수밖에 난 <br>게임부터 공부 축구마저 못해 <br>나도 저들과 같이 운동장서 <br>어울리고 싶었지 낀다고 해도 <br>수비만 보는 몸치 병신 <br>나도 최전방에 서고 싶었다 <br>모두를 제껴 골을 넣고 싶었다 <br>교실에 박혀 아이팟만 들었던 <br>찐따는 시간이 지나도 <br>방안에 박혀 있잖아 <br>나의 식대로 태도를 지켰을뿐인데 <br>극히 비주류라며 손가락질을 해 <br>일관을 가지면 꼰대가 되는 <br>세상에서 용케 똬리를 트고 <br>질긴 뿌리를 내리네 <br>남의 호의는 필요없어 <br>get the fuck out of here <br>내 공간에 훈수 두러왔담다면 꺼져 <br>남들과 다르단 우월감 <br>하나에 살아왔지 <br>아니 실은 섞이고 싶어도 못 섞여 <br>그래 나는 철저히 FUCKIN MINOR <br>그래 나는 철저히 FUCKIN MINOR <br>그래 나는 철저히 FUCKIN MINOR <br>그래 나는 철저히 FUCKIN MINOR <br>그래 나는 철저히 FUCKIN MINOR <br>그래 나는 철저히 FUCKIN MINOR <br>그래 나는 철저히 FUCKIN MINOR <br>ya 핍박에서 탈출하려 힙합을 <br>시작해도 생활의 질은 지하에 <br>방을 나와 집 밖엔 사방에 <br>적들만이 그들의 시선엔 되려 <br>내가 이방인 <br>취급 당하겠지 냉정히 말해 <br>앨범 하나 아다 겨우 뗏고 <br>아직 자리 못잡았지 <br>아니 내 사정은 꽤 평타인 듯해 <br>저들은 길치에 이미 뚫린 <br>길만 쫓아가니 <br>지나치며 듣자하니 <br>어떤 메이저 랩펀 레슨으로 <br>벤츠를 탄다하대 <br>ya 일반화는 특히나 위험하다지만 <br>하나같이 걔네 눈꺼풀은 <br>게슴츠레하네 <br>트렌드 속에 불참하는 것이 <br>주변에선 불통인 마냥 <br>이미 나는 낙인 찍혀있고 <br>내 앞에서 취해 메이저 <br>뒷담을 열변하던 그는 1차 예선 <br>탈락자 출신이죠 <br>현실은 한때 우상들은 <br>해명 하나 없이 자본 아래서의 <br>굴복과 변질을 <br>철저히 합리화 하는중 <br>그 대가로 쌓아온 커리어는 <br>통편집 당하는중 <br>방문을 열때 몇 안되는 <br>인맥조차 내게 타협 여부를 <br>물어올때 <br>분명히 PR 했지 나의 노선을 <br>그들이 틀린건 상관없고 <br>내가 다를 뿐인데 <br>엄밀히 말해 조명 한번 받고 <br>싶지 물론 사람인데 그렇다고 <br>이름값을 위해 홍등가 불빛에 <br>몸을 쬘건가 저들의 수입에 <br>쉽사리 고무 될건가 <br>최소한의 생활비조차 <br>보장받지 못해도 <br>말 한마디 조차 위안받지 못해도 <br>이런 길을 택했기에 <br>너는 더욱 기억해줘 <br>성취를 이뤘을때 배로 대접해줘 <br>그래 난 <br>실은 되고 싶어 FUCKIN` MAJOR <br>떳떳히 되고 싶어 FUCKIN` MAJOR <br>떳떳히 되고 싶어 FUCKIN` MAJOR <br>떳떳히 되고 싶어 FUCKIN` MAJOR <br>떳떳히 되고 싶어 FUCKIN` MAJOR <br>떳떳히 되고 싶어 FUCKIN` MAJOR <br>떳떳히 되고 싶어 FUCKIN` MAJOR <br>단 한번만이라도 인생의 MAJOR <br>]]></content><category term="Gimmiky" label="Gimmiky"/><category term="Minor" label="Minor"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/GFU/</id><title>Gimmiky - G.F.U. - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:51:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:51:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/GFU/" title="Gimmiky - G.F.U. - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>I told u suck ma dick now <br>I told u pussy is mine <br>I told u suck ma dick now <br>I told u pussy is mine <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>I told u suck ma dick now <br>I told u pussy is mine <br>I told u suck ma dick now <br>I told u pussy is mine <br>yeah 나는 너를 따먹었지 <br>yeah 너는 내게 따먹혔지 yeah <br>나는 니가 맛있었지 yeah <br>너도 내가 맛있던지 yeah <br>파트너로 남기던지 yeah <br>전혀 상관없어 이야기를 잠시 <br>듣자하니 니 남친도 자칭 <br>랩퍼라고 떠든다메 <br>부산에서 잘나가는 크루 <br>들어있다 카대 근데 멜론에서 <br>앨범은 안나오네 <br>걔뿐만 아녀 한낱 사클이나 <br>페북에서 자위해봐 쇼미 <br>출신들도 똑같더라 병신 <br>2차 올라간걸 자랑하더라고 병신 <br>랩퍼가 랩퍼한테 심사받네 병신 <br>작품으로 증명안함 취급안해 <br>병신 난 병신의 여친과 fuck with <br>니 남친 욕한건 미안한데 <br>너도 까놓고 내 싹을 알아보고 <br>오늘 떡친거맞지 yeah <br>그새끼가 잘될거같애 <br>전혀 아니아니아니 <br>죽었다가 깨나도 안돼 <br>yeah right yeah right <br>나도 한땐 좆밥이었지만 <br>좆뺑이 치다보니 <br>어찌 여기까지 왔네 <br>아직 갈 길이 멀지만 <br>나랑 잠을 잔걸 미래에 <br>무용담으로 말해 <br>감히 너 따위 bitch 가 운좋게 <br>전에 기미키란 진짜와 진짜로 잤네 <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>I told u suck ma dick now <br>I told u pussy is mine <br>I told u suck ma dick now <br>I told u pussy is mine <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>I told u suck ma dick now <br>I told u pussy is mine <br>I told u suck ma dick now <br>I told u pussy is mine <br>어 누구더라 아 맞아 <br>안녕 번호가 없어 <br>그래 요즘 잘 지내냐고 <br>나야물론 잘지내지 새꺄 <br>돈 없어서 좆같기는 하지만은 <br>죽기야 하겠냐 뭐 <br>아 곡하나 같이하자고 아직도 <br>안그만뒀네 징하다 짜샤 <br>너한테 녹음 노하우 물어보고 <br>내 랩 지적당할때가 아직 <br>엊그제같단말야 <br>기억나 내가 크루나가고서 <br>연락 한번 없어 아니 <br>그래 사실 다 이해해 <br>꽤 심란했겠지 기대하라 <br>입털던 2개의 믹스테잎 모조리 실패 <br>괜찮아 친구야 괜찮아 친구야 <br>재능이 없는걸 그만했음 됐잖아 <br>니말대로 인맥이 없는것이 죄같아 <br>no 너가 제일 못하는게 랩같아 <br>니 새끼가 잘될거같애 <br>전혀 아니아니아니 <br>죽었다가 깨나도 안돼 <br>yeah right yeah right <br>나도 한땐 좆밥이었지만 <br>좆뺑이 치다보니 어찌 여기까지 왔네 <br>아직 갈 길이 멀지만 나랑 <br>크루한걸 미래에 무용담으로 말해 <br>친구야 끊어야 될거 같애 <br>난 니 여친과 내 방에 함께 ㅋㅋ <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>I told u suck ma dick now <br>I told u pussy is mine <br>I told u suck ma dick now <br>I told u pussy is mine <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>GIMMIKY FUCK WITH ME <br>I told u suck ma dick now <br>I told u pussy is mine <br>I told u suck ma dick now <br>I told u pussy is mine <br>]]></content><category term="Gimmiky" label="Gimmiky"/><category term="G.F.U." label="G.F.U."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/Gore_Gang/</id><title>Gimmiky - Gore Gang - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:51:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:51:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/Gore_Gang/" title="Gimmiky - Gore Gang - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Mofuckin gore I`m fuckin gore <br>내가 잡은 <br>바이브의 장르는 horror <br>나를 가두고 25년을 <br>홀로 방문을 잠그고 자물쇠를 걸어 <br>Mofuckin gore I`m fuckin gore <br>내가 잡은 <br>바이브의 장르는 horror <br>고개를 처박고 고통에 썩어 <br>똑같이 겪어봐라 <br>너의 치부를 저격 <br>I`M FUCKIN <br>GORE GANG GORE GANG <br>GORE GANG GORE I`M FUCKIN <br>GORE GANG GORE GANG <br>GORE GANG GORE I`M FUCKIN <br>GORE GANG GORE GANG <br>GORE GANG GORE I`M FUCKIN <br>GORE GANG GORE GANG <br>GORE GANG GORE <br>I`M FUCKIN GORE <br>방이 다소 고요하지 <br>얼굴이 썩어있네 겁이 많군 <br>한때의 자신감은 대체 어디 갔어 <br>하나만은 여전하네 <br>남을 짓밟는 말투는 <br>너무나도 학수고대했지 <br>얼마나 기다려왔나 <br>이 광경을 위해 <br>가해자가 피해자로 바뀌어 <br>울부짖는 꼴을 촬영하고 <br>관전하며 자위해 <br>과거라는 것을 <br>나의 가슴 안에 파묻고 <br>너는 기억들이 가물가물하지 또 <br>변명하네 그땐 철이 없었다고 <br>좆까는 소리 할꺼면 좆이나 빨어 <br>나의 가랑이로 기어가 개처럼 <br>눈을 부라리네 역시 존심 못 버려 <br>개를 키워봐서 알지 <br>역시 남 못 주네 <br>태생이 개새끼들의 버릇 <br>헤헤헤 ok 봐주는 조건 <br>난 옆의 여자의 가랑이가 꼴려 <br>그러니까 닥치고 가랑이를 벌려 <br>너의 여자를 범하는 내 모습이 보여 <br>이제서야 기억이 나지 넌 <br>허릴 두르면서 자랑했지 그년 <br>이 얼마나 잘하는지 <br>얼마나 잘 빠는지 묘사했지 <br>내가 흠모하고 교류한걸 알면서도 <br>몰골에 침을 ㅌㅌ 오줌을 분출 <br>이제 알겠냐 니 분수를 <br>다시 한번 <br>가랑이로 무릎을 꿇고 기어가봐 <br>마지못해 용서해줄 수도 <br>난 fuckin` gore gang <br>자비 따윈 없지 <br>난 fuckin` gore gang <br>난 모두 기억하지 <br>난 fuckin` gore gang <br>자비 따윈 없지 <br>난 fuckin` gore gang <br>난 모두 기억하고 <br>말고 한땐 지니고 다녔지 <br>커터 칼을 물어뜯기 위해서 <br>갈았지 이빨을 <br>반면에 넌 까기 바빴지 <br>이빨을 입 발린 말들로 <br>형들 자지를 빨고 <br>괴롭혔지 만만한 남을 <br>그 많은 남중에 <br>내가 메인이구 말구 <br>궁금해서 물어 무얼 잘못했지 <br>내가 죽어주면 <br>아니 죽여주면 되는 건가 너를 <br>YEAHA <br>하루라도 대접받고 <br>싶었어 YEAHA <br>니 새끼의 배를 까고 싶었다 <br>YEAHA 난 정복하고 반대로 <br>너는 복종해야지 좆까 니 심부름 <br>YEAHA 타인에게 <br>과시할 권위를 위해 <br>원인과 동기 따위라곤 <br>fuck it <br>OK 쇼는 끝내야지 새꺄 <br>눈을 감아 내 방에서 영원히 안식 해 <br>Mofuckin gore I`m fuckin gore <br>내가 잡은 <br>바이브의 장르는 horror <br>나를 가두고 25년을 홀로 <br>방문을 잠그고 자물쇠를 걸어 <br>Mofuckin gore I`m fuckin gore <br>내가 잡은 <br>바이브의 장르는 horror <br>고개를 처박고 고통에 썩어 <br>똑같이 겪어봐라 <br>너의 치부를 저격 <br>I`M FUCKIN <br>GORE GANG GORE GANG <br>GORE GANG GORE I`M FUCKIN <br>GORE GANG GORE GANG <br>GORE GANG GORE I`M FUCKIN <br>GORE GANG GORE GANG <br>GORE GANG GORE I`M FUCKIN <br>GORE GANG GORE GANG <br>GORE GANG GORE <br>]]></content><category term="Gimmiky" label="Gimmiky"/><category term="Gore Gang" label="Gore Gang"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/Freaky_City_Feat_Caknow/</id><title>Gimmiky - Freaky City (Feat. Caknow) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:51:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:51:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/Freaky_City_Feat_Caknow/" title="Gimmiky - Freaky City (Feat. Caknow) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ya 빌어먹을 이곳이 <br>내 나와바리 ya <br>빌어먹을 서울예댈 자퇴한 뒤 <br>ya 광안리 문둥이 촌놈새끼 <br>단원구 고잔동 <br>639-10 살고 있지 <br>상경할 때 모은 돈 천오백 남짓 <br>보증금과 싸구려 장비에 퍼붓곤 <br>계집 좋아하는 천성 죽어도 못 버려 <br>돈 없어도 유흥과 담배는 못 끊어 <br>umm 돈 쪼달려 <br>야간이나 주말 잔업 뛰고 <br>퇴근하고 작업하는 일상의 반복 <br>umm 자퇴생이 <br>안산에 박혀서 뭐해 <br>탈출을 바란지 <br>어언 1년이 다 돼가고 <br>그래 피할 수 없다면 즐겨 <br>언제 봐도 중앙동의 처자들은 죽여 <br>77번 버스에 몸을 싣고 도착해 <br>하이에나들이 가득한 <br>야생의 풍경 ohh <br>익숙한 VIBE <br>안산 젊은이들이 욕구를 펼칠 <br>유일무이한 번화가 <br>전단지와 꽁초로 덮인 보도와 <br>안쪽엔 존재하지 업소와 보도가 <br>적나라하게 가슴골을 깐 <br>처자들 사이에서 <br>잔뜩 힘이 들어간 수컷 놈들은 <br>괜히 행인들을 야려 봐 <br>가오 살려야지 <br>나도 역시 고개 안숙이고 쳐다봐 <br>물어봐 나만큼 raw 한 놈 <br>어디에도 없어 <br>내가 추파 던짐 닥치고 벗어 <br>구석탱이 엠투 삼구 별밤 <br>짝 죄다 내 영역 맛있게 먹어 <br>Welcome to ma hood! <br>insane ansan <br>보여 이 도시의 환부 <br>이 도시의 삶을 밤새 보여줄게 <br>나와 함께 달려보자고 <br>마음껏 향유 해 <br>Freaky City <br>기이한 도시 <br>남녀 상관없이 <br>사방이 BITCHES <br>Freaky City <br>기이한 도시 <br>문화 따윈 없지 윤락의 성지 <br>Freaky City <br>기이한 도시 <br>돈 간수 잘해 자나깨나 몸조심 <br>Freaky City <br>기이한 도시 <br>이곳에서 안정을 바라는 건 <br>욕심 FUCK <br>네온사인 가득한 도시 <br>화려한 바닥에 깔린 전단지 <br>높은 하이힐 담배에 묻은 립스틱 <br>또 그걸 차지하려는 놈들은 <br>허황된 돈을 쫓지 <br>그래 이곳은 내게 삭막한 꿈을 줬지 <br>ya 안녕하십니까 선배님 <br>흐 반갑습니다 후배님 haha <br>잘 지내셨죠 형님들 호칭은 좆까 <br>취급 안 해 병신들 <br>사투리 쓰던 레게 머리 <br>꼰대 복학생 결국 <br>전공에 적응 못해 <br>뛰쳐나가 한낱 음악 한다 <br>거들먹대던 놈팽인 <br>기어이 첫 앨범을 냈네 <br>YA 그래 꽤나 방황했지 <br>문화라곤 없는 <br>이 빌어먹을 도시에서 <br>술과 담배 헌팅과 <br>원나잇 따위 말고는 <br>즐길 놀 거리가 전무했고 <br>심지어 한번은 친한 형님 <br>따라서 후기가 좋다는 <br>업소를 예약하고 <br>헌데 내상만 입었지 <br>이딴 창녀마저 나를 얕잡아보고 <br>서비스를 생략하대 <br>제기랄 내 돈 주고 <br>호구 취급 당하는 건 <br>어딜 가나 다 똑같네 <br>한창 공장 일할 때도 <br>그곳 반장들 하는 말은 <br>잘 지내보재 가족같이 <br>지랄 개똥 싸네 <br>나를 엿멕인 <br>수많은 썅놈년들과 윗대가리들 <br>한땐 증오감이 넘쳤지만 <br>더욱 자립하게 만들어줬지 <br>나의 마음가짐을 <br>정말 짜릿하네 이 도시는 말야 <br>매일이 지옥 같은 이 도시는 말야 <br>결국에 나란 놈을 구원하고 <br>구성한 건 역설적이게도 <br>이 도시 안산이란 말야 <br>Welcome to ma hood <br>insane ansan <br>보여 이 도시의 환부 <br>이 도시를 탈출함을 <br>드디어 이뤘어도 <br>막상 떠나오니 느끼는 <br>향수 FUCK it <br>Freaky City <br>기이한 도시 <br>남녀 상관없이 <br>사방이 BITCHES <br>Freaky City <br>기이한 도시 <br>문화 따윈 없지 윤락의 성지 <br>Freaky City <br>기이한 도시 <br>돈 간수 잘해 자나깨나 몸조심 <br>Freaky City <br>기이한 도시 <br>이곳에서 안정을 바라는 건 <br>욕심 FUCK <br>네온사인 가득한 도시 <br>화려한 바닥에 깔린 전단지 <br>높은 하이힐 담배에 묻은 립스틱 <br>또 그걸 차지하려는 놈들은 <br>허황된 돈을 쫓지 <br>그래 이곳은 내게 삭막한 꿈을 줬지 <br>]]></content><category term="Gimmiky" label="Gimmiky"/><category term="Freaky City (Feat. Caknow)" label="Freaky City (Feat. Caknow)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/Pray_Feat_QM/</id><title>Gimmiky - Pray (Feat. QM) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:51:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:51:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/Pray_Feat_QM/" title="Gimmiky - Pray (Feat. QM) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[간절히 Pray 해 우리아빠 씨발 <br>환갑에 나가는 노가다 그만두길 <br>간절히 Pray 해 우리엄마 보세 <br>옷가게 존나게 팔아먹어 번창하길 <br>간절히 Pray 해 우리형 은행원 <br>자랑스러워 먹어버려 은행장까지 <br>간절히 Pray 해 이 노랠 Playlist <br>에 더 많은 인간들이 추가하길 <br>fuckin` 부자 필요없어 빌어먹을 <br>투잡만 아니면 돼 잔액 없어 통장 <br>영원하자던 부산 부랄들은 떠났고 <br>허구한날 형들 자지만 blow job <br>이 씬의 정식 근로자 <br>그딴 인정 좆까고 <br>비정규직으로 기어코 살아남어 <br>개미새끼처럼 짓밟혀도 발악하죠 <br>누구처럼 매춘 할바엔 <br>목따고 자살하죠 <br>난 기도한다 중학교때 날 괴롭혔던 <br>ㅅㅈㅁ 니 새끼가 객사해 뒤지기를 <br>아님 에누리없이 똑같이 당해보고 <br>살려달라 개처럼 울부짖기를 또 <br>하나 바라는건 내 이야길 필터없이 <br>뱉기위한 단상대에 <br>자리 잡기를 원해 <br>유토피아를 향해 이륙하네 추락 <br>따윈 없이 안전히 안착하길 바래 <br>날 곧이곧대로 지켜봐 25년간 <br>짓눌렸던 삶 항상 빵사오던 <br>위치에 발악못했던 병신 <br>방안에서 개독처럼 접신 <br>불쌍한 저를 구원해주소서 탁한 <br>현실의 때를 씻을 <br>성수를 전라에 부어주소서 <br>야비하게 두 눈과 두 귀를 <br>구슬리는 악귀들을 <br>참담히 죽여주소서 <br>간절히 Pray 해 I PRAY I PRAY <br>I PRAY I PRAY I PRAY I PRAY <br>간절히 Pray 해 GO CRAY GO CRAY <br>GO CRAY GO CRAY GO CRAY GO CRAY <br>간절히 Pray 해 야훼 야훼 야훼 <br>야훼 오 나의 야훼 <br>간절히 Pray 해 oh my god <br>이 방안의 방황을 탈피할 때까지 <br>간절히 pray 해 사람들이 <br>내가 뭐를 해도 박수치며 <br>내가 내는 앨범 사길 <br>간절히 pray 해 언젠가 내가 만들 <br>회사가 돈을 쓸어담고 기부하길 <br>간절히 pray 해 그 돈으로 <br>정치해서 나이 60엔 대통령 <br>나랑 같이 음악해서 코꼈던 내 <br>팀의 얼굴에 돈다발 던지고서 헤엄 <br>구린음악을 내어 평론가의 귀마저 <br>속아넘겼던 래퍼를 베어 <br>여덞 개로 나눠 8도에 뿌리고 해줄 <br>말은 새마을식당 체인이나 해여 <br>혹시나 개업 한다면 내게 디엠보내 <br>니가 썼던 먼지덮인 <br>마잌 잘라 택빼여 <br>로 보내 개 떼가 몰려드네 그 위 <br>먹이뿌리는 난 이미해버렸지 액땜 <br>씨와이 형과 방구석에서 <br>만든 앨범으로 돈 퍼부어 <br>만든 앨범 짓누르기가 취미 <br>도끼도 버린 톰소여 <br>나도 궁금해 만약 내가 <br>회사가 있다면 흠 아마도 <br>내가 다 씹어먹을 듯해 <br>이미 나는 배가 부른데도 <br>2 년간 날 가둔 감옥 그 안에서 <br>앨범 석장을 찍어내고 나서 <br>shit 느낀 바론 <br>난 씻바 될 놈이군 뭔가 궁찍기도 <br>전에 잡아버린 기분 크 바론 <br>여름 반팔옷 하나로 버티길 잘했지 <br>회사들 컨택이 와도 <br>최고를 기다리는 중 기도 첫 줄은 <br>내가 최고 신 왕 알파고 <br>간절히 Pray 해 I PRAY I PRAY <br>I PRAY I PRAY I PRAY I PRAY <br>간절히 Pray 해 GO CRAY GO CRAY <br>GO CRAY GO CRAY GO CRAY GO CRAY <br>간절히 Pray 해 야훼 야훼 야훼 <br>야훼 오 나의 야훼 <br>간절히 Pray 해 oh my god <br>이 방안의 방황을 탈피할 때까지 <br>그리고 허물을 탈피할 때까지 <br>성충이 되어 최고의 <br>체급에 도달하기까지 <br>유혹하는 지름길이 진흙밭이라면 <br>도로 돌아가서 <br>거추장스러운 사지를 자르지 <br>종교따위 좆까고 무형의 우상을 <br>만들어내 맹목적이게도 기도를 했고 <br>내 머릴 짓이긴 신발 주인들의 <br>혼을 죽여 고개 숙여 <br>너희 무덤위에 침을 뱉어 <br>]]></content><category term="Gimmiky" label="Gimmiky"/><category term="Pray (Feat. QM)" label="Pray (Feat. QM)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/Life_Sucks/</id><title>Gimmiky - Life Sucks - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:51:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:51:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/Life_Sucks/" title="Gimmiky - Life Sucks - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[평화라는 것은 침묵에서 오는 <br>법칙 결국 친목이 <br>불화의 원인이자 권력관계를 <br>성립 포장하기 바쁜 서로의 껍질 <br>더욱 견고하게 지껄이는 <br>거짓 케이스는 친족에도 예외없지 <br>날아가는 수저 깨지는 접시 <br>새벽마다 기도하네 주와 접신 <br>왜 고성을 질러 아버지는 무엇땜에 <br>왜 울분을 토해 어머니는 무엇땜에 <br>왜 가출을 했지 우리 형은 무엇땜에 <br>무엇땜에 난 이꼴이지 대체 무엇땜에 <br>나는 묻네 진짜로 숙명이란 것이 <br>실존하면 왜 저분은 <br>모든 이를 거둔다고 이빨을 깟죠 <br>그래 뿌린대로 거둔다고 <br>난 씨발 예수와 신을 혐오하죠 <br>빌어먹을 야바위꾼들 혀를 잘러 <br>봉사하는 척 앞에선 좆을 빨고 <br>지 무리인척 뒤에선 통수까고 치가 <br>떨려 방에 박힌채 몸을 사려 <br>분위기는 심히 고어하지 <br>불청객들 죄다 좆까 <br>내 음악 못들려주지 절대로 <br>회피하는 엄마의 전화 <br>난 떳떳해보고 싶다 과거 <br>가정환경과 학창 시절 <br>단 한번도 나선 적 없던 놈은 <br>무대에 서면 아직도 <br>버릇처럼 시선을 까 <br>어깰 못피고 척추를 움츠리는 <br>병신의 삶 겉치레만 유난이지 <br>속은 문드러 무너져 fuck it ma life <br>yeah ma life sucks <br>yeah ma life sucks <br>yeah ma life sucks a men <br>ma life sucks yeah ma life sucks <br>yeah ma life sucks a men <br>ma life sucks yeah ma life sucks <br>yeah ma life sucks a men <br>ma life sucks yeah ma life sucks <br>yeah ma life sucks a men <br>]]></content><category term="Gimmiky" label="Gimmiky"/><category term="Life Sucks" label="Life Sucks"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Maurice_Moore/Selfless_Feat_Jeff_Sanon/</id><title>Maurice Moore - Selfless (Feat. Jeff Sanon) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:51:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:51:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Maurice_Moore/Selfless_Feat_Jeff_Sanon/" title="Maurice Moore - Selfless (Feat. Jeff Sanon) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You must've thought that I was waiting for you <br>You were wrong, so wrong <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah <br>You were disappointed <br>Thought that I was everything you wanted, nah <br>Everything you wanted nah <br>And now I don't see the point in making up, in making up Whoa <br>I don't see the point in making up, in making up <br>Oh <br><br>Chorus: Maurice Moore <br>I wanna make it right, yeah <br>Oh baby I wanna make it right <br>If I asked would you love me even when it gets hard <br>Baby would you say yeah, yeah <br>Say yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Yeah, yeah <br>Tell me would you say yeah <br>Would you say yeah, yeah <br>Yeah, yeah <br>Nah, 'cause you're just not that selfless <br><br>Verse 1: Maurice Moore <br>I can't help but feel lonely when you're not around <br>When you're not around, ay <br>Ya, ya, I fought so hard for you to trust me <br>Then realize that you don't love me <br>You just love yourself, you love yourself <br>And now I don't see the point in making up, in making up Oh <br>No I don't see the point in making up, in making up <br>Oh <br><br>Chorus: Maurice Moore <br>I wanna make it right, yeah <br>Oh baby I wanna make it right <br>If I asked would you love me even when it gets hard <br>Baby would you say yeah, yeah <br>Say yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Yeah, yeah <br>Tell me would you say yeah <br>Would you say yeah, yeah <br>Yeah, yeah <br>Nah, 'cause you're just not that selfless <br><br>Verse 2: Jeff Sanon <br>You was my baby no sitter <br>Who would have thought it would ever differ <br>But thinkin' bout you with another nigga <br>Got me sick to my stomach it hurt like I'm doing sit-ups Huh <br>But most of these women out here is litter Damn <br>So maybe I should reconsider <br>I don't know though <br>I'm better off dolo <br>Plus it's a lil' too late for that shit word to JoJo <br>But I miss hittin' that on the low, low <br>Give you that physical training like a dojo <br>I deleted all your provocative photos <br>You so fine you almost made my nigga break the bro code Damn <br>See I bet you feeling restless, huh <br>Don't be lying I know you feeling helpless, huh <br>Like a tilapia vendor you feeling selfish, huh <br>I bet you wish you was lil' more selfless, huh <br><br>Chorus: Maurice Moore &amp; Jeff Sanon <br>I wanna make it right, yeah <br>I bet you wish you was lil' more selfless, huh <br>Oh baby I wanna make it right <br>If I ask would love me even when it gets hard <br>Baby would you say yeah, yeah <br>Say yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Yeah, yeah <br>Tell me would you say yeah <br>Would you say yeah, yeah <br>Yeah, yeah <br>Nah, 'cause you're just not that selfless]]></content><category term="Maurice Moore" label="Maurice Moore"/><category term="Selfless (Feat. Jeff Sanon)" label="Selfless (Feat. Jeff Sanon)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Whole_Doubts/Leave_Feat_Kevin_Garrett/</id><title>Whole Doubts - Leave (Feat. Kevin Garrett) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:51:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:51:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Whole_Doubts/Leave_Feat_Kevin_Garrett/" title="Whole Doubts - Leave (Feat. Kevin Garrett) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We've come a long way <br>Saying the same things <br>My one and only <br>Make that the old me <br>You're still in my brain <br>I can't take it <br>Who's gon' save us <br><br>Pre-Chorus <br>But do you ever wanna go back <br>Tell me do you wanna go back <br>Do you ever need to go back <br>Cause i ain't never gonna go back <br><br>Chorus <br>But if you leave me now <br>Don't let me know cause i won't make it <br>Yeah if you leave me now <br>Take what you want if it's not worth breaking <br>Uh-uh i'm not sure how much more i can take baby <br>So would you leave me now <br>Just leave me now <br>Just leave me now <br><br>Verse 2 <br>It's too cold to hold on <br>Lately it feels wrong <br>I can't sleep <br>Turning out the sheets <br>Yeah you'd sure love to talk <br>And i know that you moved on <br>You ain't too proud to show it off <br><br>Pre-Chorus <br>But do you ever wanna go back <br>Tell me do you wanna go back <br>Do you really to go back <br>Cause i ain't never gonna go back <br><br>Chorus <br>But if you leave me now <br>Don't let me know cause i won't make it <br>Yeah if you leave me now <br>Take what you want if it's not worth breaking <br>Uh-uh i'm not sure how much more i can take baby <br>So would you leave me now <br>Just leave me now <br><br>Bridge <br>I only wanna go back <br>Only wanna go back if it's back to you <br>I only wanna go back <br>Only wanna go back if it's back to you <br>I only wanna go back <br>Only wanna go back if it's back to you <br>I only wanna go back <br>Only wanna go back if it's back to you <br><br>Chorus <br>But if you leave me now <br>Don't let me know cause i won't make it <br>Yeah if you leave me now <br>Take what you want if it's not worth breaking <br>Uh-uh i'm not sure how much more i can take baby <br>So would you leave me now <br>Just leave me now]]></content><category term="Whole Doubts" label="Whole Doubts"/><category term="Leave (Feat. Kevin Garrett)" label="Leave (Feat. Kevin Garrett)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dru_Hill/Get_Away/</id><title>Dru Hill - Get Away - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:51:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:51:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dru_Hill/Get_Away/" title="Dru Hill - Get Away - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Away <br>Away <br>Away <br><br>Listen <br><br>VERSE 1 - Sisqo <br>We started out together on a love journey <br>We said we would be together to the very end <br>Ain't nobody ever made love like we did Oh Yea <br>I must admit we had something special <br>Almost perfect some things we couldn't let go <br>You did yo dirt, girl <br>I did mine too <br>Now you want me gone away so <br><br>BRIDGE <br>So easy making mistakes <br>All broken down, beyond repair uhh <br>With being selfish <br>It had our selveless <br>Now it's better that we go away <br><br>Chorus - Dru Hill <br>Away <br>Never thought that we would be apart Away <br>And even with broken hearts <br>How did we let our love get away <br>How could I love give Away <br>What ever happen to your yesterdayAway <br>Never thought we would let it get away <br><br>Our future we had faded <br>Away, away, away <br><br>VERSE 2 - Sisqo <br>It's so ugly in the equation <br>That for each other had changed to us hurting <br>No more vacation <br>No more celebrations <br>Not even anniversaries <br>Joint accounts closed, moving out slow <br>No more late night walks after making love <br>It's just fading out It's just fading out <br>It's just faidng out woa <br><br>Chorus REPEAT - Dru Hill <br>Talking - Nokio <br>The first time I ever saw you girl <br>Is the day I really started believing that there were a GOD in heaven Mmmm <br>Why would he take you away Oh why, why, oh why <br><br>Repeat 3X <br>Away <br>Away <br>Away <br><br>Chorus REPEAT - Dru Hill]]></content><category term="Dru Hill" label="Dru Hill"/><category term="Get Away" label="Get Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Verse_Simmonds/Aint_For_Everybody_Feat_Wanya_Morris_Of_Boyz_II_Men/</id><title>Verse Simmonds - Ain`t For Everybody (Feat. Wanya Morris Of Boyz II Men) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:51:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:51:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Verse_Simmonds/Aint_For_Everybody_Feat_Wanya_Morris_Of_Boyz_II_Men/" title="Verse Simmonds - Ain`t For Everybody (Feat. Wanya Morris Of Boyz II Men) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pick you up, hold you <br>I'm checking for you, yeah <br>You that one, showing off <br>I'm checking for you, yeah <br><br>Hook: Verse Simmonds <br>Cause you ain't for everybody <br>You ain't just for anybody <br>You don't do things for just anybody <br>Are you really that somebody if I want somebody <br><br>Verse 1: Verse Simmonds <br>I know you tired playin' with them losers <br>So hot, need a fan or a cooler <br>Make up just for fun, you don't need it <br>Rock them clip ins when you want, don't need it <br>Yellin' money over bitches, and you mean it <br>You ain't trippin' on these niggas, you don't need 'em <br>Full time on your job, you be on it <br>It might take a little time, but you on it <br><br>Hook: Verse Simmonds <br>Cause you ain't for everybody <br>You ain't just for anybody <br>You don't do things for just anybody <br>Are you really that somebody <br>Found somebody <br>Cause you ain't for everybody <br>You ain't just for anybody <br>You don't do things for just anybody <br>Are you really that somebody if I want somebody <br><br>Verse 2: Verse Simmonds <br>Love them probably, you don't do it like the others <br>Every time you go missin', you come back later <br>You're not the easy type, you like to take your time <br>If anythin' meant for you girl, that's meant for you girl <br>I know you heard it all your life, I just wanna be a prayer for you <br>Heard you lookin' for a real one, never had a man pray for you <br>You keep it all on the low, you ain't competin' with hoes <br>You know exactly how this thing gon' go, these niggas is mad and bitches gon' hate <br><br>Hook: Verse Simmonds <br>Cause you ain't for everybody <br>You ain't just for anybody <br>You don't do things for just anybody <br>Are you really that somebody <br>Found somebody <br>Cause you ain't for everybody <br>You ain't just for anybody <br>You don't do things for just anybody <br>Are you really that somebody if I want somebody <br><br>Verse 3: Verse Simmonds <br>Girl, you rockin' with a real one <br>I can hit it, make you feel good <br>Top it off and make it real wet <br>That's the type of shit they can't get <br>I do the things that they won't do <br>I'm goin' hard cause I want you <br>I want you <br><br>Hook: Verse Simmonds <br>Cause you ain't for everybody <br>You ain't just for anybody <br>You don't do things for just anybody <br>Are you really that somebody <br>Found somebody <br>Cause you ain't for everybody <br>You ain't just for anybody <br>You don't do things for just anybody <br>Are you really that somebody if I want somebody <br><br>Bridge: Verse Simmonds <br>Cause if everybody already had it, I don't want it <br>If everybody already had it, I don't want it, keepin' it 100 <br>Cause you're too good for that <br>Are you really that somebody if I want somebody <br><br>Outro: Wanya Morris <br>Somebody, somebody to love me <br>Oh, yeah <br>I need some-somebody to care, yeah <br>I only need somebody]]></content><category term="Verse Simmonds" label="Verse Simmonds"/><category term="Ain`t For Everybody (Feat. Wanya Morris Of Boyz II Men)" label="Ain`t For Everybody (Feat. Wanya Morris Of Boyz II Men)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Travis_Mills/Just_Like_Us_This_Song_Doesnt_Have_A_Title/</id><title>Travis Mills - Just Like Us, This Song Doesn`t Have A Title - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:51:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:51:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Travis_Mills/Just_Like_Us_This_Song_Doesnt_Have_A_Title/" title="Travis Mills - Just Like Us, This Song Doesn`t Have A Title - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been moving like i never learned how to stop <br>the stickiest, eyes glued, intrigued to watch <br>i've been hearing things, actually shit alot <br>how come the pretty people speak that ugly talk <br><br>feelin me now, tryin to figure me out <br>my secrets stay where i stay as well <br>dont tell, gotta keep the mystery <br>but they want every piece they can get from me <br><br>im alone on my own <br>gotta seize my shit <br>and tell your friends to get off my dick <br>new money, young kid and they copycat the favorite <br><br>forget how i feel for right now <br>you always have a way to find things out <br>it's hard as i try to keep it low <br>you bring it up again up again <br><br>you dont care, oh just like me <br>dont go there, oh just like me <br>you can't do what i can do <br>you want to be oh just like me <br>got secrets too, oh just like me <br>creepin up on you, oh just like me <br>you can't do what i can do <br>you want to be oh just like me <br><br>Nothings free but if its for me <br>then it dont apply, im a rule changey <br>get my weed from her or she <br>bring it over delivery <br>what's the deal with these copycats <br>wash your mouth, landrymats <br>like stains tryin to be stuck to me <br>but im too damn sharp, cutlery <br><br>one of a kind and ahead of my time <br>miss that shit, make you hit rewind <br>tough to shine when your stuck behind <br>cause i ate you up now im down with nine <br><br>im sick inside from the way i drive <br>to the way i write, to the way i type <br>to the way i fly and get high, i get high <br><br>forget how i feel for right now <br>you always have a way to find things out <br>it's hard as i try to keep it low <br>you bring it up again up again <br><br>you dont care, oh just like me <br>dont go there, oh just like me <br>you can't do what i can do <br>you want to be oh just like me <br>got secrets too, oh just like me <br>creepin up on you, oh just like me <br>you can't do what i can do <br>you want to be oh just like me <br><br>oh just like me <br><br>forget how i feel for right now <br>you always have a way to find things out <br>it's hard as i try to keep it low <br>you bring it up again up again <br><br>you dont care, oh just like me <br>dont go there, oh just like me <br>you can't do what i can do <br>you want to be oh just like me <br>got secrets too, oh just like me <br>creepin up on you, oh just like me <br>you can't do what i can do <br>you want to be oh just like me]]></content><category term="Travis Mills" label="Travis Mills"/><category term="Just Like Us, This Song Doesn`t Have A Title" label="Just Like Us, This Song Doesn`t Have A Title"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Victoria_Monet/Next_Thing_-_Bet_You_Didnt_Know/</id><title>Victoria Monet - Next Thing - Bet You Didn`t Know - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:51:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:51:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Victoria_Monet/Next_Thing_-_Bet_You_Didnt_Know/" title="Victoria Monet - Next Thing - Bet You Didn`t Know - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I bet you didn't know last time was the last time <br>'Cause you woulda kissed me like it was the last time <br>Boy you gotta worry if somebody's taking your place <br>Laying their head where you used to lay <br>You know, that's life <br><br>Chorus <br>If you did right you would be right <br>Where your body wants you to be tonight <br>But you let go, shoulda held tight <br>Coulda been the one that was saying goodnight <br><br>Now I'm on the next thing <br>Next thing, next thing yeah <br>Now I'm on the next thing <br>Next thing, next thing, next thing yeah <br><br>Verse 2 <br>Bet you didn't know that while you was texting her <br>I was thinking 'bout the fact that <br>I got all these fuckin' options <br>Bet you didn't know that these n****s wait in line <br>And they hold their numbers up <br>Like they're at the fucking auction <br>Bet you didn't know that them girls that send you pictures <br>Be lookin' at my Insta so they can get the pose right <br>Bet you didn't know that I'd really up and leave <br>'Cause you don't deserve a thing <br>Hope it's fucking up your whole night <br><br>Outro <br>'Cause really you just fuckin' up your whole life <br>It's your life <br>I bet you didn't know, oh <br>I-I bet you didn't know, oh <br>I-I bet you didn't know, oh]]></content><category term="Victoria Monet" label="Victoria Monet"/><category term="Next Thing - Bet You Didn`t Know" label="Next Thing - Bet You Didn`t Know"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aaron_Camper/Guns_and_Roses/</id><title>Aaron Camper - Guns and Roses - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:51:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:51:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aaron_Camper/Guns_and_Roses/" title="Aaron Camper - Guns and Roses - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dangerous kind of love we makin <br>girl i know that you can take it <br>just make it right before you go <br><br>yeah <br>We fight <br>we argue <br>make love next day it's strange <br>just like guns and roses <br>just like guns and roses <br>if u win then i loose <br>spend my time try to get back at you <br>just like guns and roses <br>just like guns and roses <br>we going on and all night <br>cuz baby I know you can take it <br>they just love when we naked <br>but we both know that we should take it slow oh oh <br>cuz baby I get jealous whenever we ain't together <br>it's just man i never been playin games forever yeah <br>ooh oh baby oh u know u know she got bad taste yeah i'm going crazy, oh baby oh u know u know she got bad taste yeah <br>sometimes she get wild and i get loud <br>and we make up all in the same day it's crazy <br>but like guns and roses <br>just like guns and roses <br>if u stay then I go <br>spend my day try to get back to you <br>like guns and roses <br>like guns and roses <br>going on in all night <br>cuz baby I know you can take it <br>they just love when we naked <br>but we both know that we should take it slow oh oh <br>cuz baby I get jealous whenever we ain't together <br>it's just man i never been playin games forever yeah <br>ooh oh baby oh u know u know she got bad taste yeah i'm going crazy, oh baby oh u know u know she got bad taste yeah <br>dangerous kind of love we makin <br>dan-dangerous kind of love we makin <br>dan-dangerous kind of love we makin <br>dan-dangerous kind of love we makin <br>girl i know that you can take it <br>just make it right before you go <br>ooh oh baby oh u know u know she got bad taste yeah i'm going crazy, oh baby oh u know u know she got bad taste yeah <br>ooh oh baby oh u know u know she got bad taste yeah i'm going crazy, oh baby oh u know u know she got bad taste yeah <br>oh baby <br>I'm going crazy <br>oh baby <br>yeah I'm going crazy <br>but like guns and roses <br>but like guns and roses <br>yeah yeah]]></content><category term="Aaron Camper" label="Aaron Camper"/><category term="Guns and Roses" label="Guns and Roses"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JNYR/TWENTY_TEN/</id><title>JNYR - TWENTY TEN - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:52:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:52:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JNYR/TWENTY_TEN/" title="JNYR - TWENTY TEN - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wish it still was two thousand and ten babe <br><br>Verse 1 <br><br>She set the tone <br>I just performed <br>Making you moan <br>All in the zone <br><br>I need you right now, or I need a clone <br>I'm pulling up right now, I hope that you home home <br>Thinking bout your body I'm, craving <br>Watching you go down girl a-mazing <br>How did I lose you girl I'm faded Ohh, I'm faded <br><br>Fucking with these LA girls was stupid <br>When I'm in the six I think of you <br>If I sent you roses you'd discard them <br>Running out of things that I could do <br><br>Seen you on the gram and now you flexing <br>25 and in the prime of your life <br>No one likes to give out second chances <br>Though I promise I won't waste your time <br><br>Hook <br><br>Wish it still was two thousand and ten babe <br>Always on my mind I won't pretend babe <br>Wonder where you are and how you been babe <br>And I'm still bout you if you bout this babe <br><br>Like it still was two thousand and ten babe <br>Always on my mind I won't pretend babe <br>Wonder where you are and how you been babe <br>And I'm still bout you if you bout this babe <br><br>Verse 2 <br><br>I was fucking with strippers <br>I was a heavy tipper <br>I was mr long dicker <br>I was mr dismiss-her <br><br>Always thinking about my self and <br>Living living life selfish <br>Young black and helpless <br>I know I know I know <br><br>I've made mistakes but girl let go let go let go <br>You can't move forward living in the past oh no <br>Ain't no more talking now it's time to let it show <br><br>Nothing I wouldn't do <br>To prove myself to you <br>This time I'll make it right <br>Hope that you see it through <br><br>Yeah I made so much mistake yeah girl I'm to blame <br>We ain't teenagers no more it won't be the same <br>Ready if you ready girl I ain't with the games <br>No games, no games <br><br>Hook <br><br>Wish it still was two thousand and ten babe <br>Always on my mind I won't pretend babe <br>Wonder where you are and how you been babe <br>And I'm still bout you if you bout this babe <br><br>Like it still was two thousand and ten babe <br>Always on my mind I won't pretend babe <br>Wonder where you are and how you been babe <br>And I'm still bout you if you bout this babe]]></content><category term="JNYR" label="JNYR"/><category term="TWENTY TEN" label="TWENTY TEN"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trevor_Jackson/NightTime/</id><title>Trevor Jackson - NightTime - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:52:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:52:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Trevor_Jackson/NightTime/" title="Trevor Jackson - NightTime - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hook <br>In the night time, I find <br>We start to lose control <br>Cause in the night time, the moon is so bright <br>Animals we turn into <br>But it only happens when I'm with you baby <br>You be scratching, biting, got you howling at me when I get it <br>In the night time <br>I know you feel it babe <br>All this sinning, there ain't no forgiveness when I'm in it babe <br>In the night time yeah <br><br>Verse 1 <br>Said she wanna see me in the night time yeah <br>She know I'm a beast in the night time yeah <br>Call me anytime like a lifeline yeah <br>Say less, the whip now I'm in it, I be on my way in a minute <br>I just gotta pull up, park the car by the corner store <br>Apartment 304's where I'm headed to <br>I opened up the door, already on the floor <br>And she's on all fours, she know I transform <br>When she do it in the night time <br><br>Hook <br>In the night time, I find <br>We start to lose control <br>Cause in the night time, the moon is so bright <br>Animals we turn into <br>But it only happens when I'm with you baby <br>You be scratching, biting, got you howling at me when I get it <br>In the night time <br>I know you feel it babe <br>All this sinning, there ain't no forgiveness when I'm in it babe <br>In the night time yeah <br><br>Verse 2 <br>The curse fall upon me at night, and girl you got nowhere to hide <br>I start bursting outta my clothes, now there's no more white in my eyes <br>Now I got claws for my hands, I am no longer a man <br>Thought you know what happens this hour, so why didn't you tie me down <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah babe, what happened babe <br>Why didn't you tie me down tonight whoa <br>You better get ready babe, you better stop running babe <br>Cause I'm about to tear that ass up tonight <br><br>Hook <br>In the night time, I find <br>We start to lose control <br>Cause in the night time, the moon is so bright <br>Animals we turn into <br>But it only happens when I'm with you baby <br>You be scratching, biting, got you howling at me when I get it <br>In the night time <br>I know you feel it babe <br>All this sinning, there ain't no forgiveness when I'm in it babe <br>In the night time yeah]]></content><category term="Trevor Jackson" label="Trevor Jackson"/><category term="NightTime" label="NightTime"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김유연/오늘도_좋아해/</id><title>김유연 - 오늘도 좋아해 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:52:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:52:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9C%A0%EC%97%B0/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98%EB%8F%84_%EC%A2%8B%EC%95%84%ED%95%B4/" title="김유연 - 오늘도 좋아해 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[수줍게 웃는 너의 얼굴이 보여 <br>살랑살랑 내 가슴을 뛰게 하네 <br>짙은 눈썹 매력적인 입 꼬리까지 <br>나도 몰래 살짝 미소 짓게 하네 <br>그냥 느낌이 좋았던 걸까 <br>사랑이란 이 느낌 <br>오늘도 좋아해 My lover <br>어제보다 오늘 더 좋아해요 <br>특별한 네 인사에 <br>오늘도 사랑해 My lover <br>어제보다 오늘 더 사랑할래요 <br>Then I'll be kissing you <br>말없이 바라보던 네 눈빛에 취해 <br>수줍어 얼굴이 좀 빨개질 때면 <br>귀엽다며 살짝 미소를 지어줄 때 <br>나도 몰래 행복해져 어떡해 <br>안아줄까 살짝 키스를 할까 <br>하루 종일 난 생각해 <br>오늘도 좋아해 My lover <br>어제보다 오늘 더 좋아해요 <br>특별한 네 인사에 <br>오늘도 사랑해 My lover <br>어제보다 오늘 더 사랑할래요 <br>Then I'll be kissing you <br>어느덧 서로가 편해져 가도 <br>달콤한 순간 기억해줄래요 <br>누군가 우리를 가볍다 생각해도 <br>이런 특별한 만남이 <br>운명처럼 느껴지게 하네요 <br>오늘도 좋아해 My lover <br>어제보다 오늘 더 좋아해요 <br>특별한 우리 인사 <br>오늘도 사랑해 My lover <br>어제보다 더 <br>사랑할래요 매일을 <br>이렇게 속삭여요 <br>언제까지나 함께해 <br>사랑하는 너와 나 <br>백일이 지나 <br>이백일 삼백일까지 사랑할게 <br>]]></content><category term="김유연" label="김유연"/><category term="오늘도 좋아해" label="오늘도 좋아해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Four_Lads/Time_After_Time_From_Stage_Show/</id><title>The Four Lads - Time After Time (From `Stage Show`) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:55:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:55:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Four_Lads/Time_After_Time_From_Stage_Show/" title="The Four Lads - Time After Time (From `Stage Show`) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What could I words I say to you <br>They can convey to you what's in my heart <br>If you could hear it's this <br><br>The things I've learned and said <br>Time after time <br>I tell myself that I'm so lucky to be loving you <br>So lucky to be the one I run to see <br>In the evening when the day is trough <br>I only know what I know <br>The passing years will show <br>You've kept my love so young, so new <br>And time after time <br>You heard me say that I'm so lucky to be loving you <br>I only know what I know <br>The passing years will show <br>You've kept my love so young, so new <br>And time after time <br>You heard me say that I'm so lucky to be loving you]]></content><category term="The Four Lads" label="The Four Lads"/><category term="Time After Time (From `Stage Show`)" label="Time After Time (From `Stage Show`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Four_Lads/Moments_To_Remember_From_Stage_Show/</id><title>The Four Lads - Moments To Remember (From `Stage Show`) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:55:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:55:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Four_Lads/Moments_To_Remember_From_Stage_Show/" title="The Four Lads - Moments To Remember (From `Stage Show`) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[January to December <br>We'll have moments to remember <br><br>The New Years Eve <br>We did the town <br>The day we tore <br>The goal post down <br>We'll have these <br>Moments to remember <br><br>The quiet walks <br>The noisy fun <br>The ballroom prize <br>We almost won <br>We'll have these <br>Moments to remember <br><br>Though summer <br>Turns to winter and <br>The present disappears <br>The laughter we <br>Were glad to share will <br>Echo through the years <br><br>When other nights <br>And other days <br>May find us gone <br>Our separate ways <br>We will have these <br>Moments to remember <br><br>The drive in movie <br>Where we'd go and somehow <br>Never watched the show <br>We will have these <br>Moments to remember <br><br>Though summer <br>Turns to winter and <br>The present disappears <br>The laughter we <br>Were glad to share will <br>Echo through the years <br><br>When other nights <br>And other days <br>May find us gone <br>Our separate ways <br>We will have these <br>Moments to remember]]></content><category term="The Four Lads" label="The Four Lads"/><category term="Moments To Remember (From `Stage Show`)" label="Moments To Remember (From `Stage Show`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Four_Lads/Love_Is_A_Many-Splendored_Thing_From_Stage_Show/</id><title>The Four Lads - Love Is A Many-Splendored Thing (From `Stage Show`) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:55:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:55:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Four_Lads/Love_Is_A_Many-Splendored_Thing_From_Stage_Show/" title="The Four Lads - Love Is A Many-Splendored Thing (From `Stage Show`) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love is a many splendored thing <br>It's the April rose that only grows in the early Spring <br>Love is nature's way of giving a reason to be living <br>The golden crown that makes a man a king <br>Once on a high and windy hill, In the morning mist <br>Two lovers kissed and the world stood still <br>Then your fingers touched my silent heart and taught it how to sing <br>Yes, true love's a many splendored thing <br><br>Love is a many splendored thing <br>It's the April rose that only grows in the early Spring <br>Love is nature's way of giving a reason to be living <br>The golden crown that makes a man a king <br>Once on a high and windy hill, In the morning mist <br>Two lovers kissed and the world stood still <br>Then your fingers touched my silent heart and taught it how to sing <br>Yes, true love's a many splendored thing]]></content><category term="The Four Lads" label="The Four Lads"/><category term="Love Is A Many-Splendored Thing (From `Stage Show`)" label="Love Is A Many-Splendored Thing (From `Stage Show`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sleek_Jeezy/이래도_돼_Feat_Steel_Prod_Charcoal/</id><title>Sleek Jeezy - 이래도 돼 (Feat. Steel) (Prod. Charcoal) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:56:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:56:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sleek_Jeezy/%EC%9D%B4%EB%9E%98%EB%8F%84_%EB%8F%BC_Feat_Steel_Prod_Charcoal/" title="Sleek Jeezy - 이래도 돼 (Feat. Steel) (Prod. Charcoal) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다 비워 둬 오늘밤 미러볼 아래 <br>Rockin' on that speaker <br>내가 누구였건 날 어떻게 기억하던 <br>상관 없으니 다 미뤄 <br>결국 붙잡아도 nothing <br>나만 구차했던 something <br>다시 말해 끝난 거라 말했고 <br>너는 도망갔지 멀리 <br>머리부터 발까지 fresh 하게 <br>멋도 냈어 gold chain <br>세 개나 걸치고 나와서 아빠차 <br>핸들을 붙잡아 <br>죽을 준비 됐어 오늘밤에 ya <br>줄었어 손가락에 무게 <br>술잔에 나를 담궈 <br>아무런 생각이 없게 <br>아티산 향이 내 앞에 <br>너에게 베이게 할거야 <br>밤새도록 어깨 부딪혀 <br>up all night yeah <br>Fresh more cash <br>Don't worry about that <br>전부 다 증발시켜 <br>너의 기억까지 yeah <br>Fresh more dance <br>Hey baby I don't care <br>신경 끄고 폰 집어 넣어둬 <br>나는 이래도 돼 <br>Don't worry about me <br>Don't worry yeah <br>추억들까지 다 정리해 <br>Don't worry about me <br>Don't worry yeah <br>baby I don't care baby <br>I don't care <br>이래도 돼 나는 이래도 <br>나는 이래도 돼 전부 치워줘 <br>집에 안가도 돼 니가 나라도 <br>이랬을 거야 all day <br>지울 거야 all day <br>이쯤 되면 잊어버리고도 남았어 <br>그래서 더욱 깊은 밤을 걸어 다녔어 <br>머리 속은 매일 여름이야 <br>일주일 내내 장마가 찾아와도 <br>난 계속 party야 yeah <br>나를 적시고 있는 말리부 <br>온더락 잔 들고 act like Holly Wood <br>내 발걸음 따라 오는 프라다 shoes <br>Oh my god 내 노래처럼 <br>흘러가는 밤이야 <br>너 없이 맞는 아침 어떨지 아직도 <br>감이 안오네 잡은 손은 <br>그래 너가 아닌걸 yeah <br>어지럽던 머리가 아침쯤 깨면 <br>난 깨닫겠지 너와 나의 <br>freakin' break up tonight <br>Fresh more cash <br>Don't worry about that <br>전부 다 증발시켜 <br>너의 기억까지 yeah <br>Fresh more dance <br>Hey baby I don't care <br>신경 끄고 폰 집어 넣어둬 <br>나는 이래도 돼 <br>Don't worry about me <br>Don't worry yeah <br>추억들까지 다 정리해 <br>Don't worry about me <br>Don't worry yeah <br>baby I don't care baby <br>I don't care <br>이래도 돼 나는 이래도 <br>나는 이래도 돼 전부 치워줘 <br>집에 안가도 돼 니가 나라도 <br>이랬을 거야 all day <br>지울 거야 all day <br>다 비워 둬 오늘밤 미러볼 아래 <br>Rockin' on that speaker <br>너가 누구였건 날 어떻게 기억하던 <br>상관 없으니 다 미뤄 <br>]]></content><category term="Sleek Jeezy" label="Sleek Jeezy"/><category term="이래도 돼 (Feat. Steel) (Prod. Charcoal)" label="이래도 돼 (Feat. Steel) (Prod. Charcoal)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sleek_Jeezy/Down_Feat_Steel_Prod_Charcoal/</id><title>Sleek Jeezy - Down (Feat. Steel) (Prod. Charcoal) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T18:56:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T18:56:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sleek_Jeezy/Down_Feat_Steel_Prod_Charcoal/" title="Sleek Jeezy - Down (Feat. Steel) (Prod. Charcoal) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 계속 얘기를 흘려 들어 <br>이젠 지칠 대로 지쳐 있어 <br>너는 모를 거야 아마 <br>아닌 척 하려 해도 티가 나 <br>마음이 식어버린 네게 <br>기름을 부어 봤자 무슨 소용 이야 <br>Last night baby <br>너가 어디 간지 알고 있지 <br>네 친구는 내게 <br>걱정 말라는 헛소리를 늘어 놓지 <br>말이 되는 소리를 해 <br>그러면 어제 밤 네 허리에 <br>손을 두른 놈은 뭔데 <br>말을 해봐 대체 <br>핑계를 두른 너는 all night <br>거짓말을 하고 all night <br>둘러 대지 말아줘 <br>매일 그런 건 아니라는 <br>헛소리는 하지 말아줘 <br>인정 하는 너는 all night <br>웃어보려 해도 <br>I'm down down down <br>넘어가보려 해도 <br>I'm down down down <br>신이 난 척을 해도 <br>I'm down down down <br>아무렇지 않은 척 <br>I'm down down down <br>down down down <br>Why do i think of our love is <br>going down and down <br>나도 날 믿고 싶어 물론 지금은 아냐 <br>hey 니 폰이 꺼진 뒤로 <br>달려나갔지 지금 <br>we bout to go down for real <br>that's why we crazy now <br>ay 듣기 싫은 소린 계속 들려오네 <br>비어있지 않길 바래 니 손에 moet <br>택시 요금은 끝도 없이 오르고있네 <br>지갑을 들고 나온 지도 <br>모른 채로 go 해 <br>The sky is fallin' <br>I can't handle bout that <br>이게 우리 마지막이 아니기를 바래 <br>이번에도 전화 안받으면 어떡할래 <br>제발 오늘이 가기 전에 <br>핑계를 두른 너는 all night <br>거짓말을 하고 all night <br>둘러 대지 말아줘 <br>매일 그런 건 아니라는 <br>헛소리는 하지 말아줘 <br>인정 하는 너는 all night <br>웃어보려 해도 <br>I'm down down down <br>넘어가보려 해도 <br>I'm down down down <br>신이 난 척을 해도 <br>I'm down down down <br>아무렇지 않은 척 <br>I'm down down down <br>down down down <br>I'm down down down <br>니 주위를 맴돌아 <br>around round round <br>막이 내리고 있잖아 마지막 <br>장면이 끝나고 난 뒤에 나갈 시간이 <br>되어버린 거겠지 우리 사이 <br>오늘 밤에 난 대체 뭐 때문에 ride <br>돌아서는 모습마저 끝내 못본 다음 <br>내일 아침이면 남보다 못한 <br>사이가 되어버리고 말아 <br>복잡해진 머리 속이 아프네 <br>너를 마주할 땐 대체 무슨 말을 해 <br>어차피 끝난 거라면 뒤 돌아 서는게 <br>맞는게 아닐까 싶어서 핸들을 돌리네 <br>웃어보려 해도 안되는 건 안되나 봐 <br>풀지 못한 오늘 밤 우리처럼 <br>널 잊어보려 해도 답이 안 나오잖아 <br>더 귀찮게 할 생각은 없으니까 <br>돌아 갈래 난 <br>웃어보려 해도 <br>I'm down down down <br>넘어가보려 해도 <br>I'm down down down <br>신이 난 척을 해도 <br>I'm down down down <br>아무렇지 않은 척 <br>I'm down down down <br>down down down <br>]]></content><category term="Sleek Jeezy" label="Sleek Jeezy"/><category term="Down (Feat. Steel) (Prod. Charcoal)" label="Down (Feat. Steel) (Prod. Charcoal)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/심재준/그댈_보내고/</id><title>심재준 - 그댈 보내고 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:00:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:00:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%AC%EC%9E%AC%EC%A4%80/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%88_%EB%B3%B4%EB%82%B4%EA%B3%A0/" title="심재준 - 그댈 보내고 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 그대가 내곁을 떠났죠 <br>안녕이란 말 짧은 인사도 없이 <br>나는 이별을 믿을 수가 없어요 <br>함께 만든 추억들 모두 가져가 줘요 <br>오늘 그대를 멀리 떠나 보냈죠 <br>잘가라는 말 한 마디 못하고 <br>나는 그대를 잊을 수가 없어요 <br>함께 나눈 사랑도 잊을 수가 없어요 <br>그대가 그리워 눈물나는 날에는 <br>함께 걷던 그길도 함께 갔던 카페도 <br>가끔 나 혼자서 찾아가 보곤 해요 <br>그대의 숨결이 남아 있는 그곳에 <br>오늘 그대를 멀리 떠나 보냈죠 <br>잘가라는 말 한 마디 못하고 <br>나는 그대를 잊을 수가 없어요 <br>함께 나눈 사랑도 잊을 수가 없어요 <br>그대가 그리워 눈물나는 날에는 <br>함께 걷던 그길도 함께 갔던 카페도 <br>가끔 나 혼자서 찾아가 보곤 해요 <br>그대의 숨결이 남아 있는 그곳에 <br>그대가 그리워 잠 못 이루는 밤엔 <br>함께 보던 영화도 함께 찍은 사진도 <br>가끔 나 울면서 보다 잠이 들어요 <br>오늘도 이렇게 그댈 생각 하면서 <br>사랑했지만 떠나 보냈고 <br>사랑했기에 늘 그리워 하네 <br>오늘 그대가 내곁을 떠났죠 <br>안녕이란 말 짧은 인사도 없이 <br>나는 그대를 잊을 수가 없어요 <br>사랑 합니다 나의 소중한 추억 <br>사랑 합니다 나의 소중한 사람 <br>]]></content><category term="심재준" label="심재준"/><category term="그댈 보내고" label="그댈 보내고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/심재준/산/</id><title>심재준 - 산 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:00:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:00:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%AC%EC%9E%AC%EC%A4%80/%EC%82%B0/" title="심재준 - 산 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[산에 오르면 숨은 가빠도 <br>마음만은 상쾌한 걸 <br>맑은 공기와 파란 하늘이 <br>내 가슴 깊이 들어오네 <br>산에 오르면 세상 모든게 <br>아름답게 느껴지네 <br>부는 바람에 구름을 따라 <br>근심 걱정 모두 잊고 <br>나는 어느새 한그루의 나무되어 <br>깊은 숲 속 한 가운데 서 있네 <br>내 맘 어느새 흩날리는 꽃잎처럼 <br>부는 바람에 춤을 추고 있네 <br>산에 살고 싶다 했지 <br>그 언젠가 풍진 세상을 떠나 <br>산이 되고 싶다 했지 <br>그 언젠가 네가 들려준 얘기 <br>그래도 그저 나무는 <br>한그루 나무일 뿐 <br>산에 오르면 좁은 가슴도 <br>하늘처럼 넓어질까 <br>세월이 가도 수많은 계절 <br>언제나 늘 그자리에 <br>나는 어느새 한그루의 나무되어 <br>깊은 숲 속 한 가운데 서 있네 <br>내 맘 어느새 흩날리는 꽃잎처럼 <br>부는 바람에 춤을 추고 있네 <br>산에 살고 싶다 했지 <br>그 언젠가 풍진 세상을 떠나 <br>산이 되고 싶다 했지 <br>그 언젠가 네가 들려준 얘기 <br>그래도 그저 나무는 <br>한그루 나무일 뿐 <br>그래도 그저 나무는 <br>한그루 나무일 뿐 <br>]]></content><category term="심재준" label="심재준"/><category term="산" label="산"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brian_Fallon/My_Name_Is_The_Night_Color_Me_Black/</id><title>Brian Fallon - My Name Is The Night (Color Me Black) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:01:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:01:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brian_Fallon/My_Name_Is_The_Night_Color_Me_Black/" title="Brian Fallon - My Name Is The Night (Color Me Black) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Can you give me something <br>Tonight, I'm so alone <br>The moon is upside down <br>Hanging on a telephone <br>But I remember every little bad dream <br>Every pretty slow dance <br><br>Pre-Chorus <br>So can I pick you up later <br>When your temperature's better <br>If you need a little shelter <br>Be your cool operator <br>Keep it all quiet, yeah <br>Just a little louder <br>Let the night wind you down, baby, down <br><br>Chorus <br>And she smiles, how 'bout that <br>I was just about to jump before you called me back <br>And you know the pain comes home <br>And the whispers come to call me in my bed when I'm alone <br>And I've lost so much more than I ever had <br>Now my name is the night, honey, color me black <br>C-color me black <br><br>Verse 2 <br>Can I take you somewhere <br>Would it make a difference <br>Like pretty roses on a deathbed <br>But I remember you in your white dress <br>In your mama's hands <br><br>Pre-Chorus <br>So can I pick you up later <br>When your temperature's better <br>If you need a little shelter <br>Be your cool operator <br>Keep it all quiet, yeah <br>Just a little louder <br>Let the night wind us down, baby, down <br><br>Chorus <br>And she smiles, how 'bout that <br>I was just about to jump before you called me back <br>And you know the pain comes home <br>And the whispers come to call me in my bed when I'm alone <br>And I've lost so much more than I ever had <br>Now my name is the night, honey, color me black <br>C-color me black <br><br>Bridge <br>And how long, how long <br>Until you believe that part of me is gone <br>With your sweet, naive kiss <br>Well I used to feel the same until I let the darkness in <br>And it cost me nothing, baby <br>Nah, nothing more than this <br>Nothing more than this useless heart in my chest <br>Nothing that I needed, nothing I regret <br>Nothing that I needed, and I'd do it all again <br>I'd do it all again <br><br>Chorus <br>And she smiles, how 'bout that <br>I was just about to jump before you called me back <br>But you know the pain comes home <br>And the whispers come to call me in my bed when I'm alone <br>Singing, Ooh, not just yet <br>When I go, I'll be going out in flames and fiery wrecks <br>And the quiet to me, such an ominous sound <br>Said my name is the nighttime now <br>Yes, the quiet to me, such an ominous sound <br>And my name is the night, honey, color me black]]></content><category term="Brian Fallon" label="Brian Fallon"/><category term="My Name Is The Night (Color Me Black)" label="My Name Is The Night (Color Me Black)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stella_Donnelly/Mechanical_Bull/</id><title>Stella Donnelly - Mechanical Bull - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:04:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:04:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stella_Donnelly/Mechanical_Bull/" title="Stella Donnelly - Mechanical Bull - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm gonna throw you all off me <br>Like a mechanical bull and you'll be sorry <br>I'll be your sweet sugar muffin with the cream <br>But stay on my back for too long and I'll spin ya <br><br>Chorus <br>I need to be alone <br>You've been at my throat <br>I need to be alone <br>You've been at my throat <br><br>Verse 2 <br>I'm gonna put you in place like a fixture <br>On an emotional blackmail bookshelf <br>I'll be your darling, tits, legs, honey, sweet pea <br>But I'm a fucking arsehole if you ask me <br><br>Chorus <br>I need to be alone <br>You've been at my throat <br>I need to be alone <br>You've been at my throat <br>Need to be alone <br>You've been at my throat <br>I need to be alone <br>You've been at my throat <br><br>Bridge <br>I'm gonna throw you all off me <br>Like a mechanical bull and you'll be sorry <br>I'm gonna throw you all off me <br>Like a mechanical bull and you'll be sorry <br>I'm gonna throw you all off me <br>Like a mechanical bull then you'll be sorry <br>I'm gonna throw you all off me <br>Like a mechanical bull then you'll be sorry <br><br>Chorus <br>I need to be alone <br>You've been at my throat <br>I need to be alone <br>You've been at my throat <br>I need to be alone <br>You've been at my throat <br>I need to be alone <br>You've been at my throat]]></content><category term="Stella Donnelly" label="Stella Donnelly"/><category term="Mechanical Bull" label="Mechanical Bull"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김홍일/Say_Goodbye_Feat_한지원/</id><title>김홍일 - Say Goodbye (Feat. 한지원) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:04:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:04:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%99%8D%EC%9D%BC/Say_Goodbye_Feat_%ED%95%9C%EC%A7%80%EC%9B%90/" title="김홍일 - Say Goodbye (Feat. 한지원) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 나를 믿었니 그렇게 울고말 것을 <br>나 아니면 행복히 <br>웃고 있었을 너인데 <br>하지만 아직도 보내야 했었던 내가 <br>뒤늦은 후회 속에 <br>힘겨운 눈물만이 흘러 <br>기억해 그대 내게 <br>우리 영원할 수 있다고 <br>그랬던 말에 내가 <br>너무 가슴 아프게 했나 <br>미안해 날 잊을만큼 <br>너 행복하라고 나 <br>이제는 보낼 수 있어 <br>그 어디에로 say goodbye <br>왜 나를 떠나니 그렇게 아파하면서 <br>표정없는 얼굴로 <br>널 잊어야 한다며 가니 <br>세상에 아름다움 <br>모두 작아진 것처럼 <br>행복해했던 여린 너의 마음 <br>슬프게 했나 <br>미안해 날 잊을만큼 <br>너 행복하라고 나 <br>이제는 보낼 수 있어 <br>그 어디에로 say goodbye <br>날 용서해줘 난 아무 말 하지 못해 <br>가끔 아프면 눈물로 대신하면 돼 <br>My love <br>기억해 그대 내게 <br>우리 영원할 수있다고 <br>그랬던 말에 내가 <br>너무 가슴 아프게 했나 <br>미안해 날 잊을만큼 <br>너 행복하라고 나 <br>이제는 보낼 수 있어 <br>그 어디에로 say goodbye <br>say goodbye <br>]]></content><category term="김홍일" label="김홍일"/><category term="Say Goodbye (Feat. 한지원)" label="Say Goodbye (Feat. 한지원)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Wandering_Hearts/If_I_Fall/</id><title>The Wandering Hearts - If I Fall - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:04:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:04:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Wandering_Hearts/If_I_Fall/" title="The Wandering Hearts - If I Fall - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If I were to fall <br>Would you catch me now <br>And before I crumble <br>In all my doubts <br><br>If I were to fall <br>Would I hit the ground <br>If I were to fall <br>Would you catch me now <br><br>Got this bottle of red <br>Thoughts in my head <br>Blue eyes of surprise <br>And pain <br>I won't spend my whole <br>In heartache and pain <br>If I fall <br>Would you catch me again <br><br>If I were to fly <br>Spread your wings and see <br>We can be free like birds <br>Love like it don't hurt you and me <br><br>And help me climb high <br>I won't look down <br>But if I asked you to save me <br>Would you catch me now <br><br>I've got this bottle of red <br>Thoughts in my head <br>Blue eyes of surprise <br>And pain <br>I won't spend my whole <br>In heartache and pain <br>If I fall <br>Would you catch me again <br><br>I don't recognize the face <br>That stares back at me <br>The empty cries that help us <br>Ease the pain <br><br>Got this bottle of red <br>Thoughts in my head <br>Blue eyes of surprise <br>And pain <br>I won't spend my whole <br>In heartache and pain <br>If I fall <br>Would you catch me <br>If I fall <br>Would you catch me <br>If I fall <br>Would you catch me again]]></content><category term="The Wandering Hearts" label="The Wandering Hearts"/><category term="If I Fall" label="If I Fall"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Noels_Chemical_Effluence/</id><title>The Fall - Noel&apos;s Chemical Effluence - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:04:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:04:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Noels_Chemical_Effluence/" title="The Fall - Noel&apos;s Chemical Effluence - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Noel's chemical effluence <br><br>We were going right through the Alps <br>When we picked up this fabulous scent <br>Of Noel's Chemical Effluence <br><br>Noel's chemical effluence <br><br>There was a fuss about the elements <br>Waiting for the keyboards as ever <br>The firmament of it is going out the exit <br><br>Noel's chemical effluence <br><br>There's an inherent disease <br>Goes with an inbalance of the juices <br>In the brain that in transit <br>Causes one to envisage white faces <br>As if spiked by mescalin <br><br>Noel's chemcial effluence <br><br>And we're going right through the Alps <br>Look what happened at the lodge <br>Look what happened at the castle <br>Look at the red-purple vomit stream <br>From the bed, angled <br>Right into the bathroom <br><br>On the finger of your banker bound <br>And when all else fails <br>We can always blow your whistle <br><br>In work, in pleasure, I'll come for you <br>The abdominizer, in excellence]]></content><category term="The Fall" label="The Fall"/><category term="Noel&apos;s Chemical Effluence" label="Noel&apos;s Chemical Effluence"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Eds_Babe/</id><title>The Fall - Ed&apos;s Babe - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:04:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:04:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Eds_Babe/" title="The Fall - Ed&apos;s Babe - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Edward lived with Mary <br>Like sister and brother <br>Till one night <br>Men are this <br>Men are that <br>DIY <br>Women too <br>DIY <br>DIY <br>Then there was three <br>DIY <br>A new start <br>DIY <br>A wierd wake <br>DIY <br>It all changed after Ed's babe <br>DIY <br><br>Ed's babe x3 <br><br>See Ed on a plane <br>DIY <br>White bundle <br>DIY <br>In his arms <br>DIY <br>Ed's baby <br><br>DIY <br>See them working away <br>DIY <br>In bar rocking <br>DIY <br>Folly is a cloak of knavery <br>DIY <br><br>Ed's babe x3 <br><br>OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOhs till end <br><br>Ed's babe <br>See him working away <br>Fucking in a bar <br>Folly is the cloak of knavery <br>Cos on each arm, girls, twenty one <br><br>Ed's babies x6 <br><br>Life up in smoke <br>Babe rolled like a joint <br>DIY <br>Hunger in their home <br>DIY <br><br>Ed's babe x3]]></content><category term="The Fall" label="The Fall"/><category term="Ed&apos;s Babe" label="Ed&apos;s Babe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Crew_Filth/</id><title>The Fall - Crew Filth - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:05:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:05:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Crew_Filth/" title="The Fall - Crew Filth - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[From the valleys of Leicestershire <br>And all over <br>Came mystic crew filth <br>The first was Dave Bush-babe <br>The second was Graham pony-tail <br>They were mystic crew filth <br>Crew filth <br><br>mock Urdu or Punjabi <br><br>Then from the land of the accordion <br>Came Dave Kiwi <br>He was crew filth <br>He had the shirts <br>He wouldn't meditate <br>On his monitor room <br>Mystic <br>Crew filth <br><br>Hey mystic crew filth <br>Crew filth X4 <br>Where did they come from <br>The little motherfuckers <br>Nobody knows <br>Nobody bothers <br>Crew filth <br>Crew filth <br><br>Crew filth <br><br>One was a Kiwi <br>One was a Bush-baby <br>One had tattoos on his legs <br>One had brown spectacles on his head <br>Motherfuckers <br>Crew filth <br><br>Crew filth <br><br>Hey Kenny, tell us about crew filth <br><br>Crew filth X3 <br><br>But those crew filth <br>They had sensitive sides to their nature <br>They would smoke pot in their rooms <br>They were always behind you <br>That's why we kept our backs to the walls <br>You gotta watch your wallet, man <br>Crew filth <br><br>What about crew filth Bill <br>Bill was King of the fucking Motherfucker crew filth <br>He had to do some work one night <br>Then his hair turned white <br>Crew filth baby X3 <br><br>Crew filth motherfucker <br><br>He was the worst, one of the worst X3 <br>Gotta watch your friends <br>Watch your girl <br>You never can tell <br>He might kill a tab <br>While you're jumping off <br>All your friends might turn out to be <br>Crew filth]]></content><category term="The Fall" label="The Fall"/><category term="Crew Filth" label="Crew Filth"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Married_2_Kids/</id><title>The Fall - Married, 2 Kids - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:05:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:05:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Married_2_Kids/" title="The Fall - Married, 2 Kids - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In 1978 <br>Was in a hotel in Notting Hill Gate <br>Now in 1992 <br>Staying in a hotel in Notting Hill Gate <br><br>Abject <br><br>I'm too busy to think <br>Too busy to work <br>Just can't cut it <br><br>Married, 2 kids <br>Married, 2 kids <br><br>I pretend to go to work <br>I pretend to go to work <br>Got a porta-fax <br>Aftershave like mustard <br>Two pints of lager do me in <br>And The Spirit of Man <br>Is a pub I go in <br>I'm married, 2 kids <br>Have a peculiar goatish smell <br>Am a long-winded article <br>I get livid <br>Married, 2 kids <br>Married, 2 kids]]></content><category term="The Fall" label="The Fall"/><category term="Married, 2 Kids" label="Married, 2 Kids"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Gentlemens_Agreement/</id><title>The Fall - Gentlemen&apos;s Agreement - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:05:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:05:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Gentlemens_Agreement/" title="The Fall - Gentlemen&apos;s Agreement - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We plough the fields together <br>In all types of intemperance <br>Our bones cracked in unison <br>Gentlemen's, gentlemen's agreement <br><br>You know what he is <br>And probably still is <br>Sticking his colours <br>To whatever new mast there is <br>But our agreement is over <br><br>I thought we had some kind of agreement <br>But with you it was just prurience <br>You're addicted to excitement <br>My energies are down now with yours <br>And you're sitting on my back fence <br>But I thought we had an agreement <br>Gentlemen's, gentlemen's agreement <br><br>Your brain is software <br>Your brain is Game Boy <br>It's filled with excretement <br>And your short-term memory <br>Will fleetingly remember <br>Our gentlemen's, gentlemen's agreement <br><br>Gentlemen's, gentlemen's agreement <br>Gentlemen's, gentlemen's agreement]]></content><category term="The Fall" label="The Fall"/><category term="Gentlemen&apos;s Agreement" label="Gentlemen&apos;s Agreement"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/So-Called_Dangerous/</id><title>The Fall - So-Called Dangerous - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:05:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:05:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/So-Called_Dangerous/" title="The Fall - So-Called Dangerous - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The selfish smiling fool and the sullen frowning fool shall both be thought wise <br><br>Think <br>Like mountain climbing <br>or skiing in the alps <br>Think of it <br>I don't <br><br>It was a big fat February <br>Wet, the ugly pavement cracked <br>Pause, unsafe <br><br>I thought <br>Insect posse will be crushed <br>It was a bit of Code Selfish <br><br>There was not much going on <br>in the minds of the weak <br>They were unprepared to be torched <br>By lighter kleptomaniacs <br>So-called dangerous <br><br>There is mad <br>And there is bad <br>And there is sad <br>And there is bad and sad <br>Dangerous <br><br>And the meek shall inherit the mirth <br><br>They were big, panoramic <br>Same again, sir <br>How can you have the same again <br><br>But they say <br>Dangerous]]></content><category term="The Fall" label="The Fall"/><category term="So-Called Dangerous" label="So-Called Dangerous"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Just_Waiting/</id><title>The Fall - Just Waiting - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:05:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:05:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Just_Waiting/" title="The Fall - Just Waiting - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pensioner's waiting for leap year to come <br>And the young singer's waiting to sing <br>And there's a gardener outside a big estate <br>Waiting for the grass to turn green <br><br>The drunk is waiting for an easy mark <br>The hitchhiker is waiting for a ride <br>And the prisoner's waiting for a prison break <br>And the surfer is waiting for the tide <br><br>Ah just waiting <br><br>You know everything comes to a standstill <br>Nothing seems to make a turn <br>Cause the worm's still waitin' for the early bird <br>And the early bird's waitin' for the worm <br><br>And nobody wants to do nothing <br>Just waiting for a finger in the pie <br>And waitin' for a call from a TV show <br>Or waitin' for an uncle to die 1-2-3 <br><br>Everybody's waitin' for something <br>And nothing ever turns out right <br>Because the night shift is waiting for the morning <br>And the burglar is waiting for the night <br><br>Congregation is waitin' for the vicar <br>And the vicar is waitin' for the groom <br>The groom is waiting for his new bride <br>But the bride is waitin' for June <br><br>And everybody is just waitin' <br>And nobody wants to settle down <br>They got their heads in a holo-video <br><br>The cretin is waitin for U2 to come on MTV again <br>But the producer is waiting for the blonde bird <br>And the blonde girl's waitin' for him <br><br>Nobody wants to do nothing <br>Just waiting for their chips and their pie <br>Waitin' for a call from a big quiz show <br>Or waitin' for some rich relation to die <br><br>You know everything comes to a standstill <br>Nothing ever makes a turn <br>And the worm is waitin' for the grass to turn green <br>While the early bird is waitin' for the worm <br><br>I don't think I can really stand it no more <br>I don't think I can go through it again <br>I'm just waiting <br>I'm just waiting <br>I'm just waiting <br>I'm just waiting <br><br>Yeah bees are waitin' for honey <br>And I'm putting it on the back burner for now <br>Cause everybody's racing and fawning and skivin' <br>And honey I'm waitin' for you <br>Ah-just waitin' <br>Ah-just waitin' <br>Ah-just waitin' <br>Ah-just waitin']]></content><category term="The Fall" label="The Fall"/><category term="Just Waiting" label="Just Waiting"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Two-Face/</id><title>The Fall - Two-Face! - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:05:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:05:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Two-Face/" title="The Fall - Two-Face! - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Two-face <br>That's what they call me <br>They call me a two-face <br>Two-face <br><br>That's what they call me <br>They call me a two-face <br>Two-face, boat-race disgraced <br>His face displaced again <br><br>Into two dimensions <br>Into two directions <br>Two-face, boat-race displaced <br>My face disgraced again <br><br>Into the dimensions <br>Into two directions <br><br>Nowhere for him to go <br>Nowhere for him to go <br><br>That's what they call me <br>They call me a two-face <br>Two-face <br>That's what they call me <br><br>They call me a two-face <br>Two-face, boat-race <br>Disgraced his face <br>Displaced again <br><br>Into two dimensions <br>Into two directions <br>Two-face, boat-race <br>Displaced his face <br><br>Disgraced <br>Into two dimensions <br>Into two directions <br>Origin horrible <br><br>Two-face, boat race <br>Disgraced <br>His face Displaced again <br><br>Into two dimensions <br>Into two directions <br>For all <br>For all to see <br><br>He thinks at dawn <br>He acts at noon <br>He stays alone <br>And in the evening <br><br>Two-face, both ways <br>Disgraced <br>His face displaced again <br><br>Into two directions <br>Into two dimensions <br><br>Left-side, horrible <br>Two-face, boat race <br>Disgraced <br>His face displaced again <br><br>Into two directions <br>Into two dimensions <br><br>Two-face <br>That's what they call me <br>They call me a two-face <br>Two-face <br><br>That's what they call me <br>They call me a two-face <br><br>Two-face, both ways disgraced <br>His face displaced again <br><br>Into two directions <br>Into two directions]]></content><category term="The Fall" label="The Fall"/><category term="Two-Face!" label="Two-Face!"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Immortality/</id><title>The Fall - Immortality - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:05:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:05:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Immortality/" title="The Fall - Immortality - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You try and change it <br>You try and arrange it <br>You try and shape it <br>But it's immortality, yeah <br>It's immortality <br><br>You cannot change it <br>Or rearrange it <br>It's immortality <br><br>Immortality <br>Immortality <br><br>That's where you're at, dear <br>You're shedding your mentality <br>But it's immortality <br>And you cannot buy it <br>You cannot put it in your pocket book <br>You cannot put it in your BCI <br>Don't try and shape it <br>Cos it's immortality <br>It's immortality, yeah <br>Immortality, yeah <br><br>It's where you're at, yeah <br><br>Immortality <br>Immortality <br><br>The Viking gods had it <br>Lord/Nord Odin had it <br>Don't try and change it <br>Don't try and put it in your pock-book-et <br>It's immortality <br>It's immortality, yeah <br><br>And you cannot change it <br>And you cannot rearrange it <br>And you cannot shape it <br>Cos it's reality, yeah <br>It's immortality, yeah <br>You cannot buy it <br>And that's all you're gonna get <br>From immortality <br>Immortality]]></content><category term="The Fall" label="The Fall"/><category term="Immortality" label="Immortality"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Time_Enough_At_Last/</id><title>The Fall - Time Enough At Last - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:05:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:05:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Time_Enough_At_Last/" title="The Fall - Time Enough At Last - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's time I started thinking on my feet <br>Instead of on my back <br>Now I got time <br>Time enough at last <br>Time enough at last boy <br>Time enough at last <br>It's been the bane of my life <br>But I've got time enough at last <br>I got time <br>Time enough at last <br>Time enough at last boy <br>Time enough at last <br>And sometimes people think you're just stupid <br>But I got time enough at last <br>I got time <br>Time enough at last <br>Time enough at last boy <br>Time enough at last <br>Time enough at last boy <br>Time enough at last <br>Cos I got time <br>Time enough at last <br>It's just stupid thinkin' 'bout the past <br>Cos I got time enough at last <br>In the city inferno <br>Is how to extract <br>Your brains from the head of a minor executive <br>Now I got time <br>Time enough at last <br>Time enough at last boy <br>Time enough at last <br>Time enough at last boy <br>Time enough at last <br>And the projectors eat you <br>When you least expect it <br>But I got time <br>Time enough at last <br>From a summer of experience <br>To a pit of its knowledge <br>Cos I got time <br>Time enough at last <br>Time enough at last boy <br>Time enough at last <br>I got time <br>Time enough at last]]></content><category term="The Fall" label="The Fall"/><category term="Time Enough At Last" label="Time Enough At Last"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Return_SINCD8_Single/</id><title>The Fall - Return (SINCD8 Single) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:05:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:05:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Return_SINCD8_Single/" title="The Fall - Return (SINCD8 Single) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[God bless the cold winds and its refreshing consequence, uh-huh <br>Oh please return <br><br>Hellas did tremble <br>Hellas did go away <br>Finding it difficult <br>To stand in its fury <br>Over the ironing board <br>But still this golden curl <br>Vented its Hellas fury <br><br>Return, baby baby baby come back to me <br>Come back to me, return <br><br>I was told to go easy and this one did <br>But still this golden creature raised its fury <br>Head sparkles <br><br>Return <br>Baby baby baby come back to me <br>Return <br><br>Is that a hair extension <br>It's soaked in hair lotion <br>How can you smell your own head <br>Return <br><br>Baby baby baby come back to me <br><br>I'll change the latch on the door <br>I'll get locks all over <br>I ran on up ahead <br>Sparkle and pander her]]></content><category term="The Fall" label="The Fall"/><category term="Return (SINCD8 Single)" label="Return (SINCD8 Single)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Free_Range/</id><title>The Fall - Free Range - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:05:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:05:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fall/Free_Range/" title="The Fall - Free Range - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In 2001 <br>A Life code: <br>It pays to talk to no one <br>Proliferating across the earth <br>Also Sprach Zarathustra* <br>Faction Europa <br>Free Range <br><br>2001 <br>Also Sprach Zarathustra <br>Proliferating across the earth <br>Pressure guilt <br>Grudge match <br>12 cm flak unit <br>Range 1 stroke 35 <br><br>This is the spring without end <br>This is the summer of malcontent <br>This is the winter of your mind <br><br>By 2001 <br>Also Sprach Zarathustra <br>It pays to talk to no one <br>Europa, faction <br>Proliferating across the earth <br>Free Range <br><br>This is the spring without end <br>This is the summer of malcontent <br>This is the winter of your mind <br><br>Insect posse <br>Will be crushed <br><br>Moravia, trouble <br>Moldavia <br>Europa <br>Every second third word <br>Europa <br>It pays to talk to no one <br><br>Free Range]]></content><category term="The Fall" label="The Fall"/><category term="Free Range" label="Free Range"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Dolph/Blonde__A_Onion_Clean/</id><title>Young Dolph - Blonde &amp; A Onion (Clean) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:08:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:08:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Dolph/Blonde__A_Onion_Clean/" title="Young Dolph - Blonde &amp; A Onion (Clean) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>Yeah <br><br>Verse 1 <br>I turn one ayy into two ayy, I turn three ayy into four ayy, million <br>But I remember clear as day the days when I was broke yup <br>Sellin' nicks and dimes right in front the corner store for real <br>Them white and blue lights pull up, take off runnin', that's the folks that's 12 <br>Told mama I ain't with that starvin' shit no more fuck that <br>You ain't gotta ask me, hell yeah I'm sellin' dope ayy who that <br>That lil nigga 'round the corner got it for the low it's Dolph <br>You ain't gotta ask me, hell yeah I smashed your ho uh <br>Ball around the globe whoa, rock a lot of gold whoa <br>I call your bitch green light shawty 'cause that bitch on go on go <br>I call all y'all niggas pussy 'cause all y'all some hoes hah <br>She looked me up and down and she said what the fuck are those drippy <br>Fucked her on the top floor now she loungin' in my robe yeah <br>I can't trust a nigga 'cause that's just the way it goes for real <br>I can't fuck with you lil nigga, I heard that you told <br>Got a ghetto East Oakland bitch, I call her Keyshia cole ayy ayy ayy <br><br>Chorus <br>Long hair yeah yeah, she don't care yeah yeah <br>Extended clips thirty thirty, hollow tips fire fire <br>Fast motor skrrt, marijuana odor yeah yeah <br>High roller, bitches say he bipolar ayy what you on <br>Rich nigga yeah yeah, bad bitches yeah yeah <br>You can't tell me shit why, I don't listen I don't listen <br>Money counter ayy, lot of hundreds ayy <br>Me and a blonde bitch just smoked a whole onion hey, hey <br><br>Verse 2 <br>Ayy what you doin' <br>Me and my white bitch just smoked a whole zip stankin' <br>Too much ice on me, damn I gave the bitch the chills woo <br>Found out that he wasn't real, that shit brought me to tears damn <br>Found out her booty wasn't real and I didn't give a damn haha <br>What's that on your back girl, that thing look like a ham fat <br>She said she get it from her mama, I said bitch you lyin' you lyin' <br>A hundo for my time a huncho, they like how I shine, hey <br><br>Chorus <br>Long hair yeah yeah, she don't care yeah yeah <br>Extended clips thirty thirty, hollow tips fire fire <br>Fast motor skrrt, marijuana odor yeah yeah <br>High roller, bitches say he bipolar ayy what you on <br>Rich nigga yeah yeah, bad bitches yeah yeah <br>You can't tell me shit why, I don't listen I don't listen <br>Money counter ayy, lot of hundreds ayy <br>Me and a blonde bitch just smoked a whole onion hey, hey <br><br>Outro <br>Me and a blonde bitch just smoked a whole onion <br>Me and a blonde bitch just smoked a whole onion <br>When we walk in, that's a lot of money <br>A whole lot of drip, uh-huh, that's how I'm comin']]></content><category term="Young Dolph" label="Young Dolph"/><category term="Blonde &amp; A Onion (Clean)" label="Blonde &amp; A Onion (Clean)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Dolph/Playa_Clean/</id><title>Young Dolph - Playa (Clean) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:08:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:08:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Dolph/Playa_Clean/" title="Young Dolph - Playa (Clean) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ayy, ayy <br>Ayyyy <br>Buddah blessed this beat <br><br>Verse 1 <br>What up <br>All of these diamonds on me, they say I ain't playin' fair damn <br>Pull up at the mansion, I got cameras everywhere uh <br>Dobermans in the backyard like the president uh <br>Fifty bitches on my dick, call me Dolph the pimp hey <br>Don't give a fuck, ain't a rich nigga, you a shrimp lil boy <br>Court side with my lil son watchin' LeBron and them, hah <br>P's of cannabis, my nigga I sold tons of them, hah <br>Drop a bag on his head, each and every one of them, hah <br>And these bitches what, nah, we don't love none of them nah <br>The police get behind this Rari, I'ma run from them skrrt <br>You know that they smokin' weed and they got guns in there yeah yeah <br>Got a bad bitch waitin' on me with no underwear yeah yeah <br>Black skirt, not a lick of panties under there uh-huh <br>Gangster from the start, my heart ain't got no love in there uh-huh <br>They always on my IG just to see what I wear <br>Got somebody's bitch bent over, from the back and pullin' hair huh <br>Fuck it, I don't care fuck it <br>Count better than I spell fuck it <br>It smoke how it smell fuck it <br>Fuck 'em, send some shells fuck 'em <br>I just bought a P to smoke and I ain't got shit for sale nah <br>I know you can tell what, I'm a fuckin' player player <br><br>Chorus <br>Player player, player player, player player, player player <br>Motherfuckin' player motherfuckin' player, I'm a fuckin' player <br>Player player player, player player <br>I'm a fuckin' player motherfuckin' player <br>I'm a fuckin' player motherfuckin' player, motherfuckin' player <br><br>Verse 2 <br>Look how that shit hit shine, Michael Jackson dancin' dance <br>White bitch told me she wanna go fuck to Marilyn Manson hol' up <br>My hood bitch said she wanna fuck me good then make a sandwich okay <br>I turned it to a traphouse but at first it was abandoned trap <br>The game been good to me yeah <br>A quarter milly every week yeah <br>I dream about cake when I sleep yeah <br>I wake up like it's time to eat, hey <br>Fuck you, pay me give me that <br>Secure the bag daily whoa whoa <br>I'm thinkin' new Mercedes <br>Your main bitch my baby hah <br>I fucked your favorite public figure but she say we dated uh-uh <br>My lil nigga can't stay out of jail, he keep catchin' cases damn <br>Two of my dogs, they fell out 'bout money and I swear I hate it shit man <br>I put extra ice on my wrist because it keep on achin' woo <br>I put her legs behind her head and now she keep on shakin' woo <br>Bitch I went from a Cutlass Cutlass, to a double R R <br>Light up my blunt then push a button, that motherfucker start yeah <br>Trap nigga living large yeah <br>I put that on God ayy <br><br>Chorus <br>Player player, player player, player player, player player <br>Motherfuckin' player motherfuckin' player, I'm a fuckin' player <br>Player player player, player player <br>I'm a fuckin' player motherfuckin' player <br>I'm a fuckin' player motherfuckin' player, motherfuckin' player]]></content><category term="Young Dolph" label="Young Dolph"/><category term="Playa (Clean)" label="Playa (Clean)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Dolph/Paranoid_Clean/</id><title>Young Dolph - Paranoid (Clean) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:08:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:08:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Dolph/Paranoid_Clean/" title="Young Dolph - Paranoid (Clean) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Izze The Producer <br>Yeah, yeah yup, yeah yup, yeah yup <br>Yeah yup, yeah yup, yeah yup, yeah yup <br>Yeah yup, yeah, yeah <br>Ayy fire that weed up man, ayy <br><br>Chorus <br>Money on the floor floor, chopper by the door whoa <br>I smoke too much weed, it's reekin' out my pores strong <br>Lil bitty waist woo, but she got ass galore <br>I just count a hundred K and spent it all 'cause I got bored fuck it <br>Smashin' from the back, her face on the headboard <br>She graduated with masters but I treat her like a whore it's Dolph <br>Sold a lot of dope, I do it for the dope boys for real <br>The feds in the hood, this shit got me paranoid whoa <br><br>Verse 1 <br>The feds in the hood whoa <br>And I heard they taking pictures, let me knock on wood shit <br>I hope those folks don't come and get us <br>Talkin' ass bitch shut up <br>I cut her off, didn't need no scissors nah <br>Nah I don't like that nigga fuck 'em <br>So I fucked his sister yeah yeah <br>I'm tripple blessed, so today I'm rockin' a jesus piece yeah yeah <br>Pull out my garage in some shit you drive on Need for Speed yeah yeah <br>I gave her a job at my traphouse sackin' up P's trap <br>Fur across my back, Balenciagas on my feet swag <br>Go and get a sack young nigga, and be all you can be uh-huh <br>I spent two hundred stacks on a coupe with two seats uh-huh <br>I used to go to sleep hungry, didn't have shit to eat remember that <br>Now I gotta smoke a blunt of weed just to eat <br><br>Chorus <br>Money on the floor floor, chopper by the door whoa <br>I smoke too much weed, it's reekin' out my pores strong <br>Lil bitty waist woo, but she got ass galore <br>I just count a hundred K and spent it all 'cause I got bored fuck it <br>Smashin' from the back, her face on the headboard <br>She graduated with masters but I treat her like a whore it's Dolph <br>Sold a lot of dope, I do it for the dope boys for real <br>The feds in the hood, this shit got me paranoid whoa <br><br>Verse 2 <br>Patek Philippe with residue on it uh, yeah, yeah <br>These diamonds they hit every time I move, don't it, uh, uh <br>You can't eat with me if you ain't hungry nah <br>I keep some shit up my sleeve and it always got something to do with money know that <br>I'm throwin' money on Monday yup <br>I got the bitch off the runway yup <br>Boy you know I'm about gunplay yup <br>Then go pay my tithes on Sunday thank you God <br>I might stop pimpin' one day yeah <br>I might stop sippin' one day damn <br>I got so high I'm goin' the wrong way on the fuckin' one way <br>The way I put this shit on me, they be like how do he do it hah <br>Don't you bring that bitch 'round me my nigga, 'cause you might lose her yeah <br>She told me that she wanna smoke a blunt and fuck to my music yeah <br>Then she gave me head and told me I should go make a movie, ah <br><br>Chorus <br>Money on the floor floor, chopper by the door whoa <br>I smoke too much weed, it's reekin' out my pores strong <br>Lil bitty waist woo, but she got ass galore <br>I just count a hundred K and spent it all 'cause I got bored fuck it <br>Smashin' from the back, her face on the headboard <br>She graduated with masters but I treat her like a whore it's Dolph <br>Sold a lot of dope, I do it for the dope boys for real <br>The feds in the hood, this shit got me paranoid whoa]]></content><category term="Young Dolph" label="Young Dolph"/><category term="Paranoid (Clean)" label="Paranoid (Clean)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Dolph/Flodgin_Clean/</id><title>Young Dolph - Flodgin (Clean) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:08:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:08:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Dolph/Flodgin_Clean/" title="Young Dolph - Flodgin (Clean) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>I like this shit <br><br>Chorus <br>The codeine got me noddin', got me noddin' yeah <br>Sloppy toppy, she be slobbin', she be slobbin' yeah yeah <br>Told you she don't give head, she flodgin', she flodgin' that bitch lyin' <br>Foreigns back to back, we mobbin', we mobbin' <br>Ayy, ayy, they ask me am I greedy and I said yeah man <br>Ayy, ayy, fuck you pay me, I need all my bread man <br>Ayy, ayy, I got folks to feed and that's on everything yeah <br>When I walk in the bank they call me by my last name uh-huh <br><br>Verse 1 <br>Big direct deposits yeah <br>Playin' hide and go seek in the walk-in closet whoa <br>Got so high I fell asleep and I left the Porsche runnin' damn <br>Three bitches in the bed, I'm just being honest whoa <br>I'm just being real for real <br>Driving with one knee, rollin' a blunt 'cause I got skill for real <br>Pop a bottle, cheers cheers <br>Runnin' through this cash got me smilin' ear to ear hah <br>Runnin' red lights and smokin' weed like I'm in Belly hey <br>Fuck the police, if they want me first they gotta catch me gone <br>I had an eight left, I drank one raw, now I got seven raw <br>Bumpin' Mack 10, loadin' up my MAC-11 it's Dolph <br>She came with her friend then both of 'em gave me Becky <br>Cam and Leslie, uh <br><br>Chorus <br>The codeine got me noddin', got me noddin' yeah <br>Sloppy toppy, she be slobbin', she be slobbin' yeah yeah <br>Told you she don't give head, she flodgin', she flodgin' that bitch lyin' <br>Foreigns back to back, we mobbin', we mobbin' <br>Ayy, ayy, they ask me am I greedy and I said yeah man <br>Ayy, ayy, fuck you pay me, I need all my bread man <br>Ayy, ayy, I got folks to feed and that's on everything <br>When I walk in the bank they call me by my last name uh-huh <br><br>Verse 2 <br>Lyin' ass niggas be flodgin', flodgin', flodgin', flodgin' liar <br>Smashed her once, now every time she call me I'm dodgin' ayy who that <br>Ratchet ass bitch but she look just like a barbie <br>So many people at the trap, look like we havin' a party yeah yeah <br>Bad attitude like I'm Charles Barkley yeah yeah <br>It's just me and my yopper slidin' in the Rari yeah yeah <br>If I offend you, fuck you, I can't say I'm sorry hah <br>Still pull up in the hood just to get some tamales skrrt <br>I'm all about my chicken, extra Teriyaki whoa <br>No love for these bitches, I just want some noggin some top <br>I been countin' all night, it got me noddin' woo <br>She in that sundress and her booty soft as cotton ayy <br><br>Chorus <br>The codeine got me noddin', got me noddin' yeah <br>Sloppy toppy, she be slobbin', she be slobbin' yeah yeah <br>Told you she don't give head, she flodgin', she flodgin' that bitch lyin' <br>Foreigns back to back, we mobbin', we mobbin' <br>Ayy, ayy, they ask me am I greedy and I said yeah man <br>Ayy, ayy, fuck you pay me, I need all my bread man <br>Ayy, ayy, I got folks to feed and that's on everything <br>When I walk in the bank they call me by my last name uh-huh]]></content><category term="Young Dolph" label="Young Dolph"/><category term="Flodgin (Clean)" label="Flodgin (Clean)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Dolph/Slave_Owner_Clean/</id><title>Young Dolph - Slave Owner (Clean) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:08:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:08:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Dolph/Slave_Owner_Clean/" title="Young Dolph - Slave Owner (Clean) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hit 'em with the Jab <br>Buddah blessed this beat <br><br>Chorus <br>Whole lotta of drip drip <br>Money callin' back to back so I keep takin' trips go get it <br>Spend a couple mil yeah, just on one crib yeah <br>Hold up, let me crack the seal, take another sip pour up <br>Whole lotta drip drip <br>Whole lotta drip drip, whole lotta chips baow <br>I'm a slave owner what, whole lotta whips skrrt <br>I don't like niggas nah, I might get 'em killed bah <br>He like poppin' pills thirties, I like countin' mils ayy <br><br>Verse 1 <br>She like poppin' pussy twerk, I like throwin' paper yeah <br>That boy there a pussy swear, 'cause that nigga a hater damn <br>Show up in all black yeah, like the Undertaker yeah <br>Designer everything, diamond watch and diamond ring hey <br>Yeah you right, I'm such a big deal big deal <br>Rolls Royce on some big wheels uh-huh <br>I had to hustle for mine, bitch I'm out the field straight out the streets <br>Ballin' in Chiraq like I'm coach Phil Phil Jackson <br>Drop a pill in her drink like Bill whoa <br>Smash her on the first night, I bet I will uh-huh <br>You wanna get in this car, take off them heels take them off <br>A whole truck load, I just made a deal hey, hey <br>What's the business, what's the motherfuckin' word ayy what's poppin' <br>Put a dick in your ear, fuck what you heard haha <br>Another check just cleared, oh yeah oh yeah <br>All that hatin' ain't gon' get you nowhere woo <br><br>Chorus <br>Whole lotta of drip drip <br>Money callin' back to back so I keep takin' trips go get it <br>Spend a couple mil yeah, just on one crib yeah <br>Hold up, let me crack the seal, take another sip pour up <br>Whole lotta drip drip <br>Whole lotta drip drip, whole lotta chips baow <br>I'm a slave owner what, whole lotta whips skrrt <br>I don't like niggas nah, I might get 'em killed bah <br>He like poppin' pills thirties, I like countin' mils ayy <br><br>Verse 2 <br>All this swag on me whoa, got a bag on me whoa <br>An eighty ball in my book bag, got a shag on me whoa <br>I let my nuts hang yeah, I gotta sag homie yeah <br>I heard a fuck nigga got a price tag on me hah <br>Ayy come and ask me do I really give a fuck hell nah <br>Come and ask me how much I made this month hey <br>Puerto Ricans and Jamaicans, nigga pick one yeah <br>Playin' with these M's, you should go and get one uh-huh <br>I smoke, I drink drink <br>I'm supposed to stop damn, but fuck it 'cause I can't ayy who that <br>Met her at the bank okay, fucked her at the penthouse ayy <br>I was fucked up but I'm the shit now it's Dolph <br><br>Chorus <br>Whole lotta of drip drip <br>Money callin' back to back so I keep takin' trips go get it <br>Spend a couple mil yeah, just on one crib yeah <br>Hold up, let me crack the seal, take another sip pour up <br>Whole lotta drip drip <br>Whole lotta drip drip, whole lotta chips baow <br>I'm a slave owner what, whole lotta whips skrrt <br>I don't like niggas nah, I might get 'em killed bah <br>He like poppin' pills thirties, I like countin' mils ayy]]></content><category term="Young Dolph" label="Young Dolph"/><category term="Slave Owner (Clean)" label="Slave Owner (Clean)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Dolph/Kush_On_The_Yacht_Clean/</id><title>Young Dolph - Kush On The Yacht (Clean) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:08:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:08:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Dolph/Kush_On_The_Yacht_Clean/" title="Young Dolph - Kush On The Yacht (Clean) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ayy, yeah skrrt <br>Three hundred thousand dollar deposit <br><br>Verse 1 <br>I never changed for a bitch uh-uh <br>Got rich, still didn't switch nah <br>Might split a mil with the clique yeah <br>Fake love, I don't feel that shit I hate that shit <br>I spend a dub on a fit dizzub <br>Ayy come get your girl off my dick ugh <br>My shooting guards don't miss nah <br>I just pulled up in the six hundred <br>Fucked her and call her a Lyft bitch <br>Lil bitch I got shit to do bitch <br>I just poured codeine in my cranberry apple juice haha, pour up <br>Quarter milly on me, flyin' around Malibu skrrt <br>It's too much ice, ridiculous wah <br>We do what we wanna, you dig it you dig it <br>My boots and my jacket Givenchy yeah <br>Might wake up and go buy a Bentley yeah <br>My neck and my wrist, they hittin' yeah <br>Pulled out 'cause she tried to kiss me get out <br>My number in her phone then I smashed it ugh <br>Once, maybe twice, then I passed it yeah <br>Lil mama bougie and nasty yeah <br>My lil nigga robbin' and trappin' yeah <br>Dolph why you don't never want to sign a major deal umm <br>'Cause I'm shittin' on every nigga with a major deal facts <br>I own all my shit and I collect all of my mils facts <br>Remember my best friend used to be my vacuum seal trap <br>Three bombs, one day, that's a half a mil trap <br>Too much money up in here, no company at the crib hahaha <br>Can you get some money, fuck you, get it how you live fuck you <br>Bitch I went from sellin' pounds to sellin' ad-libs it's Dolph <br>One show, two shows, three shows, four four <br>I might take that lil money and go buy a Lambo, hey <br>RIP my nigga Sambo RIP <br>Big money shit what I stand for big shit <br>Got the plug on speed dial, yeah brrt <br>Yeah, got your bitch on redial hello <br><br>Chorus <br>Drop top skrrt, black Glock Glock <br>I put work work, on my block yeah <br>Bust down ayy, my chain ayy <br>Bust down ayy, my watch blaow <br>Syrup in my soda pop raw <br>It's killin' me but I can't stop raw <br>Yeah I'm addicted to guap yeah <br>They want me dead like Pac hey <br>Fuck 'em, go buy another car fuck 'em <br>Fuck 'em, go buy some more rocks fuck 'em <br>I'm smokin' kush on the yacht hah <br>Young nigga playin' with a lot a lot <br>I just pulled up on the block hah <br>Nigga like look what I got haha <br>Young nigga playin' with a lot, yeah a lot <br>Young nigga playin' with a lot what he doin' <br><br>Verse 2 <br>Lil nigga playin' with a lot a lot <br>And I put that shit on God on God <br>Boy all that you do is 'flauge liar <br>My niggas gon' shoot if I nod get 'em <br>Your bitch gon' fuck if I let her ayy come here <br>Your bitch gon' fuck when I tell her hah <br>Gabbana my sneakers and sweater Dolce <br>She wanna feel Ferrari leather ah <br>I bought my lil boy a Tesla Tesla <br>I said, This what you want he said, Yessir yes sir <br>Too many chains, my neck hurt damn <br>I dive in that money bitch, headfirst woo <br>Too many racks on me <br>Damn, man, this shit got my leg hurtin' damn <br>I don't want to hit your weed why <br>Damn, man, that shit make my head hurt hah <br>Came out like it's fashion week <br>Damn, man, shit that boy fresh as hell <br>I mix the Tom Ford with the Fear Of God <br>Guccis with the new Chanel Dolph <br>Diamonds bitin', your bitch barkin' <br>Get out his way, no one can stop him <br>Lil nigga playin' with a lot a lot <br>That young nigga playin' with a lot hey <br><br>Chorus <br>Drop top skrrt, black Glock Glock <br>I put work work, on my block yeah <br>Bust down ayy, my chain ayy <br>Bust down ayy, my watch blaow <br>Syrup in my soda pop raw <br>It's killin' me but I can't stop raw <br>Yeah I'm addicted to guap yeah <br>They want me dead like Pac hey <br>Fuck 'em, go buy another car fuck 'em <br>Fuck 'em, go buy some more rocks fuck 'em <br>I'm smokin' kush on the yacht hah <br>Young nigga playin' with a lot a lot <br>I just pulled up on the block hah <br>Nigga like look what I got haha <br>Young nigga playin' with a lot, yeah a lot <br>Young nigga playin' with a lot]]></content><category term="Young Dolph" label="Young Dolph"/><category term="Kush On The Yacht (Clean)" label="Kush On The Yacht (Clean)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/심재준/난_괜찮아/</id><title>심재준 - 난 괜찮아 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:12:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:12:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%AC%EC%9E%AC%EC%A4%80/%EB%82%9C_%EA%B4%9C%EC%B0%AE%EC%95%84/" title="심재준 - 난 괜찮아 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어두워진 거릴 걸으면 <br>스치는 수 많은 사람들 <br>희미해진 불빛사이로 <br>다시 그대 모습 보일것 같아 <br>사랑했던 기억이라면 <br>이렇게 힘들어 했을까 <br>언제 다시 그댈 만나면 <br>나는 사랑한다 말을 할거야 <br>다시 돌아갈 수 없는 걸 <br>아쉬움에 눈물 흘러도 <br>이젠 다시 볼 수 없는 걸 <br>흘러가는 세월 속에 <br>흩어져버릴 기억 <br>다시 찾지 못해도 난 괜찮아 <br>내가 살아 온 날 만큼 <br>내가 살아 갈 날들도 <br>아직 남아 있을지 몰라도 <br>그댈 다시 볼 수 있는 <br>그댈 다시 만날 기횐 <br>이젠 남아 있지 않은 걸 <br>다시 돌아갈 수 없는 걸 <br>그리움에 가슴 아파도 <br>이젠 다시 볼 수 없는 걸 <br>흘러가는 세월속에 <br>흩어져 버릴 기억 <br>다시 찾지 못해도 난 괜찮아 <br>다시 찾지 못해도 난 괜찮아 <br>]]></content><category term="심재준" label="심재준"/><category term="난 괜찮아" label="난 괜찮아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luxxury/I_Need_You/</id><title>Luxxury - I Need You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:12:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:12:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luxxury/I_Need_You/" title="Luxxury - I Need You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lost control I'm drifting far from home <br>Not sure how much longer i can even long <br>I find trouble when I'm not with you <br>Don't wanna lost my way <br>So please don't leave me on my own tonight <br>I need you <br>When i feel blast and pain <br>I need you <br>You are the one who understand <br>I need you <br>To take me by the heights <br>I need you <br>To make of me a better men <br>Who in my heart ever everytime <br>I'm back my self whenever i'm alone <br>Sometimes i feel like I'm flouting thorough the darkness <br>But i can wait you for the night <br>I need you <br>When i feel blast and pain <br>I need you <br>you're the one who understand <br>I need you <br>To take me by the heights <br>I need you <br>To make of me a better men <br>I need you <br>When i feel blast and pain <br>I need you <br>You are the one who understands <br>I need you <br>To take me by heights <br>I need you <br>To make of me a better men <br>I need you <br>When i feel blast and pain <br>I need you <br>You are the one who understands <br>I need you <br>To take me by heights <br>I need you <br>To make of me a better men <br>I need you <br>By the heights]]></content><category term="Luxxury" label="Luxxury"/><category term="I Need You" label="I Need You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Holydrug_Couple/Its_Dawning/</id><title>The Holydrug Couple - It`s Dawning - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:12:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:12:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Holydrug_Couple/Its_Dawning/" title="The Holydrug Couple - It`s Dawning - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Aaahh aahhh <br>We'll call 'maybe' <br>To this state of being <br>Nothing between your eyes <br>Oohh ohhh ohh <br>We're going to faint <br>We all forget how to wake up and <br>Don't miss night <br>Ahhh ahhh <br>I can't feel nothing <br>With all that melted sound upon my bed <br>I won't wake up <br>Ooohh oohh <br>Sometimes it feels <br>Like you go without moving <br>Like floating high <br>Ooohh ohhh <br>And I'll tell you more <br>You think you pass through the night <br>You wanna die <br>Ahhh ahhh <br>Like tiny flowers <br>Moving and shaking all over <br>My two hands <br>My shoes are very tight]]></content><category term="The Holydrug Couple" label="The Holydrug Couple"/><category term="It`s Dawning" label="It`s Dawning"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Holydrug_Couple/Wonder/</id><title>The Holydrug Couple - Wonder - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:12:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:12:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Holydrug_Couple/Wonder/" title="The Holydrug Couple - Wonder - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I would like to wonder <br>I would like to go <br>Give me a little fire <br>High up in the sky <br>Give me a little higher <br>High up in the clouds]]></content><category term="The Holydrug Couple" label="The Holydrug Couple"/><category term="Wonder" label="Wonder"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Holydrug_Couple/Red_Moon/</id><title>The Holydrug Couple - Red Moon - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:12:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:12:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Holydrug_Couple/Red_Moon/" title="The Holydrug Couple - Red Moon - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All I've got inside <br>But you don't have to wait <br>Here with open arms <br>But you don't have to stay <br>Here with all inside <br>We're gonna try <br>But I really want to say <br>Here we're gonna try <br>But you don't really have to wait <br>Seems they never knew <br>That sun follows the night <br>If your love don't glow <br>Must be the river's fault <br>Please don't wait for us <br>If you don't want to stay <br>Here with all inside <br>We're gonna try <br>But I really want to say <br>Here we're gonna try <br>But you don't really have to wait <br>Ahhhh ahhh ahhhhh]]></content><category term="The Holydrug Couple" label="The Holydrug Couple"/><category term="Red Moon" label="Red Moon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Holydrug_Couple/Out_of_Sight/</id><title>The Holydrug Couple - Out of Sight - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:12:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:12:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Holydrug_Couple/Out_of_Sight/" title="The Holydrug Couple - Out of Sight - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was born <br>Long time ago <br>I'm the light <br>Tell me who am i <br>Cause I, here I am <br>Far far away <br>Cause I, here I am <br>Out out out of sight <br>Night, darkest home <br>Fades our soul <br>Give me hazey eyes <br>Find me, desert time <br>Cause I, here I am <br>Far far away <br>Cause I, here I am <br>Out out out of sight]]></content><category term="The Holydrug Couple" label="The Holydrug Couple"/><category term="Out of Sight" label="Out of Sight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Holydrug_Couple/Follow_Your_Way/</id><title>The Holydrug Couple - Follow Your Way - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:12:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:12:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Holydrug_Couple/Follow_Your_Way/" title="The Holydrug Couple - Follow Your Way - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fall, we'll never gave up get up <br>Change, we're strange than any <br>Fall, like follow your way <br>Let's get to <br>Fall, like follow your way <br>Everytime you want to come to <br>Here I feel like someone saying <br>Goodbye <br>Goodbye <br>Fall, like follow your way <br>Let's get to <br>Fall, like follow your way]]></content><category term="The Holydrug Couple" label="The Holydrug Couple"/><category term="Follow Your Way" label="Follow Your Way"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Holydrug_Couple/Counting_Sailboats/</id><title>The Holydrug Couple - Counting Sailboats - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:12:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:12:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Holydrug_Couple/Counting_Sailboats/" title="The Holydrug Couple - Counting Sailboats - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll be there <br>Waiting to sail <br>I don't know <br>Where I'll go <br>Go to the sailboats <br>To the end of the world]]></content><category term="The Holydrug Couple" label="The Holydrug Couple"/><category term="Counting Sailboats" label="Counting Sailboats"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백새비/눈꽃_Snow_Flower/</id><title>백새비 - 눈꽃 (Snow Flower) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:14:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:14:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%EC%83%88%EB%B9%84/%EB%88%88%EA%BD%83_Snow_Flower/" title="백새비 - 눈꽃 (Snow Flower) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오래 밴 어스름 <br>살포시 내려앉아 속삭여 <br>이제껏 왔다고 <br>귀 기울여 달라고 소리 내 <br>부드럽게 감싸는 기분 <br>차가운 듯 손등에 키스 <br>더 가까이 와 내게로 머물러줘 <br>사라지지마 영원히 <br>꽃이 된 사랑이라 <br>향기 머금고 다시 와줘요 <br>만발한 꽃이 수놓을 때면 <br>잊지 말고 하얗게 와줘요 <br>울고 간 사랑이라 <br>눈물 보이지 말고 와줘요 <br>멀리 간다고 서두르지만 <br>잠시라도 곁에 있다 가요 <br>멈춰서 있는 내 발자국 <br>저만치 따라 가지 못해 <br>그리움이 하늘 위로 <br>보고 싶은 맘이 눈꽃에 피어나 <br>꽃이 된 사랑이라 <br>향기 머금고 다시 와줘요 <br>만발한 꽃이 수놓을 때면 <br>잊지 말고 하얗게 와줘요 <br>울고 간 사랑이라 <br>눈물 보이지 말고 와줘요 <br>멀리 간다고 서두르지만 <br>잠시라도 곁에 있다 가요 <br>]]></content><category term="백새비" label="백새비"/><category term="눈꽃 (Snow Flower)" label="눈꽃 (Snow Flower)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/심재준/내_사랑은/</id><title>심재준 - 내 사랑은 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:14:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:14:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%AC%EC%9E%AC%EC%A4%80/%EB%82%B4_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%80/" title="심재준 - 내 사랑은 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가끔씩 찾아와 또 다가와 <br>내 맘속에 들어와 <br>지난날 함께 머물던 시간 속에 <br>그때 그 모습 그대로 <br>지금도 생각해 늘 그리워 <br>다시 볼 수 없지만 <br>어쩌면 너도 내 맘과 <br>같은 건지 알 수 없지만 <br>함께 했던 시간들 <br>이젠 모두 떠나가고 <br>이렇게 멍하니 나 혼자서 <br>외로운 밤을 또 보내야 하나 <br>이런 내 맘을 이해 해줘 <br>나는 너를 잊을 수가 없나봐 <br>언제나 내게 영원히 내게 <br>내 사랑은 너 하나 뿐인 걸 <br>지금도 생각해 늘 그리워 <br>다시 볼 수 없지만 <br>어쩌면 너도 내 맘과 <br>같은 건지 알 수 없지만 <br>함께 했던 시간들 <br>이젠 모두 떠나가고 <br>이렇게 멍하니 나 혼자서 <br>외로운 밤을 또 보내야 하나 <br>이런 내 맘을 이해 해줘 <br>나는 너를 잊을 수가 없나봐 <br>언제나 내게 영원히 내게 <br>내 사랑은 너 하나 뿐인 걸 <br>내 사랑은 너 하나 뿐인 걸 <br>]]></content><category term="심재준" label="심재준"/><category term="내 사랑은" label="내 사랑은"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/세븐어클락/君だった君だし君のはず___Kimidatta_Kimidasi_Kiminohazu_너였고_너이고_너일_거라서/</id><title>세븐어클락 - 君だった君だし君のはず / Kimidatta Kimidasi Kiminohazu (너였고 너이고 너일 거라서) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:14:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:14:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%B8%EB%B8%90%EC%96%B4%ED%81%B4%EB%9D%BD/%E5%90%9B%E3%81%A0%E3%81%A3%E3%81%9F%E5%90%9B%E3%81%A0%E3%81%97%E5%90%9B%E3%81%AE%E3%81%AF%E3%81%9A___Kimidatta_Kimidasi_Kiminohazu_%EB%84%88%EC%98%80%EA%B3%A0_%EB%84%88%EC%9D%B4%EA%B3%A0_%EB%84%88%EC%9D%BC_%EA%B1%B0%EB%9D%BC%EC%84%9C/" title="세븐어클락 - 君だった君だし君のはず / Kimidatta Kimidasi Kiminohazu (너였고 너이고 너일 거라서) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[차갑게 불던 한줄기 바람결 <br>風(かぜ)がふき　僕(ぼく)の思(おも)いを <br>kazega huki bokuno omoiwo <br>바람이 불어 내 마음을 <br><br>너의 마음마저 흔들었던 걸까 <br>連(つ)れ去(さ)って　？(かく)してしまう <br>tsuresatte kakusitesimau <br>데리고 가 숨겨버려 <br><br>Hoo woo- 아득히 멀어지는 네가 <br>Hoo woo-遠(とお)く離(はな)れていく <br>Hoo woo-tooku hanareteiku <br>Hoo woo-아득히 멀어져 <br><br>Hoo woo- 눈부신 채 슬픈 네가 <br>Hoo woo-君(きみ)を思(おも)うだけ <br>Hoo woo-kimiwo omoudake <br>Hoo woo-널 그릴 뿐 <br><br>※ <br>괜찮지가 않아 <br>離(はな)さないよ <br>hanasanaiyo <br>놓치지 않아 <br><br>아니 미치도록 아파 <br>募(つの)る君(きみ)の　LOVE <br>tsunoru kimino LOVE <br>점점 더 깊어지는 너의 LOVE <br><br><br>가슴이 부러진 듯 <br>？(こわ)れても　ただ <br>kowaretemo tada <br>무너진대도 그저 <br><br>한걸음 뗄 수가 없어 <br>守(まも)るだけの　TRUE　LOVE <br>mamorudakeno TRUE LOVE <br>지킬 수 밖에 없는 TRUE LOVE <br><br>쏟아지는 숱한 기억마다 <br>あふれる　君(きみ)の記(き)憶(おく)が <br>ahureru kimino kiokuga <br>쏟아지는 너의 기억이 <br><br>이토록 따스한 너이기에 <br>思(おも)いが悲(かな)しくて　え～ <br>omoiga kanasikute yeah~ <br>생각이 슬퍼서 예~ <br><br>슬퍼 <br>ただ <br>tada <br>그저 <br><br>눈이 멀만큼 눈부셨던 날들 <br>眩(くら)むほど眩(まぶ)しい日？(ひび)が <br>kuramuhodo mabusii hibiga <br>눈이 멀 만큼 눈부셨던 날들 <br><br>아플 줄 몰라 더 행복했던 걸까 <br>遠(とお)ざかる　君(きみ)の笑顔(えがお)が <br>toozakaru kimino egaoga <br>멀어지는 너의 웃는 얼굴이 <br><br>Hoo woo- 하얗게 흐르던 시간들 <br>Hoo woo-優(やさ)しく微笑(ほほえ)んで <br>Hoo woo-yasasiku hohoennde <br>Hoo woo-다정하게 미소지어 <br><br>Hoo woo- 낯선 선물 같았던 너 <br>Hoo woo-僕(ぼく)がほしいだけ <br>Hoo woo-bokuga hosiidake <br>Hoo woo-내가 갖고싶을 뿐 <br><br>※ <br>괜찮지가 않아 <br>離(はな)さないよ <br>hanasanaiyo <br>놓치지 않아 <br><br>아니 미치도록 아파 <br>募(つの)る君(きみ)の　LOVE <br>tsunoru kimino LOVE <br>점점 더 깊어지는 너의 LOVE <br><br>눈물이 빗물인 듯 <br>？(こわ)れても　ただ <br>kowaretemo tada <br>무너진대도 그저 <br><br>한걸음 뗄 수가 없어 <br>守(まも)るだけの　TRUE　LOVE <br>mamorudakeno TRUE LOVE <br>지킬 수 밖에 없는 TRUE　LOVE <br><br>떨어지는 눈물 속에서도 <br>あふれる　君(きみ)の記(き)憶(おく)が <br>ahureru kimino kiokuga <br>쏟아지는 너의 기억이 <br><br>이토록 빛나는 너이기에 <br>こんなに悲(かな)しくて～　Oh～ <br>konnnani kanasikute~ Oh~ <br>이토록 슬퍼서~ Oh~ <br><br>세상은 너였고 <br>僕(ぼく)のLOVE Heart <br>bokuno LOVE Heart <br>나의 LOVE Heart <br><br>너이고 너일 거라서 <br>君(きみ)にあげたLOVE <br>kimini ageta LOVE <br>네게 준 LOVE <br><br>돌아설 수가 없어 <br>僕(ぼく)は？(こわ)れて <br>bokuha kowarete <br>나는 무너져 <br>또 널 보낼 수가 없어 <br>かまわないよMy Heart <br>kamawanaiyo My Heart <br>상관없어 My Heart <br><br>사랑한다 가슴 뛰는 만큼 <br>たとえば　君(きみ)は見(み)えなく <br>tatoeba kimiha mienaku <br>설령 니가 보이지 않아 <br><br>끝내 그리움이 덮여도 <br>僕(ぼく)の思(おも)いだけでも　いいよ <br>bokuno omoidakedemo iiyo <br>내 그리움뿐이래도 괜찮아 <br><br>단 한 사람 <br>ただ <br>tada <br>그저 <br><br>너를 <br>君(きみ) <br>kimi <br>그대 <br>]]></content><category term="세븐어클락" label="세븐어클락"/><category term="君だった君だし君のはず / Kimidatta Kimidasi Kiminohazu (너였고 너이고 너일 거라서)" label="君だった君だし君のはず / Kimidatta Kimidasi Kiminohazu (너였고 너이고 너일 거라서)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Roll_The_Wheel/</id><title>Magnolia Electric Co. - Roll The Wheel - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:17:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:17:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Roll_The_Wheel/" title="Magnolia Electric Co. - Roll The Wheel - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[kentucky moon <br>roll it down the pike <br>tell whatever news you have from home tonight <br><br>use any sign <br>you haven't shown <br>now who rolls the wheel <br>who rolls the wheel <br><br>bayou moon <br>come down from the crossroads <br>sing the hymm you heard the alligators moan <br>shout the news <br>baby if you've been told <br><br>who rolls the wheel <br>who rolls away the stone <br><br>who rolls the wheel <br><br>ressurection moon <br>i have no friends like you <br>who'd give me the gleaming railroad <br>then roll the wheel <br>roll the stone <br>roll the wheel <br>then roll away the stone <br>roll the wheel]]></content><category term="Magnolia Electric Co." label="Magnolia Electric Co."/><category term="Roll The Wheel" label="Roll The Wheel"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Take_One_Thing_Along/</id><title>Magnolia Electric Co. - Take One Thing Along - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:17:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:17:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Take_One_Thing_Along/" title="Magnolia Electric Co. - Take One Thing Along - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We turn life and death around <br>Who each have earned our pain <br>God is not gone but is not sure <br>How we earned this thing that can stay ours <br><br>Take this one thing along <br>It is a sin but it is not wrong <br>It is a sin but it is not wrong <br>Take this one thing along <br><br>The twilight, you know it now by heart <br>What is quiet and what's alone <br>Take this one thing along <br>If horizons ride before us <br>Who rides beside <br>Who rides beside <br><br>Leave this one thing behind <br>Turn the mirror to the door <br>Where death has come in the same place twice <br>Leave this one thing behind <br>Leave this one thing behind <br><br>Sorrow rides before us <br>Who rides beside <br>Who rides beside <br>Take this one along <br>Leave this one behind]]></content><category term="Magnolia Electric Co." label="Magnolia Electric Co."/><category term="Take One Thing Along" label="Take One Thing Along"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/The_Spell/</id><title>Magnolia Electric Co. - The Spell - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:17:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:17:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/The_Spell/" title="Magnolia Electric Co. - The Spell - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do not wake, oh little ghost <br>There is work here still to do <br>High lights the moon <br><br>Hides its face from you <br>Do not wake, oh little ghost <br>The work is almost through <br>I'll wield the river and the mistletoe <br>Into the crown for you <br>Come the early dawn <br>Come the early dawn <br>Hem of the crossroads be thine <br>Heart of the serpent be thine <br>Hand of the scarecrow clasp thine <br>Will-o-the-wisp be your eye <br>Voice of the hall be thine <br>Wings of ruby be thine <br>Beak of coral be thine <br>All things eaten be thine <br>All things forgotten be thine <br>Wake, oh wake little queen <br>I have the crown for you]]></content><category term="Magnolia Electric Co." label="Magnolia Electric Co."/><category term="The Spell" label="The Spell"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Shiloh_Temple_Bell/</id><title>Magnolia Electric Co. - Shiloh Temple Bell - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:17:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:17:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Shiloh_Temple_Bell/" title="Magnolia Electric Co. - Shiloh Temple Bell - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Two hundred miles from turning back <br>Two hundred from ever going home <br>A man can be so easy lost <br><br>When he's on the mountain road, oh Shiloh <br>Is it only the temple that falls <br>Is it only the temple that falls <br>It's pain and then it's pain then is it pain <br>And then it's pain that never comes <br>The only bridge I haven't burned is the one I'm standing on <br>Oh Shiloh, do you hear the night bird call <br>Because the night bird calls <br>My ghost in flames on the desert road <br>Horizon to horizon, oh woe <br>I weep for it all and I weep for nothing at all <br>Oh Shiloh, it's not that falls <br>It's not only the temple that falls]]></content><category term="Magnolia Electric Co." label="Magnolia Electric Co."/><category term="Shiloh Temple Bell" label="Shiloh Temple Bell"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Night_Country/</id><title>Magnolia Electric Co. - Night Country - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:17:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:17:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Night_Country/" title="Magnolia Electric Co. - Night Country - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here is the lone pine who named the wind <br>Gave the starry crown <br>The saddest bird in the wilderness <br>Who would lay no nest down <br><br>Sent to seek death in the World <br>The night country comes <br>Clasp both wings together now <br>The night country comes <br><br>I have to live this way <br>Be the builder of no house <br>Oh, lone pine on the fading trail <br>I join you now <br><br>The night country comes <br>Oooooo <br>The night country comes]]></content><category term="Magnolia Electric Co." label="Magnolia Electric Co."/><category term="Night Country" label="Night Country"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Spanish_Moon_Fall_And_Rise/</id><title>Magnolia Electric Co. - Spanish Moon Fall And Rise - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:17:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:17:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Spanish_Moon_Fall_And_Rise/" title="Magnolia Electric Co. - Spanish Moon Fall And Rise - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Even like your loss <br>Sadder than every sorrow <br>Even like the night <br>At the edge of the world <br>There's still farther to fall <br>Even like the twilight <br>Hymns to sister <br>Even like the shadows <br>We all miss her <br>I leave the road with the ghost of the road <br>Spanish moon fall and rise <br>Spanish moon fall and rise <br>I leave you now with my ghost in this room <br>Two wanderers eyes, two eyes <br>Old Spanish moon fall and rise <br>Old Spanish moon fall and rise <br>Old Spanish moon fall and rise]]></content><category term="Magnolia Electric Co." label="Magnolia Electric Co."/><category term="Spanish Moon Fall And Rise" label="Spanish Moon Fall And Rise"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Steady_Now/</id><title>Magnolia Electric Co. - Steady Now - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:17:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:17:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Steady_Now/" title="Magnolia Electric Co. - Steady Now - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Everything in it's place <br>The world does have to end in pain <br>Oh steady now <br><br>North star finds the cross-road <br>Though I walk always away from it <br>Pale moon lights the rocky shore <br>Though I always head straight for it <br>Steady now <br>Steady now <br><br>Whatever is set before us <br>Will it all ever be enough <br>Will it be enough <br><br>Great bird into serpent <br>Oh steady now <br>Serpent then to wing <br>Oh steady now <br><br>Circle ghost with me <br>Above the cyprus grove <br>Steady now <br>Still a long way from home <br>The world does have to go in pain <br>Oh steady now <br>Everything in it's place <br>Steady now]]></content><category term="Magnolia Electric Co." label="Magnolia Electric Co."/><category term="Steady Now" label="Steady Now"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Trouble_In_Mind/</id><title>Magnolia Electric Co. - Trouble In Mind - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:17:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:17:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Trouble_In_Mind/" title="Magnolia Electric Co. - Trouble In Mind - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Trouble in mind, I'm blue <br>But I won't be blue always <br>You know the sun is gonna shine <br>In my back door someday <br><br>I'm gonna lay my head on some lonesome railroad line <br>Gonna let that big 800 satisfy this, my dull mind <br><br>Trouble in mind, I'm blue <br>My poor heart is sinking low <br>You know I ain't had so much trouble <br>In my life before <br><br>Trouble in mind, I'm blue <br>But I won't be blue always <br>You know the sun is gonna shine <br>In my back door someday]]></content><category term="Magnolia Electric Co." label="Magnolia Electric Co."/><category term="Trouble In Mind" label="Trouble In Mind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Memphis_Moon/</id><title>Magnolia Electric Co. - Memphis Moon - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:17:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:17:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Memphis_Moon/" title="Magnolia Electric Co. - Memphis Moon - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tea for two stars falling from the memphis sky <br>Tea for two stars falling from the memphis sky <br><br>I know the night bird called you now <br>Everything is fine <br>I know it's soon to be fading out <br>But oh, didn't we shine <br>Didn't we shine <br><br>Some people say that the memphis blues ain't bad <br>Some people say that the memphis blues ain't bad <br><br>Put your little hand in mine darling <br>I know you're fading fast <br>It weren't the memphis blues you had <br>But baby you still shine <br><br>Goodbye my love, goodbye my love, goodbye <br>Turn your lamp down low my love, goodbye <br>I hear the whistle singing now to the lonesome pine <br>I know that we faded out <br>But oh, didn't we shine <br>Didn't we shine]]></content><category term="Magnolia Electric Co." label="Magnolia Electric Co."/><category term="Memphis Moon" label="Memphis Moon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Talk_To_Me_Devil_Again/</id><title>Magnolia Electric Co. - Talk To Me Devil, Again - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:17:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:17:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magnolia_Electric_Co/Talk_To_Me_Devil_Again/" title="Magnolia Electric Co. - Talk To Me Devil, Again - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Roll the moon over my heart <br>Roll my heart out with the tide <br>I talked to the wolf in the mountain <br>And I talked to the mule in the mine <br><br>Devil unwind what's empty <br>Devil unwind my heart <br>Devil make the two ends meet <br>Devil when I fall <br><br>Talk to me devil, again <br>Talk to me devil, again <br>Talk to me devil, again <br>Baby I still have time <br><br>Smell the lightning burning the starry sky <br>Rhododendron now under the moon <br>All hearts still in the tide <br>Devil if I fall hold out no water to me <br>Devil when I fall, hold out no hand <br><br>Devil unwind what's empty <br>Devil unbind my heart <br>Devil make the two ends meet <br>Devil if I fall apart <br><br>Talk to me devil, again <br>Talk to me devil, again <br>Talk to me devil, again <br>Baby I still have time]]></content><category term="Magnolia Electric Co." label="Magnolia Electric Co."/><category term="Talk To Me Devil, Again" label="Talk To Me Devil, Again"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/divin/SFA_Sing_For_Amanda/</id><title>divin` - S.F.A (Sing For Amanda) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:17:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:17:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/divin/SFA_Sing_For_Amanda/" title="divin` - S.F.A (Sing For Amanda) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I feel you ah- ah <br>da ra du- <br>da ra du- <br>and dance up <br>I feel you ah- ah <br>da ra du- <br>da ra du- <br>난 너의 눈을 본 순간 <br>내 눈을 감아 <br>네 손을 잡아 <br>멈춰진 시간 속에 난 <br>내 숨이 가빠 <br>난 너를 잡아 <br>애써 딴 곳을 바라만 본채 넌 <br>내 속에 앉아 <br>아직도 station <br>내 길었던 기다림 끝에서 넌 <br>내 눈을 잡아 나를 봐 <br>I'll take it 난 <br>네게 다가 <br>가는 순간 <br>그곳에 나 <br>I'll stay your mind <br>네게 남아 <br>네 앞에 난 <br>I'll give you 날 <br>I feel you ah- ah <br>da ra du- <br>da ra du- <br>and dance up <br>I feel you ah- ah <br>da ra du- <br>da ra du- <br>난 네게 다가가 <br>너를 눈에 담아 널 가진 것 같아 <br>널 잡으려 네게로 날 데려가 <br>너와 눈이 마주친 순간 <br>난 망설임 없이 널 잡아 <br>애써 딴 곳을 바라만 본채 넌 <br>내 속에 앉아 <br>아직도 station <br>내 길었던 기다림 끝에서 넌 <br>내 눈을 잡아 나를 봐 <br>I feel you ah- ah <br>da ra du- <br>da ra du- <br>and dance up <br>I feel you ah- ah <br>da ra du- <br>da ra du- <br>da ra du- <br>da ra du- <br>da ra du- <br>da ra du- ah <br>da ra du- <br>da ra du- ah <br>da ra du- <br>da ra du- ah <br>da ra du- ah <br>]]></content><category term="divin`" label="divin`"/><category term="S.F.A (Sing For Amanda)" label="S.F.A (Sing For Amanda)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amen_Dunes/Christopher/</id><title>Amen Dunes - Christopher - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:18:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:18:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amen_Dunes/Christopher/" title="Amen Dunes - Christopher - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Christopher fought <br>With big allie too <br>In his little mind <br>He meant something to her <br><br>Now he sits there and cries <br>In the pit of his bed <br>He's a man to ignore <br><br>I heard your stories <br>And nobody cares <br>Are you fit for my mind <br>Are you tinted aquarius <br><br>I don't knock at no doors <br>I am quietly shared <br>I'm for people who know <br><br>Should <br>If i die, i <br>Chris <br>If i die <br>Chris <br>If you die, i <br><br>Chris <br>All this time <br>You never learned from me <br><br>I took the fall <br>When christopher said <br>That he thought he had died <br>From something i gave him <br><br>But i'll open the door <br>And i'll do it again <br>And i'm up till tomorrow <br><br>I heard your stories <br>And nobody cares <br>Are you fit for my mind <br>Are you tinted aquarius <br><br>I don't knock at no doors <br>I am quietly shared <br>I'm for people who know <br><br>Should <br>If i die, i <br>Chris <br>If i die <br>Chris <br>If you die, i <br><br>Should <br>If i die, i <br>Chris <br>If i die <br>Chris <br>If you die, i <br><br>Chris <br>A thousand times <br>Better you than me]]></content><category term="Amen Dunes" label="Amen Dunes"/><category term="Christopher" label="Christopher"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amen_Dunes/Swim_Up_Behind_Me/</id><title>Amen Dunes - Swim Up Behind Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:18:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:18:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amen_Dunes/Swim_Up_Behind_Me/" title="Amen Dunes - Swim Up Behind Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Darling I can see you up in the night <br>Nothing that I ever say <br>Only want to hide it <br>Hide in the righty <br>Looks on my life <br>Soon look behind me <br>Since I'm divided <br><br>Darling I can see you up in the night <br>Nothing that I ever say <br>Only want to hide it <br>Hide in the righty <br>Looks on my life <br>Soon look behind me <br>Since I'm divided <br><br>Somewhere beside us you <br>Silent light us for you <br>Time comes for you <br>I'm hollidew <br><br>Feel free to correct mistakes]]></content><category term="Amen Dunes" label="Amen Dunes"/><category term="Swim Up Behind Me" label="Swim Up Behind Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amen_Dunes/Lower_Mind/</id><title>Amen Dunes - Lower Mind - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:18:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:18:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amen_Dunes/Lower_Mind/" title="Amen Dunes - Lower Mind - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh let the lower mind come <br>When you leave it just unreal does <br>When you give it sweetly <br>Keep my king young <br>And you spill it from your tongue <br>We would all like the lake of love <br>But we really want to jump <br>Oh deep in the lower mind love <br>I could use you when I'm done <br>I don't need to listen <br>I don't need to listen <br>I don't need to listen <br>To a beast under the sun]]></content><category term="Amen Dunes" label="Amen Dunes"/><category term="Lower Mind" label="Lower Mind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amen_Dunes/Baba_Yaga/</id><title>Amen Dunes - Baba Yaga - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:18:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:18:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amen_Dunes/Baba_Yaga/" title="Amen Dunes - Baba Yaga - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You stay dumb <br>Won't you save it on my heart <br>You say that i'm negative <br>But you know it's all made up <br>You know that a song is a sign <br>Let it be soft <br>Thank God that i find <br>To think at all <br><br>You know that I, I lie <br>You know that I, I lie <br>With high girls in motion <br>They're light <br>And they're bright <br>Eager in my den]]></content><category term="Amen Dunes" label="Amen Dunes"/><category term="Baba Yaga" label="Baba Yaga"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/심재준/길/</id><title>심재준 - 길 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:18:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:18:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%AC%EC%9E%AC%EC%A4%80/%EA%B8%B8/" title="심재준 - 길 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[길 끝없는 길 시작도 없는 길 <br>그 무엇을 향해 한없이 뻗은 길 <br>길 그길 그 길 그 길 <br>길 드넓은 길 수많은 갈래 길 <br>그 어디로 가든 또다시 만날 길 <br>길 그길 그 길 그 길 <br>길 앞에 서있는 우리 길 <br>떠나 다시 만날 우리 <br>나 자신을 찾아 떠나는 그길 <br>머나먼 길 쓸쓸한 길 <br>길 외로운 길 나 홀로 <br>가는 길 눈물이 흘러도 <br>멈출 수 없는 길 <br>길 그길 그 길 그 길 <br>길 떠나온 길 또다시 <br>떠날 길 한없이 가다가 <br>가다가 못 갈 길 <br>길 그길 그 길 그 길 <br>길 앞에 서있는 우리 길 <br>떠나 다시 만날 우리 <br>나 자신을 찾아 떠나는 그길 <br>머나먼 길 쓸쓸한 길 <br>길 걸어온 길 길 쓸쓸한 길 <br>길 가야 할 길 길 머나먼 길 <br>길 걸어온 길 길 흐뭇한 길 <br>길 가야 할 길 길 꿈꾸는 길 <br>]]></content><category term="심재준" label="심재준"/><category term="길" label="길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/심재준/비가_내리네/</id><title>심재준 - 비가 내리네 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:18:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:18:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%AC%EC%9E%AC%EC%A4%80/%EB%B9%84%EA%B0%80_%EB%82%B4%EB%A6%AC%EB%84%A4/" title="심재준 - 비가 내리네 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람이 부네 내 마음 속에 <br>갈라진 내 가슴 속에 <br>비가 내리네 내 마음 속에 <br>메마른 내 가슴 속에 <br>흐르는 빗물 따라서 <br>눈물도 따라 흘러 <br>내 아픈 기억 <br>빗물에 흘려 보내 본다 <br>밤이 지나고 아침이 오면 <br>눈부신 그 햇살 아래 <br>빗물에 젖어 슬픔에 젖은 <br>내 마음 달래 본다 <br>바람이 부네 내 마음 속에 <br>갈라진 내 가슴 속에 <br>비가 내리네 내 마음 속에 <br>메마른 내 가슴 속에 <br>흐르는 빗물 따라서 <br>내 맘도 따라 흘러 <br>고운님 소식 <br>빗물에 띄워 보내 본다 <br>밤이 지나고 아침이 오면 <br>눈부신 그 햇살 아래 <br>빗물에 젖어 슬픔에 젖은 <br>내 마음 달래 본다 <br>비가 내리네 바람이 부네 <br>메마른 내 가슴은 <br>시간을 기다리네 <br>시간을 기다리네 <br>]]></content><category term="심재준" label="심재준"/><category term="비가 내리네" label="비가 내리네"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스위머스_Swiimers/영원을_믿지_않아도/</id><title>스위머스 (Swiimers) - 영원을 믿지 않아도 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:18:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:18:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%EC%9C%84%EB%A8%B8%EC%8A%A4_Swiimers/%EC%98%81%EC%9B%90%EC%9D%84_%EB%AF%BF%EC%A7%80_%EC%95%8A%EC%95%84%EB%8F%84/" title="스위머스 (Swiimers) - 영원을 믿지 않아도 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[막연한 슬픔 속을 헤엄치며 <br>무엇에도 쓸모 없는 사람으로 <br>태어나 살아가요 <br>나 혼자 깨어있는 밤이면 <br>유일한 나의 것인 <br>그림자를 빼앗겨버려 <br>무엇을 바라보아도 괜찮을 것 같아 <br>나를 위해 변해 달라고 하면 <br>영원을 믿지 않아도 <br>이 삶에 아무런 의미 없다고 해도 <br>영원을 믿지 않는 그대 나에게 <br>약속해 줄 건가요 <br>약속해 줄 건가요 <br>약속해 줄 건가요 <br>불안을 끌어안고 떠다니며 <br>숨죽여 우는 날이 <br>매일 조금씩 번져가요 <br>절망은 죽음처럼 늘 곁에 있죠 <br>나를 위해 잊어 달라고 하면 <br>영원을 믿지 않아도 <br>한 철을 머물다 가는 짧은 마음에 <br>영원을 믿지 않는 내게 그대는 <br>이 삶에 아무런 의미 없다고 해도 <br>영원을 믿지 않는 그대 나에게 <br>약속해 줄 건가요 <br>약속해 줄 건가요 <br>약속해 줄 건가요 <br>약속해 줄 건가요 <br>괜찮아요 <br>]]></content><category term="스위머스 (Swiimers)" label="스위머스 (Swiimers)"/><category term="영원을 믿지 않아도" label="영원을 믿지 않아도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/희원/딱_한번만/</id><title>희원 - 딱 한번만 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:21:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:21:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9D%AC%EC%9B%90/%EB%94%B1_%ED%95%9C%EB%B2%88%EB%A7%8C/" title="희원 - 딱 한번만 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 사랑했던 기억이 <br>점점 잊혀져가고 <br>깨진 기억을 붙잡아도 <br>자꾸만 사라져가 <br>처음과 많이 달라진 모습이 <br>말해줘 준비하라고 <br>애써 외면했던 <br>이별을 피할 수가 없다고 <br>보고 싶단 그 말도 <br>이제 네겐 할 수가 없고 <br>주고받던 일상도 <br>이제 더는 알 수가 없어 <br>꼭 다시 돌아온다면 <br>내 마음 숨김없이 <br>더 사랑할 수 있으니 <br>꿈에라도 나를 찾아와서 <br>머물다 가 <br>한 번만 딱 한 번만 <br>시간을 되돌려 <br>널 품에 안고 싶어 <br>너와 했던 모든 게 <br>지난 영화처럼 잊혀져 <br>기억이 사라지면 <br>다시 행복할 수 있을까 <br>꼭 다시 돌아온다면 <br>내 마음 숨김없이 <br>더 사랑할 수 있으니 <br>꿈에라도 나를 찾아와서 <br>머물다 가 <br>한 번만 딱 한 번만 <br>시간을 되돌려 <br>널 품에 안고 싶어 <br>]]></content><category term="희원" label="희원"/><category term="딱 한번만" label="딱 한번만"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리마크/항상_웃어줘/</id><title>리마크 - 항상 웃어줘 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:21:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:21:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%A7%88%ED%81%AC/%ED%95%AD%EC%83%81_%EC%9B%83%EC%96%B4%EC%A4%98/" title="리마크 - 항상 웃어줘 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밝게 웃는 너의 모습 <br>내 마음에 비칠 때 <br>잠시 생각해봐 <br>잘 지내는지 <br>아름다운 햇살이 비치는 <br>오늘 같은 날이면 <br>더욱 생각나 <br>예쁘게 웃던 너의 미소가 <br>날 보며 반기던 너의 품이 <br>아직도 많이 생각나네 <br>내 아름다운 시간 속의 너로 <br>웃으며 행복하면 좋겠다 <br>내 진심이 그런 거야 <br>항상 웃어줘 제발 <br>밝게 웃는 너의 모습 <br>내 마음에 비칠 때 <br>잠시 생각해봐 <br>잘 지내는지 <br>아름다운 햇살이 비치는 <br>오늘 같은 날이면 <br>더욱 생각나 <br>예쁘게 웃던 너의 미소가 <br>날 보며 반기던 너의 품이 <br>아직도 많이 생각나네 <br>내 아름다운 시간 속의 너로 <br>웃으며 행복하면 좋겠다 <br>내 진심이 그런 거야 <br>항상 웃어줘 제발 <br>]]></content><category term="리마크" label="리마크"/><category term="항상 웃어줘" label="항상 웃어줘"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루하/바람이_불어/</id><title>루하 - 바람이 불어 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:21:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:21:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%ED%95%98/%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B6%88%EC%96%B4/" title="루하 - 바람이 불어 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람이 불어와 날 스치고 간다 <br>너와의 추억 가득한 이 거리에 <br>혼자서 걸을 줄은 정말 몰랐어 <br>우리 함께한 푸르던 이 길 <br>이제는 차가운 흔적들만 남았어 <br>낙엽만이 뿌려진 <br>그 사이로 다시 바람이 불어 <br>부서져 가는 기억 <br>눈앞에 보이는 이 얼굴 너겠지 <br>그게 참 아파오는 밤이야 <br>바라지 않아도 그리움은 커져가 <br>의미 없는 바람만 불어 <br>바람이 불어와 날 스치고 간다 <br>너와의 추억 가득한 이 거리에 <br>혼자서 걸을 줄은 정말 몰랐어 <br>우리 함께한 푸르던 이 길 <br>이제는 차가운 흔적들만 남았어 <br>낙엽만이 뿌려진 <br>그 사이로 다시 바람이 불어 <br>부서져 가는 기억 <br>눈앞에 보이는 이 얼굴 너겠지 <br>그게 참 아파오는 밤이야 <br>바라지 않아도 그리움은 커져가 <br>의미 없는 바람만 불어 <br>]]></content><category term="루하" label="루하"/><category term="바람이 불어" label="바람이 불어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레베카/야경/</id><title>레베카 - 야경 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:25:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:25:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EB%B2%A0%EC%B9%B4/%EC%95%BC%EA%B2%BD/" title="레베카 - 야경 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[도로 위를 스쳐 달리는 <br>저 멀리 저편 작은 불빛 하나 <br>수많은 빛 속에서 <br>난 그들 중에 하나일 뿐 <br>있는 힘껏 달려가 봐도 <br>작고 작은 난 티가 나지 않아 <br>어차피 저 사진 속 <br>야경의 주인공은 내가 아냐 <br>나 이대로 멈춰 서 버려도 <br>누가 날 알아봐 줄까 <br>So far away 내 빛을 보지 못해도 <br>나 이대로 그저 걸어가려해 <br>오늘도 저 야경 속에 하나 되어 <br>빛나겠지 <br>있는 힘껏 달려가 봐도 <br>작고 작은 난 티가 나지 않아 <br>어차피 저 사진 속 <br>야경의 주인공은 내가 아냐 <br>나 이대로 멈춰 서 버려도 <br>누가 날 알아봐 줄까 <br>So far away 내 빛을 보지 못해도 <br>나 이대로 그저 걸어가려해 <br>오늘도 저 야경 속에 하나 되어 <br>빛나겠지 <br>]]></content><category term="레베카" label="레베카"/><category term="야경" label="야경"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서혁신/달이_넘어간다/</id><title>서혁신 - 달이 넘어간다 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:25:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:25:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%ED%98%81%EC%8B%A0/%EB%8B%AC%EC%9D%B4_%EB%84%98%EC%96%B4%EA%B0%84%EB%8B%A4/" title="서혁신 - 달이 넘어간다 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[해가 지던 언덕 너머로 <br>달이 넘어간다 달이 넘어간다 <br>지금은 어둡지만 <br>달이 넘어간다 달이 넘어간다 <br>언젠가는 다시 <br>태양도 떠오르겠지 내게 <br>기를 써도 발광을 해도 <br>달이 넘어간다 달이 넘어간다 <br>부딪쳐도 자빠져도 <br>달이 넘어간다 달이 넘어간다 <br>저 태양이 날 밝게 비춰주는 날까지 예 <br>덜된 놈들 못된 놈들 <br>모두 지나간다 모두 지나간다 <br>다들 지가 영원할 줄 <br>착각하며 살지 그래도 괜찮아 <br>널 괴롭히는 건 <br>우리가 아냐 이놈들 너야 <br>불이 나도 홍수가 나도 <br>달이 넘어간다 다시 해가 뜬다 <br>호랑이한테 물려가도 <br>아따 정신만 차려부러 <br>그라믄 살 수 있당께 <br>널 괴롭히는 모든 것들은 이제 없어 <br>이 세상 근심 걱정 <br>모두 던져버리고 이제 <br>]]></content><category term="서혁신" label="서혁신"/><category term="달이 넘어간다" label="달이 넘어간다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나로/첫눈에/</id><title>나로 - 첫눈에 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:25:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:25:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%A1%9C/%EC%B2%AB%EB%88%88%EC%97%90/" title="나로 - 첫눈에 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그때 너의 모습 너무나 <br>예뻤었어 내가 첫눈에 반했으니까 <br>널 따라 다니던 내 모습이 <br>지금 생각하면 너무 부끄러워 <br>그렇게 내 마음 몰라주던 너도 <br>조금씩 내가 눈에 밟혔는지 <br>결국엔 내 옆자리에 있어주는 <br>아름다운 네가 있어 참 고마워 <br>늘 곁에서 지금처럼 사랑해줘 <br>더 잘할게 <br>그때 너의 모습 너무나 <br>예뻤었어 내가 첫눈에 반했으니까 <br>널 따라 다니던 내 모습이 <br>지금 생각하면 너무 부끄러워 <br>그렇게 내 마음 몰라주던 너도 <br>조금씩 내가 눈에 밟혔는지 <br>결국엔 내 옆자리에 있어주는 <br>아름다운 네가 있어 참 고마워 <br>늘 곁에서 지금처럼 사랑해줘 <br>더 잘할게 <br>]]></content><category term="나로" label="나로"/><category term="첫눈에" label="첫눈에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Autograf/Sleepless_In_NYC/</id><title>Autograf - Sleepless In NYC - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:25:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:25:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Autograf/Sleepless_In_NYC/" title="Autograf - Sleepless In NYC - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[City, city <br><br>[Verse 1] <br>Could I stand by, while we watched it fall <br>Fortunes are fading, do we hit the wall <br>So stay right next to me <br>'Cause your body's all I need <br>Maybe we're not what we were before <br>Strangers passing, all for starters now <br>There's nothing left to hold <br>And the night is all I know <br><br>[Pre-Chorus] <br>Getting high 'til the sun goes down <br>Lift my head and I leave the ground <br>I know I said that I need this town <br>I need you back, wrap it up did the best of me <br>Neon lights come and set me free <br>Close my eyes and I know I'll be <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Sleepless in New York City, City, City <br>Sleepless in New York City, City, City <br>Sleepless in New York City, City, City <br>Sleepless in New York City, City, City <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>If I could try getting you alone <br>You could remember that I feel like home <br>But I can't sleep and the night is all I see <br><br>[Pre-Chorus] <br>Getting high 'til the sun goes down <br>Lift my head and I leave the ground <br>I know I said that I need this town <br>I need you back, wrap it up did the best of me <br>Neon lights come and set me free <br>Close my eyes and I know I'll be <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Sleepless in New York City, City, City <br>Sleepless in New York City, City, City <br>Sleepless in New York City, City, City <br>Sleepless in New York City, City, City]]></content><category term="Autograf" label="Autograf"/><category term="Sleepless In NYC" label="Sleepless In NYC"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/성영주/냉장고/</id><title>성영주 - 냉장고 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:26:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:26:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%B1%EC%98%81%EC%A3%BC/%EB%83%89%EC%9E%A5%EA%B3%A0/" title="성영주 - 냉장고 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[목말라 무심코 연 <br>냉장고 속 네가 날 위해 만든 <br>그 요리에 네 생각에 <br>터져 나와 운다 <br>이 새벽에 또 울고 <br>있는 나는 또 뭔데 <br>이 까짓 게 다 뭐라고 <br>아직도 못 버리는데 <br>첫 한입 먹기도 전 <br>맛있냐고 몇 번씩 묻던 너는 <br>어디에서 누구에게 <br>사랑 받고 있나 <br>이 새벽에 또 울고 <br>있는 나는 또 뭔데 <br>이 까짓 게 다 뭐라고 <br>아직도 못 버리는데 <br>난 또 왜 <br>이러는 건데 <br>남는 게 <br>뭐가 있는데 <br>이 까짓 게 <br>다 뭐라고 <br>아직도 못 버리는데 <br>내 마음의 유통기한이 <br>다 지날 때까지만 <br>거기 머물러줘 <br>]]></content><category term="성영주" label="성영주"/><category term="냉장고" label="냉장고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한때소년단/싼_남자/</id><title>한때소년단 - 싼 남자 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:26:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:26:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EB%95%8C%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84%EB%8B%A8/%EC%8B%BC_%EB%82%A8%EC%9E%90/" title="한때소년단 - 싼 남자 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[배고파 너의 오빠 <br>나나나나나나나나나나나나 <br>배고파 너의 오빠 <br>나나나나나나나나나나나나 <br>뭐라는데 와 이라는데 <br>뭘 어쨌다고 이러는데 <br>너는 뭔데 네가 뭔데 <br>남의 쫀심을 후벼 파 <br>됐다는데 냅두라는데 <br>왜 자꾸 들쑤셔 대는데 <br>너는 넌데 나는 난데 <br>대체 뭘 어쩌라는 건데 <br>평민 위에 물주 물주 위에 <br>교주 교주 위에 조물주 <br>조물주 위에 건물주 <br>이런 거지같은 상황 속에서 <br>나는 열나게 달려 <br>하지만 쳇바퀴 같은 현실 속에서 <br>나는 제 자릴 지켜 <br>그래요 보다시피 나는 싼 남자에요 <br>가진 건 1도 없지만 나 꿈은 있어요 <br>아직 부족해 보여도 뭐라 하지 마요 <br>인생 많이 길어요 아직 안 끝났어요 <br>돈이 없지 깡이 없냐 <br>빳빳하게 고개 팍 쳐들어 <br>언젠가는 보란 듯이 <br>인생 역전 간다 간다 간다 <br>뭐라는데 와 이라는데 <br>뭐가 맘에 안 드는 건데 <br>너는 뭔데 네가 뭔데 <br>감히 누구를 평가해 <br>됐다는데 냅두라는데 <br>언제까지 오지랖인데 <br>너는 넌데 나는 난데 <br>대체 뭘 어쩌라는 건데 <br>그래 오늘도 그러거나 말거나 <br>놀려 대거나 말거나 <br>어떻게 말을 하겠어 <br>결과로 보여 주겠어 <br>니들은 깨닫게 될 거야 <br>결국은 후회할 거야 <br>그렇게 무시했던 내가 <br>너보다 우뚝 서겠어 <br>그래요 보다시피 나는 싼 남자에요 <br>가진 건 1도 없지만 나 꿈은 있어요 <br>아직 부족해 보여도 뭐라 하지 마요 <br>인생 많이 길어요 아직 안 끝났어요 <br>돈이 없지 깡이 없냐 <br>빳빳하게 고개 팍 쳐들어 <br>언젠가는 보란 듯이 <br>인생 역전 간다 간다 간다 <br>고단하고 힘들어도 <br>울지 않는다 다시 일어선다 <br>그래 나는 싼 남자다 <br>밑도 끝도 없이 싼 남자다 <br>해 뜰 날이 돌아온다 <br>그래 오늘도 그러거나 말거나 <br>놀려 대거나 말거나 <br>어떻게 말을 하겠어 <br>결과로 보여 주겠어 <br>니들은 깨닫게 될 거야 <br>결국은 후회할 거야 <br>그렇게 무시했던 <br>내가 너보다 우뚝 서겠어 <br>배고파 너의 오빠 <br>나나나나나나나나나나나나 <br>배고파 너의 오빠 <br>나나나나나나나나나나나나 <br>]]></content><category term="한때소년단" label="한때소년단"/><category term="싼 남자" label="싼 남자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/라미스/우리/</id><title>라미스 - 우리 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:27:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:27:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9D%BC%EB%AF%B8%EC%8A%A4/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC/" title="라미스 - 우리 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생각은 나니 그때 우리 함께 <br>했던 많은 시간들 <br>실감은 나니 이제 우리 함께 <br>하지 못한 순간들 <br>어느새 시간이 흘러 여기까지 오게 된 <br>우리들 너와 함께 지내온 날들 <br>더없이 소중했던 시간들 <br>이젠 희미해져버린 내 기억 속 네 모습 <br>너무나 안타깝던 순간들 <br>이미 희미해져버린 네 기억 속 내 모습 <br>어느새 시간이 흘러 여기까지 오게 된 <br>우리들 너와 함께 지내온 날들 <br>더없이 소중했던 시간들 <br>이젠 희미해져버린 내 기억 속 네 모습 <br>너무나 안타깝던 순간들 <br>이미 희미해져버린 네 기억 속 <br>너무나 안타깝던 순간들 <br>이미 희미해져버린 네 기억 속 내 모습 <br>]]></content><category term="라미스" label="라미스"/><category term="우리" label="우리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/황선정/삶의_무게/</id><title>황선정 - 삶의 무게 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:27:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:27:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%A9%EC%84%A0%EC%A0%95/%EC%82%B6%EC%9D%98_%EB%AC%B4%EA%B2%8C/" title="황선정 - 삶의 무게 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈부신 그대가 있어 <br>내 삶이 행복을 알고 <br>그대와 함께했던 그 길이 <br>눈부신 삶의 무게야 <br>나 이제 그대를 위해 <br>내 꿈을 가꾸고 싶어 <br>그대와 함께했던 그 길이 <br>나만의 그대 삶이야 <br>그대 우리이제 <br>사랑만 하기로 해요 <br>이유도 많고 갈등 많았던 <br>지난일 잊기로 했잖아요 <br>지난 과거 때문에 <br>남겨진 상처를 <br>다시 떠올려 아파 할 <br>시간이 없어 오 그대 <br>화려했었던 우리 지난 상처는 <br>다시는 말하지 않기로 해요 <br>그대 우리 이제 <br>사랑만 하기로 해요 <br>이유도 많고 갈등 많았던 <br>지난일 잊기로 했잖아요 <br>지난 과거 때문에 <br>남겨진 상처를 <br>다시 떠올려 아파 할 <br>시간이 없어 오 그대 <br>화려했었던 우리 지난 상처는 <br>다시는 말하지 않기로 해요 <br>화려했었던 우리 지난 상처는 <br>다시는 말하지 않기로 해요 <br>]]></content><category term="황선정" label="황선정"/><category term="삶의 무게" label="삶의 무게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Ink/I_Just_Want_It_All_Clean/</id><title>Kid Ink - I Just Want It All (Clean) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-03-19T19:30:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-03-19T19:30:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kid_Ink/I_Just_Want_It_All_Clean/" title="Kid Ink - I Just Want It All (Clean) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Chorus <br>I just want it all, money and the cars right <br>I don't wear a tie but they say I live a boss life <br>I just want it all, pullin' a bad bitch, way back then <br>Thought that we would never have this <br>Now I just want it all, all, all, all, all, all, yeah <br>I just want it all, all, all, all, all, yeah yeah <br><br>Verse 1 <br>I just want it all, high above the law <br>Kill 'em so cool you can call me Mr. Frost <br>Come and find me where the money is, ever feeling lost <br>I just wanna ball, so sick of playing toss <br>I remember back then I had a dream since then <br>I've been sleep walking all the ups and downs I was see-sawing <br>Only made me strong like steroids <br>Game time 'bout served these niggas like a bell boy <br>Tell them that it's over , finito <br>I can make it bump bump bump like a mosquito <br>It's just all in my steelo <br>And my pockets are the only thing bigger than my ego <br><br>Chorus <br>I just want it all, money and the cars right <br>I don't wear a tie but they say I live a boss life <br>I just want it all, pullin' a bad bitch, way back then <br>Thought that we would never have this <br>Now I just want it all, all, all, all, all, all, yeah <br>I just want it all, all, all, all, all, yeah yeah <br><br>Verse 2 <br>I don’t wanna stall, I would never leave me <br>I don't wanna fall, no matter the cost <br>I'm all in, 'til the coffin <br>Kush coughing nicer than your conscience <br>Finally everywhere you wanna be, moving high velocity <br>Driving irresponsibly but I think you should come <br>And take a ride see the world through my eyes <br>Every day is a surprise <br>So I party like my birthday, LA is my birthplace <br>First place, west side, loud as a I wanna be <br>They been sleeping on me, now they in the fetal <br>Yeah I'm nito everything's in tuxedo <br><br>Chorus <br>I just want it all, money and the cars right <br>I don't wear a tie but they say I live a boss life <br>I just want it all, pullin' a bad bitch, way back then <br>Thought that we would never have this <br>Now I just want it all, all, all, all, all, all, yeah <br>I just want it all, all, all, all, all, yeah yeah <br><br>Outro <br>You ain't got to give it to me, I'll take it from y'all]]></content><category term="Kid Ink" label="Kid Ink"/><category term="I Just Want It All (Clean)" label="I Just Want It All (Clean)"/></entry></feed>