<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:30:25+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노희정/아리랑_원_코리아/</id><title>노희정 - 아리랑 원 코리아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:30:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:30:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%ED%9D%AC%EC%A0%95/%EC%95%84%EB%A6%AC%EB%9E%91_%EC%9B%90_%EC%BD%94%EB%A6%AC%EC%95%84/" title="노희정 - 아리랑 원 코리아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오 아리랑 아리랑 <br>원 코리아 <br>오 오 아리랑 아리랑 <br>원 코리아 <br>하늘 위엔 평화로운 세상 <br>땅 위엔 자유의 세상 <br>동방의 작은 나라 <br>우리 이젠 하나되어 <br>세계의 중심 되자 <br>아리랑 아리랑 <br>one race one korea <br>모두가 꿈꿔왔던 <br>아리랑 원 코리아 <br>아 우리 모두가 <br>일어서야만 해 <br>영원토록 하나되어 살리라 <br>뛰어라 우린 모두 하나야 <br>아리랑 원 코리아 <br>아리랑 원 코리아 <br>서로가 안고 포옹하며 <br>마음의 문을 활짝 열어 <br>모두가 한마음으로 <br>평화를 위해 <br>오 아리랑 아리랑 <br>원 코리아 <br>오 오 아리랑 아리랑 <br>원 코리아 <br>아리랑 아리랑 <br>one race one korea <br>모두가 꿈꿔왔던 <br>아리랑 원 코리아 <br>아 우리 모두가 <br>일어서야만 해 <br>영원토록 하나되어 살리라 <br>뛰어라 우린 모두 하나야 <br>아리랑 원 코리아 <br>아리랑 원 코리아 <br>서로가 안고 포옹하며 <br>마음의 문을 활짝 열어 <br>모두가 한마음으로 <br>평화를 위해 <br>오 아리랑 아리랑 <br>원 코리아 <br>오 오 아리랑 아리랑 <br>원 코리아 <br>오 아리랑 아리랑 <br>원 코리아 <br>오 오 아리랑 아리랑 <br>원 코리아 <br>오 아리랑 아리랑 <br>원 코리아 <br>오 오 아리랑 아리랑 <br>원 코리아 <br>]]></content><category term="노희정" label="노희정"/><category term="아리랑 원 코리아" label="아리랑 원 코리아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노희정/돈돌라리_사랑_BGM/</id><title>노희정 - 돈돌라리 사랑 (BGM) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:30:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:30:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%ED%9D%AC%EC%A0%95/%EB%8F%88%EB%8F%8C%EB%9D%BC%EB%A6%AC_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_BGM/" title="노희정 - 돈돌라리 사랑 (BGM) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[님 찾아 구름 속 헤매일 때 <br>그 님이 내 님인 줄 몰랐었네 <br>그리운 님 떠난 후 사랑 찾아 <br>저 넘어 강을 건넜다네 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>다시는 돌아갈 수 없다면 <br>그 강을 건너지 말 것을 <br>야속 허다 야속해 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 내님아 돈돌라리 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>북향 바람에 내 맘 전하네 <br>언제나 오려나 내 사랑아 <br>이생에 만나지 못한다면 <br>저 생에라도 만나리요 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>다시는 돌아갈 수 없다면 <br>그 강을 건너지 말 것을 <br>야속허다 야속해 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 내님아 돈돌라리 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>북향 바람에 내 맘 전하네 <br>언제나 오려나 내 사랑아 <br>이생에 만나지 못한다면 <br>저생에라도 만나리요 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>내 사랑 내 님아 돈돌라리요 <br>]]></content><category term="노희정" label="노희정"/><category term="돈돌라리 사랑 (BGM)" label="돈돌라리 사랑 (BGM)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노희정/그리움_Inst/</id><title>노희정 - 그리움 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:30:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:30:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%ED%9D%AC%EC%A0%95/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9B%80_Inst/" title="노희정 - 그리움 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[푸른 빗물에 비취는 <br>너의 모습에 <br>미치도록 보고 싶어서 <br>난 너를 보고 싶어서 <br>너를 불러보지만 <br>돌아오는 건 외로움 <br>전하는 너의 모습뿐 <br>너를 두고 돌아설 때에 <br>사랑한다고 <br>그 말을 못 했던 <br>너에게 또 어떤 <br>약속을 하고 싶어서 <br>널 간절히 너를 불렀을까 <br>너를 불렀을까 <br>보고파 보고파서 <br>소리 질러서 <br>꿈에서라도 <br>꼭 만날 수 있게 <br>가고파 가고파서 <br>빗속을 달렸어 <br>널 위해 내 눈물 삼킬거야 <br>영원히 <br>어린 새 한 마리 <br>나무 위에 두고 <br>뒤돌아 올 때 <br>비가 내렸지 <br>비가 내리는 날엔 <br>너무도 그리워서 <br>난 빗속을 달려 <br>눈물 감췄네 <br>너를 두고 돌아 설 때에 <br>사랑한다고 <br>그 말을 못 했던 <br>너에게 또 어떤 <br>약속을 하고 싶어서 <br>널 간절히 <br>너를 불렀을까 <br>너를 불렀을까 <br>보고파 보고파서 <br>소리 질러서 <br>꿈에서라도 <br>꼭 만날 수 있게 <br>가고파 가고파서 <br>빗속을 달렸어 <br>널 위해 내 눈물 삼킬거야 <br>영원히 <br>널 만나도 널 <br>안아줄 힘이 없어 <br>그리워만 하나봐 <br>난 널 보아도 <br>뛰어갈 힘이 없어 <br>그리워만 하나봐 <br>]]></content><category term="노희정" label="노희정"/><category term="그리움 (Inst.)" label="그리움 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노희정/돈돌라리_사랑_피리/</id><title>노희정 - 돈돌라리 사랑 (피리) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:30:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:30:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%ED%9D%AC%EC%A0%95/%EB%8F%88%EB%8F%8C%EB%9D%BC%EB%A6%AC_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_%ED%94%BC%EB%A6%AC/" title="노희정 - 돈돌라리 사랑 (피리) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[님 찾아 구름 속 헤매일 때 <br>그 님이 내 님인 줄 몰랐었네 <br>그리운 님 떠난 후 사랑 찾아 <br>저 넘어 강을 건넜다네 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>다시는 돌아갈 수 없다면 <br>그 강을 건너지 말 것을 <br>야속 허다 야속해 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 내님아 돈돌라리 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>북향 바람에 내 맘 전하네 <br>언제나 오려나 내 사랑아 <br>이생에 만나지 못한다면 <br>저 생에라도 만나리요 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>다시는 돌아갈 수 없다면 <br>그 강을 건너지 말 것을 <br>야속허다 야속해 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 내님아 돈돌라리 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>북향 바람에 내 맘 전하네 <br>언제나 오려나 내 사랑아 <br>이생에 만나지 못한다면 <br>저생에라도 만나리요 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>내 사랑 내 님아 돈돌라리요 <br>]]></content><category term="노희정" label="노희정"/><category term="돈돌라리 사랑 (피리)" label="돈돌라리 사랑 (피리)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노희정/그리움/</id><title>노희정 - 그리움 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:30:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:30:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%ED%9D%AC%EC%A0%95/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9B%80/" title="노희정 - 그리움 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[푸른 빗물에 비취는 <br>너의 모습에 <br>미치도록 보고 싶어서 <br>난 너를 보고 싶어서 <br>너를 불러보지만 <br>돌아오는 건 외로움 <br>전하는 너의 모습뿐 <br>너를 두고 돌아설 때에 <br>사랑한다고 <br>그 말을 못 했던 <br>너에게 또 어떤 <br>약속을 하고 싶어서 <br>널 간절히 너를 불렀을까 <br>너를 불렀을까 <br>보고파 보고파서 <br>소리 질러서 <br>꿈에서라도 <br>꼭 만날 수 있게 <br>가고파 가고파서 <br>빗속을 달렸어 <br>널 위해 내 눈물 삼킬거야 <br>영원히 <br>어린 새 한 마리 <br>나무 위에 두고 <br>뒤돌아 올 때 <br>비가 내렸지 <br>비가 내리는 날엔 <br>너무도 그리워서 <br>난 빗속을 달려 <br>눈물 감췄네 <br>너를 두고 돌아 설 때에 <br>사랑한다고 <br>그 말을 못 했던 <br>너에게 또 어떤 <br>약속을 하고 싶어서 <br>널 간절히 <br>너를 불렀을까 <br>너를 불렀을까 <br>보고파 보고파서 <br>소리 질러서 <br>꿈에서라도 <br>꼭 만날 수 있게 <br>가고파 가고파서 <br>빗속을 달렸어 <br>널 위해 내 눈물 삼킬거야 <br>영원히 <br>널 만나도 널 <br>안아줄 힘이 없어 <br>그리워만 하나봐 <br>난 널 보아도 <br>뛰어갈 힘이 없어 <br>그리워만 하나봐 <br>]]></content><category term="노희정" label="노희정"/><category term="그리움" label="그리움"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노희정/사애가/</id><title>노희정 - 사애가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:30:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:30:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%ED%9D%AC%EC%A0%95/%EC%82%AC%EC%95%A0%EA%B0%80/" title="노희정 - 사애가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너와 나 사랑타가 <br>생사가 한이 되면 <br>너의 혼은 꽃이 되고 <br>나의 넋은 나비 되어 <br>두 날개 활짝 펴고 <br>니 꽃송이를 안어 <br>너울너울 춤추거든 <br>날 인줄 알려므나 <br>이곳에 한일랑 <br>추풍에 낙엽마냥 이 세상에 <br>미련 없이 버려두고 <br>사랑만 허자꾸나 <br>사랑 사랑 내 사랑이야 <br>어허 둥둥 내 사랑이지 <br>생시에 못한 사랑 <br>천국에서 다해보세 내 사랑아 <br>내가 먼저 가거들랑 <br>너를 찾아 헤매일 적 <br>하얀 나비 보이거든 <br>사랑사랑 불러주오 <br>니가 먼저 가는 날엔 <br>나도 따라 갈 테이니 <br>나를 찾을 일은 무일 <br>허니 걱정일랑 하지 마오 <br>이곳에 한일랑 <br>추풍에 낙엽마냥 이 세상에 <br>미련 없이 버려두고 <br>사랑만 허자꾸나 <br>사랑 사랑 내 사랑이야 <br>어허 둥둥 내 사랑이지 <br>생시에 못한 사랑 <br>천국에서 다해보세 내 사랑아 <br>]]></content><category term="노희정" label="노희정"/><category term="사애가" label="사애가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노희정/돈돌라리_사랑/</id><title>노희정 - 돈돌라리 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:30:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:30:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%ED%9D%AC%EC%A0%95/%EB%8F%88%EB%8F%8C%EB%9D%BC%EB%A6%AC_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="노희정 - 돈돌라리 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[님 찾아 구름 속 헤매일 때 <br>그 님이 내 님인 줄 몰랐었네 <br>그리운 님 떠난 후 사랑 찾아 <br>저 넘어 강을 건넜다네 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>다시는 돌아갈 수 없다면 <br>그 강을 건너지 말 것을 <br>야속 허다 야속해 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 내님아 돈돌라리 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>북향 바람에 내 맘 전하네 <br>언제나 오려나 내 사랑아 <br>이생에 만나지 못한다면 <br>저 생에라도 만나리요 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>다시는 돌아갈 수 없다면 <br>그 강을 건너지 말 것을 <br>야속허다 야속해 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 내님아 돈돌라리 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>북향 바람에 내 맘 전하네 <br>언제나 오려나 내 사랑아 <br>이생에 만나지 못한다면 <br>저생에라도 만나리요 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 사랑아 <br>돈돌라리 돈돌라리 내 님아 <br>내 사랑 내 님아 돈돌라리요 <br>]]></content><category term="노희정" label="노희정"/><category term="돈돌라리 사랑" label="돈돌라리 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TIKKIT/I_NEED_YOU/</id><title>TIKKIT - I NEED YOU - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:30:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:30:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TIKKIT/I_NEED_YOU/" title="TIKKIT - I NEED YOU - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[baby you baby you <br>baby you no no no <br>baby i need you right now <br>너가 보고싶은데 너와 <br>함께하는 매일이 매 순간이 <br>내겐 선물인 걸 <br>하루종일 이렇게 <br>또 나혼자 <br>그새를 못참고 또 아 <br>널 만날 생각에 <br>니 생각에 빠져난 <br>좋아하는 노래를 들어도 <br>혼자 밤거릴 걸어도 <br>너를 바라보고 있어도 <br>니가 보고 싶어 <br>하루종일 너와 눈 맞추고 <br>예쁜 너의 입술에 입 맞추고 <br>너무나 소중해 지금 이 모든게 <br>i need you right now <br>나랑 만날래 지금 당장 <br>보고싶어 미치겠어 <br>난 어떡해야돼 <br>baby i need you right now <br>널 보러갈래 지금 당장 <br>니 생각에 미치겠어 <br>널 어떡해야돼 no no <br>i need you baby woo <br>i need you baby woo <br>i need you baby baby <br>i need you baby woo <br>i need you baby woo <br>i need you baby woo <br>i need you baby baby <br>i need you baby woo <br>너와 함께 있을때면 <br>세상을 다 가진것 같아 <br>아마 너의 웃음이 <br>너무도 이쁜 탓이겠지 <br>딱히 꾸미진 않아도 <br>너무 섹시하고 귀여워 넌 <br>내가 꿈꾸던 여자보다 <br>훨씬 아름다운 걸 <br>좋아하는 노래를 들어도 <br>혼자 밤거릴 걸어도 <br>너를 바라보고 있어도 <br>니가 보고 싶어 <br>하루종일 너와 눈 맞추고 <br>예쁜 너의 입술에 입 맞추고 <br>너무나 사랑스러워 <br>지금 너의 모든게 <br>i need you right now <br>나랑 만날래 지금 당장 <br>보고싶어 미치겠어 <br>난 어떡해야돼 <br>baby i need you right now <br>널 보러갈래 지금 당장 <br>니 생각에 미치겠어 <br>널 어떡해야돼 <br>가끔은 불안해져 <br>이런 마음이 다 사라질까봐 <br>너와 단 한순간도 1분 1초도 <br>떨어져 있고싶지가 않아 baby <br>i need you right now <br>나랑 만날래 지금 당장 <br>보고싶어 미치겠어 <br>난 어떡해야돼 <br>baby i need you right now <br>널 보러갈래 지금 당장 <br>니 생각에 미치겠어 <br>널 어떡해야돼 no no <br>i need you baby woo <br>i need you baby woo <br>i need you baby baby <br>i need you baby woo <br>i need you baby woo <br>i need you baby woo <br>i need you baby baby <br>i need you baby woo <br>]]></content><category term="TIKKIT" label="TIKKIT"/><category term="I NEED YOU" label="I NEED YOU"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정단/하얀_손수건_Feat_이신애/</id><title>정단 - 하얀 손수건 (Feat. 이신애) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:30:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:30:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EB%8B%A8/%ED%95%98%EC%96%80_%EC%86%90%EC%88%98%EA%B1%B4_Feat_%EC%9D%B4%EC%8B%A0%EC%95%A0/" title="정단 - 하얀 손수건 (Feat. 이신애) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[헤어지자 보내 온 <br>그녀의 편지 속에 <br>곱게 적어 함께 부친 하얀 손수건 <br>고향을 떠나올 때 <br>언덕에 홀로 서서 <br>눈물로 흔들어 주던 하얀 손수건 <br>그 때의 눈물 자욱 <br>사라져 버리고 <br>흐르는 내 눈물이 그 위를 적시네 <br>고향을 떠나올 때 <br>언덕에 홀로 서서 <br>눈물로 흔들어 주던 하얀 손수건 <br>그 때의 눈물 자욱 <br>사라져 버리고 <br>흐르는 내 눈물이 그 위를 적시네 <br>흐르는 내 눈물이 그 위를 적시네 <br>]]></content><category term="정단" label="정단"/><category term="하얀 손수건 (Feat. 이신애)" label="하얀 손수건 (Feat. 이신애)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/타투_TATU/And_You/</id><title>타투 (TATU) - And You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:31:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:31:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%80%ED%88%AC_TATU/And_You/" title="타투 (TATU) - And You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh 넌 알 필요 있어 너의 위치 <br>쳐다 보지마 여긴 꽤나 높지 <br>나와 내 팀 We are fine so much <br>and u 물어보니 <br>헛기침만 Why <br>음 난 매일밤 Party Night <br>ah 빼고 주일만 <br>난 달라지고 있지 <br>니들 생각과는 <br>가까이 살고 있어 <br>성공이란 놈과 <br>오늘이 안 되면 내일 해 <br>놀면서 생각을 we JumpMan <br>언제나 삶에 <br>내 위치는 가운데 <br>각자의 중심에서 <br>외치는 건배 <br>밥 먹을 때 마다 <br>신께 기도하는 습관처럼 <br>삶 이자 숨 쉬듯 하는 음악 <br>손가락질 무시하던 꼰대들과 <br>JB 또한 이젠 <br>날 인정하는 눈치 <br>but so what <br>I'm chillin' not like you do <br>I'm chillin' not like you do <br>니가 뭘 아냐고 하냐고 <br>비웃고는 했지만 yeah <br>I'm still here not like you do <br>I'm feeling everything for life <br>That's why <br>여전히 난 내 멋대로 <br>I'm doing doing doing <br>and you and you and you and <br>Still doing doing doing <br>and you and you and you and <br>I'm doing doing doing <br>and you and you and you and <br>Still doing doing doing <br>넌 대체 언제까지 우물 안에 <br>개구리를 훔쳐보며 자위할래 <br>태초에 신께서 창조한 <br>세상은 아름다워 <br>그렇게 평생을 <br>탓만 하며 살래 <br>더러운건 너희들의 <br>생각과 시각 <br>의미 없는 시간 <br>그 틀에 맞춰 생겨 그 모양 <br>기분 나쁘다면 <br>넌 거기 남기 충분해 <br>난 이제 확실하게 <br>말 할 수 있어 더 기대해 <br>달라고 난 내일을 더 믿거든 <br>내 존재 자체가 <br>내게는 밑거름 <br>남 일로 받는 <br>stress 없이 다리 꼬고 <br>우리 일만 하니까 <br>이게 청춘인가 싶어 피 끓는 <br>그 새끼는 불평만 하지 <br>오늘도 남 일에 신경 쓸 처지도 <br>못되면서 왈가왈부 <br>물어뜯으려고만 <br>핏불 인척 하지만 <br>위치는 엄마의 등골 <br>I'm chillin' not like you do <br>I'm chillin' not like you do <br>니가 뭘 아냐고 하냐고 <br>비웃고는 했지만 yeah <br>I'm still here not like you do <br>I'm feeling everything for life <br>That's why <br>여전히 난 내 멋대로 <br>I'm doing doing doing <br>and you and you and you and <br>Still doing doing doing <br>and you and you and you and <br>I'm doing doing doing <br>and you and you and you and <br>Still doing doing doing <br>이 친구는 월 30 <br>역시 나도 마찬가지 <br>저 사람은 아직 학생 <br>umm 그래 거기 까지 <br>비록 주머니는 <br>가난해도 우리의 대화는 <br>항상 높은 곳으로 <br>우릴 이끌고는 해 <br>더 큰 꿈을 갖게 돼 <br>이건 꽤나 짜릿해서 <br>멈출 수가 없네 <br>I'm doing doing doing <br>and you and you and you and <br>Still doing doing doing <br>and you and you and you and <br>I'm doing doing doing <br>and you and you and you and <br>Still doing doing doing <br>I'm doing doing doing <br>and you and you and you and <br>Still doing doing doing <br>and you and you and you and <br>I'm doing doing doing <br>and you and you and you and <br>Still doing doing doing <br>and you <br>]]></content><category term="타투 (TATU)" label="타투 (TATU)"/><category term="And You" label="And You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ragoon/이미/</id><title>Ragoon - 이미 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:42:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:42:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ragoon/%EC%9D%B4%EB%AF%B8/" title="Ragoon - 이미 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한 순간 니 연락이 없음 <br>불안해하는 <br>나를 숨겨도 또 언젠가는 <br>알게 되겠지 <br>나의 모든 시간 내겐 <br>특별함이 돼줘서 <br>화창한 거린 매일이 돼 <br>오늘 이 밤에 더욱 <br>네게 다가가고 싶게 <br>이젠 꿈이 아닌 <br>너를 잡고서 <br>그저 바라만 볼 수 있게 <br>넌 알걸 이미 내 안에 <br>아니라 해봐도 <br>이 모든 게 너 앞이면 <br>흐르듯 사라져 <br>내 맘은 이미 너의 <br>숨소리마저 담아 <br>그러니 오늘도 나에게 <br>달려와야만 해 <br>내일 아침이 더욱 <br>네게 가까워질 수 있게 <br>이젠 꿈이 아는 <br>너를 안고서 <br>그저 바라만 볼 수 있게 <br>넌 알걸 이미 내 안에 <br>아니라 해봐도 <br>이 모든 게 너 앞이면 <br>흐르듯 사라져 <br>내 맘은 이미 너의 <br>숨소리마저 담아 <br>그러니 오늘도 나에게 <br>달려와야만 해 <br>언제나 머뭇거리지만 <br>이젠 나에게 조금 더 <br>어디를 가도 난 <br>oh baby <br>너와 마주하길 원해 <br>그저 그렇게 <br>네게 입맞추고 싶어 <br>oh <br>넌 알걸 이미 내 안에 <br>아니라 해봐도 <br>이 모든 게 너 앞이면 <br>흐르듯 사라져 <br>내 맘은 이미 너의 <br>숨소리마저 담아 <br>그러니 오늘도 나에게 <br>달려와야만 해 <br>]]></content><category term="Ragoon" label="Ragoon"/><category term="이미" label="이미"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ragoon/Have_You_Been/</id><title>Ragoon - Have You Been - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:42:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:42:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ragoon/Have_You_Been/" title="Ragoon - Have You Been - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[따스한 햇살 시원한 <br>바람이 부는 거리 <br>널 처음 본 날 썬글라스에 <br>빛나는 머리 <br>카페에 커피 완벽한 분위기 <br>girl <br>천천히 조심스레 다가가 <br>조금은 어려워 내겐 <br>널 마주하는 것도 난 <br>도도한 너의 미소에 <br>빠져드는 나를 느껴 <br>솔직히 두려워 매번 <br>널 마주칠 때마다 난 <br>맘을 숨기는 것도 <br>그만하고 싶어 <br>천천히 <br>take it slow <br>나의 맘속으로 <br>Have you been girl <br>have you have you been girl <br>Baby your <br>오 나의 입술로 <br>Have you been girl <br>have you have you been girl <br>Black white <br>그 무엇도 잘 어울리는 듯해 <br>촉촉한 red lips도 <br>널 수놓은 것만 같애 <br>환상적인 your body line <br>다들 너만 봐 저 밖에 <br>Beautiful star <br>넌 내 안에 빛나는 것만 같애 <br>ma girl <br>조금은 걱정돼 내게 <br>널 곁에 두는 것도 난 <br>혹시나 하는 마음에 <br>약해지는 나를 느껴 <br>날 보는 눈빛에 매번 <br>괜한 생각할 때도 넌 <br>내게 입맞춰줘 <br>달콤한 입술로 baby <br>천천히 <br>take it slow <br>나의 맘속으로 <br>Have you been girl <br>have you have you been girl <br>Baby your <br>오 나의 입술로 <br>Have you been girl <br>have you have you been girl <br>좀더 가까이 내게 <br>숨소리가 들리게 <br>입술이 닿을 수 있게 <br>ma lady <br>no no no <br>please don't go go go go <br>아직은 천천히 <br>take it slow <br>천천히 <br>take it slow <br>나의 맘속으로 <br>Have you been girl <br>have you have you been girl <br>Baby your <br>오 나의 입술로 <br>Have you been girl <br>have you have you been girl <br>천천히 <br>take it slow <br>나의 맘속으로 <br>Have you been girl <br>have you have you been girl <br>Baby your <br>오 나의 입술로 <br>Have you been girl <br>have you have you been girl <br>]]></content><category term="Ragoon" label="Ragoon"/><category term="Have You Been" label="Have You Been"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ragoon/달아올라_Feat_Amillo/</id><title>Ragoon - 달아올라 (Feat. Amillo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:42:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:42:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ragoon/%EB%8B%AC%EC%95%84%EC%98%AC%EB%9D%BC_Feat_Amillo/" title="Ragoon - 달아올라 (Feat. Amillo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[매번 내 손을 잡을 때 <br>넌 깍지낀 다음 <br>한번 꽉잡는 <br>습관이 있어 girl <br>날 바라봐줄때도 <br>지그시 한번 감았다 <br>떴을때 또 키스해줘 <br>가끔 술에 취한 날 <br>또 전화하잖아 <br>오빠라고 불러대 <br>넌 나보다 위잖아 <br>그럴때면 난 <br>웃음 지어지잖아 <br>널 데려가 오늘 <br>우린 달아오르잖아 <br>달아올라 baby 달아올라 <br>침대위에서 아침까지 <br>나와 놀아 <br>아무도 몰라 baby <br>나와 all night <br>Oh baby wanna <br>get your mind <br>더 달아올라 <br>달아올라 순간 날아올라 <br>귓가에 울린 <br>니 숨결에 달아올라 <br>Baby 넌 계속 두들겨 <br>내 맘에 knock해 <br>들어와도 돼 <br>뭐 그리 급하게 들어와 <br>진정해 oh no 침착해 <br>낮져밤이야 넌 <br>한밤에 사바나 <br>달아오른 온도에 <br>쉽게 벗겨 너는 날 <br>물이 오를대로 올라 <br>너는 날 적신뒤 <br>오르락 내리락 <br>정신도 없이 <br>너의 움직임은 <br>내 입술을 더말려 <br>내가 말이라도 된듯 <br>부여잡고 달려 <br>날아올라 더 높이 <br>우린 쉴틈이 없지 <br>oh 많은걸 하긴 <br>너무 짧아 이 밤이 <br>달아올라 baby <br>달아올라 <br>오늘밤 여기 너와 나 <br>have a good night <br>So 편히쉬어 girl <br>다른건 신경꺼 <br>Oh baby wanna <br>get your mind <br>더 달아올라 <br>달아올라 girl <br>밤새 너와 나 <br>너의 몸 움직임에 <br>난 더 달아올라 <br>나만혼자 있는건 겁나 <br>너 없인 깊은밤에 <br>잠도 잘 못자 <br>넌 always so nice <br>뭐든지 골라 <br>니가 웃음질때까지 <br>계속 달아올라 <br>달아올라 baby 달아올라 <br>오늘밤 여기 너와 나 <br>have a good night <br>So 편히쉬어 girl <br>다른건 신경꺼 <br>Oh baby wanna <br>get your mind <br>더 달아올라 <br>달아올라 girl <br>밤새 너와 나 <br>너의 몸 움직임에 <br>난 더 달아올라 <br>달아올라 baby 달아올라 <br>침대위에서 아침까지 <br>나와 놀아 <br>아무도 몰라 baby <br>나와 all night <br>Oh baby wanna <br>get your mind <br>더 달아올라 <br>달아올라 순간 날아올라 <br>귓가에 울린 <br>니 숨결에 달아올라 <br>]]></content><category term="Ragoon" label="Ragoon"/><category term="달아올라 (Feat. Amillo)" label="달아올라 (Feat. Amillo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ragoon/내일하고_내일모레_Feat_Roydo/</id><title>Ragoon - 내일하고 내일모레 (Feat. Roydo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:42:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:42:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ragoon/%EB%82%B4%EC%9D%BC%ED%95%98%EA%B3%A0_%EB%82%B4%EC%9D%BC%EB%AA%A8%EB%A0%88_Feat_Roydo/" title="Ragoon - 내일하고 내일모레 (Feat. Roydo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너 혼자있을 땐 <br>내게 전화를 걸어 <br>나와 눈을 맞출땐 <br>천천히 다가와 girl <br>내게 미소지을 땐 <br>살며시 손을 올려 <br>내가 입을 맞출땐 <br>이미 니 맘을 다 알어 <br>눈을 감어 <br>수화기 속 너의 목소리 <br>오늘은 안될것 같아 우리 <br>내일밤엔 어때 baby <br>니가 나의 곁에 lady <br>좀더 서롤 알아가는것까지 <br>그래 그럼 <br>오늘 말고 내일 해 <br>뭐해 내일하고 내일 모레 <br>묻는 나의 눈빛에 <br>흔들리는 너를 보네 <br>It's gonna be ok <br>우리둘 아무도 몰래 몰래 <br>손내밀어 내손을 꽉잡아 girl <br>내일은 누구보다 꽉안아 널 <br>오늘은 안되겠지 <br>널 품안에 <br>사실 니 일정을 <br>난 전부 이미 알고 있었는데 <br>그게 속아주는건 <br>그리 어렵지 않은 걸 baby <br>그러니까 이것만 말을 해줘 <br>내일 넌 어때 woo wa <br>매력적인 너의 두눈이 <br>날 부르는 baby <br>너의 입술에 yeah <br>잠이 올때까지 baby <br>내 위에 올라타 girl lady <br>좀더 과격해지는것까지 <br>그래 그럼 오늘말고 내일 해 <br>뭐해 내일하고 내일 모레 <br>묻는 나의 눈빛에 <br>흔들리는 너를 보네 <br>It's gonna be ok <br>우리둘 아무도 몰래 몰래 <br>손내밀어 내손을 꽉잡아 girl <br>내일은 누구보다 꽉안아 널 <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah baby <br>더도 말고 매일 oh <br>그리고 내게로 오게 <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah baby <br>오늘 말고 내일 baby <br>그리고 내일 모레 <br>적당히 봐주기엔 <br>매력적이기는해 <br>날 깨우는 수화기속 <br>목소린 너무 섹시해 <br>오늘 말고 내일해 <br>더 외로워지지 않게 <br>더는 유혹하지말고 내일 봐 <br>그리고 내일 또 모레 <br>뭐해 내일하고 내일 모레 <br>묻는 나의 눈빛에 <br>흔들리는 너를 보네 <br>It's gonna be ok <br>우리둘 아무도 몰래 몰래 <br>손내밀어 내손을 꽉잡아 girl <br>내일은 누구보다 꽉안아 널 <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah baby <br>더도 말고 매일 oh <br>그리고 내게로 오게 <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah baby <br>오늘 말고 내일 baby <br>그리고 내일 모레 <br>]]></content><category term="Ragoon" label="Ragoon"/><category term="내일하고 내일모레 (Feat. Roydo)" label="내일하고 내일모레 (Feat. Roydo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ragoon/Up__Down/</id><title>Ragoon - Up &amp; Down - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:42:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:42:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ragoon/Up__Down/" title="Ragoon - Up &amp; Down - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루 종일 떠오르던 니 소식에 <br>인스타에 너의 사진에 또 흠칫해 <br>누구보다 빛나던 너의 눈동자에 <br>너의 눈물이 보여서 <br>It's alright <br>넌 나만의 uhhuh <br>넌 나만의 star <br>기다리기만 해 <br>너의 환히 웃는 모습 <br>It's alright <br>넌 나만의 uhhuh <br>넌 나만의 star <br>너의 귓가에 <br>밤새 속삭이고만 싶어 <br>I always you girl <br>내 손을 잡아 너 <br>니 눈 속에 내 입술에 <br>서롤 담았으면 해 <br>Always you girl <br>이 밤이 지날 땐 <br>니 맘속에 내 귓가엔 <br>서로를 속삭이게 <br>You go up and down <br>go up and down <br>up and down <br>아침이 올 때까지 <br>beautiful girl <br>You go up and down <br>go up and down <br>up and down <br>너와 헤엄치고 싶어 <br>Sweety girl <br>풀이 죽어있는 너의 모습에 <br>괜찮아 한잔하며 <br>잊어버려 오늘 밤이 더 길게 <br>잘했잖아 누구보다 빛나던 <br>니 눈동자에 <br>너의 눈물이 보여서 <br>It's alright <br>넌 나만의 uhhuh <br>넌 나만의 star <br>기다리기만 해 <br>너의 환히 웃는 모습 난 <br>넌 나만의 yeah <br>넌 나만의 star <br>너의 귓가에 <br>밤새 속삭이고만 싶어 <br>I always you girl <br>내 손을 잡아 너 <br>니 눈 속에 내 입술에 <br>서롤 담았으면 해 <br>Always you girl <br>이 밤이 지날 땐 <br>니 맘속에 내 귓가엔 <br>서로를 속삭이게 <br>춤을 춰 이 밤이 달아오르게 <br>꿈을 꿔 머리허리다리 <br>only that's mine <br>풀이 죽은 너의 카톡문자 <br>쌓인 stress <br>오늘 다 나랑 풀자 <br>모두가 모르고 있어 너의 진가 <br>pretty rap star <br>너만 진짜니까 <br>화려한 니 조던 미모가 물 오른 <br>이 밤 조명이 <br>good night this moment <br>I always you girl <br>내 손을 잡아 너 <br>니 눈 속에 내 입술에 <br>서롤 담았으면 해 <br>Always you girl <br>이 밤이 지날 땐 <br>니 맘속에 내 귓가엔 <br>서로를 속삭이게 <br>You go up and down <br>go up and down <br>up and down <br>아침이 올 때까지 <br>beautiful girl <br>You go up and down <br>go up and down <br>up and down <br>너와 헤엄치고 싶어 <br>]]></content><category term="Ragoon" label="Ragoon"/><category term="Up &amp; Down" label="Up &amp; Down"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/오늘도_힘들었지_/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 오늘도 힘들었지? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:43:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:43:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98%EB%8F%84_%ED%9E%98%EB%93%A4%EC%97%88%EC%A7%80_/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 오늘도 힘들었지? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 하루는 어땠나요 <br>상사가 염장을 지르진 않았나요 <br>오늘 하루도 수고했어요 <br>험난하고 고달픈 <br>일과를 잘 버텨줘서 <br>상사에게 올린 보고서 역시 <br>김과장은 내 이름을 지우고 있고 <br>술자리에선 팔랑귀 이대리 <br>부장한테 내 욕을 하고 있어 <br>이런 제길 거지같은 나의 하루 <br>시키면 시키는 대로 의 인생 <br>그래도 오늘 하루 잘 버텼어 <br>너무 기특해 소중한 나 <br>이런 제길 노예 같은 나의 하루 <br>까라면 까는 대로 의 인생 <br>그래도 오늘 하루 잘 견뎠어 <br>너무 훌륭해 소중한 나 <br>오늘 하루는 어땠나요 <br>회사에서 왕딸 <br>당하지는 않았나요 <br>오늘 하루도 수고했어요 <br>이 힘든 일을 꿋꿋이 잘 버텨줘서 <br>남들이 날 볼 땐 부러워해도 <br>속사정을 들여다보면 <br>알게 될 거야 <br>이 회사 일이 쉽지 만은 않다는 걸 <br>내가 쉽게 산다고 생각하지마 <br>이런 제길 거지같은 나의 하루 <br>시키면 시키는 대로 의 인생 <br>그래도 오늘 하루 잘 버텼어 <br>너무 기특해 소중한 나 <br>이런 제길 노예 같은 나의 하루 <br>까라면 까는 대로 의 인생 <br>그래도 오늘 하루 잘 견뎠어 <br>너무 훌륭해 소중한 나 <br>하루하루 회사 생활이 힘들어 <br>일 보단 사람 <br>상대하는 게 더 힘들어 <br>회사에 아무리 충성한다고 해도 <br>불투명한 나의 미래는 암울해 <br>그렇게 하루를 마무리 <br>아무리 애를 써도 느껴지는 건 <br>깊은 외로움 <br>늦게 퇴근 해도 <br>힘든 업무에도 더 힘든 건 외로움 <br>회식자리에 앉아있어도 괴로움 <br>오늘 하루도 수고했어 <br>비록 내일도 <br>힘든 하루가 되겠지만 <br>오늘 같이만 버티면 돼 <br>넌 잘 할 수 있으니까 <br>자 힘을 내고 <br>남은 오늘은 푹 쉬어 <br>모든걸 다 내려놓고 <br>모든 걸 다 잊고서 <br>기분 좋은 하루의 끝을 마무리 해 <br>이런 제길 거지같은 나의 하루 <br>시키면 시키는 대로 의 인생 <br>그래도 오늘 하루 잘 버텼어 <br>너무 기특해 소중한 나 <br>이런 제길 노예 같은 나의 하루 <br>까라면 까는 대로 의 인생 <br>그래도 오늘 하루 잘 견뎠어 <br>너무 훌륭해 소중한 나 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="오늘도 힘들었지?" label="오늘도 힘들었지?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/좋은아빠되기/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 좋은아빠되기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:43:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:43:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/%EC%A2%8B%EC%9D%80%EC%95%84%EB%B9%A0%EB%90%98%EA%B8%B0/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 좋은아빠되기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나에겐 10살짜리 <br>아들이 하나 있어 <br>커오는 동안 건강하게 자라줬어 <br>하지만 가끔 내가 <br>아빠로서 잘하고 있는지 <br>걱정이 될 때가 있어 <br>왜냐하면 난 아버지를 <br>본 적이 없기 때문이야 <br>내가 태어나고 한 달만에 <br>아버지는 돌아가셨어 <br>초등학교 시절에는 아버지가 <br>돌아가신 줄도 몰랐어 <br>그냥 외국에 계신 줄만 알았어 <br>모든 사람들이 <br>그렇게 나에게 얘기해 주었어 <br>그렇게 <br>비록 돈을 많이 벌지는 못해도 <br>그렇게 잘 나가지는 못해도 <br>많은 시간을 함께 <br>보내려고 노력하고 <br>비록 원하는걸 <br>다 갖게 해줄 순 없지만 <br>사달라는 장난감도 <br>다 사줄 순 없지만 <br>좋은 아빠가 되었으면 해 <br>그래서 아버지에 대한 롤모델이 <br>나는 없어 아들에게 <br>좋은 아빠가 되고픈데 <br>좋은 아빠가 무엇인지 <br>어떻게 되는 건지 <br>솔직히 나는 잘 모르겠어 <br>돈이 많은 아빠가 더 좋은 건지 <br>잘 놀아주는 아빠가 더 좋은 건지 <br>모두가 원하는 <br>그런 아빠가 되고 싶지만 <br>그건 불가능 한 것 같애 <br>아이가 원하는 대로 <br>아이가 하고 싶어 하는 대로 <br>마음껏 누리게 <br>해주고 싶지만 <br>그 모든 게 쉽지 않아 쉽지 않아 <br>그 모든 게 <br>비록 돈을 많이 벌지는 못해도 <br>그렇게 잘 나가지는 못해도 <br>많은 시간을 함께 <br>보내려고 노력하고 <br>비록 원하는걸 <br>다 갖게 해줄 순 없지만 <br>사달라는 장난감도 <br>다 사줄 순 없지만 <br>좋은 아빠가 되었으면 해 <br>아직 어린 아들에게 <br>그나마 해줄 수 있는 건 <br>건강히 오래 오래 <br>아들 곁을 지켜주는 일 <br>그리고 아들이 원하는 일을 <br>할 수 있도록 뒤에서 <br>묵묵히 백업해 주는 일 <br>비록 아버지에 대한 <br>롤 모델은 없지만 <br>아들에게 만은 좋은 아빠가 <br>될 수 있을 거야 <br>그렇게 믿어 믿어 <br>비록 돈을 많이 벌지는 못해도 <br>그렇게 잘 나가지는 못해도 <br>많은 시간을 함께 <br>보내려고 노력하고 <br>비록 원하는걸 <br>다 갖게 해줄 순 없지만 <br>사달라는 장난감도 <br>다 사줄 순 없지만 <br>좋은 아빠가 되었으면 해 <br>비록 돈을 많이 벌지는 못해도 <br>그렇게 잘 나가지는 못해도 <br>많은 시간을 함께 <br>보내려고 노력하고 <br>비록 원하는걸 <br>다 갖게 해줄 순 없지만 <br>사달라는 장난감도 <br>다 사줄 순 없지만 <br>좋은 아빠가 되었으면 해 <br>좋은 아빠가 되었으면 해 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="좋은아빠되기" label="좋은아빠되기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/가난하고_늙은_음악가/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 가난하고 늙은 음악가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:43:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:43:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/%EA%B0%80%EB%82%9C%ED%95%98%EA%B3%A0_%EB%8A%99%EC%9D%80_%EC%9D%8C%EC%95%85%EA%B0%80/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 가난하고 늙은 음악가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밖에 나가 내가 음악 한다고 하면 <br>사람들은 모두 와 하지 <br>그렇지만 나는 아직 못 뜬 음악가 <br>이걸로 들어오는 건 <br>저작권료 3만원 <br>생계 땜에 부업으로 가던 회사 <br>또 짤리게 생겼고 <br>앞으로 먹고 살일 <br>걱정하게 생겼고 <br>이 음악 때려 치고 <br>노가다를 해야 하나 <br>고민해야 하고 <br>다른 직장 알아보며 <br>잡코리아 사람인을 뒤져봐 <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>난 아직 할 수 있을 거라 믿는데 <br>왜 이리 나에게는 <br>기회가 안 오는지 <br>내 음악이 아이들의 <br>취향은 아니지만 <br>그래도 누군가는 듣지 않을까 <br>이렇게 한 달에 두 곡씩 <br>꾸준히 열심히 <br>작업해서 발표해도 <br>들어주는 사람이 없으면 <br>계속할 의미가 없어 <br>그래도 회사에 출근할 때 <br>버스 안에서도 가사는 뭘 쓸까 <br>고민하고 퇴근할 때 <br>어떤 음악을 만들까 계속 궁리해 <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>난 믿어 언젠간 나에게도 <br>기회가 올 거라고 HOPE <br>난 믿어 열심히 일하면 <br>나도 언젠간 뜰 거라고 <br>The Hope <br>나 같은 가난한 음악가가 <br>가질 수 있는 유일한 것 <br>The Hope <br>내가 지금 꿈꾸고 바라는 <br>Happy 한 미래 <br>가난하고 늙은 <br>음악가가 바라는 건 <br>Only My Music <br>많은 사람들에게 들려주고 <br>희망과 즐거움을 주는 것 <br>That’s my only HOPE <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>난 가난하고 늙은 음악가 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="가난하고 늙은 음악가" label="가난하고 늙은 음악가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/Go_Hard_어느_취준생의_하루/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - Go Hard (어느 취준생의 하루) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:43:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:43:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/Go_Hard_%EC%96%B4%EB%8A%90_%EC%B7%A8%EC%A4%80%EC%83%9D%EC%9D%98_%ED%95%98%EB%A3%A8/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - Go Hard (어느 취준생의 하루) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Go Hard <br>니가 더 단단해 질 때까지 <br>Go Hard <br>기다려 하루 하루 고통을 즐기며 <br>Go Hard <br>니가 더 좀 더 굳을 때까지 <br>기다려 꼭 연락이 올 테니 <br>오늘도 아침에 늦으막이 일어나 <br>컴퓨터를 키고 이메일을 확인해 <br>사람인 잡코리아 <br>사이트를 다니며 <br>갈 만한 회사 없나 찾기 시작해 <br>비록 내 스펙에 맞는 <br>회사는 보이지는 않지만 <br>혹시나 하는 마음으로 <br>저장해 놓은 이력서를 <br>하나 하나 보내보기 시작해 <br>Go Hard <br>니가 더 단단해 질 때까지 <br>Go Hard <br>기다려 하루 하루 고통을 즐기며 <br>Go Hard <br>니가 더 좀 더 굳을 때까지 <br>기다려 꼭 연락이 올 테니 <br>오늘도 안방에서 <br>들려오는 부모님의 <br>한숨 소리가 내 가슴을 흔들어 <br>이러쿵 저러쿵 <br>남의 얘기 듣지 말고 <br>너 할 일만 열심히 하라고 <br>항상 말씀은 하시지만 <br>아들 걱정이 <br>하늘 높은 건 나도 알아 알아 <br>하지만 아무리 뒤져 봐도 <br>갈 데는 없고 <br>보내는 곳 마다 연락은 없고 <br>Go Hard <br>니가 더 단단해 질 때까지 <br>Go Hard <br>기다려 하루 하루 고통을 즐기며 <br>Go Hard <br>니가 더 좀 더 굳을 때까지 <br>기다려 꼭 연락이 올 테니 <br>Go Hard <br>니가 더 단단해 질 때까지 <br>Go Hard <br>기다려 하루 하루 고통을 즐기며 <br>Go Hard <br>니가 더 좀 더 굳을 때까지 <br>기다려 꼭 연락이 올 테니 <br>슬슬 배고파지기 시작해 <br>밥 차려먹는 것도 <br>슬슬 눈치가 보여 <br>귀찮은데 라면이나 하나 먹을까 <br>치킨이나 하나 시켜 먹을까 <br>엄마한테 돈 달라고 <br>하긴 눈치가 보여 <br>찬장에 라면은 있나 <br>한번 찾아보자 <br>Go Hard <br>니가 더 단단해 질 때까지 <br>Go Hard <br>기다려 하루 하루 고통을 즐기며 <br>Go Hard <br>니가 더 좀 더 굳을 때까지 <br>기다려 꼭 연락이 올 테니 <br>대충 점심 차려먹고 나니 <br>어두 컴컴 남들은 하루 세끼 <br>나는 한끼로 버텨 <br>하는 일도 없는데 <br>왜 이렇게 졸린지 <br>제발 내일은 연락이 오길 <br>간절하게 기도해 <br>Go Hard <br>니가 더 단단해 질 때까지 <br>Go Hard <br>기다려 하루 하루 고통을 즐기며 <br>Go Hard <br>니가 더 좀 더 굳을 때까지 <br>기다려 꼭 연락이 올 테니 <br>Go Hard <br>니가 더 단단해 질 때까지 <br>Go Hard <br>기다려 하루 하루 고통을 즐기며 <br>Go Hard <br>니가 더 좀 더 굳을 때까지 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="Go Hard (어느 취준생의 하루)" label="Go Hard (어느 취준생의 하루)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/서울촌놈/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 서울촌놈 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:43:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:43:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/%EC%84%9C%EC%9A%B8%EC%B4%8C%EB%86%88/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 서울촌놈 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[회사에서 외국 바이어가 <br>서울에 왔는데 <br>상담미팅 끝나고 <br>나보고 관광 좀 시키래 <br>근데 이런 어떡하지 <br>나도 가본 곳이 없는데 <br>서울 시내에서 오래 <br>살았어도 남들만큼 몰라요 <br>헤이 난 서울 <br>촌놈이야 서울에서 <br>몇 십 년을 살아도 <br>그 흔한 서울 관광 <br>해본 적 없어 <br>서울 토박이면 뭐해 <br>이거 촌놈이 따로 없네 <br>사장님 한 말씀 <br>나에게 던지네 <br>아무리 가본 곳이 <br>없어도 서울 사람인데 <br>그것도 모르냐고 <br>남산타워 63빌딩 <br>경복궁 덕수궁 깔렸잖아 <br>인터넷이라도 뒤져서 <br>니가 알아서 잘 좀 해봐라 <br>헤이 난 서울 촌놈이야 <br>서울에서 몇 십 년을 살아도 <br>그 흔한 서울 관광 <br>해본 적 없어 <br>서울 토박이면 뭐해 <br>헤이 난 서울 촌놈이야 <br>서울에서 몇 십 년을 살아도 <br>그 흔한 서울 관광 <br>해본 적 없어 <br>서울 토박이면 뭐해 <br>그렇게 쉬우면 <br>사장님이 직접 해봐 <br>라고 얘기하고 <br>싶지만 현실은 <br>네 알겠습니다 <br>헤이 난 서울 촌놈이야 <br>서울에서 몇 십 년을 살아도 <br>그 흔한 서울 관광 <br>해본 적 없어 <br>서울 토박이면 뭐해 <br>헤이 난 서울 촌놈이야 <br>서울에서 몇 십 년을 살아도 <br>그 흔한 서울 관광 <br>해본 적 없어 <br>서울 토박이면 뭐해 <br>헤이 촌놈 헤이 촌놈 <br>헤이 촌놈 헤이 촌놈 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="서울촌놈" label="서울촌놈"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/사랑_노래/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 사랑 노래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:43:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:43:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 사랑 노래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘도 어제와 같이 <br>나는 또 잠들지 못해 <br>오래 전 내 핸드폰 속에 <br>사랑노래를 찾아본다 <br>어젯밤 니가 나에게 <br>무심코 던진 말이 <br>너무 아파서 혹시 <br>함께 듣던 그때 그 노래를 <br>다시 들어보면 <br>내맘이 괜찮아 질까 <br>그때로 시간을 되돌려 <br>그 사랑 노래를 너와 함께 <br>다시 들을 수 있을까 <br>함께 했던 추억 <br>지울 수 있을까 <br>이 노랠 들을 때 마다 <br>난 니가 항상 <br>생각이 날테니까 <br>그래 내가 인정 할께 <br>나도 좀 심했어 <br>그래도 넌 그럼 안돼 <br>매일 싸움도 지겨워 <br>어젯밤 니가 했던말 <br>더 이상 버티기는 <br>너무 힘들어 <br>너무 아려서 너무 지쳤어 <br>이제 그만 끝내자 <br>그때로 시간을 되돌려 <br>그 사랑 노래를 <br>너와 함께 <br>다시 들을 수 있을까 <br>함께 했던 추억 <br>지울 수 있을까 <br>이 노랠 들을 때 마다 <br>난 니가 항상 <br>생각이 날테니까 <br>저장된 그 노랠 <br>삭제해 버릴까 <br>아니면 전화길 <br>그냥 바꿔 버릴까 <br>그때로 시간을 되돌려 <br>그 사랑 노래를 <br>너와 함께 <br>다시 들을 수 있을까 <br>함께 했던 추억 <br>지울 수 있을까 <br>이 노랠 들을 때 마다 <br>난 니가 항상 <br>생각이 날테니까 <br>그때로 시간을 되돌려 <br>그 사랑 노래를 <br>너와 함께 <br>다시 들을 수 있을까 <br>함께 했던 추억 <br>지울 수 있을까 <br>이 노랠 들을 때 마다 <br>난 니가 항상 <br>생각이 날테니까 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="사랑 노래" label="사랑 노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/꿈을_적는다/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 꿈을 적는다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:43:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:43:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/%EA%BF%88%EC%9D%84_%EC%A0%81%EB%8A%94%EB%8B%A4/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 꿈을 적는다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아침에 눈을 뜨자마자 <br>하루 일과를 <br>생각하기 전에 <br>나의 꿈이 무엇이었는지 <br>생각하고 오늘 <br>하루를 시작해 <br>노래 가사에도 있지 <br>그렇게 꿈은 <br>말하는대로 <br>이루어진다고 <br>모든 꿈이 <br>이뤄질수 없겠지만 <br>그래도 이루게 <br>해달라 기도해 <br>이젠 하루 하루 조금씩 <br>나의 꿈이 이뤄진다 <br>매일 전화기 메모장에 <br>적어 논다 하나 둘씩 <br>하루 하루 버티는 <br>삶의 무게가 <br>너무 무거워 <br>그래도 희망을 <br>놓지 않는다 <br>버스에 앉아 <br>휴대폰을 꺼내 <br>메모장을 열어 <br>나의 꿈을 적어 <br>적어놓은 꿈들을 <br>매일 매일 바라보며 <br>그 꿈들이 <br>이루어질거라고 믿어 <br>1년 후가 될지 <br>10년 후가 될지 <br>아무도 모르지만 <br>그 꿈들만을 바라보며 <br>오늘 하루를 <br>열심히 버텨 견뎌 <br>오늘 하루를 <br>열심히 버텨 견뎌 <br>노래 가사에도 있지 <br>그렇게 꿈은 <br>말하는대로 <br>이루어진다고 <br>그렇게 말을 하고 <br>기도하고 적다보면 <br>보일거야 <br>꿈을 이룬 나를 <br>이젠 하루 하루 <br>조금씩 나의 꿈이 <br>이뤄진다 <br>매일 전화기 <br>메모장에 적어 논다 <br>하나 둘씩 <br>하루 하루 버티는 <br>삶의 무게가 <br>너무 무거워 <br>그래도 희망을 <br>놓지 않는다 <br>하지만 꿈을 적는다고 <br>하느님이 그걸 볼까 <br>그리고 그 꿈을 <br>이루어 주실까 <br>꿈을 말한다고 <br>누군가 그걸 듣고 <br>그 꿈을 이루도록 <br>도와줄까 <br>난 벤츠를 타고 싶어 <br>매일 호텔에서 좋은 음식을 <br>먹고 싶어 그렇게 <br>적기만 한다고 <br>그렇게 되면 <br>누구나 그렇게 하겠지 <br>인생은 터프해 <br>하루 하루 견디는 <br>삶의 무게조차 <br>무겁다고 느끼는데 <br>과연 생기는 의심들 <br>그렇지만 꿈을 적고 <br>매일 보면서 그꿈을 <br>이루기 위해 <br>노력하고 또 노력하면 <br>현실 적인 방법도 <br>생길것이고 <br>그 방법들을 하나하나 <br>실천 하면 언젠간 <br>이루어질거야 <br>절대 포기하지마 <br>이젠 하루 하루 <br>조금씩 나의 꿈이 <br>이뤄진다 <br>매일 전화기 <br>메모장에 적어 논다 <br>하나 둘씩 <br>하루 하루 버티는 <br>삶의 무게가 <br>너무 무거워 <br>그래도 희망을 <br>놓지 않는다 <br>이젠 하루 하루 <br>조금씩 나의 꿈이 <br>매일 전화기 <br>메모장에 적어 논다 <br>하루 하루 버티는 <br>삶의 무게가 <br>너무 무거워 <br>그래도 희망을 <br>놓지 않는다 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="꿈을 적는다" label="꿈을 적는다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/귀신스토리/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 귀신스토리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:43:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:43:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/%EA%B7%80%EC%8B%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EB%A6%AC/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 귀신스토리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오오오 오 나의 귀신스토리 <br>오오오 이젠 추억 <br>오오오 오 나의 귀신스토리 <br>오오오 무서운 기억 <br>아주 오래전 스튜디오 할때 <br>경숙이란 귀신이 살았어 <br>그 이름도 내가 지어준 이름 <br>그 이유는 남자를 좋아해서 <br>스튜디오 공사 후 <br>일 시작하자 마자 <br>그녀와의 만남은 <br>아주 깜짝 놀랐어 <br>내 뒤를 스치는 <br>오싹한 바람 그리고 <br>기름통을 걷어차는 <br>놀라운 그녀의 기술 <br>오오오 오 나의 귀신스토리 <br>오오오 이젠 추억 <br>오오오 오 나의 귀신스토리 <br>오오오 무서운 기억 <br>그 이후로 고사를 <br>지내봐도 <br>제사를 지내봐도 <br>사라지지 않는 그녀 <br>여자가 있을땐 <br>나타나지도 않아 <br>오로지 남자만을 <br>좋아했지 <br>스튜디오를 접을 때까지 <br>오픈 후 <br>5년 동안 남자들만 <br>있으면 언제나 <br>언제든 나타나 <br>날 놀래켰어 <br>혼자 있을때나 <br>여럿이 있을때나 <br>다양한 기술들을 보여줘 <br>오오오 오 나의 귀신스토리 <br>오오오 이젠 추억 <br>오오오 오 나의 귀신스토리 <br>오오오 무서운 기억 <br>자 이제부터 그녀의 <br>기술들을 들려줄께 <br>스튜디오 문열었다 닫기 <br>뒤에서 작업하는 <br>날 째려 보기 <br>돌아보면 스커트 <br>휘날리며 사라지기 <br>향 빨아 마시기 <br>그림 속 눈깜박이기 <br>물통 넘어뜨리기 <br>사람 밀치기 <br>발 보이며 왔다 <br>갔다 하기 <br>문밖에서 래디에이터 <br>두들기기 <br>이제는 내곁에서 <br>떠나가 달라고 <br>애원도 해봤지만 <br>절대로 떠날 <br>생각은 안해 <br>결국 나를 <br>문을 닫게 해 <br>오오오 오 나의 귀신스토리 <br>오오오 이젠 추억 오오오 <br>오 나의 귀신스토리 <br>오오오 무서운 기억 <br>오오오 오 나의 귀신스토리 <br>오오오 이젠 추억 오오오 <br>오 나의 귀신스토리 <br>오오오 무서운 기억 <br>이젠 더 이상 <br>기억하고 싶지 않아 <br>날 바라보던 <br>너의 그 모습 <br>너의 그 모습 <br>이젠 더 이상 <br>기억하고 싶지 않아 <br>날 바라보던 <br>너의 그 모습 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="귀신스토리" label="귀신스토리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/비_온_뒤/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 비 온 뒤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:44:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:44:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/%EB%B9%84_%EC%98%A8_%EB%92%A4/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 비 온 뒤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘은 시원한 <br>봄비가 내렸어 <br>늦봄의 쌓인먼지를 <br>씻어줬어 <br>하지만 난 아직 <br>힘든 날들을 <br>보내고 있어 아프고 <br>힘들 날들을 <br>비가 내린 후엔 <br>밝은 해가 뜨는 것 처럼 <br>나에게도 밝은 빛이 <br>비쳐주었으면 해 <br>어떻게 한 평생이 <br>이렇게 고될 수 있을까 <br>내게도 한번쯤은 <br>기회를 줄 수 있지 않을까 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 단단히 굳듯이 <br>나도 나도 더 <br>단단해 질거야 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 촉촉해 지듯이 <br>내 맘도 더 <br>촉촉해 질거야 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 단단히 굳듯이 <br>모든 고난 <br>다 지나갈거야 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 촉촉해 지듯이 <br>다 추억으로 남을거야 <br>오늘은 아침 <br>일찍 일어나 <br>밖으로 나가봤어 <br>그렇게 <br>맑아진 시야가 <br>나를 상쾌하게 해주었어 <br>답답한 내마음을 <br>비가 내린 후엔 <br>이렇게 따뜻한 것 처럼 <br>나도 그렇게 따뜻한 <br>날이 어서 왔으면 해 <br>이렇게 비가 온 뒤 <br>시야가 맑은 것 처럼 <br>나의 미래도 그렇게 <br>맑아 질 순 없을까 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 단단히 굳듯이 <br>너도 너도 더 <br>단단해 질거야 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 촉촉해 지듯이 <br>니 맘도 더 <br>촉촉해 질거야 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 단단히 굳듯이 <br>모든 고난 다 <br>지나갈거야 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 촉촉해 지듯이 <br>다 추억으로 남을거야 <br>내 인생에선 비가 <br>너무 많이 왔어 <br>먹구름도 너무 <br>많이 끼었었어 <br>아주 맑은 밝은 해가 <br>뜬적이 거의 <br>없었던 것 같아 <br>그렇게 내맘은 점점 <br>더 어두워져만 갔어 <br>아프기만 했어 <br>상처만 계속 커졌어 <br>나에게도 비 온 뒤 <br>뜨는 맑은 해 처럼 <br>빛이 비춰질 수 있을까 <br>그렇게 밝게 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 단단히 굳듯이 <br>너도 너도 더 <br>단단해 질거야 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 촉촉해 지듯이 <br>니 맘도 더 <br>촉촉해 질거야 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 단단히 굳듯이 <br>모든 고난 다 <br>지나갈거야 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 촉촉해 지듯이 <br>다 추억으로 남을거야 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 단단히 굳듯이 <br>너도 너도 더 <br>단단해 질거야 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 촉촉해 지듯이 <br>니 맘도 더 <br>촉촉해 질거야 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 단단히 굳듯이 <br>모든 고난 다 <br>지나갈거야 <br>비 온 뒤 땅이 <br>더 촉촉해 지듯이 <br>다 추억으로 남을거야 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="비 온 뒤" label="비 온 뒤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/마마/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 마마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:44:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:44:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/%EB%A7%88%EB%A7%88/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 마마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[엄마 나에요 <br>뭐라 말 좀 해봐요 <br>맨날 걱정만 <br>끼치던 막내에요 <br>엄마 이젠 너무 <br>늦은 거 같아요 <br>정말 미안해요 <br>이젠 후회 해봐도 <br>소용 없어요 <br>엄마가 예전 같아 <br>지실 순 없잖아요 <br>하지만 나도 <br>노력하고 있어요 <br>엄마가 건강해지면 <br>자랑스럽게 말이죠 <br>지금 내가 할 수 있는 건 <br>엄말 위해 기도하는 것 <br>언젠가 엄마가 <br>내게 말 한마디 해주길 <br>지금 내게 남아있는 건 <br>우리 가족들뿐이에요 <br>제발 손자라도 보고 <br>웃어주기를 기도해 <br>엄마 나에요 <br>이젠 눈 좀 떠봐요 <br>내게 할 말이 <br>있는 것 같아 보여 <br>엄마 이젠 너무 <br>늦은 건 아니겠죠 <br>제발 툴툴 <br>털고서 일어나요 <br>이젠 후회 해봐도 <br>소용 없어요 <br>다시 예전으로 <br>돌아갈 순 없잖아요 <br>하지만 나도 <br>열심히 살고 있어요 <br>엄마에게 자랑스러운 <br>아들이 되려고 말이죠 <br>지금 내가 할 수 있는 건 <br>엄말 위해 기도 하는 것 <br>언젠가 엄마가 내게 <br>말 한마디 해주길 <br>지금 내게 남아있는 건 <br>우리 가족들뿐이에요 <br>제발 손자라도 보고 <br>웃어주기를 기도해 <br>지난번 병원에 들렀을 때 <br>엄마가 날 바라보던 <br>그 눈빛은 <br>마치 무언가 하고 싶은 <br>이야기가 있는 것처럼 <br>보였었어 느꼈었어 <br>제발 엄마 하고 싶은 <br>이야기가 있다면 <br>맘속에 담아두지 마시고 <br>제발 이야기해요 <br>무엇이 엄마 맘을 <br>그렇게 아프게 했는지 <br>슬프게 했는지 <br>지금 내가 할 수 있는 건 <br>엄말 위해 기도하는 것 <br>언젠가 엄마가 내게 <br>말 한마디 해주길 <br>지금 내게 남아있는 건 <br>우리 가족들뿐이에요 <br>제발 손자라도 보고 <br>웃어주기를 기도해 <br>엄마 나도 <br>그동안 엄마를 <br>행복하게 하지 <br>못한 거 잘 알아요 <br>하지만 나도 <br>열심히 살아왔고 <br>최선을 다했어요 <br>하지만 일이 <br>뜻대로 잘 안됐어요 <br>전생에 내가 뭘 <br>그리 잘못했는지 <br>하는 일마다 잘 안 되는 걸 <br>그렇지만 포기하지 않아요 <br>아직 기회가 있다고 믿어요 <br>엄마 그때까지만 <br>버텨줘요 제발 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="마마" label="마마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/Good_Day_굿_데이/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - Good Day! (굿 데이) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:44:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:44:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/Good_Day_%EA%B5%BF_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - Good Day! (굿 데이) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어둡고 힘든 <br>고단한 길을 걸어왔어 <br>하는 일마다 <br>벽에 부딪쳤었지 <br>하지만 그때마다 <br>내 곁엔 가족 있어 <br>항상 날 믿어주고 <br>힘이 돼주는 <br>조금은 느리지만 <br>건강한 아들과 <br>내 곁을 버텨주는 와이프 <br>또 다른 힘든 일이 <br>많이 있겠지만 <br>함께라면 <br>이겨 낼 수 있을 거야 <br>우린 잘 해낼 수 있어 <br>그 동안 그래 왔듯이 <br>앞만 보고 나아가면 <br>밝은 미래가 우릴 기다려 <br>우린 잘해 낼 수 있어 <br>비록 힘든 시간이라도 <br>함께 이겨 내면 <br>나에게도 좋은 날이 오겠지 <br>조금은 느리지만 <br>건강한 아들과 <br>내 곁을 버텨주는 와이프 <br>또 다른 힘든 일이 <br>많이 있겠지만 <br>함께라면 <br>이겨 낼 수 있을 거야 <br>우린 잘 해낼 수 있어 <br>그 동안 그래 왔듯이 <br>앞만 보고 나아가면 <br>밝은 미래가 우릴 기다려 <br>우린 잘 해낼 수 있어 <br>비록 힘든 시간이라도 <br>함께 이겨 내면 <br>나에게도 좋은 날이 오겠지 <br>우린 잘 해낼 수 있어 <br>그 동안 그래 왔듯이 <br>앞만 보고 나아가면 <br>밝은 미래가 우릴 기다려 <br>우린 잘 해낼 수 있어 <br>비록 힘든 시간이라도 <br>함께 이겨 내면 <br>나에게도 좋은 날이 오겠지 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="Good Day! (굿 데이)" label="Good Day! (굿 데이)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/Hey_Smokers/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - Hey Smokers - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:44:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:44:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/Hey_Smokers/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - Hey Smokers - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[헤이 스모커즈 <br>금연 건물 인데도 <br>왜 자꾸 담밸 피는지 <br>이해를 할 수 없어 <br>헤이 스모커즈 아무리 <br>자기 집이래도 <br>담배냄새가 안 난다고 <br>생각은 하지 마요 <br>덕트를 통해 들어오는 <br>너의 담배냄새 <br>역겨워 역겨워 <br>넌 모르겠지 흡연자니까 <br>입장을 한번 바꿔봐 <br>시도 때도 없이 <br>슬금슬금 흘러 들어오는 <br>고약한 너의 담배냄새 <br>길거릴 걸어 다니면서 <br>담배 냄샐 풍기고 <br>다니는 운전 중 <br>차 창문 내리고 꽁초를 <br>함부로 버리는 <br>담배를 피우고 거리에서 <br>가래침 뱉어 버리는 <br>꼴 보기 싫은 <br>이런 사람들 <br>내 노랠 잘 들어봐 <br>이봐 헤이 스모커즈 <br>제발 남 좀 배려해줘 <br>이봐 헤이 스모커즈 담배 <br>안 피우는 사람들 <br>어떻게 하라고 <br>이봐 헤이 스모커즈 <br>왜 니 생각들만 하는지 <br>이봐 헤이 스모커즈 <br>괴로워 괴로워 <br>담배 냄새가 참기가 괴로워 <br>헤이 스모커즈 <br>아침에 나가자 마자 <br>제일 먼저 맡는 냄새 <br>너의 담배 냄새 <br>헤이 스모커즈 <br>밖에서 피는 것까지 <br>뭐라 할 순 없지만 <br>이것만 은 알아줘 좀 <br>아이가 학교 가는 <br>등교길 앞에서 <br>담배를 피우는 <br>너의 모습 흉한 모습 <br>꼭 그 앞에서 그렇게 <br>연기를 뿜어야 하는지 <br>니 아이 앞에서도 <br>그럴 수 있는지 궁금해 <br>길거릴 걸어 다니면서 <br>담배 냄샐 풍기고 <br>다니는 운전 중 <br>차 창문 내리고 <br>꽁초를 함부로 버리는 <br>담배를 피우고 거리에서 <br>가래침 뱉어 버리는 <br>꼴 보기 싫은 이런 사람들 <br>내 노랠 잘 들어봐 <br>이봐 헤이 스모커즈 <br>제발 남 좀 배려해줘 <br>이봐 헤이 스모커즈 담배 <br>안 피우는 사람들 <br>어떻게 하라고 <br>이봐 헤이 스모커즈 <br>왜 니 생각들만 하는지 <br>이봐 헤이 스모커즈 <br>괴로워 괴로워 <br>담배 냄새가 참기가 괴로워 <br>이봐 헤이 스모커즈 <br>제발 남 좀 배려해줘 <br>이봐 헤이 스모커즈 담배 <br>안 피우는 사람들 <br>어떻게 하라고 <br>이봐 헤이 스모커즈 <br>왜 니 생각들만 하는지 <br>이봐 헤이 스모커즈 <br>괴로워 괴로워 <br>복도에서 마주친 버려진 <br>너의 담배꽁초 경비실에 <br>계속된 경고에도 계속 피우는 <br>너의 꿋꿋함 <br>너의 눈엔 이게 보이지 않니 <br>꽁초라도 줍던가 <br>어제 엘리베이터 에서도 <br>담배 냄새가 나던데 쿨럭 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="Hey Smokers" label="Hey Smokers"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/Imymemine_두번째_인생/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - Imymemine (두번째 인생) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:44:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:44:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/Imymemine_%EB%91%90%EB%B2%88%EC%A7%B8_%EC%9D%B8%EC%83%9D/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - Imymemine (두번째 인생) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 음악을 관둔 지 <br>13년만에 음악을 <br>다시 시작했어 <br>그렇지만 1년동안 <br>감 못 잡아 하는 내내 <br>나는 완전 헤맸어 <br>이제 그럭저럭 감 잡았어 <br>아니 내 갈 길의 <br>방향을 잡았어 <br>그렇다고 내가 <br>대박 작곡가는 아냐 <br>초반에는 후배들이 <br>도와줬어 가끔 가다 <br>곡 의뢰가 들어왔어 <br>남의 음악 만드는 게 <br>너무 힘들어 장난이 아니야 <br>계속되는 빠꾸 <br>이젠 너무 지쳐 <br>히트곡 만든 거 <br>이젠 포기했어 <br>그냥 내가 하고 싶은 거 <br>하기로 해 <br>디스토션49 <br>나의 두 번째 인생이 시작 됐어 <br>IMYMEMINE IMYMEMINE <br>이제는 행복한 미래만 기다릴 뿐 <br>IMYMEMINE IMYMEMINE <br>노래는 내가 대출 불러 <br>내 노래에 자신 별로 없어 <br>하지만 내 노래를 불러 줄 <br>가수도 없어 <br>잘 나가지 않아 <br>랩도 그냥 해 Of course <br>난 랩퍼가 아니니까 <br>내가 하는 랩 가지고 <br>토 달지만 뭐라 하지마 <br>그냥 할 사람이 없어서 <br>내가 하는 거야 <br>내 음악이니까 <br>오래 전 같이 하던 후배들은 <br>이미 머리가 컸어 <br>내 노래에 랩을 해 줄 <br>애들도 없어 <br>이젠 돈이 없으면 <br>랩퍼도 못 구해 그냥 내가 해 <br>잘 하든 못 하든 싫든 좋든 <br>색안경을 벗고 들어 <br>이게 나의 뮤직 이게 나의 휴식 <br>I'm too old for this <br>나의 두 번째 인생이 시작 됐어 <br>IMYMEMINE IMYMEMINE <br>이제는 행복한 미래만 기다릴 뿐 <br>IMYMEMINE IMYMEMINE <br>디스토션49 나만의 DIY <br>세션비 없어 헬퍼도 없어 <br>죽을 만큼 힘들어도 <br>이러고 노는 게 <br>나의 유일한 휴식처 <br>이렇게 매월 작업하고 <br>녹음하고 하던 대로 <br>하루하루 하다 보면 <br>언젠간 크레딧 쌓이고 <br>들어주는 사람도 생기겠지 <br>조만간 생기겠지 <br>어차피 다시 시작했어 <br>나의 뮤직라이프 <br>나의 세컨드 라이프 <br>어차피 다시 시작된 거 <br>이걸로 랩하는 애들한테 <br>곡이나 줬으면 좋겠네 <br>나의 두 번째 인생이 시작 됐어 <br>IMYMEMINE IMYMEMINE <br>이제는 행복한 미래만 기다릴 뿐 <br>IMYMEMINE IMYMEMINE <br>내 노래를 하면서 <br>직접 랩과 노랠 하면서 <br>마음만은 꽉 찬 듯 <br>뿌듯하겠지만 <br>남겨진 건 현실뿐 <br>하지만 안정적인 미래와 <br>사랑하는 가족이 <br>항상 곁에 있어 <br>무엇이 두려워 <br>어차피 이렇게 <br>음악을 내는 것도 <br>밝은 미래를 위해 <br>가족을 위해 <br>지금은 하루 하루가 <br>힘들지만 내일을 바라보며 <br>내년을 바라보며 다시 <br>돌아갈 그날을 위해 <br>Let's go Distortion49 <br>나의 두 번째 인생이 시작 됐어 <br>IMYMEMINE IMYMEMINE <br>이제는 행복한 미래만 기다릴 뿐 <br>IMYMEMINE IMYMEMINE <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="Imymemine (두번째 인생)" label="Imymemine (두번째 인생)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/또_한해가_우울하게_지나간다/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 또 한해가 우울하게 지나간다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:44:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:44:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/%EB%98%90_%ED%95%9C%ED%95%B4%EA%B0%80_%EC%9A%B0%EC%9A%B8%ED%95%98%EA%B2%8C_%EC%A7%80%EB%82%98%EA%B0%84%EB%8B%A4/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 또 한해가 우울하게 지나간다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우연히 쳐다본 달력 한 장 찢어 <br>종이비행기 접어 날려 <br>벌써 한 장 밖에 남지 않았는데 <br>올해는 이뤄놓은 것도 없이 <br>하루 하루 버텨 <br>이렇게 또 한 살을 먹는구나 <br>애는 점점 더 커져만 가는구나 <br>돈은 점점 더 들어 만 가고 <br>빚은 계속 늘어만 가고 <br>생활은 계속 힘들어지고 <br>너무 너무 가슴이 답답해서 <br>점 집을 찾아갔어 <br>없는 살림에 복비까지 챙겨주며 <br>내 미래를 물어봤어 <br>점장이 말로는 <br>내 인생의 말로는 <br>내년부터 너무 너무 좋아지고 <br>85세까지 운이 좋다고 <br>말을 했어 <br>또 한 해가 우울하게 지나간다 <br>과연 내년 말에는 웃을 수 있을까 <br>또 한 해가 우울하게 지나간다 <br>과연 내년에는 행복할 수 있을까 <br>난 오늘도 버릇처럼 <br>작업실에 처박혀 <br>노랠 만들고 있어 <br>근데 왜 난 이렇게 <br>우울한 노래만 쓸까 <br>인생은 노래 가사처럼 된다던데 <br>미래는 노래 제목처럼 된다던데 <br>좀 더 행복한 노래를 <br>써야 되지 않을까 <br>나도 한번 해볼까 아니 해야지 <br>근데 이미 나이는 너무 먹어 <br>젊은 애들처럼 <br>사랑노랠 하긴 글렀고 <br>그래도 아니 억지로라도 <br>한번 써볼까 <br>손이 오그라들어 쪼글 쪼글 <br>사랑 노래 아니면 히트는 불가능 <br>차트 안에 있기만 해도 <br>난 성공가능 <br>하루에도 나오는 수십 개의 음원 <br>내년엔 그게 가능할 지 <br>점장이 말대로 잘은 될지 <br>또 한 해가 우울하게 지나간다 <br>과연 내년 말에는 웃을 수 있을까 <br>또 한 해가 우울하게 지나간다 <br>과연 내년에는 행복할 수 있을까 <br>또 한 해가 우울하게 지나간다 <br>과연 내년 말에는 웃을 수 있을까 <br>또 한 해가 우울하게 지나간다 <br>과연 내년에는 행복할 수 있을까 <br>어차피 지금 할 수 있는 건 <br>노력하는 것 희망을 갖는 것 <br>어차피 지금 할 수 있는 건 <br>노력하는 것 희망을 갖는 것 <br>또 한 해가 우울하게 지나간다 <br>과연 내년 말에는 웃을 수 있을까 <br>또 한 해가 우울하게 지나간다 <br>과연 내년에는 행복할 수 있을까 <br>또 한 해가 우울하게 지나간다 <br>과연 내년 말에는 웃을 수 있을까 <br>또 한 해가 우울하게 지나간다 <br>과연 내년에는 행복할 수 있을까 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="또 한해가 우울하게 지나간다" label="또 한해가 우울하게 지나간다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/헤진_천_가방/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 헤진 천 가방 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:44:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:44:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/%ED%97%A4%EC%A7%84_%EC%B2%9C_%EA%B0%80%EB%B0%A9/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 헤진 천 가방 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[정말 오랜만에 당신과 함께 <br>나서는 외출이었어 <br>근데 내 눈에 띈 당신의 가방 <br>오래된 헤진 천가방 <br>남들 다 갖는 그 흔한 명품도 <br>하나 없는 당신을 보며 <br>내가 그 동안 뭘 하고 살았는지 <br>후회가 됐어 <br>마음이 아팠어 <br>가슴속엔 눈물이 났어 <br>당신을 이렇게 만든 날 용서해 <br>같이 사는 동안 <br>가방 하나 사주지 못한 <br>능력 없는 남편을 용서해줘 <br>여보 미안해요 고생시켜서 <br>앞으로 좋은 날이 곧 올 거에요 <br>가방 하나 반지 하나 못해줬지만 <br>내가 더 잘할게요 <br>당신과 함께 한지도 벌써 15년 <br>당신한테 한 약속들도 못 지켰어 <br>그렇게 참고 살아준 당신 고마워 <br>그렇게 힘든 나날을 보내게 해서 <br>미안해 <br>마음이 아팠어 <br>가슴속엔 눈물이 났어 <br>당신을 이렇게 만든 날 용서해 <br>같이 사는 동안 <br>가방 하나 사주지 못한 <br>능력 없는 남편을 용서해줘 <br>여보 미안해요 고생시켜서 <br>앞으로 좋은 날이 곧 올 거에요 <br>가방 하나 반지 하나 못해줬지만 <br>내가 더 잘할게요 <br>여보 미안해요 고생시켜서 <br>앞으로 좋은 날이 곧 올 거에요 <br>가방 하나 반지 하나 못해줬지만 <br>내가 더 잘할게요 더 사랑할게요 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="헤진 천 가방" label="헤진 천 가방"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_디스토션49/새해_복_많이_받으세요/</id><title>Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 새해 복 많이 받으세요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:44:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:44:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Distortion49_%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A0%EC%85%9849/%EC%83%88%ED%95%B4_%EB%B3%B5_%EB%A7%8E%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B0%9B%EC%9C%BC%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94/" title="Distortion49 (디스토션49) - 새해 복 많이 받으세요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새해 복 많이 받으세요 <br>해피 뉴 이어 해피 뉴 이어 <br>내년엔 더 나아질 거에요 <br>그렇게 기대해요 기대해요 <br>올해도 힘든 한 해를 보내셨죠 <br>자영업 하는 분들 <br>월세 내기도 빠듯해 <br>아르바이트 직원들은 <br>사고치고 잠수 타고 <br>신용카드 수수료 내고 나면 <br>남는 것도 없어요 <br>한달 한달 갈수록 떨어지는 매출 <br>달달이 들어가는 애들 학원비에 <br>와이프는 한숨 쉬고 <br>매달 매달 빠져나가는 자동이체 <br>통장잔고 숫자 단위가 <br>하루 사이 바뀌네 <br>새해 복 많이 받으세요 <br>해피 뉴 이어 해피 뉴 이어 <br>작년 보다 나쁘진 않겠죠 <br>올해도 힘을 내요 <br>힘을 내요 해피 뉴 이어 <br>새해 복 많이 받으세요 <br>해피 뉴 이어 해피 뉴 이어 <br>내년엔 더 나아질 거에요 <br>그렇게 기대해요 기대해요 <br>올해도 힘든 한 해를 보내셨죠 <br>직장인 여러분들 <br>언제 짤릴지 불안해 <br>상사들은 내가 맘에 안 들어 <br>오늘도 깨져 쥐꼬리 만한 월급에 <br>시키는 일은 산더미 <br>기획서 백날 올려봐야 <br>퇴짜가 대부분 <br>공은 니 꺼 잘못은 내 꺼 <br>숫자로 보여주는 회사매출 <br>오늘도 내 거래처로 <br>발에 땀나도록 뛰어 <br>이래도 뭐라 하면 나도 열 받아 <br>이젠 사표 써야지 뭐 <br>새해 복 많이 받으세요 <br>해피 뉴 이어 해피 뉴 이어 <br>작년 보다 나쁘진 않겠죠 <br>올해도 힘을 내요 <br>힘을 내요 해피 뉴 이어 <br>새해 복 많이 받으세요 <br>해피 뉴 이어 해피 뉴 이어 <br>내년엔 더 나아질 거에요 <br>그렇게 기대해요 기대해요 <br>올해도 힘든 한 해를 보내셨죠 <br>취준생 여러분들 <br>이제는 취직 되려나 <br>대학 가면 모든 것이 <br>전부 될 줄 알고 <br>고등학교 3년을 죽도록 공부해 <br>그렇지만 대학은 <br>모든 것을 해결해 주지는 않아 <br>어학연수 각종 자격증 <br>나대로 스펙은 쌓아야 해 <br>오늘도 눈치 보여 <br>학교 도서관에 나가 <br>한자라도 더 읽어야지 <br>나의 취직은 언제 되려나 <br>새해 복 많이 받으세요 <br>해피 뉴 이어 해피 뉴 이어 <br>작년 보다 나쁘진 않겠죠 <br>올해도 힘을 내요 <br>힘을 내요 해피 뉴 이어 <br>새해 복 많이 받으세요 <br>내년엔 더 나아 질 거에요 <br>새해 복 많이 받으세요 <br>내년엔 더 나아 질 거에요 <br>]]></content><category term="Distortion49 (디스토션49)" label="Distortion49 (디스토션49)"/><category term="새해 복 많이 받으세요" label="새해 복 많이 받으세요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이데이_HEYDAY/그리워_Feat_용현_of_조이어클락/</id><title>헤이데이 (HEYDAY) - 그리워 (Feat. 용현 of 조이어클락) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:44:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:44:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4_HEYDAY/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9B%8C_Feat_%EC%9A%A9%ED%98%84_of_%EC%A1%B0%EC%9D%B4%EC%96%B4%ED%81%B4%EB%9D%BD/" title="헤이데이 (HEYDAY) - 그리워 (Feat. 용현 of 조이어클락) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[처음 널 만났던 <br>유난히 춥던 날 <br>함께였던 너와 나 <br>내 무력했었던 젊음 <br>너로 채워왔던 날들 <br>불어오는 구나 <br>내 맘 녹여주던 <br>네 따스한 온기 손길 <br>날 바라봐주던 유일했던 눈 <br>그렇게 버텨온 시절 그 계절 <br>그리워 널 내 품에 안고서 <br>늘 바라봤던 하늘 <br>떨리던 입맞춤까지 <br>그 아련한 추억들 <br>저기 네가 보여 <br>차갑게 뱉은 말 <br>애써 외면하려 떨군 <br>꼭 다문 입술에 고인 <br>그땐 보이지 않았던 <br>너의 눈물이 또 다시 흘러 <br>미안해 널 내 품에 안고서 <br>늘 다짐했던 말들 지키지 못했어 <br>눈 부시던 너를 <br>돌아갈 수 없는 이길 끝에서 <br>날 빛나게 해주던 너를 떠올려 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이데이 (HEYDAY)" label="헤이데이 (HEYDAY)"/><category term="그리워 (Feat. 용현 of 조이어클락)" label="그리워 (Feat. 용현 of 조이어클락)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zane_Smith/Black_Thoughts_Andale/</id><title>Zane Smith - Black Thoughts (Andale) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:45:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:45:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zane_Smith/Black_Thoughts_Andale/" title="Zane Smith - Black Thoughts (Andale) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let's get it in, see I been on my grind <br>Clocking like it's 9 5 keeping tabs and clocking time <br>If I waste it then it's fine cause it's mine <br>I admit it, I be lying in the bed <br>Daydreaming of dying <br>Fanaticizing bout islands <br>Take a trip to Heaven <br>It's life that I been dreading <br>Which direction am I headed <br>Will I live up to my parents expectations <br>Or surpass em' <br>Die young or outlast em' <br>I don't really have no passions <br>Living my life in fractions <br>With me it's all or nothing <br>Some might say I be bugging <br>I'm all in, if I wanna, when I wanna <br>Hysterical laugh <br>Man this shit crazy <br><br>I ain't never played with money <br>I ain't never played at all <br>Matter fact I'm hungry, that's a scratch I can't itch <br>I want a bad bitch, lettuce, chees lots of chips <br>Pasta, broccoli, and lots of dip <br>Most people in this world want lots of it <br>But it still won't make you shit <br>andale andale <br>I'm ready to start this race, get in yo place <br>Imma set my pace, it's more like a marathon <br>I'm running but I don't know where I'm going <br>No clue when I'm done <br>We weren't born just to rake funds, I wanna have fun <br>Everybody else yelling out run Run <br>andale andale <br>I got no time to waste <br>I got no time to play <br>andale andale <br><br>andale andale <br>I got no time to waste <br>I got no time to play <br>andale andale <br>I got no time to waste <br>I got no time to play <br>andale andale <br>I got no time to waste <br>I got no time to play <br>andale andale <br>I got no time to waste <br>I got no time to play <br>andale andale <br>I got no time to waste <br>I got no time to play <br><br>People look at me and see the stuff I don't see <br>Surrounding me and drowning me in prophecies as if I shared philosophies <br>In each other people see the qualities they wished they possessed <br>I too am a victim of neglecting myself <br>People compliment without hesitation <br>My first thought, people be hating <br>People be faking, hating, but I don't know <br>I'm my own best friend and worst enemy <br>Sometimes I tell myself I ain't shit <br>I have to constantly remind myself I am somebody <br>It's not always where you are but where you wanna be <br>Even when you get there happiness isn't guaranteed <br>Between you and me, this ain't at all how I expected life to be <br>I truly wanna be free <br>Sometimes I wanna fly, but I can't spread my wings <br>Held back by a couple things <br>There's a lot I don't have <br>A lot I want <br>But there's a lot I already have <br>I should be thankful <br>I'm blessed <br>Thank God]]></content><category term="Zane Smith" label="Zane Smith"/><category term="Black Thoughts (Andale)" label="Black Thoughts (Andale)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zane_Smith/Black_Women_All_I_Need/</id><title>Zane Smith - Black Women (All I Need) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:45:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:45:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zane_Smith/Black_Women_All_I_Need/" title="Zane Smith - Black Women (All I Need) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All I All I All I All I <br>All I need All I need All I need <br><br>All I need in my life is forty acres and some chickens <br>A nice size house and some thick black women <br>All I need in my life is forty acres and some chickens <br>A nice size house and some thick black women <br><br>Every man thinks, not every man speaks <br>Unbalanced society, strong prey on the weak <br>Hard to defeat, the struggles of this world <br>Between money, power, and big booty girls <br>Vanity, insanity, plan for me I don't know though <br>Bread is nice, but life is not about the dough ho' <br>Imma simple man, just get me some land <br>Couple hunnid grand, every woman need a man <br>Vice versa <br>No model, no commercial <br>Ain't nothing wrong with some meat up on them bones <br>Just give me the word and baby I'm coming home <br>Tired of being lone <br>Need a goddess on the throne <br>Backbone, spare a rib, Got a crib, couple kids <br>Blowing kisses to the misses <br>She ain't doing dishes cause she out here tryna get it <br>We both got dreams <br>I only ask her to believe as I'm painting vivid scenes <br>Walking hand in hand, life ain't always how you plan <br>Stup up, be a man <br>Willing able, I just wanna be stable <br>I want beauty and brains, not a charm on my arm <br>Keeping me calm, keeping me warm <br>Knows where I'm from <br>Supports where I'm going <br>That's all I really want <br><br>All I need in my life is forty acres and some chickens <br>A nice size house and some thick black women <br>All I need in my life is forty acres and some chickens <br>A nice size house and some thick black women]]></content><category term="Zane Smith" label="Zane Smith"/><category term="Black Women (All I Need)" label="Black Women (All I Need)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zane_Smith/Black_Wealth_Riches/</id><title>Zane Smith - Black Wealth (Riches) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:45:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:45:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zane_Smith/Black_Wealth_Riches/" title="Zane Smith - Black Wealth (Riches) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Since a youngin' I wanted to get rich <br>Since a youngin' I wanted to get rich <br><br>Since a youngin' I wanted to get rich <br>If it don't make dollars, it don't make sense <br>But they never told me this <br>All the money in this world won't make me SHIT <br>Since a youngin' I wanted to get rich <br>If it don't make dollars, it don't make sense <br>But they never told me this <br>All the money in this world won't make me SHIT <br><br>Ain't shit with it, ain't shit without it <br>Thought you was the man, bullshit, yeah I doubt it <br>Don't know what ya heard, but they got your vision cloudy <br>It don't even matter if you stack it up like mountains <br>It's levels to this shit, can't afford this <br>Got some more bread, got a bad bitch <br>Sucking on a million dollar dick <br>Got them lips, got them hips <br>Foreign chick, foreign whip <br>Everything high class, upgrade kits <br>Get Gallardo and a grotto <br>Wife too old, better go and get a model <br>Mae it rain today, the sun come out tomorrow <br>Chapter five, why possessions get glorified <br>That false pride, they really empty on the inside <br>I'm still alive but I been dead <br>The shit in my head is so pretty <br>This world is ugly <br>I ain't from it but I been corrupted <br><br>Since a youngin' I wanted to get rich <br>If it don't make dollars, it don't make sense <br>But they never told me this <br>All the money in this world won't make me SHIT <br>Since a youngin' I wanted to get rich <br>If it don't make dollars, it don't make sense <br>But they never told me this <br>All the money in this world won't make me SHIT <br><br>We got dreams, so they sell us hope <br>Where the cash at Robbing all these folks <br>Guess I'm gradually, facing reality <br>I'm a black man, living in man made culture <br>Seeing hella rats, cats, snakes, and the vultures <br>A little bit of this, want a little bit of that <br>Got what you wanted and the thirst comes back <br>Distraction, I'm talking temporary satisfaction <br>What's my passion <br>Let me examine my situation <br>I said motha fuck an occupation <br>Someday imam chill in the shade with the lemonade <br>Never have to worry bout each day, cause I don't care <br>Mamma always said that life ain't fair <br>Pearly white teeth talking show and tell <br>Smiling for the camera that's fake as Hell <br>Another spell, another lie, that you tell <br>It ain't all good, it ain't all bad <br>No matter what you have <br>Money won't solve yo problems <br>Still be drama whether rich or poor <br>Ion even wanna feel pain no more <br>Been waiting for a knock up on my door <br>Know you hear me Lord <br>Please don't ignore <br>What am I here for <br><br>Since a youngin' I wanted to get rich <br>If it don't make dollars, it don't make sense <br>But they never told me this <br>All the money in this world won't make me SHIT <br><br>Since a youngin' I wanted to get rich <br>If it don't make dollars, it don't make sense <br>But they never told me this <br>All the money in this world won't make YOU SHIT <br><br>You still ain't shit You still ain't shit You still ain't shit <br>You still ain't shit You still ain't shit You still ain't shit <br>You still ain't shit You still ain't shit <br>Stupid bitch]]></content><category term="Zane Smith" label="Zane Smith"/><category term="Black Wealth (Riches)" label="Black Wealth (Riches)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zane_Smith/Black_Dollars_Where_The_Cash_At/</id><title>Zane Smith - Black Dollars (Where The Cash At) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:45:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:45:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zane_Smith/Black_Dollars_Where_The_Cash_At/" title="Zane Smith - Black Dollars (Where The Cash At) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Would you steal Would you kill <br>For a hunnid dollar bill Just be honest keep it real <br>I know just how you feel, pay the bill, eat a meal <br>Living like a rat running circles in a wheel <br>That's the way it feel hah <br>That's the ways it is hah <br>How you wanna live <br>How much money is really enough money <br>I'm broke as Hell too so you can't take from me <br>Man I need it all, twenties, fifties, and them hunnids <br>All that money <br>Hey <br><br>Where the cash at <br>Gimme that money <br>Add it up fast <br>Twenties, fifties, and them hunnids <br>Where the cash at <br>Gimme that money <br>Add it up fast <br>Twenties, fifties, and them hunnids <br>Where the cash at <br>Gimme that money <br>Add it up fast <br>Twenties, fifties, and them hunnids <br><br>Add it up fast twenties, fifties, and them hunnids <br>Add it up fast twenties, fifties, and them hunnids <br>Add it up fast twenties, fifties, and them hunnids <br><br>Momma said don't steal , God said don't kill <br>Tryna do a couple years, Imma tell you how it is <br>Do you wanna survive Or do you wanna live <br>You can't take from me and mine <br>Bitch I work nine to five <br>Tryna make that profit, empty wallet <br>Don't be digging in my pockets <br>Man I need a raise <br>If you ain't the boss, you ain't getting paid <br>Working like a slave eight hours a day <br>Every payday Zane Smith gone be saying <br>Hey, Hey <br><br>Where the cash at <br>Gimme that money <br>Add it up fast <br>Twenties, fifties, and them hunnids <br>Where the cash at <br>Gimme that money <br>Add it up fast <br>Twenties, fifties, and them hunnids <br>Where the cash at <br>Gimme that money <br>Add it up fast <br>Twenties, fifties, and them hunnids <br><br>Kick it in the burbs, still living with my folks <br>Somewhere between Good Times, Different Strokes <br>We ain't rich, we ain't broke <br>It's a shame, couple dollars to my name <br>Like twenty and some change <br>Need some change, want a Range <br>Couple chains, Blang blang, panky rangs <br>I'd admit, I want a couple nice things <br>There's gotta be more that this life brings <br>Adding value to material things <br>Washington, Tubman twenties, and Benjis all the same <br>Play a game, here's a lighter watch it burn <br>Hard to earn, Better learn <br>That it's plenty ways to get it <br>But you gotta work hard for them digits <br>This shit only matters cause I'm living preach <br>What would you do with a couple black dollars <br>Clean or dirty, money can't solve all my problems <br><br>Where the cash at <br>Gimme that money <br>Add it up fast <br>Twenties, fifties, and them hunnids <br>Where the cash at <br>Gimme that money <br>Add it up fast <br>Twenties, fifties, and them hunnids <br>Where the cash at <br>Gimme that money <br>Add it up fast <br>Twenties, fifties, and them hunnids <br><br>Where that cash Where that cash Where that cash <br>Where that cash Where that cash Where that cash <br>Where that cash <br>Gimme that]]></content><category term="Zane Smith" label="Zane Smith"/><category term="Black Dollars (Where The Cash At)" label="Black Dollars (Where The Cash At)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zane_Smith/Black_Success_Aim_High/</id><title>Zane Smith - Black Success (Aim High) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:45:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:45:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zane_Smith/Black_Success_Aim_High/" title="Zane Smith - Black Success (Aim High) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This my real life man <br>So that's all I know <br>Yeah, Zane Smith <br>They like what you wanna be <br>Where you wanna go <br>What you tryna get <br>Honestly I don't know <br>Like I said before <br>How would I ever know if I never tried <br>Momma told me aim high <br>If I shoot for the moon, at least I'll land on the stars <br>There's more to this world than money, women, and cars <br>Ain't no measure to success, I just wanna go far <br>Oh LordOh Lord <br>Hold OnHold On <br><br>Momma told me aim high, so I'm shooting for the sky <br>Cause I gotta get it, get in before I die <br>Like they always say, you never know you never try <br>That's why I get it in, three sixty five <br>Momma told me aim high, so I'm shooting for the sky <br>Cause I gotta get it, get in before I die <br>Like they always say, you never know you never try <br>That's why I get it in, three sixty five <br><br>Do you want that watch <br>Do you want that drop <br>Oh you want that chain <br>That shit don't mean a thing <br>Two crabs in a bucket, man I need substance <br>Benn searching for something, found a whole lotta nothing <br>Everybody want a lot, I'm working with what I got <br>Have's and have not's, piss but no pot <br>What really is success <br>Plenty hours of rest, a life without stress <br>My family just want the best, I guess <br>I get excited about the future <br>Place myself in situations I ain't used to <br>Tryna be a Martin Luther <br>King, everybody got a dream as hard as it seems <br>Put in work behind the scenes then they'll finally see <br>Only God knows what was meant for me <br>I'm tryna take the galaxy <br>Momma told me aim high, so I'm shooting for the sky <br>Yeah I gotta try, yeah I gotta try <br><br>Momma told me aim high, so I'm shooting for the sky <br>Cause I gotta get it, get in before I die <br>Like they always say, you never know you never try <br>That's why I get it in, three sixty five <br><br>Momma told me aim high <br>Aim high Aim high Aim high <br>Aim high Aim high Aim high <br>So I'm shooting for the sky <br>I'm shooting for the sky <br>I got to get it in <br>Before I die <br>I gotta try <br>I gotta try]]></content><category term="Zane Smith" label="Zane Smith"/><category term="Black Success (Aim High)" label="Black Success (Aim High)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zane_Smith/Black_Life_Depressed/</id><title>Zane Smith - Black Life (Depressed) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:45:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:45:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zane_Smith/Black_Life_Depressed/" title="Zane Smith - Black Life (Depressed) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the black life <br>Drowning inside my mind <br>It's light but it get dark sometime <br>They said search and you will find <br>Throwing two cents, so I stack loose change <br>But they don't really know interpretations of my brain <br>Giving advice How you wanna live yo life <br>What's wrong or right <br>Peace at night must be nice <br>Life's a pie, I want my slice <br>Parents said better be polite, is that right <br>The way it seems, those demanding get everything <br>I'm starting to see, starting to learn <br>Everything just don't go my way <br>Day by day, each mistake, that I make <br>Feeling like running away to a place <br>Where no one knows my name, feel my pain <br>Bout sick and tired of the same ol' same <br>The same ol' game, no improvements <br>I keep losing, tryna keep it moving <br>But I'm going round in circles <br>I been hurting been feeling worthless <br>Like what's my purpose <br>Sip moscato, downed that bottle <br>Tryna solve my problems, they got worse <br>I yell, I slur, I curse <br>Probably should've prayed first <br>Probably should've read a verse <br>Haven't even been to church <br>Everybody else seem to know my worth <br>For what it's worth, giving no fucks <br>Middle fingers up <br>Black thoughts make me so irrational <br>Ninety five down Old National <br>Windows down, music blasting <br>Fuck this shit Fuck that bitch <br>Suck my dick Blah blah This and this <br>I ain't rich bitch, but I got dreams <br>Drifting from where I'm supposed to be <br>Going outside gotta show my teeth <br>Clean my face, like it's okay <br>At ain't all good, nah it ain't all great <br>Asking me, where's the positive energy <br>Bitch are you hearing me <br>It's the pain that you don't see, living depressed <br>I could give a fuck about the way I dress <br>Who the fuck is you I ain't tryna impress <br>As of late I been real stressed, thinking about what's next <br>See I got a lot on my mind, but like half the time <br>I guess I should be thankful that I'm still alive <br>I guess I should be thankful that I've survived <br>I guess I should thank God <br>That little bit of light, in my black life]]></content><category term="Zane Smith" label="Zane Smith"/><category term="Black Life (Depressed)" label="Black Life (Depressed)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zane_Smith/Black_Prayers/</id><title>Zane Smith - Black Prayers - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:45:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:45:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zane_Smith/Black_Prayers/" title="Zane Smith - Black Prayers - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Life <br>Whatcha need in ya life <br>Tell me whatcha need in ya life <br><br>Help me God, I want a daughter and a son <br>They be raking up ya funds <br>Can't be living like the Grinch <br>Fuck a CHRISTmas list <br>All you want is this and this, selfish bastard <br>I know you love yourself, but could you love another <br>On my mind daily, got me going crazy <br>Should I pursue my dreams <br>Or do a 180 Living like George Bailey <br>I'd admit, it's a wonderful life <br>I want a house and a wife <br>Blow me like bagpipes <br>Skirt ain't too tight, but that ass just right <br>I'm addicted to them cakes <br>I love the way it shake <br>Panties off, throw that pussy in my face <br>Black woman hold me down <br>Every time they come around frozen <br>Women get to choose, so I guess I get chosen <br>My heart is what she holding <br>That's why the shop ain't open <br>I been hoping, I been scoping <br>Nah I still ain't got no girl, I wanna see the world <br>Getting tired of the photos and the murals <br>Memories or the pearls, gold or the silver <br>Sifting by the river, smoking on some o's <br>Tryna make the stress go away quicker <br><br>Tell me whatcha need in ya life <br>Tell me whatcha need in ya life <br>Tell me whatcha need in ya life <br>Tell me whatcha need in ya life <br>Tell me whatcha need in ya life]]></content><category term="Zane Smith" label="Zane Smith"/><category term="Black Prayers" label="Black Prayers"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Helena_Paparizou/Agkaliase_Me/</id><title>Helena Paparizou - Agkaliase Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:45:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:45:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Helena_Paparizou/Agkaliase_Me/" title="Helena Paparizou - Agkaliase Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Kita ti kano poso mikreno <br>Otan to soma sou sto soma mou akoubas <br>Oute milao oute anaseno <br>San pedaki perimeno na mou pis <br>Pos m'agapas <br><br>Agkaliase me <br>Ki mi mafisis mes ta maxia kitaxe me <br>Ke mi milas <br>Ela san kima na me tilixis <br>Ke de me niazi <br>Ston vitho sou an me pas <br><br>Akou ti leo pos se kitazo <br>Mesa sta matia sou kontevo na hatho <br>Tremo, dakrizo, den anaseno <br>San pedaki perimeno na mou pis <br>S'agapo <br><br>Agkaliase me <br>Ki mi mafisis mes ta matia kitaxe me <br>Ke mi milas <br>Ela san kima na me tilixis <br>Ke de me niazi <br>Ston vitho sou an me pas <br><br>Agkaliase me <br>Ki mi mafisis mes ta matia kitaxe me <br>Ke mi milas <br><br>Agkaliase me <br>Ki mi mafisis mes ta matia kitaxe me <br>Ke mi milas <br>Ela san kima na me tilixis <br>Ke de me niazi <br>Ston vitho sou, ston vitho sou an me pas]]></content><category term="Helena Paparizou" label="Helena Paparizou"/><category term="Agkaliase Me" label="Agkaliase Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Ghost_Love/</id><title>Keshia Chante - Ghost Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:46:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:46:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Ghost_Love/" title="Keshia Chante - Ghost Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In the mist of the night <br>In the mist of the night <br>When everyone's asleep <br>He comes out from way height <br>It's a different life <br>Filled with hurt filled with fright <br>And for me and what's love <br>So he tries and he tries <br><br>It feels like I'm way passed the clouds <br>And being pulled to the other side <br>The other side <br>Our feelings need tonight and I'm flying towards the light <br>But it's just not right <br>It's just not right <br><br>It's ridiculous It's so unnatural <br>I'm feeling so unnatural <br>I just want to give it up <br>I just wanna lose it <br>Now I live my life without your Ghost Love <br>Ghost Love <br><br>It's ridiculous It's so unnatural <br>I'm feeling so unnatural <br>And I just want to give it up <br>Just wanna lose it <br>Now I live my life without you being a Ghost Love <br><br>A Ghost Love A Ghost Love <br>Ah no no <br><br>I'm so moved by his touch <br>I'm so moved by his touch <br>And his arms I'm wrapped up <br>Feels so good but it's rough <br>To know he's not for real <br>And it ain't gonna be <br>Nothing but a mystery <br><br>Feels like I'm way passed the clouds <br>And being pulled to the other side <br>The other side <br>Our feelings need tonight and I'm flying towards the light <br>But it's just not right <br>It's just not right <br><br>It's ridiculous It's so unnatural <br>I'm feeling so unnatural Unnatural Love <br>I just want to give it up <br>Just wanna lose it <br>Now I live my life without your Ghost Love <br>Ghost Love <br><br>It's ridiculous It's so unnatural <br>I'm feeling so unnatural Unnatural Love <br>I just want to give it up <br>Just wanna lose it <br>Now I live my life without you being a Ghost Love <br><br>Tell me what doing to me <br>Doing to me <br>Doing to me <br>You don't know what this does to me <br>Does to me <br>Does to me <br>Tell me what you doing to me <br>This just not right for me <br>I don't want this <br>Tell me what doing to me <br>Doing to me <br>Doing to me <br>You don't know what this does to me <br>Does to me <br>Does to me <br>Tell me what you doing to me <br>This just not right for me <br>I don't want this <br><br>Ghost Love <br><br>It's ridiculous It's so unnatural <br>I'm feeling so unnatural Unnatural Love <br>I just want to give it up <br>I just wanna lose it <br>Now I live my life without your Ghost Love <br><br>It's ridiculous It's so unnatural <br>I'm feeling so unnatural I don't wanna go <br>I just want to give it up give it up <br>I just wanna lose it lose it <br>Now I live my life without you being a Ghost Love <br><br>Tell me what doing to me <br>Doing to me <br>Doing to me <br>You don't know what this does to me <br>Does to me <br>Does to me <br>Tell me what you doing to me <br>This just not right for me <br>I don't want this <br>GHOST LOVE]]></content><category term="Keshia Chante" label="Keshia Chante"/><category term="Ghost Love" label="Ghost Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/If_U_Say/</id><title>Keshia Chante - If U Say - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:46:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:46:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/If_U_Say/" title="Keshia Chante - If U Say - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Eh ey, oh no no, yeah eh <br><br>You promised me last night that things gonna change <br>Woke up this morning babe and things were just the same <br>Walking down the hallway and looking at the photographs <br>Looking at all the times you used to make me laugh <br><br>Now you gone and it's wrong <br>I'm in this kitchen cooking breakfast alone <br>It's so wrong cause you gone, I don't care <br><br>If you say you love me then just make it right <br>If you say you need me why we argue and fight <br>If you say you need me then just make it work <br>Just make it right, just make it right <br><br>Why am I still waiting for you at the front door <br>I got myself all dolled up, your favorite dress down to the floor <br>Its 945 wait, this reservations at 8 <br>You couldn't even call me, to tell me you'd be late <br><br>And it's wrong, still not home <br>I'm in this kitchen cooking dinner alone <br>It's so wrong, you ain't home, I don't care <br><br>If you say you love me then just make it right <br>If you say you need me why we argue and fight <br>If you say you need me then just make it work <br>Just make it right, just make it right, just make it right, just make it right <br><br>Oh no, I'm sick of everything that you said oohh always promising tomorrow <br>Did you think that I'm the girl who would stay for you your promises are hollow <br>I really don't know what to do ohh <br>I deserve much better than you <br><br>Now you home all alone <br>You're in the kitchen thinking where we went wrong <br>I'm so gone I'm so gone, I don't care <br><br>If you say you love me then just make it right <br>If you say you love me why we argue and fight <br>If you say you need me then just make it work <br>Just make it right, just make it right <br>Just make it right, just make it right <br>Just make it right, just make it right <br>Just make it right, just make it right]]></content><category term="Keshia Chante" label="Keshia Chante"/><category term="If U Say" label="If U Say"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Test_Drive/</id><title>Keshia Chante - Test Drive - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:46:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:46:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Test_Drive/" title="Keshia Chante - Test Drive - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I found myself drawn to you <br>Looking for something new <br>Only to find it was used <br>I was tired of waiting <br>Was looking to trade in <br>You left me with not much to choose <br>You had me thinking of <br>How I'm a sucker for love <br>You were such a good sales man <br>I signed on the dotted line <br>Didn't take me much time <br>You had me sold <br><br>U wanted me so bad <br>Fallen for the best pitch that u had <br>Selling me what I don't have <br>I was mistaken <br>From the outside you looked so good <br>Shoulda double checked under that hood <br>Ey I was just taken <br><br>Is it too late to change lanes <br>Feels like I'm going to fast <br>Were driving on a one way <br>I knew I shoulda taken that test drive <br>test drive, test drive <br>Cause something didn't look right <br>Look right, look right <br>Should taken that test drive <br>Test drive, test drive <br>Something didn't feel right <br><br>Soon as I started the engine <br>It was a lemon <br>Won't make this mistake again <br>Red lights start blinkin <br>It got me thinking <br>What kinda mess am I in <br>Feels like I'm riding on empty <br>U won't get the best of me <br>Shoulda read my policy, policy <br>Shoulda got me that warranty <br>Cause I got no guarantees <br>I got no guarantees <br><br>U wanted me so bad <br>Fallen for the best pitch that u had <br>Selling me what I don't have <br>I was mistaken <br>From the outside U looked so good <br>Shoulda double checked under that hood <br>Ey <br>I was just taken <br><br>Is it too late to change lanes <br>Feels like I'm going to fast <br>Were driving on a one way <br>I knew I shoulda taken that test drive <br>test drive, test drive <br>Cause something didn't look right <br>Look right, look right <br>Should taken that test drive <br>Test drive, test drive <br>Something didn't feel right <br><br>When this car goes a blazing <br>me, you wont be taking down <br>before these tires get deflated <br>I wont be around <br>no, test drive <br><br>Shoulda shoulda shoulda baby]]></content><category term="Keshia Chante" label="Keshia Chante"/><category term="Test Drive" label="Test Drive"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Hush/</id><title>Keshia Chante - Hush - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:46:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:46:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Hush/" title="Keshia Chante - Hush - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do you really wanna talk, there's nothing left to say, you said it all you said it all <br>And I can't change your mind, that you've already made, you know it all you know it all <br>And if moving on, is where you are, I've already heard it, so don't say a word <br>Just hush just hush <br><br>Don't try <br>It only makes it complicated <br>baby when you try to fake, in your eyes <br>they are saying everything, so go ahead and keep it in <br>just hush hush <br><br>I don't see the point to relive everyday <br>we had it all we had it all <br>Cause when you get so high <br>And give your heart away, you gonna fall you gonna fall <br>And if moving on, is where you are, I've already heard it, so don't say a word <br>just hush hush <br><br>Don't try <br>It only makes it complicated <br>baby when you try to fake, in your eyes <br>they are saying everything, go ahead and keep it in <br>and if moving on, is where you are <br>I've already heard it so don't say a word <br>Don't try <br>It only makes it complicated <br>baby when you try to fake, in your eyes <br>they are saying everything, so go ahead and keep it in <br>just hush]]></content><category term="Keshia Chante" label="Keshia Chante"/><category term="Hush" label="Hush"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/I_Miss_U/</id><title>Keshia Chante - I Miss U - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:46:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:46:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/I_Miss_U/" title="Keshia Chante - I Miss U - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Long sleepless nights <br>and everything's not right <br>you should be here by my side <br>Things just ain't the same <br>how could we let it change <br>cause we were everything <br><br>I need you to know <br>I'll never let go of you and me <br>And I need you to trust <br>the love between us <br>when times are so tough I need you to see <br><br>That I miss you, eh eh <br>That I miss you, eh eh <br>That I miss you, eh eh <br>At the end of the day I need you to say <br>I miss you <br>I miss you <br><br>Long restless days <br>I'm battling with this pain <br>wish you could take it away from me <br>We're miles and miles apart <br>it's like living in the dark <br>it's messing with my heart, yes it is <br><br>I need you to know <br>I'll never let go of you and me <br>And I need you to trust <br>the love between us <br>when times are so tough I need you to see <br><br>That I miss you, eh eh <br>That I miss you, eh eh <br>That I miss you, eh eh <br>At the end of the day I need you to say <br>I miss you <br><br>I'm sick of watching the clock <br>you know I'm tired of waiting, waiting, waiting <br>Cause all this time apart <br>you know it's driving me crazy, crazy, crazy <br><br>I need you to know, I'll never let go of you and me <br><br>That I miss you, eh eh <br>That I miss you, eh eh <br>That I miss you, eh eh <br>At the end of the day I need you to say <br>I miss you <br>I miss you]]></content><category term="Keshia Chante" label="Keshia Chante"/><category term="I Miss U" label="I Miss U"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Pillow_Talk/</id><title>Keshia Chante - Pillow Talk - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:46:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:46:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Pillow_Talk/" title="Keshia Chante - Pillow Talk - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lay your head down on my pillow <br>You don't need words 'cause I I know <br>But sometimes you walking around feeling defeated, hey yeah <br>Tell me your fears, I'll keep it a secret <br><br>Is it the moon Is it the stars <br>Why didn't I that you open your heart <br>Is it the moon Is it my eyes <br>It's always an I even to realize <br><br>I never felt a love like this <br>I never felt a love like this <br>I never though it could exist <br>I can never get enough love <br><br>I never felt a love like this <br>I never felt a love like this <br>I never though it could exist <br>I can never get enough love <br>Of your love love <br><br>Pillow talk talk talk talk <br>I get you when it's pillow talk talk talk talk <br>I get you when it's pillow talk talk talk talk <br>I get you when it's pillow talk, pillow talk <br><br>You can't weight the world right up on your shoulders <br>And you still act up on me when I tell you that I hurt <br>Tell me how you hold it inside when you're heated <br>Open up your heart and let me in, boy you need it <br><br>Is it the moon Is it the stars <br>Why didn't I that you open your heart <br>Is it the moon Is it my eyes <br>It's always an I even to realize <br><br>I never felt a love like this <br>I never felt a love like this <br>I never though it could exist <br>I can never get enough love <br><br>I never felt a love like this <br>I never felt a love like this <br>I never though it could exist <br>I can never get enough love <br>Of your love love <br><br>Pillow talk talk talk talk <br>I get you when it's pillow talk talk talk talk <br>I get you when it's pillow talk talk talk talk <br>I get you when it's pillow talk, pillow talk <br><br>Seconds, minutes, hours I'll been waiting <br>Seconds, minutes, hours I'll been waiting <br>Seconds, minutes, hours I'll been waiting <br>Just to hear you talk, talk, love it when you talk, talk <br><br>Seconds, minutes, hours I'll been waiting <br>Seconds, minutes, hours I'll been waiting <br>Seconds, minutes, hours I'll been waiting <br>Just to hear you talk, talk <br><br>I never felt a love like this <br>I never felt a love like this <br>I never though it could exist <br>I can never get enough love <br><br>I never felt a love like this <br>I never felt a love like this <br>I never though it could exist <br>I can never get enough love <br>Of your love love <br><br>Pillow talk talk talk talk <br>I get you when it's pillow talk talk talk talk <br>I get you when it's pillow talk talk talk talk <br>I get you when it's pillow talk, pillow talk <br><br>When the sun goes down I know you will come around <br>When the sun goes down <br>When the sun goes down I know you will come around <br>And baby we can talk, I love it when we talk <br><br>I can never get enough love <br>Of your love love <br><br>I can never get enough love <br>Of your love love]]></content><category term="Keshia Chante" label="Keshia Chante"/><category term="Pillow Talk" label="Pillow Talk"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Hang_My_Jersey_Up_Feat_P_Reign/</id><title>Keshia Chante - Hang My Jersey Up (Feat. P. Reign) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:46:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:46:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Hang_My_Jersey_Up_Feat_P_Reign/" title="Keshia Chante - Hang My Jersey Up (Feat. P. Reign) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ah ah ah eh eh <br>ah ah ah eh eh <br>ah ah ah eh eh <br><br>I, I never saw, this, this happening <br>thought I knew of a place <br>I was MVP, top gunner in my league <br>what's the word on the streets <br><br>that you ooh ooh ooh came through ooh ooh ooh <br>and it's over now I'll be a solider <br>and baby what you do ooh ooh ooh <br>to me ooh ooh ooh, when I hold ya, boy when I hold ya <br><br>you make me hang my jersey up <br>jersey up, jersey up, jersey up <br>put it up in the sky <br>you make me hang my jersey up <br>jersey up, jersey up, jersey up <br>put my number up high put my number up high <br>the game is over, the game is over, ooh ooh ooh <br>the game is over, the game is over, ooh ooh ooh <br>ooh ooh ooh <br><br>ah ah ah eh eh <br>ah ah ah eh eh <br>ah ah ah eh eh <br><br>it was, was the little things <br>attention that you bring, showing me love <br>butterflies from head to toe, never rushed, took it slow <br>and that's how know <br><br>that you ooh ooh ooh came through ooh ooh ooh <br>it was over cause I'll be a solider <br>and baby what you do ooh ooh ooh <br>to me ooh ooh ooh, when I hold ya, boy when I hold ya <br><br>you make me hang my jersey up <br>jersey up, jersey up, jersey up <br>put it up in the sky <br>you make me hang my jersey up <br>jersey up, jersey up, jersey up <br>put my number up high put my number up high <br>the game is over, the game is over, ooh ooh ooh <br>there is no time left on the clock <br>the game is over, the game is over, ooh ooh ooh <br>ooh ooh ooh <br><br>yeah <br>ohhhhh, oh oh oh <br>I've had to quit this game <br>brings on my whole fame <br>your the reason too in my ring <br>I'm tired with my number babe <br>I don't wanna play no more <br>tired, I run the score <br>our team's the only one I'm fighting for <br>I'm fighting for <br><br>Keshia, know I got you right <br>ain't you ready baby <br>yeah, it like every other chick was a loose loose <br>them other birds, drove me coo coo <br>and I see you in the street tryna' do you <br>tell em' I put my spell on you, voodoo <br>yeah, and if you really tryna' do me <br>then hang it up like jordan, 2 3 <br>Now I got your little friends like, who is he <br>3 letters baby, MVP <br>ha, run one more play for me <br>I pick you, and you roll with me <br>I just wanna be the coach you can lean on <br>'cause baby I'm the king, lebron <br>first pick when you enter the draft <br>got a ring on you finger much bigger than Shaq <br>she got a jersey on the wall with my name on the back <br>and on the defense, back board when I make an attack <br><br>you make me hang my , jersey up <br>jersey up, jersey up, jersey up <br>put it up in the sky <br>you make me hang my jersey up <br>jersey up, jersey up, jersey up <br>put my number up high put my number up high <br>the game is over, the game is over, ooh ooh ooh <br>there is no time left on the clock <br>the game is over, the game is over, ooh ooh ooh <br>ooh ooh ooh <br><br>yeah <br>ohhhhh, oh oh oh]]></content><category term="Keshia Chante" label="Keshia Chante"/><category term="Hang My Jersey Up (Feat. P. Reign)" label="Hang My Jersey Up (Feat. P. Reign)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Shooting_Star/</id><title>Keshia Chante - Shooting Star - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:46:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:46:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Shooting_Star/" title="Keshia Chante - Shooting Star - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I done been down there before and I ain't going back <br>Been through the fire <br>Through the storm <br>What yall know bout that <br>Whatchu really really know bout that <br>I've been through so much crap <br>It's unbelievable how I kept my sanity in tact <br><br>I done figured it out <br>I am no longer afraid the world's for the taken <br>I done figured it out <br>Imma fly <br>So watch me fly <br><br>Imma shooting star <br>Shooting Star <br>I'm unbreakable <br>I'm invincible <br>Shooting Star <br>Shooting Star <br><br>You can't stop me now <br>You can't break me down <br>I'm flying higher than I've ever been with places that I've seen <br>Ain't no turning back <br>I'm a shooting star <br>Shooting Star <br>Shooting Star <br><br>It's unbelievable <br>This feeling that I'm feeling <br>Like a miracle just hit me with a healing <br>I betcha like that to feel like that <br>Got the world in your head like that <br>From top to bottom you got it going like that <br>I was flat on the ground <br>Now look where I'm at <br><br>I done figured it out <br>I am no longer afraid the world's for the taken <br>I done figured it out <br>Imma fly <br>So watch me fly <br><br>Imma shooting star <br>Shooting Star <br>I'm unbreakable <br>I'm invincible <br>Shooting Star <br>Shooting Star <br><br>You can't stop me now <br>You can't break me down <br>I'm flying higher than I've ever been with places that I've seen <br>Ain't no turning back <br>I'm a shooting star <br>Shooting Star <br>Shooting Star <br><br>Flying so ha ha high <br>Look up you might see me now <br>Soaring above the clouds <br>Don't think I'll ever come down <br><br>Flying so ha ha high <br>Way over closed doors <br>Can't hold me down no more <br>I'm bout to show em why <br><br>Flying so ha ha high <br>Look up you gonna see me now <br>Soaring above the clouds <br>Don't think I'll ever come down <br><br>Flying so ha ha high <br>Way over closed doors <br>Can't hold me down no more <br><br>Cause I'm a Shooting Star Oh yeeah <br>I'm unbreakable Oh <br>I'm invincible <br>Shooting Star <br>Shooting Star <br><br>You can't stop me now <br>You can't break me down <br>I'm flying higher than I've ever been with places that I've seen <br>Ain't no turning back <br><br>I'm a shooting star <br>Shooting Star <br>I'm unbreakable <br>I'm invincible <br><br>Shooting Star <br>Shooting Star <br>You can't stop me now <br>You can't break me down <br>Cause Imma Shooting Star <br>I'm flying higher than I've ever been with places that I've seen <br>Ain't no turning back Oh no <br><br>I'm a shooting star <br>Shooting Star <br>Shooting Star]]></content><category term="Keshia Chante" label="Keshia Chante"/><category term="Shooting Star" label="Shooting Star"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/I_Hope_U_Cry/</id><title>Keshia Chante - I Hope U Cry - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:46:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:46:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/I_Hope_U_Cry/" title="Keshia Chante - I Hope U Cry - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I gave you everything but was it enough <br>Can't believe how you neglected my love wish I would see <br>Wish I woulda seen you for who you are baby I was just a foool <br>Baby I was just a fool in love what was I thinking of <br><br>You say you, found somebody new now you don't want me, noo ohh <br>Hope she do, the same thing to you I hope that she makes you <br><br>Cry cry, Cry cry, Cryyyy cryyyyy <br>Cry cry, Cry cry, Cryyyy cryyyyy <br>Cry cry, Cry cry, Cryyyy cryyyyy <br>Cry cry, Cry cry, Cryyyy cryyyyy <br><br>Never thought that we'd be where we are nooooo <br>Always thought that we would reach the stars yeaa <br>I guess you just weren't capable <br>Of being truly faithful <br>But it's all good cause now I know who you are <br><br>You say you, found somebody new now you don't want me, noo ohh <br>Hope she do, the same thing to you I hope that she makes you <br><br>Cry cry, Cry cry, Cryyyy cryyyyy <br>Cry cry, Cry cry, Cryyyy cryyyyy <br>Cry cry, Cry cry, Cryyyy cryyyyy <br>Cry cry, Cry cry, Cryyyy cryyyyy <br><br>Think of everything you put me through <br>Now imagine you in the position but beings onto you <br>Never thought that we would end this way <br>And I'm sorry babe but karma's coming back in the worst way <br>I know the vagant thing to do would be just to forgive you <br>But I'm sorry baby cause I already too <br>Now I hope you realize that telling me all those lies <br>Is gonna be the thing that's gonna Make Ya <br><br>Cry cry, Cry cry, Cryyyy cryyyyy <br>Cry cry, Cry cry, Cryyyy cryyyyy <br>Cry cry, Cry cry, Cryyyy cryyyyy <br>Cry cry, Cry cry, Cryyyy cryyyyy]]></content><category term="Keshia Chante" label="Keshia Chante"/><category term="I Hope U Cry" label="I Hope U Cry"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Victorious/</id><title>Keshia Chante - Victorious - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:46:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:46:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Victorious/" title="Keshia Chante - Victorious - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm on my own,on my own, in the middle in the middle of the universe <br>And noone's there to lend a hand, and I'm so so cold <br>I'm in the race, in the race, with nothing there's no way I'm about to lose this <br>I'm the boss, yes gonna be first, I'll go journey that road <br><br>There is only one life to win, one chance to win <br>One hill to climb, to prove that you're a champion <br>I'm gonna ride, no wind with the tide, does not horror, I will survive cause now <br>I'm on top of the world, ain't no mountain I can't climb <br>Guess this is the final destination, I'm flying home victorious <br>I'm on top of the world, ain't no mountain I cant climb <br>Guess this is the final destination, I'm flying home victorious <br><br>I'm letting you know even if I fall down, I'mma get up off that get up off that <br>I'm flying home victorious, the journey is hard sometimes I wanna give up <br>Imma get up off that get up off that, I'm flying home victorious <br>Ohhh I'm on top of the world <br><br>I'm almost there, almost there <br>The finishing line is just a mile away <br>I'm tired out, thirsty now, still moving on <br>I've come so far, come so far, like a pyramid I'm way too up to go back down <br>I hold my faith, make no mistake, I'm gon get that goal <br><br>I'm on top of the world, ain't no mountain I can't climb <br>Guess this is the final destination, I'm flying home victorious <br>I'm on top of the world, ain't no mountain I cant climb <br>Guess this is the final destination, I'm flying home victorious <br><br>I'm flying home victorious, flyin victorious <br>I made it through against all odds <br><br>There is only one life to win, one chance to win <br>One hill to climb, to prove that you're a champion <br>I'm gonna ride, no wind with the tide, does not horror, I will survive cause now <br>I'm on top of the world, ain't no mountain I can't climb <br>Guess this is the final destination, I'm flying home victorious <br>I'm on top of the world, ain't no mountain I cant climb <br>Guess this is the final destination, I'm flying home victorious]]></content><category term="Keshia Chante" label="Keshia Chante"/><category term="Victorious" label="Victorious"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Edit_Cut__Delete_U/</id><title>Keshia Chante - Edit, Cut &amp; Delete U - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:46:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:46:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Edit_Cut__Delete_U/" title="Keshia Chante - Edit, Cut &amp; Delete U - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You had me almost convinced that <br>Something really special was about to happen <br>In our lives ya ya you said that <br>But now it seems like you don't really mean what you were saying <br>You thought that you could play me <br>Thought you could have me hooked on you so easily <br>Thought wrong ya you shoulda known that <br>This aint no chick <br>This aint no chick <br>That you should be messing with <br><br>You keep telling me that I'm the only one <br>You keep telling me that I'm the only one <br>You said that I'm the one <br>But I know that you mess around with just about everyone <br><br>No I gotchu now <br>No I gotchu now <br>No I gotchu now where I want you <br>It's all over now <br>All over now <br>Boy Imma Edit, Cut and Delete U <br>No I gotchu now <br>No I gotchu now <br>No I gotchu now where I want you <br>It's all over now <br>All over now <br>Boy Imma Edit, Cut and Delete U <br><br>Cut and Delete U <br>Imma Edit, Cut and Delete U Cut and Delete U <br>Cut, cut, cut, cut and Delete <br><br>Its too bad for you now you lost me <br>So whats up with that running back looking for forgiveness <br>I moved on I hope you get there <br>I've already written you off of my list <br>Crying trippin off now <br>As if you dont know what goes around comes around <br>Oh no who's playing who now <br>This aint no bitch <br>This aint no bitch <br>You should be messing with <br><br>You keep telling me that I'm the only one <br>You keep telling me that I'm the only one <br>You said that I'm the one <br>But I know that you mess around with just about everyone <br><br>No I gotchu now <br>No I gotchu now <br>No I gotchu now where I want you <br>It's all over now <br>All over now <br>Boy Imma Edit, Cut and Delete U <br>No I gotchu now <br>No I gotchu now <br>No I gotchu now where I want you <br>It's all over now <br>All over now <br>Boy Imma Edit, Cut and Delete U <br><br>Imma Edit, Cut and Delete U Yeah, Yeah, Yay, Oh no <br><br>You keep telling me that I'm the only one <br>You keep telling me that I'm the only one <br>You said that I'm the one But <br>I know that you mess around with just about everyone <br><br>No I gotchu now <br>No I gotchu now <br>No I gotchu now where I want you <br>It's all over now <br>All over now <br>Boy Imma Edit, Cut and Delete U <br>No I gotchu now <br>No I gotchu now <br>No I gotchu now where I want you <br>It's all over now <br>All over now <br>Boy Imma Edit, Cut and Delete U <br><br>Ah no no <br>Cut and Delete U yeah, yeah <br>Imma Edit, Cut and Delete U <br>All over now Ay yeah <br>Boy Imma Cut and Delete U]]></content><category term="Keshia Chante" label="Keshia Chante"/><category term="Edit, Cut &amp; Delete U" label="Edit, Cut &amp; Delete U"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Set_U_Free/</id><title>Keshia Chante - Set U Free - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:46:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:46:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Set_U_Free/" title="Keshia Chante - Set U Free - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stimulated cause your body's so amazing <br>I can not believe your acting so abrasive <br>What you need, you can get from me <br>Dont you that I can set your body free <br>Taking time, tell me why your tryna tease me <br>Got your body all over me than you leave me <br>What you need, you can get from me <br>Dont you know that I can set your body <br><br>Free ee ee ee <br>Set your body Free ee <br>If you want it <br>Set your body Free ee ee ee ee <br>Set your body Free ee <br>If you want it <br>All you gotta do, is call on me <br>And I can set you Free <br>If you want it <br>Set your body Free ee ee ee ee <br>Set your body Free ee <br>If you want it <br><br>Baby dont you know your body's so persuasive <br>Threw my fingers, why you acting so invasive <br>What you need, you can get from me <br>Dont you know that I can set your body free <br>My position is I'm tripping going crazy <br>Boy your presence making everything go hazy <br>What you need, you can get from me <br>Dont you know that I can set your body <br><br>Let me take you to a place that you aint never been <br>Where the night shines with gold and emerald green <br>Where the music never stops we can rock til light <br>Turn the bass and be right up and set this floor on fire <br>Let me take you to a place you that you aint never been <br><br>Cause you got me going <br>Ooo Ooo Ooo <br>Cause you got me saying <br>Set your body, set your body <br>Ooo Ooo Ooo <br>Set your body, set your body <br>Ooo Ooo Ooo <br>Set your body, set your body <br>Ooo Ooo Ooo <br>Set your body, set your body]]></content><category term="Keshia Chante" label="Keshia Chante"/><category term="Set U Free" label="Set U Free"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Table_Dancer/</id><title>Keshia Chante - Table Dancer - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:46:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:46:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Keshia_Chante/Table_Dancer/" title="Keshia Chante - Table Dancer - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you DJ, for playing my song <br>Put that sh*t on replay, all night long <br>Hey Bartender, better move those bottles <br>Better clear those tables, cause they 'bout to be filled with models <br><br>DJ, DJ <br>Put that sh*t on <br>Replay, Replay <br>Spin it all night long <br><br>Cause I'll be Table Dancing <br>This is your chance <br>To be with me, and you will see <br>Up on the table dancing <br>That's where romance is <br>If your with me <br>And you will see <br>Say <br><br>Whoa oah oah oah oah oh <br>Whoa oah oh Woah oah oh <br>Whoa oah oah oah oah oh <br>Whoa oah oh Woah oah oh <br><br>Come on closer into my world <br>Show you all the reasons why I'm your favorite girl <br>Be be beside me, don't let me fall <br>Just hold me close and don't let go until last call]]></content><category term="Keshia Chante" label="Keshia Chante"/><category term="Table Dancer" label="Table Dancer"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/An_Honest_Mistake/Aint_Christmas_Without_You/</id><title>An Honest Mistake - Ain`t Christmas Without You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:46:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:46:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/An_Honest_Mistake/Aint_Christmas_Without_You/" title="An Honest Mistake - Ain`t Christmas Without You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Walking through this crowded street, people are laughing with no sign of tears <br>Happiness and cheer, I guess it's just that time of year <br>A year's gone by in a blink of an eye, just like a shooting star across the night sky <br>You've been the one thing on my mind forever you and I <br><br>As the lights light up the skyline, you've got me on my knees, praying you're the one for me <br>There's no room for goodbyes, I'm not gonna be alone this holiday <br><br>I wish you were home tonight, and you were by my side <br>Because I've been so lost without you so lost without you <br>I wish you were home tonight, and you'd be by my side <br>Because all I really want is you all I really want is you <br>This year's Christmas, ain't Christmas without you <br><br>You've got a way to make me smile <br>The way you make me feel <br>You make me feel alive inside <br>Nothing can replace you even if I tried <br>Not even the strongest of tides <br>Please say that you're coming home tonight <br><br>It's not the same without you <br>I want you here, I need you here tonight <br><br>I wish you were home tonight, and you'd be by my side <br>Because all I really want is you <br>This year's Christmas, ain't Christmas without you <br><br>I'm coming home tonight, and I'll be by your side <br>All I really want is you all I really want is you <br>I'm coming home tonight, and I'll be by your side <br>I've been so lost without you, so lost without you <br>This year's Christmas ain't Christmas without you]]></content><category term="An Honest Mistake" label="An Honest Mistake"/><category term="Ain`t Christmas Without You" label="Ain`t Christmas Without You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/An_Honest_Mistake/Finding_My_Way/</id><title>An Honest Mistake - Finding My Way - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:46:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:46:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/An_Honest_Mistake/Finding_My_Way/" title="An Honest Mistake - Finding My Way - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I remember last December <br>Don't know if you remember <br>The summer when everything felt right <br>That kiss under the mistletoe meant everything to me <br>You know <br><br>I don't wanna be without you <br>Not another year without you <br>Now where do we begin <br>It's Christmas time again <br><br>You're the light that guides me home <br>Shines brighter than the morning <br>Finding my way back to you <br>And I hope that you're feeling it too <br><br>Take me back to the places where we both felt <br>We both felt alive <br>Take me back to the time where it was only <br>Only you and I <br>I know I'll never be the same without you <br>Won't you take my hand and we'll drive into the night <br><br>You're the air that I breathe <br>You're the only one I need <br>Finding my way back to you <br>And I hope that you're feeling it too <br><br>You're the light that guides me home <br>Shines brighter than the morning <br>You're the air that I breathe <br>You're the only one I need <br>Finding my way back to you <br>And I hope that you feel the same way too]]></content><category term="An Honest Mistake" label="An Honest Mistake"/><category term="Finding My Way" label="Finding My Way"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/RimK/Cellophane/</id><title>Rim`K - Cellophane - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:48:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:48:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/RimK/Cellophane/" title="Rim`K - Cellophane - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[J'ai le tampon du Roi du Maroc sur ma plaquette <br>Renverse du champagne a 1000€ sur la moquette <br>Passe une soiree marvelous avec une Kardash' <br>Claque mes sous a Amster' avec mes kardesh <br>J'ai les pochetons avec les feuilles de canna' <br>C'est la mafia d'Italie, le cartel de Cali <br>Devant le hall 13, je coupais des lamelles <br>Je fais sonner l'alarme incendie a l'hotel <br>Nouvelle floraison, je me roule un petard <br>Fabrication maison, de la weed et du miel <br>Pour trouver le sommeil a 6 du mat', la police me reveille <br><br>Ils ont appele la police pour moi <br>ca sentait la weed devant chez moi <br>J'ai planque mes billets, planque la pe fra <br>Je vais etre en galere, peut etre au placard <br>Donc j'allume un gros spliff, nocif, gros spliff <br>En club la Grey Goose je la siffle, je la siffle <br>Je me prends pour un grossiste, grossiste <br><br>Smartphone pour la prison, cellophane <br>J'arrive a me da les coffee sont fermes <br>Une liasse de billets, cellophanee <br>20 grammes de peu fra cellophanes <br>Sur le t shirt, weed life, rim'kush <br>Elle en perd son string, elle en perd son kerche <br>Pour nous c'est bleche, y a pas de saison seche <br>Et meme quand le prix du kilo monte en fleche <br>Je passe les crash tests, tous les alcootests <br>Quand la volaille arrive, pas meilleure cachette que les fesses <br>Dans l'habitacle, j'ai cache la beu her <br>Et du na3na3 de Chefchaouen dans la theiere <br>La sel3a vient de Marbella <br>On marche sur l'hchiche et le narguile <br>Avec les copains on fait les grillades <br>Nique ta mere, t'es pas invite <br><br>Ils ont appele la police pour moi <br>ca sentait la weed devant chez moi <br>J'ai planque mes billets, planque la pe fra <br>Je vais etre en galere, peut etre au placard <br>Donc j'allume un gros spliff, nocif, gros spliff <br>En club la Grey Goose je la siffle, je la siffle <br>Je me prends pour un grossiste, grossiste <br>Ils ont appele la police pour moi <br>ca sentait la weed devant chez moi <br>J'ai planque mes billets, planque la pe fra <br>Je vais etre en galere, peut etre au placard <br>Donc j'allume un gros spliff, nocif, gros spliff <br>En club la Grey Goose je la siffle, je la siffle <br>Je me prends pour un grossiste, grossiste]]></content><category term="Rim`K" label="Rim`K"/><category term="Cellophane" label="Cellophane"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OTHANKQ_오땡큐/1분_1초_1min_1sec/</id><title>OTHANKQ (오땡큐) - 1분 1초 (1min 1sec) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:49:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:49:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OTHANKQ_%EC%98%A4%EB%95%A1%ED%81%90/1%EB%B6%84_1%EC%B4%88_1min_1sec/" title="OTHANKQ (오땡큐) - 1분 1초 (1min 1sec) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루가 참 길었어 <br>네 생각에 힘들었어 <br>빠져 나올 수 없어 <br>너에게서 미안해 <br>스쳐 지나가는 <br>인연이 아니길 바래 <br>흔한 커플이 아니었길 난 바래 <br>널 다시 생각하면 <br>1분 1초가 너무 괴로워 <br>I’m crying <br>가슴은 찢어지고 <br>1분 1초가 너무 힘들어 <br>I’m crying <br>언제쯤 이 시간이 <br>지나갈까 지워질까 <br>언제쯤 너에게서 <br>빠져 나올 수 있을까 <br>스쳐 지나가는 <br>인연이 아니길 바래 <br>흔한 커플이 아니었길 난 바래 <br>널 다시 생각하면 <br>1분 1초가 너무 괴로워 <br>I’m crying <br>가슴은 찢어지고 <br>1분 1초가 너무 힘들어 <br>I’m crying <br>언제나 내 곁에 있어 줄거라 <br>나 믿었었는데 왜 <br>언제나 우리는 함께 일거라 <br>나 믿었었는데 왜 <br>1분 1초가 너무 괴로워 <br>I’m crying <br>가슴은 찢어지고 <br>1분 1초가 너무 힘들어 <br>I’m crying <br>널 다시 생각하면 <br>1분 1초가 너무 괴로워 <br>I’m crying <br>가슴은 찢어지고 <br>1분 1초가 너무 힘들어 <br>I’m crying <br>1분 1초가 <br>]]></content><category term="OTHANKQ (오땡큐)" label="OTHANKQ (오땡큐)"/><category term="1분 1초 (1min 1sec)" label="1분 1초 (1min 1sec)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OTHANKQ_오땡큐/프로포즈_하는_노래_Propose_Song/</id><title>OTHANKQ (오땡큐) - 프로포즈 하는 노래 (Propose Song) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:49:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:49:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OTHANKQ_%EC%98%A4%EB%95%A1%ED%81%90/%ED%94%84%EB%A1%9C%ED%8F%AC%EC%A6%88_%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98_Propose_Song/" title="OTHANKQ (오땡큐) - 프로포즈 하는 노래 (Propose Song) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니가 원할때면 항상 <br>니옆에 있어줄게 <br>니가 힘들때면 항상 <br>니얘길 들어줄게 <br>특별히 말하지 않아도 <br>니옆에 있어줄게 <br>특별히 원하지 않아도 <br>모든걸 들어줄게 <br>우리라는 울타리를 쳐줄게 <br>내가 항상 니옆에 <br>있다는걸 기억해 <br>우리라는 울타리를 쳐줄게 <br>내가 항상 니옆에 <br>있다는걸 기억해 <br>널 사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>우리 엄마아빠 걸고 <br>내 모든걸 바쳐 사랑해 <br>널 사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>우리 엄마아빠 걸고 <br>내 모든걸 바쳐 널 사랑해 <br>널 바라보면 내 기분이 <br>너무 좋아져 <br>니가 웃는 모습도 <br>가만히 있는 모습도 <br>널 바라보면 내 기분이 <br>너무 좋아져 <br>니가 먹는 모습도 <br>뛰노는 모습 까지도 <br>우리라는 울타리를 쳐줄게 <br>내가 항상 니옆에 <br>있다는걸 기억해 <br>우리라는 울타리를 쳐줄게 <br>내가 항상 니옆에 <br>있다는걸 기억해 <br>널 사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>우리 엄마아빠 걸고 <br>내 모든걸 바쳐 사랑해 <br>널 사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>우리 엄마아빠 걸고 <br>내 모든걸 바쳐 널 사랑해 <br>우리라는 울타리를 쳐줄게 <br>내가 항상 니옆에 <br>있다는걸 기억해 <br>우리라는 울타리를 쳐줄게 <br>내가 항상 니옆에 <br>있다는걸 기억해 <br>널 사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>우리 엄마아빠 걸고 <br>내 모든걸 바쳐 사랑해 <br>널 사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>우리 엄마아빠 걸고 <br>내 모든걸 바쳐 널 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="OTHANKQ (오땡큐)" label="OTHANKQ (오땡큐)"/><category term="프로포즈 하는 노래 (Propose Song)" label="프로포즈 하는 노래 (Propose Song)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/춘자_春子/빨아빨아_아이스크림/</id><title>춘자 (春子) - 빨아빨아 아이스크림 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:49:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:49:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%98%EC%9E%90_%E6%98%A5%E5%AD%90/%EB%B9%A8%EC%95%84%EB%B9%A8%EC%95%84_%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%BC/" title="춘자 (春子) - 빨아빨아 아이스크림 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대로 녹지마 <br>혀끝에 살며시 스며 <br>더이상 녹지마 <br>달콤히 살며시 스며 <br>내곁을 떠나지마 <br>널느끼는 이 순간이 좋아 <br>멈출수 없자나 <br>그래서 이제 나는 다시한번 <br>빨아빨아 아이스크림 <br>빨아빨아 아이스크림 <br>너무좋아 아이스크림 <br>빨아빨아 아이스크림 <br>너무좋아 아이스크림 <br>달콤한 향기가 <br>입속에 살며시 스며 <br>시원한 공기가 <br>입속에 살며시 스며 <br>내곁을 떠나지마 <br>널느끼는 이 순간이 좋아 <br>멈출수 없자나 <br>그래서 이제 나는 다시한번 <br>빨아빨아 아이스크림 <br>빨아빨아 아이스크림 <br>너무좋아 아이스크림 <br>빨아빨아 아이스크림 <br>너무좋아 아이스크림 <br>I like ice cream <br>You like ice cream <br>We like ice cream <br>Everybody like ice cream <br>I like ice cream <br>You like ice cream <br>We like ice cream <br>빨아빨아 아이스크림 <br>빨아빨아 아이스크림 <br>빨아빨아 아이스크림 <br>너무좋아 아이스크림 <br>빨아빨아 아이스크림 <br>너무좋아 아이스크림 <br>]]></content><category term="춘자 (春子)" label="춘자 (春子)"/><category term="빨아빨아 아이스크림" label="빨아빨아 아이스크림"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OTHANKQ_오땡큐/Stay/</id><title>OTHANKQ (오땡큐) - Stay - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:49:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:49:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OTHANKQ_%EC%98%A4%EB%95%A1%ED%81%90/Stay/" title="OTHANKQ (오땡큐) - Stay - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘도 술잔에 난 <br>술대신 널 채우고 <br>지겹게 했던 얘길 <br>또 하면서 널 욕해 <br>잊으려 한두잔씩 <br>비워내도 니가 생각나 <br>우리 좋았었는데 <br>아니 나는 좋았었는데 <br>아무 준비도 없이 떠나가 <br>I wanna stay <br>예전처럼 <br>바람은 감싸 안는데 <br>I wanna stay <br>예전처럼 <br>지낼수 없어 <br>넌 먼지처럼 떠나가 <br>천천히 거슬러 <br>너와 나의 기억을 <br>스치듯 떠오르는 수많았던 <br>warning bell <br>알면서 모르는척 외면했던 <br>못난 지난날 <br>우리 좋았었는데 <br>아니 나는 좋았었는데 <br>아무 준비도 없이 떠나가 <br>I wanna stay <br>예전처럼 <br>바람은 감싸 안는데 <br>I wanna stay <br>예전처럼 <br>지낼수 없어 <br>넌 먼지처럼 떠나가 <br>I know this is a dream <br>아침이면 <br>It was a bad dream <br>제자리로 <br>I know <br>I wanna stay <br>예전처럼 <br>바람은 감싸 안는데 <br>I wanna stay <br>예전처럼 <br>지낼수 없어 <br>넌 먼지처럼 떠나가 <br>I wanna stay <br>예전처럼 <br>바람은 감싸 안는데 <br>I wanna stay <br>예전처럼 <br>지낼수 없어 <br>넌 먼지처럼 떠나가 <br>]]></content><category term="OTHANKQ (오땡큐)" label="OTHANKQ (오땡큐)"/><category term="Stay" label="Stay"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OTHANKQ_오땡큐/너무_이쁘세요_Feat_창우/</id><title>OTHANKQ (오땡큐) - 너무 이쁘세요 (Feat. 창우) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:49:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:49:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OTHANKQ_%EC%98%A4%EB%95%A1%ED%81%90/%EB%84%88%EB%AC%B4_%EC%9D%B4%EC%81%98%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94_Feat_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9A%B0/" title="OTHANKQ (오땡큐) - 너무 이쁘세요 (Feat. 창우) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wanna hold you girl <br>뻔뻔해 보이지만 <br>그딴 건 신경 안 써 난 <br>I wanna hold you girl <br>뻔뻔해 보이지만 <br>그딴 건 신경 안 써 난 <br>톡 까놓고 말할게 <br>나 너에게 관심 있어 <br>처음 본 그 순간 <br>너 하나만 딱 보였어 <br>내 머리 머물러 떠나가질 않아 <br>날 이렇게 만들어 <br>내 성격 좀 들이대는데 <br>넌 생각할거야 <br>대체 무얼 안다 그래 <br>그래 맞아 <br>너에 대해 아는 거 정말 1도 없어 <br>단지 그냥 너는 이뻐 <br>다리도 몸매도 <br>이게 당연한 거야 <br>널 처음 봤으니까 <br>난 다른 놈들과 달라 <br>쭈삣쭈삣 머뭇머뭇 <br>필터 같은건 없어 <br>이쁜 것도 이유 없어 <br>그래 다른 놈들과 달라 <br>이게 나야 <br>지금 너에게 걸어가고 있어 <br>할말이 있어서 <br>이 말은 꼭 해야겠어 <br>아무 이유 없어도 <br>넌 이 말을 들을 가치가 <br>충분히 있다고 생각해 <br>정말 너무 이쁘세요 <br>I wanna hold you girl <br>뻔뻔해 보이지만 <br>그딴 건 신경 안 써 난 <br>I wanna hold you girl <br>뻔뻔해 보이지만 <br>그딴 건 신경 안 써 난 <br>미안 많이 당황했죠 <br>밑도 끝도 없죠 <br>이 말이 하고 싶었어요 <br>당신 너무 이뻐요 <br>그렇다고 내 여친이 되 달라는 <br>말은 아니에요 <br>부담 갖지 않아도 되니 <br>그냥 그렇다는 거에요 <br>싱거운 놈일 수도 있어 내가 <br>But 속마음은 <br>널 갖겠다는 야수 <br>하지만 오늘은 너의 미소 <br>하나로 만족하는 <br>I'm a gentle man <br>뻔뻔한 놈도 <br>막 들이대지는 않아 <br>기분 좋은 말로 일단 <br>너를 웃게 만들어놔 <br>싱거운 놈 인척 <br>실없는 놈 인척 <br>나의 센스 하나로 <br>너의 긴장을 싹 풀어놔 <br>다시 너에게 걸어가고 <br>아무 대책이 없어도 go <br>시선이 멈춰서고 <br>신경이 쓰이는 건 <br>다시 봐도 정말 <br>너무 이쁘세요 <br>I wanna hold you girl <br>뻔뻔해 보이지만 <br>그딴 건 신경 안 써 난 <br>I wanna hold you girl <br>뻔뻔해 보이지만 <br>그딴 건 신경 안 써 난 <br>I think I'm little <br>난 좀 뻔뻔해 <br>내 맘에 가두고 싶어 <br>I think I'm little <br>난 좀 뻔뻔해 <br>내 맘에 가두고 싶어 <br>I wanna hold you girl <br>뻔뻔해 보이지만 <br>그딴 건 신경 안 써 난 <br>I wanna hold you girl <br>뻔뻔해 보이지만 <br>그딴 건 신경 안 써 난 <br>I wanna hold you girl <br>뻔뻔해 보이지만 <br>그딴 건 신경 안 써 난 <br>I wanna hold you girl <br>뻔뻔해 보이지만 <br>그딴 건 신경 안 써 난 <br>]]></content><category term="OTHANKQ (오땡큐)" label="OTHANKQ (오땡큐)"/><category term="너무 이쁘세요 (Feat. 창우)" label="너무 이쁘세요 (Feat. 창우)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤용빈/꺼내지_못한_말/</id><title>윤용빈 - 꺼내지 못한 말 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:49:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:49:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%9A%A9%EB%B9%88/%EA%BA%BC%EB%82%B4%EC%A7%80_%EB%AA%BB%ED%95%9C_%EB%A7%90/" title="윤용빈 - 꺼내지 못한 말 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루가 지나갈 때쯤 <br>너의 목소리가 <br>내 귓가에 맴돈다 <br>아침에 눈을 뜨고 나면 <br>날 보고 웃어주던 <br>니 모습이 눈에 <br>아른거린다 <br>가끔씩 그리운 마음으로 <br>거리를 걸을 때 <br>나 없이도 <br>살 수 있다고 말하던 <br>니가 계속 생각나 <br>내가 널 널 널 정말 <br>사랑해 사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>지나간 추억까지도 <br>내가 널 널 널 정말 <br>사랑해 널 위해 <br>아껴두고 꺼내지 못한 말 <br>나 이제 말할게 널 사랑해 <br>아픔을 잊어갈 때쯤 <br>다시 저 멀리서 <br>니 얼굴이 보인다 <br>아무리 눈을 감아봐도 <br>내 귀를 막아도 <br>거리에서 니 소식이 들린다 <br>가끔씩 가슴 저미어와 <br>니가 날 떠날 때 <br>나 없이도 살 수 있다고 <br>말하던 니가 계속 생각나 <br>내가 널 널 널 정말 <br>사랑해 사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>잊혀진 기억까지도 <br>내가 널 널 널 정말 <br>사랑해 널 위해 <br>아껴두고 꺼내지 못한 말 <br>나 이제 말할게 널 사랑해 <br>괜찮아질 거란 <br>내 거짓말도 <br>니 앞에서 차마 <br>말 못했던 내 진심들도 <br>일년이면 십 년이면 <br>그저 사라지겠죠 <br>점점 희미해지는 <br>저 별처럼 <br>내가 널 널 널 정말 <br>사랑해 사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>천 번도 해주고픈 말 <br>내가 널 널 널 정말 <br>사랑해 널 위해 <br>아껴두고 꺼내지 못한 말 <br>나 이제 말할게 널 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="윤용빈" label="윤용빈"/><category term="꺼내지 못한 말" label="꺼내지 못한 말"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Liam_Cacatian_Thomassen/Playing_With_Fire/</id><title>Liam Cacatian Thomassen - Playing With Fire - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:49:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:49:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Liam_Cacatian_Thomassen/Playing_With_Fire/" title="Liam Cacatian Thomassen - Playing With Fire - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Uhh <br>Yeah Yeah Yeah <br>Lights burning, see it through the tunnel <br>So close now, baby everything on that <br>We will get there, when we're over another <br>So don't bother, ever try to hold us back <br><br>We used to always say that, we'd be royals on the throne <br>And though I'm always running <br>Yeah, that far away from home <br>I'm chasing after something <br>I know I'm not alone <br>I make myself a promise, and I'm never let them go <br><br>Playing with fire, matches and lighters <br>Down to the wire, let it go <br>Don't let it go <br>Playing with fire, all our desires <br>Down to the wire, let it go <br>Don't let it go <br>Don't let it go <br>Don't let it go <br><br>LAK gliders starting up fires <br>Gets brighter, all we ever wanna do <br>That wombush living for the hairbrush <br>Can't touch us <br>We are gonna see this through <br><br>We used to always say that, we'd be royals on the throne <br>And though I'm always running <br>Yeah, that far away from home <br>I'm chasing after something <br>I know I'm not alone <br>I make myself a promise, and I'm never let them go <br><br>Playing with fire, matches and lighters <br>Down to the wire, let it go <br>Don't let it go <br>Playing with fire, all our desires <br>Down to the wire, let it go <br>Don't let it go <br>Don't let it go <br>Uhh <br>Don't let it go <br><br>Playing with fire, matches and lighters <br>Down to the wire, let it go <br>Don't let it go <br>Playing with fire, all our desires <br>Down to the wire, let it go <br>Don't let it go <br>Don't let it go <br>Uhh <br>Don't let it go <br>Don't let it go]]></content><category term="Liam Cacatian Thomassen" label="Liam Cacatian Thomassen"/><category term="Playing With Fire" label="Playing With Fire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엄정화/버들숲/</id><title>엄정화 - 버들숲 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:49:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:49:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%84%EC%A0%95%ED%99%94/%EB%B2%84%EB%93%A4%EC%88%B2/" title="엄정화 - 버들숲 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나른해 눈을 감을 때 아스라이 <br>달콤한 노래가 귓가를 어질러 <br>못참게 해 <br>버들 수풀 사이로 아름다운 멜로 <br>잠이 덜 깬듯 몽롱해지네 <br>너의 리듬이 uh uhuh <br>내 몸을 감싸네 uh uhuh <br>달빛의 노래 부드럽게 <br>내게만 속삭여줘 <br>너의 선율에 uh uhuh <br>내 맘은 춤추네 uh uhuh <br>색다른 곳에 <br>화려한 그림을 채우고 싶어 <br>가볍게 눈을 맞출 때 아련히 <br>알듯 말듯하게 <br>맘 속을 헤집어 미치게 해 <br>버들 수풀 사이로 아름다운 멜로 <br>잠이 덜 깬 듯 몽롱해지네 <br>너의 리듬이 uh uhuh <br>내 몸을 감싸네 uh uhuh <br>달빛의 노래 부드럽게 <br>내게만 속삭여줘 <br>너의 선율에 uh uhuh <br>내 맘은 춤추네 uh uhuh <br>색다른 곳에 <br>화려한 그림을 채우고 싶어 <br>환상일까 <br>사라질까 <br>구름너머 <br>날 데려가줘 <br>너의 사랑이 uh uhuh <br>내 안에 꽃피네 uh uhuh <br>더 늦기 전에 <br>너의 낙원으로 날 데려가줘 <br>너의 선율에 uh uhuh <br>내 맘은 춤추네 uh uhuh <br>색다른 곳에 <br>화려한 그림을 채우고 싶어 <br>환상일까 <br>구름너머 <br>]]></content><category term="엄정화" label="엄정화"/><category term="버들숲" label="버들숲"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엄정화/Watch_Me_Move/</id><title>엄정화 - Watch Me Move - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:49:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:49:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%84%EC%A0%95%ED%99%94/Watch_Me_Move/" title="엄정화 - Watch Me Move - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[my eyes 짙게 물든 저 하늘에 <br>외로움 안고 <br>조용히 달콤하게 노래하던 lips <br>노래 부르던 lips <br>시린 내 손끝부터 더 식어가 <br>온몸을 감싸고 <br>and my heartbeat <br>숨이 막혀 날 데려가 <br>데려가 나를 <br>나를 담았던 모든 걸 점점 잃어가 <br>점점 모든 걸 잃어가 <br>어느 누구도 나를 찾지 않아 <br>눈을 감아 난 <br>달빛이 다가와 <br>watch me move watch me move <br>난 다시 깨어나 꽃은 피어나 <br>watch me move watch me move <br>순간은 빛이나 지금 너와 나 <br>watch me move <br>my dreams <br>흔적도 없이 부서져 <br>흔적 하나 없이 <br>go away <br>사라지는 내 그림자 <br>그림잔 사라져 <br>저기 자그만 한줄기 빛을 쫓아가 <br>저기 저 빛을 쫓아가 <br>이 선을 넘어 이젠 날 따라와 <br>좀더 특별한 <br>너만을 보여봐 <br>watch me move watch me move <br>난 다시 깨어나 꽃은 피어나 <br>watch me move watch me move <br>순간은 빛이나 지금 너와 나 <br>watch me move <br>갈라진 저 틈 사이 <br>초대를 또 시작해 <br>조금씩 날 끌어당길래 <br>깊어져 가 <br>쏟아지는 빛 사이 <br>신세계를 또 경험해 <br>온 세상에 나만 채울래 <br>변해가 <br>watch me move watch me move <br>내 빛은 터져와 여기 피어나 <br>watch me move watch me move <br>찰나로 스쳐가 지금 너와 나 <br>watch me move <br>watch me move <br>눈뜨면 거품처럼 <br>난 흔적 없이 사라져 <br>watch me move <br>눈감고 더 느껴봐 <br>오늘만 네게 녹아줘 <br>watch me move <br>]]></content><category term="엄정화" label="엄정화"/><category term="Watch Me Move" label="Watch Me Move"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엄정화/Dreamer/</id><title>엄정화 - Dreamer - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:49:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:49:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%84%EC%A0%95%ED%99%94/Dreamer/" title="엄정화 - Dreamer - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[boy don’t you cry <br>never never cry <br>boy don’t you cry <br>maybe everything is alright <br>거짓말처럼 예뻐 <br>내 품에 잠든 니 모습 <br>솔직히 나도 슬퍼 <br>여기까지란 생각에 <br>첫 번째 밤 우린 참 <br>궁금한 게 많았었지 <br>나 하나 너 하나 <br>보여주면서 <br>두 번째 그 밤 <br>더 이상은 뛰지 않던 <br>가슴이 너무 미안했어 <br>boy don’t you cry <br>don’t you ever ever cry <br>그 땐 누구보다 <br>널 사랑했던 나잖아 <br>dreamer dreamer <br>내 깊은 꿈속에 <br>니가 잠시 <br>왔다가는 것뿐이야 <br>I love your face when you cry <br>but you never never know <br>마치 모든 걸 잃은 <br>어린 아이 같잖아 <br>dreamer dreamer <br>더 깊은 꿈을 꿔 <br>그 밤 다시 올지 몰라 <br>그때까진 goodbye <br>do you wanna love again <br>do you wanna play again <br>니 맘대로 해도 돼 <br>우리 지난 얘기들은 <br>어차피 멋대로 <br>퍼질 말들 <br>두 사람 중에 한 명은 <br>나쁜 거라면 <br>아마도 내가 아니겠니 <br>boy don’t you cry <br>don’t you ever ever cry <br>그 땐 누구보다 <br>널 사랑했던 나잖아 <br>dreamer dreamer <br>내 깊은 꿈속에 <br>니가 잠시 <br>왔다가는 것뿐이야 <br>I love your face when you cry <br>but you never never know <br>마치 모든 걸 잃은 <br>어린 아이 같잖아 <br>dreamer dreamer <br>더 깊은 꿈을 꿔 <br>그 밤 다시 올지 몰라 <br>그때까진 <br>가까이선 많은 게 <br>내겐 아름답질 않아 <br>모든 게 다 꿈속의 <br>해프닝이라면 좋겠어 <br>boy don’t you cry <br>don’t you ever ever cry <br>그 땐 누구보다 <br>널 사랑했던 나잖아 <br>dreamer dreamer <br>내 깊은 꿈속에 <br>니가 잠시 <br>왔다가는 것뿐이야 <br>I love your face when you cry <br>but you never never know <br>마치 모든 걸 잃은 <br>어린 아이 같잖아 <br>dreamer dreamer <br>더 깊은 꿈을 꿔 <br>그 밤 다시 올지 몰라 <br>그때까진 goodbye <br>]]></content><category term="엄정화" label="엄정화"/><category term="Dreamer" label="Dreamer"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엄정화/Oh_Yeah_Feat_종현/</id><title>엄정화 - Oh Yeah (Feat. 종현) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:49:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:49:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%84%EC%A0%95%ED%99%94/Oh_Yeah_Feat_%EC%A2%85%ED%98%84/" title="엄정화 - Oh Yeah (Feat. 종현) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[oh yeah <br>사랑한단 말보다 <br>더 기막힌 건 없을걸 <br>너무 달기만 해서 <br>만질 수도 없을걸 <br>사랑한단 말보다 <br>더 기막힌 건 없을걸 <br>I just wanna make it sure <br>정말 답답해 <br>사랑은 영원함이 아냐 <br>잠깐 머물다 가는 <br>머릿속의 장난일지 몰라 <br>아냐 내 맘속에 있던 <br>모든 신경 <br>전부 다 엉켜버린 풍경 <br>이 매듭을 푸는 건 <br>사랑 말곤 없을 거야 <br>oh yeah <br>사랑한단 말보다 <br>더 기막힌 건 없을걸 <br>너무 달기만 해서 <br>만질 수도 없을걸 <br>사랑한단 말보다 <br>더 기막힌 건 없을걸 <br>I just wanna make it sure <br>우연 속에서 <br>어쩌다 만들어진 순간 <br>잠시 취하고 싶은 <br>기분 좋은 거짓말인 거야 <br>아냐 어느 때보다도 <br>너무 선명한 <br>기분 설명할 순 없고 <br>당황스런 니 맘은 <br>나중으로 미뤄줄래 <br>oh <br>oh yeah <br>사랑한단 말보다 <br>더 기막힌 건 없을걸 <br>너무 달기만 해서 <br>만질 수도 없을걸 <br>사랑한단 말보다 <br>더 기막힌 건 없을걸 <br>I just wanna make it sure <br>yes please <br>사랑한단 말보다 <br>더 기막힌 건 없을걸 <br>yes please <br>사랑한단 말보다 <br>더 기막힌 건 없을걸 <br>oh yeah <br>사랑한단 말보다 <br>더 기막힌 건 없을걸 <br>I just wanna make it sure <br>oh-yeah <br>날 잡아봐 어서 baby <br>날 잡아봐 어서 baby <br>날 잡아봐 어서 baby <br>uh uh baby <br>날 잡아봐 어서 baby <br>날 잡아봐 어서 baby <br>날 잡아봐 어서 baby <br>uh uh baby <br>날 잡아봐 어서 baby <br>날 잡아봐 어서 baby <br>날 잡아봐 어서 baby <br>uh uh baby <br>날 잡아봐 어서 baby <br>날 잡아봐 어서 baby <br>날 잡아봐 어서 baby <br>uh uh baby <br>]]></content><category term="엄정화" label="엄정화"/><category term="Oh Yeah (Feat. 종현)" label="Oh Yeah (Feat. 종현)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/진원/So_Beautiful_Inst/</id><title>진원 - So Beautiful (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:49:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:49:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%84%EC%9B%90/So_Beautiful_Inst/" title="진원 - So Beautiful (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보일 리가 없는 어둠 속의 길에서 <br>멈춰 주지 않는 시간이란 틈에서 <br>그대 힘든가요 <br>반짝이지 않는 거울 속의 모습에 <br>아무 표정 없이 살아가는 시간에 <br>그대 아파하나요 <br>눈 감아요 지금 이 순간은 <br>내 목소리 들어봐요 <br>you're so beautiful <br>내 뒤에 숨어요 그댈 지켜줄게요 <br>나만 봐요 날 믿어요 <br>you're so beautiful <br>baby you're so beautiful <br>자꾸 흐려지는 기억 속의 꿈들을 <br>빛을 잃어가는 마음속의 촛불을 <br>잊지는 말아요 <br>매일 지쳐가는 그대 하루 끝에서 <br>잔뜩 움츠러든 그대 어깨 뒤에서 <br>내가 안아줄게요 <br>눈 감아요 지금 이 순간은 <br>내 목소리 들어봐요 <br>you're so beautiful <br>내 뒤에 숨어요 그댈 지켜줄게요 <br>나만 봐요 날 믿어요 <br>you're so beautiful <br>baby you're so beautiful <br>beautiful beautiful <br>아름다운 그대가 웃네요 <br>언제나 늘 지금처럼 <br>you're so beautiful <br>내 말만 믿어요 늘 지켜줄게요 <br>아름다운 사랑스러운 <br>그대 모습을 <br>baby you're so beautiful <br>baby you're so beautiful <br>]]></content><category term="진원" label="진원"/><category term="So Beautiful (Inst.)" label="So Beautiful (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/진원/So_Beautiful/</id><title>진원 - So Beautiful - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:49:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:49:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%84%EC%9B%90/So_Beautiful/" title="진원 - So Beautiful - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보일 리가 없는 어둠 속의 길에서 <br>멈춰 주지 않는 시간이란 틈에서 <br>그대 힘든가요 <br>반짝이지 않는 거울 속의 모습에 <br>아무 표정 없이 살아가는 시간에 <br>그대 아파하나요 <br>눈 감아요 지금 이 순간은 <br>내 목소리 들어봐요 <br>you're so beautiful <br>내 뒤에 숨어요 그댈 지켜줄게요 <br>나만 봐요 날 믿어요 <br>you're so beautiful <br>baby you're so beautiful <br>자꾸 흐려지는 기억 속의 꿈들을 <br>빛을 잃어가는 마음속의 촛불을 <br>잊지는 말아요 <br>매일 지쳐가는 그대 하루 끝에서 <br>잔뜩 움츠러든 그대 어깨 뒤에서 <br>내가 안아줄게요 <br>눈 감아요 지금 이 순간은 <br>내 목소리 들어봐요 <br>you're so beautiful <br>내 뒤에 숨어요 그댈 지켜줄게요 <br>나만 봐요 날 믿어요 <br>you're so beautiful <br>baby you're so beautiful <br>beautiful beautiful <br>아름다운 그대가 웃네요 <br>언제나 늘 지금처럼 <br>you're so beautiful <br>내 말만 믿어요 늘 지켜줄게요 <br>아름다운 사랑스러운 <br>그대 모습을 <br>baby you're so beautiful <br>baby you're so beautiful <br>]]></content><category term="진원" label="진원"/><category term="So Beautiful" label="So Beautiful"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리즈/1234_Lalalala/</id><title>리즈 - 1234 Lalalala - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:50:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:50:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EC%A6%88/1234_Lalalala/" title="리즈 - 1234 Lalalala - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The brightest light <br>of shiny Star Rise <br>Gazing me embracing me <br>Clear sanity <br>the iron shields <br>Guarding me awaking me <br>A falling leaf turns <br>to a golden bird <br>Takes a journey to Venus <br>The Phoenix shall pass it <br>on to me <br>The key I am longing for <br>One step closer <br>to my heart to heal <br>One step closer <br>to my soul to cheer <br>Me the lonely odd <br>one full of uncertain tales <br>Singing me reciting magic spells <br>1234 1234 1234 lalalala <br>1234 1234 lalalala <br>1234 1234 lalalala <br>1234 1234 <br>A falling leaf turns <br>to a golden bird <br>Takes a journey to Venus <br>The Phoenix shall pass it <br>on to me <br>The key I am longing for <br>One step closer <br>to my heart to heal <br>One step closer <br>to my soul to cheer <br>Me the lonely odd <br>one full of uncertain tales <br>Singing me reciting magic spells <br>Oh my Destiny starry Destiny <br>Bring me hope bring me <br>joy bring me love <br>Fairy Fate <br>Oh my Destiny starry Destiny <br>Bring me hope bring me <br>joy bring me love <br>Fairy Fate <br>Please do <br>1234 1234 1234 lalalala <br>1234 1234 lalalala <br>1234 1234 lalalala <br>1234 1234 <br>1234 1234 1234 lalalala <br>1234 1234 lalalala <br>1234 1234 lalalala <br>1234 1234 <br>]]></content><category term="리즈" label="리즈"/><category term="1234 Lalalala" label="1234 Lalalala"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소울_페이퍼/물고기_같아_Vocal_한올/</id><title>소울 페이퍼 - 물고기 같아 (Vocal 한올) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:50:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:50:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EC%9A%B8_%ED%8E%98%EC%9D%B4%ED%8D%BC/%EB%AC%BC%EA%B3%A0%EA%B8%B0_%EA%B0%99%EC%95%84_Vocal_%ED%95%9C%EC%98%AC/" title="소울 페이퍼 - 물고기 같아 (Vocal 한올) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[숨조차도 쉴 수가 없는 <br>캄캄한 이곳에 나를 놓아주던 너 <br>그래야 행복해진다는 그 말을 <br>난 믿어버렸어 <br>나 요즘 하루 종일 짠 내만 느껴져 <br>잊으려 무리를 지어 돌아다녀도 <br>정작 하루의 끝은 맴돌고 돌아 <br>남은 건 네 이름뿐 <br>사랑이 너무 깊었나 봐 <br>오늘도 아픔에 이렇게 <br>잠겨있는 걸 보면 난 괜찮을까 <br>너 없이 난 물고기 같아 <br>저 풍경에 매달려 바람에 춤추는 <br>그냥 물고기 같아 <br>하루 종일 두 눈이 시려와 <br>시간을 거슬러 기억을 지워봐도 <br>끝내 우리가 있었던 <br>그 시절을 떠올려내고 있어 <br>사랑이 너무 깊었나 봐 <br>오늘도 아픔에 이렇게 <br>잠겨있는 걸 보면 난 괜찮을까 <br>너 없이 난 물고기 같아 <br>저 풍경에 매달려 바람에 춤추는 <br>작은 물고기 <br>그 언젠가 그 어디선가 <br>아름다운 추억에 잠겨서 울 때면 <br>가끔 내게 있어줘 <br>]]></content><category term="소울 페이퍼" label="소울 페이퍼"/><category term="물고기 같아 (Vocal 한올)" label="물고기 같아 (Vocal 한올)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/성유진/안개속으로/</id><title>성유진 - 안개속으로 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:50:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:50:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%B1%EC%9C%A0%EC%A7%84/%EC%95%88%EA%B0%9C%EC%86%8D%EC%9C%BC%EB%A1%9C/" title="성유진 - 안개속으로 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[저 구름 틈으로 스며드는 <br>별빛들은 내 길을 비추네 <br>희미하게 희미하게 <br>내 길 비추네 <br>마치 안개 속에서 헤매는 듯 해 <br>불안함 속에서 사는 듯해도 <br>희미하지만 한걸음 내딜 때 <br>그 길은 선명해질 거야 <br>구름은 바람을 타고 걷히겠지 <br>별빛은 더 환하게 날 비추겠지 <br>그 시간 꼭 올 거야 <br>멈추지 말고 달려가 <br>마치 안개 속에서 헤매는 듯 해 <br>불안함 속에서 사는 듯해도 <br>희미하지만 한걸음 내딜 때 <br>그 길은 선명해질 거야 <br>구름은 바람을 타고 걷히겠지 <br>별빛은 더 환하게 날 비추겠지 <br>그 시간 꼭 올 거야 <br>멈추지 말고 달려가 <br>아침이 오면 더 밝은 태양이 <br>널 비추고 구름은 <br>나를 쉬게 하는 <br>그 곳에 있을 거야 <br>여전히 거기 있다면 <br>]]></content><category term="성유진" label="성유진"/><category term="안개속으로" label="안개속으로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ricky_Martin/Vente_Pa_Ca_Feat_웬디_Of_레드벨벳/</id><title>Ricky Martin - Vente Pa` Ca (Feat. 웬디 Of 레드벨벳) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:50:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:50:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ricky_Martin/Vente_Pa_Ca_Feat_%EC%9B%AC%EB%94%94_Of_%EB%A0%88%EB%93%9C%EB%B2%A8%EB%B2%B3/" title="Ricky Martin - Vente Pa` Ca (Feat. 웬디 Of 레드벨벳) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Say you like me <br>one more time <br>And I won't care about <br>the troubles in my life <br>Say you want me <br>you'd be mine <br>When the sunlight <br>is reflected in your eyes <br>Oh baby I <br>I wanna know <br>Are we for real <br>Some kind of dream <br>I I wanna know <br>Now can you feel <br>the way that I feel <br>If you want me <br>like I want you baby <br>I won't live without you <br>We've been through <br>the morning light <br>If you're thinking <br>what I'm thinking <br>and you're drinking <br>what I'm drinking <br>Then it's all right <br>If you want me <br>like I want you <br>Baby I won't live without you <br>Let our dreams come <br>through tonight <br>Vente pa' ca <br>Vente pa' ca <br>Vente pa' ca oh oh <br>Don't tomorrow <br>Just tonight <br>Yet together we could leave <br>the world behind <br>In the starlight we will shine <br>Secret lovers <br>in the secret paradise <br>Oh baby I <br>I wanna know <br>Are we for real <br>Some kind of dream <br>Oh I I wanna know <br>Now can you feel <br>the way that I feel <br>If you want me <br>like I want you baby <br>I won't live without you <br>We've been through <br>the morning light <br>If you're thinking <br>what I'm thinking <br>and you're drinking <br>what I'm drinking <br>Then it's all right <br>If you want me <br>like I want you <br>Baby I won't live without you <br>Let our dreams come <br>through tonight <br>Vente pa' ca <br>Vente pa' ca <br>Vente pa' ca oh oh <br>Baby touch me <br>Hold me in this dream <br>And never wake me up <br>don't ever wake me up <br>With every heartbeat <br>I'm falling even deeper <br>I don't wanna stop <br>I can't never get enough <br>Say you want me <br>Say you need me yeah <br>I can't wait no more <br>I gotta know <br>If you want me <br>like I want you baby <br>I won't live without you <br>We've been through <br>the morning light <br>If you're thinking <br>what I'm thinking <br>and you're drinking <br>what I'm drinking <br>Then it's all right <br>If you want me <br>like I want you <br>Baby I won't live without you <br>Let our dreams come <br>through tonight <br>Vente pa' ca <br>Vente pa' ca <br>Vente pa' ca oh oh <br>Vente pa' ca <br>Vente pa' ca <br>Vente pa' ca oh oh <br>]]></content><category term="Ricky Martin" label="Ricky Martin"/><category term="Vente Pa` Ca (Feat. 웬디 Of 레드벨벳)" label="Vente Pa` Ca (Feat. 웬디 Of 레드벨벳)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pentatonix/Hallelujah/</id><title>Pentatonix - Hallelujah - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:50:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:50:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pentatonix/Hallelujah/" title="Pentatonix - Hallelujah - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've heard there was a secret chord <br>That David played and it pleased the Lord <br>But you don't really care for music, do ya? <br>Well it goes like this <br>The fourth, the fifth, the minor fall, the major lift <br>The baffled king composing Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br><br>Well, your faith was strong but you needed proof <br>You saw her bathing on the roof <br>Her beauty in the moonlight overthrew ya <br>She tied you to the kitchen chair <br>She broke your throne and she cut your hair <br>And from your lips, she drew the Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br><br>Well baby I've been here before <br>I've seen this room and I've walked this floor <br>I used to live alone before I knew ya <br>And I've seen your flag on the marble arch <br>And love is not a vict'ry march <br>It's a cold and it's a broken Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br><br>Well, maybe there's a God above <br>But all I've ever learned from love <br>Was how to shoot somebody who outdrew ya <br>And it's not a cry that you hear at night <br>It's not somebody who's seen the light <br>It's a cold and it's a broken Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br><br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah <br>Hallelujah, Hallelujah]]></content><category term="Pentatonix" label="Pentatonix"/><category term="Hallelujah" label="Hallelujah"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Christopher/World_Without_Super_Man/</id><title>Luke Christopher - World Without Super Man - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:50:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:50:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Christopher/World_Without_Super_Man/" title="Luke Christopher - World Without Super Man - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh woah woah <br>I’m a man but I’m no superman <br>All these people they need saving, baby <br>Cause life’s too crazy <br>If they turn around and I’m not there then what are they gonna do? <br><br>This one girl, she says I’m not as mean as I seem <br>My pictures make me look like I’m a fiend <br>She thinks the people I've, I know better <br>So I’m sorry if I scream <br>Fuck it all, cover your ears, my people <br>I’m just embarrassed just to fear my people <br>How am I supposed to be honest with the world <br>When I still haven’t been able to be honest with a girl? <br>So middle finger to the way that love treats me <br>Nigga with a flow like "how my muthafuckin' beat be?" <br>Ain’t it ironic how that every girl that leaves me <br>Week later sees me, got the nerve to tweet me <br>If Twitter be the fuit of fame, tweet on man <br>But I ain’t Tweetin’ if the damn beat’s on man <br>And if you’re smokin’ like them damn trees on <br>I ain't like that, I put a future Grammy on that <br><br>Oh woah woah <br>I’m a man but I’m no superman <br>All these people they need saving, baby <br>Cause life’s too crazy <br>If they turn around and I’m not there then what are they gonna do? <br><br>How do they say a little rain have never hurt nobody? <br>I’ve gotta say that philosophy ain’t been workin’ for me <br>Cuz lately it’s been pourin’ round here girl <br>Better yet, straight stormin’ ‘round here, girl <br>And I’ve been tryin’ to apologize in my way <br>Instead of doing what these niggas do and hide away <br>Far away, or behind a face <br>And try to make it seem like everything’s okay <br>You liar, you hider <br>You tried to defy me but found out it’s back where it used to be <br>It’s crazy how people get lazy and think they can play me by using me <br>You’ve got a one track mind: Vanilla ice <br>But one track's all you need on the realest nights <br>You’d be surprised, kill the lights <br>Put your headphones on and get hypnotized <br><br>Oh woah woah <br>I’m a man but I’m no superman <br>All these people they need saving, baby <br>Cause life’s too crazy <br>If they turn around and I’m not there then what are they gonna do?]]></content><category term="Luke Christopher" label="Luke Christopher"/><category term="World Without Super Man" label="World Without Super Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fifth_Harmony/Better_Together/</id><title>Fifth Harmony - Better Together - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:50:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:50:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fifth_Harmony/Better_Together/" title="Fifth Harmony - Better Together - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When we were together <br>We were just strangers <br>I was just playing around <br>So I didn't wanna work it out <br>No, I didn't wanna work it out <br><br>Thought something was missing <br>Were we too different <br>Baby I'm a-looking back now <br>And I really should've worked it out <br>Yeah, I really should've worked it out <br><br>Because now that you're gone and I sleep alone <br>I can't help it, I want you back 'cause I... <br><br>Boy I miss you, said I really do, boy I miss you <br>Now I understand that we're better together <br>Boy I miss you, said I really really do, boy I miss you <br>Now I understand that we're better together <br><br>We're better, we're better, we're better, we're better, we're better <br>You know we're better together <br>We're better, we're better, we're better, we're better, we're better <br>You know we're better together <br><br>I'm watching you with her, thinking I had you <br>How was I ever so dumb? <br>Boy I should've known that you're the one <br>Boy I should've known that you're the one <br><br>So, if it's not too late <br>I just wanna know babe <br><br>And tell me if we could still run <br>'Cause I finally know that you're the one <br>Yeah, I really know that you're the one <br><br>Because now that you're gone and I sleep alone <br>I can't help it, I want you back 'cause I... <br><br>Boy I miss you, said I really do, boy I miss you <br>Now I understand that we're better together <br>Boy I miss you, said I really really do, boy I miss you <br>Now I understand that we're better together <br><br>We're better, we're better, we're better, we're better, we're better <br>You know we're better together <br>We're better, we're better, we're better, we're better, we're better <br>You know we're better together <br><br>And now that you're gone and I sleep alone <br>I can't help it, I want you back 'cause I <br><br>We're better, we're better, we're better, we're better, we're better <br>You know we're better together <br>We're better, we're better, we're better, we're better, we're better <br>You know we're better together <br><br>Boy I miss you, said I really do, boy I miss you <br>Now I understand that we're better together <br>Boy I miss you, said I really really do, boy I miss you <br>Now I understand that we're better together <br><br>We're better, we're better, we're better, we're better, we're better <br>You know we're better together <br>We're better, we're better, we're better, we're better, we're better <br>You know we're better together]]></content><category term="Fifth Harmony" label="Fifth Harmony"/><category term="Better Together" label="Better Together"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Miley_Cyrus/Hands_Of_Love/</id><title>Miley Cyrus - Hands Of Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:50:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:50:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Miley_Cyrus/Hands_Of_Love/" title="Miley Cyrus - Hands Of Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When the white flag sails, covered in streaks of blood <br>There'll be an endless sea, of us rising up <br>And the preacher man, and the preacher's son <br>Will stand arm in arm, just like everyone <br><br>Me longing to be free, I won't let you fade away <br>We shed so many dreams, I'll let them fade away <br><br>In the hands of love, we carry on <br>Stronger than we started <br>Be ashamed of the trail behind us <br>Wicked is the blinded <br>Who we are comes to life, yeah <br>Who we are comes to life <br><br>When the water spills, the glass will break <br>It drips like tears, running up your face <br>And the hounds will cry, for the dance of war <br>But the sons of joy, their victory will soar <br><br>Me longing to be free, I won't let you fade away <br>We shed so many dreams, I'll let them fade away <br><br>In the hands of love, we carry on <br>Stronger than we started <br>Be ashamed of the trail behind us <br>Wicked is the blinded <br>Who we are comes to life, yeah <br>Who we are comes to life <br><br>Me longing to be free, I won't let you fade away <br><br>In the hands of love, we carry on <br>Stronger that we started <br>Be ashamed of the trail behind us <br>Wicked is the blinded <br>Who we are comes to life, yeah <br>Who we are comes to life <br><br>We come alive <br>We come alive <br>We come alive <br>We come alive <br>We come to life]]></content><category term="Miley Cyrus" label="Miley Cyrus"/><category term="Hands Of Love" label="Hands Of Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Paloma_Faith/Just_Be/</id><title>Paloma Faith - Just Be - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:50:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:50:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Paloma_Faith/Just_Be/" title="Paloma Faith - Just Be - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let's get old together <br>Let's be unhappy forever <br>Cause there's no one else in this world <br>That I'd rather be unhappy with <br>Let's be exposed and unprotected <br>Let's see one another when we're weak <br>Let's go our separate ways in the night <br>Like two moths <br>But know that you're flying home to me. <br><br>I was born thinking <br>It would all be dreamy <br>But I know that I wouldn't be happy that way <br>You wear me out with frustration and heartache and anger <br>But we wait for the wave just to wash it away <br><br>Don't say nothing <br>Just sit next to me <br>Don't say nothing <br>Shhh <br>Just be, just be, just be. <br><br>Let's let go together <br>Let us unfold one another <br>And watch all the little things that once drew me to you <br>Eventually get on my nerves <br><br>I wear you out with frustration and heartache and anger <br>But we wait for the wave just to wash it away <br><br>Don't say nothing <br>Just sit next to me <br>Don't say nothing <br>Shhh <br>Just be, just be, just be. <br><br>When you're sick of the every day oh <br>When you're tired of my voice <br>When you tell me <br>You'll walk out that door <br>That's when I know that you'll stay. <br><br>Don't say nothing <br>Just sit next to me <br>Don't say nothing <br>Just be, just be <br>Just don't say nothing <br>Just sit next to me <br>Don't say nothing <br>Just be, just be, just be. <br><br>Don't say nothing <br>Shhhhh.]]></content><category term="Paloma Faith" label="Paloma Faith"/><category term="Just Be" label="Just Be"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/Shadow_Days/</id><title>John Mayer - Shadow Days - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Mayer/Shadow_Days/" title="John Mayer - Shadow Days - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know <br>that you could be wrong <br>And swear you're right <br>Some people been known to do it <br>All their lives <br>But you find yourself alone <br>Just like you found yourself before <br>Like I found myself in pieces <br>On the hotel floor <br>Hard times help me see <br>I'm a good man with a good heart <br>Had a tough time <br>got a rough start <br>But I finally learned to let it go <br>Now I'm right here <br>and I'm right now <br>And I'm open <br>knowing somehow <br>That my shadow days are over <br>My shadow days are over now <br>Well I ain't no trouble maker <br>And I never meant her harm <br>But it doesn't mean I didn't make it <br>Hard to carry on <br>Well it sucks to be honest <br>honest <br>And it hurts to be real <br>But it's nice to make some love <br>That I can finally feel <br>Hard times let me be <br>I'm a good man with a good heart <br>Had a tough time <br>got a rough start <br>But I finally learned to let it go <br>Now I'm right here <br>and I'm right now <br>And I'm open <br>knowing somehow <br>That my shadow days are over <br>My shadow days are over now <br>I'm a good man with a good heart <br>Had a tough time <br>got a rough start <br>But I finally learned to let it go <br>Now I'm right here <br>and I'm right now <br>And I'm open <br>knowing somehow <br>That my shadow days are over <br>My shadow days are over now <br>]]></content><category term="John Mayer" label="John Mayer"/><category term="Shadow Days" label="Shadow Days"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/We_Are_Here/</id><title>Alicia Keys - We Are Here - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/We_Are_Here/" title="Alicia Keys - We Are Here - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We are here <br>We are here for all of us <br>We are here for all of us <br>That's why we are here, why we are here <br>We are here <br><br>Bombs over Baghdad, tryna get something we ain't never had <br>Let's start with a good dad <br>So real but it's so sad <br>And while we burnin' this incense, we gon' pray for the innocent <br>Cause right now it don't make sense <br>Right now it don't make sense <br>Let's talk about Chi town <br>Let's talk about Gaza <br>Let's talk about, let's talk about Israel <br>Cause right now it is real <br>Let's talk about, let's talk Nigeria <br>In a mass hysteria, yeah <br>Our souls are brought together so that we could love each other <br>Brother <br><br>We are here <br>We are here for all of us <br>We are here for all of us <br>That's why we are here, why we are here <br>We are here <br><br>No guns made in Harlem, but yet crime is a problem <br>He wanna shine, they wanna rob him <br>Single mother, where they come from? <br>How we gonna save the nation, with no support for education <br>Cause right now it don't make sense <br>Right now it don't make sense <br>Let's talk about our part <br>My heart touch your heart <br>Let's talk about, let's talk about living <br>Had enough of dying, not what we all about <br>Let's do more giving <br>Do more forgiving, yeah <br>Our souls were brought together so that we could love each other <br>Sister <br><br>We are here <br>We are here for all of us <br>We are here for all of us <br>That's why we are here, why we are here <br>We are here <br>We are here for all of us <br>We are here for all of us <br>That's why we are here, why we are here <br>We are here <br>Oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh <br>Oh, oh <br><br>Oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh, oh <br><br>We are here (oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh) <br>We are here for all of us (oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh) <br>(oh, oh) <br>We are here for all of us (oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh) <br>(oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh) <br>that's why we are here, why we are here (oh, oh) <br><br>Cause we are here <br>We are here for all of us <br>We are here for all of us <br>That's why we are here, why we are here <br>We are, here <br>We are here for all of us <br>We are here for all of us <br>That's why we are here <br>Why we are here]]></content><category term="Alicia Keys" label="Alicia Keys"/><category term="We Are Here" label="We Are Here"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christina_Aguilera/Change/</id><title>Christina Aguilera - Change - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christina_Aguilera/Change/" title="Christina Aguilera - Change - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I was young I would look in the mirror <br>Didn't know it then but now it couldn't be clearer <br>That I remember being filled with such wonder <br>Before learnin' that the world can be harsher <br><br>Who you love or the color of your skin <br>Or the place that you were born and grew up in <br>Shouldn't decide how you will be treated <br>Cause we're all the same when everybody's breathing <br><br>Waiting for a change to set us free <br>Waiting for the day when you can be you and I can be me <br>Waiting for hope to come around <br>Waiting for the day when hate is lost and love is found <br>Waiting for a change <br>Waiting for a change <br>(Change, change) <br><br>For all the brave and the souls who went before us <br>Stand tall, be proud and lift your voices <br>Let 'em know who we are and our choices <br>And one day we won't have to sing this chorus <br><br>Waiting for a change to set us free <br>Waiting for the day when you can be you and I can be me <br>Waiting for hope to come around <br>Waiting for the day when hate is lost and love is found <br>Waiting for a change <br>Waiting for a change <br>(Change, change) <br>Hold on <br>Waiting for a change <br>(Change, change) <br><br>When I was young I would look in the mirror <br>Didn't see it then but now it couldn't be clearer]]></content><category term="Christina Aguilera" label="Christina Aguilera"/><category term="Change" label="Change"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/A_Great_Big_World/Hold_Each_Other/</id><title>A Great Big World - Hold Each Other - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/A_Great_Big_World/Hold_Each_Other/" title="A Great Big World - Hold Each Other - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I miss the words we used to say <br>I miss the sounds of yesterday <br>I miss the games we used to play like ohhh <br>I was trapped inside a dream <br>I couldn't see her next to me <br>I didn't know she'd set me free like ohhh <br><br>Something happens when I hold her <br>She keeps my heart from getting older <br>When the days get short and the nights get a little bit colder <br>We hold each other <br>We hold each other <br>We hold each other <br><br>Everything looks different now <br>All this time my head was down <br>He came along and showed me how to let go <br>I can't remember where I'm from <br>All I know is who I've become <br>That our love has just begun like ohhh <br><br>Something happens when I hold him <br>He keeps my heart from getting broken <br>When the days get short and the nights get a little bit frozen <br>We hold each other <br>We hold each other <br>We hold each other <br><br>[Futuristic:] <br>If I'm stressing you that blessing that's sent from heaven <br>These days start to feel like hours and hours feel more like seconds <br>People judged us they couldn't see the connection <br>When I look at you, it's like I'm looking back at my reflection <br>I don't see nothing different, our pigments they coincide <br>We hold each other so tight they couldn't break us if they tried <br>My eyes are those of the blind, I see no color or size <br>I feel the love in your touch and I trust what's inside your mind, ok <br><br>I know that we've been through a lot <br>I know that we both grew up <br>You know I missed you a lot <br>When I was young I was dumb <br>Didn't think you'd fit in my plot <br>And I appreciate the break because I love what we got now <br>You give me chills and I can't imagine you leaving <br>If I could build a perfect person honestly you would be it <br>And you know nobody knows you like I know you <br>I can't wait to come back home so I can hold you <br><br>Something happens when I hold her <br>She keeps my heart from getting older <br>When the days get short and the nights get a little bit colder <br>We hold each other <br>We hold each other <br>We hold each other <br>We hold each other <br>We hold each other <br>We hold each other]]></content><category term="A Great Big World" label="A Great Big World"/><category term="Hold Each Other" label="Hold Each Other"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Aiken/On_My_Way_Here/</id><title>Clay Aiken - On My Way Here - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Aiken/On_My_Way_Here/" title="Clay Aiken - On My Way Here - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I took my first step <br>On that black and white kitchen floor <br>I sometimes wonder if that house <br>Is even there, anymore <br>I had my first glimpse of love <br>When I was five <br>I watched two people split apart <br>But still the three of us survived <br><br>I've seen the best <br>I've seen the worst <br>I wouldn't change what I've been through <br>I've touched the sky <br>I've hit the wall <br>But I did what I had to <br>Ooooohhhh <br><br>On my way here <br>Where I am now <br>I've learned to fly <br>I have to want to leave the ground <br>I've fallen hard <br>But I've been loved <br>And in the end it all works out <br>My faith has conquered fear <br>On my way here. <br><br>Oh yeah yeaaah <br><br>My address has changed <br>Almost every year <br>I've found that standing still <br>Can quickly make a lifetime disappear <br>I'd rather try and fail <br>A thousand times denied <br>And this, whenever you feel pain <br>It lets you know that you're alive <br><br>I've been a fool <br>I've been afraid <br>Yeah, I've been loved <br>I've been lied to <br>I've been wrong <br>And I've been right <br>I stood up when I had to <br><br>Yeah Yeahhhh <br><br>On my way here <br>Where I am now <br>I've learned to fly <br>I have to want to leave the ground <br>I've fallen hard <br>But I've been loved <br>And in the end it all works out <br>My faith has conquered fear <br>On my way here. <br><br>No guarantees <br>I believed that I would find <br>An open door or a light <br>To lead me to the other side <br>I guess that is why <br><br>On my way here <br>Where I am now <br>I've learned to fly <br>I have to want to leave the ground <br>I've fallen hard <br>But I've been loved <br>And in the end it all works out <br>My faith has conquered fear <br>On my way here <br><br>Yeahhhh <br>Oooooohh]]></content><category term="Clay Aiken" label="Clay Aiken"/><category term="On My Way Here" label="On My Way Here"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Avril_Lavigne/Everybody_Hurts/</id><title>Avril Lavigne - Everybody Hurts - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Avril_Lavigne/Everybody_Hurts/" title="Avril Lavigne - Everybody Hurts - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't know, don't know if I can do this on my own <br>Why do you have to leave me? <br>It seems I'm losing something deep inside of me <br>Hold on onto me <br><br>Now I see, now I see <br><br>Everybody hurts some days <br>It's okay to be afraid <br>Everybody hurts, everybody screams <br>Everybody feels this way and it's okay <br>Ladadadada, it's okay <br><br>It feels like nothing really matters anymore <br>When you're gone, I can't breathe <br>And I know you never meant to make me feel this way <br>This can't be happening <br><br>Now I see (now I see), now I see <br><br>Everybody hurts some days <br>It's okay to be afraid <br>Everybody hurts, everybody screams <br>Everybody feels this way and it's okay <br><br>Ladadadada it's okay <br><br>Lalalala <br><br>So many questions, so much on my mind <br>So many answers I can't find <br>I wish I could turn back the time <br>I wonder why <br><br>Everybody hurts some days (some days) <br>Everybody hurts some days (some days) <br><br>Everybody hurts some days (some days) <br>It's okay to be afraid (I'm afraid) <br>Everybody hurts, everybody screams <br>Everybody feels this way and it's okay <br><br>Ladadadada it's okay <br>Lalalalala it's okay <br><br>Everybody hurts some days <br>(Some days) <br>It's okay to be afraid <br>(I'm afraid) <br>Everbody hurts some days <br>Yeah, we all feel pain (It's okay) <br>Everybody feels this way <br>But it'll be okay (some days) <br>Can't somebody take me away <br>To a better place? <br>Everybody feels this way <br><br>(Ahhhh-ahhhh-ahhhh-ahhhh-ahhhh-ahhhh-ahhhh-ahhhh-ahhhh) <br><br>Ladadada it's okay <br>Lalalala, it's okay <br>Ladadada it's okay <br>Lalalala, it's okay]]></content><category term="Avril Lavigne" label="Avril Lavigne"/><category term="Everybody Hurts" label="Everybody Hurts"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pink/Todays_The_Day/</id><title>Pink - Today`s The Day - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pink/Todays_The_Day/" title="Pink - Today`s The Day - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've spent enough time alone <br>Up in my bedroom at home <br>Been kinda bored lately. <br>I hate on all I see <br>It's all mundane to me <br>This box I painted pains me. <br>But you could watch me <br>You could help me down the rabbit hole with you <br>I could go with you <br>You could lead the way I'd go hand in hand with you. <br><br>Oh oh oh <br>Today's the day I've been waiting for <br>Tomorrow won't come after all <br>Yesterday's so far away <br>This today is the only day <br>Somebody please stop the clock <br>Oh oh oh <br>Don't ever let this day stop <br>Oh oh oh <br>I never wanna go home <br>No <br>No, no no <br><br>I used to want to grow up <br>I thought that I could be free <br>But now I'm realizing <br>It's cool, it ain't for me <br>It's cool, cause all my dreams <br>Are more than possibilities <br>I get so vicious <br>When I don't feel delicious <br>I just need a friend <br>So much to carry <br>These days are kinda scary I don't want the fun to end <br><br>Oh oh oh <br>Today's the day I've been waiting for <br>Tomorrow won't come after all <br>Yesterday's so far away <br>This today is the only day <br>Somebody please stop the clock <br>Oh oh oh <br>Don't ever let this day stop <br>Oh oh oh <br>I never wanna go home <br>No <br>No, no no <br><br>I'm a say today's my day <br>I'm a say today's my day <br>I'm a say today's my day <br>I'm a say it's gonna go my way <br><br>I'm a say today's my day <br>I'm a say today's my day <br>I'm a say today's my day <br>I'm a say it's gonna go my way <br><br>Oh oh oh <br>Today's the day I've been waiting for <br>Tomorrow won't come after all <br>Yesterday's so far away <br>This today is the only day <br>Somebody please stop the clock <br>Oh oh oh <br>Don't ever let this day stop <br>Oh oh oh <br>I never wanna go home <br>No no no oh oh oh <br><br>I'm a say today's my day <br>I'm a say today's my day <br>I'm a say today's my day <br>I'm a say it's gonna go my way <br>I'm a say today's my day <br>I'm a say today's my day <br>I'm a say today's my day <br>I'm a say it's gonna go my way <br>I'm a say today's my day <br>I'm a say today's my day <br>I'm a say today's my day <br>I'm a say it's gonna go my way]]></content><category term="Pink" label="Pink"/><category term="Today`s The Day" label="Today`s The Day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kelly_Clarkson/Stronger_What_Doesnt_Kill_You/</id><title>Kelly Clarkson - Stronger (What Doesn`t Kill You) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kelly_Clarkson/Stronger_What_Doesnt_Kill_You/" title="Kelly Clarkson - Stronger (What Doesn`t Kill You) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You know the bed feels warmer <br>Sleeping here alone <br>You know I dream in colour <br>And do the things I want <br><br>You think you got the best of me <br>Think you've had the last laugh <br>Bet you think that everything good is gone <br>Think you left me broken down <br>Think that I'd come running back <br>Baby you don't know me, cause you're dead wrong <br><br>What doesn't kill you makes you stronger <br>Stand a little taller <br>Doesn't mean I'm lonely when I'm alone <br>What doesn't kill you makes a fighter <br>Footsteps even lighter <br>Doesn't mean I'm over cause you're gone <br><br>What doesn't kill you makes you stronger, stronger <br>Just me, myself and I <br>What doesn't kill you makes you stronger <br>Stand a little taller <br>Doesn't mean I'm lonely when I'm alone <br><br>You heard that I was starting over with someone new <br>They told you I was moving on over you <br><br>You didn't think that I'd come back <br>I'd come back swinging <br>You try to break me, but you see <br><br>What doesn't kill you makes you stronger <br>Stand a little taller <br>Doesn't mean I'm lonely when I'm alone <br>What doesn't kill you makes a fighter <br>Footsteps even lighter <br>Doesn't mean I'm over cause you're gone <br><br>What doesn't kill you makes you stronger, stronger <br>Just me, myself and I <br>What doesn't kill you makes you stronger <br>Stand a little taller <br>Doesn't mean I'm lonely when I'm alone <br><br>Thanks to you I got a new thing started <br>Thanks to you I'm not the broken-hearted <br>Thanks to you I'm finally thinking about me <br>You know in the end the day you left was just my beginning <br>In the end... <br><br>What doesn't kill you makes you stronger <br>Stand a little taller <br>Doesn't mean I'm lonely when I'm alone <br>What doesn't kill you makes a fighter <br>Footsteps even lighter <br>Doesn't mean I'm over cause you're gone <br><br>[2x] <br>What doesn't kill you makes you stronger, stronger <br>Just me, myself and I <br>What doesn't kill you makes you stronger <br>Stand a little taller <br>Doesn't mean I'm lonely when I'm alone <br><br>(When I'm alone)]]></content><category term="Kelly Clarkson" label="Kelly Clarkson"/><category term="Stronger (What Doesn`t Kill You)" label="Stronger (What Doesn`t Kill You)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Script/Superheroes/</id><title>The Script - Superheroes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Script/Superheroes/" title="The Script - Superheroes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All her life she has seen <br>All the meanest side of me <br>They took away the prophet's dream for a profit on the street <br><br>Now she's stronger than you know <br>A heart of steel starts to grow <br><br>All his life he's been told <br>He'll be nothing when he's old <br>All the kicks and all the blows <br>He won't ever let it show <br><br>'Cause he's stronger than you know <br>A heart of steel starts to grow <br><br>When you've been fighting for it all your life <br>You've been struggling to make things right <br>That's how a superhero learns to fly <br>(Every day, every hour <br>Turn the pain into power) <br><br>When you've been fighting for it all your life <br>You've been working every day and night <br>That's how a superhero learns to fly <br>(Every day, every hour <br>Turn the pain into power) <br><br>All the hurt, all the lies <br>All the tears that they cry <br>When the moment is just right <br>You see fire in their eyes <br><br>'Cause he's stronger than you know <br>A heart of steel starts to grow <br><br>When you've been fighting for it all your life <br>You've been struggling to make things right <br>That's how a superhero learns to fly <br>Every day, every hour <br>Turn the pain into power <br><br>When you've been fighting for it all your life <br>You've been working every day and night <br>That's how a superhero learns to fly <br><br>(Every day, every hour <br>Turn the pain into power) <br><br>(Power, power, power, power, power) <br>(Power, power, power, power, power) <br><br>(Every day, every hour <br>Turn the pain into power) <br><br>(Power, power, power, power, power) <br>(Power, power, power, power, power) <br><br>(Every day, every hour <br>Turn the pain into power) <br><br>She's got lions in her heart <br>A fire in her soul <br>He's got a beast in his belly <br>That's so hard to control <br>'Cause they've taken too much hits <br>Taking blow by blow <br>Now light a match, stand back, watch them explode <br><br>She's got lions in her heart <br>A fire in her soul <br>He's got a beast in his belly <br>That's so hard to control <br>'Cause they've taken too much hits <br>Taking blow by blow <br>Now light a match, stand back, watch them explode, explode, explode, explode <br><br>When you've been fighting for it all your life <br>You've been struggling to make things right <br>That's how a superhero learns to fly <br><br>(Every day, every hour <br>Turn the pain into power) <br><br>When you've been fighting for it all your life <br>You've been working every day and night <br>That's how a superhero learns to fly <br><br>(Every day, every hour <br>Turn the pain into power) <br><br>(Power, power, power, power, power) <br>Oh, yeah... <br>(Power, power, power, power, power) <br><br>(Every day, every hour <br>Turn the pain into power) <br><br>(Power, power, power, power, power) <br>(Power, power, power, power, power) <br><br>Ooh, yeah <br>Whoa <br><br>(Every day, every hour <br>Turn the pain into power) <br><br>When you've been fighting for it all your life <br>You've been struggling to make things right <br>That's how a superhero learns to fly]]></content><category term="The Script" label="The Script"/><category term="Superheroes" label="Superheroes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rachel_Platten/Fight_Song/</id><title>Rachel Platten - Fight Song - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rachel_Platten/Fight_Song/" title="Rachel Platten - Fight Song - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Like a small boat <br>On the ocean <br>Sending big waves <br>Into motion <br>Like how a single word <br>Can make a heart open <br>I might only have one match <br>But I can make an explosion <br><br>And all those things I didn't say <br>Wrecking balls inside my brain <br>I will scream them loud tonight <br>Can you hear my voice this time? <br><br>This is my fight song <br>Take back my life song <br>Prove I'm alright song <br>My power's turned on <br>Starting right now I'll be strong <br>I'll play my fight song <br>And I don't really care if nobody else believes <br>'Cause I've still got a lot of fight left in me <br><br>Losing friends and I'm chasing sleep <br>Everybody's worried about me <br>In too deep <br>Say I'm in too deep (in too deep) <br>And it's been two years <br>I miss my home <br>But there's a fire burning in my bones <br>Still believe <br>Yeah, I still believe <br><br>And all those things I didn't say <br>Wrecking balls inside my brain <br>I will scream them loud tonight <br>Can you hear my voice this time? <br><br>This is my fight song <br>Take back my life song <br>Prove I'm alright song <br>My power's turned on <br>Starting right now I'll be strong <br>I'll play my fight song <br>And I don't really care if nobody else believes <br>'Cause I've still got a lot of fight left in me <br><br>A lot of fight left in me <br><br>Like a small boat <br>On the ocean <br>Sending big waves <br>Into motion <br>Like how a single word <br>Can make a heart open <br>I might only have one match <br>But I can make an explosion <br><br>This is my fight song (Hey!) <br>Take back my life song (Hey!) <br>Prove I'm alright song (Hey!) <br>My power's turned on <br>Starting right now I'll be strong (I'll be strong) <br>I'll play my fight song <br>And I don't really care if nobody else believes <br>'Cause I've still got a lot of fight left in me <br><br>No I've still got a lot of fight left in me]]></content><category term="Rachel Platten" label="Rachel Platten"/><category term="Fight Song" label="Fight Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sia/Big_Girls_Cry/</id><title>Sia - Big Girls Cry - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sia/Big_Girls_Cry/" title="Sia - Big Girls Cry - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tough girl <br>In the fast lane <br>No time for love <br>No time for hate <br>No drama no time <br>For games <br>Tough girl <br>Whose soul aches <br>I'm at home <br>On my own <br>Check my phone <br>Nothing though <br>Act busy <br>Order in <br>Pay TV <br>It's agony <br>I may cry ruining my makeup <br>Wash away all the things <br>you've taken <br>And I don't care <br>if I don't look pretty <br>Big girls cry when their <br>hearts are breaking <br>Big girls cry when their <br>hearts are breaking <br>Big girls cry when their <br>heart is breaking <br>Tough girl <br>I'm in pain <br>It's lonely at the top <br>Blackouts and airplanes <br>I still pour you a glass <br>of champagne <br>Tough girl <br>Whose soul aches <br>I'm at home <br>On my own <br>Check my phone <br>Nothing though <br>Act busy <br>Order in <br>Pay TV <br>It's agony <br>I may cry ruining my makeup <br>Wash away all the things <br>you've taken <br>And I don't care <br>if I don't look pretty <br>Big girls cry when their <br>hearts are breaking <br>Big girls cry when their <br>hearts are breaking <br>Big girls cry when their <br>hearts are breaking <br>I wake up I wake up I wake up <br>I wake up I wake up I wake up <br>I wake up I wake up I wake up <br>I wake up alone <br>I may cry ruining my makeup <br>Wash away all the things <br>you've taken <br>And I don't care <br>if I don't look pretty <br>Big girls cry when their <br>hearts are breaking <br>Big girls cry when their <br>hearts are breaking <br>Big girls cry when their <br>heart is breaking <br>]]></content><category term="Sia" label="Sia"/><category term="Big Girls Cry" label="Big Girls Cry"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alan_Parsons_Project/Days_Are_Numbers_The_Traveller/</id><title>Alan Parsons Project - Days Are Numbers (The Traveller) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alan_Parsons_Project/Days_Are_Numbers_The_Traveller/" title="Alan Parsons Project - Days Are Numbers (The Traveller) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The traveller is always leaving town <br>He never has the time to turn around <br>And if the road he's taken isn't leading anywhere <br>He seems to be completely unaware <br><br>The traveller is always leaving home <br>The only kind of life he's ever known <br>When every moment seems to be <br>A race against the time <br>There's always one more mountain left to climb <br><br>Days are numbers <br>Watch the stars <br>We can only see so far <br>Someday, you'll know where you are <br>Remember <br>Days are numbers <br>Count the stars <br>We can only go so far <br>One day, you'll know where you are <br><br>The traveller awaits the morning tide <br>He doesn't know what's on the other side <br>But something deep inside of him <br>Keeps telling him to go <br>He hasn't found a reason to say no <br><br>The traveller is only passing through <br>He cannot understand your point of view <br>Abandoning reality, unsure of what he'll find <br>The traveller in me is close behind <br><br>Days are numbers <br>Watch the stars <br>We can only see so far <br>Someday, you'll know where you are <br>Remember <br>Days are numbers <br>Count the stars <br>We can only go so far <br>One day, you'll know where you are]]></content><category term="Alan Parsons Project" label="Alan Parsons Project"/><category term="Days Are Numbers (The Traveller)" label="Days Are Numbers (The Traveller)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simon__Garfunkel/Bridge_Over_Troubled_Water/</id><title>Simon &amp; Garfunkel - Bridge Over Troubled Water - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simon__Garfunkel/Bridge_Over_Troubled_Water/" title="Simon &amp; Garfunkel - Bridge Over Troubled Water - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you're weary, feeling small <br>When tears are in your eyes <br>I will dry them all <br>I'm on your side <br>When times get rough <br>And friends just can't be found <br>Like a bridge over troubled water <br>I will lay me down <br>Like a bridge over troubled water <br>I will lay me down <br><br>When you're down and out <br>When you're on the street <br>When evening falls so hard <br>I will comfort you <br>I'll take your part <br>When darkness comes <br>And pain is all around <br>Like a bridge over troubled water <br>I will lay me down <br>Like a bridge over troubled water <br>I will lay me down <br><br>Sail on, silvergirl <br>Sail on by <br>Your time has come to shine <br>All your dreams are on their way <br>See how they shine <br>If you need a friend <br>I'm sailing right behind <br>Like a bridge over troubled water <br>I will ease your mind <br>Like a bridge over troubled water <br>I will ease your mind]]></content><category term="Simon &amp; Garfunkel" label="Simon &amp; Garfunkel"/><category term="Bridge Over Troubled Water" label="Bridge Over Troubled Water"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bob_Dylan/Blowin_In_The_Wind/</id><title>Bob Dylan - Blowin` In The Wind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bob_Dylan/Blowin_In_The_Wind/" title="Bob Dylan - Blowin` In The Wind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How many roads must a man walk down <br>Before you can call him a man? <br>How many seas must a white dove sail <br>Before she sleeps in the sand? <br>Yes, how many times must the cannon balls fly <br>Before they're forever banned? <br>The answer my friend is blowin' in the wind <br>The answer is blowin' in the wind. <br><br>Yes, how many years can a mountain exist <br>Before it's washed to the sea? <br>Yes, how many years can some people exist <br>Before they're allowed to be free? <br>Yes, how many times can a man turn his head <br>Pretending he just doesn't see? <br>The answer my friend is blowin' in the wind <br>The answer is blowin' in the wind. <br><br>Yes, how many times must a man look up <br>Before he can really see the sky? <br>Yes, how many ears must one man have <br>Before he can hear people cry? <br>Yes, how many deaths will it take till he knows <br>That too many people have died? <br>The answer my friend is blowin' in the wind <br>The answer is blowin' in the wind]]></content><category term="Bob Dylan" label="Bob Dylan"/><category term="Blowin` In The Wind" label="Blowin` In The Wind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Melanie/The_Saddest_Thing/</id><title>Melanie - The Saddest Thing - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Melanie/The_Saddest_Thing/" title="Melanie - The Saddest Thing - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And the saddest thing <br>Under the sun above <br>Is to say goodbye <br>To the ones you love. <br><br><br>All the things that I have known. <br>Be came my life my very own. <br>But before you know you say goodbye. <br>Oh, good time, goodbye <br>It's time to cry <br>But I will not weep nor make a scene <br>Just say "thank you <br>Life for having been." <br><br><br>And the hardest thing <br>Under the sun above. <br>Is to say goodbye to the ones you love. <br>No I will not weep nor make a scene <br>I'm gonna say "thank you <br>Life for having been." <br><br><br>And the loudest cry <br>Under the sun above <br>Is to silent goodbye <br>From the ones you love. <br>Aaahaaha]]></content><category term="Melanie" label="Melanie"/><category term="The Saddest Thing" label="The Saddest Thing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sara_Bareilles/Gravity/</id><title>Sara Bareilles - Gravity - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sara_Bareilles/Gravity/" title="Sara Bareilles - Gravity - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Something always brings me back to you. <br>It never takes too long. <br>No matter what I say or do <br>I'll still feel you here 'til the moment I'm gone. <br><br>You hold me without touch. <br>You keep me without chains. <br>I never wanted anything so much <br>Than to drown in your love and not feel your rain. <br><br>Set me free <br>Leave me be. <br>I don't wanna fall another moment into your gravity <br>Here I am and I stand so tall, just the way I'm supposed to be. <br>But you're on to me and all over me. <br><br>Oh, you loved me 'cause I'm fragile <br>When I thought that I was strong. <br>But you touch me for a little while <br>And all my fragile strength is gone. <br><br>Set me free <br>Leave me be. <br>I don't wanna fall another moment into your gravity <br>Here I am and I stand so tall, just the way I'm supposed to be. <br>But you're on to me and all over me <br><br>I live here on my knees <br>As I try to make you see <br>That you're everything I think I need here on the ground. <br><br>But you're neither friend nor foe <br>Though I can't seem to let you go. <br>The one thing that I still know is that you're keeping me down. <br><br>You're keeping me down, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>You're on to me, on to me, and all over... <br><br>Something always brings me back to you. <br>It never takes too long.]]></content><category term="Sara Bareilles" label="Sara Bareilles"/><category term="Gravity" label="Gravity"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/R_Kelly/The_Worlds_Greatest/</id><title>R. Kelly - The World`s Greatest - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/R_Kelly/The_Worlds_Greatest/" title="R. Kelly - The World`s Greatest - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, uhh... <br>Uhh... <br>Yeah.. <br>It's the world's greatest, yo <br>It's the world's greatest, come on <br>World's greatest, ever <br><br>I am a mountain <br>I am a tall tree <br>Oh, I am a swift wind <br>Sweepin' the country <br>I am a river <br>Down in the valley <br>Oh, I am a vision <br>And I can see clearly <br><br>If anybody asks you who I am <br>Just stand up tall, look 'em in the face and say <br><br>I'm that star up in the sky <br>I'm that mountain peak up high <br>Hey, I made it <br>I'm the worlds greatest <br>And I'm that little bit of hope <br>When my back's against the ropes <br>I can feel it mmm <br>I'm the world's greatest <br><br>I am a giant <br>I am an eagle <br>I am a lion <br>Down in the jungle <br>I am a marchin' band <br>I am the people <br>I am a helpin' hand <br>And I am a hero <br><br>If anybody asks you who I am <br>Just stand up tall, look 'em in the face and say <br><br>I'm that star up in the sky <br>I'm that mountain peak up high <br>Hey, I made it <br>I'm the world's greatest <br>And I'm that little bit of hope <br>When my back's against the ropes <br>I can feel it <br>I'm the world's greatest <br><br>In the ring of life I'll reign love (I will reign) <br>And the world will notice a king (oh, yeah) <br>When all is darkest, I'll shine a light (shine a light) <br>And mirrors of success reflect in me (me) <br><br>I'm that star up in the sky <br>I'm that mountain peak up high <br>Hey, I made it <br>I'm the world's greatest <br>And I'm that little bit of hope <br>When my back's against the ropes <br>I can feel it <br>I'm the world's greatest <br><br>I'm that star up in the sky <br>I'm that mountain peak up high <br>Hey, I made it <br>I'm the world's greatest <br>And I'm that little bit of hope <br>When my back's against the ropes <br>I can feel it <br>I'm the world's greatest <br><br>I'm that star up in the sky <br>I'm that mountain peak up high <br>Hey, I made it <br>I'm the world's greatest <br>And I'm that little bit of hope <br>When my back's against the ropes <br>I can feel it <br>I'm the world's greatest <br><br>It's the greatest <br>Can you feel it <br>It's the greatest <br>Can you feel it <br><br>I saw the light <br>At the end of a tunnel <br>Believe in the pot of gold <br>At the end of the rainbow <br>And faith was right there <br>To pull me through, yeah <br>Used to be locked doors <br>Now I can just walk on through <br>Hey, uh, hey, hey, hey <br>It's the greatest <br>I'm that star up in the sky <br><br>I'm that star up in the sky <br>I'm that mountain peak up high <br>Hey, I made it <br>I'm the world's greatest <br>And I'm that little bit of hope <br>When my back's against the ropes <br>I can feel it <br>I'm the world's greatest]]></content><category term="R. Kelly" label="R. Kelly"/><category term="The World`s Greatest" label="The World`s Greatest"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Backstreet_Boys/Drowning/</id><title>Backstreet Boys - Drowning - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Backstreet_Boys/Drowning/" title="Backstreet Boys - Drowning - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't pretend you're sorry <br>I know you're not <br>You know you got the power <br>To make me weak inside <br>Girl you leave me breathless <br>But it's okay 'cause <br>You are my survival <br>Now hear me say <br>I can't imagine life <br>Without your love <br>Even forever don't seem <br>Like long enough <br><br>'Cause everytime I breathe <br>I take you in <br>And my heart beats again <br>Baby I can't help it <br>You keep me <br>Drowning in your love <br>Everytime I try to rise above <br>I'm swept away by love <br>Baby I can't help it <br>You keep me <br>Drowning in your love <br><br>Maybe I'm a drifter <br>Maybe not <br>'Cause I have known the safety <br>Of floating freely <br>In your arms <br>I don't need another lifeline <br>It's not for me <br>'Cause only you can save me <br>Oh can't you see <br>I can't imagine life <br>Without your love <br>And even forever don't seem <br>Like long enough <br><br>'Cause everytime I breathe <br>I take you in <br>And my heart beats again <br>Baby I can't help it <br>You keep me <br>Drowning in your love <br>Everytime I try to rise above <br>I'm swept away by love <br>Baby I can't help it <br>You keep me <br>Drowning in your love <br><br>Go on and pull me under <br>Cover me with dreams, yeah <br>Love me mouth to mouth now <br>You know I can't resist <br>'Cause you're the air <br>That I breathe <br><br>'Cause everytime I breathe <br>I take you in <br>And my heart beats again <br>Baby I can't help it <br>You keep me <br>Drowning in your love <br>Everytime I try to rise above <br>I'm swept away by love <br>And baby I can't help it <br>You keep me <br>Drowning your love <br><br>Baby I can't help it <br>Keep me drowning <br>In your love <br>I keep drowning <br>In your love <br>Baby I can't help it <br>Can't help it no, no <br><br>'Cause everytime I breathe <br>I take you in <br>And my heart beats again <br>Baby I can't help it <br>You keep me <br>Drowning in your love <br>Everytime I try to rise above <br>I'm swept away by love <br>Baby I can't help it <br>You keep me <br>Drowning in your love]]></content><category term="Backstreet Boys" label="Backstreet Boys"/><category term="Drowning" label="Drowning"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fray/How_To_Save_A_Life/</id><title>The Fray - How To Save A Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Fray/How_To_Save_A_Life/" title="The Fray - How To Save A Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Step one, you say, "We need to talk." <br>He walks, you say, "Sit down. It's just a talk." <br>He smiles politely back at you <br>You stare politely right on through <br>Some sort of window to your right <br>As he goes left and you stay right <br>Between the lines of fear and blame <br>You begin to wonder why you came <br><br>Where did I go wrong? I lost a friend <br>Somewhere along in the bitterness <br>And I would have stayed up with you all night <br>Had I known how to save a life <br><br>Let him know that you know best <br>'Cause after all you do know best <br>Try to slip past his defense <br>Without granting innocence <br>Lay down a list of what is wrong <br>The things you've told him all along <br>Pray to God, he hears you <br>And I pray to God, he hears you <br><br>And where did I go wrong? I lost a friend <br>Somewhere along in the bitterness <br>And I would have stayed up with you all night <br>Had I known how to save a life <br><br>As he begins to raise his voice <br>You lower yours and grant him one last choice <br>Drive until you lose the road <br>Or break with the ones you've followed <br>He will do one of two things <br>He will admit to everything <br>Or he'll say he's just not the same <br>And you'll begin to wonder why you came <br><br>Where did I go wrong? I lost a friend <br>Somewhere along in the bitterness <br>And I would have stayed up with you all night <br>Had I known how to save a life <br><br>Where did I go wrong? I lost a friend <br>Somewhere along in the bitterness <br>And I would have stayed up with you all night <br>Had I known how to save a life <br><br>How to save a life <br><br>How to save a life <br><br>Where did I go wrong? I lost a friend <br>Somewhere along in the bitterness <br>And I would have stayed up with you all night <br>Had I known how to save a life <br><br>Where did I go wrong? I lost a friend <br>Somewhere along in the bitterness <br>And I would have stayed up with you all night <br>Had I known how to save a life <br>How to save a life <br><br>How to save a life]]></content><category term="The Fray" label="The Fray"/><category term="How To Save A Life" label="How To Save A Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daughtry/Its_Not_Over/</id><title>Daughtry - It`s Not Over - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daughtry/Its_Not_Over/" title="Daughtry - It`s Not Over - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was blown away. <br>What could I say? <br>It all seemed to make sense. <br>You've taken away everything <br>And I can't deal with that. <br>I try to see the good in life <br>But good things in life are hard to find. <br>We'll blow it away, blow it away. <br>Can we make this something good? <br>Well, I'll try to do it right this time around. <br><br>Let's start over. <br>I'll try to do it right this time around. <br>It's not over. <br>'Cause a part of me is dead and in the ground. <br>This love is killing me <br>But you're the only one. <br>It's not over. <br><br>Taken all I could take <br>And I cannot wait. <br>We're wasting too much time <br>Being strong, holding on. <br>Can't let it bring us down. <br>My life with you means everything <br>So I won't give up that easily. <br>I'll blow it away, blow it away. <br>Can we make this something good? <br>'Cause it's all misunderstood. <br>Well, I'll try to do it right this time around. <br><br>Let's start over. <br>I'll try to do it right this time around. <br>It's not over. <br>'Cause a part of me is dead and in the ground. <br>This love is killing me <br>But you're the only one. <br>It's not over. <br><br>We can't let this get away. <br>Let it out, let it out. <br>Don't get caught up in yourself. <br>Let it out. <br><br>Let's start over. <br>I'll try to do it right this time around. <br>It's not over. <br>'Cause a part of me is dead and in the ground. <br>This love is killing me <br>But you're the only one. <br>It's not over. <br><br>Let's start over. <br>It's not over, yeah... <br>This love is killing me <br>But you're the only one. <br>It's not over.]]></content><category term="Daughtry" label="Daughtry"/><category term="It`s Not Over" label="It`s Not Over"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shayne_Ward/No_Promises/</id><title>Shayne Ward - No Promises - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shayne_Ward/No_Promises/" title="Shayne Ward - No Promises - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey baby, when we are together doing things that we love. <br>Every time you're near I feel like I’m in heaven feeling high <br>I don’t want to let go, girl. <br>I just need you to know, girl. <br><br>I don’t wanna run away, baby, you’re the one I need tonight. <br>No promises. <br>Baby, now I need to hold you tight, I just wanna die in your arms here tonight <br><br>Hey baby, when we are together doing things that we love. <br>Every time you're near I feel like I’m in heaven feeling high <br>I don’t want to let go, girl. <br>I just need you to know, girl. <br><br>I don’t wanna run away, baby, you’re the one I need tonight. <br>No promises. <br>Baby, now I need to hold you tight, I just wanna die in your arms. <br><br>I don’t want to run away, I want to stay forever, through time and time. <br>No promises <br><br>I don’t wanna run away, I don’t wanna be alone. <br>No promises. <br>Baby, now I need to hold you tight, now and forever, my love. <br>No promises <br><br>I don’t wanna run away, baby, you’re the one I need tonight <br>No promises. <br>Baby, now I need to hold you tight, I just wanna die in your arms here tonight. <br><br>I don’t wanna run away, baby, you’re the one I need tonight. <br>No promises. <br>Baby, now I need to hold you tight, I just wanna die in your arms here tonight.]]></content><category term="Shayne Ward" label="Shayne Ward"/><category term="No Promises" label="No Promises"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leona_Lewis/Better_In_Time/</id><title>Leona Lewis - Better In Time - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T17:51:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T17:51:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leona_Lewis/Better_In_Time/" title="Leona Lewis - Better In Time - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's been the longest winter without you <br>I didn't know where to turn to <br>See somehow I can't forget you <br>After all that we've been through <br><br>Going coming thought I heard a knock <br>Who's there no one <br>Thinking that I deserve it <br>Now I realize that I really didn't know <br>If you didn't notice you mean everything <br>Quickly I'm learning to love again <br>All I know is I'm gonna be OK <br><br>Thought I couldn't live without you <br>It's gonna hurt when it heals too <br>It'll all get better in time <br>And even though I really love you <br>I'm gonna smile cause I deserve to <br>It'll all get better in time <br><br>I couldn't turn on the TV <br>Without something there to remind me <br>Was it all that easy <br>To just put aside your feelings <br><br>If I'm dreaming don't wanna laugh <br>Hurt my feelings but that's the path <br>I believe in <br>And I know that time will heal it <br>If you didn't notice boy you meant everything <br>Quickly I'm learning to love again <br>All I know is I'm gonna be OK <br><br>Thought I couldn't live without you <br>It's gonna hurt when it heals too <br>It'll all get better in time <br>And even though I really love you <br>I'm gonna smile cause I deserve to <br>It'll all get better in time <br><br>Since there's no more you and me <br>It's time I let you go <br>So I can be free <br>And live my life how it should be <br>No matter how hard it is I'll be fine without you <br>Yes I will <br><br>Thought I couldn't live without you <br>It's gonna hurt when it heals too <br>It'll all get better in time <br>And even though I really love you <br>I'm gonna smile cause I deserve to <br>It'll all get better in time]]></content><category term="Leona Lewis" label="Leona Lewis"/><category term="Better In Time" label="Better In Time"/></entry></feed>