<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:27:09+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/프리티브라운/애매해_Inst/</id><title>프리티브라운 - 애매해 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:15:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:15:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC%ED%8B%B0%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%95%A0%EB%A7%A4%ED%95%B4_Inst/" title="프리티브라운 - 애매해 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[친구들이 나를 보고 말해 <br>나가서 데이트라도 해 주말에 <br>나는 아직 이불 속이 편한데 <br>친구들이 나를 보고 말해 <br>너 같은 거 다 잊고 시작하래 <br>그게 사실 말처럼 쉽지 않은데 <br>어느 거릴 걷던지 우 Baby <br>너와의 기억들 가득해서 <br>새로운 사람과 함께하는 건 힘들어 <br>술에 취해 보낸 문자도 <br>새벽에 찍힌 부재중 전화도 <br>너도 나와 같은 기분이잖아 <br>너와 나 사이 애매 애매해 <br>우리 둘 사이 고민을 했지만 <br>답이 있기나 한 걸까 <br>너와 나 사이 애매 애매해 <br>너무나 답답한 마음에 <br>오늘도 멍하니 또 하늘만 봐 <br>You &amp; I 계속 이런 어정쩡한 사이 <br>질질 끌 순 없어 필요해 어떤 변화가 <br>혹시나 혼자서 먼저 <br>상상이 앞서는 거라면 내게 말해줘 <br>견딜 수 없을 거야 너라면 <br>한밤중에 술 취해 보낸 messages <br>맴돌고 있네 <br>please tell me where the exit is <br>너무 애매해 이제 물어볼게 네게 <br>우리 무슨 사인지에 대해 <br>다 아니까 그만 내게 말해 <br>시간은 약이 아냐 내겐 <br>누가 뭐라 든 간에 이젠 못해 <br>이런 내 맘 신경 쓰지 마 Baby <br>매일 술을 마셔도 <br>지독한 감기에 걸려도 <br>갑갑한 내 맘 몰라도 돼 <br>제발 모르는 척 그냥 지나가 <br>어떤 영활 보던지 우 Baby <br>너와의 장면들 가득해서 <br>뭐든 너 없이 혼자 하는 건 힘들어 <br>술에 취해 보낸 문자도 <br>새벽에 찍힌 부재중 전화도 <br>너도 나와 같은 기분이잖아 <br>너와 나 사이 애매 애매해 <br>우리 둘 사이 고민을 했지만 <br>답이 있기나 한 걸까 <br>너와 나 사이 애매 애매해 <br>너무나 답답한 마음에 <br>오늘도 멍하니 또 하늘만 봐 <br>얼마나 많이 지난 지 <br>딱히 세본 적 없었지만 <br>그냥 그렇게 지내는 건지 <br>나 이렇게 <br>너와 나 사이 애매 애매해 <br>우리 둘 사이 고민을 했지만 <br>답이 있기나 한 걸까 <br>너와 나 사이 애매 애매해 <br>너무나 답답한 마음에 <br>지금도 멍하니 또 하늘만 봐 <br>]]></content><category term="프리티브라운" label="프리티브라운"/><category term="애매해 (Inst.)" label="애매해 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/프리티브라운/Beautiful/</id><title>프리티브라운 - Beautiful - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:15:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:15:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC%ED%8B%B0%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/Beautiful/" title="프리티브라운 - Beautiful - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You like the sun <br>눈부셔 너를 볼 때면 <br>따뜻해서 널 향한 맘이 <br>피어나는 것 같아 <br>I want you to know <br>지금 이 순간이 <br>Best time in my life <br>너는 단 하나의 기적인 걸 <br>너의 두 눈이 내겐 우주 <br>It's more than universe <br>끝없는 공간 속에 <br>너랑 영원히 살고 싶어 <br>Beautiful Beautiful Beautiful <br>믿을 수 없이 아름다워 <br>Don't wanna lose wanna lose <br>어떤 것도 널 대신할 수 없어 Baby <br>Ooh trust me 나를 믿어주기를 <br>Beautiful Beautiful Beautiful <br>이젠 말할게 영원토록 사랑해 <br>You like the star <br>빛이나 모든 것들이 <br>아름다워 너무나 예뻐서 <br>꿈을 꾸는 것 같아 <br>I promise you 너 하나뿐인 걸 <br>나에겐 only only only only u <br>can't you believe it <br>나의 가슴이 내겐 바다 <br>It's too deep so I could dive <br>둘만의 해변에서 너와 <br>영원히 살고 싶어 영원히 널 <br>Beautiful Beautiful Beautiful <br>믿을 수 없이 아름다워 <br>Don't wanna lose wanna lose <br>어떤 것도 널 대신할 수 없어 Baby <br>Ooh trust me 나를 믿어주기를 <br>Beautiful Beautiful Beautiful <br>이젠 말할게 영원토록 사랑해 <br>Ooh trust me 나를 믿어주기를 <br>Beautiful Beautiful Beautiful <br>너를 사랑해 이 손 놓지 않을게 <br>]]></content><category term="프리티브라운" label="프리티브라운"/><category term="Beautiful" label="Beautiful"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/프리티브라운/옆에_Feat_HENNEY/</id><title>프리티브라운 - 옆에 (Feat. HENNEY) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:15:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:15:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC%ED%8B%B0%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%98%86%EC%97%90_Feat_HENNEY/" title="프리티브라운 - 옆에 (Feat. HENNEY) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[알람을 못 듣고 자버렸네 <br>오늘도 지각이군 <br>양치하고 대충 차려입고 <br>난 집을 나서네 <br>어제 먹은 음식이 문제인지 <br>속이 좋지 않아 <br>약국이나 들려야겠네 <br>난 이미 늦었는데 <br>불길한 느낌 <br>오늘은 왠지 <br>힘든 하루가 될 것만 같아 <br>이 입이 방정이네 <br>밀리는 차도 겨우 탄 만원 버스도 <br>괜히 짜증 나 방금 켜진 빨간 불도 <br>세상은 뒤숭숭 뒤숭숭해 <br>숨을 쉬어도 갑갑해 <br>지친 내 하루의 끝에 <br>yo the only one <br>너마저 없었다면 <br>어떡해 난 어떻게 <br>살았을지 정말 착잡해 <br>때로는 참 허무해 <br>바쁜 하루 일도 무의미해 <br>누군가 별 뜻 없이 한말에 <br>혼자 상처받고 괜히 끙끙대 <br>돈을 벌어도 <br>멋진 옷을 사도 <br>티비에 나온 맛 집에 가도 <br>여전히 난 허전해 <br>무엇을 더해도 <br>왠지 잃어가는 느낌 <br>이젠 알겠어 <br>너만이 날 채우는 걸 <br>세상은 뒤숭숭 뒤숭숭해 <br>숨을 쉬어도 갑갑해 <br>지친 내 하루의 끝에 <br>yo the only one <br>너마저 없었다면 <br>어떡해 난 어떻게 <br>살았을지 정말 착잡해 <br>내가 말했었지 babe <br>그래 yo the only one <br>별처럼 반짝이는 애들은 많아도 <br>my moon 나의 밤엔 나의 너 말곤 <br>누구도 아무도 <br>ain't nobody like my 너 <br>난 너밖에 없어 <br>날 비춰주는 네가 보여 <br>아니 내가 볼 땐 <br>넌 늘 빛나고 있는 걸 <br>세상은 뒤숭숭 뒤숭숭해 <br>숨을 쉬어도 갑갑해 <br>지친 내 하루의 끝에 <br>yo the only one <br>너마저 없었다면 <br>어떡해 난 어떻게 <br>살았을지 정말 착잡해 <br>]]></content><category term="프리티브라운" label="프리티브라운"/><category term="옆에 (Feat. HENNEY)" label="옆에 (Feat. HENNEY)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/프리티브라운/그런_사람_없어_Feat_한해/</id><title>프리티브라운 - 그런 사람 없어 (Feat. 한해) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:15:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:15:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC%ED%8B%B0%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%B0_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C_%EC%97%86%EC%96%B4_Feat_%ED%95%9C%ED%95%B4/" title="프리티브라운 - 그런 사람 없어 (Feat. 한해) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 또 뭐가 문제니 왜 또 싸웠니 <br>내가 볼 땐 별거 아냐 신경 쓰지 마 <br>니가 이해해 그러려니 해 <br>걘 그냥 친굴뿐이야 <br>걔가 좀 착하잖아 <br>걔가 좀 착하잖아 바보 같을 정도로 <br>술 좀 그만 따라 마셔 설마 널 두고 <br>다른데 가서 엄한 짓 할 <br>놈이 못돼 걔는 <br>나보다 훨씬 니가 더 <br>잘 알잖아 이제는 <br>알아 알면서도 신경 쓰이는 <br>아무나한테 흘리는 <br>것처럼 보이는 지금 <br>혹시 그렇담 내가 <br>죽이 되던 밥이 되던 <br>해결해 줄 테니 <br>걱정 말고 택시 타 싫어도 <br>그런 사람은 없어 그런 사람은 없어 <br>너를 너무 아껴주잖아 나만큼 널 <br>그런 사람은 없어 나를 대신할 사람 <br>너와 있는 시간만으로 난 충분해 <br>벌써 시간이 벌써 새벽 두시 반 <br>계속 울리는 전화만 바라보는 너 <br>데리러 온다잖아 나 먼저 일어날게 <br>그 사람이 오기 전에 <br>괜히 긁어 부스럼은 <br>그냥 만들지 말어 <br>나 만났다고 하지 마 <br>또 둘이 싸움 나잖아 <br>진짜로 방해되기 싫어 <br>너네 둘 관계 안에서 <br>나 불만은 없어 아직도 날 못 믿어 <br>오히려 니가 날 걱정하면 심장 뛰어 <br>옛날처럼 헷갈려 하며 힘들기는 싫어 <br>오늘은 이까지만 할 게 늦었다 <br>빨리 들어가 <br>아냐 나 먼저 택시 타고 갈게 <br>그런 사람은 없어 나를 대신할 사람 <br>너와 있는 시간만으로 난 충분해 <br>혼자 돌아오는 길 <br>생각보다 추웠던 밤 <br>잘 들어갔냔 문자 또 보자는 말 <br>그저 웃던 나 하지만 <br>오늘은 좀 취했나 봐 <br>보고 싶다 <br>그런 사람은 없어 그런 사람은 없어 <br>너를 너무 아껴주잖아 나만큼 널 <br>그런 사람은 없어 나를 대신할 사람 <br>너와 있는 시간만으로 난 충분해 <br>너와 있는 시간만으로 난 행복해 <br>]]></content><category term="프리티브라운" label="프리티브라운"/><category term="그런 사람 없어 (Feat. 한해)" label="그런 사람 없어 (Feat. 한해)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/프리티브라운/QA/</id><title>프리티브라운 - Q&amp;A - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:15:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:15:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC%ED%8B%B0%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/QA/" title="프리티브라운 - Q&amp;A - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>2 0 1 6 hey babe <br>I wanna make a love to you tonight <br>So tell me how you want <br>You know what <br>You are turning me on <br>I want you so bad <br>I will be your Q n A <br>Pretty Brown <br>좀 편하게 말해 <br>내가 오빠 같은데 <br>그럼 먼저 내가 말 놓을까 <br>난 뻔한 말 안 해 <br>그럴 시간도 없어 <br>바로 궁금한 건 물어 난 <br>Baby 거리를 두려 하지 마 <br>이미 이곳 안엔 우리 둘 뿐 <br>몇 번씩 눈 마주친 건 <br>혹시 너도 내 맘 같았던 거니 <br>사실 내가 궁금했던 건 <br>너의 향기와 촉감 같은 거 <br>말로 굳이 설명 안 해도 <br>느낄 수 있는 감정 같은 거 <br>Oh 둘만의 party party <br>지금을 즐겨 <br>내일 걱정 그만해 안 해 <br>이 밤을 즐겨 <br>넌 너무나 hot해 hot해 <br>미치겠어 난 <br>자 뭐든지 말해 말해 <br>다 들어줄게 baby <br>레드와인 같은 숨결 <br>내 맘 더 날 더 재촉하지 <br>너와 항해 아침을 향해 <br>잠은 들 수 없어 우린 tonight <br>Baby 어디든 괜찮은 거지 <br>오늘 밤에 우리 둘이 둘이 <br>취한 듯 살짝 기댄 건 <br>혹시 너도 내 맘 같았던 거니 <br>사실 내가 궁금했던 건 <br>너의 향기와 촉감 같은 거 <br>말로 굳이 설명 안 해도 <br>느낄 수 있는 감정 같은 거 <br>널 알고 싶어 안고 싶어 <br>점점 욕심나는 너 <br>널 알고 싶어 널 갖고 싶어 <br>이 밤이 가기 전에 baby <br>사실 내가 궁금했던 건 <br>너의 향기와 촉감 같은 거 <br>말로 굳이 설명 안 해도 <br>느낄 수 있는 감정 같은 거 <br>Oh 둘만의 party party <br>지금을 즐겨 <br>내일 걱정 그만해 안 해 <br>이 밤을 즐겨 <br>넌 너무나 hot해 hot해 <br>미치겠어 난 <br>자 뭐든지 말해 말해 <br>다 들어줄게 baby <br>]]></content><category term="프리티브라운" label="프리티브라운"/><category term="Q&amp;A" label="Q&amp;A"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/프리티브라운/더치페인_Feat_마이노스_Of_이루펀트/</id><title>프리티브라운 - 더치페인 (Feat. 마이노스 Of 이루펀트) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:15:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:15:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC%ED%8B%B0%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EB%8D%94%EC%B9%98%ED%8E%98%EC%9D%B8_Feat_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8%EC%8A%A4_Of_%EC%9D%B4%EB%A3%A8%ED%8E%80%ED%8A%B8/" title="프리티브라운 - 더치페인 (Feat. 마이노스 Of 이루펀트) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[얼마나 힘들어했는지 <br>얼마나 아파했는지 다 알아 Baby <br>어떤 일이 일어난 건지 몰라도 <br>절대 니 잘못은 아냐 <br>너를 괴롭히던 <br>그 사람이 다 잘못했어 <br>이렇게 여린 너의 맘속에 <br>상처를 남긴 걸 <br>이제부터 지금부터 <br>내가 너의 아픔을 <br>덜어 내주고 싶어 <br>여태 니가 감당해왔던 <br>슬픔의 가격 <br>내가 볼 땐 비싸 보여 <br>너무나 비싸 보여 <br>더 이상은 혼자 낼 필요 없어 <br>니 곁엔 내가 있잖아 Baby <br>Oh 이제부턴 Dutch pain <br>Dutch pain Dutch pain <br>나와 너의 아픔만 반반해 <br>너의 행복은 내가 낼게 <br>Okay Dutch pain <br>Dutch pain with me <br>언제든지 내게 말만 해 <br>널 위한 지갑은 열려있어 <br>얼마나 얘기해야 아니 <br>미안해하지 않아도 돼 <br>어쩌면 당연한 건데 <br>널 힘들게 만드는 일이 <br>생길 때면 말해줘 <br>내가 반으로 줄여줄게 <br>시간이 오래 걸려도 카페인 빠진 <br>더치커피로만 마셔 <br>밤새 까칠까칠해진 피부 <br>퉁퉁 부은 눈 <br>야 화장도 안 먹겠다 <br>착해 빠져가지고 <br>혼자 아파하지 또 <br>텅텅 비어버린 네 맘의 저금통 <br>걱정 말고 매일 나만 만나 <br>내 맘이 네 행복까지 <br>Oh 이제부턴 Dutch pain <br>Dutch pain Dutch pain <br>나와 너의 아픔만 반반해 <br>너의 행복은 내가 낼게 <br>Okay Dutch pain <br>Dutch pain with me <br>언제든지 내게 말만 해 <br>널 위한 지갑은 열려있어 <br>난 너만 행복하다면 <br>뭐든지 다 나눠주고 싶어 네게 <br>그 어떤 일이라도 힘이 든다면 <br>나에게 기대줘 <br>여태 니가 감당해왔던 <br>슬픔의 가격 <br>내가 볼 땐 비싸 보여 <br>너무나 비싸 보여 <br>더 이상은 혼자 낼 필요 없어 <br>니 곁엔 내가 있잖아 Baby <br>Oh 이제부턴 Dutch pain <br>Dutch pain Dutch pain <br>나와 너의 아픔만 반반해 <br>너의 행복은 내가 낼게 <br>Okay Dutch pain <br>Dutch pain with me <br>언제든지 내게 말만 해 <br>널 위한 지갑은 열려있어 <br>]]></content><category term="프리티브라운" label="프리티브라운"/><category term="더치페인 (Feat. 마이노스 Of 이루펀트)" label="더치페인 (Feat. 마이노스 Of 이루펀트)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/프리티브라운/니_멋대로_살아/</id><title>프리티브라운 - 니 멋대로 살아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:15:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:15:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC%ED%8B%B0%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EB%8B%88_%EB%A9%8B%EB%8C%80%EB%A1%9C_%EC%82%B4%EC%95%84/" title="프리티브라운 - 니 멋대로 살아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지금까지 비운 <br>술병이 몇 병인지 <br>지금까지 피운 <br>담배가 몇 갑인지도 <br>모를 만큼 고민했어 <br>What am I doing now <br>Oh 시간은 또 <br>왜 이리도 빨리 가는지 <br>나이는 또 어느새 <br>이리 먹었는지 <br>나다운 게 대체 뭘까 <br>어떻게 살아가야 하는 걸까 <br>맘속에서 치밀어와 <br>더 이상 바보가 될 순 없다고 <br>진절머리가 난다고 <br>니 멋대로 살아 니 멋대로 살아 <br>뭐 하러 눈치 봐 왜 눈치 봐 <br>대신 살아줄 사람 없어 hey <br>니 멋대로 살아 끌리는 대로 <br>니 멋대로 멋대로 살아 <br>아무도 믿지 마 다 믿지 마 <br>영원한 건 절대 없어 <br>말은 참 쉽지 지키지 못할 약속 <br>이젠 안 잡지 척하며 내미는 손 <br>수없이 찍힌 발등과 <br>뒤통수 가득 채웠지 <br>내 옷장 속 가면들로 <br>후회는 또 왜 이리 쌓여만 가는지 <br>언제쯤 내가 내 자신을 용서할지 <br>날 위한 삶은 대체 뭘까 <br>행복이란 건 대체 뭘까 <br>눈물 대신 차올라와 <br>더 이상 휘둘리지 않겠다고 <br>내 편은 나뿐이라고 oh <br>니 멋대로 살아 니 멋대로 <br>니 멋대로 살아 <br>뭐 하러 눈치 봐 왜 눈치 봐 <br>대신 살아줄 사람 없어 hey <br>니 멋대로 살아 끌리는 대로 <br>니 멋대로 멋대로 살아 <br>아무도 믿지 마 다 믿지 마 <br>영원한 건 절대 없어 <br>영원한 친구도 없어 <br>영원한 사랑도 없어 <br>더는 바라는 것도 없어 <br>하루를 살아도 <br>니 멋대로 살아 니 멋대로 살아 <br>뭐 하러 눈치 봐 왜 눈치 봐 <br>대신 살아줄 사람 없어 hey <br>니 멋대로 살아 끌리는 대로 <br>니 멋대로 멋대로 살아 <br>아무도 믿지 마 다 믿지 마 <br>영원한 건 절대 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="프리티브라운" label="프리티브라운"/><category term="니 멋대로 살아" label="니 멋대로 살아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/프리티브라운/피노키오_Feat_몰리디/</id><title>프리티브라운 - 피노키오 (Feat. 몰리디) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:15:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:15:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC%ED%8B%B0%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%ED%94%BC%EB%85%B8%ED%82%A4%EC%98%A4_Feat_%EB%AA%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%94%94/" title="프리티브라운 - 피노키오 (Feat. 몰리디) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잘 지냈어 <br>그래 아직 나는 서툴지만 <br>혼자 있는 것도 어색하지만 <br>그저 그런대로 <br>그래 아직 나는 서툴지만 <br>혼자 있는 것도 괜찮지만 <br>너도 그런대로 잘 살고 있어 <br>난 아직 준비 안됐는데 <br>널 무덤덤하게 맞이하지를 못해 <br>아직도 떠올라 작년 추운 날 <br>다투다 욱해 <br>순간 너의 헤어지자는 말에 그만 <br>하필 내 앞에서 너의 냄새가 <br>내 몸에 묻어나던 너의 향기가 <br>피노키오처럼 코가 커질까 <br>그래 못 잊었어 <br>널 쉽게 지운다면 <br>그건 거짓말 거짓말 <br>답답했어 뭘 하든 <br>체한 사람처럼 사실 난 <br>아직 난 널 많이 <br>그렇게 그렇게 널 많이 <br>모질게 떠났던 <br>반밖에 못 잊어 아직 난 <br>그래 같아 원래 연애라는 게 <br>다 그렇다고들 말해 <br>말이야 쉽지 it ain't easy <br>웃기더라 널 보니 <br>다시 떨린 나란 놈이 <br>Ay 형식적인 안부 섞인 말들 <br>그래 남자 친군 잘 지내고 <br>멋쩍은 미소 이제는 남인데도 <br>겉과 속이 다른 <br>나의 혹시나 한 신호 <br>그렇게 말했어 혼자인 게 되려 <br>편하다고 당분간 <br>난 이런 게 좋다고 <br>아프지 않았어 눈물도 안 났어 <br>잘 살고 있었어 그런데 널 봤어 <br>그래 못 잊었어 <br>널 쉽게 지운다면 <br>그건 거짓말 거짓말 <br>답답했어 뭘 하든 <br>체한 사람처럼 사실 난 <br>아직 난 널 많이 <br>그렇게 그렇게 널 많이 <br>모질게 떠났던 <br>반밖에 못 잊어 아직 난 <br>그래 못 잊었어 <br>그래 못 잊었어 <br>널 쉽게 지운다면 <br>그건 거짓말 거짓말 <br>답답했어 뭘 하든 <br>체한 사람처럼 사실 난 <br>아직 난 널 많이 <br>그렇게 그렇게 널 많이 <br>모질게 떠났던 <br>반밖에 못 잊어 아직 난 <br>]]></content><category term="프리티브라운" label="프리티브라운"/><category term="피노키오 (Feat. 몰리디)" label="피노키오 (Feat. 몰리디)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/프리티브라운/딱_좋은_온도_Feat_배치기/</id><title>프리티브라운 - 딱 좋은 온도 (Feat. 배치기) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:15:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:15:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC%ED%8B%B0%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EB%94%B1_%EC%A2%8B%EC%9D%80_%EC%98%A8%EB%8F%84_Feat_%EB%B0%B0%EC%B9%98%EA%B8%B0/" title="프리티브라운 - 딱 좋은 온도 (Feat. 배치기) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어느덧 코끝에서 멀어지는 <br>시큰한 겨울 <br>이 손을 잡고 날 일으켜 이끄는 곳 <br>꽤 낯설어 따스하게 비추는 빛이 <br>오랜만에 너의 손을 잡고 걷는 거리 <br>옷차림만큼이나 가벼워졌어 <br>차디찬 바람 뒤에 가리어졌던 <br>봄 꽃들이 기지개를 필 때 <br>늘 봄이었던 너의 미소를 <br>새삼 느끼네 <br>여기서 조금만 더 걷자 우리 <br>딱 좋은 이온도가 너무 아까워서 <br>따뜻한 차 한 잔도 이젠 사치 <br>추억 실은 내음들이 너무 반가워서 <br>다시 들어봐 보자 그때 그 BGM <br>이제야 볼 수 있겠네 봄비의 무지개 <br>다행이야 늦은 봄에 널 만난 건 <br>이맘때쯤 꼭 나를 그때로 데려가 <br>두근거림의 고백을 다시 되뇌게 해 <br>햇살 좋은 아침처럼 <br>넌 늘 내게 기분 좋은 꿈 <br>매일매일 날 설레게 하잖아 <br>너무 눈부셔 널 어쩌면 좋아 <br>곁에 있어도 너만 보면 눈물이 나 <br>좋으니까 사랑하니까 <br>누구보다 더 행복해 <br>오랜만이야 이렇게 달려보는 것도 <br>봄을 담은 이 노래가 <br>보물 같은 추억이다 <br>때가 되면 들려오는 <br>노래 따라 불러 그냥 웃음 짓지 <br>아직도 여전한 둘이라 다행이야 <br>지금도 설레는 둘만의 여행이야 <br>두근거림 기분 좋은 긴장이 <br>계절이 바뀌며 느끼게 해 <br>매일같이 음악을 선물해 <br>귀에 맴돌게 <br>그날들의 기억과 이야기가 <br>끊기지 않고 머물게 <br>걱정은 안 해도 돼 <br>어쩌면 지금이 우리 생에 <br>가장 빛나는 날일지도 <br>지금만 같다면 바랄 건 <br>없을까 그럴까 <br>햇살 좋은 아침처럼 <br>넌 늘 내게 기분 좋은 꿈 <br>매일매일 날 설레게 하잖아 <br>너무 눈부셔 널 어쩌면 좋아 <br>곁에 있어도 너만 보면 눈물이 나 <br>좋으니까 사랑하니까 <br>누구보다 더 행복해 <br>이 노래는 song one <br>널 위한 내 첫 번째 소원 <br>달콤하게 달콤하게 <br>부드럽게 부드럽게 <br>약속해 song for you <br>햇살 좋은 아침처럼 <br>햇살이 좋아 <br>넌 늘 내게 기분 좋은 꿈 <br>기분이 좋아 <br>여기서 조금만 더 걷자 우리 <br>딱 좋은 이온도가 너무 아깝잖아 <br>언제나 네 옆에서 너를 지킬게 <br>둘이서 걷자 세상이 끝날 때까지 <br>네 두 볼에 그 미소처럼 <br>둘이서 함께 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="프리티브라운" label="프리티브라운"/><category term="딱 좋은 온도 (Feat. 배치기)" label="딱 좋은 온도 (Feat. 배치기)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/프리티브라운/이별과_이별하다_Feat_칸토/</id><title>프리티브라운 - 이별과 이별하다 (Feat. 칸토) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:15:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:15:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC%ED%8B%B0%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84%EA%B3%BC_%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84%ED%95%98%EB%8B%A4_Feat_%EC%B9%B8%ED%86%A0/" title="프리티브라운 - 이별과 이별하다 (Feat. 칸토) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이별하고 또 이별하고 <br>지겨워서 또 사랑 않고 <br>살겠다며 울먹이던 날들 <br>사랑이란 사랑은 혼자 <br>다해봤다 생각을 하며 <br>결국엔 다 부질없는 거라 생각했어 <br>근데 이번엔 아냐 <br>긴 긴 이별과 방황 <br>그 속에 니가 나타났어 <br>이거야 이거야 이번엔 <br>정말 느낌이 와 <br>이젠 너와 진짜 사랑을 하고 싶어 <br>이별아 우리 이제 <br>이별하자 이별하자 <br>난 너보다 사랑을 사랑하니까 <br>아픔아 우리 이제 <br>이별하자 이별하자 <br>이번엔 정말 영원할 것만 같은 <br>그런 느낌이 와 <br>A girl 내게 말만 해를 <br>외치며 내 모든 걸 줬고 <br>우리 사이에 <br>켜진 그린라이트 but <br>오래 못 가 변해가 <br>결국 남은 건 아픔 사랑은 <br>미친 짓이야를 <br>불러대던 나한테 니가 왔네 <br>내가 해왔던 생각들을 <br>다 바꿔놓았네 <br>넌 지금까지와는 느낌이 달라 <br>만났던 여자들의 이름 기억도 안 나 <br>니 매력은 좀 지나쳐서 <br>내 모든 게 다 녹아내려 <br>상상도 하지 못한 이 기분 <br>사람마다 색다른 느낌 <br>근데 결국 똑같은 끝이 <br>사랑을 재미없게 만들고 했었지만 <br>근데 이번엔 아냐 <br>긴긴 이별과 방황 <br>그 속에 니가 나타났어 <br>온 거야 온 거야 넌 정말 <br>다른 느낌이야 <br>이젠 너와 진짜 사랑을 하고 싶어 <br>이별아 우리 이제 <br>이별하자 이별하자 <br>난 너보다 사랑을 사랑하니까 <br>아픔아 우리 이제 <br>이별하자 이별하자 <br>이번엔 정말 영원할 것만 같은 <br>그런 느낌이 와 <br>오 느낌이 와 넌 <br>그 전과는 달라 내가 숨이 막혀와 <br>서쪽에 태양이 뜬 것 같아 <br>그렇게 넌 말이 안 되는 <br>아름다움이야 <br>이별아 우리 이제 <br>이별하자 이별하자 <br>난 너보다 사랑을 사랑하니까 <br>아픔아 우리 이제 <br>이별하자 이별하자 <br>이번엔 정말 영원할 것만 같은 <br>그런 느낌이 와 <br>슬픔이 무슨 뜻이죠 <br>I don't know <br>내 눈에 모든 게 다 아름다워 보여 <br>슬픔이란 감정이 뭐였는지 <br>I don't know <br>외로움이 무슨 뜻이죠 <br>I don't know <br>전에 걔랑 헤어지고 운거 다 까먹어 <br>외로움은 뭐죠 먹는 건가 <br>I don't know <br>]]></content><category term="프리티브라운" label="프리티브라운"/><category term="이별과 이별하다 (Feat. 칸토)" label="이별과 이별하다 (Feat. 칸토)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/프리티브라운/애매해_Feat_버벌진트/</id><title>프리티브라운 - 애매해 (Feat. 버벌진트) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:15:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:15:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC%ED%8B%B0%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%95%A0%EB%A7%A4%ED%95%B4_Feat_%EB%B2%84%EB%B2%8C%EC%A7%84%ED%8A%B8/" title="프리티브라운 - 애매해 (Feat. 버벌진트) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[친구들이 나를 보고 말해 <br>나가서 데이트라도 해 주말에 <br>나는 아직 이불 속이 편한데 <br>친구들이 나를 보고 말해 <br>너 같은 거 다 잊고 시작하래 <br>그게 사실 말처럼 쉽지 않은데 <br>어느 거릴 걷던지 우 Baby <br>너와의 기억들 가득해서 <br>새로운 사람과 함께하는 건 힘들어 <br>술에 취해 보낸 문자도 <br>새벽에 찍힌 부재중 전화도 <br>너도 나와 같은 기분이잖아 <br>너와 나 사이 애매 애매해 <br>우리 둘 사이 고민을 했지만 <br>답이 있기나 한 걸까 <br>너와 나 사이 애매 애매해 <br>너무나 답답한 마음에 <br>오늘도 멍하니 또 하늘만 봐 <br>You &amp; I 계속 이런 어정쩡한 사이 <br>질질 끌 순 없어 필요해 어떤 변화가 <br>혹시나 혼자서 먼저 <br>상상이 앞서는 거라면 내게 말해줘 <br>견딜 수 없을 거야 너라면 <br>한밤중에 술 취해 보낸 messages <br>맴돌고 있네 <br>please tell me where the exit is <br>너무 애매해 이제 물어볼게 네게 <br>우리 무슨 사인지에 대해 <br>다 아니까 그만 내게 말해 <br>시간은 약이 아냐 내겐 <br>누가 뭐라 든 간에 이젠 못해 <br>이런 내 맘 신경 쓰지 마 Baby <br>매일 술을 마셔도 <br>지독한 감기에 걸려도 <br>갑갑한 내 맘 몰라도 돼 <br>제발 모르는 척 그냥 지나가 <br>어떤 영활 보던지 우 Baby <br>너와의 장면들 가득해서 <br>뭐든 너 없이 혼자 하는 건 힘들어 <br>술에 취해 보낸 문자도 <br>새벽에 찍힌 부재중 전화도 <br>너도 나와 같은 기분이잖아 <br>너와 나 사이 애매 애매해 <br>우리 둘 사이 고민을 했지만 <br>답이 있기나 한 걸까 <br>너와 나 사이 애매 애매해 <br>너무나 답답한 마음에 <br>오늘도 멍하니 또 하늘만 봐 <br>얼마나 많이 지난 지 <br>딱히 세본 적 없었지만 <br>그냥 그렇게 지내는 건지 <br>나 이렇게 <br>너와 나 사이 애매 애매해 <br>우리 둘 사이 고민을 했지만 <br>답이 있기나 한 걸까 <br>너와 나 사이 애매 애매해 <br>너무나 답답한 마음에 <br>지금도 멍하니 또 하늘만 봐 <br>]]></content><category term="프리티브라운" label="프리티브라운"/><category term="애매해 (Feat. 버벌진트)" label="애매해 (Feat. 버벌진트)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/프리티브라운/Pretty_Brown/</id><title>프리티브라운 - Pretty Brown - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:15:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:15:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC%ED%8B%B0%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/Pretty_Brown/" title="프리티브라운 - Pretty Brown - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[열다섯 열여섯 아이는 <br>신이 나는 일을 찾아냈어 <br>아무도 몰랐지 이 길을 택할 줄은 <br>말할 수 없었지 afraid to tell 모든 <br>밴드 그룹 대학을 거치며 <br>오디션 끝에 만난 현중이 형 <br>생각대로 되진 않았어 <br>맘 따로 몸 따로 어렸나 봐 <br>밀리고 밀릴 대로 밀려 <br>조르고 졸라 나오게 된 M.A.C <br>난 기억해 그날의 모든 것 <br>그 냄새까지도 생생해 <br>I will fly high sky 불러 my story <br>우리만의 노래 널 미치게 만들 거야 <br>We fly high can't you see me <br>together we can make it <br>start 나의 노래 <br>노래가 좋았어 <br>많은 사람들의 칭찬과 박수갈채 <br>내가 일등일 줄만 알았지 그랬었지 <br>그렇게 시작된 <br>내 음악의 날개가 달린 듯이 좋은 <br>기회 또한 찾아왔었지 <br>Pretty Brown <br>이제 다시 날아오를 준비됐어 <br>I will fly high sky 불러 my story <br>우리만의 노래 널 미치게 만들 거야 <br>We fly high can't you see me <br>together we can make it <br>나의 노래 <br>이 노랜 just a first track <br>너에게 들려줄 my song <br>Pretty Brown <br>Pretty Brown <br>Pretty Brown <br>Pretty Brown <br>]]></content><category term="프리티브라운" label="프리티브라운"/><category term="Pretty Brown" label="Pretty Brown"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김홍석/그대여_울지마/</id><title>김홍석 - 그대여 울지마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:16:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:16:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%99%8D%EC%84%9D/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EC%97%AC_%EC%9A%B8%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88/" title="김홍석 - 그대여 울지마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대여 울지마 세상은 <br>그렇게 녹록지 않잖아 <br>미안해 하지마 아직은 <br>웃어줄 사람 있잖아 <br>그렇게도 사랑을 믿고 <br>그렇게 살아도 <br>내 그리움은 아직 널 향해 <br>손을 내밀고만 있지 <br>한번만 더 날 잡아줘 <br>내가 웃어줄게 <br>한번만 더 오 날 돌아봐줘 <br>내가 웃어줄게 <br>그렇게도 사랑을 믿고 <br>그렇게 살아도 <br>내 그리움은 아직 널 향해 <br>손을 내밀고만 있지 <br>한번만 더 날 잡아줘 <br>내가 웃어줄게 <br>한번만 더 오 날 돌아봐줘 <br>내가 웃어줄게 <br>내가 웃어줄게 <br>]]></content><category term="김홍석" label="김홍석"/><category term="그대여 울지마" label="그대여 울지마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김홍석/Beautiful_Love/</id><title>김홍석 - Beautiful Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:16:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:16:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%99%8D%EC%84%9D/Beautiful_Love/" title="김홍석 - Beautiful Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[말할 수 없었던 우리의 날들 <br>바람이었나 비켜 서있네 <br>서로가 너무나 원했던 바램 <br>그늘 되어 비켜 서있네 <br>살다 보면 잊고 잊고 말 것을 어허 <br>우리는 전부인 듯 살아 <br>전부를 잃고 비켜 서있네 <br>잊을 수 없어서 지울 수 없단 <br>그 말에 또 속으려 하네 <br>달에서 걸음을 걷는 것처럼 <br>춤을 추듯 사라져가네 <br>살다 보면 잊고 잊고 말 것을 어허 <br>우리는 전부인 듯 살아 <br>전부를 잃고 비켜 서있네 <br>춤을 추듯 사라져가네 <br>전부를 잃고 비켜 서있네 <br>]]></content><category term="김홍석" label="김홍석"/><category term="Beautiful Love" label="Beautiful Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오렌지핀/솜사탕/</id><title>오렌지핀 - 솜사탕 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:16:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:16:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%A0%8C%EC%A7%80%ED%95%80/%EC%86%9C%EC%82%AC%ED%83%95/" title="오렌지핀 - 솜사탕 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘따라 울적한 기분도 떠나가고 <br>두근두근 너의 눈빛 <br>내 마음을 살살 녹여 <br>부드러운 눈빛에 솜사탕처럼 <br>두근두근 너의 눈빛 <br>내 마음을 살살 녹여 <br>조금 전까지만 해도 통화 했었는데 <br>매일 너의 귀여운 목소리 듣고 싶다 <br>너와 함께 어디를 가도 <br>내 마음은 너무 행복해 <br>오늘따라 저 달만 봐도 <br>우리의 소원이 이루어진대 <br>깊은 밤에 너의 집 앞에 <br>작고 예쁜 손을 잡고서 <br>약속했어 힘들다 해도 함께할게 <br>오늘따라 울적한 기분도 떠나가고 <br>두근두근 너의 눈빛 <br>내 마음을 살살 녹여 <br>부드러운 눈빛에 솜사탕처럼 <br>두근두근 너의 눈빛 <br>내 마음을 살살 녹여 <br>조금 전까지만 해도 통화 했었는데 <br>매일 너의 귀여운 목소리 듣고 싶다 <br>너와 함께 어디를 가도 <br>내 마음은 너무 행복해 <br>오늘따라 저 달만 봐도 <br>우리의 소원이 이루어진대 <br>깊은 밤에 너의 집 앞에 <br>작고 예쁜 손을 잡고서 <br>약속했어 힘들다 해도 함께할게 <br>오늘따라 울적한 기분도 떠나가고 <br>두근두근 너의 눈빛 <br>내 마음을 살살 녹여 <br>부드러운 눈빛에 솜사탕처럼 <br>두근두근 너의 눈빛 <br>내 마음을 살살 녹여 <br>오늘따라 울적한 기분도 떠나가고 <br>두근두근 너의 눈빛 <br>내 마음을 살살 녹여 <br>부드러운 눈빛에 솜사탕처럼 <br>두근두근 너의 눈빛 <br>내 마음을 살살 녹여 <br>]]></content><category term="오렌지핀" label="오렌지핀"/><category term="솜사탕" label="솜사탕"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/곽진언/환생/</id><title>곽진언 - 환생 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:16:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:16:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%BD%EC%A7%84%EC%96%B8/%ED%99%98%EC%83%9D/" title="곽진언 - 환생 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다시 태어난 것 같아요 <br>내 모든 게 달라졌어요 <br>그대 만난 후로 난 새사람이 됐어요 <br>우리 어머니가 제일 놀라요 <br>할 때도 안 된 샤워를 하며 <br>그 멜로디를 따라 해요 <br>늘 힘들었던 나의 아침이 <br>이렇게 즐거울 수 있나요 <br>오 놀라워라 그대 향한 내 마음 <br>오 새로워라 처음 보는 내 모습 <br>매일 이렇다면 모진 이 세상도 <br>참 살아갈 만 할 거예요 <br>관심도 없던 꽃가게에서 <br>발길이 멈춰져요 <br>주머니 털어 한 다발 샀죠 <br>오늘은 아무 날도 아닌데 <br>오 놀라워라 그대 향한 내 마음 <br>오 새로워라 처음 보는 내 모습 <br>매일 이렇다면 <br>모진 이 세상도 <br>참 살아갈 만 할 거야 <br>오 놀라워라 그대 향한 내 마음 <br>오 새로워라 처음 보는 내 모습 <br>매일 이렇다면 모진 이 세상도 <br>참 살아갈 만 할 거예요 <br>오 놀라워라 그대 향한 내 마음 <br>오 새로워라 처음 보는 내 모습 <br>매일 이렇다면 모진 이 세상도 <br>참 살아갈 만 할 거예요 <br>참 살아갈 만 할 거예요 <br>참 살아갈 만 할 거예요 <br>]]></content><category term="곽진언" label="곽진언"/><category term="환생" label="환생"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로이킴/오래전_그날/</id><title>로이킴 - 오래전 그날 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:16:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:16:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EC%9D%B4%ED%82%B4/%EC%98%A4%EB%9E%98%EC%A0%84_%EA%B7%B8%EB%82%A0/" title="로이킴 - 오래전 그날 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[교복을 벗고 <br>처음으로 만났던 너 <br>그때가 너도 가끔 생각나니 <br>뭐가 그렇게도 좋았었는지 <br>우리 둘만 있으면 <br>너의 집 데려다주던 길을 걸으며 <br>수줍게 나눴던 많은 꿈 <br>너를 지켜주겠다던 다짐 속에 <br>그렇게 몇 해는 지나 <br>너의 새 남자친구 얘길 들었지 <br>나 제대하기 얼마 전 <br>이해했던 만큼 미움도 커졌었지만 <br>오늘 난 감사드렸어 <br>몇 해 지나 얼핏 너를 봤을 때 <br>누군가 널 그처럼 아름답게 <br>지켜주고 있었음을 <br>그리고 지금 내 곁엔 <br>나만을 믿고 있는 한 여자와 <br>잠 못 드는 나를 달래는 <br>오래전 그 노래만이 <br>새 학기가 시작되는 학교에는 <br>그 옛날 우리의 모습이 있지 <br>뭔가 분주하게 약속이 많은 <br>스무 살의 설레임 <br>너의 학교 그 앞을 난 가끔 거닐지 <br>일상에 찌들어 갈 때면 <br>우리 슬픈 계산은 없었던 시절 <br>난 만날 수 있을 테니 <br>너의 새 남자친구 얘길 들었지 <br>나 제대하기 얼마 전 <br>이해했던 만큼 미움도 커졌었지만 <br>오늘 난 감사드렸어 <br>몇 해 지나 얼핏 너를 봤을 때 <br>누군가 널 그처럼 아름답게 <br>지켜주고 있었음을 <br>그리고 지금 내 곁엔 <br>나만을 믿고 있는 한 여자와 <br>잠 못 드는 나를 달래는 <br>오래전 그 노래만이 <br>]]></content><category term="로이킴" label="로이킴"/><category term="오래전 그날" label="오래전 그날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이석훈/Annie/</id><title>이석훈 - Annie - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:16:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:16:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%9D%ED%9B%88/Annie/" title="이석훈 - Annie - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Annie 혹시나 알고 있나요 <br>내가 사랑한다는 걸 <br>안다면 그대는 나빠요 <br>얼마나 애태웠는지 <br>Annie 이 노랠 듣고 있나요 <br>그대가 바로 Annie예요 <br>말하지 못했던 내 마음 <br>이제는 털어놓을게요 <br>야 이 바보야 <br>난 널 사랑하고 있어 <br>얼마나 내게 위안이 됐는지 <br>긴 아픔 멈춘 게 <br>다시 웃게 만든 게 너야 <br>Annie 조금은 후련하네요 <br>정말 외치고 싶었는데 <br>내 앞에 Annie는 없지만 <br>고백한 것 같아 좋아요 <br>야 이 바보야 <br>야 이 바보야 <br>난 널 사랑하고 있어 <br>얼마나 내게 위안이 됐는지 <br>긴 아픔 멈춘 게 <br>다시 웃게 만든 게 너야 <br>느끼고 싶어 <br>네가 내게 주는 사랑 <br>바라기만 하는 내 모습 <br>이해해주길 바래 <br>내게로 올 수 있다면 <br>아주 긴 시간 동안 보답할게 <br>아주 긴 시간 동안 보답할게 <br>Annie 그래도 모르겠나요 <br>그대가 바로 Annie란 걸 <br>]]></content><category term="이석훈" label="이석훈"/><category term="Annie" label="Annie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신용재_포맨/거리에서/</id><title>신용재 (포맨) - 거리에서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:16:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:16:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9A%A9%EC%9E%AC_%ED%8F%AC%EB%A7%A8/%EA%B1%B0%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C/" title="신용재 (포맨) - 거리에서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[네가 없는 거리에는 <br>내가 할 일이 없어서 <br>마냥 걷다 걷다 보면 <br>추억을 가끔 마주치지 <br>떠오르는 너의 모습 <br>내 살아나는 그리움 한 번에 <br>참 잊기 힘든 사람이란 걸 <br>또 한 번 느껴지는 하루 <br>어디쯤에 머무는지 <br>또 어떻게 살아가는지 <br>걷다 보면 누가 말해줄 것 같아 <br>이 거리가 익숙했던 <br>우리 발걸음이 나란했던 <br>그리운 날들 <br>오늘 밤 나를 찾아온다 <br>널 그리는 널 부르는 내 하루는 <br>애태워도 마주친 추억이 반가워 <br>날 부르는 목소리에 돌아보면 <br>텅 빈 거리 어느새 <br>수많은 네 모습만 가득해 <br>막다른 길 다다라서 <br>낯익은 벽 기대보며 <br>가로등 속 환히 비춰지는 <br>고백하는 네가 보여 <br>떠오르는 그 때 모습 <br>내 살아나는 설레임 한 번에 <br>참 잊기 힘든 순간이란 걸 <br>또 한 번 느껴지는 하루 <br>아직 나를 생각할지 <br>또 그녀도 나를 찾을지 <br>걷다 보면 누가 말해줄 것 같아 <br>이 거리가 익숙했던 <br>우리 발걸음이 나란했던 <br>그리운 날들 <br>오늘 밤 나를 찾아온다 <br>널 그리는 널 부르는 내 하루는 <br>애태워도 마주친 추억이 반가워 <br>날 부르는 목소리에 돌아보면 <br>텅 빈 거리 어느새 <br>수많은 네 모습만 가득해 <br>부풀은 내 가슴이 <br>밤하늘에 외쳐본다 <br>이 거리는 널 기다린다고 <br>널 그리는 널 부르는 내 하루는 <br>널 그리는 널 부르는 내 하루는 <br>널 그리는 널 부르는 내 하루는 <br>애태워도 마주친 추억이 반가워 <br>날 부르는 목소리에 돌아보면 <br>텅 빈 거리 어느새 <br>수많은 네 모습만 가득해 <br>]]></content><category term="신용재 (포맨)" label="신용재 (포맨)"/><category term="거리에서" label="거리에서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스윙스/뭔말알/</id><title>스윙스 - 뭔말알 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:17:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:17:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%EC%9C%99%EC%8A%A4/%EB%AD%94%EB%A7%90%EC%95%8C/" title="스윙스 - 뭔말알 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 삶 for 죽이는 Bars <br>다 갖다 받쳐 popping <br>아직 밥벌이는 nah <br>똑같지만 날 막지 못 해 <br>돈은 종이일 뿐이고 <br>내 꿈은 더 높이 있지 그래 우주를 봐 <br>랩하는 애들은 넘쳐나고 <br>나같은 놈은 찾기 힘들지 <br>what is going on here <br>너넨 왜 매일 랩을 해 <br>여긴 에버랜드 쟤넨 전부 다 꼬마들 <br>i just wanna kill them <br>all one by one like I'm J <br>sippin smokin 필요없이 <br>취할 줄 알지 fly high ooh yeah <br>주홍이랑 chillin in our dreams <br>김신이랑 swimming in the wave <br>my fam got my back <br>난 무서울 게 하나 없이 계속 유영해 <br>finally bigger payback <br>빚어냈지 내 소리로 꿈에 다가가 잡아 <br>wack ass rappers 너네 뭣같은 음악들 <br>겁 없이 내 앞에 다 가져와봐 <br>세대교체는 시작됐고 <br>너네들은 자리를 다 겁내잖아 <br>세대교체는 시작됐고 <br>너네들은 자리를 다 겁내잖아 <br>결국엔 올라간다 난 의심하지 않아 <br>무슨 말인지 알아 무슨 말인지 알아 <br>난 장난이 아냐 내 얼굴을 봐봐 <br>무슨 말인지 알아 <br>무슨 말인지 알아 <br>내가 볼 땐 모르는 것 같아 <br>무슨 말인지 알아 무슨 말인지 알아 <br>진짜로 무슨 말하는지 이제 알아 <br>can ya dig it <br>ya dig it <br>ya dig it <br>ya dig it 뭔말알 <br>ya dig it ya dig it ya dig it <br>디기 디기 뜨 띠기 띠기 띠기 띠기 <br>ya dig it ya dig it <br>디기 디기 뜨 띠기 띠기 띠기 <br>난 적당히 유행하는 것 <br>건드려보는 정도 안 따라해 <br>뒤를 볼 땐 애들 챙길 뿐 <br>정상에 집중해 난 산악회 <br>내 존재 자체가 Las Vegas <br>여기 이 문화적인 사막에 <br>한국에서 가장 큰 trend setter <br>2037 대선 나갈래 <br>누가 나만큼 야망 있어 <br>내가 한 것의 절반 <br>안 했으면 가만 있어 <br>내 앞에서 hater 얘기 <br>마 다 아가리 shut <br>골목서 나와도 아직 <br>골목이 남아있어 내 안에 <br>그러니 따가리 켜 불 붙여 임마 <br>한 날라리의 판타진 이제 <br>10년 뒤에 됐지 문 대표님 시대 <br>난 맨날 꿈 꿔 잘 때도 일해 <br>내가 원래 이래 간지 돼지 <br>초딩 때 맨날 했던 말이 뭔지 알아 <br>100년에 한 번 나올까 말까하는 애기 <br>가짜들은 내 앞에서 작아지지 <br>회장이 될 놈 <br>나를 정말 사랑하지 하나님이 <br>장애물 따위 그래 뭐 있어 <br>새로 사귄 여자친군 또 이뻐 <br>코끼리는 개미들과 싸우지 않지 <br>난 맘모스 급 <br>의식도 못하고 밟지만 oops <br>절대 누구 뒤에 숨은 적이 <br>한 번 없어 hater 나와보라고 <br>고등래퍼 왜 나가냐 하는 힙찔이 <br>내년에도 생각이 똑같기를 <br>진심으로 바래 <br>show me the 할 때도 <br>똑같았지 뭐 싹 다 <br>말 바꿨지 <br>구라가 아냐 모두가 내 발 아래 <br>결국엔 올라간다 난 의심하지 않아 <br>무슨 말인지 알아 무슨 말인지 알아 <br>난 장난이 아냐 내 얼굴을 봐봐 <br>무슨 말인지 알아 <br>무슨 말인지 알아 <br>내가 볼 땐 모르는 것 같아 <br>무슨 말인지 알아 무슨 말인지 알아 <br>진짜로 무슨 말하는지 이제 알아 <br>can ya dig it <br>ya dig it <br>ya dig it <br>ya dig it 뭔말알 <br>ya dig it ya dig it ya dig it <br>디기 디기 뜨 띠기 띠기 띠기 띠기 <br>ya dig it ya dig it <br>디기 디기 뜨 띠기 띠기 띠기 <br>]]></content><category term="스윙스" label="스윙스"/><category term="뭔말알" label="뭔말알"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/기리보이/Bunzi_번지/</id><title>기리보이 - Bunzi (번지) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:17:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:17:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4/Bunzi_%EB%B2%88%EC%A7%80/" title="기리보이 - Bunzi (번지) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Y O U N G B <br>나머진 받아가 페널티 <br>게을러진 형들 덕에 배려진 기준 <br>다시 세워 이제 <br>분발 못한 꼰대 넌 쉬고 <br>꿈나무들 배워 <br>기부하고 첫 번째 Level <br>위험해 내 ground <br>No flex zone b-site <br>전부 비벼내 뒤에 더 피곤해 <br>져도 괜찮아 얼마 뒤 <br>진열될 내 방 <br>gold ring gold chain <br>빌렸네 <br>1년을 또 한 번 쇼미 4 and 5 <br>나와도 다 통 편집 돼 <br>다 먹어 17년엔 <br>dickids on wave <br>내 앞에 빛이 된 내 Flow <br>Some people talk about me <br>난 귀여운 건 됐고 <br>넌 갇히지 facebook에 <br>날 보고 다 비명을 뱉어 <br>여기 내 위치지 space <br>넌 못 미치지 rappers <br>이건 Chapter 말했지 <br>fake or real 상관없고 <br>난 전부 챙겨 찢어진 신발 바꿔 <br>계속해 올라 게이지 <br>배낭에 담아 내 mic <br>뿌릴때야 이젠 삼다수 when I splash <br>다른 세상으로 번지 <br>네비에 안찍히는 번지 <br>세상에 이런 일이 일어나 <br>일어나 일어나 <br>일어나 일어나 일어나 <br>세상에 이런 일이 일어나 <br>일어나 일어나 <br>일어나 일어나 일어나 <br>세상에 이런 일이 <br>내방을 바꾸고 싶어 <br>너무나 뻔한게 싫어 <br>내 슬럼픈 항상 내 밤보다 길어 <br>괜히 또 방이나 치워 이제는 <br>다른 게 필요해 검은색 물감이 싫어 <br>When I paint a picture 다른 칠을 해 <br>아는 건 지루해 다른 곳으로 갈래 <br>내가 최고인 곳에 질투심은 놓고 가 <br>지름길은 괜찮아 <br>니들끼리 잘해봐라 <br>난 이미 짐 쌌어 <br>내 동료는 만화 책에 살아서 <br>난 집을 나왔어 <br>이제 갈 거야 <br>원피스 보다 쩌는 것을 찾아서 <br>Oh 반겨줘 오직 Hello to the ladies <br>술만 먹는 래퍼들이 <br>너무 많아 왜이리 <br>I gotta get that feeling <br>얘넨 없어 느낌이 <br>내 성공이 운이라면 <br>내 능력치는 Amazing <br>난 수업 같은 미팅들은 쨌어 <br>카메라든 불청객들은 됐어 <br>이젠 혼자서라도 난 가야겠어 <br>내 친구는 안전벨트를 맸어 <br>다른 세상으로 번지 <br>네비에 안찍히는 번지 <br>세상에 이런 일이 일어나 <br>일어나 일어나 <br>일어나 일어나 일어나 <br>세상에 이런 일이 일어나 <br>일어나 일어나 <br>일어나 일어나 일어나 <br>세상에 이런 일이 <br>우린 밤 새고 다른 세계로 뛰어 <br>걔네들은 못 할 체계로 더 <br>헤매었던 그때와 달리 <br>난 제대로 걷지 <br>더 한걸 내게 던져 <br>난 더 세게 뻗어 가 <br>엄마 여긴 높아 <br>공 차다 질려 했던 바보짓 <br>돌아보니 완전히 변한 <br>내 모습을 난 봤고 <br>그와 반대로 변함없는 <br>2년 전의 나의 pride <br>so time to shine <br>날개 달고 비상하지 fly <br>다른 세상으로 번지 <br>네비에 안찍히는 번지 <br>세상에 이런 일이 일어나 <br>일어나 일어나 <br>일어나 일어나 일어나 <br>세상에 이런 일이 일어나 <br>일어나 일어나 <br>일어나 일어나 일어나 <br>세상에 이런 일이 <br>]]></content><category term="기리보이" label="기리보이"/><category term="Bunzi (번지)" label="Bunzi (번지)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/매드클라운/엄석대_Bully/</id><title>매드클라운 - 엄석대 (Bully) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:17:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:17:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%A4%EB%93%9C%ED%81%B4%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%97%84%EC%84%9D%EB%8C%80_Bully/" title="매드클라운 - 엄석대 (Bully) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[uh 두리번대 <br>거들먹대며 복도를 걷네 ay ay <br>종이 땡땡 울리면 장난감 포착하고 <br>당장 play game해 <br>너 똑바로 어딜 봐 <br>미친놈아 너 눈깔어 <br>아가리는 쭉 닫어 하 <br>바닥에다가 확 전부 갈어 <br>친구라는 놈들이 <br>대체 구해줄까 누가 널 <br>폭력은 여기저길 스며들고 <br>선생은 보질 못하네 <br>올라타고서 주먹질을 <br>미친듯이 하고 보니 <br>중학교 때 제일 친한 친구네 <br>울엄만 또 걱정해 <br>매일 매일이 내 걱정 예 <br>점점 떨어지는 성적 <br>저녁 식사 정적 <br>damn I'm messed up <br>훔친 오토바일 타고 <br>오락실로 가면 <br>동전을 쌓은 형들이 날 때리고 <br>그때 배웠지 <br>이빨 사이 침을 뱉는 법을 <br>새로 나온 신발을 뺏는 법을 <br>권력은 나이를 가리지 않아 <br>엄마 pray for me <br>devil keep away from me <br>입에 구름물고 난 콜록댔고 <br>아마 그때부터 <br>아마 그때부터 <br>똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>느그 아부지 뭐 하노 엄석대 <br>야 똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>야 똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>누가 널 좋아하냐 엄석대 <br>친구와 함께 쉬는 시간에 <br>매점을 가는 게 낙 ay <br>수업시간에 잠자는 <br>애들이 한심해 보여 <br>옛 친구가 또 내 친굴 때렸대 <br>이제는 그러려니 해 <br>이르러 간 교무실 안에 <br>걔네 담임이 날 보고 먼저 한숨을 하 <br>익숙해 이런 날들도 <br>정신 좀 차리라고도 많이 해봤어 <br>많이 맞고 되려 정신 챙기고 <br>다니란 말 듣고 알았다며 울었어 ay <br>그저 두려운 마음 <br>내일은 돈까지 달래 <br>몰래 어머니의 지갑에 손대 <br>선재야 그러면 안 돼 <br>몰라 엄마보다 얘가 더 세 <br>ay 복돌 거닐 때가 두려워서 <br>이제는 매점도 못 가네 <br>짜피 돈 그것도 친구 <br>주머니에 들어있어 <br>빡치지만 나는 약자잖아 <br>참어 그냥 좀 참어 알잖아 <br>학교 선생도 이건 막아 봤자잖아 <br>많이 일러 봤었잖아 <br>결국 더 아픈 건 너야 <br>졸업할 때까지만 그냥 참어 <br>그냥 좀 참어 <br>똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>야 똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>느그 아부지 뭐 하노 엄석대 <br>똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>너 똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>야 똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>누가 널 좋아해 엄석대 <br>긴 시간을 버텨왔어 이제 <br>나를 비추지 않는듯해 빛이 <br>혼자 아파한 것도 몇 날 며칠 이젠 <br>견딜 수가 없어 갑자기 <br>머리를 스치는 생각 일단 감어 <br>눕기밖에 더해 그게 나을 수도 있지 <br>눈 딱 감고 쭉 뒤로 누워 실신 <br>알람은 안 맞출거야 부러진 시침 <br>똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>야 똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>느그 아부지 뭐 하노 엄석대 <br>똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>너 똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>야 똑바로 살어 엄석대 <br>누가 널 좋아해 엄석대 <br>]]></content><category term="매드클라운" label="매드클라운"/><category term="엄석대 (Bully)" label="엄석대 (Bully)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제시_Jessi/IM_GOOD/</id><title>제시 (Jessi) - I`M GOOD - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:17:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:17:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%8B%9C_Jessi/IM_GOOD/" title="제시 (Jessi) - I`M GOOD - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They call me jessi Ho <br>Don't act like you don't know <br>I got a real bad temper <br>and I'm boutta blow <br>Try to push my buttons <br>You ain't got the codes <br>steph curray in this state boy <br>I'm about the gold <br>I need a va cay <br>놀면서 벌어 네가 버는 거에 백배 <br>Mo was good was good <br>You ain't bout the bidness <br>Why you actin Hollywood <br>Thinkin that you know me <br>Hatin on me <br>cause you probably cant afford these <br>그냥 계속 질투해 <br>나도 그럴 거 같아 이제는 익숙해 <br>I'm good tho <br>난 내 갈 길을 가 <br>점점 빨라지는 속도 <br>질러 쭉 in the coupe with the roof <br>missing easy <br>badabing badaboom <br>I'm good <br>I'm good <br>I'm good <br>I'm good <br>나를 싫어해도 난 <br>나를 미워해도 난 <br>baby i'm still good <br>Um ah 인마 내 엉덩이 <br>난 이제 돈을 알아 <br>I wanna cheese cake <br>I don't chase money the money <br>be chase to me <br>VJ 말에 여전히 감전 된 뒤에 <br>Wo 이렇게 된 거 더 얄밉게 <br>넌 고등래퍼 본방 보고 잠 자 집에서 <br>난 너보다 잘하니까 이 Stage 위에 <br>난 너가 원하는 거 이제 다 가질게 <br>More friends wanna <br>빛나는 Gold chains도 Wanna <br>값 비싼 옷들도 원하고 <br>이 Good vibe도 Wanna <br>I'm good 내가 얼마나 증명해야 <br>이들은 반성을 하고 끝을 내 <br>그래 Fool 여유롭게 춤을 출래 <br>I wanna dancing <br>여친과 함께 있을 때는 <br>I don't watch it ESPN <br>Real recognize real <br>한 여기 상황도 넌 질투하지만 <br>yes I'm real and good <br>I'm good <br>I'm good <br>I'm good <br>I'm good <br>나를 싫어해도 난 <br>나를 미워해도 난 <br>baby i'm still good <br>Get back <br>You don't really want that <br>Get mad <br>You can't even have that <br>Step back <br>이런 내가 지금 어때 <br>Whatever you say <br>imma get it anyway <br>Get back <br>You don't really want that <br>Get mad <br>You can't even have that <br>Step back <br>이런 내가 지금 어때 <br>Whatever you say <br>imma get it anyway <br>I'm good <br>I'm good <br>I'm good <br>I'm good <br>나를 싫어해도 난 <br>나를 미워해도 난 <br>baby i'm still good <br>Still good Still good <br>Baby i'm still good <br>]]></content><category term="제시 (Jessi)" label="제시 (Jessi)"/><category term="I`M GOOD" label="I`M GOOD"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엄정화/나는_누구__Inst/</id><title>엄정화 - 나는 누구? (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:17:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:17:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%84%EC%A0%95%ED%99%94/%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%88%84%EA%B5%AC__Inst/" title="엄정화 - 나는 누구? (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어딜 둘러봐도 어둠뿐이야 <br>눈과 귀를 막고 <br>숨쉬는 것 조차 힘겨워 <br>슬픔이란 장막 안에 갇힌 나 <br>나는 누굴까 나는 누굴까 <br>밝은 미소라는 가면을 쓰고 <br>아름다움이란 <br>거짓 옷이 걸쳐져 있고 <br>뻔한 만남 속에 기쁜척하는 <br>나는 누굴까 나는 누구야 <br>내 안에 나는 이토록 울고 있는데 <br>찢어질 대로 찢어진 맘은 <br>죽어가는데 <br>다시 내 얼굴은 짙은 화장에 <br>다시 숨겨져 모두 가려져 <br>살아도 사는 게 아닌 하루 속에서 <br>깊은 한숨이 아닌 척 <br>크게 웃어야 하는 <br>이렇게 가려진 삶을 살아갈 <br>나는 누굴까 <br>이런 나에게도 찾아와줄까 <br>나의 상처 모두 사랑으로 <br>덮고 감싸줄 <br>밤새 품에 안겨 크게 울고픈 <br>너는 누굴까 너는 누구야 <br>내 안에 나는 이토록 울고 있는데 <br>찢어질 대로 찢어진 맘은 <br>죽어가는데 <br>다시 내 얼굴은 짙은 화장에 <br>다시 숨겨져 모두 가려져 <br>살아도 사는 게 아닌 하루 속에서 <br>깊은 한숨이 아닌 척 <br>크게 웃어야 하는 <br>이렇게 가려진 삶을 살아갈 <br>나는 누굴까 <br>보기 싫어 더 이상 번진 <br>너의 마스카라 <br>내 손에 닦아도 새까만한 게 <br>너의 가슴만할까 <br>이제 숨기지마 내게 니 맘을 <br>넌 다 알아 널 이해하니까 물론 <br>내게 기대도 돼 이제 너 혼자서 <br>괴로움에 떨지 않았으면 해 baby <br>이제 너의 대본에 <br>슬픔이란 단어는 빼 잦은 질문 앞에 <br>니가 너일 수 있게 <br>내 안에 나는 이토록 울고 있는데 <br>찢어질 대로 찢어진 맘은 <br>죽어가는데 <br>다시 내 얼굴은 짙은 화장에 <br>다시 숨겨져 모두 가려져 <br>살아도 사는 게 아닌 하루 속에서 <br>깊은 한숨이 아닌 척 <br>크게 웃어야 하는 <br>이렇게 가려진 삶을 살아갈 <br>나는 누굴까 <br>]]></content><category term="엄정화" label="엄정화"/><category term="나는 누구? (Inst.)" label="나는 누구? (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엄정화/나는_누구__Feat_덕배/</id><title>엄정화 - 나는 누구? (Feat. 덕배) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:17:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:17:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%84%EC%A0%95%ED%99%94/%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%88%84%EA%B5%AC__Feat_%EB%8D%95%EB%B0%B0/" title="엄정화 - 나는 누구? (Feat. 덕배) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어딜 둘러봐도 어둠뿐이야 <br>눈과 귀를 막고 <br>숨쉬는 것 조차 힘겨워 <br>슬픔이란 장막 안에 갇힌 나 <br>나는 누굴까 나는 누굴까 <br>밝은 미소라는 가면을 쓰고 <br>아름다움이란 <br>거짓 옷이 걸쳐져 있고 <br>뻔한 만남 속에 기쁜척하는 <br>나는 누굴까 나는 누구야 <br>내 안에 나는 이토록 울고 있는데 <br>찢어질 대로 찢어진 맘은 <br>죽어가는데 <br>다시 내 얼굴은 짙은 화장에 <br>다시 숨겨져 모두 가려져 <br>살아도 사는 게 아닌 하루 속에서 <br>깊은 한숨이 아닌 척 <br>크게 웃어야 하는 <br>이렇게 가려진 삶을 살아갈 <br>나는 누굴까 <br>이런 나에게도 찾아와줄까 <br>나의 상처 모두 사랑으로 <br>덮고 감싸줄 <br>밤새 품에 안겨 크게 울고픈 <br>너는 누굴까 너는 누구야 <br>내 안에 나는 이토록 울고 있는데 <br>찢어질 대로 찢어진 맘은 <br>죽어가는데 <br>다시 내 얼굴은 짙은 화장에 <br>다시 숨겨져 모두 가려져 <br>살아도 사는 게 아닌 하루 속에서 <br>깊은 한숨이 아닌 척 <br>크게 웃어야 하는 <br>이렇게 가려진 삶을 살아갈 <br>나는 누굴까 <br>보기 싫어 더 이상 번진 <br>너의 마스카라 <br>내 손에 닦아도 새까만한 게 <br>너의 가슴만할까 <br>이제 숨기지마 내게 니 맘을 <br>넌 다 알아 널 이해하니까 물론 <br>내게 기대도 돼 이제 너 혼자서 <br>괴로움에 떨지 않았으면 해 baby <br>이제 너의 대본에 <br>슬픔이란 단어는 빼 잦은 질문 앞에 <br>니가 너일 수 있게 <br>내 안에 나는 이토록 울고 있는데 <br>찢어질 대로 찢어진 맘은 <br>죽어가는데 <br>다시 내 얼굴은 짙은 화장에 <br>다시 숨겨져 모두 가려져 <br>살아도 사는 게 아닌 하루 속에서 <br>깊은 한숨이 아닌 척 <br>크게 웃어야 하는 <br>이렇게 가려진 삶을 살아갈 <br>나는 누굴까 <br>]]></content><category term="엄정화" label="엄정화"/><category term="나는 누구? (Feat. 덕배)" label="나는 누구? (Feat. 덕배)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동안/달려볼까/</id><title>동안 - 달려볼까 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:17:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:17:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EC%95%88/%EB%8B%AC%EB%A0%A4%EB%B3%BC%EA%B9%8C/" title="동안 - 달려볼까 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[달려볼까 <br>햇살 비치는 그 길을 따라 <br>떠나볼까 <br>너와 함께 할 그 길을 따라 <br>저 멀리 우릴 비춰오는 <br>태양을 보며 <br>그래 한번 가보자 <br>참 많이 오래 기다렸지 <br>왠지 떠나고 싶은 날이야 <br>뭘 망설이고 있는 거야 <br>내일은 내일로 오늘 나와 함께 <br>떠나자 둘이서 <br>시원한 바람맞으며 <br>저 높이 파란 하늘 끝까지 <br>날아보자 <br>달려볼까 <br>햇살 비치는 그 길을 따라 <br>떠나볼까 <br>너와 함께 할 그 길을 따라 <br>저 멀리 우릴 비춰오는 <br>태양을 보며 <br>그래 한번 가보자 <br>참 많이 오래 기다렸지 <br>왠지 떠나고 싶은 날이야 <br>뭘 망설이고 있는 거야 <br>내일은 내일로 오늘 나와 함께 <br>떠나자 둘이서 <br>시원한 바람맞으며 <br>저 높이 파란 하늘 끝까지 <br>날아보자 <br>달려볼까 <br>햇살 비치는 그 길을 따라 <br>떠나볼까 <br>너와 함께 할 그 길을 따라 <br>저 멀리 우릴 비춰오는 <br>태양을 보며 <br>그래 한번 가보자 <br>떠나자 둘이서 <br>시원한 바람맞으며 <br>저 높이 파란 하늘 끝까지 <br>날아보자 <br>달려볼까 <br>햇살 비치는 그 길을 따라 <br>떠나볼까 <br>너와 함께 할 그 길을 따라 <br>]]></content><category term="동안" label="동안"/><category term="달려볼까" label="달려볼까"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fromdear_프롬디어/출근길/</id><title>Fromdear (프롬디어) - 출근길 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:17:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:17:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fromdear_%ED%94%84%EB%A1%AC%EB%94%94%EC%96%B4/%EC%B6%9C%EA%B7%BC%EA%B8%B8/" title="Fromdear (프롬디어) - 출근길 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[출근하는 길 내 굽어있는 두 눈이 <br>지쳐가는 날 위로해주는 사진들 <br>힘든 일에도 웃을 수 있던 <br>친구들과 함께 <br>돌아가지 못할 지나가는 시간 <br>그리운 사람들 <br>집 앞에 멈춰 텅 빈 의자 위 <br>오래 전에 새긴 그때의 사랑도 <br>한적한 공원 운동장 위에 <br>교복 대신 삶을 걸친 <br>한 아저씨 하나 <br>퇴근하는 길 지나온 나의 하루가 <br>지쳐가는 날 일으켜 세운 사건들 <br>힘든 일에도 웃을 수 있던 <br>가족들과 함께 <br>돌아가지 못할 멈춰버린 시간 <br>아쉬움과 함께 <br>어두운 골목 처진 어깨 위 <br>오래 전에 새긴 그때의 느낌도 <br>오래된 선반 흐릿해진 기억 <br>웃음 대신 삶을 걸친 <br>한 아버지 하나 <br>]]></content><category term="Fromdear (프롬디어)" label="Fromdear (프롬디어)"/><category term="출근길" label="출근길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나윤성/Sunny_Day/</id><title>나윤성 - Sunny Day - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:17:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:17:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EC%9C%A4%EC%84%B1/Sunny_Day/" title="나윤성 - Sunny Day - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[봄은 어느새 다가와 <br>이젠 따스한 햇살이 <br>내 몸을 감싸 안으며 <br>나의 몸을 녹이고 <br>햇살처럼 내 맘에 <br>살며시 다가온 널 보며 <br>밝아진 내 얼굴엔 미소가 피네 <br>넌 날 웃게 해 <br>따스한 저 햇살처럼 <br>날 감싸 안으며 <br>네 미소가 날 비출 때 난 <br>아무런 생각 조차 할 수가 없어 <br>이미 나의 맘은 너에게로 <br>A Sunny Day <br>A Sunny Time <br>네 생각에 난 자꾸만 웃음이 나와 <br>오늘처럼 눈부시게 <br>날 보며 웃어줘 햇살처럼 <br>넌 날 웃게 해 <br>따스한 저 햇살처럼 <br>날 감싸 안으며 <br>네 미소가 날 비출 때 난 <br>아무런 생각조차 할 수가 없어 <br>이미 나의 맘은 너에게로 <br>A Sunny Day <br>A Sunny Time <br>네 생각에 난 자꾸만 웃음이 나와 <br>오늘처럼 눈부시게 <br>날 보며 웃어줘 <br>A Sunny Day <br>오늘처럼 나의 곁에서 <br>눈부시게 웃어줘 다시 햇살처럼 <br>]]></content><category term="나윤성" label="나윤성"/><category term="Sunny Day" label="Sunny Day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neptunica/Alive_Feat_Matt_DeFreitas/</id><title>Neptunica - Alive (Feat. Matt DeFreitas) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:17:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:17:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neptunica/Alive_Feat_Matt_DeFreitas/" title="Neptunica - Alive (Feat. Matt DeFreitas) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been on me own <br>Try'na <br>Find my way home <br>My way home <br>A familiar home <br>That I never <br>Never <br>Seem to let go <br>To let go <br>I've got Heaven and Hell on my shoulders <br>They're fighting over who will take over now <br>I'm just try'na <br>Try'na <br>Find my way home <br>My way home <br>The voices in my head are saying way to much <br>But I don't mind <br>Yeah I'm alive <br>The voice and then the bullet until I had enough <br>But I don't mind <br>Yeah <br>I'M ALIVE <br>Drop <br>Drowning in my dreams <br>But my dreams, they sense a blur to reality <br>To reality <br>A familiar scene <br>The truth is that I never know who I will be <br>Who I'll be <br>I've got Heaven and Hell on my shoulders <br>They're fighting over who will take over now <br>I'm just try'na <br>Try'na <br>Find my way home <br>My way home <br>The voices in my head are saying way to much <br>But I don't mind <br>Yeah I'm alive <br>The voice and then the bullet until I had enough <br>But I don't mind <br>Yeah <br>But I don't mind <br>Yeah <br>I'M ALIVE <br>Drop <br>Hey <br>The voices in my head are saying way to much <br>But I don't mind Yeah I'm alive]]></content><category term="Neptunica" label="Neptunica"/><category term="Alive (Feat. Matt DeFreitas)" label="Alive (Feat. Matt DeFreitas)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/몬스터_드럼/</id><title>트니트니 - 몬스터 드럼 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:17:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:17:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EB%AA%AC%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B0_%EB%93%9C%EB%9F%BC/" title="트니트니 - 몬스터 드럼 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 4) <br>앞으로 굴러갔다 (앞으로 굴러갔다) <br>뒤로 돌아와요 (뒤로 돌아와요) <br>앞으로 굴러갔다 (앞으로 굴러갔다) <br>뒤로 돌아와요 (서프라이즈) <br><br>몬스터 드럼 힘차게 두드려요 <br>몬스터 드럼 신나게 두드려요 <br>몬스터 드럼 힘차게 두드려요 <br>몬스터 드럼 신나게 두드려요 <br><br>(다같이 리듬에 맞춰서 1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 4) <br>앞으로 굴러갔다 (앞으로 굴러갔다) <br>뒤로 돌아와요 (뒤로 돌아와요) <br>앞으로 굴러갔다 (앞으로 굴러갔다) <br>뒤로 돌아와요 (서프라이즈) <br><br>몬스터 드럼 힘차게 두드려요 <br>몬스터 드럼 신나게 두드려요 <br>몬스터 드럼 힘차게 두드려요 <br>몬스터 드럼 신나게 두드려요]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="몬스터 드럼" label="몬스터 드럼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/몬스터_똥/</id><title>트니트니 - 몬스터 똥 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:17:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:17:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EB%AA%AC%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B0_%EB%98%A5/" title="트니트니 - 몬스터 똥 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(몬스터 똥똥 몬스터 똥똥 <br>몬스터 똥똥 몬스터 똥똥) <br>뚫어 뚫어 뚫어 뽕~ <br>뚫어 뚫어 뚫어 뽕~ <br>뚫어 뚫어 뚫어 뽕~ 몬스터 똥똥 <br>뚫어 뚫어 뚫어 뽕~ <br>뚫어 뚫어 뚫어 뽕~ <br>뚫어 뚫어 뚫어 뽕~ 몬스터 똥똥 <br><br>영차 영차 영차 붙여봐요 (뽕) <br>영차 영차 영차 눌러봐요 (뽕) <br>영차 영차 영차 당겨봐요 (뽕) <br>영차 영차 영차 잘했어요 유후~ <br><br>(몬스터 똥똥 몬스터 똥똥 <br>몬스터 똥똥 몬스터 똥똥) <br>뚫어 뚫어 뚫어 뽕~ <br>뚫어 뚫어 뚫어 뽕~ <br>뚫어 뚫어 뚫어 뽕~ 몬스터 똥똥 <br>뚫어 뚫어 뚫어 뽕~ <br>뚫어 뚫어 뚫어 뽕~ <br>뚫어 뚫어 뚫어 뽕~ 몬스터 똥똥 <br><br>영차 영차 영차 붙여봐요 (뽕) <br>영차 영차 영차 눌러봐요 (뽕) <br>영차 영차 영차 당겨봐요 (뽕) <br>영차 영차 영차 잘했어요 유후]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="몬스터 똥" label="몬스터 똥"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/몬스터_우주선/</id><title>트니트니 - 몬스터 우주선 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:17:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:17:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EB%AA%AC%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B0_%EC%9A%B0%EC%A3%BC%EC%84%A0/" title="트니트니 - 몬스터 우주선 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(몬스터 우주선) <br>삐리삐리 우주선 타고 날아가요 <br>멀리 날아가요 (슝슝) <br>삐리삐리 우주선 타고 날아가요 <br>멀리 날아가 <br><br>차차차 몬스터 차차차 우주선 <br>차차차 외계인 <br>차차 찾아봐요 <br>차차차 몬스터 차차차 우주선 <br>외계인 찾아 떠나요 출동~ <br><br>삐리삐리 우주선 타고 날아가요 <br>멀리 날아가요 (슝슝) <br>삐리삐리 우주선 타고 날아가요 <br>멀리 날아가 <br><br>차차차 몬스터 차차차 우주선 <br>차차차 외계인 <br>차차 찾아봐요 <br>차차차 몬스터 차차차 우주선 <br>외계인 찾아 떠나요 출동]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="몬스터 우주선" label="몬스터 우주선"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/별이_되었네/</id><title>트니트니 - 별이 되었네 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EB%B3%84%EC%9D%B4_%EB%90%98%EC%97%88%EB%84%A4/" title="트니트니 - 별이 되었네 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[“트니트니 친구들 <br>세모난 세모난 세모가 별이 됐대요” <br><br>세모난 세모가 세모를 만났네 (뾰족) <br>세모난 세모가 세모를 만났네 (뾰족) <br>세모난 세모가 세모를 만났네 (뾰족) <br>반짝반짝 빛나네 (반짝) <br><br>별이되어 (숑) 별이되어 (숑) <br>반짝반짝 빛나는 별이되어 (숑숑) <br>별이되어 (숑) 별이되어 (숑) <br>반짝반짝 빛나는 별이되었네 (숑숑) <br><br>“반짝 반짝 반짝 반짝 별이 보이네” <br>세모난 세모가 세모를 만났네 (뾰족) <br>세모난 세모가 세모를 만났네 (뾰족) <br>세모난 세모가 세모를 만났네 (뾰족) <br>반짝반짝 빛나네 (반짝) <br><br>별이되어 (숑) 별이되어 (숑) <br>반짝반짝 빛나는 별이되어 (숑숑) <br>별이되어 (숑) 별이되어 (숑) <br>반짝반짝 빛나는 별이되었네 (숑숑)]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="별이 되었네" label="별이 되었네"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/불가사리와_반짝_별/</id><title>트니트니 - 불가사리와 반짝 별 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EB%B6%88%EA%B0%80%EC%82%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%99%80_%EB%B0%98%EC%A7%9D_%EB%B3%84/" title="트니트니 - 불가사리와 반짝 별 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(우리 둘은 서로 닮았죠~ 정말? ) <br>불가사리 반짝반짝 별 <br>불가사리 반짝반짝 별 <br>우리 둘이 닮았나요 <br>우리 둘이 닮았나요 <br><br>별빛 별빛 친구야 (반짝) <br>불빛 불빛 친구야 (활활) <br>별빛 별빛 친구야 (반짝) <br>불빛 불빛 친구야 (활활) <br><br>(우리 둘은 서로 닮았죠~ 정말? ) <br>불가사리 반짝반짝 별 <br>불가사리 반짝반짝 별 <br>우리 둘이 닮았나요 <br>우리 둘이 닮았나요 <br><br>별빛 별빛 친구야 (반짝) <br>불빛 불빛 친구야 (활활) <br>별빛 별빛 친구야 (반짝) <br>불빛 불빛 친구야 (활활)]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="불가사리와 반짝 별" label="불가사리와 반짝 별"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/빙글빙글/</id><title>트니트니 - 빙글빙글 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EB%B9%99%EA%B8%80%EB%B9%99%EA%B8%80/" title="트니트니 - 빙글빙글 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(빙글빙글 돌면서 열어 볼까요?) <br>열려라 열려라 열려라 <br>열려라 열려 열려 <br>열려라 열려라 열려라 <br>열려라 열려 열려 <br>열려라 열려라 열려라 <br>열려라 열려 열려 <br>열려라 열려라 열려라 <br>열려라 열려 열려 <br><br>(빙글빙글 돌면서 열어 볼까요?) <br>열려라 열려라 열려라 <br>열려라 열려 열려 <br>열려라 열려라 열려라 <br>열려라 열려 열려 <br>열려라 열려라 열려라 <br>열려라 열려 열려 <br>열려라 열려라 열려라 <br>열려라 열려 열려]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="빙글빙글" label="빙글빙글"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/불가사리/</id><title>트니트니 - 불가사리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EB%B6%88%EA%B0%80%EC%82%AC%EB%A6%AC/" title="트니트니 - 불가사리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(깊고 깊은 바다에서 온 나는 불가사리) <br>사리사리사리 난 불가사리 <br>사리사리사리 불가사리 (사리) <br>사리사리사리 난 불가사리 <br>사리사리사리 불가사리 (사리) <br><br>깊고 깊은 바닷속에 (반짝) <br>깊고 깊은 바닷속에 (반짝) <br>깊고 깊은 바닷속에 (반짝) <br>깊고 깊은 바닷속에 (반짝) <br><br>(깊고 깊은 바다에서 온 나는 불가사리) <br>사리사리사리 난 불가사리 <br>사리사리사리 불가사리 (사리) <br>사리사리사리 난 불가사리 <br>사리사리사리 불가사리 (사리) <br><br>깊고 깊은 바닷속에 (반짝) <br>깊고 깊은 바닷속에 (반짝) <br>깊고 깊은 바닷속에 (반짝) <br>깊고 깊은 바닷속에 (반짝)]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="불가사리" label="불가사리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/어쩐지/</id><title>트니트니 - 어쩐지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EC%96%B4%EC%A9%90%EC%A7%80/" title="트니트니 - 어쩐지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(누구 있나요 누구 있나요 누구 있나요) <br>똑똑똑 누가 있나요 (저기요) <br>누가 있나요 (없나요~?) <br>똑똑똑 누가 있나요 (저기요) <br>누가 있나요 (없나요~?) <br>나는 나무꾼이에요 <br>혹시 누가 있다면 <br>대답을 해 주세요 대답해줘요 <br><br>어쩐지 어쩐지~ 누가 있을 것 같더라 <br>어쩐지 어쩐지~ 누가 있을 것 같더라 <br>어쩐지 어쩐지~ 누가 있을 것 같더라 <br>어쩐지 어쩐지~ 누가 있을 것 같더라 <br>어쩐지 <br><br>(누구 있나요 누구 있나요 누구 있나요) <br>똑똑똑 누가 있나요 (저기요) <br>누가 있나요 (없나요~?) <br>똑똑똑 누가 있나요 (저기요) <br>누가 있나요 (없나요~?) <br>나는 나무꾼이에요 <br>혹시 누가 있다면 <br>대답을 해 주세요 <br>대답해줘요 (어쩐지)]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="어쩐지" label="어쩐지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/왜_그러는_건데/</id><title>트니트니 - 왜 그러는 건데 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EC%99%9C_%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%AC%EB%8A%94_%EA%B1%B4%EB%8D%B0/" title="트니트니 - 왜 그러는 건데 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(와이 와이 와이 와이) <br>도대체 도대체 도대체 <br>왜 그러는 건데 (왜) 왜 그러는데 (왜) <br>도대체 도대체 도대체 <br>왜 그러는 건데 (왜) 왜 그러는데 (왜) <br><br>네가 나무를 베려 했잖아 (네가) <br>네가 나무를 베려 했잖아 (네가) <br>네가 나무를 베려 했잖아 <br>여긴 우리 집이란 말이야 <br><br>(와이 와이 와이 와이) <br>도대체 도대체 도대체 <br>왜 그러는 건데 (왜) 왜 그러는데 (왜) <br>도대체 도대체 도대체 <br>왜 그러는 건데 (왜) 왜 그러는데 (왜) <br><br>네가 나무를 베려 했잖아 (네가) <br>네가 나무를 베려 했잖아 (네가) <br>네가 나무를 베려 했잖아 <br>여긴 우리 집이란 말이야]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="왜 그러는 건데" label="왜 그러는 건데"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/나무꾼/</id><title>트니트니 - 나무꾼 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EB%82%98%EB%AC%B4%EA%BE%BC/" title="트니트니 - 나무꾼 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(나무꾼 나가신다~~ <br>모두 길을 비켜라~~~) <br>나무하자 하 나무하자 하 <br>다 베어버리겠다 (하하) <br>나무하자 하 나무하자 하 <br>다 썰어버리겠다 <br>나무하자 하 나무하자 하 <br>다 베어버리겠다 (하하) <br>나무하자 하 나무하자 하 <br>다 썰어버리겠다 <br><br>도끼 타고 달려가자 (다다다) <br>도끼 타고 달려가자 (다다다) <br>도끼 타고 달려가자 (다다다) <br>다 썰어버릴까~ <br><br>(나무꾼 나가신다~~ <br>모두 길을 비켜라~~~) <br>나무하자 하 나무하자 하 <br>다 베어버리겠다 (하하) <br>나무하자 하 나무하자 하 <br>다 썰어버리겠다 <br>나무하자 하 나무하자 하 <br>다 베어버리겠다 (하하) <br>나무하자 하 나무하자 하 <br>다 썰어버리겠다 <br><br>도끼 타고 달려가자 (다다다) <br>도끼 타고 달려가자 (다다다) <br>도끼 타고 달려가자 (다다다) <br>다 썰어버릴까~]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="나무꾼" label="나무꾼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/나무_아파트/</id><title>트니트니 - 나무 아파트 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EB%82%98%EB%AC%B4_%EC%95%84%ED%8C%8C%ED%8A%B8/" title="트니트니 - 나무 아파트 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(짹짹 짹짹, 어흥, 이히히히히, 음메에에에) <br>1층에는 여왕벌 작은 여왕벌 <br>(엥~~~~~) <br>2층에는 다람쥐 작은 다람쥐 <br>(찍찍찍찍찍찍) <br>3층에는 꼬꼬닭 작은 꼬꼬닭 <br>(꼬꼬꼬꼬꼬꼬) <br>우리 집에 놀러와 집에 놀러와 (컴온) <br><br>파트 파트 아파트 나무 아파트 <br>(1층입니다) <br>파트 파트 아파트 나무 아파트 <br>(2층입니다) <br>파트 파트 아파트 나무 아파트 <br>모두 모여 살고 있어요 (예~~~) <br><br>1층에는 여왕벌 작은 여왕벌 <br>(엥~~~~~) <br>2층에는 다람쥐 작은 다람쥐 <br>(찍찍찍찍찍찍) <br>3층에는 꼬꼬닭 작은 꼬꼬닭 <br>(꼬꼬꼬꼬꼬꼬) <br>우리 집에 놀러와 집에 놀러와 (컴온)]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="나무 아파트" label="나무 아파트"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/욕심부리지_말아요/</id><title>트니트니 - 욕심부리지 말아요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EC%9A%95%EC%8B%AC%EB%B6%80%EB%A6%AC%EC%A7%80_%EB%A7%90%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94/" title="트니트니 - 욕심부리지 말아요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(나눠 줘 나눠 줘 나눠 줘 나눠 줘) <br>나눠주세요 나눠주세요 친구들에게 <br>행복 두 배 된데요 <br>기쁨 두 배 된데요(두 배 두 배) <br><br>안돼요 안돼요 안돼 안돼요 <br>욕심부리면 안 돼 (안돼) <br>안돼요 안돼요 안돼 안돼요 <br>욕심부리면 안 돼 (안돼요~) <br><br>(나눠 줘 나눠 줘 나눠 줘 나눠 줘) <br>나눠주세요 나눠주세요 친구들에게 <br>행복 두 배 된데요 <br>기쁨 두 배 된데요(두 배 두 배) <br><br>안돼요 안돼요 안돼 안돼요 <br>욕심부리면 안 돼 (안돼) <br>안돼요 안돼요 안돼 안돼요 <br>욕심부리면 안 돼 <br>(욕심부리지 말아요~)]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="욕심부리지 말아요" label="욕심부리지 말아요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/무거운_나의_집/</id><title>트니트니 - 무거운 나의 집 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EB%AC%B4%EA%B1%B0%EC%9A%B4_%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%A7%91/" title="트니트니 - 무거운 나의 집 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(이건 딱~~~봐도 내 집이야~~~) <br>(그런데) <br>너무 무거워 너무 무거워 <br>휘청 휘청 휘청 휘청 휘~청 <br>너무 무거워 너무 무거워 <br>흔들 흔들 흔들 흔들 흔~들 <br><br>내 거야 이건 내 거야 <br>내 거야 내 거야 내 거야 <br>예쁘고 멋진 나의 집 내 거야 <br>내 거야 내 거야 <br><br><br>(그런데) <br>너무 무거워 너무 무거워 <br>휘청 휘청 휘청 휘청 휘~청 <br>너무 무거워 너무 무거워 <br>흔들 흔들 흔들 흔들 흔~들 <br><br>(만지지 마~ 이건 내 거야~~~) <br>내 거야 이건 내 거야 <br>내 거야 내 거야 내 거야 <br>예쁘고 멋진 나의 집 내 거야 <br>내 거야 내 거야 <br><br>(그런데) <br>너무 무거워 너무 무거워 <br>휘청 휘청 휘청 휘청 휘~청 <br>너무 무거워 너무 무거워 <br>흔들 흔들 흔들 흔들 흔~들 (낑낑)]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="무거운 나의 집" label="무거운 나의 집"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/걱정이_된다_큰_집_찾은_달식이/</id><title>트니트니 - 걱정이 된다 (큰 집 찾은 달식이) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EA%B1%B1%EC%A0%95%EC%9D%B4_%EB%90%9C%EB%8B%A4_%ED%81%B0_%EC%A7%91_%EC%B0%BE%EC%9D%80_%EB%8B%AC%EC%8B%9D%EC%9D%B4/" title="트니트니 - 걱정이 된다 (큰 집 찾은 달식이) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(우리 달식이~~~ 때문에 달식이 때문에) <br>걱정이 된다 걱정이 된다 <br>큰 집 찾은 달식이~ 걱정이 된다 <br>걱정이 된다 걱정이 된다 <br>큰 집 찾은 달식이~ 걱정이 된다 <br><br>(우리 달식이~~~ 때문에 달식이 때문에) <br>걱정이 된다 걱정이 된다 <br>큰 집 찾은 달식이~ 걱정이 된다 <br>걱정이 된다 걱정이 된다 <br>큰 집 찾은 달식이~ 걱정이 된다]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="걱정이 된다 (큰 집 찾은 달식이)" label="걱정이 된다 (큰 집 찾은 달식이)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/큰_집_주세요/</id><title>트니트니 - 큰 집 주세요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%ED%81%B0_%EC%A7%91_%EC%A3%BC%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94/" title="트니트니 - 큰 집 주세요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(작은 집 싫어! 큰 집! 좋~아 <br>작은 집 싫어! 큰 집! 좋~아) <br>나도 큰집을 갖고 싶어요 (큰 집) <br>아니 아니 아니 아니 <br>그건 안돼요 (그건) <br>나도 큰집을 갖고 싶어요 (아아~) <br>아니 아니 아니 아니 <br>그건 안돼요 (안돼요~) <br>나도 큰집을 갖고 싶어요 (큰 집) <br>아니 아니 아니 아니 <br>그건 안돼요 (그건) <br>나도 큰집을 갖고 싶어요 (아아~) <br>아니 아니 아니 아니 <br>그건 안돼요 (안돼요~) <br><br>왜 안되는데 왜 안되는데요 <br>너무너무 갖고 싶단 말이에요 (제발요~) <br>왜 안되는데 왜 안되는데요 <br>너무 갖고 싶어요 (큰 집~~~!) <br><br>나도 큰집을 갖고 싶어요 (큰 집) <br>아니 아니 아니 아니 <br>그건 안돼요 (그건) <br>나도 큰집을 갖고 싶어요 (아아~) <br>아니 아니 아니 아니 <br>그건 안돼요 (안돼요~) <br>그건 안돼요 (음~)]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="큰 집 주세요" label="큰 집 주세요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/걱정이_된다_욕심쟁이_달식이/</id><title>트니트니 - 걱정이 된다 (욕심쟁이 달식이) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EA%B1%B1%EC%A0%95%EC%9D%B4_%EB%90%9C%EB%8B%A4_%EC%9A%95%EC%8B%AC%EC%9F%81%EC%9D%B4_%EB%8B%AC%EC%8B%9D%EC%9D%B4/" title="트니트니 - 걱정이 된다 (욕심쟁이 달식이) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(우리 달식이~~~ 때문에 달식이 때문에) <br>걱정이 된다 걱정이 된다 <br>욕심쟁이 달식이~ 걱정이 된다 <br>걱정이 된다 걱정이 된다 <br>욕심쟁이 달식이~ 걱정이 된다 <br><br>(우리 달식이~~~ 때문에 달식이 때문에) <br>걱정이 된다 걱정이 된다 <br>욕심쟁이 달식이~ 걱정이 된다 <br>걱정이 된다 걱정이 된다 <br>욕심쟁이 달식이~ 걱정이 된다]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="걱정이 된다 (욕심쟁이 달식이)" label="걱정이 된다 (욕심쟁이 달식이)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/욕심쟁이_달식이/</id><title>트니트니 - 욕심쟁이 달식이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EC%9A%95%EC%8B%AC%EC%9F%81%EC%9D%B4_%EB%8B%AC%EC%8B%9D%EC%9D%B4/" title="트니트니 - 욕심쟁이 달식이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(달식이가 나타났다~~) <br>욕심쟁이 달식이 <br>달식이 달식이 (다 내 것) <br>욕심쟁이 달식이 <br>달식이 달식이 (다 내 것) <br>욕심쟁이 달식이 <br>달식이 달식이 (다 내 것) <br>욕심쟁이 달식이 <br>달식이 달식이 (다 내 것) <br><br>내 것 내 것도 내 것 <br>네 것 네 것도 내 것 <br>내 것 내 것도 내 것 <br>네 것 네 것도 내 것 (다 내 것~~~~) <br><br>욕심쟁이 달식이 <br>달식이 달식이 (다 내 것) <br>욕심쟁이 달식이 <br>달식이 달식이 (다 내 것) <br>욕심쟁이 달식이 <br>달식이 달식이 (다 내 것) <br>욕심쟁이 달식이 달식이 달식이 <br>달식이 달식이 (다 내 것~~~)]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="욕심쟁이 달식이" label="욕심쟁이 달식이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Honeymoon_Suite/New_Girl_Now_Live_At_The_Phoenix_Club_Toronto_Canada___2016/</id><title>Honeymoon Suite - New Girl Now (Live At The Phoenix Club, Toronto, Canada / 2016) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Honeymoon_Suite/New_Girl_Now_Live_At_The_Phoenix_Club_Toronto_Canada___2016/" title="Honeymoon Suite - New Girl Now (Live At The Phoenix Club, Toronto, Canada / 2016) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hot summer night <br>Storm lies in the air <br>My eyes are a little heavy <br>I'm feeling in the past tense <br>I'm hardly aware <br><br>I don't want you on the phone <br>don't you play that good girl with me <br>Why must I always say it again <br><br>I've got a new girl now <br>I've got a new girl now <br>I've got a new girl now <br>And she's a lot like you <br><br>I tried to wash my face <br>But my head fell to low <br>I tried to bury myself <br>But my mind wouldn't stay at home <br><br>I don't care if you're sitting at home <br>somebody has broken into me <br>Why must I always say it again <br><br>I got a new girl now <br>I got a new girl now <br>I got a new girl now <br>And she's a lot like you <br><br>I don't want you on the phone <br>don't you play good girl with me <br>Why must I always say it again <br><br>I've got a new girl now <br>I've got a new girl now <br>I've got a new girl now <br>And she's a lot like you]]></content><category term="Honeymoon Suite" label="Honeymoon Suite"/><category term="New Girl Now (Live At The Phoenix Club, Toronto, Canada / 2016)" label="New Girl Now (Live At The Phoenix Club, Toronto, Canada / 2016)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Honeymoon_Suite/Burning_In_Love_Live_At_The_Phoenix_Club_Toronto_Canada___2016/</id><title>Honeymoon Suite - Burning In Love (Live At The Phoenix Club, Toronto, Canada / 2016) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Honeymoon_Suite/Burning_In_Love_Live_At_The_Phoenix_Club_Toronto_Canada___2016/" title="Honeymoon Suite - Burning In Love (Live At The Phoenix Club, Toronto, Canada / 2016) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What did I say to you, what did you see me do <br>That made ya turn to stone overnight <br>I thought I played it right <br>Lovin' you deep in the night <br>The chain of love is broken now <br>Why can't we start again <br>'Cause my heart won't mend <br>But you say no, then you go, and I break down <br><br>I'm still a lonely man burning in love <br>I'm still a lonely man burning in love <br><br>What did he say to you <br>What did he promise you <br>That made you change from white to black <br>I don't understand it <br>It seems so underhanded <br>I want to hate you but I'm still in love <br>Why can't we start again <br>'Cause my heart won't mend <br>But you say no, then you go <br>And I break down <br><br>I'm still a lonely man burning in love <br>I'm still a lonely man burning in love <br><br>Why can't we start again <br>'Cause my heart won't mend <br>But you say no, then you go <br>And I break down <br><br>I'm still a lonely man burning in love <br>I'm still a lonely man burning in love <br><br>I'm still a lonely man burning in love <br>I'm still a lonely man burning in love <br><br>Burning in love <br>Burning, burning in love <br>Burning in love <br>Burning in love]]></content><category term="Honeymoon Suite" label="Honeymoon Suite"/><category term="Burning In Love (Live At The Phoenix Club, Toronto, Canada / 2016)" label="Burning In Love (Live At The Phoenix Club, Toronto, Canada / 2016)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Honeymoon_Suite/Hands_Up/</id><title>Honeymoon Suite - Hands Up - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:18:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:18:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Honeymoon_Suite/Hands_Up/" title="Honeymoon Suite - Hands Up - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Every single day I got somebody on me <br>Wants a piece of something that they just can't have <br>I never tell them nothing and I walk away smiling <br>Keep my mouth shut and I stick with the plan <br><br>Get your hands up <br>Don't look them in the eye <br>Get you hands up <br>They don't need a reason why <br>And everything you love will one day fade <br>'Cause everything you want yeah it's taken away <br><br>I don't want to be just another soul lost in the fire <br>Just another face in the crowd of lonely desire <br>Try walking down, this road of mine <br>You'll never find your way out <br><br>For a moment I was standing on the top of the world <br>I was living on the life they all paid to see <br>But it was cold up there I didn't like the view <br>So I burned it down and brought it back to me <br><br>Get your hands up <br>Don't look me in the eye <br>Get you hands up <br>Don't need a reason why <br>I ain't going down no memory lane <br>There just to many tears I won't cry again <br><br>I don't want to be just another soul lost in the fire <br>Just another face in the crowd of lonely desire <br>Try walking down, this road of mine <br>You'll never find your way out <br><br>Every single day I got somebody on me <br>Wants a piece of something that they just can't have <br><br>I don't want to be just another soul lost in the fire <br>Just another face in the crowd of my own desire <br>Try walking down, this road of mine <br>You'll never find your way out <br><br>I don't want to be just another soul lost in the fire <br>Just another face in the crowd of lonely desire <br>Try walking down, this road of mine <br>You'll never find your way out your way out <br><br>Try walking down <br>Get your hands up <br>Get your hands up]]></content><category term="Honeymoon Suite" label="Honeymoon Suite"/><category term="Hands Up" label="Hands Up"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LaPorsha_Renae/Somebody_Does/</id><title>La`Porsha Renae - Somebody Does - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:19:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:19:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LaPorsha_Renae/Somebody_Does/" title="La`Porsha Renae - Somebody Does - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Spending no time on the weekend <br>And we don't talk, barely even anymore <br>We don't even kiss as a reason <br>I'm pretty sure it's safe to assume you cheated on me <br>Somebody else been checking on me for the last 2 weeks <br><br>Neither one of us is blind, it's plain to see <br>You were never ever mine, you don't want me <br>You don't want this to be yours if you don't want this good love <br>Baby, baby, you can try trust that somebody does <br>Somebody, that somebody does <br>Somebody <br><br>Oh, you wanna talk now, do ya <br>I don't got a thing to say to ya, no <br>Matter fact, beep, beep, there's your Uber <br>I really, really don't think that I was asking too much <br>But everything that you wouldn't do would make me hate us <br><br>Neither one of us is blind, it's plain to see <br>You were never ever mine, you don't want me <br>You don't want this to be yours if you don't want this good love <br>Baby, baby, you can try trust that somebody does <br>Somebody, that somebody does <br>Somebody <br><br>I hope you get your thing together <br>Really need to get your thing together <br>For the next girl, whoever she is, you need to get your thing together <br>Man, you ain't never gon' get your thing together <br><br>Neither one of us is blind, it's plain to see <br>You were never ever mine, you don't want me <br>You don't want this to be yours if you don't want this good love <br>Baby, baby, you can try trust that somebody does <br>Neither one of us is blind, it's plain to see <br>You were never ever mine, you don't want me <br>You don't want this to be yours if you don't want this good love <br>Baby, baby, you can try trust that somebody does <br>Somebody, that somebody does <br>Somebody]]></content><category term="La`Porsha Renae" label="La`Porsha Renae"/><category term="Somebody Does" label="Somebody Does"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/Parallels/</id><title>Binoculers - Parallels - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:20:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:20:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/Parallels/" title="Binoculers - Parallels - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Step outside, walk down the road <br>Feel the noise locked up in the quiet ones <br>Remember the parallels that run among everyone <br>Not for too long I join in a choir, for a verse <br>Then I reverse, step back into a sheltered place <br>Breathing my own breath <br>Though it's stale like the stuck fog around my eyes <br><br>A grounded ship bleeds to death <br>Find some sleep in its bow <br>When the tide is low I feel like I should run to meet the water <br>Though I long for I will never call at a port <br>And my reports ain't true enough <br>All the words I hear pressed into an overall language <br>T hat I speak to you <br><br>All that I knew separates from you, separates from me, too <br>Empty and nude all angles turn into one blank view]]></content><category term="Binoculers" label="Binoculers"/><category term="Parallels" label="Parallels"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/Riverlights/</id><title>Binoculers - Riverlights - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:20:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:20:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/Riverlights/" title="Binoculers - Riverlights - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, I have decided to take the other way <br>The world turns on as before <br>I stop comparing my face to faces, my hand to hands <br>Still I swim with the tide, but on my own floe of ice <br>The river's speed won't be the measure of mine <br><br>The riverlights at the riversides <br>Like satellites' eyes so electric <br><br>I let you take over the time and places elapsed for me <br>Heartbeat's not lower but less in trouble with rest and wait <br><br>Where there is no illusion let me rest <br>Let the raft ride on while I stay here in the river bend]]></content><category term="Binoculers" label="Binoculers"/><category term="Riverlights" label="Riverlights"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/Quiet_Sea/</id><title>Binoculers - Quiet Sea - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:20:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:20:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/Quiet_Sea/" title="Binoculers - Quiet Sea - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Like ruins in wild landscapes <br>My dreams adhere to dried up land <br>Sort the days on the hours of sunshine <br>Sort the days and put them away <br><br>Cast feathers all at once no feathers <br>For now unable to fly <br>Grow tired, quiet sea <br>Grow tired of keeping the waves in the lee]]></content><category term="Binoculers" label="Binoculers"/><category term="Quiet Sea" label="Quiet Sea"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/But_Oh/</id><title>Binoculers - But Oh! - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:20:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:20:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/But_Oh/" title="Binoculers - But Oh! - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm on my way to you <br>And my heart is full of colours <br>You sway in a globe of glass <br>And your garden is full of flowers <br><br>But oh what can I say to you <br>I'm down like everyone else, too <br>Don't let our good times go <br>And fade upon a long and lonesome road]]></content><category term="Binoculers" label="Binoculers"/><category term="But Oh!" label="But Oh!"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/Come_With_Me/</id><title>Binoculers - Come With Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:20:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:20:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/Come_With_Me/" title="Binoculers - Come With Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't know about the ending of a storm <br>In times the waves are higher than the wall <br><br>Come with me <br><br>We print our fear white on a sheet <br>Aboard a ship to a blank shore <br><br>After all we lower all that we increased <br>Cargo's handed over, our estates are seized <br><br>The view is nor new, no, it's only skewed <br>As blind as trust in a stranger's home]]></content><category term="Binoculers" label="Binoculers"/><category term="Come With Me" label="Come With Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/Saturate_The_Darkness/</id><title>Binoculers - Saturate The Darkness - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:20:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:20:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/Saturate_The_Darkness/" title="Binoculers - Saturate The Darkness - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't benefit from the darkness <br>But it benefits from me <br>It is hungrier than the light is <br>Makes sure I'm always going to feed <br><br>Who can saturate the darkness <br><br>Something foreign to the body <br>Swamped the colour out the eyes <br>How I want to be a bright eyed ninja <br>Make a difference with a fight]]></content><category term="Binoculers" label="Binoculers"/><category term="Saturate The Darkness" label="Saturate The Darkness"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/Same_Sun/</id><title>Binoculers - Same Sun - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:20:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:20:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/Same_Sun/" title="Binoculers - Same Sun - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Always under the same sun <br>Stay run run stop stay run <br>Along a lonely horizon <br>The light's not gone as long as we run on <br><br>Sun sun sounds <br><br>We move at the same pace as the globe <br>But the opposed way <br>Keep up, we always run <br>All day we stay under the same sun <br><br>It takes us where they're all around <br>Sun sun sounds <br><br>Set on track <br>The same sun calling us <br><br>These are the tracks we're set to <br>You set me and I set you <br>Along a lonely horizon <br>And rays of light lead us away]]></content><category term="Binoculers" label="Binoculers"/><category term="Same Sun" label="Same Sun"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/The_Window/</id><title>Binoculers - The Window - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:20:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:20:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/The_Window/" title="Binoculers - The Window - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look into the wild, in the wide, in the night <br>The eyes hold on to one spot <br>Clouds pushed by the wind <br>Move in between the glass and the scene <br>Sometimes somebody's world turns away from a window <br>So take a photograph and hang it up on the wall <br><br>Look at the stars in the vast of the sky <br>Nothing will last, not the emptiest while <br><br>Spring, come, release the dimmed sun <br>The next beat of the heart excites <br>Though it's one of the last <br>Memories fade into a rough idea <br>Still bright enough for me to see you <br>As clear as you ever were <br><br>Look at the stars in the vast of the sky <br>Focus on few, on the ones speaking to you]]></content><category term="Binoculers" label="Binoculers"/><category term="The Window" label="The Window"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/The_Cities/</id><title>Binoculers - The Cities - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:20:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:20:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/The_Cities/" title="Binoculers - The Cities - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There you go along the cities' boundaries, at the outside <br>Get around the centre of life <br>Oh I thought that I could catch you <br>make you love my favourite sight <br>Get along with the centre of life <br><br>You never mind my invite, though it hits you like a meteorite <br>The invite for a ride even sparks another fight <br><br>I clear away the scenery I made up for you and I let go <br>It's all about another one's <br>Variety, monotony <br>History, futurity <br><br>Not any of your rejections got the wind from behind <br>Mask your eyes for everyone else <br>And while I run after your heart my love slowly falls apart <br>Reduced to signs in a chart, now both they stray in the dark <br><br>There you go around the cities]]></content><category term="Binoculers" label="Binoculers"/><category term="The Cities" label="The Cities"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/My／We/</id><title>Binoculers - My／We - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:20:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:20:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Binoculers/My%EF%BC%8FWe/" title="Binoculers - My／We - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Before our lives move away <br>Into liquid crystal displays <br>We slip through between two sample rates <br>Completely dissolve out of everything <br>Shift from ourselves and run onto an open field <br>Where we can breathe again]]></content><category term="Binoculers" label="Binoculers"/><category term="My／We" label="My／We"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Dejarte_De_Amar/</id><title>Dulce Maria - Dejarte De Amar - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:21:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:21:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Dejarte_De_Amar/" title="Dulce Maria - Dejarte De Amar - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cuantas veces tengo que disimular <br>Esconder la realidad mientras muero por tenerte <br>Como es que no puedo decirte que no <br>Aceptar que es un error <br>Y borrarte de mi mente <br>He llegado al punto de perder la razon <br>Pero hay algo que me ata a tu calor <br><br>Y este corazon que miente <br>Y que intenta parecer valiente <br>Mas no te puede dejar de pensar <br>Este corazon que miente <br>Me recuerda que no soy tan fuerte <br>No he logrado dejarte de amar <br>De amar <br><br>Cuantas veces te he mentido al disfrazar <br>La tristeza que hay detras desta falsa alegria <br>De reir por no llorar <br>He llegado al punto de perder la razon <br>Y si sigo resistiendo es por amor <br><br>Y este corazon que miente <br>Y que intenta parecer valiente <br>Mas no te puede dejar de pensar <br>Este corazon que miente <br>Me recuerda que no soy tan fuerte <br>No he logrado dejarte de amar <br><br>He pensado hasta buscarte en otros labios <br>Sentirte en otras manos, borrar nuestro pasado <br>Y ya no hacerle caso <br><br>Y este corazon que miente <br>Y que intenta parecer valiente <br>Mas no te puede dejar de pensar <br>Este corazon que miente <br>Me recuerda que no soy tan fuerte <br>Y no he logrado dejarte de amar <br><br>No he logrado dejarte de amar <br>De amar]]></content><category term="Dulce Maria" label="Dulce Maria"/><category term="Dejarte De Amar" label="Dejarte De Amar"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/No_Se_Llorar/</id><title>Dulce Maria - No Se Llorar - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:21:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:21:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/No_Se_Llorar/" title="Dulce Maria - No Se Llorar - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Simplemente yo no se llorar <br>Si no duele que no me conoces <br>Tu no sabes de lo que estoy hecha <br>No te equivoques <br><br>Pero te voy a confesar <br>Que si me da curiosidad <br>Saber lo que te hizo pensar <br>Que me podias lastimar <br>Quien te creias <br><br>Tendrias que haber sido todo para mi <br>Si me querias dejar alguna cicatriz <br>Se necesita mas que un hombre como tu <br>Para sufrir asi <br>Romperme el corazon a mi <br>Va a ser dificil para ti <br>Y yo jamas lo voy a permitir <br><br>Me parece injusto darle mas <br>Importancia a algo que no lo tiene <br>Lo que tu llamas amor hoy yo lo llamo diferente <br><br>Pero te voy a confesar <br>Que si me da curiosidad <br>Saber lo que te hizo pensar <br>Que me podias lastimar <br>Quien te creias <br><br>Tendrias que haber sido todo para mi <br>Si me querias dejar alguna cicatriz <br>Se necesita mas que un hombre como tu <br>Para sufrir asi <br>Romperme el corazon a mi <br>No fue dificil para ti <br>Y yo jamas lo voy a permitir <br><br>Tendrias que haber sido todo para mi <br>Si me querias dejar alguna cicatriz <br><br>Tendrias que haber sido todo para mi <br>Si me querias dejar alguna cicatriz <br>Se necesita mas que un hombre como tu <br>Para sufrir asi <br>Romperme el corazon a mi <br>No fue dificil para ti <br>Y yo jamas lo voy a permitir <br><br>Simplemente yo no se llorar <br>Si no duele, tu no me conoces]]></content><category term="Dulce Maria" label="Dulce Maria"/><category term="No Se Llorar" label="No Se Llorar"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Despidete/</id><title>Dulce Maria - Despidete - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:21:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:21:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Despidete/" title="Dulce Maria - Despidete - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sabes bien que siempre quiso estar contigo <br>Que vivi tan solo para ti <br>Y por esperarte me perdi <br>En este labirinto frio y gris <br><br>Me canse <br>De tanto de perseguir tu sombra <br>De sentir un amor a la mitad <br>Y mi corazon no pudo mas <br>No quiero dar un paso atras, es hora decir adios <br><br>Despidete <br>El tiempo se acabo <br>Has perdido este juego <br>Te burlaste de mi amor <br>Y olvideme <br>Como cuando estaba ahi <br>A tu lado suplicando <br>Que me amaras como yo te ame a ti <br><br>No podras ni tu ni nadie convencerme <br>De seguir <br>Que caso tiene ya <br>Me ensenaste amar la soledad <br>No quiero dar un paso atras, es hora decir adios <br><br>Despidete <br>El tiempo se acabo <br>Has perdido este juego <br>Te burlaste de mi amor <br>Y olvideme <br>Como cuando estaba ahi <br>A tu lado suplicando <br>Que me amaras como yo te ame a ti <br><br>Ya no hay nada por salvar <br>Esto es punto final <br>Despidete de mi <br><br>Despidete <br>El tiempo se acabo <br>Has perdido este juego <br>Te burlaste de mi amor <br>Y olvideme <br>Como cuando estaba ahi <br>A tu lado suplicando <br>Que me amaras como yo te ame a ti]]></content><category term="Dulce Maria" label="Dulce Maria"/><category term="Despidete" label="Despidete"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Volvamos_Feat_Joey_Montana/</id><title>Dulce Maria - Volvamos (Feat. Joey Montana) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:21:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:21:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Volvamos_Feat_Joey_Montana/" title="Dulce Maria - Volvamos (Feat. Joey Montana) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dulce <br>Joey Montana <br>Predi <br><br>Me duelen los dia si no estas <br>Todo lo que intento sale mal <br>Ando sin rumbo y direccion <br>Dime tu sin mi, si te va mejor <br><br>No puedo mentirle al corazon <br>Desde que no estas no sale el sol <br>Yo te extrano, me hace dano el estar sin ti <br>Vuelve por favor <br><br>Todavia yo, yo sigo amandote, sigo extranandote <br>Volvamos hoy, hoy, hoy <br>Volvamos hoy, hoy, hoy, volvamos hoy <br>Baby, para volver a ser feliz <br><br>Todavia yo, yo sigo amandote y mucho mas que ayer <br>Volvamos hoy, hoy, hoy <br>Volvamos hoy, hoy, hoy, volvamos hoy <br>Baby, para volver a ser feliz <br><br>Que quiere que diga mami <br>Lo que me esta pasando a mi <br>Es que tu adios fue como un tsunami <br>Que todo derrumbo <br><br>Besar otros labios se siente fatal <br>Tocar las canciones me hacen recordar <br>Que fui tan feliz y ahora nada es igual <br>No hay baby <br><br>Dime, si me amas a mi <br>Como te amo yo a ti <br>Olvidemoslo todo y volvamos <br><br>Dime, si me amas a mi <br>Como te amo yo a ti <br>Olvidemoslo todo y volvamos <br><br>Todavia yo, yo sigo amandote, sigo extranandote <br>Volvamos hoy, hoy, hoy <br>Volvamos hoy, hoy, hoy, volvamos hoy <br>Baby, para volver a ser feliz <br><br>Todavia yo, yo sigo amandote y mucho mas que ayer <br>Volvamos hoy, hoy, hoy <br>Volvamos hoy, hoy, hoy, volvamos hoy <br>Baby, para volver a ser feliz <br><br>Me duelen los dia si no estas <br>Todo lo que intento sale mal <br>Ando sin rumbo y direccion <br>Dime tu sin mi, si te va mejor <br><br>No puedo mentirle al corazon <br>Desde que no estas no sale el sol <br>Yo te extrano, me hace dano el estar sin ti <br>Vuelve por favor <br><br>Volvamos hoy, hoy, hoy <br>Volvamos hoy, hoy, hoy, volvamos hoy <br>Joey Montana, Dulce Maria <br>Predikador]]></content><category term="Dulce Maria" label="Dulce Maria"/><category term="Volvamos (Feat. Joey Montana)" label="Volvamos (Feat. Joey Montana)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Rompecorazones/</id><title>Dulce Maria - Rompecorazones - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:21:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:21:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Rompecorazones/" title="Dulce Maria - Rompecorazones - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tu me prometiste tantas letras de canciones <br>Y cuando estas no llegaron no prometiste flores <br>Tu me prometiste estar cuando llegara el frio <br>Y yo me fui acostumbrando a las desilisiones <br>Yo no estaba preparada para la batalla <br>Pero es que al final el amor no se ensaya <br>Y duele tanto que te vayas <br><br>Falsificador de besos, un ilusionista <br>Parece verdad aunque tu amor no exista <br>En enganarme un artista <br>Es que no hay nadie que resista <br><br>Y vas rompiendo corazones <br>Especialista en ilusiones <br>Recuerdame cerrar la puerta fuerte cuando me abandones <br>Y aunque hoy me pierda en tu mirada <br>Y siga estando equivocada <br>Te juro que sere mas fuerte que lo que me enamoraba <br>Querido rompecorazones <br>A ti ya no te creo nada <br><br>Una vez es suficiente para esta agonia <br>Y si esto me vuelve a pasar ya sera culpa mia <br>Y aunque tu hayas reemplazado amor por sufrimiento <br>Tal vez este muy mal pero de nada me arrepiento <br><br>Falsificador de besos, un ilusionista <br>Parece verdad aunque tu amor no exista <br>En enganarme un artista <br>Es que no hay nadie que resista <br><br>Y vas rompiendo corazones <br>Especialista en ilusiones <br>Recuerdame cerrar la puerta fuerte cuando me abandones <br>Y aunque hoy me pierda en tu mirada <br>Y siga estando equivocada <br>Te juro que sere mas fuerte que lo que me enamoraba <br>Querido rompecorazones <br>A ti ya no te creo nada <br><br>Te pido rompecorazones <br>No seas egoista <br>Vete por favor <br>Que no soy masoquista <br>Y te lo ruego no me insistas <br>Hoy que estoy debil no me insistas <br><br>Y vas rompiendo corazones <br>Especialista en ilusiones <br>Recuerdame cerrar la puerta fuerte cuando me abandones <br>Y aunque hoy me pierda en tu mirada <br>Y siga estando equivocada <br>Te juro que sere mas fuerte que lo que me enamoraba <br>Querido rompecorazones <br>A ti ya no te creo nada]]></content><category term="Dulce Maria" label="Dulce Maria"/><category term="Rompecorazones" label="Rompecorazones"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Al_Otro_Lado_De_La_Lluvia/</id><title>Dulce Maria - Al Otro Lado De La Lluvia - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:21:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:21:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Al_Otro_Lado_De_La_Lluvia/" title="Dulce Maria - Al Otro Lado De La Lluvia - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Te miraba y no te vi <br>Porque me cegaba el miedo <br>Tanto que dejaste en mi <br>Levantandome del suelo <br>Me perdi y te perdi <br><br>Te ame mas de lo que cres <br>No lo dudes ni un momento <br>Me arrepiento cada vez de no haber lo hecho a tiempo <br>Me perdi y te perdi <br><br>Al otro lado de la lluvia donde sale el sol <br>Llevo siempre tu recuerdo y la mitad de un adios <br>Tatuado en mi corazon oh <br><br>Al otro lado de la lluvia lejos del dolor <br>Me pregunto si en secreto sientes lo mismo que yo <br>Siento en mi algun rincon <br>Aun existimos los dos <br><br>Intentaste remendar con tu amor mi suenos rotos <br>Y me duele la verdade que no pude darte todo <br>Me perdi Y te perdi <br><br>Te ame mas de lo que cres <br>No lo dudes ni un momento <br>Me arrepiento cada vez de no haber lo hecho a tiempo <br>Me perdi y te perdi <br><br>Al otro lado de la lluvia donde sale el sol <br>Llevo siempre tu recuerdo y la mitad de un adios <br>Tatuado en mi corazon oh <br><br>Al otro lado de la lluvia lejos del dolor <br>Me pregunto si en secreto sientes lo mismo que yo <br>Siento en mi algun rincon <br>Aun existimos los dos <br><br>Al otro lado de la lluvia]]></content><category term="Dulce Maria" label="Dulce Maria"/><category term="Al Otro Lado De La Lluvia" label="Al Otro Lado De La Lluvia"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Cicatrices/</id><title>Dulce Maria - Cicatrices - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:21:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:21:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Cicatrices/" title="Dulce Maria - Cicatrices - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Veo luces en mi piel <br>Sirenas acercandose <br>Y desperte <br>Mu duele respirar <br>Me cuesta tanto caminar <br>Una vez mas <br><br>Lo que no te mata te hace fuerte <br>Si me levante no fue por suerte <br>Solo los cobardes nunca pierden <br>Entiendelo <br><br>Cicatrices que dicen sobreviviste <br>A una traicion <br>Borrame el dolor <br>Cicatrices que dicen que aunque yo te quise <br>Sin ti estoy mejor <br>Solo eres para mi otra cicatriz <br><br>Hoy me toco perder <br>Jugue con fuego y me queme <br>Pero estoy bien <br>Pronto lo vas a ver <br>Que entre cenizas del ayer <br>Renacere <br><br>Lo que no te mata te hace fuerte <br>Si me levante no fue por suerte <br>Solo los cobardes nunca pierden <br>Entiendelo <br><br>Cicatrices que dicen sobreviviste <br>A una traicion <br>Borrame el dolor <br>Cicatrices que dicen que aunque yo te quise <br>Sin ti estoy mejor <br>Solo eres para mi otra cicatriz <br><br>A pesar de todo no me arrepentire <br>Y te llevo siempre en mi piel <br><br>Cicatrices que dicen sobreviviste <br>A una traicion <br>Borrame el dolor <br>Cicatrices que dicen que aunque yo te quise <br>Sin ti estoy mejor <br>Solo eres para mi otra cicatriz <br>Solo eres para mi otra cicatriz]]></content><category term="Dulce Maria" label="Dulce Maria"/><category term="Cicatrices" label="Cicatrices"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Tal_Vez_En_Roma/</id><title>Dulce Maria - Tal Vez En Roma - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:21:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:21:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Tal_Vez_En_Roma/" title="Dulce Maria - Tal Vez En Roma - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Amor, el hilo del destino se enredo <br>Nuestro planeta se salio de alieneacion <br>Quiero luchar con la distancia <br>Aunque hoy nuestros caminos <br>Van en otra direccion <br><br>Mi vuelo casi esta despegando <br>Y no podemos cambiarlo <br>Promete que me alcanzaras <br>Tarde o temprano <br><br>Tal vez en Roma, Dublin o Barcelona <br>En un cafe en Madrid <br>Que va a ser de ti <br>Nadando en Grecia <br>Besandote en Venecia <br>Paseando por Paris <br>Abrazame y no te olvides de mi <br>No te olvides de mi <br><br>Me voy y guardo en la maleta <br>Nuestro adios <br>En mi memoria esta grabada tu cancion <br>Y no, no vayas a portarte mal <br>Que yo, llevo tu foto impresa <br>En este corazon <br><br>Mi vuelo casi esta despegando <br>Y no podemos cambiarlo <br>Promete que me alcanzaras <br>Tarde o temprano <br><br>Tal vez en Roma, Dublin o Barcelona <br>En un cafe en Madrid <br>Que va a ser de ti <br>Nadando en Grecia <br>Besandote en Venecia <br>Paseando por Paris <br>Abrazame y no te olvides de mi <br>No te olvides de mi <br>No te olvides de mi <br><br>Tal vez en Roma, Dublin o Barcelona <br>En un cafe en Madrid <br>Que va a ser de ti <br>Nadando en Grecia <br>Besandote en Venecia <br>Paseando por Paris <br>Abrazame y <br><br>Tal vez en Roma, Dublin o Barcelona <br>En un cafe en Madrid <br>Que va a ser de ti <br>Nadando en Grecia <br>Besandote en Venecia <br>Paseando por Paris <br>Abrazame y no te olvides de mi <br>No te olvides de mi <br>No te olvides de mi]]></content><category term="Dulce Maria" label="Dulce Maria"/><category term="Tal Vez En Roma" label="Tal Vez En Roma"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Invencible/</id><title>Dulce Maria - Invencible - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:21:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:21:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Invencible/" title="Dulce Maria - Invencible - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Soy como el viento no me detengo <br>Dejo mi esencia donde quiera <br>Que voy, vivo el hoy <br>No tengo miedo, levanto el vuelo <br>Y aunque de urgencia deba aterrizar <br>Vuelvo a despegar <br><br>Una mas y otra mas <br>Cierrame las puertas <br>Se las vuelvo a derrumbar <br>Y ademas me hacen <br>Cada vez mas fuerte <br><br>Encierrame yo se como escaparme <br>Y borrame tengo la tinta <br>Para reinventarme <br>Simple, yo soy invencible <br>Mi alma no se rinde <br>Entierrame que soy semilla <br>Y para mi no hay impossibles <br>Soy invencible, yo soy invencible <br><br>Tengo raspones y cicatrices <br>Mi piel es armadura contra el mal <br>Aunque no soy de metal <br><br>Una mas y otra mas <br>Cierrame las puertas <br>Se las vuelvo a derrumbar <br>Y ademas me hacen <br>Cada vez mas fuerte <br><br>Encierrame yo se como escaparme <br>Y borrame tengo la tinta <br>Para reinventarme <br>Simple, yo soy invencible <br>Mi alma no se rinde <br>Entierrame que soy semilla <br>Y para mi no hay impossibles <br>Soy invencible, yo soy invencible <br><br>No tiengo miedo, mantego el vuelo <br>Si hay turbulencia <br>Se como aguantar <br>Salto del suelo <br>Hasta el mismo cielo <br>Mi fe me eleva siempre mas alla <br><br>Encierrame yo se como escaparme <br>Y borrame tengo la tinta <br>Para reinventarme <br>Simple, yo soy invencible <br>Mi alma no se rinde <br>Entierrame que soy semilla <br>Y para mi no hay impossibles <br>Soy invencible, yo soy invencible <br><br>Encierrame yo se como escaparme <br>Y borrame tengo la tinta <br>Para reinventarme <br>Simple, yo soy invencible <br>Mi alma no se rinde <br>Entierrame que soy semilla <br>Y para mi no hay impossibles <br>Soy invencible, yo soy invencible]]></content><category term="Dulce Maria" label="Dulce Maria"/><category term="Invencible" label="Invencible"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Presentimiento/</id><title>Dulce Maria - Presentimiento - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:21:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:21:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Presentimiento/" title="Dulce Maria - Presentimiento - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Te he ocultado un gran secreto <br>No se por donde deberia empezar <br>No se como explicar <br>Que estoy enamorada <br>De ti, de ti <br><br>Me haces olvidar y me haces recordar <br>Al mismo tiempo <br>Haces lo que quieres de mi <br><br>Y presiento que llegas para darme la calma <br>Y llegas en el justo momento <br>Y ese efecto me lo haces tu <br>Y hace tiempo que al verte <br>Siento que me desarmas <br>Que haces que cambiemos de rumbo <br>Hacia un encuentro donde estas tu <br><br>Tengo un gran presentimiento <br>Yo se que esto iba a pasar <br>Que algo iba a cambiar <br>Que el mundo se ha pintado <br>De ti y de mi <br><br>Y presiento que llegas para darme la calma <br>Y llegas en el justo momento <br>Y ese efecto me lo haces tu <br>Y hace tiempo que al verte <br>Siento que me desarmas <br>Que haces que cambiemos de rumbo <br>Hacia un encuentro donde estas tu <br><br>Y tengo un presentimiento que llegas para darme la calma <br>Que llegas en el justo momento <br>Y ese efecto me lo haces tu <br>Y hace tiempo que al verte <br>Siento que me desarmas <br>Que haces que cambiemos de rumbo <br>Hacia un encuentro donde estas tu <br><br>Y presiento que llegas para darme la calma <br>Y llegas en el justo momento <br>Y ese efecto me lo haces tu <br>Y hace tiempo que al verte <br>Siento que me desarmas <br>Que haces que cambiemos de rumbo <br>Hacia un encuentro donde estas tu]]></content><category term="Dulce Maria" label="Dulce Maria"/><category term="Presentimiento" label="Presentimiento"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Un_Minuto_Sin_Dolor/</id><title>Dulce Maria - Un Minuto Sin Dolor - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:21:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:21:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Un_Minuto_Sin_Dolor/" title="Dulce Maria - Un Minuto Sin Dolor - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Camine sobre el fuego a tu lado <br>Me entregue como un ciego de la mano <br>Fuiste tu como hielo en mis pies ya cansados <br>Y yo no supe verlo <br><br>Yo se muy bien que en tus planes no existo <br>No hay nada que esconder <br><br>Quedate, solo un minuto entre los dos sera eterno <br>Mirame, no digas nada, abrazame en silencio <br>Si quieres huir despues, yo no te seguire <br>Quedate, aunque no hay nada entre tu y yo <br>Dame un minuto sin dolor <br>Dame un minuto sin dolor <br><br>Descubriste en mis ojos mil tormentas del pasado <br>Y encontre que los tuyos me miraban como extrano <br>Fueron noches enteras esperando <br>Tu paciencia expiro <br><br>Yo se muy bien que en tus planes no existo <br>No hay nada que esconder <br><br>Quedate, solo un minuto entre los dos sera eterno <br>Mirame, no digas nada, abrazame en silencio <br>Si quieres huir despues, yo no te seguire <br>Quedate, aunque no hay nada entre tu y yo <br>Dame un minuto sin dolor <br>Dame un minuto sin dolor <br><br>Yo se muy bien que en tus planes no existo <br>No hay nada que esconder <br><br>Quedate, solo un minuto entre los dos sera eterno <br>Mirame, no digas nada, abrazame en silencio <br><br>Quedate, solo un minuto entre los dos sera eterno <br>Mirame, no digas nada, abrazame en silencio <br>Si quieres huir despues, yo no te seguire <br>Quedate, aunque no hay nada entre tu y yo <br>Dame un minuto sin dolor <br>Dame un minuto sin dolor <br>Dame un minuto sin dolor]]></content><category term="Dulce Maria" label="Dulce Maria"/><category term="Un Minuto Sin Dolor" label="Un Minuto Sin Dolor"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Sin_Ti_Yo_Estoy_Muy_Bien/</id><title>Dulce Maria - Sin Ti Yo Estoy Muy Bien - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:21:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:21:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Sin_Ti_Yo_Estoy_Muy_Bien/" title="Dulce Maria - Sin Ti Yo Estoy Muy Bien - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tu no sabes cuanto me costo entender <br>Que lo nuestro nunca fue <br>Pare de respirar <br>Me supo amargo <br>Pero te olvide al fin lo supere <br><br>Despues de todo no hay una razon <br>Para intentarlo asi estamos mejor <br><br>Y si vuelves arrepentido a mis pies <br>Mas te vale creer <br>Sin ti yo estoy muy bien <br>En algun lugar el dolor te dejo <br>Y no vuelvo a caer <br>Sin ti yo estoy muy bien <br>Sin ti yo estoy muy bien <br><br>Tu perdiste el rumbo <br>Me dejaste ir <br>Pensaste solo en ti <br><br>Despues de todo no hay una razon <br>Para intentarlo asi estamos mejor <br><br>Y si vuelves arrepentido a mis pies <br>Mas te vale creer <br>Sin ti yo estoy muy bien <br>En algun lugar el dolor te dejo <br>Y no vuelvo a caer <br>Sin ti yo estoy muy bien <br>Sin ti yo estoy muy bien <br><br>Mas de una vez <br>El precio fue muy alto <br>Pero por ti lo pague <br><br>Y si vuelves arrepentido a mis pies <br>Mas te vale creer <br>Sin ti yo estoy muy bien <br>En algun lugar el dolor te dejo <br>Y no vuelvo a caer <br>Sin ti yo estoy muy bien <br><br>Y si vuelves arrepentido a mis pies <br>Mas te vale creer <br>Sin ti yo estoy muy bien <br>En algun lugar el dolor te dejo <br>Y no vuelvo a caer <br>Sin ti yo estoy muy bien <br>Sin ti yo estoy muy bien]]></content><category term="Dulce Maria" label="Dulce Maria"/><category term="Sin Ti Yo Estoy Muy Bien" label="Sin Ti Yo Estoy Muy Bien"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Hoy_Te_Entierro/</id><title>Dulce Maria - Hoy Te Entierro - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:21:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:21:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dulce_Maria/Hoy_Te_Entierro/" title="Dulce Maria - Hoy Te Entierro - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hoy me voy, me voy de aqui <br>Me voy feliz directo al cementerio <br>No me vesti muy sexy asi <br>No como te gustaba a ti <br>De negro y com ese sombrero <br><br>Para yo salir de ti <br>Tuviste que morir, morirte para mi <br>Tu recuerdo embalsame <br>Y ya descansa aqui <br>El beso de un pobre infeliz <br>Pero hoy te entierro <br><br>Ando de fiesta hoy es tu funeral <br>Como te voy a llorar <br>Pero de felicidad <br>Cuantos rosarios te tuve que rezar <br>Para poderte olvidar <br>Para poderte olvidar <br>Pero hoy te entierro <br><br>Hoy deje tu insensatez <br>Tu estupidez <br>Dos metros bajo el suelo <br>Enviude, me fui y cobre <br>La herencia que he esperado tanto <br>Por haberte amado en vano <br><br>Para yo salir de ti <br>Tuviste que morir, morirte para mi <br>Tu recuerdo embalsame <br>Y ya descansa aqui <br>El beso de un pobre infeliz <br>Pero hoy te entierro <br><br>Ando de fiesta hoy es tu funeral <br>Como te voy a llorar <br>Pero de felicidad <br>Cuantos rosarios te tuve que rezar <br>Para poderte olvidar <br>Para poderte olvidar <br>Pero hoy te entierro <br><br>Ando de fiesta hoy es tu funeral <br>Como te voy a llorar <br>Pero de felicidad <br>Cuantos rosarios te tuve que rezar <br>Para poderte olvidar <br>Para poderte olvidar <br>Pero hoy te entierro <br><br>Para yo salir de ti <br>Tuviste que morir, morirte para mi <br>Tu recuerdo embalsame <br>Y ya descansa aqui <br>El beso de un pobre infeliz <br>Pero hoy te entierro <br><br>Ando de fiesta hoy es tu funeral <br>Como te voy a llorar <br>Pero de felicidad <br>Cuantos rosarios te tuve que rezar <br>Para poderte olvidar <br>Para poderte olvidar <br>Pero hoy te entierro <br><br>Pero hoy te entierro <br>Pero hoy te entierro]]></content><category term="Dulce Maria" label="Dulce Maria"/><category term="Hoy Te Entierro" label="Hoy Te Entierro"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Departures/</id><title>Blessthefall - Departures - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:22:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:22:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Departures/" title="Blessthefall - Departures - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Father, don't cry <br>It's not so bad here <br>I'm doing this all on my own <br>Everyone else keeps passing me by <br>I float through this place all alone <br><br>I know it doesn't feel like you'll recover <br>Suffering that never goes away <br>But I'm here with you <br>So carry me through <br>Use me as a light to guide your way <br><br>Revisiting this old familiar place <br>Just to see if you could find a trace <br>It's time to say goodbye <br>At least you have to try <br>For me <br><br>Waiting <br>Wasting <br>Away without you here <br>I'll come around just give me a reason <br>Drifting <br>Sinking <br>Searching for a way <br>To reach out and pull you close <br><br>I know it doesn't feel like you'll recover <br>Suffering that never goes away <br>But I'm here with you <br>So carry me through <br>Use me as a light to guide your way <br><br>I know it doesn't feel like you'll recover <br>Suffering that never goes away <br>But I'm here with you <br>So carry me through <br>Use me as a light to guide your way <br><br>Don't you cry now <br>Go to sleep <br>Dry your eyes <br>Don't wait for me <br><br>Don't you cry now <br>Go to sleep <br>Dry your eyes <br>Don't wait for me <br><br>Don't you cry now <br>Go to sleep <br>Dry your eyes <br>Don't wait for me <br><br>Don't you cry now <br>Go to sleep <br>Dry your eyes <br>Don't wait <br>Don't wait for me <br><br>Don't you cry now <br>Go to sleep <br>Dry your eyes <br>Don't wait for me <br><br>Don't you cry now <br>Go to sleep <br>Dry your eyes <br>Don't wait for me <br><br>I know it doesn't feel like you'll recover <br>Suffering that never goes away <br>But I'm here with you <br>So carry me through <br>Use me as a light to guide your way <br><br>I know it doesn't feel like you'll recover <br>Suffering that never goes away <br>But I'm here with you <br>So carry me through <br>Use me as a light to guide your way]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Departures" label="Departures"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/To_Those_Left_Behind/</id><title>Blessthefall - To Those Left Behind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:22:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:22:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/To_Those_Left_Behind/" title="Blessthefall - To Those Left Behind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Where is the life within us <br>Buried inside <br>Where is the light that blinds us <br>Buried alive not ready to die <br>Go <br><br>You found me at my worst <br>When I was far too weak to grow <br>Speaking all your shallow words <br>And always casting the first stone <br>In spite of all my fears <br>And how I may have lost my way <br>Only now I know the truth <br>You tried to suffocate me <br>Suffocate me <br>Look at what we've become <br>Suffocate me <br>Buried alive not ready to die <br><br>Awake and coming clean <br><br>If you can't sleep <br>It's your conscience <br>That's eating away <br>At the mess you made <br>So let's end this <br>Sew this last stitch <br>Lift this weight off my chest <br>I'll put you to rest <br>The past should stay dead <br><br>How did we find ourselves here <br>Haunted by our own design <br>With everything that's come to pass <br>Makes it harder to confine <br>Reach up with open hands <br>Nobody left to pull me through <br>And if I lose my grief <br>Still better off without you <br><br>If you can't sleep <br>It's your conscience <br>That's eating away <br>At the mess you made <br>So let's end this <br>Sew this last stitch <br>Lift this weight off my chest <br>I'll put you to rest <br><br>If you can't sleep <br>It's your conscience <br>That's eating away <br>At the mess you made <br>The past should stay dead <br><br>You're like a cancer living inside of me <br>I feel the pressure it's getting harder to breathe <br>You're like a cancer living inside of me <br>I feel the pressure it's getting harder to breathe <br><br>You're like a cancer living inside of me <br>If you can't sleep <br>It's your conscience <br>You're like a cancer living inside of me <br>So let's end this <br>Sew this last stitch <br>You're like a cancer living inside of me <br>The past should stay dead]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="To Those Left Behind" label="To Those Left Behind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Oathbreaker/</id><title>Blessthefall - Oathbreaker - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:22:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:22:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Oathbreaker/" title="Blessthefall - Oathbreaker - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Take back all the years that we've wasted <br>Your face hasn't changed <br>But you've become what we hated <br>What happened to us versus them <br>Our worlds are divided <br>I'll never give in <br><br>It's too it late to turn it around <br>How can you live with yourself <br>Your loyalty can't be found <br>How can you live with yourself <br><br>In time <br>Their thoughts will fade <br>Their words won't mean <br>What we want them to say <br>Inside we watched them be <br>The enemy <br>That I thought that they'd never be <br><br>I took the fall for all your decisions <br>You call this love <br>I call it blind ambition <br>You've turned all your diamonds to dust <br>I've tried so hard <br>But it wasn't enough <br><br>It's too it late to turn it around <br>How can you live with yourself <br>Your loyalty can't be found <br>How can you live with yourself <br><br>In time <br>Their thoughts will fade <br>Their words won't mean <br>What we want them to say <br>Inside we watched them be <br>The enemy <br>That I thought that they'd never be <br>Fighting in cycles <br>Living in shadows <br>Inside we watched them be <br>The enemy <br>That I thought that they'd never be <br><br>I would have given my life for you <br>But the path that you've chosen <br>Has fucked everything <br>You fucked everything <br><br>Take back all the years that we've wasted <br>Your face hasn't changed <br>But you've become what we hated <br>Take back all the time that we've lost <br>I've tried so hard <br>But it was never enough <br><br>In time <br>Their thoughts will fade <br>Their words won't mean <br>What we want them to say <br>Inside we watched them be <br>The enemy <br>That I thought that they'd never be <br>Fighting in cycles <br>Living in shadows <br>Inside we watched them be <br>The enemy <br>That I thought that they'd never be]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Oathbreaker" label="Oathbreaker"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Condition____Comatose/</id><title>Blessthefall - Condition // Comatose - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:22:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:22:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Condition____Comatose/" title="Blessthefall - Condition // Comatose - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Angels keep coming after me <br>Chalk outlines they captivate <br>Comatose concrete <br>Stole my hopes and dreams <br>It's getting hard to sink <br>When you're six feet deep <br><br>Am I dying <br>Floating above my body <br>Armageddon running through my veins <br>I never wanted it to end this way <br>Dying <br>Floating above my body <br>I wish that I could numb this pain <br>We live and then we medicate <br><br>Hold me so close <br>Don't let me drift away <br>My whole world slips <br>Right out from under me <br><br>Comatose concrete <br>Stole my hopes and dreams <br>It's getting hard to sink <br>When you're six feet deep <br><br>Am I dying <br>Floating above my body <br>Armageddon running through my veins <br>I never wanted it to end this way <br>Dying <br>Floating above my body <br>I wish that I could numb this pain <br>We live and then we medicate <br><br>Clarity <br>Is missing from everything <br>The fear that's inside of me <br>Pulling like tidal waves <br>Clarity <br>Is missing from everything <br>The fear that's inside of me <br>Pulling like tidal waves <br><br>Angels keep coming after me <br>Chalk outlines they captivate <br><br>Am I dying <br>Floating above my body <br>Armageddon running through my veins <br>I never wanted it to end this way <br>Dying <br>Floating above my body <br>I wish that I could numb this pain <br>We live and then we medicate]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Condition // Comatose" label="Condition // Comatose"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Keep_What_We_Love__Burn_The_Rest/</id><title>Blessthefall - Keep What We Love &amp; Burn The Rest - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:22:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:22:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Keep_What_We_Love__Burn_The_Rest/" title="Blessthefall - Keep What We Love &amp; Burn The Rest - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I hear your voice inside my head <br>Like a ghost returning <br>Got you on my mind <br>Well my eyes are not the same <br>When you're nowhere near me <br>Always on my mind <br><br>I try to tell myself <br>That I'll see you again <br>Try to understand <br>Why I still pretend <br>So I lie awake <br>Waiting for the day <br>You'll need me <br><br>The times we had <br>The moment's passed <br><br>I try to tell myself <br>That I'll see you again <br>Try to understand <br>Why I still pretend <br><br>I try to tell myself <br>That I'll see you again <br>Try to understand <br>Why I still pretend <br>So I lie awake <br>Waiting for the day <br>You'll need me <br><br>I try to tell myself <br>That I'll see you again <br>Try to understand <br>Why I still pretend <br>So I lie awake <br>Waiting for the day <br>You'll need me]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Keep What We Love &amp; Burn The Rest" label="Keep What We Love &amp; Burn The Rest"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Looking_Down_From_The_Edge/</id><title>Blessthefall - Looking Down From The Edge - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:22:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:22:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Looking_Down_From_The_Edge/" title="Blessthefall - Looking Down From The Edge - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wake up <br>Do I need these things that I'm asking for <br>So I'll give up <br>And turn in the dreams that I've been sold <br>You'll never know <br>The lines that were crossed <br>Just to make it home <br>So I'll cover up <br>The fear that I'm not there for anybody <br><br>Wish I was getting used to this <br>Every chance I get I let it go <br>Every moment spent is not enough <br>Wish I was getting used to all of this <br><br>I'm looking down from the edge <br>And would I do it again <br>Would I trade the world that I know now <br>For a day that I don't miss you <br>I'm looking down from the edge <br>And would I do it again <br>But it's getting hard to understand <br>Why I'm wide awake but barely breathing <br><br>I've spent all my energy <br>Justifying my failures at close range <br>Every chance I get I let it go <br>Every moment spent is not enough <br>Pull the trigger, I've been such a waste <br>Neglecting life and love it's one in the same thing <br>Every chance I get I let it go <br>Every moment spent is not enough <br><br>Wish I was getting used to all of this <br><br>I'm looking down from the edge <br>And would I do it again <br>Would I trade the world that I know now <br>For a day that I don't miss you <br>I'm looking down from the edge <br>And would I do it again <br>But it's getting hard to understand <br>Why I'm wide awake but barely breathing <br><br>I know I've got too much to lose <br>For me to turn my back on you <br>The writings on the wall <br>We were meant to fall <br>Don't regret the life we chose <br><br>Looking down from the edge <br>Would I do it again <br>I'm looking down from the edge <br><br>I'm looking down from the edge <br>And would I do it again <br>Would I trade the world that I know now <br>For a day that I don't miss you <br>I'm looking down from the edge <br>And would I do it again <br>But it's getting hard to understand <br>Why I'm wide awake but barely breathing]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Looking Down From The Edge" label="Looking Down From The Edge"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Against_The_Waves/</id><title>Blessthefall - Against The Waves - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:22:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:22:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Against_The_Waves/" title="Blessthefall - Against The Waves - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How will I find the strength <br>To make it out when you're pulling me under <br>How can I make them see <br>You're so worthless to me <br>Recognize what lies before me <br>I will stare death in the face <br>Recognize what lies before me <br>I'll stand against the waves <br><br>So talk all you want <br>You can't see us <br>But we're at the top now <br>Never lost our way <br>Can't break our stride <br>You don't have what it takes <br><br>We hold our own <br>On our own <br>Still undefeated <br><br>I know it's hard to stay true <br>With vultures pulling at you <br>But if it's all the same <br>They'll find the worst in you <br>If we can take what we know <br>And give them somewhere to go <br>So if it's all the same <br>They'll find the worst in you <br><br>I won't be used <br>I refuse to be <br>I refuse to be misled <br>All the bullshit I've been fed <br>You're worthless to me <br><br>Don't count us out <br>The more you push only fuels the fire <br>We've paid the price <br>We're taking back <br>What you took away <br><br>We hold our own <br>On our own <br>Still undefeated <br><br>I know it's hard to stay true <br>With vultures pulling at you <br>But if it's all the same <br>They'll find the worst in you <br>If we can take what we know <br>And give them somewhere to go <br>So if it's all the same <br>They'll find the worst in you <br><br>Nothing can last forever <br>I won't let you tell me how to live my life <br>You can't control me <br>I won't let you tell me how to live my life <br>You'll never bring me down <br><br>I know it's hard to stay true <br>With vultures pulling at you <br>But if it's all the same <br>They'll find the worst in you <br>I know it's hard to stay true <br>With vultures pulling at you <br>But if it's all the same <br>They'll find the worst in you <br>If we can take what we know <br>And give them somewhere to go <br>So if it's all the same <br>They'll find the worst in you <br><br>So if it's all the same <br>They'll find the worst in you]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Against The Waves" label="Against The Waves"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Up_In_Flames/</id><title>Blessthefall - Up In Flames - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:22:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:22:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Up_In_Flames/" title="Blessthefall - Up In Flames - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You always took me for granted <br>And never gave me a reason why <br>You left me stranded feeling worthless <br>Now all I see is death in your eyes <br>All I see is death in your eyes <br><br>If you're counting all my sins <br>Hope they all add up so pull the pin <br>Watch it all go up in flames <br>Watch it all go up in flames <br><br>Don't drag me through your nightmare <br>Don't tear apart what I am <br>You've got your demons, they parallel mine <br>You're not the victim, you're my parasite you're my parasite <br><br>You're not the only one <br>How could you be so selfish <br>You never lie, you'll never see the truth <br>Your body's rising from ashes <br><br>If you want to point the blame <br>Hope you marked your words, you're not a saint <br>Watch it all go up in flames <br>Watch you all go up in flames <br><br>Don't drag me through your nightmare <br>Don't tear apart what I am <br>You've got your demons, they parallel mine <br>You're not the victim, you're my parasite <br>Don't drag me through your nightmare <br>Don't tear apart what I am <br>You've got your demons, they parallel mine parallel mine <br>You're not the victim, you're my parasite you're my parasite <br><br>If it makes sense <br>When you can see through clearer eyes see through clearer eyes <br>If we can't learn <br>If we can't learn to put the past behind <br>So <br>If it makes sense <br>When you can read between the lines read between the lines <br>Why can't you learn <br>We'll never find what we lost inside <br><br>Don't drag me through your nightmare <br>Don't tear apart what I am <br>You've got your demons, they parallel mine <br>You're not the victim, you're my parasite <br><br>Parasite <br>You've got your demons, they parallel mine parallel mine <br>You're not the victim, you're my parasite you're my parasite <br>You're my parasite <br>We'll never find what we lost inside]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Up In Flames" label="Up In Flames"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Dead_Air/</id><title>Blessthefall - Dead Air - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:22:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:22:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Dead_Air/" title="Blessthefall - Dead Air - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So long, this is harder than you know <br>But we'll remember everything <br>It's tough to let it go <br><br>Think of the nights we spent when we were not alone <br>They remember everything <br>It's tough to let it go <br><br>Here we are again, falling for it <br>Here we are again and we're falling for it <br><br>You won't find me there <br>Cause I'm already gone <br>Looking for what's left to hang on <br>Where did we go <br><br>Now all that we have left are cemetery sights <br>Monuments of memories to those we left behind <br><br>Here we are again and we're falling for it <br><br>You won't find me there <br>Cause I'm already gone <br>Looking for what's left to hang on <br>Where did we go wrong <br>You won't find me there <br>Cause I'm already gone <br>Looking for what's left to hang on <br>Where did we go wrong <br><br>So long, this is harder than we know <br>But we'll remember everything <br>It's tough to let it go <br>Here we are again, again <br><br>You won't find me there <br>Cause I'm already gone <br>Looking for what's left to hang on <br>Where did we go wrong <br>You won't find me there <br>Cause I'm already gone <br>Looking for what's left to hang on <br>Where did we go wrong]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Dead Air" label="Dead Air"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Walk_On_Water/</id><title>Blessthefall - Walk On Water - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:22:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:22:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Walk_On_Water/" title="Blessthefall - Walk On Water - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We're reading psalms to the dead <br>Lighting candles to make amends <br>For a voice never to speak again <br>Six feet under for what never should've been <br><br>Stop living like you walk on water <br>Looking down on all those left to drown <br>Stop living like you walk on water <br>Looking down on all those left to drown <br><br>And you know I couldn't find the words before <br>Only if I had another day left here <br>I'd tell you, I'd tell you <br>If I had another day to try to take away your pain <br>Now you're so far out of reach <br>It's a lesson you can't teach <br><br>You love and you lose <br>I wish that you know <br>That it's just a lesson you can't teach <br>You love and you lose <br>I wish that you know <br>That it's just a lesson you can't teach <br><br>I've seen the scars you've tried to hide <br>Searching for answers when you look to the sky <br>Say I'm liar, say I'm a fake <br>I'm far from a saint <br>So I'll live with my mistakes <br><br>If I'm a liar, if I'm a fake <br>I'll take all these sins <br>And you can burn me at the stake <br>I'll take all these sins <br>And you can burn me at the stake <br><br>And you know I couldn't find the words before <br>Only if I had another day left here <br>I'd tell you, I'd tell you <br>If I had another day to try to take away your pain <br>Now you're so far out of reach <br>It's a lesson you can't teach <br><br>You love and you lose <br>I wish that you know <br>That it's just a lesson you can't teach <br>You love and you lose <br>I wish that you know <br>That it's just a lesson you can't teach <br><br>Son of God, are you listening <br>Son of God, can you hear my cry <br>We put our faith into you <br>How could you just watch them die <br>Son of God, are you listening <br>Son of God, can you hear my cry <br>We put our faith into you <br>How could you just watch us die]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Walk On Water" label="Walk On Water"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Decayer/</id><title>Blessthefall - Decayer - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:22:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:22:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Blessthefall/Decayer/" title="Blessthefall - Decayer - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sever the ties or it's all for nothing <br><br>Without a warning out of site <br>All these thoughts keep plaguing my mind <br>You saw this coming, you're out of time <br>So you can rot with the ones left behind <br><br>Nowhere to run, had this feeling <br>Right from the start <br>Another lie that I could not forgive <br>And now the rope's around your neck <br>Well it never was, yeah it never was <br>Well I hope you're good at starting over <br>Yeah it never was <br>And it never is going be <br><br>You act like nobody knows <br>If you're not at fault <br>Then who is in control <br>Don't try to put this on me <br>Burn your bridges <br>Buried beneath <br>This can't be all for nothing <br>Sever the ties or it's all for nothing <br><br>Nowhere to run, had this feeling <br>Right from the start <br>Another lie that I could not forgive <br>And now the rope's around your neck <br>Well it never was, yeah it never was <br>Well I hope you're good at starting over <br>Yeah it never was <br>And it never is going be <br><br>One by one <br>You reap what you sew <br>The thought of revenge is all that I know <br>One by one <br>You reap what you sew <br>I'm calling you out <br>Just to watch you choke <br><br>One by one <br>The thought of revenge is all that I know <br>One by one <br>I'm calling you out <br>Just to watch you choke <br><br>Nowhere to run <br>Had this feeling <br>Right from the start <br>Another lie that I could not forgive <br>And now the rope's around your neck <br>Well it never was, yeah it never was <br>Well I hope you're good at starting over <br>Yeah it never was <br>And it never is going be <br>Well it never was, yeah it never was <br>Well I hope you're good at starting over <br>Yeah it never was <br>And it never is going be <br><br>This can't be all for nothing]]></content><category term="Blessthefall" label="Blessthefall"/><category term="Decayer" label="Decayer"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Greywind/Hear_You_Me/</id><title>Greywind - Hear You Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:23:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:23:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Greywind/Hear_You_Me/" title="Greywind - Hear You Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's no one in town I know <br>You gave us some place to go <br>I never said thank you for that <br>I thought I might get one more chance <br>What would you think of me now <br>So lucky so strong so proud <br>I never said thank you for that <br>Now I'll never have a chance <br>May angels lead you in <br>Hear you me my friends <br>On sleepless roads the sleepless go <br>May angels lead you in <br>So what would you think of me now <br>So lucky so strong so proud <br>I never said thank you for that <br>Now I'll never have a chance <br>May angels lead you in <br>Hear you me my friends <br>On sleepless roads the sleepless go <br>May angels lead you in <br>May angels lead you in <br>May angels lead you in <br>And if you were with me tonight <br>I'd sing to you just one more time <br>A song for a heart so big <br>God wouldn't let it live <br>May angels lead you in <br>Hear you me my friends <br>On sleepless roads the sleepless go <br>May angels lead you in <br>May angels lead you in <br>Hear you me my friends <br>On sleepless roads the sleepless go <br>May angels lead you in <br>May angels lead you in]]></content><category term="Greywind" label="Greywind"/><category term="Hear You Me" label="Hear You Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/민제_MINJE/Yellow/</id><title>민제 (MINJE) - Yellow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:23:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:23:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AF%BC%EC%A0%9C_MINJE/Yellow/" title="민제 (MINJE) - Yellow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[알 수는 없지만 <br>길에 멈춰선 널 <br>계속 바라봐 <br>너는 알지만 <br>Let's going down <br>Try everything <br>시간을 모른 채 <br>같은 시간을 살겠지 <br>우린 알아도 모른 채 <br>또 같은 시간을 살겠지 <br>우린 시간을 모른 채 <br>또 같은 시간을 살겠지 <br>우린 알아도 모른 채 <br>또 같은 시간을 살겠지 <br>]]></content><category term="민제 (MINJE)" label="민제 (MINJE)"/><category term="Yellow" label="Yellow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이주아/끝에_서서/</id><title>이주아 - 끝에 서서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:23:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:23:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%A3%BC%EC%95%84/%EB%81%9D%EC%97%90_%EC%84%9C%EC%84%9C/" title="이주아 - 끝에 서서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[괜스레 불안한 하룰 보내고 <br>억지로 눈을 감아보기도 하고 <br>계속 뒤척이다가 <br>잠든 그날 밤엔 꿈을 꾸었어 <br>내가 너무 행복한 모습인데도 <br>눈물이 났어 이유는 모른 채 <br>기나긴 터널의 끝에 서서 <br>빛나는 한 점의 빛을 따라가 <br>언제쯤이면 밝은 그 빛에 <br>닿을지는 몰라도 <br>언젠간 다다를 끝에 서서 <br>예쁘게 웃을래 두려워하진 않아 <br>할 수 있어 울지 않고 <br>더 힘을 내 보는 거야 <br>익숙한 일상에 지친 오늘도 <br>쓰러지듯 침대에 누워 눈을 감고 <br>나도 모르게 그만 <br>잠든 그날 밤엔 꿈을 꾸었어 <br>내가 너무 행복한 모습인데도 <br>눈물이 났어 이유는 모른 채 <br>기나긴 터널의 끝에 서서 <br>빛나는 한 점의 빛을 따라가 <br>언제쯤이면 밝은 그 빛에 <br>닿을지는 몰라도 <br>언젠간 다다를 끝에 서서 <br>예쁘게 웃을래 두려워하진 않아 <br>할 수 있어 울지 않고 <br>더 힘을 내 보는 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="이주아" label="이주아"/><category term="끝에 서서" label="끝에 서서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Playboi_Carti/Lookin_Feat_Lil_Uzi_Vert/</id><title>Playboi Carti - Lookin (Feat. Lil Uzi Vert) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:23:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:23:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Playboi_Carti/Lookin_Feat_Lil_Uzi_Vert/" title="Playboi Carti - Lookin (Feat. Lil Uzi Vert) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look at these niggas <br>Look at these <br><br>Look at these niggas, what <br>Look at these niggas, ooh <br>Look at these niggas, what <br>Look at these niggas, what <br>Fuck these niggas, yuh <br>Fuck these niggas, yuh <br>Fuck these niggas, uh <br>Fuck these niggas, uh <br>Yuh, lil bitch <br>Fuck these niggas, yuh <br>Look at these niggas, yuh <br>Look at these niggas, yuh <br>Look at these niggas, yuh <br>Look at these niggas, yuh <br>Yuh, yuh <br><br>Aude' on my wrist, yuh, might just take your bitch, ooh <br>Might just take that Rick, yuh, take her on a trip, ooh <br>Head on her tongue, ooh, put it right there bitch, ooh <br>Hit 'em with the drum, ooh, they gon' feel this shit, ooh <br>Drivin' like I'm drunk, ooh but I'm off that lean <br>Bitches wanna fuck, ooh, hoe come lean on me, ooh <br>Yeah Promethazine, ooh, I can't even see, ooh <br>Niggas envy me, bitch I'm MVP <br><br>Oh yeah, shit yeah <br>What the, what the fuck you <br>Oh I forgot, I forgot, I forgot, I forgot, I forgot <br>I don't fuck with these niggas <br>Look at these niggas <br>Look at these <br><br>Look at these niggas, what <br>Look at these niggas, ooh <br>Look at these niggas, what <br>Look at these niggas, what <br>Fuck these niggas, yuh <br>Fuck these niggas, yuh <br>Fuck these niggas, uh <br>Fuck these niggas, uh <br>Yuh, lil bitch <br>Fuck these niggas, yuh <br>Look at these niggas, yuh <br>Look at these niggas, yuh <br>Look at these niggas, yuh <br>Look at these niggas, yuh <br>Yuh, yuh <br><br>Chopper with the stick and it got the kick <br>Ayy Uzi, where my gun at, bruh Stop playin' with me, man <br>Got a lot of kick, make you do back flip, yuh <br>I'm a walking lick, woo, lick, lick, lick, lick <br>Told the girl I do not wanna fuck told her just lick, woo <br>Lick, lick, lick, ohh, ohh, ohh <br>I cannot fuck you no bitch, get the fuck out my whip, ohh, ohh, ohh <br>Walk with your shawty, that 40 that's all on my hip <br>Pull up them forgies that's all on my vip <br>I ain't got time to be callin' no bitch <br>That's why I always be stallin' lil bitch <br>Don't wanna know more, I'm passin' assists <br>Ay stop, stop playin' with me, stop fuckin' playin' <br>Jump out the back, run for the pit <br>Smokin' that gas,you smoke that mid <br>Fucked at my crib, met her at LIV <br>She laugh at these niggas, look at these bitches <br>Its young Carti bitch <br><br>Look at these niggas, what <br>Look at these niggas, ooh <br>Look at these niggas, what <br>Look at these niggas, what <br>Fuck these niggas, yuh <br>Fuck these niggas, yuh <br>Fuck these niggas, uh <br>Fuck these niggas, uh <br>Yuh, lil bitch <br>Fuck these niggas, yuh <br>Look at these niggas, yuh <br>Look at these niggas, yuh <br>Look at these niggas, yuh <br>Look at these niggas, yuh <br>Yuh, yuh <br><br>Lil snitch ass nigga, I don't fuck with these niggas <br>I forgot, nigga <br>I think they forgot]]></content><category term="Playboi Carti" label="Playboi Carti"/><category term="Lookin (Feat. Lil Uzi Vert)" label="Lookin (Feat. Lil Uzi Vert)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rabbit_Mac/Muax/</id><title>Rabbit Mac - Muax - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:24:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:24:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rabbit_Mac/Muax/" title="Rabbit Mac - Muax - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, yen azhagey, naan unnai paarkirean <br>Naan un vizhiyil, ennai kaangirean <br>Naan oru chedi pol, thinam vaadurean <br>Owh, intha kodumai thinam kaangirean <br><br>Oru naal, thannaleh uyir poghumea <br>Naan unnakaghe uyir vazhuvean <br><br>Unmai kathaiyeh, keatkameh poghathe <br>Solla vanthethe sollamal nee pogathe <br>ithayathulleh kaathaleh valakkathe <br>Tha na na na na na na na na na na x 2 <br><br>Siru khaagitham, athil ooviyam <br>athu aanathey oru khaagitham <br>varainthen, varainthen mayi theereveah <br>unnakai varainthean, virral noghevea <br><br>Yen thevethey, yen khathaleh <br>Unnakagevea uyir vaazhuven <br><br>Unmai kathaiyeh, keatkameh poghathe <br>Solla vanthethe sollamal nee pogathe <br>ithayathulleh kaathaleh valakkathe <br>Tha na na na na na na na na na na x 2 <br><br>Oru naal, thannaleh uyir poghumea <br>Naan unnakaghe uyir vazhuvean]]></content><category term="Rabbit Mac" label="Rabbit Mac"/><category term="Muax" label="Muax"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/People_At_War/</id><title>Bush - People At War - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:24:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:24:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/People_At_War/" title="Bush - People At War - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a stranger to your people <br>I'm a stranger to your love <br>I am miles from your systems <br>I've seen you up above <br><br>We hurt together <br>We hurt apart <br><br>Peaceful people at war <br>We're peaceful people at war <br><br>I'm the refugee of angels <br>I'm the refugee of war <br>These lights can be so frightening <br>When you don't know what's happening <br><br>We hurt together <br>We hurt apart <br>We hurt forever <br>We hurt so hard <br><br>Peaceful people of war <br>We're peaceful people of war <br><br>We are lost floating nowhere <br>And the storms are closing in <br>Under cover of <br>Is you, me and the stars <br><br>Every ending is a beginning <br>Every ending is a start <br>I am so far from my homeland <br>So far from your arms <br><br>Peaceful people of war <br>We are peaceful people of war <br>Peaceful, peaceful <br>We are peaceful, peaceful]]></content><category term="Bush" label="Bush"/><category term="People At War" label="People At War"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/The_Edge_Of_Love/</id><title>Bush - The Edge Of Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:24:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:24:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/The_Edge_Of_Love/" title="Bush - The Edge Of Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I never thought I'd see your face again <br>I always felt that we both knew it was the end of things <br>You're strong like a fire, you're beautiful and wild in a dangerous wind <br>Now you are here, despite all the fears that we share within <br><br>We're on the edge of love <br>Dive in a drowning pool <br>We lose ourselves <br>See a light shining through <br>On the edge of love <br>On the edge of love <br>See a light shining through <br><br>I see the flicker of the valley lights <br>A million heartbeats, so bittersweet that go out of time <br>A million mistakes, the way that we break to never return again <br>I've waited to bloom, I'm clinically blue but I won't fade on you <br><br>We're on the edge of love <br>Dive in a drowning pool <br>We lose ourselves <br>See a light shining through <br>On the edge of love <br>On the edge of love <br>See a light shining through <br><br>I tried to run <br>Destroyed all I can <br>Forms a round <br>On a beach of quicksand <br><br>We're on the edge love <br>Dive in a drowning pool <br>We lose ourselves <br>See a light shining through <br>On the edge of love <br>Dive in a drowning pool <br>We lose ourselves <br>See a light shining through <br>On the edge of love <br>On the edge of love <br>See a light shining through]]></content><category term="Bush" label="Bush"/><category term="The Edge Of Love" label="The Edge Of Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/Nothing_But_A_Car_Chase/</id><title>Bush - Nothing But A Car Chase - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:24:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:24:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/Nothing_But_A_Car_Chase/" title="Bush - Nothing But A Car Chase - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's blood on the walls, this town <br>Some screams have no sound <br>Been around the world for love <br>You been around the world for love <br>There's violence in the silence <br>The flowers in your hair <br><br>Hang on to yourself, babe <br>Hang on to yourself, babe <br>Oh <br><br>It's all so temporary <br>Changes like the rivers running through the mountains <br>Your heart was a sanctuary <br>Now it's just a mystery to me <br><br>This will pass, it's like suicide <br>Don't give up, if you make it alive <br>It's nothing but a car chase, babe <br>Nothing but a mind gone crazed <br>Trouble in spades, yeah <br>At 75 miles per hour <br><br>Hang on to yourself, babe <br>Hang on to yourself, babe <br>Oh <br><br>It's all so temporary <br>Changes like the rivers running through the mountains <br>Your heart was a sanctuary <br>Now it's just a mystery to me <br><br>A house of mirrors <br>A house of mirrors <br>A house of mirrors <br><br>Made my way to the city <br>There was no one around <br>I remember you so beautiful <br>I remember you so down, down <br><br>It's all so temporary <br>Changes like the rivers running through the mountains <br>Your heart was a sanctuary <br>Now it's just a mystery to me <br><br>A house of mirrors <br>A house of mirrors]]></content><category term="Bush" label="Bush"/><category term="Nothing But A Car Chase" label="Nothing But A Car Chase"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/Ray_Of_Light/</id><title>Bush - Ray Of Light - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:24:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:24:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/Ray_Of_Light/" title="Bush - Ray Of Light - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a dreamscape, this is my scape <br>I was miles away, you're so far from me <br>It's a crime babe, Your fingers and thumbs <br>Speak in tongues, your language <br>You're a wild one, but you love like candy <br><br>If I can be a ray of light for you <br>If I could help to pull you through <br>If I can be a ray of light for you <br>If I could help to pull you through <br><br>See you disappear, on a blood moon <br>Tthe orchestra surrounded you <br>With your pale eyes and your lipstick face <br>Never made it clear, when you fade away <br><br>And you kiss me, and you love like candy <br>Love like candy <br><br>If I can be a ray of light for you <br>If I could help to pull you through <br>If I can be a ray of light for you <br>If I could help to pull you through <br><br>We hurt the most as she said her last goodbye <br>Words to the tune of a tragic lullaby <br><br>It's a crime babe, Your fingers and thumbs <br>Speak in tongues, your language <br>You're a wild one, but you love like candy <br><br>If I can be a ray of light for you <br>If I could help to pull you through <br>If I can be a ray of light for you <br>If I could help you, if i could help you <br><br>Ray of light <br>Ray of light <br>Ray of light <br>To help you <br>To help you]]></content><category term="Bush" label="Bush"/><category term="Ray Of Light" label="Ray Of Light"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/Dystopia/</id><title>Bush - Dystopia - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:24:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:24:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/Dystopia/" title="Bush - Dystopia - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We don't know what is coming, we know where we've been <br>In this city of ghosts I find myself again <br>There's seventeen ways you tried to kill me from the inside <br>And now all this scars all this wounds will be healed <br><br>Dystopia <br>Things got so out of control <br>Dystopia <br>I find so hard to let go <br>Dystopia <br>Things got so out of control <br>Dystopia <br>I find so hard to let go <br>Dystopia <br><br>I know you're living on the edge, in a minefield <br>I've waited such a long time for you to feel <br>I've missed you for the longest, it has been so long <br>There was a time you were but now I know you're gone <br><br>Dystopia <br>Things got so out of control <br>Dystopia <br>I find so hard to let go <br>Dystopia <br>Things got so out of control <br>Dystopia <br>I find so hard to let go <br>Dystopia <br><br>Everything you know is wrong <br>Everything you know is sand <br>Everything you know is broken <br>Everything you know is gone <br>Everything you know <br>Everything you know <br>Everything you know <br>Everything you know <br><br>Dystopia <br>Things got so out of control <br>Dystopia <br>I find so hard to let go <br>Dystopia <br>Things got so out of control <br>Dystopia <br>I find so hard to let go <br>Dystopia]]></content><category term="Bush" label="Bush"/><category term="Dystopia" label="Dystopia"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/All_The_Worlds_Within_You/</id><title>Bush - All The Worlds Within You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:25:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:25:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/All_The_Worlds_Within_You/" title="Bush - All The Worlds Within You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The longest night is over <br>The longest day has just begun <br>I turn myself into someone <br>I should've been all along <br>But these trials are here to mould us <br>We are how we reply <br><br>And all the worlds within you <br>And all the places that you go <br>All the love that's inside you <br>All the scars and the lows <br>All the worlds <br>All the worlds <br><br>There's murder in the streets <br>Don't need matter in the houses <br>We lost our minds, lost Valentines <br>You push so far, you push so low <br><br>And all the worlds within you <br>And all the places that you go <br>All the love that's inside you <br>All the scars and the lows <br>And all the worlds within you <br>All the places that you go <br>All the love that's inside you <br>All the scars and the lows <br>All the worlds <br>All the worlds <br><br>When will you come around <br>I'm so tired of this waiting <br>Tired of this waiting <br>I'm so tired of this waiting <br><br>To all the worlds within you <br>To all the worlds within you <br>To all the worlds]]></content><category term="Bush" label="Bush"/><category term="All The Worlds Within You" label="All The Worlds Within You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/Lost_In_You/</id><title>Bush - Lost In You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:25:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:25:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/Lost_In_You/" title="Bush - Lost In You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She rests her head close to mine <br>I feel her in me all the time <br>It's been a while since I've seen her around <br>We weren't at our best when she left town <br>I've seen the red of the sun <br>It's dull compared to what I've done <br><br>And you're haunting me from space <br>As I crush my car again <br><br>I, I get lost in you <br>A safe place to come <br>Cause you, you were the only one <br>To help to see me through <br><br>Faces can tell you've been used <br>I've seen how much there is to lose <br>Love seems to shine falls down <br>All the new tattoos have gone wrong <br><br>And you're haunting me from space <br><br>I, I get lost in you <br>A safe place to come <br>And you, you were the only one <br>To help to see me through <br><br>It's hard not to miss what you destroy <br>All that weakness knows no joy <br>Will I ever see her again <br>Once I was inside her <br><br>I, I get lost in you <br>A safe place to come <br>And you, you were the only one <br>To help to see me through <br><br>I, I get lost in you <br>And I try, try, try not to fade]]></content><category term="Bush" label="Bush"/><category term="Lost In You" label="Lost In You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/Water/</id><title>Bush - Water - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:25:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:25:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/Water/" title="Bush - Water - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I will always be yours <br>You stole my heart some time ago <br>Now in the madness of this winter <br>We wait for Spring to grow, yeah <br><br>Till the blossom blows <br>Till the blossom blows <br>Till the blossom blows <br><br>Got to be like water <br>Got to be like rain <br>Got to be myself again <br>No matter what you say <br><br>You will always be mine <br>Together or apart <br>Now we're dead forever <br>Nothing kills like covered hearts, yeah <br><br>Till the blossom blows <br>Till the blossom blows <br>Till the blossom blows <br><br>Got to be like water <br>Got to be like rain <br>Got to be myself again <br>No matter what you say <br>Got to be like water <br>Got to be like rain <br>Got to be myself again <br>I'm in an inner space <br><br>Breathe life into dead things <br>Breathe life into beauty, yeah <br><br>Got to be like water When you can't see your enemies <br>Got to be like rain When your enemies can't see you <br>Got to be myself again When you can't see your enemies <br>No matter what you say When your enemies can't see you <br><br>When you can't see your enemies <br>When your enemies can't see you <br>When you can't see your enemies <br><br>Got to be like water <br>Got to be like water <br>Got to be like water <br>Got to be like water]]></content><category term="Bush" label="Bush"/><category term="Water" label="Water"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/Mad_Love/</id><title>Bush - Mad Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:25:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:25:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bush/Mad_Love/" title="Bush - Mad Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No saving me from drowning <br>You were silent as a raincloud <br>The ceiling was imploding <br>The walls were closing in <br>I was feeling a prisoner <br>I was running so fast <br>I was speeding through the red lights <br>Speeding past <br><br>Still got mad love for you baby <br>Still got mad love for you baby <br>Every day you find ways to drive me crazy <br>Still got mad love for you baby <br>Still got mad love for you baby <br>Every day you find ways to drive me crazy <br><br>Oh, oh <br>Oh, oh <br>Oh, oh <br>Oh, oh <br><br>So restless, we're waiting <br>You've been gone so long <br>I fell in your slipstream <br>Fell in my arms <br>And I want you to dance now <br>To dance just for me <br>It's all out of focus <br>You make me so free <br><br>Still got mad love for you baby <br>Still got mad love for you baby <br>Every day you find ways to drive me crazy <br>Still got mad love for you baby <br>Still got mad love for you baby <br>Every day you find ways to drive me crazy <br><br>Oh, oh <br>Oh, oh <br>Oh, oh <br>Oh, oh <br><br>Still got mad love for you baby <br>Still got mad love for you baby <br>Every day you find ways to drive me crazy <br>Still got mad love for you baby <br>Still got mad love for you baby <br>Still got mad love for you baby <br><br>Oh, oh <br>Oh, oh <br>Mad love, mad love]]></content><category term="Bush" label="Bush"/><category term="Mad Love" label="Mad Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wide_Awake/Ready/</id><title>Wide Awake - Ready - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:26:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:26:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wide_Awake/Ready/" title="Wide Awake - Ready - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[wide awake <br>ever sleep into the ocean <br>follow me i'll be emotion <br>she's my quinn or your devotion <br>where's my life i miss the ocean <br>i am ready to let go now <br>i am ready to let go <br>i am ready to let go <br>i am ready to let go now <br>i am ready to let go now <br>ever sleep into the ocean <br>follow me i'll be emotion <br>she's my quinn or your devotion <br>where's my life i miss the ocean <br>i am ready to let go <br>i am ready to let go <br>i am ready to let go <br>i am ready to let go now <br>i am ready to let go now]]></content><category term="Wide Awake" label="Wide Awake"/><category term="Ready" label="Ready"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/St_Grandson/Midnight_Swim/</id><title>St. Grandson - Midnight Swim - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-12T13:27:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-12T13:27:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/St_Grandson/Midnight_Swim/" title="St. Grandson - Midnight Swim - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The moments we've been on, worn out <br>When surroundings were at light, too long <br>We've been waiting for sunday light for such a long time <br>Keep on heading <br>When the heart just doesn't bother <br>We all want and thrive to share <br>With everyone <br>From the isle <br>A night, a swim, swim as a feather <br>At night I feel, I feel like a dancer <br><br>Dancing like wild winds <br>Be loved <br>While the dusk seems to dissapear <br>We dream on <br>Keep on heading <br>When the heart just doesn't bother <br>Sometimes we're wandering <br>Some days we're longing <br>For a place to dive <br>I thrive to share <br>Another one <br>On the isle <br>We've been around and around and around <br>From the isle <br>A night, a swim, swim as a feather <br>Of this isle <br>A night I feel, I feel I feel like a dancer <br>Won't be long <br>Much better then to hide <br>Tonight we fall we fall to the light <br><br>We've been around and around and around]]></content><category term="St. Grandson" label="St. Grandson"/><category term="Midnight Swim" label="Midnight Swim"/></entry></feed>