<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T12:32:26+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Staind/Failing_Live/</id><title>Staind - Failing (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-14T12:32:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-14T12:32:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Staind/Failing_Live/" title="Staind - Failing (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, like the threat of the darkest clouds rollin' in on a sunny day... <br>Yeah, like a field that has no rain... <br>Yeah, like a dog that wanders aimless, with no mane... <br>Yeah, like a cut without the pain... <br><br>You couldn't feel this? <br>You couldn't take the pain? <br>You couldn't live this? <br><br>And I'm just trying to get through to you, <br>And I am failing <br>Lie like I'm not even here, <br>My heart is breaking <br>Trying to see through your stare, <br>It looks right through me <br>I smile and pretend I'm not there, <br>To keep from going crazy <br><br>Yeah, like the day that your guardian angel decided to fly away... <br>Yeah, like a bruise that doesn't fade... <br>Yeah, like a memory that tortures your soul until your dying day... <br>Yeah, like the life you couldn't save... <br><br>You couldn't feel this? <br>You couldn't take the pain? <br>You couldn't live this? <br><br>And I'm just trying to get through to you, <br>And I am failing <br>Lie like I'm not even here, <br>My heart is breaking <br>Trying to see through your stare, <br>It looks right through me <br>I smile and pretend I'm not there, <br>To keep from going crazy <br><br>I've tried to... get through to you <br>I've tried to... I'm trying <br>I've tried to... get through to you <br>I've tried to... <br><br>And I'm still trying to get through to you, <br>And I am failing <br>Lie like I'm not even here, <br>My heart is breaking <br>Trying to see through your stare, <br>It looks right through me <br>I smile and pretend I'm not there, <br>To keep from going crazy <br><br>I've tried to... get through to you <br>I've tried to... <br>I've tried to... get through to you <br><br>I've tried to... get through. <br><br>I've tried to... get through to you <br>I've tried to...]]></content><category term="Staind" label="Staind"/><category term="Failing (Live)" label="Failing (Live)"/></entry></feed>