<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:33:42+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/Turn/</id><title>Magna Carta Cartel - Turn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:33:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:33:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/Turn/" title="Magna Carta Cartel - Turn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Turn <br>Close your eyes <br>Let love pass like <br>Rain <br>Falls like time <br>And here we will all see <br><br>Days turn to hours <br>Days are the years <br>What is wrong <br>Everything is ours <br>This is what it plays <br>What is wrong <br><br>Turn <br>Sing with me <br>Let the birds have their say <br>Set me free <br>And now, walk away like <br><br>Days turn to hours <br>Days are the years <br>What is wrong <br>Everything is ours <br>This is what it plays <br>What is wrong <br><br>Lies won't help you <br>Lies won't help you <br>Lies won't help you <br><br>No, lies won't help you <br>No, lies won't help you <br>No, lies won't help you <br>No, lies won't help you <br><br>Days turn to hours <br>Days are the years <br>What is wrong <br>Everything's for ever <br>Maybe this as well <br>What is wrong]]></content><category term="Magna Carta Cartel" label="Magna Carta Cartel"/><category term="Turn" label="Turn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/Sway/</id><title>Magna Carta Cartel - Sway - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:33:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:33:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/Sway/" title="Magna Carta Cartel - Sway - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stops for a plane <br>Letting the last fall to ground <br>And what comes to be <br>Looking this way <br>Offer our senses <br>Facing ourselves <br><br>When looking at you <br>You're caught staring back <br>Glowing up truth <br>Reminding each other <br>The lack of themselves <br>Is nobody's loss <br><br>He says 'Hi, I'm missing my flight, and you' <br>Call for a no <br>This show is over <br>But the big one goes on <br>Next time my back will be covered <br>While you <br>Will stay <br>Astray <br><br>Reminding of me <br>Is far from success <br>Destructions befall <br>Assume as your own <br>And I spit it out <br>It still leaves a mark <br><br>Just a remainder, so many reserve them <br>And I'm still in the game <br>Hit up this way <br>See my charisma <br>Remember my name <br><br>Ask me about myself <br>And I'm fine <br><br>So if there's no hesitation <br>Will you need me <br>'Till the edge <br><br>You stay <br>Astray <br>And I see <br>Your way <br>You stay]]></content><category term="Magna Carta Cartel" label="Magna Carta Cartel"/><category term="Sway" label="Sway"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/The_Demon_King/</id><title>Magna Carta Cartel - The Demon King - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:33:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:33:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/The_Demon_King/" title="Magna Carta Cartel - The Demon King - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe I bury my freedom <br>In you <br>And maybe I rest in your kingdom <br>It's hard to make out if it's true <br><br>Please <br>Let go of me <br>Please <br>I've paid <br>Please find someone else <br>But me <br>Here comes the order <br>Here comes your call <br>And I have to follow <br>And heed to it all <br>I trust that you love me <br>Or why would you care <br>Here comes the order <br>Shackles of scare <br><br>What have I done to begin with <br>To always be bargain with fear <br>I don't even know what your name is <br>It's odd 'cause you've always been here <br><br>Please <br>Let go of me <br>Please <br>I've paid <br>Please find someone else <br>But me <br>Here comes the order <br>Here comes your call <br>And I have to follow <br>And heed to it all <br>I trust that you love me <br>Or why would you care <br>Here comes the order <br>Shackles of scare <br><br>We call ourselves legion <br>For many we be <br>And you will obey us <br>And never be free <br>So join us forever <br>Or live in despair <br>It seems that I'm changing <br>Becoming your heir <br>So hand me your kingdom <br>I'll take it from here <br>And dare no one break from <br>My circles of fear]]></content><category term="Magna Carta Cartel" label="Magna Carta Cartel"/><category term="The Demon King" label="The Demon King"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Do_As_Infinity/Iron_Hornet/</id><title>Do As Infinity - Iron Hornet - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:34:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:34:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Do_As_Infinity/Iron_Hornet/" title="Do As Infinity - Iron Hornet - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's just an ordinary day <br>In our dystopia and paranoia <br>Reigns supreme. Invades our dream <br>Fluttering wings outside our door <br><br>Second sun don't bring us joy no more <br><br>The euthanasia. The population <br>We know the agents of the rose will come <br>And never stop until their work is done <br>The fear in Asia; Depopulation <br>The iron hornets that we used to fight <br>Were turned against us in the fading light <br><br>Losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>They think more the merrier <br>Losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>Avoid crowded area <br><br>It's hard to find a way to pay <br>The cost of education breaks my body <br>Memories of a laughing child <br>Fluttering wings outside my door <br><br>Second sun don't bring us joy no more <br><br>The euthanasia. The population <br>We know the agents of the rose will come <br>And never stop until their work is done <br>The fear in Asia; Depopulation <br>The iron hornets that we used to fight <br>Were turned against us in the fading light <br><br>Losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>They think more the merrier <br>Losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>Avoid crowded area <br><br>The euthanasia. The population <br>We know the agents of the rose will come <br>And never stop until their work is done <br>The fear in Asia; Depopulation <br>The iron hornets that we used to fight <br>Were turned against us in the fading light <br><br>Losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>They think more the merrier <br>Losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>Avoid crowded area <br><br>Losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>They think more the merrier <br>Losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>We're losing our people <br>Avoid crowded area]]></content><category term="Do As Infinity" label="Do As Infinity"/><category term="Iron Hornet" label="Iron Hornet"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Do_As_Infinity/Alive/</id><title>Do As Infinity - Alive - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:34:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:34:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Do_As_Infinity/Alive/" title="Do As Infinity - Alive - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[銃を持つ少年 叫ぶ <br>쥬오모쯔쇼넨 사케부 <br>총을 든 소년 외쳐 <br>No way, No way, No way, Leave me alone <br>そっと抱きしめて？く <br>솟토다키시메테쯔부야쿠 <br>살며시 끌어안고 중얼거려 <br>No need to worry, Baby... <br>燃える空 ？ける故？(まち) <br>모에루소라 야케루마치 <br>불타는 하늘 불타는 고향 <br>We don't know "why" <br>容赦なく 潰されてく My heart <br>요샤나쿠 쯔부사레테쿠 My heart <br>가차없이 부서져가 My heart <br><br>Always my wish is only one, "just want to see your smile" <br><br>Just do it! Go there to be alive <br>不？理な 悲しみを越えてゆけ <br>후죠리나 카나시미오코에테유케 <br>부조리한 슬픔을 넘어서 가 <br>答えを求めて <br>코타에오모토메테 <br>답을 찾아서 <br>Just do it! Go there to be alive <br>荒れ果てた 大地に？く花は <br>아레하테타 다이치니사쿠하나와 <br>황폐해진 대지에 피는 꽃은 <br>君だろうか <br>키미다로우카 <br>너일까 <br>僕だろうか <br>보쿠다로우카 <br>나일까 <br><br>Stop killing now! C'mon! That's enough! <br>Why don't you see the flowers with her smile? <br>Gotta stop killing now! C'mon! That's enough! <br>Why don't you see the flowers with her smile? Ah ah <br><br>パンを持つ少女 微笑む <br>팡오모쯔쇼죠 호호에무 <br>빵을 든 소녀 미소지어 <br>Okay, Okay, Okay, How can I say... <br>きつく唇 ？みしめて <br>키쯔쿠쿠치비루 카미시메테 <br>꽉 입술을 깨물고 <br>No need to change, Baby <br>奪い合う その果てで <br>우바이아우 소노하테데 <br>서로 빼앗는 그 끝에서 <br>Will we get the love? <br>理屈(ロジック)に？されてく My mind <br>로짓쿠니코와사레테쿠 My mind <br>논리에 부서져가 My mind <br><br>Always my wish is only one, "just want to save your dream" <br>？け この願いよ <br>토도케 코노네가이요 <br>이루어져라 이 소원이여 <br>？ち切れない 悲しみを越えてゆけ <br>타치키레나이 카나시미오코에테유케 <br>끊어내지못한 슬픔을 넘어서 가 <br>答えを 求めて <br>코타에오 모토메테 <br>답을 찾아서 <br>あの日 ？いた花は <br>아노히 사이타하나와 <br>그날 핀 꽃은 <br>誰の"夢" "希望"だったのだろう <br>다레노"유메" "키보우"닷타노다로우 <br>누구의 "꿈" "희망"이였을까 <br>君だろうか <br>키미다로우카 <br>너일까 <br>僕だろうか <br>보쿠다로우카 <br>나일까 <br><br>Just do it! Go there to be alive <br>不？理な 悲しみを越えてゆけ <br>후죠리나 카나시미오코에테유케 <br>부조리한 슬픔을 넘어서 가 <br>答えを求めて <br>코타에오모토메테 <br>답을 찾아서 <br>Just do it! Go there to be alive <br>荒れ果てた 大地に？く花は <br>아레하테타 다이치니사쿠하나와 <br>황폐해진 대지에 피는 꽃은 <br>君だろうか <br>키미다로우카 <br>너일까 <br>僕だろうか <br>보쿠다로우카 <br>나일까 <br><br>Stop killing now! C'mon! That's enough! <br>Why don't you see the flowers with her smile? <br>Gotta stop killing now! C'mon! That's enough! <br>Why don't you see the flowers with her smile? Ah ah <br><br>Stop killing now! C'mon! That's enough! <br>Why don't you see the flowers with her smile? <br>Gotta stop killing now! C'mon! That's enough! <br>Why don't you see the flowers with her smile? Ah ah]]></content><category term="Do As Infinity" label="Do As Infinity"/><category term="Alive" label="Alive"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hit_Tunes_Karaoke/코코밥_Shimmy_Shimmy_Ko_Ko_Bop_Hit_Tunes_Ver/</id><title>Hit Tunes Karaoke - (코코밥) Shimmy, Shimmy, Ko Ko Bop (Hit Tunes Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:34:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:34:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hit_Tunes_Karaoke/%EC%BD%94%EC%BD%94%EB%B0%A5_Shimmy_Shimmy_Ko_Ko_Bop_Hit_Tunes_Ver/" title="Hit Tunes Karaoke - (코코밥) Shimmy, Shimmy, Ko Ko Bop (Hit Tunes Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ah <br>Oh Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ah <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Oh Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ah <br>Oh Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ah <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>You can do the ko-ko-bop <br>Now's no time to stop <br>Oh Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ah <br>Oh Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ah <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>]]></content><category term="Hit Tunes Karaoke" label="Hit Tunes Karaoke"/><category term="(코코밥) Shimmy, Shimmy, Ko Ko Bop (Hit Tunes Ver.)" label="(코코밥) Shimmy, Shimmy, Ko Ko Bop (Hit Tunes Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Golden_Oldies/Shimmy_Shimmy_Ko-Ko-Bop_코코밥___The_Golden_Oldies_Ver/</id><title>The Golden Oldies - Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop (코코밥 : The Golden Oldies Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:35:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:35:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Golden_Oldies/Shimmy_Shimmy_Ko-Ko-Bop_%EC%BD%94%EC%BD%94%EB%B0%A5___The_Golden_Oldies_Ver/" title="The Golden Oldies - Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop (코코밥 : The Golden Oldies Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ah <br>Oh Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ah <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Sittin' in a native hut <br>All alone and blue <br>Sittin' in a native hut <br>Wonderin' what to do <br>Along came a native girl <br>Did a native dance <br>It was like in paradise <br>Put me in a trance <br>Going <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Joined her in her dancin' spree <br>Felt my spine a-tingle <br>Held her tight and close to me <br>Man I'm glad I'm single <br>Then she showed me what to do <br>First I was amazed <br>Soon I learned a step or two <br>Put me in a daze <br>Going <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>You can do the ko-ko-bop <br>Now's no time to stop <br>Left foot forward right one back <br>Bring them side by side <br>Uh syncopate your last two steps <br>Now you're going to glide <br>Keep along the rhythm track <br>Girls please show 'em how <br>Now you start to arch your back <br>Man you got it now <br>Going <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy <br>]]></content><category term="The Golden Oldies" label="The Golden Oldies"/><category term="Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop (코코밥 : The Golden Oldies Ver.)" label="Shimmy Shimmy Ko-Ko-Bop (코코밥 : The Golden Oldies Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Little_Anthony__The_Imperials/Shimmy_Shimmy_Ko_Ko_Bop_Remastered_코코밥/</id><title>Little Anthony &amp; The Imperials - Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop (Remastered) (코코밥) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:36:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:36:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Little_Anthony__The_Imperials/Shimmy_Shimmy_Ko_Ko_Bop_Remastered_%EC%BD%94%EC%BD%94%EB%B0%A5/" title="Little Anthony &amp; The Imperials - Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop (Remastered) (코코밥) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Sittin' in a native hut <br>All alone and blue <br>Sittin' in a native hut <br>Wonderin' what to do <br>Along came a native girl <br>Did a native dance <br>It was like in paradise <br>Put me in a trance <br>Going <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Joined her in her dancin' spree <br>Felt my spine a tingle <br>Held her tight and close to me <br>Man I'm glad I'm single <br>Then she showed me what to do <br>First I was amazed <br>Soon I learned a step or two <br>Put me in a daze <br>Going <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>You can do the ko ko bop <br>Now's no time to stop <br>Left foot forward right one back <br>Bring them side by side <br>Uh syncopate your last two steps <br>Now you're going to glide <br>Keep along the rhythm track <br>Girls please show 'em how <br>Now you start to arch your back <br>Man you got it now <br>Going <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop <br>Shimmy Shimmy Bop <br>]]></content><category term="Little Anthony &amp; The Imperials" label="Little Anthony &amp; The Imperials"/><category term="Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop (Remastered) (코코밥)" label="Shimmy Shimmy Ko Ko Bop (Remastered) (코코밥)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/고릴라/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 고릴라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:37:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:37:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EA%B3%A0%EB%A6%B4%EB%9D%BC/" title="핑크퐁 - 고릴라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[펑가 알라피아 아셰이 아셰이 <br>펑가 알라피아 아셰이 아셰이 <br><br>붐디 붐디 붐디 붐 <br>나무를 타자 <br>붐디 붐디 붐디 붐 <br>신나는 정글 <br>신데렐라 아니고요 <br>바닐라 아니고요 <br>난 릴라 릴라 릴라 릴라 고릴라 <br><br>고릴라 <br>고릴라 <br>고릴라! <br><br>붐디 붐디 붐디 붐 <br>우 우 우 우 <br>붐디 붐디 붐디 붐 <br>붐디 붐붐 <br>신데렐라 아니고요 <br>바닐라 아니고요 <br>난 릴라 릴라 릴라 릴라 고릴라 <br><br>고릴라!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="고릴라" label="고릴라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조아람/누가_먼저랄_것도_없이/</id><title>조아람 - 누가 먼저랄 것도 없이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:37:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:37:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%95%84%EB%9E%8C/%EB%88%84%EA%B0%80_%EB%A8%BC%EC%A0%80%EB%9E%84_%EA%B2%83%EB%8F%84_%EC%97%86%EC%9D%B4/" title="조아람 - 누가 먼저랄 것도 없이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그런 표정으로 날 자꾸 바라보지 마 <br>내가 어쩔 줄 모르겠잖아 <br>그런 웃음 지으며 네가 날 바라보면 <br>아무 생각이 나질 않잖아 <br>그러다가 나도 너를 빤히 바라보면 <br>다가와 입 맞추는 널 어쩌면 좋니 <br>너와의 하루하루가 너무나도 좋아 <br>누가 먼저랄 것도 없이 <br>우리만 아는 말들로 서로를 부르고 <br>사랑한다고 말하는 우리 둘 <br>집에 보내기 싫어 맥주 한 캔 들고서 <br>하염없이 걸었던 오늘밤 <br>우리들의 내일을 말하는 네 모습을 <br>하염없이 바라본 오늘밤 <br>하나둘씩 쌓여간 우리의 처음들과 <br>그 위로 단단해지는 우리의 마음들 <br>너와의 하루하루가 너무나도 좋아 <br>누가 먼저랄 것도 없이 <br>우리만 아는 말들로 서로를 부르고 <br>사랑한다 말하는 우리 <br>몇 번을 더 말하게 될까 <br>끝도 없는 나의 마음을 <br>너와의 하루하루가 무엇보다 좋아 <br>누가 먼저랄 것도 없이 <br>사랑한다고 말했던 오늘의 밤처럼 <br>모든 게 충분한 요즘 우리 둘 <br>]]></content><category term="조아람" label="조아람"/><category term="누가 먼저랄 것도 없이" label="누가 먼저랄 것도 없이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태엽장치/중간쯤_살고_싶어/</id><title>태엽장치 - 중간쯤 살고 싶어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:37:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:37:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%BD%EC%9E%A5%EC%B9%98/%EC%A4%91%EA%B0%84%EC%AF%A4_%EC%82%B4%EA%B3%A0_%EC%8B%B6%EC%96%B4/" title="태엽장치 - 중간쯤 살고 싶어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[특별할 것도 없어 <br>그냥 내 하루는 조금 뒤쳐져 <br>중간쯤 사는 것도 <br>꽤 어려운 요즘 일인 것 같아 <br>꿈이란 걸 바랬던 <br>그때 뜨겁던 마음은 이젠 저물어 <br>무겁게 날 짓 누르는 현실에 <br>아무것도 할 수가 없는데 <br>하루를 그냥 오늘도 내일도 <br>그냥 그렇게 중간쯤 살고 싶어 <br>너무 어려운 바램인 걸까 <br>자꾸만 뒤쳐져 <br>하루쯤 그냥 그늘 막에 앉아 <br>그냥 그렇게 보통을 살고 싶어 <br>어차피 내 인생이란 건 <br>여름 밤 꿈결 같은걸 <br>연애란 걸 꿈꾸던 <br>그때 설레던 마음은 이젠 사라져 <br>차갑게 날 밀어내는 현실에 <br>아무것도 핑계조차 없는데 <br>하루를 그냥 오늘도 내일도 <br>그냥 그렇게 중간쯤 살고 싶어 <br>너무 어려운 바램인 걸까 <br>자꾸만 뒤쳐져 <br>하루쯤 그냥 그늘 막에 앉아 <br>그냥 그렇게 보통을 살고 싶어 <br>어차피 내 인생이란 건 <br>여름 밤의 꿈결 같은걸 <br>]]></content><category term="태엽장치" label="태엽장치"/><category term="중간쯤 살고 싶어" label="중간쯤 살고 싶어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태엽장치/썸타는_썸머/</id><title>태엽장치 - 썸타는 썸머 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:37:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:37:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%BD%EC%9E%A5%EC%B9%98/%EC%8D%B8%ED%83%80%EB%8A%94_%EC%8D%B8%EB%A8%B8/" title="태엽장치 - 썸타는 썸머 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모기가 날아 가네 <br>잡아야 푹 잘텐데 <br>힘이 없어 몸은 또 끈적끈적 <br>바닥에 달라 붙어 <br>찌는 태양을 따라 <br>푸른 바다로 떠나요 <br>넘실 넘실대는 파도를 건너서 <br>해변의 여인을 찾아 <br>깊은 바다로 떠나요 <br>두근 두근대는 맘을 안고 <br>여보세요 뭐하니 여름인데 <br>또 집에 붙어있어 <br>찌는 태양을 따라 <br>푸른 바다로 떠나요 <br>넘실 넘실대는 파도를 건너서 <br>해변의 여인을 찾아 <br>깊은 바다로 떠나요 <br>두근 두근대는 맘을 안고 <br>썸타는 썸머를 원해요 <br>낭만이 없어요 난 <br>그냥 티비만 봐요 <br>썸타는 썸머를 원해요 <br>재미 없어 <br>떠나자 지금 바다로 가자 <br>찌는 태양을 따라 <br>푸른 바다로 떠나요 <br>넘실 넘실대는 파도를 건너서 <br>해변의 님을 찾아 <br>지금 여행을 떠나요 <br>두근 두근대는 맘을 안고 <br>오늘은 썸타는 썸머 <br>]]></content><category term="태엽장치" label="태엽장치"/><category term="썸타는 썸머" label="썸타는 썸머"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태엽장치/수박을_좋아하는_그녀/</id><title>태엽장치 - 수박을 좋아하는 그녀 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:38:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:38:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%97%BD%EC%9E%A5%EC%B9%98/%EC%88%98%EB%B0%95%EC%9D%84_%EC%A2%8B%EC%95%84%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EA%B7%B8%EB%85%80/" title="태엽장치 - 수박을 좋아하는 그녀 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[수박을 좋아하는 <br>사랑스런 그녀는 <br>수박을 좋아하는 <br>나의 그녀는 <br>수박을 고를때도 <br>예쁘시더니 <br>수박을 쪼갤때도 <br>먹을때도 예뻐 <br>오 수박을 좋아하는 그녀는 <br>너무 아름다워 <br>수박을 싫어했던 난 이젠 <br>수박이 젤 좋아 <br>수박씨 뱉을때도 <br>붙일때도 예뻐 <br>수박을 냉장고에 <br>넣을때도 예뻐 오오 <br>수박을 좋아하는 그녀는 <br>너무 아름다워 <br>수박을 싫어했던 난 이젠 <br>수박이 젤 좋아 <br>수박이 젤 좋아 <br>]]></content><category term="태엽장치" label="태엽장치"/><category term="수박을 좋아하는 그녀" label="수박을 좋아하는 그녀"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/Hotellus_Eviction/</id><title>Magna Carta Cartel - Hotellus Eviction - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:38:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:38:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/Hotellus_Eviction/" title="Magna Carta Cartel - Hotellus Eviction - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[As fathers leaving all their flags of truth <br>another claims your eyes <br>with fires steeling sleep from us <br>we're evolving our disguise <br><br>in constant missing boredom <br>sits a child and waits for hell <br>he longs for all the dangers <br>but all seems far too well <br><br>a catchy tune leads a way to life <br>for those still here for fun <br>and heaven flirting wildly <br>with someone's lack of faith <br><br>market selling answers <br>wrapping up your wish <br>have a dream for breakfast <br>and another one for life <br><br>wise men count their fingers <br>and stare at you with <br>lustscience rolling on and on <br>there's no ending kill your trust <br><br>and as love comes passing through your gate <br>reflecting wonders dawn <br>you sense the world is sleeping <br>and you laugh at being late <br><br>and even as the fires gets you <br>there's always time for more <br>instantly with passion <br>you claim to be a whore <br>enlist yourself for freedom <br>buy a ticket from your god <br>enroll the killing drama <br>let your body serve us blood <br><br>in your righteous wait for nothing <br>beyond your sight where time will tell <br>we will all be facing answers <br>when we check out the hotel <br><br>when walking for the sunrise <br>distractions gaze our way <br>running for our safety <br>won't help in any way <br>we're here as weary questions <br>in a less sophisticated show <br>and you don't know the answer <br>but one day you will know]]></content><category term="Magna Carta Cartel" label="Magna Carta Cartel"/><category term="Hotellus Eviction" label="Hotellus Eviction"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/Valiant_Visions_Dawn/</id><title>Magna Carta Cartel - Valiant Visions Dawn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:38:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:38:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/Valiant_Visions_Dawn/" title="Magna Carta Cartel - Valiant Visions Dawn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[As always I'm chasing my fears <br>Brings me wisdom to see <br>That I'm lost in the years <br>My vision holds tight <br>And nothing's regained <br>Greetings sunrise <br>And goodmorning restrained <br>I'm facing up for once and all <br>Where mirrors help the fall <br>Somewhere from the dusty clouds <br>I can hear myself call <br>In silence I find <br>That the hours won't mind <br>If the storms comes my way <br>I Have dreamt of this day <br>When embracing the truth <br>Reach the end of your will <br>Leave the cause of the fight <br>March on in to the night <br>When thinking of tomorrow <br>Reminds you of the past <br>Warn the scouts of sorrow <br>It is coming <br>And fast <br>In every stand <br>Despite your demand <br>You cannot control the turns <br>and every flame <br>The vision the same <br>Raindrops that longs to burn]]></content><category term="Magna Carta Cartel" label="Magna Carta Cartel"/><category term="Valiant Visions Dawn" label="Valiant Visions Dawn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/Deriving_A_Distance/</id><title>Magna Carta Cartel - Deriving A Distance - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:38:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:38:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/Deriving_A_Distance/" title="Magna Carta Cartel - Deriving A Distance - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Drifting fences <br>Counting thrills <br>Advancing <br>And the stairs <br>Moral seasons <br>Heaven falls <br>Cover traces <br>Distance calls <br>And in your faceless freedoms chill <br>You offer grantings for the past <br>And when your trademarks burn <br>You let us learn <br>That wisdom leads to distance <br>Dealing titles <br>Sufficiance bloom <br>What biddings <br>Bids farewell <br>Making shaping <br>Wishful mood <br>Constant <br>And of course <br>Measure pleasure <br>Facts in hand <br>Tourist vision <br>Eyes demand <br>Finders keepers <br>Blocking sole <br>Fickle fancy <br>Deny your role <br>And in you faceless freedoms chill <br>You offer grantings for the past <br>And when your trademarks burn <br>You let us learn <br>That wisdom leads to distance]]></content><category term="Magna Carta Cartel" label="Magna Carta Cartel"/><category term="Deriving A Distance" label="Deriving A Distance"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/Metropolis_Flow/</id><title>Magna Carta Cartel - Metropolis Flow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:38:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:38:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/Metropolis_Flow/" title="Magna Carta Cartel - Metropolis Flow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Mark your points by arguments <br>Distinguished by despair <br>You'll never meet your dreams while you're awake <br>Vanishing is losing trade <br>Honest means the same you trusted your convenience was fate <br>Then there's a home <br>Regarding you more <br>But there's no you <br>And confidence grows <br>Waiting for that second time <br>Concealing matters hold <br>And evening is hunting you again <br>Pass the hills of reason <br>Infected with our gold <br>Carrying solutions back to bed <br>Slowly await your turn <br>Surely, position burns <br>Then that's your home <br>Regarding you more <br>But is it true <br>Metropolis grows]]></content><category term="Magna Carta Cartel" label="Magna Carta Cartel"/><category term="Metropolis Flow" label="Metropolis Flow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/This_Time/</id><title>Magna Carta Cartel - This Time - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:38:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:38:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magna_Carta_Cartel/This_Time/" title="Magna Carta Cartel - This Time - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[With broken feathers <br>I can't fail to smile this time my escape from daylight <br>Is by far outrunned by chime's <br>I would do anything <br>But you're not here to blame and I would do anything <br>To fail to smile this time <br>With broken feathers <br>I can't fail to smile this time as i'm shaping daylight <br>I'm walking endless halls sublime <br>I would do anything to meet my guilt and shame <br>And I would do anything to fail to smile this time]]></content><category term="Magna Carta Cartel" label="Magna Carta Cartel"/><category term="This Time" label="This Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanilla_Mousse/Bye_Bye_Bye/</id><title>Vanilla Mousse - Bye Bye Bye - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:40:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:40:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanilla_Mousse/Bye_Bye_Bye/" title="Vanilla Mousse - Bye Bye Bye - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그때 우리 어렸다면 <br>그때 널 만났더라면 <br>조금 달랐을까 그럼 어땠을까 <br>또 우리 몰랐다면 <br>만나지 않았더라면 <br>정말 좋았을까 지금과는 다를까 <br>안녕 bye bye bye 대체 why why why <br>그런 lie lie 무슨 말이 더 필요해 <br>bye bye bye 대체 why why why <br>그런 lie lie 이제 그만 <br>매일매일 바쁜 시간 속에서 <br>늘 의미없는 대화 늘 반복되는 <br>똑같은 영화 카페 흔한 데이트 <br>다 지겨워져 니 맘은 어때 <br>가끔 울리는 전화에 니 번호를 보면 <br>딱히 반갑지는 않아 <br>나도 모르게 조금씩 <br>지쳐가고 있었나봐 <br>그때 우리 어렸다면 <br>그때 널 만났더라면 <br>조금 달랐을까 그럼 어땠을까 <br>또 우리 몰랐다면 만나지 않았더라면 <br>정말 좋았을까 지금과는 다를까 <br>안녕 bye bye bye 대체 why why why <br>그런 lie lie 무슨 말이 더 필요해 <br>bye bye bye 대체 why why why <br>그런 lie lie 이제 그만 <br>이미 너무 늦어버린 걸 알아 <br>되돌릴 수는 없단 걸 알아 <br>너의 행복을 빌어줄게 <br>웃으면서 널 보내줄게 <br>점점 익숙해지겠지 <br>점점 희미해지겠지 <br>시간이 지나면 후회도 하겠지 <br>혹 생각이 나겠지 <br>그래 그럴 수 있겠지 <br>하지만 추억에 묻어 지나겠지 <br>안녕 bye bye bye 대체 why why why <br>그런 lie lie 무슨 말이 더 필요해 <br>bye bye bye 대체 why why why <br>그런 lie lie 이제 그만 <br>]]></content><category term="Vanilla Mousse" label="Vanilla Mousse"/><category term="Bye Bye Bye" label="Bye Bye Bye"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/은근_슬단/집으로_가는_길/</id><title>은근 슬단 - 집으로 가는 길 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:42:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:42:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%80%EA%B7%BC_%EC%8A%AC%EB%8B%A8/%EC%A7%91%EC%9C%BC%EB%A1%9C_%EA%B0%80%EB%8A%94_%EA%B8%B8/" title="은근 슬단 - 집으로 가는 길 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[무거운 발걸음 집으로 가는 길 <br>캄캄한 거리를 나 홀로 걷는다 <br>하늘의 별들이 날 환하게 비추네 <br>어디에서부터 날 위해 비췄을까 <br>별빛 아래 멈춰 서 <br>나를 위로하는 이 시간 <br>괜찮다고 괜찮다고 이렇게 웃어본다 <br>놀이터 벤치에 멍하니 앉아서 <br>텅 빈 내 마음을 나 홀로 채운다 <br>손에 쥔 전화기 울리는 메시지 <br>언제부터일까 날 위해 울렸을까 <br>별빛 아래 멈춰 서 <br>나를 위로하는 이 시간 <br>괜찮다고 괜찮다고 이렇게 견뎌본다 <br>눈물 속에 잠겨서 전화기를 꺼내볼 때 <br>수고했다 수고했다 이렇게 웃어본다 <br>수고했다 수고했다 이렇게 웃어본다 <br>]]></content><category term="은근 슬단" label="은근 슬단"/><category term="집으로 가는 길" label="집으로 가는 길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최재관/If_I_Could_Fly/</id><title>최재관 - If I Could Fly - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:43:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:43:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9E%AC%EA%B4%80/If_I_Could_Fly/" title="최재관 - If I Could Fly - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흩어져 버려진 기억들을 떠올려 <br>너의 마음안에 닿을 수 있다면 <br>지나버린 기억들을 모두 되돌려 <br>그 시간 그자리에 머물수 있다면 <br>if I could fly I could fly <br>바람따라 날아 가면 <br>I could fly <br>오 니곁으로 날아 가면 <br>if I could fly I could fly <br>바람따라 날아 가면 oh <br>I could fly if I could fly <br>니곁으로 날아 가면 <br>니곁으로 <br>]]></content><category term="최재관" label="최재관"/><category term="If I Could Fly" label="If I Could Fly"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최재관/쓸쓸함의_차이/</id><title>최재관 - 쓸쓸함의 차이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:43:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:43:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9E%AC%EA%B4%80/%EC%93%B8%EC%93%B8%ED%95%A8%EC%9D%98_%EC%B0%A8%EC%9D%B4/" title="최재관 - 쓸쓸함의 차이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밀려오는 파도처럼 <br>커져가는 너의 모습이 <br>쓸쓸한 미련이 되어 <br>조금씩 커지는 그리움 <br>불어오는 바람 따라 <br>실려오는 너의 향기는 <br>기나긴 아쉬움 되어 <br>또다시 떠미는 발걸음 <br>아 그렇게 그대는 다가와 <br>또 그렇게 말없이 떠나네 <br>사랑 그 잔인한 기억은 <br>언제나 왜 그리도 <br>아름답게만 남는지 <br>밀려오는 파도처럼 <br>부서지는 나의 가슴이 <br>쓸쓸히 돌아보는 건 <br>아직도 그리워 그리워 <br>아 그렇게 그대는 다가와 <br>또 그렇게 말없이 떠나네 <br>사랑 그 잔인한 기억은 <br>언제나 왜 그리도 <br>아름답게만 남는지 <br>밀려오는 파도처럼 <br>부서지는 너의 가슴이 <br>쓸쓸히 돌아보는 건 <br>아직도 그리워 그리워 <br>나 나나 나나 <br>나나나 나나나 나나나 <br>나 나나 나나 <br>나나나 나나나 나나나 <br>나 나나 나나 <br>나나나 나나나 나나나 <br>나 나나 나나 <br>나나나 나나나 나나나 <br>나 나나 나나 <br>나나나 나나나 나나나 <br>]]></content><category term="최재관" label="최재관"/><category term="쓸쓸함의 차이" label="쓸쓸함의 차이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최재관/그땐_그렇게/</id><title>최재관 - 그땐 그렇게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:43:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:43:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9E%AC%EA%B4%80/%EA%B7%B8%EB%95%90_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A0%87%EA%B2%8C/" title="최재관 - 그땐 그렇게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오 내가 걸어온 이 길들을 <br>부정하고 싶진 않았소 <br>걱정하듯 얘기해주는 <br>그대들의 그 맘 다 아오 <br>한땐 그렇게 살아갈 줄 알았소 <br>같은 꿈을 꿨지만 가는 길은 달랐소 <br>한땐 그렇게 잊혀질 줄 알았소 <br>알 수는 없지만 후회 없이 걸었소 <br>오 내가 걸어온 이 길들에 <br>아파하지만은 않겠소 <br>그러다가 가끔 마주친 <br>그대들의 마음 속에서 <br>한땐 그렇게 살아갈 줄 알았소 <br>같은 꿈을 꿨지만 가는 길은 달랐소 <br>한땐 그렇게 잊혀질 줄 알았소 <br>알 수는 없지만 후회 없이 걸었소 오 <br>그땐 그렇게 살아갈 줄 알았어 <br>그땐 그렇게 잊혀질 줄 알았어 <br>그땐 그렇게 살아가고 싶었어 <br>그땐 그렇게 워우어 예이예 <br>오 내가 가야 할 길 앞에서 <br>주저앉아 있진 않겠소 <br>돌아보면 그렇게 <br>다들 살아가고 있잖소 <br>한땐 그렇게 살아갈 줄 알았소 <br>같은 꿈을 꿨지만 가는 길은 달랐소 <br>한땐 그렇게 잊혀질 줄 알았소 <br>알 수는 없지만 후회 없이 걸었소 <br>그땐 그렇게 살아갈 줄 알았어 <br>그땐 그렇게 잊혀질 줄 알았어 <br>그땐 그렇게 살아가고 싶었어 <br>그땐 그렇게 워우어 <br>그땐 그렇게 우 우 <br>그땐 그렇게 워우워 <br>그땐 그렇게 우 우 <br>그땐 그렇게 워우워 예이예 <br>]]></content><category term="최재관" label="최재관"/><category term="그땐 그렇게" label="그땐 그렇게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최재관/넌_걱정하지마/</id><title>최재관 - 넌 걱정하지마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:43:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:43:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9E%AC%EA%B4%80/%EB%84%8C_%EA%B1%B1%EC%A0%95%ED%95%98%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88/" title="최재관 - 넌 걱정하지마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[햇볕이 잘 드는 그 어떤 곳이든 <br>니 걱정 모두 다 잘 모아 두고서 <br>나를 불러줘 <br>내가 달려갈 테니 <br>불쌍한 모습에 무심해 보이고 <br>얼굴은 가끔씩 어둡게 보여도 <br>너무 걱정하지마 <br>난 괜찮을 거야 <br>언젠가 <br>마음이 설레는 날에 <br>그대는 <br>이유 없이 눈물이 흐를 테니까 <br>그대가 <br>그토록 바래고 바랬던 <br>그 모든 것 <br>그렇게 잘되게 돼있으니까 <br>오오오오 기억해 <br>그대의 위로가 되어주던 <br>우리의 음악이 멈춘대도 <br>시간이 흐르면 지나갈 테니까 <br>오오오오 기억해 <br>그대로 그렇게 내버려둬 <br>시간이 지나면 다 괜찮아 <br>이 또한 지나갈 테니까 <br>넌 걱정하지마 넌 너무 괜찮아 <br>하 하이야 <br>언젠가 <br>마음이 설레는 날에 <br>그대는 <br>이유 없이 눈물이 흐를 테니까 <br>그대가 <br>그토록 바래고 바랬던 <br>그 모든 것 <br>그렇게 잘되게 돼있으니까 <br>오오오오 기억해 <br>그대의 위로가 되어주던 <br>우리의 음악이 멈춘대도 <br>시간이 흐르면 지나갈 테니까 <br>오오오오 기억해 <br>그대로 그렇게 내버려둬 <br>시간이 지나면 다 괜찮아 <br>이 또한 지나갈 테니까 우예 <br>오오오오 기억해 <br>그대로 그렇게 내버려둬 <br>시간이 지나면 다 괜찮아 <br>이 또한 지나갈 테니까 <br>넌 걱정하지마 넌 너무 괜찮아 <br>날 걱정하지마 난 나도 괜찮아 ha ha <br>]]></content><category term="최재관" label="최재관"/><category term="넌 걱정하지마" label="넌 걱정하지마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최재관/오직한사람/</id><title>최재관 - 오직한사람 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:43:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:43:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9E%AC%EA%B4%80/%EC%98%A4%EC%A7%81%ED%95%9C%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C/" title="최재관 - 오직한사람 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오직 한 사람 내가 사랑할 단 한 사람 <br>오직 한 사람 그대 <br>우리 처음 만난 날 지금도 기억해 <br>아름다운 니 모습 <br>내 앞을 스쳐갔지 오 <br>얼마나 시간이 많이 흘렀는지 <br>우리의 만남이 <br>이렇게 빛나고 있는 걸까 <br>그땐 알 수 없었어 <br>힘겨웠던 많은 날들 <br>함께 견뎌준 그대 <br>오직 한 사람 내가 사랑할 단 한 사람 <br>오직 한 사람 그대 오직 한 사람 그대 <br>내 행복보다 그대를 더 원해 <br>이렇게 부족한 <br>내 곁에 있어준 그대기에 <br>그땐 알 수 없었어 <br>힘겨웠던 많은 날들 <br>함께 견뎌준 그대 <br>오직 한 사람 내가 사랑할 단 한 사람 <br>오직 한 사람 그대 오직 한 사람 그대 <br>우연이라도 마주칠 운명 같은 우리 <br>지금 이대로 아름답게 <br>더욱 더 사랑해 <br>오직 한 사람 날 사랑해줄 단 한 사람 <br>오직 한 사람 그대 오직 한 사람 그대 <br>오직 아아아 그대 <br>]]></content><category term="최재관" label="최재관"/><category term="오직한사람" label="오직한사람"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/권순동/내_친구야/</id><title>권순동 - 내 친구야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:45:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:45:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B6%8C%EC%88%9C%EB%8F%99/%EB%82%B4_%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC%EC%95%BC/" title="권순동 - 내 친구야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[학교 졸업 후 30 년 <br>훌쩍 흘러버린 세월에 <br>자주보고 만나진 못했어도 <br>마음속엔 항상 네 모습 <br>먹고 사는게 바쁘고 <br>때론 직장일에 시달리다가도 <br>문득 떠오른 너의 얼굴이 <br>나를 힘나게 한다 친구야 <br>우리 이제 부터라도 <br>옛날처럼 살아보자 <br>까까머리 그 시절 그모습 <br>김치하나 달랑 담긴 <br>도시락 까먹으며 <br>행복했던 그날처럼 <br>니가 있고 내가 있어 <br>세상이 두렵지 않아 <br>두 손 꼭 잡은 친구야 <br>건강하자 친구야 <br>오래살며 행복하자 <br>세상에 둘도 없는 친구야 <br>우리 이제 부터라도 <br>옛날처럼 살아보자 <br>까까머리 그 시절 그모습 <br>김치하나 달랑 담긴 <br>도시락 까먹으며 <br>행복했던 그날처럼 <br>니가 있고 내가 있어 <br>세상이 두렵지 않아 <br>두 손 꼭 잡은 친구야 <br>건강하자 친구야 <br>오래살며 행복하자 <br>세상에 둘도 없는 친구야 <br>니가 있고 내가 있어 <br>세상이 두렵지 않아 <br>두 손 꼭 잡은 친구야 <br>건강하자 친구야 <br>오래살며 행복하자 <br>세상에 둘도 없는 친구야 <br>세상에 둘도 없는 내 친구야 <br>]]></content><category term="권순동" label="권순동"/><category term="내 친구야" label="내 친구야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신해경/명왕성/</id><title>신해경 - 명왕성 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:45:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:45:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%ED%95%B4%EA%B2%BD/%EB%AA%85%EC%99%95%EC%84%B1/" title="신해경 - 명왕성 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[수 년째 밤을 헤매어도 <br>나를 품어줄 별을 찾을 순 없어 <br>나의 행성을 떠나려고 해도 <br>어떤 슬픔이 내게 허락지 않아 <br>몇 번째 내게 되물어도 <br>난 나에게 떠날 수는 없어 <br>너의 행성이 내게 충돌해도 <br>나의 슬픔이 다시 원하지 않아 <br>아주 오랜 날 그대가 <br>나를 떠날 때 그댈 잃을 때 <br>나를 떠난 그대가 보여 <br>나를 떠난 그대가 보여 <br>내가 보낸 그대가 보여 <br>내가 보낸 그대가 보여 <br>수 년째 밤을 헤매어도 <br>나를 품어줄 별을 찾을 순 없어 <br>나의 행성을 떠나려고 해도 <br>어떤 슬픔이 내게 허락지 않아 <br>나를 돌아봐 그대야 <br>나는 떠날게 그댈 안을래 <br>아 <br>그댄 어디 아주 멀리 있어요 <br>그댄 내게 언젠가 다시 봐요 <br>그대와 나 우주를 유영해 <br>서로 미워질 때까지 그때까지 <br>그때까지 <br>나를 떠난 그대가 보여 <br>나를 떠난 그대가 보여 <br>내가 보낸 그대가 보여 <br>내가 보낸 그대가 보여 <br>나를 떠난 그대가 보여 <br>나를 떠난 그대가 보여 <br>내가 보낸 그대가 보여 <br>내가 보낸 그대가 보여 <br>나를 떠난 그대가 보여 <br>나를 떠난 그대가 보여 <br>내가 보낸 그대가 보여 <br>내가 보낸 그대가 보여 <br>]]></content><category term="신해경" label="신해경"/><category term="명왕성" label="명왕성"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/필굿_FEELGOOD/복잡미묘_Prod_by_HotSauce/</id><title>필굿 (FEELGOOD) - 복잡미묘 (Prod by HotSauce) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:45:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:45:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%84%EA%B5%BF_FEELGOOD/%EB%B3%B5%EC%9E%A1%EB%AF%B8%EB%AC%98_Prod_by_HotSauce/" title="필굿 (FEELGOOD) - 복잡미묘 (Prod by HotSauce) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[복잡미묘해 <br>새로워지네 <br>복잡미묘해 <br>새로워지네 <br>복잡미묘해 <br>새로워지네 <br>너무 달달해 달짝해 <br>괜찮은 기분 드네 <br>벅차게 완벽히 완전해진 <br>미소를 귀에 <br>걸어 네 곁에 있을 때마다 <br>걸어 한강 어디든 말야 <br>못된 아이 따뜻하게 <br>더 안아줘 <br>많은 별들 한품 가득 <br>안겨줘 <br>내 전부를 세게 안아줘 <br>빛난 것들을 보게 해줘 <br>이런 감정에 젖어 드는 게 <br>살아 왔던 내 방식도 <br>살아갈 내 방향들도 <br>I’ll give you my all my time <br>is for you is for you <br>복잡미묘해 <br>새로워지네 <br>이런 설렘에 젖어 드는 게 <br>복잡미묘해 <br>새로워지네 <br>너란 미로 빠져드는 내가 <br>이런 거 저런 거 <br>재기 전에 뭐 어떤걸 <br>더 해줄까 <br>고민이 앞서 <br>좀 낯서네 솔직히 <br>변한 내 모습이 좀 <br>솔직히 나 어색해 <br>굉장히 낯선 상황이지만 <br>또 뭐 <br>혼자 끙끙 앓고 있기에는 <br>버텨내지를 못해 <br>왜에 왜에 <br>이 순간만을 <br>기다렸단 말은 <br>뻥이지만 <br>왜에 왜에 <br>네 눈가에 고인 <br>고민들의 외침을 들어 난 <br>지켜주고 싶단 말을 <br>뻔히 돌려 말을 하지 난 <br>가장 잘 알고 있으면서 넌 <br>왜에 왜에 <br>기가 차게도 내가 왜 <br>이렇게 빠져있는 건데 왜 <br>첫눈에 진짜 반해버렸어 <br>왜에 왜에 <br>where u at 어디에 있던 <br>널 위해 걸어갈게 always <br>바칠게 <br>이런 감정에 젖어 드는 게 <br>살아 왔던 내 방식도 <br>살아갈 내 방향들도 <br>I’ll give you my all my time <br>is for you is for you <br>복잡미묘해 <br>새로워지네 <br>이런 설렘에 젖어 드는 게 <br>복잡미묘해 <br>새로워지네 <br>너란 미로 빠져드는 내가 <br>]]></content><category term="필굿 (FEELGOOD)" label="필굿 (FEELGOOD)"/><category term="복잡미묘 (Prod by HotSauce)" label="복잡미묘 (Prod by HotSauce)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/버니걸스/여보당신우리자기내사랑/</id><title>버니걸스 - 여보당신우리자기내사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:46:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:46:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B2%84%EB%8B%88%EA%B1%B8%EC%8A%A4/%EC%97%AC%EB%B3%B4%EB%8B%B9%EC%8B%A0%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EC%9E%90%EA%B8%B0%EB%82%B4%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="버니걸스 - 여보당신우리자기내사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[턴 잇 업 스윙 <br>여보 당신 우리 자기 <br>여보 당신 우리 자기 <br>여보 당신 우리자기 내 사랑 <br>내 곁에 있어줘요 내 사랑 <br>나만을 바라봐요 오 마이 달링 <br>무지하게 사랑해요 허니 <br>여보 당신 우리 자기 내 사랑 <br>언제나 예스 뭐든지 패스 <br>우리의 사랑은 완벽한 댄스 <br>똑 소리 나게 어려운 일도 <br>힘겨운 일도 <br>척척척 알아서 해결 해줘요 <br>눈물이 나게 내 머릿속을 <br>내 마음속을 <br>어쩜 그리 다 아나요 <br>오오 그대만 있어 준다면 <br>내 곁에 있어 준다면 <br>이 세상 그 어떤 시련이 와도 <br>내 사랑 <br>주저하지 않아요 <br>오오 그대만 있어 준다면 <br>내 곁에 있어 준다면 <br>영원토록 행복할거야 허니 <br>여보 당신 우리 자기 내 사랑 <br>영원히 달링 베베 <br>사랑해 허니 베베 <br>이대로 영원히 내 곁에 머물러줘 <br>i love you so much <br>내 곁에 있어줘요 내 사랑 <br>나만을 바라봐요 오 마이 달링 <br>무지하게 사랑해요 허니 <br>여보 당신 우리 자기 내 사랑 <br>언제나 콜 뭐든지 쿨 <br>우리의 사랑은 달콤한 꿀 <br>똑 소리 나게 어려운 일도 <br>힘겨운 일도 <br>척척척 알아서 해결 해줘요 <br>눈물이 나게 내 머릿속을 <br>내 마음속을 <br>어쩜 그리 다 아나요 <br>오오 그대만 있어 준다면 <br>내 곁에 있어 준다면 <br>이 세상 그 어떤 시련이 와도 <br>내 사랑 <br>주저하지 않아요 <br>오오 그대만 있어 준다면 <br>내 곁에 있어 준다면 <br>영원토록 행복할거야 허니 <br>여보 당신 우리 자기 내 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="버니걸스" label="버니걸스"/><category term="여보당신우리자기내사랑" label="여보당신우리자기내사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/알파벳/기도/</id><title>알파벳 - 기도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:46:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:46:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%8C%ED%8C%8C%EB%B2%B3/%EA%B8%B0%EB%8F%84/" title="알파벳 - 기도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무리 널 지우려고 <br>애를 써 봐도 다 쓸데가 없어 <br>그럴수록 자꾸 얼어붙어 버려 <br>내 심장이 <br>please don't go <br>태어나서 너만큼 사랑한 사람 없어 <br>이 까짓 사랑땜에 죽을 듯이 나 아퍼 <br>꿈 속에서라도 꼭 너를 만나려고 또 <br>악몽을 참아내 오늘도 tonight <br>if you go away 단 하루도 <br>버티지 못해 워어 다시 나를 안아줘 <br>내 영혼까지 다 맡길게 <br>if you were not so far away <br>네 손을 내밀어 나를 구원해줘 <br>if you were not so far away <br>악몽 같은 생에 한줄기 <br>너란 빛을 내려줘 <br>baby 간절한 나에 기도 <br>간절한 나에 기도 저 하늘에 닿기를 <br>baby 간절한 나에 기도 <br>간절한 나에 기도 기도 기도 <br>oh baby 알잖아 너 없이 <br>일분일초도 숨 쉴 수가 없어 <br>oh baby 차라리 널 만나지 않은 <br>그 시간으로 날 돌려줘 <br>if you go away 단 하루도 <br>버티지 못해 워어 다시 나를 안아줘 <br>내 영혼까지 다 맡길게 <br>if you were not so far away <br>네 손을 내밀어 나를 구원해줘 <br>if you were not so far away <br>악몽 같은 생에 한줄기 <br>너란 빛을 내려줘 <br>baby 간절한 나에 기도 <br>간절한 나에 기도 저 하늘에 닿기를 <br>baby 간절한 나에 기도 <br>간절한 나에 기도 기도 기도 <br>가슴속에 빗물처럼 계속해서 흐르는 <br>너의 빈자리 커져 <br>아무리 발버둥 쳐봐도 우워 <br>그래 널 따라 이젠 떠나고 싶어 <br>상처를 받아들이기엔 힘들어 <br>제발 이렇게는 떠나가지마 기도할게 <br>if you were not so far away <br>네 손을 내밀어 나를 구원해줘 <br>if you were not so far away <br>악몽 같은 생에 한줄기 <br>너란 빛을 내려줘 <br>baby 간절한 나에 기도 <br>간절한 나에 기도 저 하늘에 닿기를 <br>baby 간절한 나에 기도 <br>간절한 나에 기도 기도 기도 <br>]]></content><category term="알파벳" label="알파벳"/><category term="기도" label="기도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/알파벳/원해/</id><title>알파벳 - 원해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:46:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:46:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%8C%ED%8C%8C%EB%B2%B3/%EC%9B%90%ED%95%B4/" title="알파벳 - 원해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[wanna get your love <br>let me show you love <br>wanna get your love <br>love love love love love <br>let's talk 촉이 왔어 baby <br>just falling love <br>첫눈에 감이 와 널 바래 <br>마주친 네 눈빛에 달콤한 향기에 <br>수줍은 너의 미소에 숨이 멎을 것 같아 <br>끼 부리지마 그래 너 예쁜 거 알아 <br>한눈 팔지마 이제는 널 갖겠어 <br>그 어느 누구도 <br>너를 대신 할 수 없어 baby <br>무조건 나에겐 너니깐 lady <br>원해 get your love <br>yeah 원해 원해 yeah <br>yeah 원해 원해 널 <br>원해 get your love <br>yeah 원해 원해 yeah <br>yeah 원해 only one <br>원해 get your love <br>woo 망설 이지마 <br>let me see your love <br>let me show you love <br>항상 기댈 수 있게 널 지킬 수 있게 <br>네 마음을 채울 수 있게 <br>니 남자가 돼 줄게 <br>오해 하지마 장난 하는 거 아냐 <br>쉽게 보지마 널 사랑한단 말야 <br>그 어느 누구도 <br>너를 대신 할 수 없어 baby <br>무조건 나에겐 너니깐 lady <br>원해 get your love <br>yeah 원해 원해 yeah <br>yeah 원해 원해 널 <br>원해 get your love <br>yeah 원해 원해 yeah <br>yeah 원해 only one <br>원해 get your love <br>온통 네 생각에 <br>꿈속에서도 너만을 찾아 헤매이내 <br>왔다 갔다 하지마 이제 come on <br>내게 와 <br>지금부터 날 믿고 따라와줘 baby <br>yeah 원해 원해 yeah <br>yeah 원해 원해 널 <br>원해 get your love <br>yeah 원해 원해 yeah <br>yeah 원해 only one <br>원해 get your love <br>love love love love love <br>yeah 원해 원해 널 <br>원해 get your love <br>love love love love love <br>yeah 원해 only one <br>원해 get you love <br>]]></content><category term="알파벳" label="알파벳"/><category term="원해" label="원해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김나영/그럴걸/</id><title>김나영 - 그럴걸 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:46:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:46:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%82%98%EC%98%81/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%B4%EA%B1%B8/" title="김나영 - 그럴걸 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[스스로 바보가 된 나를 <br>설명할 방법이 없어 <br>넌 아직은 봄이라면 <br>난 어느새 겨울 끝에 왔어 혼자서 <br>꼬집어 말할 수가 없는 <br>달라진 마음의 모양 <br>날 도무지 모른다는 <br>넌 이미 내 곁을 멀어진 사람 <br>그게 너무 아파 <br>숨이 차면 너의 손을 잡을걸 <br>불안하면 그냥 울어버릴걸 <br>다시는 볼 수 없는 <br>처음 너의 그 미소 <br>그걸 난 보지 않을 걸 그랬어 <br>괜히 그랬어 <br>조각나버린 시간들을 <br>되돌릴 방법이 없어 <br>넌 이제와 듣고 싶은 <br>난 어느새 닫아버린 얘기들 <br>그게 너무 아파 <br>숨이 차면 너의 손을 잡을걸 <br>불안하면 그냥 울어버릴걸 <br>다시는 볼 수 없는 <br>처음 너의 그 미소 <br>그걸 난 그때 보지 않았다면 <br>화를 내면 초라해지는 내가 <br>그럴수록 멀어져 가는 네가 <br>다시는 올 수 없는 <br>처음 그 설레임들 <br>그걸 난 믿지 않을 걸 그랬어 <br>숨이 차면 너의 손을 잡을걸 <br>불안하면 그냥 울어버릴걸 <br>다시는 볼 수 없는 <br>처음 너의 그 미소 <br>그걸 난 보지 않을 걸 그랬어 <br>괜히 그랬어 <br>]]></content><category term="김나영" label="김나영"/><category term="그럴걸" label="그럴걸"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Opposites_2/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Opposites 2 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:46:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:46:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Opposites_2/" title="핑크퐁 - Opposites 2 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Opposites! <br>Short and tall. Short and tall. <br>In and out. In and out. <br>Heavy and light. Heavy and light. <br>Weak and strong. Weak and strong. <br>There are a lot of opposites. <br>Let’s sing together you and me. <br>OOOOOOOO! Opposites! <br>Short and tall. <br>In and out. <br>Heavy and light. <br>Weak and strong. <br>There are a lot of opposites. <br>Let’s sing together you and me . <br>OOOOOOOO! Opposites]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Opposites 2" label="Opposites 2"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/My_House/</id><title>핑크퐁 - My House - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:46:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:46:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/My_House/" title="핑크퐁 - My House - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey! Did you see my dad? <br>Roomba roomba roomba roomba. Roomba roomba ba! <br>Sister’s watching TV in the living room. <br>Mommy’s reading a book in the bedroom. <br>Brother’s taking a shower in the bathroom. <br>Daddy’s cooking dinner in the kitchen. <br>Living room. Bedroom and bathroom and kitchen <br>Roomba roomba roomba roomba. Welcome to my house! <br>Living room. Bedroom and bathroom and kitchen. Roomba roomba roomba roomba. <br>Roomba roomba! Roomba roomba! <br>Welcome to my house! <br>Yeah!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="My House" label="My House"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Vegetables/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Vegetables - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:46:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:46:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Vegetables/" title="핑크퐁 - Vegetables - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Veggie! Veggie! <br>Vegetables! <br>I love carrot. Carrot! <br>I love lettuce. Lettuce! <br>I love cucumber. Cucumber! <br>You know what I mean? <br>One two three four! <br>Let me tell you! <br>I love onion. Onion! <br>I love beans. Beans! <br>I love tomato. Tomato! <br>I love vegetables. <br>It’s delicious! <br>Veggie veggie vegetables! Veggie veggie vegetables! <br>Vegetables are everywhere. Let’s have some vegetables. <br>It’s delicious! <br>Carrot! Lettuce! Cucumber! Onion! Beans! Tomato! <br>Vegetables are everywhere. Let’s have some vegetables. <br>Vegetables]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Vegetables" label="Vegetables"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Nature/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Nature - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:46:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:46:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Nature/" title="핑크퐁 - Nature - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Up in the mountain. <br>Down by the river. <br>High up in the sky. <br>Tra la la la la la la <br>Flowers. Flowers. <br>Flowers and trees are loved by the bees. <br>Flowers. Flowers. <br>Flowers and trees and the bees. Tra la la la la la <br>Up in the mountain. <br>Down by the river. <br>High up in the sky. <br>Tra la la la la la la <br>Blue birds. Blue birds. <br>Birds and butterflies they all love the sky. <br>Blue birds. Blue birds. <br>Birds and butterflies in the sky. Tra la la la la la]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Nature" label="Nature"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Seasons/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Seasons - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:46:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:46:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Seasons/" title="핑크퐁 - Seasons - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Winter, spring, summer and fall. <br>Winter, spring, summer and fall. <br>Winter, spring, summer and fall. <br>Winter, spring, summer and fall. <br>Winter! <br>White snowflake’s falling down. <br>Spring! <br>There’re flowers all around. <br>Summer! <br>Let’s go to the sea, sea, sea! <br>Fall! <br>Leaves are tumbling down. Go go go! <br>Winter, spring, summer and fall. <br>Winter, spring, summer and fall. <br>Winter, spring, summer and fall. <br>Winter, spring, summer and fall. <br>One year, four seasons in all]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Seasons" label="Seasons"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/On_In_By_Under/</id><title>핑크퐁 - On In By Under - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:46:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:46:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/On_In_By_Under/" title="핑크퐁 - On In By Under - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[On In By Under <br>On In By Under <br>Oops. I lost my cats. <br>Did you see my cats? <br>Meow. On the tree. <br>Meow. In the box. <br>Meow. By the chair. <br>Under the table. <br>Oh, there you are! <br>Oops. I lost my cats. <br>Did you see my cats? <br>Meow. On the tree. <br>Meow. In the box. <br>Meow. By the chair. <br>Boo! Under the table. <br>On In By Under <br>On In By Under]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="On In By Under" label="On In By Under"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Jobs/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Jobs - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:46:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:46:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Jobs/" title="핑크퐁 - Jobs - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Firefighter. Soccer player. Teacher. Doctor. Painter. Chef. <br>Police officer. Astronaut. What do you want to be? <br>What do you want to be? <br>I want to be a teacher. <br>Let’s learn something fun. <br>I want to be a soccer player. <br>Let’s shoot the ball. <br>How about you? <br>I want to be a doctor. <br>I will make you get better. <br>I want to be a firefighter. <br>I will save you, wait! <br>Firefighter. Soccer player. Teacher. Doctor. Painter. Chef. <br>Police officer. Astronaut. What do you want to be? <br>What, what, what, what do you want to be]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Jobs" label="Jobs"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/My_Body/</id><title>핑크퐁 - My Body - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:46:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:46:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/My_Body/" title="핑크퐁 - My Body - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Move your hands! Hands hands <br>Move your arms! Arms arms <br>Move your feet! Feet feet <br>Move your legs! Legs legs <br>Clap your hands. Hands! <br>Clap your hands. Hands! <br>Listen to the music and clap your hands. <br>Move your arms. Arms! <br>Move your arms. Arms! <br>Listen to the music and Move your arms. <br>Move your body! <br>Here we go! <br>Stomp your feet. Feet! <br>Stomp your feet. Feet! <br>Listen to the music and stomp your feet. <br>Move your legs. Legs! <br>Move your legs. Legs! <br>Listen to the music and move your legs. <br>Hands and arms. Feet and legs. It’s me]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="My Body" label="My Body"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Cook/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Cook - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Cook/" title="핑크퐁 - Cook - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to my kitchen. <br>We are going to make a pancake. <br>Now, everybody! <br>Put the milk. Put! Put the milk! <br>Put the eggs. Put! Put the eggs! <br>Put the butter! Put! Put the butter! <br>“Oh! What’s missing? Ah-ha!” <br>Put the flour. Put! Put the flour! <br>Roll the pancake! Roll! Roll the pancake! <br>Now, wait! Now, wait! Now, wait! <br>“Um, smells good!” <br>“Wow!” <br>And everybody! <br>Eat the pancake. Eat! Eat the pancake! <br>Eat the pancake. Eat! Eat the pancake! <br>Yeah!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Cook" label="Cook"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Toy/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Toy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Toy/" title="핑크퐁 - Toy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bob bob bob. <br>Open the box, box. <br>Bob bob bob. <br>Open the box, box. <br>What, what’s in the box? in the box? What? What? <br>What, what’s in the box? in the box? What? What? <br>A doll. A ball. A robot. Blocks. Crayons. A truck! <br>A doll and a ball. A robot and a truck. <br>Blocks and crayons in the box. In the box! <br>A doll and a ball. A robot and a truck. <br>Blocks and crayons in the box. In the box! <br>Toy-oy-oy-oys are in the box. In the box! <br>Bob bob bob. Open the box, box. <br>Bob bob bob. Open the box, box. <br>Box]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Toy" label="Toy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Clothes/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Clothes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Clothes/" title="핑크퐁 - Clothes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ladies and gentleman! <br>It’s magic clothes show time. <br>Hey! Are you Ready? <br>Put on a magic shirt, then you can do this! <br>Shirt shirtie shirtie shirt. Shirtie shirtie shirt! Shirt! <br>Put on magic pants, then you can do this! <br>Pant pantie pantie pants. Pantie pantie pants! Pants! <br>Put on magic shoes, then you can do this! <br>Shoe shobie shobie shoes. Shobie shobie shoes! Shoes! <br>Oh, yeah! Round 2. <br>Hey! Here we go! <br>Put on magic gloves, then you can do this! <br>Glove glovie glovie gloves. Glovie glovie gloves! Gloves! <br>Put on a magic cap, then you can do this! <br>Cap capie capie cap. Capie capie cap! Cap! <br>Shirt! Pants! Shoes! Gloves! Cap! <br>Thank you. Thank you!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Clothes" label="Clothes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Colors/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Colors - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Colors/" title="핑크퐁 - Colors - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ting ting! Ting ting! <br>Tang tang! Tang tang! <br>Ten fat sausages! Go go go! <br>Ten fat sausages, sizzling in a pan. <br>The blue one goes ‘pop!’. <br>The red one goes ‘bang!’. <br>Blue Red Yellow <br>Green Purple Navy Brown <br>Pink Gray Orange <br>Ten fat sausages <br>Ten fat sausages, sizzling in a pan. <br>The yellow one goes ‘pop!’. <br>The green one goes ‘bang!’. <br>Blue Red Yellow <br>Green Purple Navy Brown <br>Pink Gray Orange <br>Sizzling in a pan. <br>Sizzling in a pan. <br>Sizzling in a pan. <br>Sizzling in a pan]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Colors" label="Colors"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/공주님이_되고_싶어/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 공주님이 되고 싶어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EA%B3%B5%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%B4_%EB%90%98%EA%B3%A0_%EC%8B%B6%EC%96%B4/" title="핑크퐁 - 공주님이 되고 싶어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쥬쥬쥬 <br>“츄!” <br>공주 공주님 <br>쥬쥬쥬 <br>“츄!” <br>공주 공주님 <br>쥬쥬쥬 <br>“츄!” <br>공주 공주님 <br>세상에서 제일 빛나는 공주님 <br>일곱 난쟁이와 백설공주 <br>“하이호!” <br>길고 긴 머릿결 라푼젤 <br>“랄랄라” <br>바닷속 인어공주 <br>잠자는 숲 속 공주 <br>아름다운 동화 속 공주님 <br>쥬쥬쥬 <br>“츄!” <br>공주 공주님 <br>쥬쥬쥬 <br>“츄!” <br>공주 공주님 <br>쥬쥬쥬 <br>“츄!” <br>공주 공주님 <br>세상에서 제일 빛나는 공주님]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="공주님이 되고 싶어" label="공주님이 되고 싶어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/공주송/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 공주송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EA%B3%B5%EC%A3%BC%EC%86%A1/" title="핑크퐁 - 공주송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쥬쥬쥬 <br>“츄!” <br>공주 공주님 <br>쥬쥬쥬 <br>“츄!” <br>공주 공주님 <br>쥬쥬쥬 <br>“츄!” <br>공주 공주님 <br>세상에서 제일 빛나는 공주님 <br>일곱 난쟁이와 백설공주 <br>“하이호!” <br>길고 긴 머릿결 라푼젤 <br>“랄랄라” <br>바닷속 인어공주 <br>잠자는 숲 속 공주 <br>아름다운 동화 속 공주님 <br>쥬쥬쥬 <br>“츄!” <br>공주 공주님 <br>쥬쥬쥬 <br>“츄!” <br>공주 공주님 <br>쥬쥬쥬 <br>“츄!” <br>공주 공주님 <br>세상에서 제일 빛나는 공주님]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="공주송" label="공주송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/라푼젤/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 라푼젤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%9D%BC%ED%91%BC%EC%A0%A4/" title="핑크퐁 - 라푼젤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[라라 라라 라푼젤 라 <br>라라 라라 라푼젤 라 <br>라라 라푼젤 <br>머리를 내려다오 <br>라라 라푼젤 <br>머리를 내려다오 <br>높은 탑에 갇혀서 꼼짝 못하지 <br>다른 그 누구도 못 올라가지 <br>라라 라라 라푼젤 라 <br>라라 라라 라푼젤 라 <br>라라 라푼젤 <br>머리를 내려다오 <br>라라 라푼젤 <br>머리를 내려다오 <br>왕자님이 첫눈에 반해버렸네 <br>공주님을 구하러 올라간다네 <br>라라 라푼젤 <br>머리를 내려다오 <br>라라 라푼젤 <br>머리를 내려다오 <br>라라 라라 라푼젤 라 <br>라라 라푼젤 라]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="라푼젤" label="라푼젤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/미녀와_야수/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 미녀와 야수 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%AF%B8%EB%85%80%EC%99%80_%EC%95%BC%EC%88%98/" title="핑크퐁 - 미녀와 야수 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[두비두비 두비두비 두비 두 <br>두비두비 두비두비 두비 두 <br>야수는 벨을 사랑해 <br>야수는 벨을 사랑해 <br>마법에 걸려 변한 내 모습 <br>벨이 날 사랑해줄까 <br>벨도 야수를 사랑해 <br>벨도 야수를 사랑해 <br>다정한 야수 마음이 보여요 <br>더이상 무섭지 않아 <br>나의 예쁜 공주님 <br>나의 멋진 왕자님 <br>우리 서로 사랑해 <br>우리 서로 사랑해 <br>두비두비 두비두비 두비 두]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="미녀와 야수" label="미녀와 야수"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/잠자는_숲_속의_공주/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 잠자는 숲 속의 공주 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EC%9E%A0%EC%9E%90%EB%8A%94_%EC%88%B2_%EC%86%8D%EC%9D%98_%EA%B3%B5%EC%A3%BC/" title="핑크퐁 - 잠자는 숲 속의 공주 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쿨쿨쿨 쿨쿨쿨 <br>쿨쿨쿨 쿨쿨쿨 <br>잠자는 숲 속의 공주님 <br>쿨쿨쿨 쿨쿨쿨 <br>쿨쿨쿨 쿨쿨쿨 <br>누가 와서 깨울까 <br>심술쟁이 요정이 나타나 <br>마법을 걸었네 <br>숲 속의 공주님 <br>깊고 깊은 잠에 빠졌네 <br>그러던 어느날 <br>용감한 왕자님이 나타나 <br>공주의 입술에 뽀뽀하니 <br>저주 풀렸네 <br>쿨쿨쿨 쿨쿨쿨 <br>쿨쿨쿨 쿨쿨쿨 <br>잠자는 숲 속의 공주님 <br>쿨쿨쿨 쿨쿨쿨 <br>쿨쿨쿨 쿨쿨쿨 <br>누가 와서 깨울까 <br>사랑해요 사랑해요 사랑해요 <br>내 사랑 공주님 <br>사랑해요 사랑해요 사랑해요 <br>내 사랑 왕자님]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="잠자는 숲 속의 공주" label="잠자는 숲 속의 공주"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/인어공주/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 인어공주 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EC%9D%B8%EC%96%B4%EA%B3%B5%EC%A3%BC/" title="핑크퐁 - 인어공주 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 모두 함께 노래해 <br>우리 모두 함께 노래해 <br>우리 모두 함께 춤을 춰 <br>우리 모두 함께 춤을 춰 <br>깊고 깊은 <br>깊고 깊은 <br>푸른 바닷속 <br>푸른 바닷속 <br>인어공주가 <br>인어공주가 <br>살고 있어요 <br>살고 있어요 <br>저 바다 아래 <br>아래 <br>저 바다 아래 <br>아래 <br>바닷속 친구들 <br>모두 모두 모여 <br>모두 모여 <br>저 바다 아래 <br>아래 <br>저 바다 아래 <br>아래 <br>인어공주와 노래해요 <br>랄랄랄라 <br>그런 어느날 <br>그런 어느날 <br>인어공주 <br>인어공주 <br>바깥 세상이 <br>바깥 세상이 <br>궁금했죠 <br>궁금했죠 <br>저 바다 넘어 <br>넘어 <br>저 바다 넘어 <br>넘어 <br>저 바다 넘어 뭐가 있을까 <br>뭐가 있을까 <br>저 바다 넘어 <br>넘어 <br>저 바다 넘어 <br>넘어 <br>멋진 왕자님 만나고 싶어요 <br>랄랄랄라 <br>저 바다 아래 <br>아래 <br>저 바다 아래 <br>아래 <br>바닷속 친구들 <br>모두 모두 모여 <br>모두 모여 <br>저 바다 아래 <br>아래 <br>저 바다 아래 <br>아래 <br>인어공주와 노래해요 <br>랄랄랄라 <br>인어공주와 노래해요 <br>랄랄랄라]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="인어공주" label="인어공주"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/신데렐라/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 신데렐라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EC%8B%A0%EB%8D%B0%EB%A0%90%EB%9D%BC/" title="핑크퐁 - 신데렐라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[링동 링어링동 <br>링동 링어링동 <br>링동 링어링동 <br>라라 신데렐라 <br>오 가엾은 신데렐라 <br>무도회에 가고 싶어요 <br>요정이 나타나서 <br>주문을 외워요 <br>“비비디 바비디 부!” <br>호박은 마차로 <br>생쥐는 백마로 <br>도마뱀은 마부로 <br>새하얀 드레스 유리구두까지 <br>공주가 되었네 <br>링동 링어링동 <br>링동 링어링동 <br>링동 링어링동 <br>라라 신데렐라 <br>링동 링어링동 <br>링동 링어링동 <br>열두 시가 되면은 <br>마법이 풀리네 <br>마법이 풀리네 <br>마법이 풀리네 <br>“어머!”]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="신데렐라" label="신데렐라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/백설공주/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 백설공주 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%B0%B1%EC%84%A4%EA%B3%B5%EC%A3%BC/" title="핑크퐁 - 백설공주 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하이호 하이호 <br>하이호 하이호 <br>하이야이야이야 하이호 <br>하이호 하이호 <br>하이호 하이호 <br>사랑해요 공주님 <br>백설공주 백설공주 <br>세상에서 제일 예쁘지 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 <br>다섯 여섯 일곱 <br>난쟁이와 살고 있어요 <br>하이호 하이호 <br>하이호 하이호 <br>하이야이야이야 하이호 <br>하이호 하이호 <br>하이호 하이호 <br>사랑해요 공주님 <br>백설공주 백설공주 <br>독사과를 먹었어요 <br>왕비가 질투해 <br>왕비가 질투해 <br>깊은 잠에 빠졌어요 <br>“ 공주님!” <br>하이호 하이호 <br>하이호 하이호 <br>하이야이야이야 하이호 <br>하이호 하이호 <br>하이호 하이호 <br>일어나요 공주님 <br>일어나요 공주님 <br>하이호]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="백설공주" label="백설공주"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/응가송/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 응가송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EC%9D%91%EA%B0%80%EC%86%A1/" title="핑크퐁 - 응가송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[빵 빵 <br>뽕 뽕 <br>뿡뿡뿡뿡 <br>응차 응차 <br>빵 빵 <br>뽕 뽕 <br>뿡뿡뿡뿡 <br>응차 응차 <br>“ 응가 할 시간이야!” <br>방귀가 뿡뿡 <br>방귀가 뿡뿡 <br>똥꼬가 움찔 <br>똥꼬가 움찔 <br>나왔나? <br>아직! <br>나왔나? <br>아직! <br>응차응차 응차응차 <br>“응!” <br>와라 와라 나왔다! <br>“잘했어!” <br>빵 빵 <br>뽕 뽕 <br>뿡뿡뿡뿡 <br>응차 응차 <br>빵 빵 <br>뽕 뽕 <br>뿡뿡뿡뿡 <br>응차 응차 <br>“ 응가 할 시간이야!” <br>방귀가 뿡뿡 <br>방귀가 뿡뿡 <br>똥꼬가 움찔 <br>똥꼬가 움찔 <br>나왔나? <br>아직! <br>나왔나? <br>아직! <br>응차응차 응차응차 <br>“응!” <br>와라 와라 나왔다! <br>“잘했어!” <br>빵 빵 <br>뽕 뽕 <br>뿡뿡뿡뿡 <br>응차 응차 <br>빠빠 빵빵 뿌뿌 뿡 <br>응차 응차 예!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="응가송" label="응가송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/까꿍_놀이/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 까꿍 놀이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EA%B9%8C%EA%BF%8D_%EB%86%80%EC%9D%B4/" title="핑크퐁 - 까꿍 놀이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[도리도리 까꿍 <br>도리도리 까꿍 <br>도리도리 도리도리 <br>까꿍 <br>병아리도 눈 가리고 <br>까꿍 까꿍 <br>돼지도 눈 가리고 <br>까꿍 까꿍 <br>귀여운 토끼가 어디 숨었나 <br>까꿍! <br>우리 모두 다 같이 도리도리 까꿍 <br>불가사리 눈 가리고 <br>까꿍 까꿍 <br>문어도 눈 가리고 <br>까꿍 까꿍 <br>귀여운 돌고래 어디 숨었나 <br>까꿍! <br>우리 모두 다 같이 도리도리 까꿍 <br>아빠도 눈 가리고 <br>까꿍 까꿍 <br>엄마도 눈 가리고 <br>까꿍 까꿍 <br>귀여운 우리 아기 어디 숨었나 <br>까꿍! <br>우리 모두 다 같이 도리도리 까꿍]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="까꿍 놀이" label="까꿍 놀이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/잘_준비송/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 잘 준비송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EC%9E%98_%EC%A4%80%EB%B9%84%EC%86%A1/" title="핑크퐁 - 잘 준비송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나 둘 하나 둘 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 <br>목욕하고 잠옷 입고 <br>이를 닦고 준비 끝 <br>별님이 반짝 까만 밤이 되면 <br>하나씩 해봐요 어렵지 않아 <br>모두 모두가 잠을 잘 시간 <br>별님 달님 쿨쿨 <br>엄마 아빠 쿨쿨 <br>나도 쿨쿨 잘 시간이야 <br>다 함께 <br>구석구석 목욕해요 <br>혼자서도 입을 수 있죠 <br>치카치카 이 닦아요 <br>모두가 잠을 잘 시간 <br>하나 둘 하나 둘 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 <br>목욕하고 잠옷 입고 <br>이를 닦고 준비 끝 <br>하나 둘 하나 둘 <br>하나 둘 하나 둘 <br>목욕하고 잠옷 입고 <br>이를 닦고 준비 끝]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="잘 준비송" label="잘 준비송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/이_닦기/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 이 닦기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EC%9D%B4_%EB%8B%A6%EA%B8%B0/" title="핑크퐁 - 이 닦기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[“이 닦을 시간이야!” <br>“치카하자!” <br>치카하자 치카하자 <br>구석구석 깨끗하게 <br>치카하자 치카하자 <br>반짝반짝 예쁜 이 <br>치타랑 치카하자 치 <br>치타는 이 닦을 때 치치치 <br>치! 치카하자 <br>코끼리랑 치카하자 카 <br>코끼리는 이 닦을 때 카카카 <br>카! 치카하자 <br>하마랑 치카하자 하 <br>하마는 이 닦을 때 하하하 <br>하! 치카하자 <br>나도 같이 치카하자 아 <br>나는야 이 닦을 때 아아아 <br>우리 아가, 아! <br>아! 치카하자 <br>치카하자 치카하자 <br>구석구석 깨끗하게 <br>치카하자 치카하자 <br>반짝반짝 예쁜 이 <br>치카하자 치카하자 <br>치카치카 치카하자 <br>치카치카 치카치카 <br>치카치카 치카 <br>“와, 내 이 좀 봐!” <br>반짝반짝 예쁜 이]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="이 닦기" label="이 닦기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/샴푸송/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 샴푸송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EC%83%B4%ED%91%B8%EC%86%A1/" title="핑크퐁 - 샴푸송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[“ 와, 샴푸 하자!” <br>“좋아! 좋아!” <br>샤와샤와샤와 샴푸를 바르고 <br>보글보글보글 거품을 만들어 <br>모두 함께 즐거운 샴푸 시간 <br>머리가 대변신 <br>샴푸! <br>샴푸 샴푸 샴푸 시간 <br>샴푸 샴푸 구석구석 <br>푸푸 푸푸 푸푸 푸푸 <br>모두 함께 샴푸 <br>샤와샤와샤와 샴푸를 바르고 <br>주룩주룩 주룩 거품이 주루룩 <br>모두 함께 즐거운 샴푸 시간 <br>머리가 대변신 <br>샴푸! <br>샴푸 샴푸 <br>샴푸시간 <br>샴푸 샴푸 <br>구석구석 <br>푸푸 푸푸 푸푸 푸푸 <br>기분이 좋아 <br>매일 매일 샴푸는 즐거워 <br>샴푸!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="샴푸송" label="샴푸송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/기상송/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 기상송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EA%B8%B0%EC%83%81%EC%86%A1/" title="핑크퐁 - 기상송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[“핑크퐁, 아침이야!” <br>아침이야 이야 이야 <br>아침이야 이야 이야 <br>아침이야 이야 이야 <br>아침이야 하! <br>아침이야 호! <br>해님이 방긋 솟아오르면 <br>이야 이야 아침이야 <br>웃는 얼굴 예쁜 얼굴로 <br>아침 인사 나눠요. <br>새들이 짹짹 인사해요 <br>벌들이 윙윙 인사해요 <br>모두 모두 일어나 인사해요 <br>이야 이야 아침이야 <br>아침이야 이야 이야 <br>아침이야 이야 이야 <br>아침이야 이야 이야 <br>아침이야 하! <br>아침이야 호! <br>아침이야 일어나]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="기상송" label="기상송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/배꼽_인사/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 배꼽 인사 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%B0%B0%EA%BC%BD_%EC%9D%B8%EC%82%AC/" title="핑크퐁 - 배꼽 인사 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[“ 핑크퐁과 함께!” <br>배! <br>꼽! <br>인! <br>사! <br>오른손 따라 랄랄라 <br>왼손 따라 랄랄라 <br>배꼽 인사 안녕하세요 랄랄라 <br>우리 모두 웃으면서 인사해요 <br>하하하 호호호 나는 인사왕 <br>“ 배꼽 인사, 안녕하세요!” <br>“ 안녕하세요!” <br>“ 배꼽 인사, 안녕하세요!” <br>“ 안녕하세요!” <br>오른손 따라 랄랄라 <br>왼손 따라 랄랄라 <br>배꼽 인사 안녕하세요 랄랄라 <br>우리 모두 웃으면서 인사해요 <br>하하하 호호호 나는 인사왕 <br>“ 배꼽 인사, 안녕하세요!” <br>“ 안녕하세요!” <br>배! <br>꼽! <br>인! <br>사! <br>“ 안녕하세요!” <br>오른손 따라 랄랄라 <br>왼손 따라 랄랄라 <br>배꼽 인사 안녕하세요 <br>고개 숙여 인사해요 <br>“안녕하세요!"]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="배꼽 인사" label="배꼽 인사"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/목욕송/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 목욕송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%AA%A9%EC%9A%95%EC%86%A1/" title="핑크퐁 - 목욕송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뽀 뽀드득 뽀 뽀드득 <br>구석구석 깨끗하게 뽀 뽀드득 <br>두 팔을 문질러 <br>쓱쓱 쓱쓱 <br>다리를 문질러 <br>싹싹 싹싹 <br>머리도 감아볼까 <br>박박박 <br>신나는 목욕시간 <br>뽀 뽀드득 뽀 뽀드득 <br>구석구석 깨끗하게 뽀 뽀드득 <br>시원한 물줄기가 <br>솨 솨 솨솨솨 <br>보글보글 거품이 <br>쭈룩쭈룩 쭈욱 <br>꼬질꼬질 내 모습이 <br>반짝반짝해 <br>신나는 목욕시간 <br>뽀 뽀드득 뽀 뽀드득 <br>구석구석 깨끗하게 뽀 뽀드득 <br>뽀 뽀드득 뽀 뽀드득 <br>구석구석 깨끗하게 뽀드득]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="목욕송" label="목욕송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/골고루송/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 골고루송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EA%B3%A8%EA%B3%A0%EB%A3%A8%EC%86%A1/" title="핑크퐁 - 골고루송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[“잘 먹겠습니다!” <br>꼬꼬꼬 꼬꼬꼬 꼭꼭 씹어 냠냠냠 <br>꼬꼬꼬 꼬꼬꼬 골고루 먹어요 <br>편식 안 돼요 안 돼 <br>투정 안 돼요 안 돼 <br>제 자리에 앉아서 <br>맛있게 먹어요 <br>OK! <br>브로콜리 꿀꺽 <br>토마토 꿀꺽 <br>양파 피망 검은콩까지 <br>꿀꺽 <br>냠 냠 냠 냠 냠 냠 <br>골고루 <br>시금치 꿀꺽 <br>버섯도 꿀꺽 <br>당근 감자 초록 파까지 <br>꿀꺽 <br>몸이 튼튼해져요 <br>키가 쑥쑥 자라요 <br>내 몸이 좋아해요 <br>맛있게 먹어요 <br>OK! <br>꼬꼬꼬 꼬꼬꼬 꼭꼭 씹어 냠냠냠 <br>꼬꼬꼬 꼬꼬꼬 골고루 먹어요 <br>꿀꺽]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="골고루송" label="골고루송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/손_씻기송/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 손 씻기송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EC%86%90_%EC%94%BB%EA%B8%B0%EC%86%A1/" title="핑크퐁 - 손 씻기송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보글보글 비누 거품 <br>구석구석 문질러요 <br>오른손 왼손 손목까지 <br>사이사이 사이사이로 <br>손바닥 손바닥 <br>마주 대고 문질러요 <br>손등에 손바닥 대고 <br>사이사이 사이사이로 <br>손가락 손가락 <br>깍지 끼고 문질러요 <br>손가락 손톱 밑도 <br>사이사이 사이사이로 <br>뽀득뽀득 손을 씻으면 <br>더러운 세균맨 안녕 <br>보글보글 비누 거품 <br>구석구석 문질러요 <br>오른손 왼손 손목까지 <br>사이사이 사이사이로 <br>사이사이 사이사이로]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="손 씻기송" label="손 씻기송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/변기송/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 변기송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%B3%80%EA%B8%B0%EC%86%A1/" title="핑크퐁 - 변기송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[“어서 와!” <br>바지를 내리고 <br>팬티를 내리고 <br>변기에 앉아서 <br>쉬! 쉬! 쉬! <br>쉬야는 변기 타고 <br>랄라 랄라 랄라라 <br>변기야 쉬야 할 때 또 만나자 <br>변기통에 변기통에 <br>변기통에 라랄라 <br>변기통에 변기통에 쉬야해요 <br>“ 캬아!” <br>“어서 와!” <br>바지를 내리고 <br>팬티를 내리고 <br>변기에 앉아서 <br>응! 응! 응! <br>응가는 변기 타고 <br>랄라 랄라 랄라라 <br>변기야 응가 할 때 또 만나자 <br>변기통에 변기통에 <br>변기통에 라랄라 <br>변기통에 변기통에 응가 해요 <br>변기통에 변기통에 <br>변기통에 라랄라 <br>변기통에 변기통에 <br>변기통에 랄랄랄라 <br>“ 캬아, 시원해!”]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="변기송" label="변기송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/치카송/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 치카송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EC%B9%98%EC%B9%B4%EC%86%A1/" title="핑크퐁 - 치카송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[치카치카 샤카샤카 <br>위로위로 아래아래 <br>치카치카 구석구석 <br>치카치카 깨끗하게 <br>샤카샤카 이를 닦자 <br>위로위로 아래아래 치카치카 <br>칫솔 들고 위아래로 <br>이를 닦자 쓱쓱 쓱쓱 <br>오른쪽 왼쪽 구석구석 <br>앞니도 어금니도 치카치카 <br>치카치카 샤카샤카 <br>위로위로 아래아래 <br>치카치카 구석구석 <br>치카치카 깨끗하게 <br>샤카샤카 이를 닦자 <br>위로위로 아래아래 치카치카 <br>모두 함께 <br>치카치카 치카 치카치카 <br>이를 닦자 <br>샤카샤카 샤카 샤카샤카 <br>엄마도 치카치카 <br>아빠도 치카치카 <br>치카치카 샤카샤카 <br>구석구석 쓱쓱 <br>반짝 <br>치카치카 샤카샤카 <br>위로위로 아래아래 <br>치카치카 구석구석 <br>치카치카 깨끗하게 <br>샤카샤카 이를 닦자 <br>위로위로 아래아래 치카치카]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="치카송" label="치카송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/기민/빈자리/</id><title>기민 - 빈자리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%B0%EB%AF%BC/%EB%B9%88%EC%9E%90%EB%A6%AC/" title="기민 - 빈자리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[문자를 하나씩 지워 <br>너와 주고 받았었던 <br>아직 실감이 나지 않는 <br>이 모든 게 다 꿈인 것 같아서 <br>사진을 한 장씩 태워 <br>널 향한 그리움으로 <br>내가 채워나갈 수 없는 <br>1분 1초가 힘들 것 같아서 <br>니가 없는 나 홀로 걷는 이 거리 <br>추억이 많다는 게 너무 힘들어 <br>우리 사랑했었던 <br>모습들을 잊어야만 <br>한다는 게 난 겁이 나 <br>좋았던 우리 행복했던 시간의 기억 <br>저편으로 사라져 멀리 <br>더욱더 커져가는 <br>너의 빈자리 지워본다 <br>니가 없는 나 홀로 걷는 이 거리 <br>추억이 많다는 게 너무 힘들어 <br>우리 사랑했었던 <br>모습들을 지워야만 <br>한다는 게 난 겁이 나 <br>좋았던 우리 행복했던 시간의 기억 <br>저편으로 사라져 멀리 <br>더욱더 커져가는 너의 빈자리 <br>그리움은 나를 미치게 만들고 <br>매달려도 봤지만 붙잡고 싶었지만 <br>더 이상 내게 아픈 기억이 되지 않기를 <br>이젠 보내줄게 <br>좋았던 우리 행복했던 시간의 기억 <br>저편으로 사라져 멀리 <br>더욱더 커져가는 <br>너의 빈자리 지워본다 <br>그렇게 널 잊는다 <br>]]></content><category term="기민" label="기민"/><category term="빈자리" label="빈자리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/기민/카페가_좋아/</id><title>기민 - 카페가 좋아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%B0%EB%AF%BC/%EC%B9%B4%ED%8E%98%EA%B0%80_%EC%A2%8B%EC%95%84/" title="기민 - 카페가 좋아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[카페가 좋아 <br>너와 있는 카페에 카페인 <br>한잔하며 얘길 나누면 피로가 풀려 <br>1분 10분 너무나 빠르게 지나가 <br>너와 있을 때면 <br>오늘 하루는 어때 별일은 없었니 <br>그래 오늘 참 힘들었구나 <br>모두 그 사람이 잘못했어 <br>정말 수고했어 <br>오늘도 넌 너무 예뻐 <br>한숨 쉬면 난 정말 속상해 <br>웃자 내가 재밌는 얘기해줄게 <br>그래 얼마나 예뻐 <br>피곤했는지 넌 눈이 감기고 <br>꾸벅꾸벅 졸음을 참는 너 <br>정말 귀여워 죽겠어 너 땜에 하루가 <br>항상 난 웃음이나 <br>오늘도 넌 너무 예뻐 <br>한숨 쉬면 난 정말 속상해 <br>웃자 내가 재밌는 얘기해줄게 <br>그래 얼마나 예뻐 <br>니가 없는 하루가 나는 상상이 안돼 <br>지금처럼 이대로 계속 머물러줄래 <br>oh 난 혹시 네가 날 떠날까 봐 <br>가끔씩은 너무 불안한 걸 <br>오늘도 넌 너무 예뻐 <br>한숨 쉬면 난 정말 속상해 <br>내가 재밌는 얘기해줄게 <br>그래 얼마나 예뻐 <br>오늘도 넌 너무 예뻐 <br>한숨 쉬면 난 정말 속상해 <br>웃자 내가 재밌는 얘기해줄게 <br>그래 얼마나 예뻐 <br>]]></content><category term="기민" label="기민"/><category term="카페가 좋아" label="카페가 좋아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/기민/자꾸만_니가/</id><title>기민 - 자꾸만 니가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:47:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:47:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%B0%EB%AF%BC/%EC%9E%90%EA%BE%B8%EB%A7%8C_%EB%8B%88%EA%B0%80/" title="기민 - 자꾸만 니가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자꾸만 니가 너무 보고 싶어져 <br>네 생각 하나로 설레긴 충분해 <br>이런 내 마음을 <br>그대는 알고 있을까 <br>햇살이 좋아 눈부신 게 꼭 너 같아 <br>너의 모습이 보이는 것만 같아 <br>자꾸만 뚫어져라 <br>보기에는 넌 눈이 부셔 <br>내가 아는 사람들 중에선 <br>니가 젤 예뻐 <br>보기만 해도 웃음 나는 사람 너인 걸 <br>어쩌다 네게 이렇게 빠진 건지 <br>나도 잘 모르겠어 <br>내게 와 같이 걸을래 설레임 마저 <br>또 너에게 모두 주고 싶은 마음 um <br>너에게 갈게 이제는 <br>내가 널 안아줄게 <br>내게 와줘 언제라도 널 기다리면서 <br>그렇게 웃고 싶은 난데 um <br>너를 사랑해 이 마음 <br>난 변하지 않아 그대로 일게 <br>눈을 뜨면 제일 먼저 하는 일 <br>너의 연락을 확인하고 또 답장하지 <br>그게 참 뭐라고 기분이 좋을까 <br>하루 시작이 설레여 난 <br>내게 와 같이 걸을래 설레임 마저 <br>또 너에게 모두 주고 싶은 마음 um <br>너에게 갈게 이제는 <br>내가 널 안아줄게 <br>내게 와줘 언제라도 널 기다리면서 <br>그렇게 웃고 싶은 난데 um <br>너를 사랑해 이 마음 <br>난 변하지 않아 그대로 일게 <br>내가 부족한 게 많아도 <br>너 하나면 난 충분한데 <br>조금씩 천천히 너에게 갈게 <br>네가 준비할 수 있게 <br>내게 와 같이 걸을래 설레임 마저 <br>또 너에게 모두 주고 싶은 마음 um <br>너를 사랑해 이 마음 <br>난 변하지 않아 그대로 일게 <br>]]></content><category term="기민" label="기민"/><category term="자꾸만 니가" label="자꾸만 니가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Arch_Enemy/War_Eternal_Live/</id><title>Arch Enemy - War Eternal (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:48:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:48:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Arch_Enemy/War_Eternal_Live/" title="Arch Enemy - War Eternal (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Friend or foe there's no way to know <br>In the battlefield of life its kill or be killed <br>So many times its a matter of degrees <br>From being up on your luck to down on your knees <br><br>Its a hellish inferno <br>This is war eternal <br><br>They try to change you, crush and break you <br><br>Try to tell you what to do <br>They love to have control of you <br>Back against the wall <br>In danger of losing it all <br>Search deep inside <br>Remember who you are <br><br>It's time like these when lines are drawn <br>Which side of the fence you are standing on <br>There will come a day not so far away <br>When the hunter becomes the prey and you will pay <br><br>Its a hellish inferno <br>This is war eternal <br><br>They try to change you, crush and break you <br><br>Try to tell you what to do <br>They love to have control of you <br>Back against the wall <br>In danger of losing it all <br>Search deep inside <br>Remember who you are <br><br>This is fucking war <br><br>They try to change you, crush and break you <br><br>Try to tell you what to do <br>They love to have control of you <br>Back against the wall <br>In danger of losing it all <br>Search deep inside <br>Remember who you are]]></content><category term="Arch Enemy" label="Arch Enemy"/><category term="War Eternal (Live)" label="War Eternal (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buffalo_Summer/Money_Live/</id><title>Buffalo Summer - Money (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:48:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:48:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Buffalo_Summer/Money_Live/" title="Buffalo Summer - Money (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well you know the time is right <br>Let's settle out the world we're creating <br>Forget the shades of black and white <br>I want you to come in the light now <br>Build this house, we're loose and wild <br>Open out go loud and high <br>Well now today we face the wind, the sun <br>Bringing to life all the broken ones <br><br>It ain't about the money <br>It ain't about the money <br>It ain't about the money <br>It ain't about the money <br><br>I still believed you played your hand <br>In all the [] <br>If this life is by design <br>The tomorrow might be one day when you're rising <br>Well now today we face the wind, the sun <br>Bringing to life all the broken ones <br><br>It ain't about the money <br>No, no <br>It ain't about the money <br>Yeah <br>It ain't about the money <br>Hey, no, no <br>It ain't about the money <br>Hey <br><br>It ain't about the money, no no <br>It ain't about the money, yeah <br>It ain't about the money, yeah, no no <br>It ain't about the money]]></content><category term="Buffalo Summer" label="Buffalo Summer"/><category term="Money (Live)" label="Money (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Steel_Panther/Community_Property_Live/</id><title>Steel Panther - Community Property (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Steel_Panther/Community_Property_Live/" title="Steel Panther - Community Property (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I would give you the stars in the sky <br>But they're too far away <br>If you were a hooker, you'd know <br>I'd be happy to pay <br>If suddenly you were a guy <br>I'd be suddenly gay <br><br>Cause my heart belongs to you <br>My love is pure and true <br>My heart belongs to you <br>But my cock is community property <br><br>You're the only girl that I like to screw <br>When I'm not on the road <br>When I come home, my dinner's made <br>And the front lawn is mowed <br>I'll kiss your mouth <br>Even after you swallow my load <br><br>Cause my heart belongs to you <br>My love is pure and true <br>My heart belongs to you <br>But my cock is community property <br><br>I wanna make it clear <br>So you retain it <br>My dick's a free spirit <br>And you can't restrain it <br>No, you just can't chain it down <br><br>I love you so much it hurts <br>From my head to my feet <br>I think of you and I can't <br>Help but fondle my meat <br>I see your face every time <br>That I go out and cheat <br><br>Cause my heart belongs to you <br>My love is pure and true <br>My heart belongs to you <br>But my cock is community property]]></content><category term="Steel Panther" label="Steel Panther"/><category term="Community Property (Live)" label="Community Property (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Therion/Son_Of_The_Staves_Of_Time_Live/</id><title>Therion - Son Of The Staves Of Time (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Therion/Son_Of_The_Staves_Of_Time_Live/" title="Therion - Son Of The Staves Of Time (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tidesson <br>Son of the Staves of Time <br>Tidesson <br>Tell us the secret rhyme <br><br>Byrger Tidesson <br>You investigate <br>Runic alphabet <br>And you innovate <br>Every stave of runes, all the secret signs <br><br>Ascending Tidher <br>Sign of inventor Idher <br><br>Byrger Tidesson <br>Foremost magistrate <br>Armed from ancient time <br>With arrows of fate <br>I'm your follower until heaven's gate <br><br>Ascending Tidher <br>Sign of inventor Idher <br><br>Byrger Tidesson <br>From the ancient time <br>Runic ancestor <br>The last of your line <br><br>Tidesson <br>Son of the Staves of Time <br>Tidesson <br>Tell us the secret rhyme <br><br>Magistrate Tidesson <br>Secret King Tidesson <br><br>Ascending Tidher <br>Inventor Idher <br><br>Byrger Tidesson <br>You're descending from Odin, Thor and Frej <br>Tetragrammaton <br>From Tiundaland <br>Your Notarikon <br><br>Tidesson <br>Son of the Staves of Time <br>Tidesson <br>Tell us the secret rhyme]]></content><category term="Therion" label="Therion"/><category term="Son Of The Staves Of Time (Live)" label="Son Of The Staves Of Time (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Metal_Church/Gods_Of_Second_Chance_Live/</id><title>Metal Church - Gods Of Second Chance (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Metal_Church/Gods_Of_Second_Chance_Live/" title="Metal Church - Gods Of Second Chance (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In an act of desperation, he put a gun to his head <br>In his mind confusion, nothing but delusion <br>Thinking he was better off dead <br><br>No one to be his savior from the vises he made <br>Voices callin' to him, left his life in ruins <br>Drugs have led his mind astray <br><br>God, don't you hear me <br>God, don't you care <br>'Cause if you did, my friend <br>You wouldn't leave me hangin' on this way <br><br>Somebody turn on the lights <br>Somebody give me some air <br>I'm in the middle of a nasty situation <br>That is leading me on nowhere <br><br>I gotta hear you tonight <br>I gotta know that you care <br>You got me down on my knees <br>And I'm praying and I gotta know you're really there <br><br>The second hand is ticking, time moves ahead <br>Feel the shadows breathing, whispering and seething <br>Dealing inside my head <br><br>A candle flame before me flickers in dance <br>As I sit here praying, hoping that I'm swaying <br>The Gods of second chance <br><br>All cry to heaven <br>All cry for truth <br>And while we wait for lights and thunder <br>The devil is on the loose <br><br>Somebody turn on the lights <br>Somebody give me some air <br>I'm in the middle of a nasty situation <br>That is leading me on nowhere <br><br>I gotta hear you tonight <br>I gotta know that you care <br>You got me down on my knees and I'm praying <br>And I gotta know you're really there <br><br>God, don't you hear me <br>God, don't you care <br>'Cause if you did, my friend <br>You wouldn't leave me hangin' on this way <br><br>Somebody turn on the lights <br>Somebody give me some air <br>I'm in the middle of a nasty situation <br>That is leading me on nowhere <br><br>I gotta hear you tonight <br>I gotta know that you care <br>You got me down on my knees <br>And I'm praying and I gotta know you're really there]]></content><category term="Metal Church" label="Metal Church"/><category term="Gods Of Second Chance (Live)" label="Gods Of Second Chance (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Borknagar/Colossus_Live/</id><title>Borknagar - Colossus (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Borknagar/Colossus_Live/" title="Borknagar - Colossus (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[From out of static time has grown <br>Existence formed by substance unknown <br>Prelude to matter shift or dissorder <br>Completion of bonds between chaos and order <br><br>The era of seasons, the essence of being <br>The continous process awakens the living <br>Absorber of every flickering sun <br>Arranging the pieces to vivid perfection <br><br>The stream of mortality flows uncontrolled <br>A boundless downward spiral to prospective void <br>Existence takes its toll, extinction unfolds <br>The Colossus falls back from its threshold <br><br>The Cosmic grip so tight Heed the celestial call <br>The rise, the voyage, the fall - tangled womb of mortal soil <br><br>Universal key of inception, pulled out of the grind <br>The growing seed of creation and time <br><br>Complex fusion, the bond of four - the nature's core <br>Universal ritual, aesthetic beauty adored <br><br>The pendulum upholds the carnal deceit <br>Eternal, endless, indefinite <br><br>The paradox render and the merge is complete <br>Nothing but the process is infinite <br><br>Nothing but the process is infinite <br>Eternal, endless, indefinite]]></content><category term="Borknagar" label="Borknagar"/><category term="Colossus (Live)" label="Colossus (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimo_Callboy/Muffin_Purper-Gurk_Live/</id><title>Eskimo Callboy - Muffin Purper-Gurk (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimo_Callboy/Muffin_Purper-Gurk_Live/" title="Eskimo Callboy - Muffin Purper-Gurk (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come on everybody <br>Put your fucking hands up <br>What <br>Fucking hands up <br>What <br>Fucking hands up <br><br>Come on everybody <br>Put your fucking hands up <br>What <br>Fucking hands up <br>What <br>Fucking hands up <br><br>Come on everybody <br>Put your fucking hands up <br>What <br>Fucking hands up <br>What <br>Fucking hands up <br><br>Oohhh <br><br>Oh yeah <br>Muffin Purper-Gurk <br><br>Come on everybody <br>Put your fucking hands up <br>What <br>Fucking hands up <br>What <br>Motherfucker <br><br>Oooohhhhh <br><br>I miss you <br>I adore you <br>It's hard to say <br>In love, Muffin Purper-Gurk <br><br>I miss you <br>I adore you <br>It's hard to say <br>Muffin Purper-Gurk <br><br>Oh boy, you got a nice bicycle <br><br>My heart hugs your hairy butt <br>Guinea pig romance <br>Romance <br>Hey your goldfish sucks <br>Alpakas make me angry <br><br>Come on everybody <br>Put your fucking hands up <br>What <br>Fucking hands up <br>What <br>Fucking hands up <br><br>Come on everybody <br>Put your fucking hands up <br>What <br>Fucking hands up <br>What <br>Fucking hands up <br><br>Come on everybody <br>Put your fucking hands up <br>What <br>Fucking hands up <br>What <br>Fucking hands up <br><br>Come on everybody <br>Put your fucking hands up <br>What <br>Fucking hands up <br>What <br>Fucking hands up <br><br>I miss you so <br>I miss you so <br>Give me an M <br>For Muffin Purper-Gurk <br>So hard to be alone <br>Now I'm on my own <br><br>I miss you <br>I adore you <br>It's hard to say <br>In love, Muffin Purper-Gurk <br><br>I miss you <br>I adore you <br>It's hard to say <br>Muffin Purper-Gurk]]></content><category term="Eskimo Callboy" label="Eskimo Callboy"/><category term="Muffin Purper-Gurk (Live)" label="Muffin Purper-Gurk (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caliban/Paralyzed_Live/</id><title>Caliban - Paralyzed (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caliban/Paralyzed_Live/" title="Caliban - Paralyzed (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm just a shadow <br>Just another brick <br>I'm just an echo <br>It makes me sick <br><br>They shove it, down my throat <br>All this bullshit <br>Makes me overdose <br><br>I'm the ghost, you're the night <br>I'm the shadow, you're the light x2 <br><br>I am paralyzed <br>Oh, I'm paralyzed <br><br>I am tired of your ties <br>My reflection of your lies <br>I am paralyzed <br><br>You fucking prick <br>Drop dead <br>You make me sick <br>Bleh <br><br>You fucking prick <br>Drop dead <br>You make me sick <br>Get out of my head <br><br>I'm still a shadow <br>It's never gonna stop <br>I'm still an echo <br>I still won't wake up <br>And they still shove it down my throat <br>They're never gonna stop until I overdose <br><br>I'm the ghost, you're the night <br>I'm the shadow, you're the light x2 <br><br>I am paralyzed <br>Oh, I'm paralyzed <br><br>I am tired of your ties <br>My reflection of your lies <br>I am paralyzed <br><br>You fucking prick <br>Drop dead <br>You make me sick <br>Bleh <br><br>You fucking prick <br>Drop dead <br>You make me sick <br>Get out of my head <br><br>I'm a ghost, I'm a shadow <br>Break out <br><br>I am lost, I'm an echo <br>Break out <br><br>I'm a ghost, I'm a shadow <br>Break out <br><br>I am lost, I am hollow <br>Break out <br><br>I'm the ghost, you're the night <br>I'm the shadow, you're the light <br><br>I am paralyzed <br>Oh, I'm paralyzed <br><br>I am tired of your ties <br>My reflection of your lies <br>I am paralyzed <br><br>You fucking prick <br>Drop dead <br>You make me sick <br>Bleh <br><br>You fucking prick <br>Drop dead <br>You make me sick <br>Get out of my head]]></content><category term="Caliban" label="Caliban"/><category term="Paralyzed (Live)" label="Paralyzed (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Red_Fang/Prehistoric_Dog_Live/</id><title>Red Fang - Prehistoric Dog (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Red_Fang/Prehistoric_Dog_Live/" title="Red Fang - Prehistoric Dog (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dogs that howl from outer space <br>Come to Earth to lay to waste <br>With fang and claw to shred your face <br>They will erase the human race <br>Time to kiss your ass goodbye <br>Prehistoric dogs of war <br>Pack of wolves is at your door <br>Their will to kill will fill the pits of hell <br>Blood is spilled and none too soon <br>Looking down from cratered moon <br>They see us flee we need to break the spell <br>Dogs that howl from outer space <br>Come to Earth to lay to waste <br>With fang and claw to shred your face <br>They will erase the human race <br>Time to kiss your ass goodbye <br>Our lives are long <br>But our flesh is gone <br>It may be wrong <br>God bless godlessness <br>We're walking tall <br>If we walk at all <br>We're living like a <br>Prehistoric dog]]></content><category term="Red Fang" label="Red Fang"/><category term="Prehistoric Dog (Live)" label="Prehistoric Dog (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Sculptor_Of_Flesh_Live/</id><title>1349 - Sculptor Of Flesh (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1349/Sculptor_Of_Flesh_Live/" title="1349 - Sculptor Of Flesh (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do you hear them calling from beyong <br><br>As a foulness ye shall know them <br>As a foulness thou knowest thyself <br><br>Freed from the shackles of morality <br>And long long gone is the need for science <br>Through the wakening of the beast within <br><br>Oh did you not rejoice <br>When you felt the power The power in your mind <br>No longer confined to nocturnal solitude <br><br>Walk among the herd <br>Mold them as you wish <br>In images of unearthly bizarrerie <br><br>Do you hear them calling from beyong <br><br>Sculptor of flesh <br>Architect of abomination <br>Mold the living flesh like clay <br><br>Sculptor of flesh <br>Warp the world <br>To your linking <br><br>And then the sun will set <br>And no new day will rise on humanity <br><br>Will you grieve for them <br><br>Will the lack of their bleating cacophony <br>Strike a note within <br><br>Rejoice, destroyer, anti-christ <br>For your deed was long overdue]]></content><category term="1349" label="1349"/><category term="Sculptor Of Flesh (Live)" label="Sculptor Of Flesh (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tarja/No_Bitter_End_Live/</id><title>Tarja - No Bitter End (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tarja/No_Bitter_End_Live/" title="Tarja - No Bitter End (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Desire is a flame alive <br>When dreams are far away <br>Open up your inner eye, Let hope save the day <br>She will fall all over you <br>Like a rain, shine the new <br>And will make the path for you to take <br>Till the end walk you through <br><br>Time won't wait <br>Lead your fate <br>Never let go <br><br>Black out the sun <br>Light no where <br>Tell me you don't need it anymore <br>No bitter end <br>Hold on don't run <br>Forever <br>Stay yourself, the one that you defend <br>No bitter end <br><br>Suddenly, mysteriously <br>How brave worlds are born <br>They cut away the misery <br>For hearts to find home <br>To be there with all you need <br>And nothing left to prove <br>Take a chance, go, but never leave <br>Know it all starts with you <br><br>Time won't wait <br>Lead your fate <br>Never let go <br><br>Black out the sun <br>Light no where <br>Tell me you don't need it anymore <br>No bitter end <br>Hold on don't run <br>Forever <br>Stay yourself, the one that you defend <br>No bitter end <br><br>There's a road for everyone <br>Cos every heart's the same <br>To forgive what you have done <br>The silent wish for change <br><br>Black out the sun <br>Light no where <br>Tell me you don't need it anymore <br>No bitter end <br>Hold on don't run <br>Forever <br>Stay yourself, the one that you defend <br>No bitter end]]></content><category term="Tarja" label="Tarja"/><category term="No Bitter End (Live)" label="No Bitter End (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bullet_For_My_Valentine/Tears_Dont_Fall_Live/</id><title>Bullet For My Valentine - Tears Don`t Fall (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bullet_For_My_Valentine/Tears_Dont_Fall_Live/" title="Bullet For My Valentine - Tears Don`t Fall (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let's go <br><br>With blood shot eyes I watch you sleeping <br>The warmth I feel beside me is slowly fading <br>Would she hear me if I called her name <br>Would she hold me if she knew my shame <br><br>There's always something different going wrong <br>The path I walk's in the wrong direction <br>There's always someone fucking hanging on <br>Can anybody help me make things better <br><br>Your tears don't fall, they crash around me <br>Her conscience calls, the guilty to come home <br>Your tears don't fall, they crash around me <br>Her conscience calls, the guilty to come home <br><br>The moments die, I hear no screaming <br>The visions left inside me are slowly fading <br>Would she hear me if I called her name <br>Would she hold me if she knew my shame <br><br>There's always something different going wrong <br>The path I walk's in the wrong direction <br>There's always someone fucking hanging on <br>Can anybody help me make things better <br><br>Your tears don't fall, they crash around me <br>Her conscience calls, the guilty to come home <br>Your tears don't fall, they crash around me <br>Her conscience calls, the guilty to come home <br><br>Oh yeah <br><br>This battered room I've seen before <br>The broken bones they heal no more, no more <br>With my last breath I'm choking <br>Will this ever end I'm hoping <br>My world is over one more time <br><br>Let's go <br><br>Would she hear me if I called her name <br>Would she hold me if she knew my shame <br><br>There's always something different going wrong <br>The path I walk's in the wrong direction <br>There's always someone fucking hanging on <br>Can anybody help me make things better <br><br>Your tears don't fall, they crash around me <br>Her conscience calls, the guilty to come home <br>Your tears don't fall, they crash around me <br>Her conscience calls, the guilty to come <br><br>Better <br><br>Your tears don't fall, they crash around me <br>Her conscience calls, the guilty to come home]]></content><category term="Bullet For My Valentine" label="Bullet For My Valentine"/><category term="Tears Don`t Fall (Live)" label="Tears Don`t Fall (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eluveitie/Havoc_Live/</id><title>Eluveitie - Havoc (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eluveitie/Havoc_Live/" title="Eluveitie - Havoc (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wonder what it's like to attack at Night <br>And mow down the defenceless <br>Invasions and Raids just called <br>Fucking, punitive Expeditions <br><br>Like a Wildfire <br>Devastation spreads <br>Across all Gallia <br><br>From Helvetia to Eburonia <br>The Ravener's Insatiate <br><br>Havoc <br>Think of yesterday <br>Ruin <br>A mass illusion How could it come this far <br>Our dormant Minds were not prepared for this <br><br>Narbonensis was not enough <br>The Empire needed more <br>From Aremorica to Carnutia <br>Plagued and War-ridden Land <br>Wars inflicted on free Gallia <br>An organised Downfall <br>A black Cloud of Imperial <br>Rapacity unleashed <br><br>Imperial needs are met <br>At the bloody Cost of free Tribes <br>Invasion, Raid and War Atrocity <br>In the Name of SPQR]]></content><category term="Eluveitie" label="Eluveitie"/><category term="Havoc (Live)" label="Havoc (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Torfrock/Presslufthammer_B-B-Bernhard_Live/</id><title>Torfrock - Presslufthammer B-B-Bernhard (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Torfrock/Presslufthammer_B-B-Bernhard_Live/" title="Torfrock - Presslufthammer B-B-Bernhard (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Die Leute erz?hlen, ich hoppel, wenn ich gehe <br>Und die Ohrn wollen auch nicht mehr so richtig <br>Inne Fr?hst?ckspause versch?ttel ich den Tee <br>Ober f?r mich ist das alles nich so wichtig <br><br>Mit mein' Presslufthammer f?hl ich mich verbunden <br>Und bin verknallt in Staub und Schutt <br>Und ich ratter euch in nichmal viereinhalb Stunden <br>Ein Einfamilienhaus in Dutt <br><br>Jeden Tag hol ich den Presslufthammer <br>Aus der Werkzeugkammer <br>Und denn mach ich Krach ? <br>Das gibt keinen der seinen Hammer so gern hat <br>Man nennt mich Presslufthammer B-B-B-B-B-Bernhard <br><br>Jeden Tag hol ich den Presslufthammer <br>Aus der Werkzeugkammer <br>Und denn mach ich Krach ? <br>Das gibt keinen der seinen Hammer so gern hat <br>Man nennt mich Presslufthammer B-B-B-B-B-Bernhard <br><br>Ratatazong, ratatazong <br>Weg ist der Balkon ? <br>Dong <br><br>Mit mein Chef versteh ich mich allerbest <br>Ich jammer ja auch nie rum <br>Von Lohnerh?hung oder Arbeitsgesetz <br>Und er findet ich bin gornich so dumm <br><br>Moin moin, mein Berhard, mach hin und gut Holz <br>Br?llt er mir manchmol ins Ohr <br>Und denn krieg ne Zigarre und denn bin ich ganz stolz <br>Und denn katter ich ihm ein' vor <br><br>Jeden Tag hol ich den Presslufthammer <br>Aus der Werkzeugkammer <br>Und denn mach ich Krach ? <br>Das gibt keinen der seinen Hammer so gern hat <br>Man nennt mich Presslufthammer B-B-B-B-B-Bernhard <br><br>Jeden Tag hol ich den Presslufthammer <br>Aus der Werkzeugkammer <br>Und denn mach ich Krach ? <br>Das gibt keinen der seinen Hammer so gern hat <br>Man nennt mich Presslufthammer B-B-B-B-B-Bernhard <br><br>Ratatazong, ratatazong <br>Weg ist der Balkon ? <br>Dong <br>H, h, h ? do geht er hin <br><br>Nur einmol ist mein Chef in Wut geroten <br>Da musste ich zu ihn nach Hause <br>Und sollte ihn sein Garten umgroben <br>Und er sochte Ich mach erstmol Pause <br><br>Hier rumzustehn hat sowieso kein Zweck <br>Ich besuch erstmol unsern Paster <br>Und ich hob verstanden Knack hier alles weg ? <br>Als zur?ckkam lag sein Haus aufn Laster <br><br>Jeden Tag hol ich den Presslufthammer <br>Aus der Werkzeugkammer <br>Und denn mach ich Krach ? <br>Das gibt keinen der seinen Hammer so gern hat <br>Man nennt mich Presslufthammer B-B-B-B-B-Bernhard <br><br>Jeden Tag hol ich den ? Ding ? <br><br>Also so'n Hammer mit harte, do ? <br>Ding <br>Ding ? no egol <br>Also ? womit man diese Steine immer so kaputtmachen tut, ne <br>Na ? no, is jo egol <br>Muss sowieso wieder zu meine Arbeit <br><br>? <br><br>Oder ? oder ? oder wat]]></content><category term="Torfrock" label="Torfrock"/><category term="Presslufthammer B-B-Bernhard (Live)" label="Presslufthammer B-B-Bernhard (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Axel_Rudi_Pell/Rock_The_Nation_Live/</id><title>Axel Rudi Pell - Rock The Nation (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Axel_Rudi_Pell/Rock_The_Nation_Live/" title="Axel Rudi Pell - Rock The Nation (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The show is over <br>Still hear the ringing in your ears <br>Another day on the road and no time for fears <br>The lights turned off <br>The stage is cleared and empty <br>The enery level you had turned down completely <br><br>Hots nights of thunder <br>All fists up in the air <br><br>We are the wild creation <br>And we will rock this town <br>We gonna rock the nation <br>So shout it out loud <br><br>A thousand miles away from home <br>You're locked inside the circus <br>Stragefright you try to stay cool and not getting nervous <br>The countdown starts, a few second to go, all hell breaks loose <br>And you're giving all that you can and sometimes even more <br><br>Hots nights of thunder <br>All fists up in the air <br><br>We are the wild creation <br>And we will rock this town <br>We gonna rock the nation <br>And there is no doubt <br><br>We are no strange sensation <br>But wanna teach you loud <br>We gonna rock the nation <br>And there is no doubt <br><br>This is your life and it means all to you <br>This is your life for breaking the rules]]></content><category term="Axel Rudi Pell" label="Axel Rudi Pell"/><category term="Rock The Nation (Live)" label="Rock The Nation (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Die_Krupps/Fatherland_Live/</id><title>Die Krupps - Fatherland (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Die_Krupps/Fatherland_Live/" title="Die Krupps - Fatherland (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I see houses burning <br>I'm ashamed <br>Before you close your eyes denyingly <br>You better ask yourself <br><br>Did I choose something I could regret <br>Did I do something <br>I should regret <br><br>Is this the place I used to call <br>Fatherland <br>Is this the place I used to know <br>As fatherland <br><br>The silence is illusion <br>Stay awake <br>I hear children crying in fear and pain <br>Do cowards ask themselves]]></content><category term="Die Krupps" label="Die Krupps"/><category term="Fatherland (Live)" label="Fatherland (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Equilibrium/Born_To_Be_Epic_Live/</id><title>Equilibrium - Born To Be Epic (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Equilibrium/Born_To_Be_Epic_Live/" title="Equilibrium - Born To Be Epic (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I walk on fire alone <br>And still consider it's cold <br>I call vulcanos my home <br><br>If they erupt I see gold <br>I walk on Mountains of ice <br>And still consider it's warm <br>Right on the top would be nice <br>10000 miles are my norm <br>No mission too hard <br>No challenge too big <br>Because I was born <br>Born to be epic <br>I fly in heaven so high <br>And still consider it's deep <br>There is no fear in my eyes <br>Across the planet I leap <br>I crawl to the center of earth <br>Deep down to find our birth <br>Faster I head to my goal <br>To spread my rock'n'roll <br>No mission too hard <br>No challenge too big <br>Because I was born <br>Born to be epic <br>No mission too hard <br>No challenge too big <br>Because I was born <br>Born to be epic]]></content><category term="Equilibrium" label="Equilibrium"/><category term="Born To Be Epic (Live)" label="Born To Be Epic (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Entombed_AD/Dead_Dawn_Live/</id><title>Entombed A.D. - Dead Dawn (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Entombed_AD/Dead_Dawn_Live/" title="Entombed A.D. - Dead Dawn (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In the cellar slowly worming <br>Feeding growing pain and fear <br>Occupied with greedy hoarding <br>Without thinking what is there <br><br>Final blast inferno on the way <br>The rolling of the dice <br>Like sheep in panic running astray <br>Extermination quick on site <br><br>Plastic ocean concrete haze <br>Concluding dead dawn <br>Eradicated this the end of days <br>Into the open hole <br><br>No one seeing what is coming <br>Monkey chatter fills the air <br>It matters not no point in running <br>Armageddon fire sear <br><br>Total blast inferno on the way <br>Last rolling of the dice <br>Like sheep in panic running astray <br>Exterminated crushed as lice <br><br>Plastic ocean concrete haze <br>Concluding dead dawn <br>Eradicated this the end of days <br>Into the open hole <br><br>And all that's on your mind <br>Hog as much as you can find <br>You'll command and rule <br>What a joke total fool <br><br>No running away <br>No reason to pray <br>No place to roam <br>All that remains <br>Is dust and bone <br><br>Plastic ocean concrete haze <br>Concluding dead dawn <br>Exsanguinated this the end of days <br>Into the open hole]]></content><category term="Entombed A.D." label="Entombed A.D."/><category term="Dead Dawn (Live)" label="Dead Dawn (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bury_Tomorrow/Man_On_Fire_Live/</id><title>Bury Tomorrow - Man On Fire (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bury_Tomorrow/Man_On_Fire_Live/" title="Bury Tomorrow - Man On Fire (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fear of the sacred <br>We're blurring lines between the real and the fake here <br>And so I scream, Return to me <br>Return to me, return to me <br><br>Fear of the sacred <br>We're blurring lines between the real and the fake here <br>And so I scream, Return to me <br>Return to me, return to me <br><br>Breathe slowly take shallow breaths <br>So I shut you down there's nothing left <br>Why are all the saints sick of governing <br>the knowledge that we're insane <br>Dear body, come to haunt me <br>We drive ourselves through the fire's light <br><br>Free me, said the man on fire <br>Release me to the higher <br>Fighting certainty I know, I won't regret this <br>Find me, said the man on fire <br>Release me to the higher <br>Forever in the dark alone, forgotten <br><br>My passion must be frightening <br>I just shout to the dark <br>And all I have is screaming <br>I see paranoia, dark is calling me <br>All the voices of the souls that used to be <br>I must find a way to drown out the sound <br>I must find a way to drown out the sound <br><br>Free me, said the man on fire <br>Release me to the higher <br>Fighting certainty I know, I won't regret this <br>Find me, said the man on fire <br>Release me to the higher <br>Forever in the dark alone, forgotten <br><br>Set me alight, for I am losing it <br>Set me alight, for I am losing it <br>Set me alight, for I am losing it <br>Set me alight, for I am losing it <br><br>Fear of the sacred <br>We're blurring lines between the real and the fake here <br>And so I scream, Return to me <br>Return to me, return to me <br><br>Fear of the sacred <br>We're blurring lines between the real and the fake here <br>And so I scream, Return to me <br>Return to me, return to me]]></content><category term="Bury Tomorrow" label="Bury Tomorrow"/><category term="Man On Fire (Live)" label="Man On Fire (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Vintage_Caravan/Expand_Your_Mind_Live/</id><title>The Vintage Caravan - Expand Your Mind (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Vintage_Caravan/Expand_Your_Mind_Live/" title="The Vintage Caravan - Expand Your Mind (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Expand your mind, baby <br>Take a look behind <br>Take a trip with me, take a trip <br>Sail into the endless sea <br>Sail away with me <br>Take a trip with me, take a trip <br><br>Take a look into my eyes <br>What they told you were all lies <br>Take a trip with me, take a trip <br>Colors blend from the moon <br>Voices whisper, look at the loon <br>Take a trip with me, take a trip <br><br>Your mind <br>Full of questions, honey <br>You will find, you will know <br>The answer lies within your heart now baby <br>You will find, you will <br><br>They're not gonna give you anything <br>They don't want you to know <br>So take a trip with us, take it <br><br>Your mind <br>Full of questions, honey <br>You will find, you will know <br>The answer lies within your heart now baby <br>You will find, you will know <br><br>Expand your mind, baby <br>Take a look behind <br>Take a trip with me, take a trip <br>Sail into the endless sea <br>Sail away with me <br>Take a trip with me, take a trip <br><br>Your mind <br>Full of questions, honey <br>You will find, you will know <br>The answer lies within your heart now baby <br>You will find, you will]]></content><category term="The Vintage Caravan" label="The Vintage Caravan"/><category term="Expand Your Mind (Live)" label="Expand Your Mind (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Monroe/78_Live/</id><title>Michael Monroe - 78 (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Monroe/78_Live/" title="Michael Monroe - 78 (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey Hey Hey Hey <br><br>Time has come to pass <br>It's time to take the middle finger out your ass <br>You've been complainin' that the man is screwin' you <br>He's lost the power yeah, so whatcha gonna do with all that attitude <br><br>They put their business outta tune Hey <br>Now the revolution's come into your living room Hey <br>Is you incapable or is you in denial Hey <br>Facing the change that they couldn't see for miles <br>They couldn't see for miles <br><br>The golden age of DIY <br>I'm getting yours and you got mine <br><br>You can take the boy outta '78 <br>The style's gonna change, but the sentiment ain't <br>You can't take '78 outta the boy <br><br>Hey <br>Yeah '78 <br>Hey <br><br>Does isolation got your tongue <br>They say that youth is often wasted on the young <br>Take out your protein pills and put your helmet on <br>You got your motor, where you takin' me today <br>So whatcha gonna say <br><br>Easy come and easier go <br>It's all a case of who you should know <br><br>You can take the boy outta '78 <br>The style's gonna change, but the sentiment ain't <br>You can't take '78 outta the boy <br><br>Hey <br>'78 <br>Hey <br>Here to stay <br>Oooh <br><br>You can take the boy outta '78 <br>The style's gonna change, but the sentiment ain't <br>You can't take '78 outta the boy <br>You can take the boy outta '78 hey, hey, hey <br>The style's gonna change, but the sentiment ain't <br>You can't take '78 outta the boy <br><br>Hey <br><br>'78 <br>Hey <br>Just '78 <br>Hey <br>'78 <br>Hey <br>Eh]]></content><category term="Michael Monroe" label="Michael Monroe"/><category term="78 (Live)" label="78 (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Therapy_/Screamager_Live/</id><title>Therapy? - Screamager (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Therapy_/Screamager_Live/" title="Therapy? - Screamager (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[With a face like this I won't break any hearts <br>And thinking like that I won't make any friends <br><br>Screw that <br>Forget about that <br>I don't want to think about anything like that <br><br>Screw that <br>Forget about that <br>I don't want to know about anything like that <br><br>I've got nothing to do, but hang around and get screwed up on you <br>I've got nothing to do, but hang around and get screwed up on you <br><br>Your beauty makes me feel alone <br>I look inside but no one's home <br><br>Screw that <br>Forget about that <br>I don't want to think about anything like that <br><br>Screw that <br>Forget about that <br>I don't want to know about anything like that <br><br>I've got nothing to do, but hang around and get screwed up on you <br>I've got nothing to do, but hang around and get screwed up on you <br><br>I've got nothing to do, but hang around and get screwed up on you <br>I've got nothing to do, but hang around and get screwed up on you <br>I've got nothing to do, but hang around and get screwed up on you <br>I've got nothing to do, but hang around and get screwed up on you <br><br>But get screwed up on you <br>But get screwed up on you]]></content><category term="Therapy?" label="Therapy?"/><category term="Screamager (Live)" label="Screamager (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Immolation/Despondent_Souls_Live/</id><title>Immolation - Despondent Souls (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Immolation/Despondent_Souls_Live/" title="Immolation - Despondent Souls (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Slaughtering the innocent <br>Massacring the weak <br>Intimidate their fearful minds <br>Corrupt their structurer world <br>Afflict with terror, their lives suppressed <br>Consuming all their hopes <br>Expurgate their thoughts, oppressing all <br>Nauseate with fright <br>Hollowed shells of living corpses <br>Pay homage to their art <br>Frail and weak, despondent souls <br>Are prematurely dead <br><br>Cherished hopes beyond Your grasp <br>Trepidation grows within <br>Time exists to test Your brain <br>Tormenting fast Your sanity <br>Dormant lives are cast aside <br>Evil slaughter, vile and sick <br>Feel the pain <br><br>Deep below damp and cold <br>Chambers filled with rotting dead <br>Sealed together cryptic cells <br>Twisted corpses in a mangled grave <br>Maggots grow deep inside <br>Multiply savored feast <br>Concealed to all unknown their fate <br>Plea for life their cries obscure <br><br>Slaughtering the innocent <br>Massacring the weak <br>Intimidate their fearful minds <br>Corrupt their structurer world <br>Afflict with terror, their lives suppressed <br>Consuming all their hopes <br>Expurgate their thoughts, oppressing all <br>Nauseate with fright <br>Hollowed shells of living corpses <br>Pay homage to their art <br>Frail and weak, despondent souls <br>Are prematurely dead <br><br>Cherished hopes beyond Your grasp <br>Trepidation grows within <br>Time exists to test Your brain <br>Tormenting fast Your sanity <br>Dormant lives are cast aside <br>Evil slaughter, vile and sick <br>Feel the pain]]></content><category term="Immolation" label="Immolation"/><category term="Despondent Souls (Live)" label="Despondent Souls (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tsjuder/Demonic_Supremacy_Live/</id><title>Tsjuder - Demonic Supremacy (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tsjuder/Demonic_Supremacy_Live/" title="Tsjuder - Demonic Supremacy (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I command the demon army <br>Riding on flames from hell <br>To destroy all living beings <br><br>And reclaim the throne of evil <br><br>Demonic supremacy <br><br>For thousands of years we have waited <br>We have hungered the demons <br>Frenzied by their bloodthirst <br>Preparing the ultimate slaughter <br><br>There is no time to fear <br>Your heads will be on stakes <br><br>We have no fear <br>Nothing to loose <br>They are my breed <br>Demonic <br><br>My demons will feast <br>Feast upon your remains <br><br>Demonic supremacy <br><br>For thousands of years we have waited <br>We have hungered the demons <br>Frenzied by their bloodthirst <br>Preparing the ultimate slaughter <br><br>We have no fear <br>Nothing to loose <br>They are my breed <br>Demonic <br><br>Your world will be lost for all eternity <br>There will be no god to save you <br>As I shall sit on the top of the throne <br>Preparing hell <br>Prepare for hell <br>Hell <br>Prepare for hell <br>Hell]]></content><category term="Tsjuder" label="Tsjuder"/><category term="Demonic Supremacy (Live)" label="Demonic Supremacy (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vader/Triumph_Of_Death_Live/</id><title>Vader - Triumph Of Death (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vader/Triumph_Of_Death_Live/" title="Vader - Triumph Of Death (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Still fallowing his rules and laws <br>Demanding, enslaving and using <br>Enthroned himself as a Lord of the Whole <br>Creator of a God of a man <br>Too proud to perceive the realities <br>His constant way to the grave <br>A Fate set up by the code <br>To the grave <br>To the grave <br>Still marching on <br>To the gates <br>To the gates <br>Where the Death awaits You <br>Come closer, my Child <br>Now sleep well in my arms <br>Cold kiss of Death <br>Shall free your final breath <br>To the grave <br>To the grave <br>Still marching on <br>To the grave <br>To the grave <br>You'll meet the Human DEAD <br>O tempera, o mores <br>How weak became this pride <br>Ad portas inferi <br>Where even Death may cry <br>Human-a child of the Earth <br>Still fallowing his rules and laws <br>Demanding, enslaving and using <br>Enthroned himself as a Lord of the World <br>To the grave <br>To the grave <br>Still marching on <br>To the grave <br>To the grave <br>You'll meet the Human DEAD <br>To the grave <br>To the grave <br>To the grave <br>To the grave <br>Still marching on]]></content><category term="Vader" label="Vader"/><category term="Triumph Of Death (Live)" label="Triumph Of Death (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Saxon/Battering_Ram_Live/</id><title>Saxon - Battering Ram (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Saxon/Battering_Ram_Live/" title="Saxon - Battering Ram (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come worship at the metal church <br>Let your voices rise as one <br>Stand before the barricades <br>Prepare yourself for what's to come <br>These walls will resonate tonight <br>To the sound of screaming hordes <br><br>Decibels will rise above to fill this concert hall <br>Are you ready to begin then let the hammer fall <br>Like a battering ram <br>Like a battering ram <br>Like a battering ram <br><br>These walls will turn to dust tonight <br>Long before the aftershock <br>Foundations crack the buildings shake <br>Reverberating pounding rock <br>Through the smoke you hear the sound <br>The sound of metal striking steel <br><br>Do you feel adrenaline <br>Racing through your heart <br>Take it up to overload <br>Let's tear this place apart <br>Like a battering ram <br>Like a battering ram <br>Like a battering ram <br><br>Let our voices fill the hall <br>Like we've never done before <br>Let me hear your battle call <br>Oh oh oh let me hear your battle call <br>Oh oh oh let me hear you one and all <br><br>Welcome to the house of steel <br>This is where we stand or fall <br>Capturing the atmosphere <br>Trapped inside these hallowed halls <br>We stand inside this metal church <br>Together now we are reborn <br><br>Decibels will rise above <br>Breaking down the walls <br>Crank it up to overload <br>Watch the hammer fall <br>Like a battering ram <br>Like a battering ram <br>Battering ram]]></content><category term="Saxon" label="Saxon"/><category term="Battering Ram (Live)" label="Battering Ram (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hamatom/Alte_Liebe_Rostet_Nicht_Live/</id><title>Hamatom - Alte Liebe Rostet Nicht (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:49:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:49:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hamatom/Alte_Liebe_Rostet_Nicht_Live/" title="Hamatom - Alte Liebe Rostet Nicht (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ich war jung von Angst zerfressen <br>Als mich dieser Lichtstrahl traf <br>Hielt sie im Arm fast engelsgleich <br>Wie einst ein K?nig der sich seiner Magd unterwarf <br><br>Sie war so rein und voller Zier <br>Hielt fest die Unschuld in der Hand <br>Bis wir die ersten Schritte wagten <br>In ein fremdes Land <br><br>Die Engel sprechen ein Gedicht <br>Alte Liebe rostet nicht <br>Die Sonne zeigt mir ihr Gesicht <br>Alte Liebe rostet nicht <br><br>Tiefe Narben langsam heilen <br>Gedanken noch sehr lang verweilen <br>Bis der Fr?hling lachend spricht <br>Alte liebe rostet nicht <br><br>Als der Docht der achten Kerze <br>Wie ein Baum im Sturm zerbrach <br>Erlosch im Haus die letzte Glut <br>Legte sich Asche wie ein grauer Schleier ?bers Dach <br><br>Seitdem probierte ich gen?gend <br>Verbotene Fr?chte laut und still <br>Doch was n?tzen tausend Messer <br>Wenn man eine Gabel will <br><br>Ungeachtet der Gezeiten <br>Die hart am Denkmal nagen <br>Werden Herzen auch nach Jahren <br>M?helos im Gleichschritt schlagen <br><br>Zwei Seelen schlagen in der Brust <br>Eine Liebe andere Frust <br>Und will ich einmal gl?cklich werden <br>Muss eine von den Beiden sterben]]></content><category term="Hamatom" label="Hamatom"/><category term="Alte Liebe Rostet Nicht (Live)" label="Alte Liebe Rostet Nicht (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/희현/이젠/</id><title>희현 - 이젠 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9D%AC%ED%98%84/%EC%9D%B4%EC%A0%A0/" title="희현 - 이젠 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이젠 만날 수가 없지만 <br>벌써 보고 싶어요 <br>내가 받았던 사랑 <br>그대에게 아직 갚지도 못했는데 <br>그 동안 함께한 그 시간들 <br>너무 눈물이 나요 <br>한번 단 한번만 <br>그댈 볼 수 있다면 <br>그대 숨소리까지 기억할게요 <br>그대 웃어주던 그 미소 <br>그대 날 감싸주던 그 두 손 <br>보고 싶어 미치겠어 <br>그리워서 미치겠어 <br>이젠 나 자신이 없어 <br>우리 함께한 그 시간들 <br>너무 생각이 나요 <br>행복한 추억만 내가 기억할게요 <br>그대 아픈 기억은 놓고 가세요 <br>그대가 불러주던 노랫말 <br>그대와 즐겨가던 그 식당 <br>보고 싶어 미치겠어 <br>그리워서 미치겠어 <br>이젠 나 자신이 없어 <br>보고 싶어 미치겠어 <br>그리워서 미치겠어 <br>이젠 널 볼 수가 없어 <br>이젠 나 자신이 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="희현" label="희현"/><category term="이젠" label="이젠"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/랄랄라_모양_여행/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 랄랄라 모양 여행 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%9E%84%EB%9E%84%EB%9D%BC_%EB%AA%A8%EC%96%91_%EC%97%AC%ED%96%89/" title="핑크퐁 - 랄랄라 모양 여행 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세모 네모 동그라미 <br>길쭉한 긴네모 긴동그라미 <br>뾰족한 마름모 하트와 별 <br>랄랄라 신나는 모양 여행 <br>둥근 달 둥근 공 <br>빙글 빙글 차 바퀴 <br>동그라미 트랄랄랄라 <br>피자박스 와플 <br>토스트 냠냠냠 <br>네모 트랄랄랄라 <br>세모 네모 동그라미 <br>길쭉한 긴네모 긴동그라미 <br>뾰족한 마름모 하트와 별 <br>랄랄라 신나는 모양 여행 <br>고깔 모자 샌드위치 <br>돛단배 통통통 <br>세모 트랄랄랄라 <br>동화책 <br>퍼즐과 문 똑똑똑 <br>긴네모 트랄랄랄라 <br>세모 네모 동그라미 <br>길쭉한 긴네모 긴동그라미 <br>뾰족한 마름모 하트와 별 <br>랄랄라 신나는 모양 여행 <br>포도알 달걀 <br>둥실둥실 풍선 <br>긴동그라미 트랄랄랄라 <br>표지판 목걸이 <br>훨훨 가오리 연 <br>마름모 트랄랄랄라 <br>세모 네모 동그라미 <br>길쭉한 긴네모 긴동그라미 <br>뾰족한 마름모 하트와 별 <br>랄랄라 신나는 모양 여행 <br>불가사리 <br>반짝반짝 작은 별 <br>별 모양 트랄랄랄라 <br>과자와 토끼풀 <br>두근두근 내 마음 <br>하트하트 트랄랄랄라 <br>랄랄 랄랄랄 랄랄 랄랄라 <br>함께 떠나는 모양 여행]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="랄랄라 모양 여행" label="랄랄라 모양 여행"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/핑크퐁_모양_그리기/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 핑크퐁! 모양 그리기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81_%EB%AA%A8%EC%96%91_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EA%B8%B0/" title="핑크퐁 - 핑크퐁! 모양 그리기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모양 그리기 <br>시작 <br>동그라미 <br>빙글 돌아 제자리 <br>빙글 돌아 제자리 <br>빙글 돌아 제자리 <br>동그라미 <br>네모 <br>옆 아래 옆 위로 <br>옆 아래 옆 위로 <br>옆 아래 옆 위로 <br>네모 <br>세모 <br>산을 그리고 옆으로 <br>산을 그리고 옆으로 <br>산을 그리고 옆으로 <br>세모 <br>긴네모 <br>길게 짧게 길게 짧게 <br>길게 짧게 길게 짧게 <br>길게 짧게 길게 짧게 <br>긴네모 <br>모양 그리기 <br>긴 동그라미 <br>길게 빙글 제자리 <br>길게 빙글 제자리 <br>길게 빙글 제자리 <br>긴 동그라미 <br>별 <br>산을 그리고 하나 둘 셋 <br>산을 그리고 하나 둘 셋 <br>산을 그리고 하나 둘 셋 <br>반짝 별 <br>하트 <br>언덕 넘고 한번 더 <br>언덕 넘고 한번 더 <br>언덕 넘고 한번 더 <br>하트 <br>다이아몬드 <br>산을 넘고 땅 속 지나 <br>산을 넘고 땅 속 지나 <br>산을 넘고 땅 속 지나 <br>다이야몬드 <br>모양 그리기]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="핑크퐁! 모양 그리기" label="핑크퐁! 모양 그리기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/모양_따라_춤춰요/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 모양 따라 춤춰요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%AA%A8%EC%96%91_%EB%94%B0%EB%9D%BC_%EC%B6%A4%EC%B6%B0%EC%9A%94/" title="핑크퐁 - 모양 따라 춤춰요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[빙글빙글 동그라미 <br>빙글빙글 동그라미 <br>빙글빙글 돌려요. <br>나를 따라 이렇게 동그라미 춤춰요 <br>쿵쿵 네모 <br>쿵쿵 쿵쿵 네모 <br>발을 쿵쿵 굴러요 <br>나를 따라 이렇게 네모 춤춰요 <br>쭉쭉 세모 <br>쭉쭉 세모 <br>팔을 쭉쭉 늘려요 <br>나를 따라 이렇게 세모 춤춰요 <br>콕콕 다이아몬드 <br>콕콕 콕콕 다이아몬드 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 콕콕 콕 <br>나를 따라 이렇게 콕콕 콕콕콕 <br>반짝반짝 별 <br>반짝 반짝 작은 별 <br>예쁘게 흔들어요. <br>나를 따라 이렇게 반짝반짝 <br>사랑해 하트 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>하트 춤을 춰봐요. <br>나를 따라 이렇게 <br>사랑해]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="모양 따라 춤춰요" label="모양 따라 춤춰요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/모양_서커스/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 모양 서커스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%AA%A8%EC%96%91_%EC%84%9C%EC%BB%A4%EC%8A%A4/" title="핑크퐁 - 모양 서커스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자, 모양 서커스단을 소개합니다. <br>동그라미 세모 <br>동그라미 세모 <br>동그라미 <br>다음은? <br>세모 <br>좋아요! <br>세모 네모 네모 <br>세모 네모 네모 <br>세모, 네모 <br>다음은? <br>네모 <br>이번엔 더 어렵게! <br>긴네모 긴네모 긴 동그라미 <br>긴네모 긴네모 긴 동그라미 <br>긴네모 긴네모 <br>그다음? <br>긴 동그라미]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="모양 서커스" label="모양 서커스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/동그라미를_만들자/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 동그라미를 만들자 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%8F%99%EA%B7%B8%EB%9D%BC%EB%AF%B8%EB%A5%BC_%EB%A7%8C%EB%93%A4%EC%9E%90/" title="핑크퐁 - 동그라미를 만들자 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세모를 만들자 <br>세모를 만들자 <br>큰 세모 작은 세모 <br>크게 크게 <br>작게 작게 <br>세모를 만들자 <br>동그라미를 만들자 <br>동그라미를 만들자 <br>위로 위로 <br>아래 아래로 <br>위 위 <br>아래 아래 <br>동그라미를 만들자 <br>네모를 만들자 <br>네모를 만들자 <br>하나 둘 셋 <br>하나 둘 셋 <br>웃어봐! <br>치즈 <br>네모를 만들자]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="동그라미를 만들자" label="동그라미를 만들자"/></entry></feed>