<feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:16:56+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ferry/Take_Me_Back_Feat_SIJEL/</id><title>Ferry - Take Me Back (Feat. SIJEL) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:16:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:16:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ferry/Take_Me_Back_Feat_SIJEL/" title="Ferry - Take Me Back (Feat. SIJEL) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Take me back <br>to your love <br>to your arms <br>to your hug <br>Hold me back <br>gimme love <br>make me alive <br>make me rise <br>Don't ever go I need you so <br>In sunshine and in darkness <br>I know your love will make me go <br>will make me go <br>My heart will break if you go <br>Can I tell you I love you so <br>Take me back you can save me so <br>grab my hand and take me back <br>grab my hand and take me back <br>take me back <br>Take me back <br>to your love <br>to your arms <br>to your hug <br>Hold me back <br>gimme love <br>make me alive <br>make me rise <br>Don't ever go I need you so <br>In sunshine and in darkness <br>I know your love will make me go <br>will make me go <br>My heart will break if you go <br>Can I tell you I love you so <br>Take me back you can save me so <br>grab my hand and take me back <br>grab my hand and take me back <br>take me back <br>]]></content><category term="Ferry" label="Ferry"/><category term="Take Me Back (Feat. SIJEL)" label="Take Me Back (Feat. SIJEL)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_블루/월화수목금토일_With_윤혜선/</id><title>PD 블루 - 월화수목금토일 (With 윤혜선) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:18:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:18:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8/%EC%9B%94%ED%99%94%EC%88%98%EB%AA%A9%EA%B8%88%ED%86%A0%EC%9D%BC_With_%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/" title="PD 블루 - 월화수목금토일 (With 윤혜선) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[월화수목금토일 난 듣고 싶어 <br>월화수목금토일 늘 보고 싶어 <br>그댈 사랑해 너만 사랑해요 <br>내 눈에는 너만 보여 <br>뒤돌아서면 보고 싶고 하루라도 <br>못 보면 미칠 것만 같고 <br>널 처음 만난 그날보다 지금이 <br>오히려 더 좋은 것만 같아 <br>니 생각에 흐뭇한 24시간 1440분 <br>그대 이름만 불러도 벅찬 86400초 <br>월요일은 원래 만나는 날 <br>화요일은 화창하게 <br>수요일은 수수하게 <br>목요일은 목 빠져라 기다려 <br>금요일은 금방 갔음 좋겠어 <br>토요일은 토끼 같은 그댈 안고 <br>일요일은 그댈 위해 요리해 <br>내 다이어리 스케줄은 <br>매일 매일 그댈 위해 준비해 <br>월화수목금토일 난 듣고 싶어 <br>월화수목금토일 늘 보고 싶어 <br>그댈 사랑해 너만 사랑해요 <br>내 눈에는 너만 보여 <br>월화수목금토일 난 듣고 싶어 <br>월화수목금토일 늘 보고 싶어 <br>그댈 사랑해 너만 사랑해요 <br>내 눈에는 너만 보여 <br>Everyday Everytime <br>이젠 니가 없으면 어색해 <br>Everything 니 모든 게 익숙해져 <br>편안해져 더 좋아 <br>널 알기 전에 나 어땠더라 <br>이젠 기억도 잘 나질 않아 <br>니가 없는 나의 하루는 <br>상상조차 할 수 없는 우웩 <br>월요일은 원래 만나는 날 <br>화요일은 화창하게 <br>수요일은 수수하게 <br>목요일은 목 빠져라 기다려 <br>금요일은 금방 갔음 좋겠어 <br>토요일은 토끼 같은 그댈 안고 <br>일요일은 그댈 위해 요리해 <br>내 다이어리 스케줄은 <br>매일 매일 그댈 위해 준비해 <br>월화수목금토일 난 듣고 싶어 <br>월화수목금토일 늘 보고 싶어 <br>그댈 사랑해 너만 사랑해요 <br>내 눈에는 너만 보여 <br>월화수목금토일 난 듣고 싶어 <br>월화수목금토일 늘 보고 싶어 <br>그댈 사랑해 너만 사랑해요 <br>내 눈에는 너만 보여 <br>월요일부터 보고 싶어 <br>화요일도 니 생각이 가득해 <br>수요일엔 달콤한 니 꿈을 꾸고 <br>목요일도 니 사진만 바라봐 <br>금요일엔 그대와 맥주한잔 <br>토요일은 와인에 멋진 음악 틀고 <br>그대와 나만의 화끈한 파티 <br>일요일엔 알콩달콩 달콤해 <br>너무 좋아 행복해 <br>월화수목금토일 난 듣고 싶어 <br>월화수목금토일 늘 보고 싶어 <br>그댈 사랑해 너만 사랑해요 <br>내 눈에는 너만 보여 <br>월화수목금토일 난 듣고 싶어 <br>월화수목금토일 늘 보고 싶어 <br>그댈 사랑해 너만 사랑해요 <br>내 눈에는 너만 보여 <br>]]></content><category term="PD 블루" label="PD 블루"/><category term="월화수목금토일 (With 윤혜선)" label="월화수목금토일 (With 윤혜선)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_블루/One_sided_lover_With_윤혜선/</id><title>PD 블루 - One sided lover (With 윤혜선) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:18:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:18:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8/One_sided_lover_With_%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/" title="PD 블루 - One sided lover (With 윤혜선) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[혼자 떠드는게 이젠 습관이 됐어 <br>니 웃는 사진 보다가 <br>미친 사람처럼 웃다 <br>애써 외면해도 떠오르는 니가 또 <br>다시 후벼 파는 내 가슴에 울다 <br>오늘 하루가 길고도 또 길구나 <br>먹는 것도 마시는 것도 <br>니가 없으니까 괴롭기만 하구나 <br>힘들다는 말조차 꺼낼 수가 없구나 <br>어울리지 않는 단걸 알아 <br>많이 부족하단 것도 알아 <br>달궈진 내 맘 <br>오직 너 하나만을 위해 <br>날 위해 내려준 비가 <br>너무 너무나 고마운걸 <br>멀어져 간다 여전히 오늘도 <br>혼자 하는 사랑 <br>One Sided lover lover <br>투덜대면 Never Never <br>애원한다면 Ever Ever <br>니 곁에 있고 싶어 <br>One Sided lover lover <br>투덜대면 Never Never <br>애원한다면 Ever Ever <br>니 곁에 있고 싶어 <br>힘들다는 말도 이젠 <br>나도 정말 지겹다 <br>매일 매일 술에 무너져가는 <br>내가 아쉽다 <br>나란 놈은 언제나 <br>이 모냥에 이꼴 <br>너란 사람 붙잡지도 못해 <br>떠나고 후회해 <br>사랑 그까짓게 뭔데 <br>One sided lover <br>나는 너를 찾아 헤매 ever <br>그게 바로 우리 운명 인가 봐 <br>foever <br>다시 돌아올 수만 있다면 <br>my lover <br>내겐 너무 커다란걸 알아 <br>내가 너무 작단 것도 알아 <br>달궈진 내 맘 <br>오직 너 하나만을 위해 <br>우연히 마주친 니가 <br>자꾸 자꾸 눈에 아른거려 <br>멀어져간다 아마 내일도 <br>난 혼자하는 사랑 <br>One Sided lover lover <br>투덜대면 Never Never <br>애원한다면 Ever Ever <br>니 곁에 있고 싶어 <br>One Sided lover lover <br>투덜대면 Never Never <br>애원한다면 Ever Ever <br>니 옆에 있고 싶어 <br>시간이 흐르면 흘러 갈수록 <br>더욱 작아지는 걸 <br>아직도 난 혼자하는 사랑 <br>One Sided lover lover <br>투덜대면 Never Never <br>애원한다면 Ever Ever <br>니 곁에 있고 싶어 <br>One Sided lover lover <br>투덜대면 Never Never <br>애원한다면 Ever Ever <br>니 곁에 있고 싶어 <br>]]></content><category term="PD 블루" label="PD 블루"/><category term="One sided lover (With 윤혜선)" label="One sided lover (With 윤혜선)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_블루/울어도_울어도_With_윤혜선/</id><title>PD 블루 - 울어도 울어도 (With 윤혜선) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:18:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:18:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8/%EC%9A%B8%EC%96%B4%EB%8F%84_%EC%9A%B8%EC%96%B4%EB%8F%84_With_%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/" title="PD 블루 - 울어도 울어도 (With 윤혜선) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[울어도 울어도 씻겨지지 않는건 <br>그댈 향한 내사랑 영원한 추억입니다 <br>지워도 지워도 지워지지 않는건 <br>그댈 향한 내마음 간절한 사랑입니다 <br>어제만해도 몰랐죠 <br>이렇게 가슴 아플 줄 <br>사랑이 이렇게 쉽게 떠난다는 걸 <br>몇 번의 이별과 몇 번의 시련에 <br>강해진 줄 알았죠 물러터진 내 심장 <br>한없이 울어도 씻겨지지 않는건 <br>아무리 지워도 지워지지 않는건 <br>허전한 그대의 흔적들이라는 게 <br>사랑한 추억의 무게만큼이라고 <br>울어도 울어도 씻겨지지 않는건 <br>그댈 향한 내사랑 영원한 추억입니다 <br>지워도 지워도 지워지지 않는건 <br>그댈 향한 내마음 간절한 사랑입니다 <br>오늘 하루는 왜 이렇게 <br>길고 허전한걸까 <br>떠난 이유는 제대로 묻지도 못하고 <br>사랑한 마음도 가져 갈순 없을까 <br>정말 날 사랑하긴 했는지 <br>한없이 울어도 씻겨지지 않는건 <br>아무리 지워도 지워지지 않는건 <br>허전한 그대의 흔적들이라는 게 <br>사랑한 추억의 무게만큼이라고 <br>떠나가던 마지막 그대의 모습 <br>기억하기 싫어 눈 감아버렸죠 <br>사랑해서 떠난다는 그말 <br>듣기 싫어서 귀를 닫아버렸죠 <br>울어도 울어도 씻겨지지 않는건 <br>그댈 향한 내사랑 영원한 추억입니다 <br>지워도 지워도 지워지지 않는건 <br>그댈 향한 내마음 간절한 사랑입니다 <br>울어도 울어도 씻겨지지 않는건 <br>그댈 향한 내사랑 영원한 추억입니다 <br>]]></content><category term="PD 블루" label="PD 블루"/><category term="울어도 울어도 (With 윤혜선)" label="울어도 울어도 (With 윤혜선)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_블루/메리투게더_With_윤혜선/</id><title>PD 블루 - 메리투게더 (With 윤혜선) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:18:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:18:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8/%EB%A9%94%EB%A6%AC%ED%88%AC%EA%B2%8C%EB%8D%94_With_%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/" title="PD 블루 - 메리투게더 (With 윤혜선) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 이제 더 이상 바랄게 없어 <br>날 보며 웃어주는 <br>니가 있으니까 <br>굿모닝 키스하고 <br>매일 같이 잠을 자고 <br>평생을 다 바쳐서 <br>메리 투게더 <br>사랑은 불쑥 내게 <br>찾아온거야 <br>언제나 꿈꿔왔던 <br>마법 같은 일 <br>첫눈을 바라보며 <br>소원을 빌었죠 <br>이제는 현실이 된거야 <br>나 역시 더 이상 바랄게 없어 <br>내 곁엔 천사같은 <br>니가 있으니까 <br>사랑해 속삭이고 <br>마주 보며 밥을 먹고 <br>평생을 다 바쳐서 <br>메리 투게더 <br>가끔씩 괴롭고 <br>힘들때도 있겠지 <br>그럴때면 첫눈의 기적 떠올려 <br>언제나 기다렸던 <br>마법 같은 일 <br>이제는 현실이 된거야 <br>난 이제 더 이상 <br>바랄게 없어 <br>날 보며 웃어주는 <br>니가 있으니까 <br>굿모닝 키스하고 <br>매일 같이 잠을 자고 <br>평생을 다 바쳐서 <br>메리 투게더 <br>사랑은 행운처럼 <br>찾아온거야 <br>언제나 꿈꿔왔던 <br>마법 같은 일 <br>겨울이 올때마다 <br>가슴이 설레죠 <br>사랑이 이루어 진거야 <br>난 이제 더 이상 바랄게 없어 <br>날 보며 웃어주는 <br>니가 있으니까 <br>사랑해 속삭이고 <br>마주 보며 밥을 먹고 <br>평생을 다 바쳐서 <br>메리 투게더 메리 투게더 <br>]]></content><category term="PD 블루" label="PD 블루"/><category term="메리투게더 (With 윤혜선)" label="메리투게더 (With 윤혜선)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_블루/새벽3시_With_윤혜선/</id><title>PD 블루 - 새벽3시 (With 윤혜선) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:18:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:18:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8/%EC%83%88%EB%B2%BD3%EC%8B%9C_With_%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/" title="PD 블루 - 새벽3시 (With 윤혜선) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[조용히 그대 이름을 불러봐도 <br>사랑을 외쳐봐도 그대는 아직인가봐 <br>난 못났어 그게 나라서 미안해 <br>그래도 이럴 수 있어 <br>어떻게 이럴 수 있어 <br>이미 다 다 끝난 얘기 <br>멀리 넌 넌 떠나버렸고 <br>그게 누구 잘못인지 <br>그게 뭐가 중요한지 <br>사랑 자체가 끝이 있는 건데 <br>그 끝이 이별이라는데 <br>나 역시 자존심 너무 쎄 <br>끝내 널 붙잡지도 못해 <br>밤새 널 그리워해봤자 <br>이제 겨우 새벽3시야 <br>그게 바로 현실이야 <br>니가 없는 텅 빈 이방 <br>난 어디로 가야 하나 <br>난 어디에 빠져 울고 있어 <br>비가 그치는 날이 오기나 할까 baby <br>난 어디에 가려질까 두려워 <br>나 그대를 잊지 못해서야 <br>가만히 그대 생각에 빠져보고 <br>발버둥을 쳐봐도 나는 아직인가봐 <br>참 못났어 나에게 너무 미안해 <br>바보 같은 날 만나 오늘도 너만 찾아 <br>술 기운을 빌려 눌러본다 <br>원모어타임 눌러봐도 <br>끝없이 귓가에 맴도는 메아린 <br>쓴 소주만 찾아 <br>정신 나간 사람처럼 중얼거려본다 <br>그래도 사랑했다고 <br>아직도 사랑한다고 그게 진심이라고 <br>어디서부터 잘못됐나 <br>새벽이 지나면 끝일 것만 같아 <br>자존심 모두 내려놔도 <br>그 사람은 떠나가네 <br>난 어디로 가야 하나 <br>난 어디에 빠져 울고 있어 <br>비가 그치는 날이 오기나 할까 baby <br>난 어디에 가려질까 <br>난 어디로 가야 하나 <br>난 어디에 빠져 울고 있어 <br>비가 그치는 날이 오기나 할까 baby <br>난 어디에 가려질까 두려워 <br>나 그대를 잊지 못해서야 <br>]]></content><category term="PD 블루" label="PD 블루"/><category term="새벽3시 (With 윤혜선)" label="새벽3시 (With 윤혜선)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_블루/치료해줄래요_With_윤혜선/</id><title>PD 블루 - 치료해줄래요 (With 윤혜선) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:18:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:18:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8/%EC%B9%98%EB%A3%8C%ED%95%B4%EC%A4%84%EB%9E%98%EC%9A%94_With_%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/" title="PD 블루 - 치료해줄래요 (With 윤혜선) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너와의 스토리 이제는 저 멀리 <br>떠나가도 돼 이젠 거짓말이 아니야 <br>너와의 스토리 이제는 저 멀리 <br>떠나가도 돼 너 하나쯤 <br>잊어버리면 돼 <br>나 맘에 드는 사람 이제 내게 와봐요 <br>내 맘 치료해줄래요 이제 <br>사랑하나 못 믿는데 어떻하나요 <br>날 다시 돌려 줄래 <br>너와의 스토리 이제는 저 멀리 <br>떠나가도 돼 이젠 거짓말이 아니야 <br>너와의 스토리 이제는 저 멀리 <br>떠나가도 돼 너 하나쯤 <br>잊어버리면 돼 <br>나 맘에 드는 사람 <br>이제 내게 와 봐요 <br>내 맘 치료해줄래요 이제 <br>사랑하나 못 믿는데 어떻하나요 <br>날 다시 돌려줄래 <br>바보 같은 나야 누굴 원망하니 <br>다시는 이런 사랑에 울지 않기 <br>살아가다보면 다 겪는 일이야 <br>다시는 이런 사랑 않할래 <br>나 맘에 드는 사람 <br>이제 내게 와 봐요 <br>내 맘 치료해줄래요 이제 <br>사랑하나 못 믿는데 어떻하나요 <br>날 다시 돌려 줄래 <br>]]></content><category term="PD 블루" label="PD 블루"/><category term="치료해줄래요 (With 윤혜선)" label="치료해줄래요 (With 윤혜선)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_블루/군화나_거꾸로_신지마_With_윤혜선/</id><title>PD 블루 - 군화나 거꾸로 신지마 (With 윤혜선) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:18:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:18:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8/%EA%B5%B0%ED%99%94%EB%82%98_%EA%B1%B0%EA%BE%B8%EB%A1%9C_%EC%8B%A0%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88_With_%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/" title="PD 블루 - 군화나 거꾸로 신지마 (With 윤혜선) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기다려줄게 항상 <br>남자라서 가는 거잖아 <br>너야말로 군화나 거꾸로 신지마 <br>나도 절대 고무신 따윈 <br>거꾸로 신지는 않을 거야 <br>너야말로 군화나 거꾸로 신지마 <br>나 솔직히 너무 많이 떨려 <br>입대할 생각에 잠도 안 와 <br>밥도 못 먹어 <br>적당히 핑계 대고 <br>빠졌으면 좋겠어 <br>사실 두려운 것도 있지만 <br>너랑 헤어지기 싫어서 그래 <br>니 얼굴 못 볼 세월이 <br>무엇보다 걱정돼서 그래 <br>요즘 군대는 편한 거라고 <br>돈도 많이 준다고 그래 <br>남자라면은 누구나 <br>당연히 갔다 와 <br>기다려줄게 항상 <br>남자라서 가는 거잖아 <br>너야말로 군화나 거꾸로 신지마 <br>나도 절대 고무신 따윈 <br>거꾸로 신지는 않을 거야 <br>너야말로 군화나 거꾸로 신지마 <br>나 솔직히 운동 너무 못해 <br>눈도 안 좋고 배도 나오고 <br>푸샵도 아예 못하고 <br>그런데도 신검 1급이야 <br>키 180에 미남 <br>우리 학교 킹카 <br>그 놈도 공익인데 <br>나 이런 놈야 <br>어때 나 멋있지 않냐 <br>요즘 군대는 편한 거라고 <br>돈도 많이 준다고 그래 <br>남자라면은 누구나 <br>당연히 갔다 와 <br>기다려줄게 항상 <br>남자라서 가는 거잖아 <br>너야말로 군화나 거꾸로 신지마 <br>나도 절대 고무신 따윈 <br>거꾸로 신지는 않을 거야 <br>너야말로 군화나 거꾸로 신지마 <br>기다려줄게 항상 <br>남자라서 가는 거잖아 <br>너야말로 군화나 거꾸로 신지마 <br>나도 절대 고무신 따윈 <br>거꾸로 신지는 않을 거야 <br>너야말로 군화나 거꾸로 신지마 <br>]]></content><category term="PD 블루" label="PD 블루"/><category term="군화나 거꾸로 신지마 (With 윤혜선)" label="군화나 거꾸로 신지마 (With 윤혜선)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_블루/미안해_이_한마디로_With_윤혜선/</id><title>PD 블루 - 미안해 이 한마디로 (With 윤혜선) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:18:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:18:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8/%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%88%ED%95%B4_%EC%9D%B4_%ED%95%9C%EB%A7%88%EB%94%94%EB%A1%9C_With_%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/" title="PD 블루 - 미안해 이 한마디로 (With 윤혜선) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[미안해 이 한마디로 <br>마지막 순간이 우리의 사이가 <br>이렇게 쉬웠던지 <br>이 오랜 시간들이 <br>눈 앞에서 안녕 <br>이제는 끝나버렸어 <br>니가 알던 사람은 없어 <br>영원할 것 같던 사랑도 끝났어 <br>너란 사람 이젠 지긋지긋해 <br>여기서 끝내 미안해 할 말 없어 <br>우리가 함께했던 <br>시간은 여기까지 <br>서로가 바래왔던 <br>미래도 여기까지 <br>영원한 사랑 따윈 없는 거니까 <br>어차피 추억 따윈 잊었으니까 <br>또 생각이나 <br>우리의 어색했던 <br>그 첫만남에 부끄러워서 <br>그래 그땐 나도 그랬었나봐 <br>널 제대로 못 보고 웃기만 했던 <br>바보 같던 내 모습들이 <br>지금 내가 바보 같아 <br>또 눈물이나 <br>어느새 멀어져 있는 <br>너를 보며 서운한 맘에 <br>알아 헌데 어쩔 수가 없나봐 <br>목소리 높이며 <br>반복된 다툼에 지쳐서 <br>초라해 지는 건 <br>어쩔 수가 없나봐 <br>사랑이 서로에 대한 <br>구속이 되고 <br>이별이 행복해 지는 <br>방법이 되고 <br>혼자가 편할 거라고 <br>기대하는 것이 <br>사랑은 끝났다라고 <br>결론 내는 것이 <br>차라리 행복해지는 지름길이야 <br>이제는 돌이킬 수 없는 거잖아 <br>너의 끊임없는 구속이 <br>날 미치게 해 <br>가식적으로 <br>행동하는 것도 지쳐가 <br>무더운 나날들이 계속 돼 <br>타들어가는 내 마음과 같아 <br>어디서부터 우리의 마음이 <br>멀어져 가버린 건지 <br>또 생각이나 <br>우리의 어색했던 <br>그 첫만남에 부끄러워서 <br>그래 그땐 나도 그랬었나봐 <br>널 제대로 못 보고 웃기만 했던 <br>바보 같던 내 모습들이 <br>지금 내가 바보 같아 <br>또 눈물이나 <br>어느새 멀어져 있는 <br>너를 보며 서운한 맘에 <br>알아 헌데 어쩔 수가 없나봐 <br>목소리 높이며 <br>반복된 다툼에 지쳐서 <br>초라해 지는 건 <br>어쩔 수가 없나봐 <br>시간이 지나 다시 만나면 <br>서로에게 돌아오자던 <br>이젠 그 약속 작은 마음도 숨겨둘게 <br>난 웃음이나 <br>날 보고 환하게 <br>미소만 지었던 <br>니 심장 소리에 <br>내 가슴이 뛰어 <br>서로만 보았던 <br>우리를 기억해낼수록 <br>널 생각하면 <br>한참을 멍하니 <br>움직일 수 없어 <br>내 이기심에 <br>난 널 놓아줬어 <br>어쩔 수 없나봐 <br>이런 나와 함께 해줘서 <br>정말 고마웠어요 <br>미안해 이런 내가 바보 같아 <br>]]></content><category term="PD 블루" label="PD 블루"/><category term="미안해 이 한마디로 (With 윤혜선)" label="미안해 이 한마디로 (With 윤혜선)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_블루/내_맘도_아파요_With_윤혜선/</id><title>PD 블루 - 내 맘도 아파요 (With 윤혜선) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:18:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:18:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8/%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%98%EB%8F%84_%EC%95%84%ED%8C%8C%EC%9A%94_With_%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/" title="PD 블루 - 내 맘도 아파요 (With 윤혜선) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[만일 나 다시 사랑할 수만 있다면 <br>그때도 내 사랑은 당연히 또 넌데 <br>언제나 너의 숨결을 <br>느껴 보고 싶어 <br>그게 바로 운명이라 <br>생각했던 우리 인연 <br>참 힘들게도 <br>내 가슴 아프게 한 사람 <br>더 슬프게도 <br>내 눈물 마르게 한 사람 <br>잊을 줄 알았는데 <br>괜찮을 줄 알았는데 <br>시간이 해결할 줄 알았는데 <br>그댈 생각하면 내 맘도 아파요 <br>나도 모르게 눈물도 흐르는 걸요 <br>우리 추억 떠오를 때마다 <br>그냥 한편의 영화를 감상하듯이 <br>다른 사람 얘기라고 생각해줘요 <br>그래야 나도 편히 <br>떠날 수 있으니까 <br>참 아프게도 <br>자존심 버리게 한 사람 <br>더 쓰리게도 <br>마지막 사랑이 돼버린 사람 <br>잊었다 믿었는데 <br>아플 줄은 몰랐는데 <br>시간이 해결할 줄 알았는데 <br>다른 사랑을 만나면 <br>널 잊을 거라 생각했어 <br>아무리 노력해도 <br>그게 나는 안 되나봐 <br>왜 떠났니 <br>한마디 물어보지도 못하고 <br>니 뒷모습만 바라보다 <br>멍하니 울고야 말았어 <br>그댈 생각하면 내 맘도 아파요 <br>나도 모르게 눈물도 흐르는 걸요 <br>우리 추억 떠오를 때마다 <br>그냥 한편의 영화를 감상하듯이 <br>다른 사람 얘기라고 생각해줘요 <br>그댈 생각하면 내 맘도 아파요 <br>나도 모르게 눈물도 흐르는 걸요 <br>우리 추억 떠오를 때마다 <br>그냥 한편의 영화를 감상하듯이 <br>다른 사람 얘기라고 생각해줘요 <br>그래야 나도 편히 <br>떠날 수 있으니까 <br>]]></content><category term="PD 블루" label="PD 블루"/><category term="내 맘도 아파요 (With 윤혜선)" label="내 맘도 아파요 (With 윤혜선)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_블루/모르는_척_With_윤혜선/</id><title>PD 블루 - 모르는 척 (With 윤혜선) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:18:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:18:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PD_%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8/%EB%AA%A8%EB%A5%B4%EB%8A%94_%EC%B2%99_With_%EC%9C%A4%ED%98%9C%EC%84%A0/" title="PD 블루 - 모르는 척 (With 윤혜선) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>이렇게 널 사랑해 <br>누가 뭐래도 나는 너 하나 뿐야 <br>이런 내 마음이 시킨 사랑을 <br>어떻게 너에게 전할 수 있을까 <br>사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>이렇게 널 사랑해 <br>얼마나 사랑해야 날 알아줄까 <br>용기가 없어 말하지 못하고 <br>어떻게 해야 좋을지 몰라 워우워 <br>사랑한다는 말 <br>너무나 어려운 거야 <br>니 눈빛만 봐도 알아 <br>난 느낄 수가 있잖아 <br>알면서 또 모르는 척 <br>니가 다가와주기를 <br>난 기다릴 거야 용기 내 어서 <br>뭘 망설이니 <br>오늘도 니 생각에 <br>니 사진보다 잠이 들어 <br>꿈속에서 만난 너는 <br>어찌 그리 달콤한데 <br>니 입술은 달달한 <br>솜사탕보다도 달콤 새콤 <br>니 향기에 취한 건지 <br>잠에 취해 그런 건지 <br>매일 아침 날 설레게 하는 <br>니 카톡 카톡 <br>점심때면 스마일에 <br>즐점 즐점 하트 문자 <br>저녁은 같이 뭘 먹을까 <br>무슨 말을 할까 <br>헤어지기 싫은 시간은 <br>어느새 굿나잇 키스 <br>사랑한다는 말 <br>너무나 어려운 거야 <br>니 눈빛만 봐도 알아 <br>난 느낄 수가 있잖아 <br>알면서 또 모르는 척 <br>니가 다가와주기를 <br>난 기다릴 거야 용기 내 어서 <br>뭘 망설이니 <br>말하지 않아도 너를 느낄 수 있어 <br>이제는 걱정 하지마 이제 알아 <br>사랑한다는 말 <br>너무나 어려운 거야 <br>니 눈빛만 봐도 알아 <br>난 느낄 수가 있잖아 <br>알면서 또 모르는 척 <br>니가 다가와주기를 <br>난 기다릴 거야 용기 내 어서 <br>뭘 망설이니 <br>]]></content><category term="PD 블루" label="PD 블루"/><category term="모르는 척 (With 윤혜선)" label="모르는 척 (With 윤혜선)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/캐슈넛보이/말투/</id><title>캐슈넛보이 - 말투 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:18:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:18:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%88%EB%84%9B%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4/%EB%A7%90%ED%88%AC/" title="캐슈넛보이 - 말투 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가끔 우리 둘이 했었던 <br>말이 생각나 <br>남들이 알아듣지 못해도 <br>너와 나만의 말투 <br>다른 사람 만나면 젠틀한 척 <br>말을 지어내 <br>남들이 유치하다고 해도 <br>너와 나만의 말투 <br>따르릉 어디야 따르릉 뭐 하는데 <br>이젠 들을 수 없는 <br>너와 나만의 너무 그리운 <br>너와 나의 말투 <br>너와 나만의 그 말투 <br>너와 나의 말투 <br>너와 나만의 그 말투 <br>너와 나의 말투 <br>너와 나만의 그 말투 <br>사랑 우리 둘이 했었던 <br>그 날이 생각나 <br>둘이 만 알아들을 수 있게 <br>너와 나만의 말투 <br>같은 생각을 하고 시크한 척 <br>투정부리고 <br>둘이 만 그냥 우리 둘이 만 <br>너와 나만의 말투 <br>따르릉 어디야 따르릉 뭐 하는데 <br>이젠 들을 수 없는 <br>너와 나만의 너무 그리운 <br>너와 나의 말투 <br>너와 나만의 그 말투 <br>너와 나의 말투 <br>너와 나만의 그 말투 <br>너와 나의 말투 <br>너와 나만의 그 말투 <br>너와 나의 말투 <br>너와 나만의 그 말투 <br>너와 나의 말투 <br>너와 나만의 그 말투 <br>너와 나의 말투 <br>너와 나만의 그 말투 <br>]]></content><category term="캐슈넛보이" label="캐슈넛보이"/><category term="말투" label="말투"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김민경/잊어줘_Prod_서경교/</id><title>김민경 - 잊어줘 (Prod. 서경교) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:22:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:22:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%AF%BC%EA%B2%BD/%EC%9E%8A%EC%96%B4%EC%A4%98_Prod_%EC%84%9C%EA%B2%BD%EA%B5%90/" title="김민경 - 잊어줘 (Prod. 서경교) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언제까지나 <br>예쁘고 멋있을 것 같지만 <br>내꺼가 되면 <br>모든 게 싫증이 나버려 <br>언제까지나 <br>사랑할 거라고 말하지만 <br>그건 모두 더러운 거짓들이지 <br>좋을 때보다도 <br>나쁠 때 더 잘 해야 한다고 <br>그래 이제 나도 그러지 않을 거야 <br>내 생각 같을 줄 알았어 <br>날 잊어줘 <br>이젠 너를 안고 싶지 않아 <br>그래 정말 정말 그래 <br>날 잊어줘 <br>이젠 너를 사랑하지 않아 <br>그래 정말 정말 그래 <br>붙잡아도 소용없어 <br>이젠 지쳐버린 거야 <br>날 사랑하긴 한 거니 <br>안고 싶긴 했니 <br>언제까지나 <br>나만 바라볼 순 없겠니 <br>니꺼가 된 난 니가 멀어져 보여 <br>언제까지나 <br>사랑할 거라고 믿었던 난 <br>그건 모두 바보 같은 생각들이지 <br>좋을 때보다도 <br>나쁠 때 더 잘해야 한다고 <br>그래 이제 나도 그러지 않을 거야 <br>내 생각 같은 줄 알았어 <br>날 잊어줘 <br>이젠 너를 안고 싶지 않아 <br>그래 정말 정말 그래 <br>날 잊어줘 <br>이젠 너를 사랑하지 않아 <br>그래 정말 정말 그래 <br>붙잡아도 소용없어 <br>이젠 지쳐버린 거야 <br>날 사랑하긴 한 거니 <br>안고 싶긴 했니 <br>날 잊어줘 <br>이젠 너를 안고 싶지 않아 <br>그래 정말 정말 그래 <br>날 잊어줘 <br>이젠 너를 사랑하지 않아 <br>그래 정말 정말 그래 <br>붙잡아도 소용없어 <br>이젠 지쳐버린 거야 <br>날 사랑하긴 한 거니 <br>안고 싶긴 했니 <br>]]></content><category term="김민경" label="김민경"/><category term="잊어줘 (Prod. 서경교)" label="잊어줘 (Prod. 서경교)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Spoiled_Child/시간이_춤을_춰/</id><title>Spoiled Child - 시간이 춤을 춰 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:22:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:22:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Spoiled_Child/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B0%84%EC%9D%B4_%EC%B6%A4%EC%9D%84_%EC%B6%B0/" title="Spoiled Child - 시간이 춤을 춰 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[tik tok <br>time is dancing in slow motion <br>between you and my moment <br>like father and daughter <br>drip drop <br>slowly wetting my emotion <br>like a drop of absolute <br>oh baby I'm fallen <br>너와 있을 때면 나의 시간은 멈춰 <br>everything just freezes <br>even no breeze <br>네가 날 볼 때면 나의 심장은 멈춰 <br>you make it freezes <br>how can i breathe <br>tik tok <br>time is dancing in slow motion <br>between you and my moment <br>like father and daughter <br>drip drop <br>slowly wetting my emotion <br>like a drop of absolute <br>oh baby I'm fallen <br>영원만이 남는 것 같애 <br>순간이 사라진 이 곳에 <br>우주보다 더 깊은 너의 눈을 <br>마주할 때 <br>태초의 시간인 것 같애 <br>모두 발가벗겨진 곳에 <br>어둠도 빛도 몰랐던 때로 <br>날 데려가네 <br>tik tok <br>time is dancing in slow motion <br>between you and my moment <br>like father and daughter <br>drip drop <br>slowly wetting my emotion <br>like a drop of absolute <br>oh baby I'm fallen <br>주위를 둘러 봐 <br>시간이 춤을 춰 <br>우리를 흐르는 시간만이 <br>느리게 왈츠를 춰 slow mo <br>멈춰진 시간에 <br>난 너란 꿈을 꿔 <br>잠을 자기 전에도 눈을 마주치며 <br>너란 꿈을 꿔 called love <br>너와 있을 때면 나의 시간은 멈춰 <br>everything just freezes <br>tik tok <br>time is dancing in slow motion <br>between u and my moment <br>like father and daughter <br>drip drop <br>slowly wetting my emotion <br>like a drop of absolute <br>oh baby I'm fallen <br>]]></content><category term="Spoiled Child" label="Spoiled Child"/><category term="시간이 춤을 춰" label="시간이 춤을 춰"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/후이크리스/일탈환생_逸脫還生/</id><title>후이크리스 - 일탈환생 (逸脫還生) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:23:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:23:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9B%84%EC%9D%B4%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%A4/%EC%9D%BC%ED%83%88%ED%99%98%EC%83%9D_%E9%80%B8%E8%84%AB%E9%82%84%E7%94%9F/" title="후이크리스 - 일탈환생 (逸脫還生) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[정해진 틀에 갖춰진 <br>내 삶이 계속 반복되지 <br>한 번쯤 꿈을 위해서 <br>틀을 벗어 날거야 <br>나를 되돌아 봐 의식하지 말고 <br>꿈을 되찾아 봐 하고픈거 하고 <br>이젠 걱정하지 말고 펼쳐봐 <br>니가 꿈꾸던 그 곳으로 <br>나는 다시 태어나 <br>꿈을 향해 달려가 <br>이 곳 저 곳 누비면서 <br>꿈을 찾아갈거야 <br>원하는 길을 걷고 <br>나는 다시 태어나 <br>꿈을 향해 달려가 <br>누가 뭐라 해도 <br>난 달려갈거야 <br>일탈환생 Hey <br>나를 되돌아 봐 의식하지 말고 <br>꿈을 되찾아 봐 하고픈거 하고 <br>이젠 걱정하지 말고 펼쳐봐 <br>니가 꿈꾸던 그 곳으로 <br>나를 되돌아 봐 의식하지 말고 <br>꿈을 되찾아 봐 하고픈거 하고 <br>이젠 걱정하지 말고 펼쳐봐 <br>니가 꿈꾸던 그 곳으로 <br>나는 다시 태어나 <br>꿈을 향해 달려가 <br>이 곳 저 곳 누비면서 <br>꿈을 찾아갈거야 <br>원하는 길을 걷고 <br>나는 다시 태어나 <br>꿈을 향해 달려가 <br>누가 뭐라 해도 <br>난 달려갈거야 <br>일탈환생 Hey <br>나는 다시 태어나 <br>꿈을 향해 달려가 <br>이 곳 저 곳 누비면서 <br>꿈을 찾아갈거야 <br>원하는 길을 걷고 <br>나는 다시 태어나 <br>꿈을 향해 달려가 <br>누가 뭐라 해도 <br>난 달려갈거야 <br>일탈환생 Hey <br>]]></content><category term="후이크리스" label="후이크리스"/><category term="일탈환생 (逸脫還生)" label="일탈환생 (逸脫還生)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤기타/우리의_여름/</id><title>윤기타 - 우리의 여름 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:23:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:23:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EA%B8%B0%ED%83%80/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EC%9D%98_%EC%97%AC%EB%A6%84/" title="윤기타 - 우리의 여름 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[봄에 살고 있는 사람과 <br>가을에 사는 사람은 <br>그 사이에 있는 여름을 <br>지나치지 않고 만날 수 없네 <br>한 번쯤 사람에게는 <br>사랑의 계절이 있네 <br>그때가 지금이라고 <br>느끼는 순간이 아름다운 것 <br>사람들은 짧은 봄을 <br>사랑의 계절이라 부르네 <br>그럼 우리가 견뎌낸 여름은 <br>어떻게 노래할 수 있을까 <br>한 번쯤 사람에게는 <br>사랑의 계절이 있네 <br>그때가 지금이라고 <br>말하는 순간이 아름다운 것 <br>한 번쯤 사람에게는 <br>사랑의 계절이 있네 <br>그 무엇이라도 좋으니 <br>가을 겨울 지나 봄이 와도 <br>나와 여름을 보내 주기를 <br>]]></content><category term="윤기타" label="윤기타"/><category term="우리의 여름" label="우리의 여름"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하프타운/이별/</id><title>하프타운 - 이별 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:23:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:23:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%ED%94%84%ED%83%80%EC%9A%B4/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84/" title="하프타운 - 이별 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[서로 젖은 두 눈을 <br>마주 바라보다 <br>보면 느끼는 <br>감정 기분 생각 모두 <br>똑같을 텐데 <br>누가 잘못한 건지 <br>누가 더 아프게 했는지 <br>감정 기분 생각 모두 <br>똑같을 텐데 <br>I don't want to live like this <br>I know nothing about that girl <br>너와 일년이 됐을 때 <br>선물로 불러주려 했는데 <br>결국 이별이 저물 땐 <br>어둔 밤하늘 만이 존재해 <br>힘들지 않어 I know <br>이 기분을 난 넘겨내기 위해 <br>또 성공을 다짐하며 <br>성숙한 내가 되는 거겠지 <br>오늘은 왠지 기분이 좋아 <br>니 노랠 만들려 <br>기억을 꺼내보니 <br>어느새 그 얇던 미소가 <br>떠올라 내 모습이 되었네 <br>니가 펴주던 구겨진 내 셔츠가 <br>거울에 퍼지던 내 미소가 <br>설레다가 울다가 웃다가 <br>집을 나섰네 <br>비가 오는 포차 안에 <br>혼자 있는 게 나 답답해서 <br>친구를 불러 내 얘기에 <br>안주에 취해가 <br>서로 곁을 떠나 <br>마주 등을 지고 흐느끼는 <br>감정 기분 생각 모두 <br>같았을 텐데 <br>I don't want to live like this <br>I know nothing about that girl <br>한잔하며 넋두리로 <br>날이 조금 추워졌다며 <br>술과 얘기로 온도를 올려 <br>떠난 사람 보내야지 <br>보고 싶어 취해보니 <br>날이 조금 추워졌다며 <br>어느새 니 사진을 꺼내 <br>너도 추울 텐데 <br>I don't want to live like this <br>I know nothing about that girl <br>아직 이렇게도 할 말이 많아 <br>또 너와 했던 얘기들은 <br>머물 곳을 찾아 <br>I don't respect what I do I never <br>지금의 내 모습 <br>그렇게도 당당했던 <br>내 모습만 기억하고 있겠지 넌 <br>하고 싶은 말 묻어둔 채 <br>지나와버린 모습 만을 만을 만을 <br>I don't want to live like this <br>I know nothing about that girl <br>]]></content><category term="하프타운" label="하프타운"/><category term="이별" label="이별"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/053/My_City/</id><title>053 - My City - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:23:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:23:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/053/My_City/" title="053 - My City - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Let's go get the money <br>go get the money <br>go get the money <br>go get the money <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Let's go digger money <br>go digger money <br>난 효자 아냐 but <br>내 방에 신사임당 <br>니네 잘 때 나는 hustle like <br>국제시장 <br>친일파는 아냐 but <br>오다 노부히로 들고 <br>아오야마 bape <br>사고 간지 마치 ZICO <br>시민권은 없어도 <br>exchange blue hunnut Franklin <br>Chicago Rio Paris <br>My passport stamp clean bling <br>I be fvckin bords like <br>I be fvckin bored <br>tvnt a dyke bitch out <br>have her fvcking boys whoa <br>날아날아 바람 타고 멀리 날아 <br>You follow me behind <br>너의 뒤엔 없지 바람 <br>내가 어디까지 가는 지 <br>지켜보기 바람 <br>내가 이룰게 얼만지 <br>느껴보기 바람 <br>Seoul city Newyork city <br>Jiyeongchi만 물어봐도 <br>알아보지 siri <br>My name goes high <br>with my hommies <br>Sexy honey cash money <br>yeong은 young원히 <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Let's go get the money <br>go get the money <br>go get the money <br>go get the money <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Let's go digger money <br>go digger money <br>뭘 아는 새끼들이 학업과 <br>진로로 십대의 깊일 키울 때 <br>난 밑창 닳은 나이키 짜가 <br>신발 신고 뒤뚱거렸네 <br>아빠의 기대치는 점차 <br>키가 산만해 지는데 <br>난 침뱉는 애들과 다르지 않게 <br>매사에 주변이 산만해 <br>지끈지끈 머리 쥐고 신발끈 <br>질끈 묶어 맨바닥 짚고 <br>오답은 찍찍 그어 찍찍대는 <br>쥐 같은 새끼 ZIP ZIP 묶어 <br>지지층 두껍게 지지 받고 <br>무대를 찍고 직진 <br>찍찍 침 뱉고 엄마 찌찌 빠는 <br>지지리 궁상 떠는 <br>찌질이 ZiGGY 찍기 <br>hello I'm biskit <br>씹으면 씹을수록 고소하지 <br>공기만 가득찬 스낵과는 달라 <br>찔러도 바람은 빠지지 않아 <br>대신 툭 치면 부러지긴 해 왜냐구 <br>깡 마른 biskit이니까 <br>Transformer yellow bumble bee가 <br>내 앞에서 날치기를 해도 <br>어느샌가 앞에 굴러가지 <br>갖다 밀어 붙여 <br>쏘아 제껴 올려 RPM <br>M U S T A N G <br>This is just ma car이지 <br>Step three point Curry지 <br>A man plenty of courage <br>02 or 053 눌러봐 여기가 my city <br>이뤘지 연봉 칠천 기다려저 <br>hundred million <br>통장 뒷자린 00 <br>더 더 붙기만 하지 word up <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Let's go get the money <br>go get the money <br>go get the money <br>go get the money <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Let's go digger money <br>go digger money <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Let's go get the money <br>go get the money <br>go get the money <br>go get the money <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Take it make it <br>Let's go digger money <br>go digger money <br>]]></content><category term="053" label="053"/><category term="My City" label="My City"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/053/Ordinary_day/</id><title>053 - Ordinary day - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:23:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:23:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/053/Ordinary_day/" title="053 - Ordinary day - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Gloomy sunday <br>my hours are slumberless <br>I wonder when my pages <br>gonna be quite fabulous <br>Patience it's the only way <br>I can see the light <br>in the darkness <br>go to my office at 8 <br>그래 그래 평일엔 항상 셔츠충 <br>멋지게 넥타이 매보려 해도 <br>삐뚤어진 마름모 <br>인생이 그래 원래 그래 <br>담배 한 대 피워보자 <br>차가운 아침 공기와 함께 <br>yo 출근하고 야근하는 <br>무한 동력 기계 <br>매일 이 game에 <br>생각 없이 써대는 mail <br>내일 낯선 issue는 <br>나를 인도해 fail <br>비참한 현실 모두가 same <br>뜨거운 곳에 데인 <br>숨막혀 차가운 새벽 공기 여의도 <br>꺼지지 않는 불빛 오늘도 내일도 <br>내 꿈은 어디에 나는 누구 <br>너는 지금 어디 where u at <br>긴 밤 이런저런 생각에 <br>잠 못 이루죠 <br>어떻게 해야 할지 <br>아무도 알려주지 않네요 <br>또 허무하게 <br>오늘도 하루가 가네요 <br>그래요 오늘 밤도 <br>별빛이 자욱하네요 <br>기똥차게 벌었던 <br>내 월급이 어색해 <br>까마득하기만 한 게 <br>별보다 아득해 <br>아침 지하철은 <br>내 지갑처럼 만원이고 <br>점심 무렵엔 와이셔츠 <br>소매가 까맣게 <br>난 괜찮은데 주변엔 내 걱정에 <br>밤 새는 지겨운 애들만 널렸네 <br>난 내가 쓴 모자로 <br>내 앞가림은 해 <br>생각의 별이 뜰 때 <br>난 기지개를 켤게 <br>053 나 잠 못 들 때 <br>미래를 그리며 우주를 상상해 <br>053 흰 티에 묵은 때 교복을 벗고 <br>넥타이를 동여매 <br>053 써커스 무대 원숭이가 되어 <br>이리저리 서성대 <br>053 그때를 추억하네 <br>어둠이 드리워지는 해질녘쯤에 <br>욕망의 수레 위 <br>나는 급해져만 가네 <br>돈의 이면에 가려진 것 <br>그것을 난 짐작만 하네 <br>알고 싶어 달리고 있어 직접 <br>정작 중요한 건 머니 하난데 <br>나이를 먹을 수록 <br>커 보이던 세상은 만만해 <br>초록색 별들이 <br>옥상 위로 떨어져 <br>버렸던 꽁초처럼 쌓여져 <br>작은 일에 상처 받던 나여서 <br>radio sound off 나였어 <br>사회생활이란 핑계에 <br>기만과 거짓말 <br>스크린 속 인생 그건 다 거짓말 <br>도시의 빛을 보며 <br>스스로에 질문해 <br>더 나은 미래 위해 <br>내 시간을 지불해 <br>So today I hustle real hard <br>I hustle real hard <br>긴 밤 이런저런 생각에 <br>잠 못 이루죠 <br>어떻게 해야 할지 <br>아무도 알려주지 않네요 <br>또 허무하게 <br>오늘도 하루가 가네요 <br>그래요 오늘 밤도 <br>별빛이 자욱하네요 <br>]]></content><category term="053" label="053"/><category term="Ordinary day" label="Ordinary day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/053/Last_Diamond/</id><title>053 - Last Diamond - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:23:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:23:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/053/Last_Diamond/" title="053 - Last Diamond - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너는 나를 달콤하게 그림 같던 우리 <br>뜨거운 아스팔트에 떨어진 ice cream <br>나는 녹기 시작하지만 너의 <br>부드러운 혀 끝에 못 닿겠지 난 <br>널 좋아한단 말 슬픔에 걸렸지만 <br>널 사랑한단 말 뒷걸음 쳤지만 <br>빛을 머금고 저 별로 떠날 것 처럼 <br>내 심장을 쥐고서 <br>우주로 날아간 저녁 <br>난 취해 말했지 날 삼킨 그림자처럼 <br>난 혼잣말 했지 Where is the love <br>겨울의 take away coffee처럼 <br>맘이 식었어도 <br>내 말 좀 들어줘 이말을 <br>하고 싶어서 꼭 <br>서툴렀던 사랑아 많이 미안했어요 <br>그 땐 모든 게 처음이라 그랬죠 <br>유치했던 사랑아 <br>고마움만 남은 사람아 <br>이젠 슬픈 그 때의 기억도 <br>웃으며 넘기네요 <br>별 사이 달이 떴고 정장은 해졌지 <br>야근에 봉지커피 좀 늦은 편이지 <br>카페인 깊게 페인 내 페부 사이사이 <br>니코틴 끼리끼리 군대처럼 부대꼈지 <br>연기가 옛사랑을 갈기갈기 회쳐놔서 <br>나홀로 술집에서 회포 풀 일 없고 <br>지지부진한 사랑에 <br>나 혼자 지랄이 나 <br>모텔이나 집집마다 <br>지진나게 밤 지새웠지 <br>난 겨울 눈내려도 <br>눈길 하나 못 받았어 <br>눈총이 박힌 몸에 은총을 내려주오 <br>빠른 게 대수는 아닌데 빠름에 <br>진도만 격하고 빠르게 빼 <br>더 바르게 살길 바라는 <br>내 사랑의 부름에 반응을 해 <br>서툴렀던 사랑아 많이 미안했어요 <br>그 땐 모든 게 처음이라 그랬죠 <br>유치했던 사랑아 <br>고마움만 남은 사람아 <br>이젠 슬픈 그 때의 기억도 <br>웃으며 넘기네요 <br>눈을 뜨면 난 웃고 있지 오늘은 널 <br>만나러 가는 날 멋지게 뭘 입어볼까 <br>옷장을 열어봐 거울 앞에서 또 <br>미친놈처럼 멋쩍게 한 번 웃어봐 <br>소복히 쌓인 눈길에 발자국 남기며 <br>한 주머니 두손을 꼭 잡은 밤 <br>기억하니 첫눈에 반했던 <br>내 표정 숨기려 <br>까칠한 척 애써 들켰지 내 미소 <br>첫 만남 길고 긴 대화 끝 서강대교 <br>걸으며 잡았던 어두운 밤의 끝자락 <br>온 사방이 까마득해도 <br>찬란히 빛나는 너 있자나 <br>언제나 우리 둘이 그때를 기억해 <br>참 많은 걸 배운 고마웠던 사람 <br>처음이라 가능한 다시는 <br>하지 못 할 그 사랑 <br>유치했던 말들 서툴렀던 행동들 <br>이제는 웃으며 회상하는 <br>아련한 추억들 <br>홀로 있는 밤이면 <br>니 생각에 눈물이 나 <br>차가워진 바람아 내 곁에 머물러주라 <br>Thirty three I'm thirsty <br>사랑에 목말라 난 <br>053 들었지 아련했던 수화기 <br>홀로 있는 밤이면 <br>니 생각에 눈물이 나 <br>차가워진 바람아 내 곁에 머물러주라 <br>Thirty three I'm thirsty <br>사랑에 목말라 난 <br>053 들었지 아련했던 수화기 <br>]]></content><category term="053" label="053"/><category term="Last Diamond" label="Last Diamond"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wolfenhords/Journey_to_the_Unknown/</id><title>Wolfenhords - Journey to the Unknown - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:24:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:24:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wolfenhords/Journey_to_the_Unknown/" title="Wolfenhords - Journey to the Unknown - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lost in the World Above <br>Like the Sky as seen from the Earth <br>Celestial Sphere <br>Something gone Wrong <br><br>Left my body Down Below <br>With Solid Steel in my Hearth <br>Bathed in my own Blood <br>Seventh Arrow finished me <br><br>Strange New World <br>Crystal Rapture <br>Rather Quiet Place <br>Today I see no War <br><br>Seven Angels Spreads their Wings <br>In Their Eyes I have seen the Tears <br>Glowing Light Appears to me <br>Upon the River Heavenly <br><br>No <br>* <br>Autumn's Mystic Rivers <br>The Coldness in my Soul <br>Void after Void <br>Where no Light Gone Before <br>I have seen your Cross <br>Turning Love into Hate <br><br>Illusion Chants over the Land of the Damned <br>Dragons of Eden Bending the Dreams to Unknown <br><br>Now I see the Missing Mirrors <br>Reflecting the Code in my Blood <br>Voice of Steel awakens my Heart from the Silence <br>Born Again <br>And Now I Know <br>The Darkness which dwells Between the Light <br>Are said to come to an end <br>These bodies inhabited by the eternal <br>The One who conquers himself <br><br>Superior to righteous battle <br>Away from the fortune they Gain <br>Any Human walking the Earth <br>Shall Embrace Sorrow and pain <br>* <br>Hear the Echos <br>Driven by the spheres <br>Illusion Chants over the Land of the Damned <br>Dragons of Eden Bending the Dreams to Unknown <br><br>Until You Feel <br>Eternal Life <br>Love Your Sorrow <br>Hope for Dreams <br>Final Dawn <br>Shall soon be here <br>Beware of <br>Journey to Unknown]]></content><category term="Wolfenhords" label="Wolfenhords"/><category term="Journey to the Unknown" label="Journey to the Unknown"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wolfenhords/Unholy_Forces_of_Evil_Immortal_Cover/</id><title>Wolfenhords - Unholy Forces of Evil (Immortal Cover) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:24:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:24:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wolfenhords/Unholy_Forces_of_Evil_Immortal_Cover/" title="Wolfenhords - Unholy Forces of Evil (Immortal Cover) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Slowly crossing <br>As red rivers run below <br>Forever passing <br>Where darkness lies unknown <br>Where soul winds burn my eyes <br>Where shadows of lost life hide <br><br>Enter the centers of darkness <br>Where all evil dwells <br>Demons present in flames <br>Oath to black souls found <br><br>Sacrifices as old as the Earth <br>OhWe cut the living flesh <br>Circles of the deepest black throne <br><br>A promise of the darkest blood found <br>Unholy forces of evil <br>Unholy forces of hell <br><br>It's the legend, the demons <br>Rise <br><br>An mayhemic silence floats <br>And we await our signs of death our circle's gathered <br>Ceremonial powers belong to us <br>A goat baptized in fire <br>We dance the circle dance the thorns <br><br>Awaiting the sign of the horns <br>A thousand black clouds storm <br>Blasphemous Northern rites <br>Mysticism touched <br>Pentagrams burning <br><br>Into the centers of the darkness <br>Where all evil dwells <br>Demons present in flames <br>Oath to black souls found <br><br>The unholy forces of evil <br>Unholy forces of hell <br><br>It's the legend, the demons <br>Rise <br><br>The unholy forces of evil <br>Server upon our diabolic souls <br>Cults of death bathed in slaught <br>As the devil's candles burn <br><br>Into the dark skies <br>Floating with the soul winds of the pentagram <br>To the death lights where the North star awaits]]></content><category term="Wolfenhords" label="Wolfenhords"/><category term="Unholy Forces of Evil (Immortal Cover)" label="Unholy Forces of Evil (Immortal Cover)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wolfenhords/Our_Banner_Conquers_All/</id><title>Wolfenhords - Our Banner Conquers All - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:24:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:24:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wolfenhords/Our_Banner_Conquers_All/" title="Wolfenhords - Our Banner Conquers All - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Running <br>Through the Realm of Doom <br>Society is raised in Gloom <br>Worship <br>Greed and Disgust <br>Heaven in flames Combusts <br><br>River runs Red <br>Hunger of the Thousand Dead <br>Tyrants Ahead <br>All Commands are Said <br><br>Evil <br>Message from Beyond <br>Revenge Shall soon to Respond <br>Death <br>Dying Light <br>Born to die in the Fight <br><br>Damn your Walls <br>If a man inside crawls <br>As cold as Ice <br>He turned into vice <br><br>Steel Weapons <br>Iron Eyes <br>Thousand Cries, Death is clear <br>Guided by the Powers they Fear <br>Ready to die for our land to be free <br>Against the truth they shall flee <br><br>Nails scraping against Your soul <br>Force you can not control <br><br>Dancing Under the songs of War <br>Shields and Swords Collide <br>Life beats rhythm no more <br>Music of those who died <br><br>Blasphemer opened the gates of Hell <br>His Evil is yet to be done <br>Mission to Strike by casting the Spell <br>Under the Banner of the Sun <br><br>Amidst the Chaos and Destruction of War <br>The Pale Dome is Crushed to the Ground <br>Death Hungers for Life no more <br>No signal of life can be Found <br><br>Dancing Under the songs of War <br>Shields and Swords Collide <br>Life beats rhythm no more <br>Melodies of those who died <br><br>Still Marching on that Road <br>Traveled the Mountains and Snow <br>Determined to present what we suspect is the Truth <br>Whatever it is <br><br>Quiet Earth <br>Embraced by the winds of the Freedom <br><br>Chess Mate <br>Our Banner Conquers All]]></content><category term="Wolfenhords" label="Wolfenhords"/><category term="Our Banner Conquers All" label="Our Banner Conquers All"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wolfenhords/Der_Sturmer_Der_Sturmer_Cover/</id><title>Wolfenhords - Der Sturmer (Der Sturmer Cover) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:24:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:24:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wolfenhords/Der_Sturmer_Der_Sturmer_Cover/" title="Wolfenhords - Der Sturmer (Der Sturmer Cover) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[With Iron Will and Aryan Might <br>A Soldier of a Higher Cause, roams to the Fight <br>His Comrades fallen, Europe's Best Sons <br>Sworn to protect their Culture and Land <br><br>Der Strmer A Spartan Reborn <br>Der Strmer A God of War <br>Der Strmer Fearless and Pure <br>Der Strmer Loyal and True <br><br>Fighting for Something Greater than Life <br>Ready to die in this Titanic Strife <br>Summoning the Spirit of Ancestors Brave <br>He follows their Steps the White Race to Save <br><br>Through Fire and Smoke, Bloodshed and mud <br>Always marches forward, Schmeizer in hand <br>He had dismissed the fear of death <br>Shouting Heil Hitler will leave his last breath <br><br>The Bravest Army the world ever knew <br>Forgotten Heroes remembered by few <br>But One Day will come, this is our Aim <br>Where All Aryan Youth will Hail their Name <br><br>With Iron Will and Aryan Might <br>A Soldier of a Higher Cause, roams to the Fight <br>His Comrades fallen, Europe's Best Sons <br>Sworn to protect their Culture and Land <br><br>Der Strmer A Spartan Reborn <br>Der Strmer A God of War <br>Der Strmer Fearless and Pure <br>Der Strmer Loyal and True <br><br>Der Strmer A Croatian Reborn <br>Der Strmer A God of War <br>Der Strmer Fearless and Pure <br>Der Strmer Loyal and True]]></content><category term="Wolfenhords" label="Wolfenhords"/><category term="Der Sturmer (Der Sturmer Cover)" label="Der Sturmer (Der Sturmer Cover)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아가동요/나의_살던_고향/</id><title>아가동요 - 나의 살던 고향 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:25:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:25:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EA%B0%80%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%82%B4%EB%8D%98_%EA%B3%A0%ED%96%A5/" title="아가동요 - 나의 살던 고향 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 어릴 적 뛰어 놀던 고향이 생각나 <br>들판에서 뛰어다니고 물놀이도 했죠 <br><br>개구리 울음소리 들으면서 <br>낮잠도 자곤 했지요 <br>그리워라 가고 싶어라 <br>나의 살던 고향 <br>나의 살던 고향 <br><br>나 어릴 적 뛰어 놀던 고향이 생각나 <br>들판에서 뛰어다니고 물놀이도 했죠 <br><br>개구리 울음소리 들으면서 <br>낮잠도 자곤 했지요 <br>그리워라 가고 싶어라 <br>나의 살던 고향 <br>나의 살던 고향 <br>]]></content><category term="아가동요" label="아가동요"/><category term="나의 살던 고향" label="나의 살던 고향"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/구현/And_You/</id><title>구현 - And You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:27:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:27:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B5%AC%ED%98%84/And_You/" title="구현 - And You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[요즘엔 내가 좀 낯설어 보여 <br>달라진 나의 모습 속엔 네가 자리해 <br>맘 가는대로 둬서 그래 <br>그리 싫진 않아 솔직히 난 <br>i wanna be like you <br>웃을 때 올라가는 눈썹마저 난 <br>닮아가려해 you are smiling <br>in my mind <br>너로 인해 생겨난 새론 습관들 <br>내 안에 너를 더 담을래 <br>whatever i'm like this <br>and you my world is changed by u <br>i wonder what about you you <br>how about you you <br>and you everything’s changed by u <br>i wonder what about you you <br>baby you're me and i’m you <br>앞만 보며 걷던 내가 주윌 <br>둘러보게 돼 <br>빠른 걸음 탓에 뒤쳐질까 <br>네 발끈 보곤 해 <br>예전과는 달라진 나의 <br>words and ma direction <br>널 향해 있는 마음만큼 닮아가려 해 <br>and you my world is changed by u <br>i wonder what about you you <br>how about you you <br>and you everything’s changed by u <br>i wonder what about you you <br>baby you're me and i’m you <br>거울 속에 비친 내 모습 <br>just feel like i’m like you <br>널 향해서만 웃는 내 모습도 <br>네 곁에 있는 내 모습 <br>just feel like i’m like you <br>내 안에 널 더 담을래 <br>just feel like i’m like you <br>and you my world is changed by u <br>i wonder what about you you <br>how about you you <br>and you everything’s changed by u <br>i wonder what about you you <br>baby you're me and i’m you <br>]]></content><category term="구현" label="구현"/><category term="And You" label="And You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Primitives/Same_Stuff/</id><title>The Primitives - Same Stuff - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:28:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:28:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Primitives/Same_Stuff/" title="The Primitives - Same Stuff - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One step through the door <br>It's not a place I've gone before <br>Two steps a path unknown <br>Slip outside the safety zone <br>Three steps come what may <br>We'll leave this world so far away <br>Four steps and then a fifth <br>Cut the cord we're set adrift <br>Cut the cord we're set adrift <br><br>Haven't we come far enough <br>To know we are the same stuff <br><br>One step through the door <br>It's not a place I've gone before <br>Two three four and then a fifth <br>Cut the cord we're set adrift <br>Cut the cord we're set adrift <br><br>Haven't we come far enough <br>To know we are the same stuff <br>We're the same stuff <br>We are the same stuff]]></content><category term="The Primitives" label="The Primitives"/><category term="Same Stuff" label="Same Stuff"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Primitives/Oh_Honey_Sweet/</id><title>The Primitives - Oh Honey Sweet - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:28:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:28:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Primitives/Oh_Honey_Sweet/" title="The Primitives - Oh Honey Sweet - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's enough to know that you will be there <br>To take away all troubles and cares <br>You brightened yesterday <br>And I promise to repay <br>I will give you my tomorrow I swear <br><br>When the dark surrounds there's a light at the end <br>Oh honey sweet I think of you then <br><br>Away from this sad world I can be <br>Freed from the chains that eyes cannot see <br>And in some hour of need <br>Should doubt and fear succeed <br>Back in your saving arms I will be <br><br>When the dark surrounds there's a light at the end <br>Oh honey sweet I think of you then]]></content><category term="The Primitives" label="The Primitives"/><category term="Oh Honey Sweet" label="Oh Honey Sweet"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Primitives/Squeak_N_Squawk/</id><title>The Primitives - Squeak `N` Squawk - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:28:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:28:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Primitives/Squeak_N_Squawk/" title="The Primitives - Squeak `N` Squawk - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Was I supposed to pay attention <br>Did you just squeak another threat <br>Or have you squawked some new opinion <br>Well I sure ain't been listening yet <br><br>Wish that I could find the time <br>To give less time to you <br><br>Think you're so cutting with your put downs <br>Your practiced off the cuff remarks <br>Your voice to me is such a small sound <br>A lonely whisper in the dark <br><br>Wish that I could find the time <br>To give less time to you <br><br>To give less time to you <br>Squeak squeak <br>To give less time to you <br>Squawk squawk]]></content><category term="The Primitives" label="The Primitives"/><category term="Squeak `N` Squawk" label="Squeak `N` Squawk"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Primitives/Ill_Trust_The_Wind/</id><title>The Primitives - I`ll Trust The Wind - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:28:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:28:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Primitives/Ill_Trust_The_Wind/" title="The Primitives - I`ll Trust The Wind - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Can you see which way to go <br>Straight ahead can you ever know <br>The right track all mapped out <br>A true course beyond all doubt <br><br>I think that I'll just trust the wind <br>It might seem aimless <br>But I'll get there in the end <br><br>Well she said you've gotta run <br>And he said don't be so dumb <br>Well my plan is not to plan <br>I just drift to where I am <br><br>I think that I'll just trust the wind <br>It might seem aimless <br>But I'll get there in the end]]></content><category term="The Primitives" label="The Primitives"/><category term="I`ll Trust The Wind" label="I`ll Trust The Wind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/싸이_PSY/예술이야/</id><title>싸이 (PSY) - 예술이야 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:30:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:30:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%B8%EC%9D%B4_PSY/%EC%98%88%EC%88%A0%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC/" title="싸이 (PSY) - 예술이야 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너와 나 둘이 <br>정신 없이 가는 곳 <br>정처 없이 가는 곳 <br>정해지지 않은 곳 <br>거기서 우리 워우워 <br>서로를 재워주고 워우워 <br>서로를 깨워주고 워우워 <br>서로를 채워주고 워우워 <br>EXCUSE ME 잠시만 <br>아직까진 우린 남 <br>하지만 조만간 <br>중독성을 자랑하는 장난감 <br>지금 이 느낌적인 <br>느낌이 통하는 느낌 <br>녹아버릴 아이스크림 <br>지금이 우리에게는 꿈이야 <br>너와 나 둘이서 추는 춤이야 <br>심장은 터질 듯이 예술이야 <br>오에오 오에오 오에오 <br>하늘을 날아가는 기분이야 <br>죽어도 상관없는 지금이야 <br>심장은 터질 듯이 예술이야 <br>오에오 오에오 오에오 <br>예술이야 예술이야 <br>예술이야 예술이야 <br>예술이야 예술이야 <br>이런 날이 올 줄이야 <br>예술이야 예술이야 <br>예술이야 예술이야 <br>오에오 오에오 오에오 <br>너와 나 둘이 워우워 <br>밤새 잔을 부딪혀 워우워 <br>밤새 뺨을 부비며 워우워 <br>밤새도록 둘이서 워우워 <br>눈이 점점 풀린다 <br>우리도 따라 풀린다 끌린다 <br>너에 대한 수수께끼가 풀린다 <br>지금 이 춤에 <br>너의 가빠진 숨에 수줍음에 <br>YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN <br>지금이 우리에게는 꿈이야 <br>너와 나 둘이서 추는 춤이야 <br>기분은 미친 듯이 예술이야 <br>오에오 오에오 오에오 <br>하늘을 날아가는 기분이야 <br>죽어도 상관없는 지금이야 <br>심장은 터질 듯이 예술이야 <br>오에오 오에오 오에오 <br>여기서 우리 <br>같은 것을 즐기고 <br>같은 것을 느끼고 <br>웃다가 흐느끼고 <br>아가씨 만나기 전엔 난 건달 <br>미녀 만나기 전엔 야수였던 날 <br>바꿔 버렸어 <br>내가 찾던 사람 너였어 <br>예술이었어 <br>지금이 우리에게는 꿈이야 <br>너와 나 둘이서 추는 춤이야 <br>기분은 미친 듯이 예술이야 <br>오에오 오에오 오에오 <br>하늘을 날아가는 기분이야 <br>죽어도 상관없는 지금이야 <br>심장은 터질 듯이 예술이야 <br>오에오 오에오 오에오 <br>예술이야 예술이야 <br>예술이야 오늘이야 <br>예술이야 예술이야 <br>이런 날이 올 줄이야 <br>예술이야 예술이야 <br>예술이야 예술이야 <br>오에오 오에오 오에오 <br>]]></content><category term="싸이 (PSY)" label="싸이 (PSY)"/><category term="예술이야" label="예술이야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SET/반했어_Inst/</id><title>S.E.T - 반했어 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:30:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:30:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SET/%EB%B0%98%ED%96%88%EC%96%B4_Inst/" title="S.E.T - 반했어 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[hot hot hot hot <br>hot hot hot hot <br>dang It's like a <br>hot hot hot feel <br>dang just like a <br>hot hot hot pill <br>반했어 하필 너라니 <br>막 해도 하필 좋다니 <br>너를 볼 땐 just like that <br>hot pill 끊을 수 없잖아 <br>나 너무 아파서 <br>왜 난 너를 만나서 <br>벗어나지 못할까 <br>내 꺼라 느껴지면 <br>조금은 나을까 <br>넌 마치 눈 가리고 <br>아웅 하듯 말해 늘 <br>똑바로 행동해 답답해 <br>말을 못해 날 가지고 놀 <br>생각 아니면 왜 말 못해 <br>난 하필 널 만나서 마음 아프게 <br>아니까 닥쳐 i wanna hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>i need a need a hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>i need a need a hot pill <br>반했어 하필 나라니 <br>뭐래 또 하필 너라니 <br>너를 볼 땐 just like that <br>hot pill 끊을 수 없잖아 <br>난 점점 심해져 <br>now I know you don't know <br>내 맘을 하나도 <br>신경 안 써 생각 안 해 <br>너에겐 나란 건 <br>넌 마치 눈 가리고 <br>아웅 하듯 말해 늘 <br>똑바로 행동해 대답해 <br>말을 못해 날 가지고 놀 <br>생각 아니면 왜 <br>말 못해 난 하필 널 만나서 <br>마음 아프게 <br>아니까 닥쳐 I wanna hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>i need a need a hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>i need a need a hot pill <br>하필 너는 멋져 누가 봐도 그렇고 <br>하필 너를 사랑할 수 밖에 없는 건 <br>It's like a hot feel <br>just like a hot pill <br>삼켜버렸어 이제 난 어떡해 <br>아니까 닥쳐 I wanna hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>i need a need a hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>아니까 닥쳐 I wanna hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>i need a need a hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>i need a need a hot pill <br>]]></content><category term="S.E.T" label="S.E.T"/><category term="반했어 (Inst.)" label="반했어 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SET/날라리_Inst/</id><title>S.E.T - 날라리 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:31:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:31:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SET/%EB%82%A0%EB%9D%BC%EB%A6%AC_Inst/" title="S.E.T - 날라리 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날라리 라리 라리 <br>날라리 <br>라라리라리 날라리라리 <br>날라리 <br>라라리라리 날라리라리 <br>You make me crazy <br>나를 재미 없게 만들래요 <br>너의 그 가식적인 <br>눈빛을 난 가릴래요 <br>You make me cry <br>아무것도 하지 않는 네 태도 <br>You make me try <br>아무것도 난 할 수 없네요 <br>난 바래 사실은 바래 <br>Baby I`m crazy <br>상처때문에 <br>삐뚤어진 내 마음을 다 줄래 <br>난 바래 사실을 말해 <br>Baby I`m crazy <br>너 때문에 난 나 때문에 넌 <br>Maybe I'm crazy <br>청천벽력 날벼락 <br>내게 또 이런 일이 생길수가 <br>소심했던 내 모습이 싫어 <br>어떻게든 돌리고 싶어 <br>Question <br>action <br>답을 알수 없는 examination <br>어차피 정답은 없어 <br>그냥 되는 대로 사는 거지 뭐 <br>You make me cry <br>아무것도 하지 않는 네 태도 <br>You make me try <br>아무것도 난 할 수 없네요 <br>난 바래 사실은 바래 <br>Baby I`m crazy <br>상처때문에 <br>삐뚤어진 내맘을 다 줄래 <br>난 바래 사실을 말해 <br>Baby I`m crazy <br>너 때문에 난 나 때문에 넌 <br>maybe I'm crazy <br>오에오에오 <br>날라리라리 <br>오에오에오 <br>날라리라리 <br>더 이상 걱정은 하지 말고 <br>오늘은 신나게 달려보자 <br>내일의 걱정은 내일로 미루고 <br>오늘은 신나게 즐겨보자 <br>날라리 라리 <br>라라리라리 날라리라리 <br>날라리 라리 <br>라라리라리 날라리라리 <br>난 바래 사실은 바래 <br>Baby I`m crazy <br>난 바래 사실을 말해 <br>Baby I`m crazy <br>어차피 정답은 없어 <br>그냥 되는대로 사는거지 뭐 <br>]]></content><category term="S.E.T" label="S.E.T"/><category term="날라리 (Inst.)" label="날라리 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SET/반했어/</id><title>S.E.T - 반했어 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:31:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:31:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SET/%EB%B0%98%ED%96%88%EC%96%B4/" title="S.E.T - 반했어 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[hot hot hot hot <br>hot hot hot hot <br>dang It's like a <br>hot hot hot feel <br>dang just like a <br>hot hot hot pill <br>반했어 하필 너라니 <br>막 해도 하필 좋다니 <br>너를 볼 땐 just like that <br>hot pill 끊을 수 없잖아 <br>나 너무 아파서 <br>왜 난 너를 만나서 <br>벗어나지 못할까 <br>내 꺼라 느껴지면 <br>조금은 나을까 <br>넌 마치 눈 가리고 <br>아웅 하듯 말해 늘 <br>똑바로 행동해 답답해 <br>말을 못해 날 가지고 놀 <br>생각 아니면 왜 말 못해 <br>난 하필 널 만나서 마음 아프게 <br>아니까 닥쳐 i wanna hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>i need a need a hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>i need a need a hot pill <br>반했어 하필 나라니 <br>뭐래 또 하필 너라니 <br>너를 볼 땐 just like that <br>hot pill 끊을 수 없잖아 <br>난 점점 심해져 <br>now I know you don't know <br>내 맘을 하나도 <br>신경 안 써 생각 안 해 <br>너에겐 나란 건 <br>넌 마치 눈 가리고 <br>아웅 하듯 말해 늘 <br>똑바로 행동해 대답해 <br>말을 못해 날 가지고 놀 <br>생각 아니면 왜 <br>말 못해 난 하필 널 만나서 <br>마음 아프게 <br>아니까 닥쳐 I wanna hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>i need a need a hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>i need a need a hot pill <br>하필 너는 멋져 누가 봐도 그렇고 <br>하필 너를 사랑할 수 밖에 없는 건 <br>It's like a hot feel <br>just like a hot pill <br>삼켜버렸어 이제 난 어떡해 <br>아니까 닥쳐 I wanna hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>i need a need a hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>아니까 닥쳐 I wanna hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>i need a need a hot pill <br>hot hot hot hit me <br>i need a I need a <br>i need a need a hot pill <br>]]></content><category term="S.E.T" label="S.E.T"/><category term="반했어" label="반했어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SET/날라리/</id><title>S.E.T - 날라리 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:31:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:31:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SET/%EB%82%A0%EB%9D%BC%EB%A6%AC/" title="S.E.T - 날라리 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날라리 라리 라리 <br>날라리 <br>라라리라리 날라리라리 <br>날라리 <br>라라리라리 날라리라리 <br>You make me crazy <br>나를 재미 없게 만들래요 <br>너의 그 가식적인 <br>눈빛을 난 가릴래요 <br>You make me cry <br>아무것도 하지 않는 네 태도 <br>You make me try <br>아무것도 난 할 수 없네요 <br>난 바래 사실은 바래 <br>Baby I`m crazy <br>상처때문에 <br>삐뚤어진 내 마음을 다 줄래 <br>난 바래 사실을 말해 <br>Baby I`m crazy <br>너 때문에 난 나 때문에 넌 <br>Maybe I'm crazy <br>청천벽력 날벼락 <br>내게 또 이런 일이 생길수가 <br>소심했던 내 모습이 싫어 <br>어떻게든 돌리고 싶어 <br>Question <br>action <br>답을 알수 없는 examination <br>어차피 정답은 없어 <br>그냥 되는 대로 사는 거지 뭐 <br>You make me cry <br>아무것도 하지 않는 네 태도 <br>You make me try <br>아무것도 난 할 수 없네요 <br>난 바래 사실은 바래 <br>Baby I`m crazy <br>상처때문에 <br>삐뚤어진 내맘을 다 줄래 <br>난 바래 사실을 말해 <br>Baby I`m crazy <br>너 때문에 난 나 때문에 넌 <br>maybe I'm crazy <br>오에오에오 <br>날라리라리 <br>오에오에오 <br>날라리라리 <br>더 이상 걱정은 하지 말고 <br>오늘은 신나게 달려보자 <br>내일의 걱정은 내일로 미루고 <br>오늘은 신나게 즐겨보자 <br>날라리 라리 <br>라라리라리 날라리라리 <br>날라리 라리 <br>라라리라리 날라리라리 <br>난 바래 사실은 바래 <br>Baby I`m crazy <br>난 바래 사실을 말해 <br>Baby I`m crazy <br>어차피 정답은 없어 <br>그냥 되는대로 사는거지 뭐 <br>]]></content><category term="S.E.T" label="S.E.T"/><category term="날라리" label="날라리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임소정/이렇게_난_숨만_쉬며_살아/</id><title>임소정 - 이렇게 난 숨만 쉬며 살아 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:32:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:32:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%86%8C%EC%A0%95/%EC%9D%B4%EB%A0%87%EA%B2%8C_%EB%82%9C_%EC%88%A8%EB%A7%8C_%EC%89%AC%EB%A9%B0_%EC%82%B4%EC%95%84/" title="임소정 - 이렇게 난 숨만 쉬며 살아 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[조금은 아무렇지 않다가도 <br>어느 순간 숨이 탁 <br>막혀올 때가 있어 <br>웃으며 얘기를 하다가도 <br>뒤돌면 하염없이 눈물이 나 <br>밤엔 잠을 깊게 못 자 <br>그래서 그럴까 <br>가끔 몸이 정말 많이 <br>아프기도 하더라 <br>밥도 제대로 먹질 못하고 <br>온종일 멍하니 <br>이렇게 난 숨만 쉬며 살아 <br>그래 널 많이 사랑했나 봐 <br>그래서 나를 원망하나 봐 <br>한마디 말도 온전히 <br>널 잡지 못하고 <br>후회로 널 헤매이다 <br>이렇게 또 하루가 흘러 <br>참 힘들겠지만 <br>우리 이겨내겠지 <br>언젠간 어떻게든 괜찮아지겠지 <br>근데 또 슬프다 <br>괜찮아지는 것도 <br>난 못 견디게 서러워 <br>아직 널 많이 사랑하나 봐 <br>쉽게 널 보내질 못하나 봐 <br>속마음마저 온전히 <br>솔직하지 못한 난 <br>미련 속 널 되새기다 <br>이렇게 <br>떠난 너를 그려보다 <br>이렇게 <br>]]></content><category term="임소정" label="임소정"/><category term="이렇게 난 숨만 쉬며 살아" label="이렇게 난 숨만 쉬며 살아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최순호/남강의_추억/</id><title>최순호 - 남강의 추억 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:34:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:34:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%88%9C%ED%98%B8/%EB%82%A8%EA%B0%95%EC%9D%98_%EC%B6%94%EC%96%B5/" title="최순호 - 남강의 추억 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1절 <br>고향의 삼강 주막집 그 추억이 그리워 <br>모래뜸질 하시던 우리 어머니 <br>우리형제 물놀이 하던 그 시절이 벌써 사십년 <br>낙동강 강물따라 흘러온 그 세월 <br>추막은 변함없이 나그네를 반기는데 <br>내고향 낙동강을 건너 갈때면 <br>어머님이 너무 그리워 <br>2절 <br>고향의 삼강 주막집 그 추억이 그리워 <br>모래뜸질 하시던 우리 아버지 <br>우리형제 물놀이 하던 그 시절이 벌써 사십년 <br>낙동강 강물따라 흘러온 그 세월 <br>주막은 변함없이 나그네를 반기는데 <br>내고향 낙동강을 건너 갈때면 <br>아버님이 너무 그리워]]></content><category term="최순호" label="최순호"/><category term="남강의 추억" label="남강의 추억"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temperance_Movement/Time_Wont_Leave/</id><title>The Temperance Movement - Time Won`t Leave - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:34:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:34:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temperance_Movement/Time_Wont_Leave/" title="The Temperance Movement - Time Won`t Leave - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1] <br>Laid down beside me, wondering fingers roll <br>All the scents and your secrets, always right under my nose <br>Sleepy daydreams, lazy mornings, sunlight on her toes <br>Kicking out of the darkness, time won't leave me alone <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Ah hah, ah hah <br>Time won't leave me alone <br>Ah hah, ah hah <br>Time won't leave me alone <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>Bathe me by candle, portions for my pain <br>Rock n Roll for my sinner, my baby's hands for my saints <br>Tiny dancers, little Susie, sweetest thing I ever saw <br>Grab it all in these moments, as time won't leave me alone <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Ah hah, ah hah <br>Time won't leave me alone <br>Ah hah, ah hah <br>Time won't leave me alone <br><br>Lose my head, lose my rage, until the end of the age <br>Ladi dah, ooh oh, ladi dah <br><br>[Verse 3] <br>I wave to my future, hillside to the sea <br>Hurrying up at those plannings, them old stars have nothing on me <br>F rom my weakness, on my blindness, on the low raise of the tone <br>I'm free, I am weightless, and time won't leave me alone <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Ah hah, ah hah <br>Time won't leave me alone <br>Ah hah, ah hah <br>Time won't leave me alone <br>Ah hah, ah hah <br>Time won't leave me alone <br>Ah hah, ah hah <br>Time won't leave me alone]]></content><category term="The Temperance Movement" label="The Temperance Movement"/><category term="Time Won`t Leave" label="Time Won`t Leave"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ice-T/Thats_How_Im_Livin_Live/</id><title>Ice-T - That`s How I`m Livin (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:35:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:35:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ice-T/Thats_How_Im_Livin_Live/" title="Ice-T - That`s How I`m Livin (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Artist: Ice-T <br>Album: Home Invasion <br>Song: That's How I'm Livin <br><br>I was born in New Jersey, I said it before <br>But I guess nobody heard me <br>My mother died young <br>No sisters or brothers, I was the only son <br>When I was twelve my pops died too <br>What a brother was supposed to do? <br>They sent me out West <br>To live with my aunt <br>I guess they though it was the best <br>But there was no love there <br>Growin' with no moms <br>I guess I was prepared to live in a vacuum <br>The bedroom, the kitchen, the hall and the bathroom <br>I didn't leave home much, didn't like L.A <br>Didn't have no friends to trust <br>Got bused to a school <br>Blacks and whites, I guess the shit was cool <br>But in highschool I changed <br>Didn't wanna bust, didn't wanna play the game <br>I walked to Crenshaw High, shit was fly <br>I hooked up with a new crew <br>Some brothers that seemed like they knew what the fuck to do <br>You might call it "gang" but we called it a set <br>And it was our own thang <br>The whole school was down <br>And one way or another everybody fucked around <br>Whether hardcore or not <br>You wore the right color or your ass got shot <br>That's how I'm livin'... <br><br>I did three years in and made close friends <br>Havin' no love my homies became my only <br>I was glad: the family I never had <br>But I grew up fast, got a girl on 10th grade pregnant <br>Needin' cash, I had to change my style <br>Switched from bangin' to hustlin' <br>No more goin' buckwild <br>Had to get a cashflow <br>But my hustle was weak, it was a no go <br>I joined the army, four years in that shit <br>Be all fucked you can be <br>Came back to the hood <br>My homies had done good <br>Had elevated their game <br>About 100 gees a lick, no mothafuckin' shame <br>Passed for the jewels <br>Baby sledgehammers with the tools <br>I speak on this with hesitation <br>Even though it passed the statue of limitations... <br><br>I checked the bank <br>Bought a porsche and gear, earn high streetrank <br>But as I grew my whole crew fell through <br>Cops had us on the books as interstate crooks <br>Murder robbery rape escape, the whole damn nine <br>You robbed a nigga blind <br>I had too much juice, I cut my boosters loose <br>I was in tread with the pimpgame <br>Took on the Ice name <br>But the pimp game moved too slow <br>Especially for a nigga who was hooked on quick dough <br>In one night late I was in a carwreck <br>And I was lucky to escape <br>Hospital for ten weeks, in bed almost dead <br>And when I got well, I got caught in a cross <br>And got locked in a jailcell <br>That's how I'm livin'... <br><br><br>They cut me loose <br>And I had to change troops <br>This time they didn't catch me <br>Next time they'll stretch me <br>Cause my time was gettin' short <br>All my homies was in court <br>Or locked in a hole, this shit was gettin' old <br>So I changed my life <br>Put down the gun and picked up the mic <br>It took ten years to get from there to here <br>But I still keep a gun, cops got me on the run <br>And they hate me more now <br>Than they ever did before <br>My homies came back from pen <br>And we all worked together <br>True friends but every once and while <br>Some punk mistakes me as a chump <br>And he gets in my face <br>Wrong mothafuckin' place <br>And I ain't lyin', that's how you dyin'...]]></content><category term="Ice-T" label="Ice-T"/><category term="That`s How I`m Livin (Live)" label="That`s How I`m Livin (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ice-T/I_Aint_New_Ta_This_Live/</id><title>Ice-T - I Ain`t New Ta This (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:35:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:35:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ice-T/I_Aint_New_Ta_This_Live/" title="Ice-T - I Ain`t New Ta This (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come on <br>Come on <br><br>[ VERSE 1 ] <br>Do this, ugh, come on, come on <br>Time to get wreck and kick the so on and so on <br>The I-c-e-T <br>O.G. M.C <br>L.A.P.D <br>H-a-t-e- <br>S (Ho!) <br>Watch the mic blow <br>I flip scripts, and the Dump drops the Ammo <br>Time to get wreck with the new style <br>It's '93 and MC's are gettin buck wild <br>But I - ain't a - nigga <br>That's gonna get left with a big zero as a figure <br>I'm gonna end up with a big sum <br>Cause if you don't like one jam, I always got another one <br>Different, specifically I don't copy <br>Tear up the track if the flow sounds sloppy <br>I don't play one game <br>I bust about a dozen cuts on my lp's, none the same <br><br>[ Hook ] <br>I ain't new to this <br>I ain't new to this <br>Never been <br>New to this <br>Nigga <br>New to this <br>I ain't new to this <br>Fool <br>New to this <br>Fuck around and catch a left and a right fist <br><br>[ VERSE 2 ] <br>Boom bam, I drop fat slang <br>When I used to hustle, used to be down with the crack game <br>When I was young, I used to roll with a street gang <br>If you wanna squabble, muthafucka, it ain't no thang <br>I ain't new to this, I ain't new to this <br>Blow your dome, I hit quick as a pugilist <br>Ugh, ah, what's up? Now your eyes swoll' <br>Thought I went soft, cause my records went gold <br>(Sucker) Buster, you'se a - muthafuckin punk fool <br>Caught you in your eye while you reached for your tool <br>Now it's mine, and you're blind <br>Pop-pop-pop-pop-pop goes the nine <br>Yeah. what you're dissin bout, friend? <br>Sayin I went out, but you ain't never been in <br>I got r-e-s-p-e-c-t in the industry <br>That's somethin that you'll never see <br><br>[ Hook ] <br><br>(They can get a smack for that) --] Flavor Flav <br>(Yeah-yeah) <br><br>[ VERSE 3 ] <br>On and on to the funk track <br>Back glass shakin like shit, that's where the trunk's at <br>That's cause my shit's - made for <br>Niggas that are hardcore <br>Brothers is quick to hook a left to your right jaw <br>Girls, come on, girls, come on, girls, come on <br>Get your clothes off and the fun on <br>Girls, come on, girls, come on, girls, come on <br>Get your clothes off and the fun on <br>It's time to check cash <br>Jump in my 4, hit the switch and lay the ass <br>While the Klan try to kill me <br>But I wrote 'riot' on my muthafuckin will, gee <br>So when I'm gone, it's on <br>Caps goin off on the streets like popcorn <br>Talkin bout Simon till the early morn' <br>Word is bond <br>But now I just cool <br>Bumpin my Gang Starr tape by my pool <br>I ain't new to this <br><br><br>[ Hook ] <br><br>[ VERSE 4 ] <br>Check, check, I got problems with the press <br>Caught the punk in traffic, stabbed the sucker in his neck <br>(Ugh) Punk reporter tried to diss me <br>(Ugh) Now the muthafucka's history <br>(Ha) I got to make a break hardcore fat tape <br>Word, I don't fantasize, I don't exaggerate <br>Just kick correct with the 1-2 mic check <br>Still quick to swing, take a sucker to the deck <br>I'm not the nigga you should step to like a sucker <br>Walk up talkin shit, you best to be a good ducker <br>Your posse best to run from my gun <br>Keep my nine off safety, and E holds the other one <br>(Yeah, sucker) <br><br>[ Hook ] <br><br>(They can get a smack for that) <br><br>And you don't stop <br><br>Fuck, fuck around and get your punk ass dropped <br><br>Yeah]]></content><category term="Ice-T" label="Ice-T"/><category term="I Ain`t New Ta This (Live)" label="I Ain`t New Ta This (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/명진/꼭_올거야_MR/</id><title>명진 - 꼭 올거야 (MR) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:36:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:36:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AA%85%EC%A7%84/%EA%BC%AD_%EC%98%AC%EA%B1%B0%EC%95%BC_MR/" title="명진 - 꼭 올거야 (MR) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘이 가고 <br>새로운 내일엔 <br>내 세상이 꼭 올거야 <br>꼭 올거야 멋진 미래가 <br>기적처럼 다가 올거야 <br>기다려봐 예쁜 내 사랑 <br>돈과 명예 모두 안겨줄게 <br>힘들지만 아프지만 <br>잘 견뎌왔으니 <br>뿌린만큼 거둔다는 <br>옛말도 있잖아 <br>오늘이 가고 <br>새로운 내일엔 <br>내 세상이 꼭 올거야 <br>힘들지만 아프지만 <br>잘 견뎌왔으니 <br>뿌린만큼 거둔다는 <br>옛말도 있잖아 <br>오늘이 가고 <br>새로운 내일엔 <br>내 세상이 꼭 올거야 <br>오늘이 가고 <br>새로운 내일엔 <br>내 세상이 꼭 올거야 <br>내 세상이 꼭 올거야]]></content><category term="명진" label="명진"/><category term="꼭 올거야 (MR)" label="꼭 올거야 (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/명진/꼭_올거야/</id><title>명진 - 꼭 올거야 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:36:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:36:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AA%85%EC%A7%84/%EA%BC%AD_%EC%98%AC%EA%B1%B0%EC%95%BC/" title="명진 - 꼭 올거야 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘이 가고 <br>새로운 내일엔 <br>내 세상이 꼭 올거야 <br>꼭 올거야 멋진 미래가 <br>기적처럼 다가 올거야 <br>기다려봐 예쁜 내 사랑 <br>돈과 명예 모두 안겨줄게 <br>힘들지만 아프지만 <br>잘 견뎌왔으니 <br>뿌린만큼 거둔다는 <br>옛말도 있잖아 <br>오늘이 가고 <br>새로운 내일엔 <br>내 세상이 꼭 올거야 <br>힘들지만 아프지만 <br>잘 견뎌왔으니 <br>뿌린만큼 거둔다는 <br>옛말도 있잖아 <br>오늘이 가고 <br>새로운 내일엔 <br>내 세상이 꼭 올거야 <br>오늘이 가고 <br>새로운 내일엔 <br>내 세상이 꼭 올거야 <br>내 세상이 꼭 올거야]]></content><category term="명진" label="명진"/><category term="꼭 올거야" label="꼭 올거야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한정선/내_뒷모습/</id><title>한정선 - 내 뒷모습 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:40:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:40:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EC%A0%95%EC%84%A0/%EB%82%B4_%EB%92%B7%EB%AA%A8%EC%8A%B5/" title="한정선 - 내 뒷모습 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 너를 잡지 못하고 <br>아혼에 잠긴 것은 <br>애당초 이유없는 이마음 때문에 <br>사랑을 저버린 후에 그대를 보냈나요 <br>가슴에 맺힐 아픔 생각 못한 채 <br>우리의 꿈을 찾아 <br>불빛따라 걸었었는데 <br>남은 것은 고독뿐 허망한 눈길 뿐 <br>가까이 두고두고 느낄 수 없는 것은 <br>정들까 두려웠던 뭇내음 때문에 <br>슬픔을 멀리해두고 그대를 보았나요 <br>말 할 수 없는 그림자 때문에 <br>우리의 꿈을 찾아 <br>별빛따라 흐느꼈는데 <br>뒷모습은 끝없이 가슴을 에이네 <br>그길로 떠나야해 <br>]]></content><category term="한정선" label="한정선"/><category term="내 뒷모습" label="내 뒷모습"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노훈/With_You/</id><title>노훈 - With You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:46:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:46:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%ED%9B%88/With_You/" title="노훈 - With You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[짧은 치마 <br>발끝에는 조던 No.5 <br>서울 하늘의 <br>미세먼지처럼 뿌옇한 <br>내 삶의 Filtering <br>맑은 공기를 내게 투여 <br>그저 틱틱거리는 말투 귀여워 <br>넌 한번도 절대로 <br>느껴보지 못한 타입 <br>어설픈 펀치라인 안 써 <br>입을 조심 하지 <br>그만큼 신중하게 말하는 거야 <br>이 신나는 리듬으로 <br>내 맘 전하는 거야 <br>많은 사람들 <br>요새 인성을 논하지만 <br>넌 당당하고 소신 있게 <br>그저 네 것을 해 <br>클럽에서 흔들어대는 <br>쟤네와는 달리 <br>다른 놈들 벌써 <br>네 꽁무니 쫓아 다니지 <br>좋은 기분 네 몸매처럼 <br>시원하게 쭉 뻗어 <br>절대 답답하지 않아 <br>아 물론 이 가사의 영감은 오로지 <br>네 생각만 하지 Take it easy <br>I wanna be with you <br>네게 많은걸 주고 싶어 <br>내 옆으로 와줘 안아줘 <br>I wanna be with you <br>너의 모든걸 알고 싶어 <br>내 곁으로 와줘 You're my girl <br>퇴근을 하고 밤은 <br>깊어가고 있지 <br>평일의 특별함을 느낄 때까지 <br>주말이 아니라도 <br>너와 함께 patry on <br>Freestyle 하는 기분으로 <br>가자 Here we go <br>정해진 건 없지 <br>이건 깨끗한 캔버스 <br>우리 만의 색감을 입혀 나는 원해 <br>점점 더워지는 날씨 덕에 Hot body <br>내 눈이 호강하고 있잖니 honey <br>군대를 다녀왔어도 <br>나는 막내아들 <br>때문에 애교 섞인 <br>감정이 뭔지 알어 <br>쓸데 없이 진지함을 갖지 않지만 <br>이 기분 마치 진실되게 <br>나는 너에게 얘기하지 <br>Good baby Good lady <br>때로는 친구 같고 <br>연인 같은 사이 Good days <br>하루하루 무뎌져 가는 <br>삶의 오아시스 <br>이제는 목 마를 일이 <br>절대로 없어졌어 <br>I wanna be with you <br>네게 많은걸 주고 싶어 <br>내 옆으로 와줘 안아줘 <br>I wanna be with you <br>너의 모든걸 알고 싶어 <br>내 곁으로 와줘 You're my girl <br>I wanna be with you <br>네게 많은걸 주고 싶어 <br>내 옆으로 와줘 안아줘 <br>I wanna be with you <br>너의 모든걸 알고 싶어 <br>내 곁으로 와줘 You're my girl <br>]]></content><category term="노훈" label="노훈"/><category term="With You" label="With You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Major_Lazer/Sua_Cara_Feat_Anitta__Pabllo_Vittar/</id><title>Major Lazer - Sua Cara (Feat. Anitta & Pabllo Vittar) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:47:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:47:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Major_Lazer/Sua_Cara_Feat_Anitta__Pabllo_Vittar/" title="Major Lazer - Sua Cara (Feat. Anitta & Pabllo Vittar) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Major Lazer run the world <br>Voce prepara mas nao dispara <br>Voce repara mas nao encara <br>Se acha o cara mas nao me para <br>Ta cheio de maldade <br>mas nao me encara <br>Voce ja ta querendo e eu tambem <br>Mas e cheio de historia e de porem <br>Virou covarde to com vontade <br>Mas voce ta demorando <br>uma eternidade <br>Se voce nao vem eu vou botar pressao <br>Nao vou te esperar to cheia de opcao <br>Eu nao sou mulher de aturar sermao <br>Me encara se prepara <br>Que eu vou jogar bem na sua cara <br>Bem na sua cara <br>Eu vou rebolar bem na sua cara <br>Bem na sua cara <br>Hoje eu vou jogar bem na sua cara <br>Cheguei <br>To preparada pra atacar <br>Quando o grave bater eu vou quicar <br>Na sua cara vou jogar ah ah <br>E rebolar ah ah <br>Eu to linda livre leve e solta <br>Doida pra beijar na boca <br>Linda livre leve e solta <br>Doida pra beijar na boca <br>Linda livre leve e solta <br>Doida pra beijar na boca <br>Linda livre leve e solta <br>Que eu vou jogar bem na sua cara <br>Bem na sua cara <br>Eu vou rebolar bem na sua cara <br>Bem na sua cara <br>Hoje eu vou jogar bem na sua cara <br>Voce prepara mas nao dispara <br>bem na sua cara <br>Voce repara mas nao encara <br>bem na sua cara <br>Se acha o cara mas nao me para <br>bem na sua cara <br>Se acha o cara mas nao me para <br>bem na sua cara <br>Se voce nao vem eu vou botar pressao <br>Nao vou te esperar to cheia de opcao <br>Eu nao sou mulher de aturar sermao <br>Me encara se prepara <br>Que eu vou jogar bem na sua cara <br>]]></content><category term="Major Lazer" label="Major Lazer"/><category term="Sua Cara (Feat. Anitta & Pabllo Vittar)" label="Sua Cara (Feat. Anitta & Pabllo Vittar)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Major_Lazer/Particula_Feat_Nasty_C_Ice_Prince_Patoranking__Jidenna/</id><title>Major Lazer - Particula (Feat. Nasty C, Ice Prince, Patoranking & Jidenna) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:47:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:47:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Major_Lazer/Particula_Feat_Nasty_C_Ice_Prince_Patoranking__Jidenna/" title="Major Lazer - Particula (Feat. Nasty C, Ice Prince, Patoranking & Jidenna) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They told me everybody's 15 minutes <br>in a different timezone <br>And since I have it at the moment <br>You the one <br>I wanna shine my light on <br>Get your life get your life <br>little mama <br>Won't you get your life on <br>Ain't nothing cooler than <br>the wrong moves <br>When you do 'em to the right song <br>the right song <br>Let's shoot this movie and <br>put the shit on repeat <br>I hope this Mary's not <br>making you fall asleep <br>Before we hit the road <br>put our phones on silent <br>Nobody's tryna bring <br>sand to the beach <br>What would it take to change <br>your plans for the weekend <br>'Cause I am tryna kick it like EA <br>The whole thing the pre-party <br>the pre-sex <br>Now we hit the Major League <br>where the G's at <br>I like you girl in particula <br>You in particula <br>Said I like your waist in particula <br>ah ha eh <br>I like you girl in particula yeah <br>You in particula <br>Said I like your waist in particula <br>ah ha eh <br>Come come give me the love girl <br>Give me the love girl <br>give me the love girl <br>Come come come <br>give me the love girl <br>Bring di dance and <br>gimme some culture <br>Come come give me the love girl <br>I wanna give you <br>what I'm feeling here yeah <br>Give me love one of these days <br>I know the first time <br>I saw you there yeah <br>Give me love one of these days <br>Carry carry cary go <br>Na u sabi mami you already know <br>Carry carry cary go <br>Me I can't lie oh <br>I like you gal in particular <br>Can I see your particulars <br>I been screening you <br>like una pelicula <br>So b-b-baby let's stir it up yeah <br>I I've come to see you <br>what's in your eyes <br>Give me that love girl <br>Bia Bia Bia Baby <br>I like you girl in particula <br>You in particula <br>Said I like your waist in particula <br>ah ha eh <br>I like you girl in particula yeah <br>You in particula <br>Said I like your waist in particula <br>ah ha eh <br>Come come give me the love girl <br>Give me the love girl <br>give me the love girl <br>Come come come <br>give me the love girl <br>Bring di dance and <br>gimme some culture <br>Come come give me the love girl <br>Give me the love girl <br>give me the love girl <br>Come come come <br>give me the love girl <br>Bring di dance gyal <br>give me some culture <br>Come come give me the love girl <br>Give me the love girl <br>give me the love girl <br>Come come come <br>give me the love girl <br>Bring di dance gyal <br>give me some culture <br>Come come give me the love girl <br>I like you girl in particula <br>You in particula <br>Said I like your waist in particula <br>ah ha eh <br>I like you girl in particula yeah <br>You in particula <br>Said I like your waist in particula <br>ah ha eh <br>]]></content><category term="Major Lazer" label="Major Lazer"/><category term="Particula (Feat. Nasty C, Ice Prince, Patoranking & Jidenna)" label="Particula (Feat. Nasty C, Ice Prince, Patoranking & Jidenna)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Major_Lazer/Buscando_Huellas_Feat_J_Balvin__Sean_Paul/</id><title>Major Lazer - Buscando Huellas (Feat. J Balvin & Sean Paul) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:47:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:47:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Major_Lazer/Buscando_Huellas_Feat_J_Balvin__Sean_Paul/" title="Major Lazer - Buscando Huellas (Feat. J Balvin & Sean Paul) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Major Lazer <br>J Balvin <br>Tell dem gyals dem <br><br>[J Balvin] <br>Mai tu parece de island <br>Hay algo en ti que no es normal <br>Y a mi ese algo me encanta <br><br>Me parece super especial <br>Se ve que no le gusta lo material <br>A ella es dificil darle <br>En su juego siempre quiere ganar <br><br>No sabe como parar <br>Cuando su cuerpo mueve <br>Mas ella pide <br>No conoce el final <br>Ahhh ey ey <br>No te dejo de mirar <br>Ay ya parezco tu detective <br>Buscando huellas para encontrarte <br>Y tu mas desapareces <br><br>Ya no me aguanta mas, yo la quiero tener <br>Su vibra poderosa la quiero tener <br>De misteriosos ojos me enamore <br>Ya oohh <br>Y queria ganar <br>De lejos la miro rechazando Botellas <br>No le importaba nada solo queria bailar <br>Le dijeron que Balvin quiere conocerla <br>Pero poco le interesaba <br><br>No sabe como parar <br>Cuando su cuerpo mueve mas ella pide <br>No conoce el final <br>Ahhh yeah yeah <br>No te dejo de mirar <br>Ay ya parezco tu detective <br>Buscando Huellas para encontrarte <br>Y tu me desapareces <br><br>[Sean Paul] <br>Heaven get send ya for me baby <br>Love how u move and me love how you stay <br>Love how you slay dem pon di daily <br>Definitely most definitely <br>Man a look time can u man a pree <br>And mi just can't get enough of your body <br>Check me now girl <br>Tell me this is destiny tell me now that <br>You want me set you free baby girl <br><br>[J Balvin] <br>No sabe como parar <br>Cuando su cuerpo mueve <br>Mas ella pide <br>No conoce el final <br><br>Ahh ya ya <br><br>No te dejo de mirar <br>Ay ya parezco tu detective <br>Buscando huellas para encontrarte <br>Y tu mas desapareces <br><br>[Sean Paul] <br>Come get with it]]></content><category term="Major Lazer" label="Major Lazer"/><category term="Buscando Huellas (Feat. J Balvin & Sean Paul)" label="Buscando Huellas (Feat. J Balvin & Sean Paul)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Major_Lazer/Know_No_Better_Feat_Quavo/</id><title>Major Lazer - Know No Better (Feat. Quavo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:47:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:47:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Major_Lazer/Know_No_Better_Feat_Quavo/" title="Major Lazer - Know No Better (Feat. Quavo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah straight up <br>Ooh <br>Wrist look like it been dipped <br>Dipped in that dipped in that <br>dipped in that <br>Script look like it been flipped <br>Flippin' that flippin' that <br>flippin' that yah <br>Pull up in that foreign <br>my God skrrr skrrr <br>Whole squad get in that <br>get in that <br>Please say it ain't true <br>I had to go and cop two <br>Hell nah we can't fit in that <br>Wild ones <br>like we fresh out the cage <br>Showtime baby <br>fresh off the stage <br>Bad lil mama fresh off the page <br>Front like you love <br>but you know <br>that you hate it <br>Yeah you know no better <br>Yeah you know no better <br>Yeah you know no better <br>Ooh <br>Yeah you know no better <br>Say you different <br>who you kiddin' <br>Yeah you know no better <br>Ooh save that talk for the ones <br>Who don't know no better <br>know no better <br>'Cause baby I know you better <br>'cause baby I know no better <br>Baby I know you better <br>baby I know <br>Baby I know you better <br>Baby I know you better <br>Straight up <br>Baby I know you better <br>Baby I know I know no better <br>Top dropped off on my whip <br>Wippin' that wippin' that <br>wippin' that <br>Yellow and that purple on mix <br>Mixin' that mixin' that <br>mixin' that yeah <br>Copped my bitch <br>from the tropics yeah <br>You know where she sittin' at <br>Takin' shots pourin' bottle <br>after bottle after bottle <br>Hell nah <br>we ain't sippin' that yah <br>Wild ones <br>like we fresh out the cage <br>Showtime baby <br>fresh off the stage <br>Bad lil mama fresh off the page <br>Front like you love <br>but you know <br>that you hate it <br>Yeah you know no better <br>straight up <br>Yeah you know no better <br>yah yah <br>Yeah you know no better <br>Ooh <br>Yeah you know no better <br>Say you different <br>who you kiddin' <br>Yeah you know no better <br>Ooh save that talk for the ones <br>Who don't know no better <br>no better <br>'Cause baby I know you better <br>'cause baby I know no better <br>Baby I know you better <br>baby I know <br>Baby I know you better <br>Baby I know you better <br>Baby I know you better <br>Baby I know I know no better <br>Quavo <br>Drop top on the whip drop top <br>Dab of ranch on the chips dab <br>Ice cream gave her chills <br>ice cream <br>Too much cash pay the bills <br>I make her ride Mercedes <br>skrrr skrrr <br>I can afford the latest yeah <br>Baby ignore the ratings <br>ignore 'em <br>'Cause pull up we pump up <br>we ragin' <br>We know no better no <br>Stack my bread up stack <br>Don't get fed up nope <br>Ain't gon' let up yeah <br>You told me to shut up shut up <br>But I'mma do better huh <br>It's not my race ooh <br>Get out my face get out <br>Drop my case drop it <br>Which way where <br>Dat way hey <br>Yeah you know no better <br>Say you different <br>who you kiddin' <br>Yeah you know no better <br>Ooh save that talk for the ones <br>who don't know no better <br>'Cause baby I know you better <br>Maybe I know you better <br>straight up <br>Maybe I know you better <br>Maybe I know you better <br>maybe I know you better <br>Baby I know I know no better <br>]]></content><category term="Major Lazer" label="Major Lazer"/><category term="Know No Better (Feat. Quavo)" label="Know No Better (Feat. Quavo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/The_Surge/</id><title>Dan Bull - The Surge - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:50:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:50:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dan_Bull/The_Surge/" title="Dan Bull - The Surge - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've got this <br>I've got this <br>I've got this <br><br>I'm slowly roasting under the solar rays <br>Been stuck in this hole for days <br>What virtuoso made the oh so great proposal <br>Of drones with blades <br>Hey, don't separate my nose and face <br>My looks will go to waste <br>I was low a moment ago <br>But pain's a way to motivate <br>I don't suppose they'll float away <br>So I'll make a new way to negotiate <br>I, turn over the page with no delay <br>I'm my own protege <br>I'm a dark soul with two hard shoulders <br>Known as the motorway <br>So don't you dare overtake <br>Or you'll need a new coat of paint <br>Severing extremities is a clever method <br>We use to lose a load of weight <br>Your tech's like your culture <br>Free for me to go and appropriate <br>Those flows provoke debate <br>Blowing up at an explosive rate <br>So debased I won't associate with you <br>You're overrated <br>I'd prefer to go on a date <br>With a moldy plate of roast potatoes <br>Craving so voracious I could float in space <br>And won't be weightless <br>How the heck did I get so big <br>Sticking tech to my exo rig <br>But it's never sufficient <br>I'm already getting ready for the next growth <br>So let's go dig <br><br>Never mind the gods and their schemes <br>We are the cogs in their machine <br>The wildest fighting dogs you've ever seen <br>Blood <br>Petrol <br>Metal <br>Sweat and dreams <br><br>Adapt to stress, disaster <br>Like a committed method actor <br>No happy ever after <br>A vicious metal raptor <br>With the extra X factor <br>Collecting tech scrap for <br>The aptitudes I have to yet master <br>Get faster <br>Test, you'll get your neck snapped <br>So It's messed up like It's Glen Baxter's sketchpad <br>That's drenched in alphabet pasta <br>Sepp blatter <br>Deceptive bastard <br>Fully fledged engine of vengeful havoc <br>A tragic ending's pending <br>When you're a drunk trying to enter traffic <br>Shrapnel spins severed limbs <br>Liquidating everything <br>From megaliths <br>To insignificant details we see the devil in <br>We go to the CREO party <br>Dismantle the demonarchy <br>Don't start when you can't complete <br>Or your arteries will receive no heartbeat <br><br>Never mind the gods and their schemes <br>We are the cogs in their machine <br>The wildest fighting dogs you've ever seen <br>Blood <br>Petrol <br>Metal <br>Sweat and dreams <br><br>I've got this <br><br>Someone call a doctor <br>I've got this <br><br>Doctor, I've got this urge <br>But I'm lost for words <br>Feel like I'm on the verge of popping off <br>Do not disturb <br>Call off the search <br>I've lost my nerve <br>Giving you just desserts <br>I'm kicking you off of the kerb <br>My golly gosh, that must have hurt <br><br>Never mind <br>Never mind the gods and their schemes <br>We are the cogs in their machine <br>The wildest fighting dogs you've ever seen <br>Blood <br>Petrol <br>Metal <br>Sweat and dreams]]></content><category term="Dan Bull" label="Dan Bull"/><category term="The Surge" label="The Surge"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kiana_Valenciano/Does_She_Know_Feat_Curtismith/</id><title>Kiana Valenciano - Does She Know (Feat. Curtismith) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:50:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:50:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kiana_Valenciano/Does_She_Know_Feat_Curtismith/" title="Kiana Valenciano - Does She Know (Feat. Curtismith) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You got a lot of nerve baby <br>Coming up to me like I did you wrong <br>Acting like you own the world lately <br>No need to deny <br>I know what's going on <br>You've been off of your pride <br>I know you're broken inside <br>You're rolling in the grave of your own mistake <br>Yes <br><br>Say hello to the girl you can't let go <br>Does she know when your home <br>It's me you're trying to call on your phone <br>I'm holding back everything I wanna say <br>Consider yourself lucky that I'm choosing to behave <br><br>Does she know tell me does she does she know <br>You're calling me every night <br>Does she know tell me does she does she know <br>And baby your wasting your time <br>Does she know tell me does she does she know <br>You're calling me every night <br>Does she know tell me does she does she know <br>Does she know <br><br>Don't go thinking you still got a hold on me <br>You're crazy if you think that I still give a damn <br>I'm sick and tired of all the games that you play <br>Stay out of my head don't think you understand <br>We been done for so long <br>I think that you should move on <br>Wasn't it you who said that I should go <br><br>Say hello to the girl you can't let go <br>Does she know when your home <br>It's me you're trying to call on your phone <br>I'm holding back everything I wanna say <br>Consider yourself lucky that I'm choosing to behave <br><br>Does she know tell me does she does she know <br>Tell me does she does she know <br>Does she know tell me does she does she know <br>You're calling me every night <br>Does she know tell me does she does she know <br>Does she know tell me does she does she know <br>Does she know <br><br>Damn girl you know I messed up <br>Letting go of my forever just to see how I could test love <br>I'm realizing you're the best of <br>Any of these other women who be thinking they be next up <br>I've been having dreams of you <br>I've been wishing I could build a team with you <br>I've been doing everything Just to satisfy my needs <br>Only after that is when I even think of you I know <br>So selfish <br>I know that I think of these feelings I wish I could hold back <br>But lately its alienating_____ <br>And after we get it I see Mona Lisa in you <br>I had your digits before all these mistresses <br>I give it all back to start back with you <br>I was adjusting to all this but now that I got it <br>I swear all I'm missing is you <br><br>Say hello to the girl you can't let go <br>Does she know when your home <br>It's me you're trying to call on your phone <br>I'm holding back everything I wanna say <br>Consider yourself lucky that I'm choosing to behave <br><br>Does she know tell me does she does she know <br>Tell me does she does she know <br>Does she know tell me does she does she know <br>You're calling me every night <br>Does she know tell me does she Does she know <br>Does she know <br>Does she know tell me does she does she know <br>You're calling me every night <br>Does she know tell me does she does she know <br>Tell me does she does she know <br>Does she know tell me does she does she know <br>Tell me tell me does she know]]></content><category term="Kiana Valenciano" label="Kiana Valenciano"/><category term="Does She Know (Feat. Curtismith)" label="Does She Know (Feat. Curtismith)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/버드리/내사랑_웬수/</id><title>버드리 - 내사랑 웬수 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:52:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:52:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B2%84%EB%93%9C%EB%A6%AC/%EB%82%B4%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_%EC%9B%AC%EC%88%98/" title="버드리 - 내사랑 웬수 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한 평생 같이 사는 <br>지겨운 당신 <br>이제는 떠나가 버렸으면 <br>내사랑 웬수웬수 야 <br>생각한 적도 많이 있었는데 <br>화가 나서 했던 생각이었어 <br>평생을 너만 위해 <br>너만 위해 살아왔어 <br>하루만 안 보여도 <br>보고 싶은 걸 <br>우리는 둘이 하나야 <br>사랑한다 사랑해 당신 <br>너무나도 사랑해 <br>이 웬수야 <br>너 없인 정말 못살아 <br>좋아한다 좋아해 당신 <br>너무나도 사랑해 <br>이 웬수야 <br>나없인 정말 못살겠지 <br>쾌지나칭칭 나네 <br>쾌지나칭칭 나네 <br>쾌지나칭칭 나네 <br>쾌지나칭칭 나네 <br>어쩔 땐 웬수 같은 <br>생각이드네 <br>사랑한 사람 맞나싶어요 <br>내사랑 웬수웬수 야 <br>그 옆집 아저씨만도 못한 사람 <br>열 받아서 했던 말들이었어 <br>평생을 너만 위해 <br>너만 위해 살아왔어 <br>하루만 안 보여도 <br>보고 싶은 걸 <br>우리는 둘이 하나야 <br>사랑한다 사랑해 당신 <br>너무나도 사랑해 <br>이 웬수야 <br>너 없인 정말 못살아 <br>좋아한다 좋아해 당신 <br>너무나도 사랑해 <br>이 웬수야 <br> 나없인 정말 못살겠지 <br>사랑한다 사랑해 당신 <br>너무나도 사랑해 <br>너 없인 정말 못살아 <br>좋아한다 좋아해 당신 <br>너무나도 사랑해 <br>이 웬수야 <br>나없인 정말 못살겠지 <br>쾌지나칭칭 나네 <br>쾌지나칭칭 나네]]></content><category term="버드리" label="버드리"/><category term="내사랑 웬수" label="내사랑 웬수"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/해나리_Hannah_Lee/그_사랑_때문에/</id><title>해나리 (Hannah Lee) - 그 사랑 때문에 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:52:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:52:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%B4%EB%82%98%EB%A6%AC_Hannah_Lee/%EA%B7%B8_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_%EB%95%8C%EB%AC%B8%EC%97%90/" title="해나리 (Hannah Lee) - 그 사랑 때문에 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주님이 걸으신 그 길 <br>붉은 피로 물든 그 길 <br>수 십번 넘어지고 <br>찢기고 상하시며 <br>홀로 걸으신 길 <br><br>나 이제 피할 수 없어 <br>붉은 길을 걸어가요 <br>피하지 않으시고 <br>날 위해 견디시며 <br>오르신 좁은 길 <br><br>그 사랑 때문에 <br>그 사랑 때문에 <br>그 길 걸어가죠 <br>십자가 길 <br>나 이제 주를 위해 살고 <br>주를 위해 죽고 <br>주와 함께 걷네 <br><br>나 이제 피할 수 없어 <br>붉은 길을 걸어가요 <br>피하지 않으시고 <br>날 위해 견디시며 <br>오르신 좁은 길 <br><br>그 사랑 때문에 <br>그 사랑 때문에 <br>그 길 걸어가죠 <br>십자가 길 <br>나 이제 주를 위해 살고 <br>주를 위해 죽고 <br>주와 함께 걷네 <br><br>그 사랑 때문에 <br>그 사랑 때문에 <br>십자가 길 <br>나 이제 주를 위해 살고 <br>주를 위해 죽고 <br>주와 함께 걷네 <br>그 길]]></content><category term="해나리 (Hannah Lee)" label="해나리 (Hannah Lee)"/><category term="그 사랑 때문에" label="그 사랑 때문에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한정선/내_뒷모습/</id><title>한정선 - 내 뒷모습 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:53:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:53:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EC%A0%95%EC%84%A0/%EB%82%B4_%EB%92%B7%EB%AA%A8%EC%8A%B5/" title="한정선 - 내 뒷모습 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 너를 잡지 못하고 아혼에 잠긴 것은 <br>애당초 이유 없는 이 마음 때문에 <br>사랑을 저버린 후에 그대를 보냈나요 <br>가슴에 맺힐 아픔생각 못한 채 <br>우리의 꿈을 찾아 <br>불빛 따라 걸었었는데 <br>남은 것은 고독뿐 허망한 눈길뿐 <br>가까이 두고두고 느낄 수 없는 것은 <br>정들까 두려웠던 뭇 내음 때문에 <br>슬픔을 멀리해두고 그대를 보았나요 <br>말할 수 없는 그림자 때문에 <br>우리의 꿈을 찾아 <br>별빛 따라 흐느꼈는데 <br>뒷모습은 끝없이 가슴을 에이네 <br>그 길로 떠나야 해 <br>]]></content><category term="한정선" label="한정선"/><category term="내 뒷모습" label="내 뒷모습"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한정선/그대_위해_바치는_꽃/</id><title>한정선 - 그대 위해 바치는 꽃 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:53:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:53:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EC%A0%95%EC%84%A0/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80_%EC%9C%84%ED%95%B4_%EB%B0%94%EC%B9%98%EB%8A%94_%EA%BD%83/" title="한정선 - 그대 위해 바치는 꽃 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비 오면 비에 젖고 <br>눈이 오면 눈에 덮인 <br>마음에 신호등 꺼져 <br>살아있는지 계절 없는지 <br>사랑했는지 행복했는지 <br>맥 아닌 선상으로 맺힌 불빛 <br>그대로 이 자리에 머물러 돌고 <br>깨어났는지 일어섰는지 <br>너를 위해 바치는 꽃 <br>홀로이 필까 <br>졸음도 허이하니 어이 덜까 <br>알 수 없는 노래는 울려 퍼지고 <br>사랑 없는지 계절 있는지 <br>울고 있는지 웃고 있는지 <br>하나의 강을 건너 맺힌 물빛 <br>그대로 그 자리에 머물러 돌고 <br>잠들었는지 인도했는지 <br>너를 위해 바치는 꽃 <br>조용히 필까 <br>]]></content><category term="한정선" label="한정선"/><category term="그대 위해 바치는 꽃" label="그대 위해 바치는 꽃"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nikka_Costa/Come_Rain_Or_Come_Shine/</id><title>Nikka Costa - Come Rain Or Come Shine - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:57:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:57:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nikka_Costa/Come_Rain_Or_Come_Shine/" title="Nikka Costa - Come Rain Or Come Shine - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm gonna love you, like nobody's loved you <br>Come rain or come shine <br>High as a mountain, deep as a river <br>Come rain or come shine <br>I guess when you met me <br>It was just one of those things <br>But don't you ever bet me <br>'Cause I'm gonna be true if you let me <br>You're gonna love me, like nobody's loved me <br>Come rain or come shine <br>Happy together, unhappy together <br>And won't be fine <br>Days may be cloudy or sunny <br>We're in or out of the money <br>But I'm with you always <br>I'm with you rain or shine <br><br>Days may be cloudy or sunny <br>We're in or out of the money <br>But I'm with you always <br>I'm with you rain or shine]]></content><category term="Nikka Costa" label="Nikka Costa"/><category term="Come Rain Or Come Shine" label="Come Rain Or Come Shine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nikka_Costa/Nothing_Compares_2_U/</id><title>Nikka Costa - Nothing Compares 2 U - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:57:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:57:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nikka_Costa/Nothing_Compares_2_U/" title="Nikka Costa - Nothing Compares 2 U - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's been seven hours and fifteen days <br>Since you took your love away <br>I go out every night and sleep all day <br>Since you took your love away <br><br>Since you been gone I can do whatever I want <br>I can see who ever I choose <br>I can eat my dinner in a fancy restaurant <br>But nothing, said nothing can take away these blues <br><br>Cause nothing compares <br>Nothing compares to you <br><br>It's been so lonely without you here <br>Like a bird without a song, oh <br>Nothing can stop these lonely tears from falling <br>Tell me, baby, where did I go wrong <br><br>I could put my arms around every boy I see <br>But they'd only remind me of you <br>I went to the doctor and guess what it told me <br>Guess what it told me <br>He said, "Girl, you better try to have fun no matter what you do" <br>But he's a fool <br><br>Cause nothing compares <br>Nothing compares to you <br><br>Nothing compares <br>Nothing compares to you <br><br>All the flowers that u planted, mam <br>In the back yard <br>All died when you went away <br>I know that living with you baby is sometimes hard <br>But I'm willing to give it another try <br><br>Nothing compares <br>Nothing compares to you, oh <br>Nothing compares <br>Nothing compares to you, ohh <br>Nothing compares <br>Nothing compares to you <br>Nothing compares <br>Nothing compares... ohhh <br>Ohhh]]></content><category term="Nikka Costa" label="Nikka Costa"/><category term="Nothing Compares 2 U" label="Nothing Compares 2 U"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/Ally/</id><title>Sinead Harnett - Ally - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:59:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:59:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/Ally/" title="Sinead Harnett - Ally - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1] <br>They say a good thing won't go away <br>Why did you go away? <br>Baby you had a role to play <br>Why were you led astray? <br>Seems all love that you were given <br>Didn't have a second for me <br>But a second's all I need <br><br>[Chorus] <br>To tell you the truth <br>So maybe you'll see <br>You were my ally, ally <br>'Cause were there was you <br>There would be me <br>You were my ally <br>Whether wrong or right <br>You were by my side <br>And I still want you, want you <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>And I don't know if you'll ever really feel the same <br>Or if I'll ever forgive the fact that maybe I'm the one to blame <br>'Cause loving you were given <br>Didn't have a second to breathe <br>But a second's all I need <br><br>[Chorus] <br>To tell you the truth <br>So maybe you'll see <br>You were my ally, ally <br>'Cause were there was you <br>There would be me <br>You were my ally <br>Whether wrong or right <br>You were by my side <br>And I still want you, want you <br>Want you, want you <br><br>[Outro] <br>Come back to me <br>Come back to me <br>Come back to me <br>Come back to me <br>Come back to me <br>Come back to me <br>Come back to me <br>Come back to me]]></content><category term="Sinead Harnett" label="Sinead Harnett"/><category term="Ally" label="Ally"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/Want_It_With_You/</id><title>Sinead Harnett - Want It With You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:59:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:59:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/Want_It_With_You/" title="Sinead Harnett - Want It With You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1] <br>Said you wanna be a better man <br>Said you folding with a losing hand <br>You think it's too hard for me to understand <br>You don't notice me, you don't know it's me <br><br>[Pre-Chorus 1] <br>Who bleeds the same as you do? <br>Who feels the suffering too? <br>I'm just as broken <br>But you don't see the truth <br>So you'll never sympathize <br>You say your love is a lie <br>If that's what it is <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I want it with you <br>I want it with you <br>You, you, you, you <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>How can you still be a stranger to me? <br>Only know you through this intimacy <br>And every riddle that I hear on repeat <br>Do you lie to me when you lay with me? <br><br>[Pre-Chorus 2] <br>This don't make sense anymore <br>You leave your ash on the floor <br>You give me nothing <br>But all I have is yours <br>It's so apparent to me <br>Your love is duplicity <br>If that's what it is <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I want it with you <br>I want it with you <br>You, you, you, you <br><br>[Bridge] <br>Saving you is breaking me, oh yeah <br>And I wondered if you know, ooh <br>I'm shattered by your broken pieces <br>Against the wall, despite it all <br>(I want it with you) <br>Despite it all <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I want it with you (you) <br>I want it with you (you) <br>I want it with you (you) <br>I want it with you (you) <br><br><br>[Outro] <br>I want it with...]]></content><category term="Sinead Harnett" label="Sinead Harnett"/><category term="Want It With You" label="Want It With You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/So_Solo/</id><title>Sinead Harnett - So Solo - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T22:59:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T22:59:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/So_Solo/" title="Sinead Harnett - So Solo - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1] <br>Lately, I lost my light <br>So jaded, I'm almost blind <br>And I didn't wanna let you down <br>But I don't wanna talk about <br>All the things that I couldn't do <br>So lately I just get high <br>Here's to another wasted day <br>Making paper airplanes <br>'Cause it seems I'm running out of words to say <br><br>[Chorus] <br>So solo <br>So solo <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>My love, she's on my side <br>But she's chocked up <br>She can't swallow her pride, no, no <br>So I sip it all, sip it all away <br>'Cause I'm not taking all, taking all the blame <br>And I know I'm acting up <br>But the emptiness is tough <br>And I wanna be, wanna be more <br>What the hell am I doing this for? <br>If I'm only running out of words to say <br><br>[Chorus] <br>So solo (Back up, back up) <br>So solo (Back up, back up) <br>So solo (Back up, back up) <br>I'm feeling so solo (Back up, back up) <br><br>[Bridge] <br>I'm forced to carry on <br>No feeling in my bones <br>How did I get so low, so low? <br><br>[Chorus] <br>So solo (Back up, back up) <br>So solo (So solo) <br>So solo (Back up, back up) <br>I'm feeling so solo (Back up, back up)]]></content><category term="Sinead Harnett" label="Sinead Harnett"/><category term="So Solo" label="So Solo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/Equation/</id><title>Sinead Harnett - Equation - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:00:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:00:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/Equation/" title="Sinead Harnett - Equation - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse] <br>You're that one equation <br>That I can never solve <br>My inner frustration <br>Always seems to show <br>And I know it's hard for you <br>You're a prisoner <br>But it doesn't mean I'm not the same <br>Every time I look at you it's like a mirror <br>So I only got myself to blame <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Do you need me <br>Need me like I need you, like I need you <br>Do you need me <br>Need me like I need you, like I need you <br><br>[Post-Chorus] <br>Now, now, now, wow <br>Now, now, now, wow]]></content><category term="Sinead Harnett" label="Sinead Harnett"/><category term="Equation" label="Equation"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/Dont_Waste_My_Time/</id><title>Sinead Harnett - Don`t Waste My Time - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:00:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:00:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/Dont_Waste_My_Time/" title="Sinead Harnett - Don`t Waste My Time - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1] <br>I give you all my love and affection now <br>I show you all my care and protection now <br>Now you don't even want it <br>Like you don't wanna notice <br>So tell me what you put in all the work for? <br>You swore me as so deep but you're at the shore <br>Remember you were floating <br>I used to be the ocean, yeah <br><br>[Pre-Chorus 1] <br>Oh yeah, what is it about my mind? <br>Masochistic by design <br>Slowly sinking and I know <br>I want you to go <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Don't waste my time <br>You think I'm blind <br>Don't waste my time <br>You're still not mine <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>I wonder if it's just an addiction now <br>I couldn't turn the fix of your friction down <br>I never had a moment <br>To see I wasn't chosen <br>So tell me what you put in all the work for? <br>I'm drowning in the deep but you're at the shore <br>Remember I was frozen <br>And now you got me soaking <br><br>[Pre-Chorus 2] <br>Oh yeah, what is it about my mind? <br>Craving things I can't define <br>Over thinking and it shows <br>Don't want you to go <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Don't waste my time <br>You think I'm blind <br>Don't waste my time <br>You're still not mine <br><br>[Bridge] <br>And I wonder who's bed you're in tonight <br>When the one that's so wrong can love your right <br>It's becoming so clear to me <br>It's a role you're playing <br><br>[Chorus 2] <br>Don't waste my time <br>You think I'm blind <br>Don't waste my time <br>Since you'll never be mine]]></content><category term="Sinead Harnett" label="Sinead Harnett"/><category term="Don`t Waste My Time" label="Don`t Waste My Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/Heal_You_Feat_Wretch_32/</id><title>Sinead Harnett - Heal You (Feat. Wretch 32) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:00:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:00:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/Heal_You_Feat_Wretch_32/" title="Sinead Harnett - Heal You (Feat. Wretch 32) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1: Sinead Harnett] <br>Watching you sleep <br>You stayed up telling me your fears <br>And how this life has done you wrong <br>It's cutting you deep <br>But you're selling yourself way too short <br>You can't see clear, but please keep strong <br>Can't begin to even know your pain <br>But I don't wanna see you hurt yourself like this <br>You know this quick fixes ain't foolin' no one <br>Just lean on me, it's now or never <br>Don't you want to see the light or feel the sun? <br><br>[Chorus: Sinead Harnett] <br>Ooh, I wish I could heal you <br>How good would it feel to <br>Let go of all you've been through? <br>How I wish that I can take it away <br>But you're the only one that can help yourself, baby <br><br>[Verse 2: Sinead Harnett] <br>Lost in your blues <br>Running away from the reality that's left you on your own <br>And If you could choose <br>You would do anything to bring him back <br>So you are not alone <br>Can't begin to even know your pain <br>But I don't wanna see you hurt yourself like this <br>Don't underestimate how far you have come <br>I'm here for you, just take my hand <br>Oh, won't you dare to see the light or feel the sun? <br><br>[Chorus: Sinead Harnett] <br>Ooh, I wish I could heal you <br>How good would it feel to <br>Let go of all you've been through <br>How I wish that I can take it away <br>But you're the only one that can help yourself, baby <br><br>Ooh, I wish I could heal you <br>How good would it feel to <br>Let go of all you've been through <br>How I wish that I can take it away <br>But you're the only one that can help yourself, baby <br><br>[Bridge: Wretch 32 &amp; Sinead Harnett] <br>Woke up beside you <br>That's the first time I slept in two months <br>My old ways have got me busy trying to find some new love <br>Just lost another brother <br>I'm gettin' touchy, nearly lost my mother <br>In and out of hospital, who's a motherfucker <br>And the feds cued your main lad Don Mark <br>Little brothers going to jail <br>It's too much for one heart <br>Baby if I cried would you respect me? <br>If not, it's probably best that you neglect me <br>Baby can you hear me? <br>I can show you where it hurts though <br>I'm only human like Superman when he's in work clothes <br>I was told for you to be the man, you stay in work mode <br>I'm with a round like the pizza man, the way I turn dough <br>Harnett, I'm asking you to place me in your harnest <br>If not, I send my best regards regardless <br>Yeah, they say the can cuts deep <br>I was hoping that you mean don't bleed, don't, no <br><br><br>[Chorus: Sinead Harnett] <br>Ooh, I wish I could heal you <br>How good would it feel to <br>Let go of all you've been through <br>How I wish that I can take it away <br>But you're the only one that can help yourself, baby <br><br>Ooh, I wish I could heal you <br>How good would it feel to <br>Let go of all you've been through <br>How I wish that I can take it away <br>But you're the only one that can help yourself, baby]]></content><category term="Sinead Harnett" label="Sinead Harnett"/><category term="Heal You (Feat. Wretch 32)" label="Heal You (Feat. Wretch 32)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/Unconditional/</id><title>Sinead Harnett - Unconditional - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:00:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:00:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/Unconditional/" title="Sinead Harnett - Unconditional - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1] <br>Sat in your car in my driveway <br>Where did we lose the time? <br>We were just living for Fridays <br>When I could call you mine <br>When I could only see blue <br>You taught me to swim <br>And when you didn't have to <br>You took me in <br><br>[Pre-Chorus] <br>If we can make it, make it <br>Make it all possible <br>Then we can take it, take it <br>Take it and have it all <br><br>[Chorus] <br>This is unconditional <br>This is unconditional <br>This is unconditional <br>This is unconditional <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>I leave yours only wanting more <br>And count the pavement stones <br>You cut me a key for the front door <br>So I could call it home <br>When I could only see blue <br>You taught me to swim <br>And when you didn't have to <br>You took me in <br><br>[Pre-Chorus] <br>If we can make it, make it <br>Make it all possible <br>Then we can take it, take it <br>Take it and have it all <br><br>If we can make it, make it <br>Make it all possible <br>Then we can take it, take it <br>Take it and have it all <br><br>[Chorus] <br>This is unconditional <br>This is unconditional <br>This is unconditional <br>This is unconditional <br><br>This is unconditional <br>This is unconditional <br>This is unconditional <br>This is unconditional <br><br>[Outro] <br>Unconditional <br>Unconditional <br>Unconditional <br>Unconditional]]></content><category term="Sinead Harnett" label="Sinead Harnett"/><category term="Unconditional" label="Unconditional"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/Still_Miss_You/</id><title>Sinead Harnett - Still Miss You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:00:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:00:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sinead_Harnett/Still_Miss_You/" title="Sinead Harnett - Still Miss You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1] <br>Your energy it scares me <br>I wanna protect my own <br>The center of my universe <br>But you are a black hole <br><br>[Pre-Chorus 1] <br>And your darkness steals the light I built for both of us <br>When you look me in the eyes I feel you cover me up <br>All the colors starts to fade and yet it's not enough <br>We're stuck in a habit <br>And it's kinda tragic <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I can't fix you up, oh no <br>I can't fix you up, no no <br>I can't fix you up, oh no <br>But I still miss you <br>(But I still miss you) <br><br>[Post-Chorus] <br>But I still miss you <br>But I still miss you <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>I was like a pillar <br>Under your pedestal <br>Even when I held you up <br>You still found a way to fall, yeah <br><br>[Pre-Chorus 2] <br>And you should've had the strength to love the both of us <br>But you never gave yourself enough to know what it was <br>And I offer you forgiveness but it's not enough <br>We're stuck in a habit <br>And it's kinda tragic <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I can't fix you up, oh no <br>I can't fix you up, no no <br>I can't fix you up, oh no <br>But I still miss you <br>(But I still miss you) <br><br>[Bridge] <br>I'm a fool for trying <br>But I'm not a fool <br>The only thing I'm guilty of <br>Is loving you <br><br>[Chorus] <br>I can't fix you up, oh no <br>I can't fix you up, no no <br>I can't fix you up, oh no <br>But I still miss you <br>(But I still miss you) <br><br><br>[Post-Chorus] <br>But I still miss you <br>But I still miss you]]></content><category term="Sinead Harnett" label="Sinead Harnett"/><category term="Still Miss You" label="Still Miss You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anne_Pe/Feuerfuchs/</id><title>Anne Pe - Feuerfuchs - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:00:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:00:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Anne_Pe/Feuerfuchs/" title="Anne Pe - Feuerfuchs - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bravado, impossible <br>Too big to climb, too wild to tame <br>If only there was something else, to show me yourself <br><br>Don't say any more, hold your tongue <br>I’ve heard it before ？？ it's not love <br>You thought you had a plan, act like a gentleman <br>You thought you had it all effortlessly in hand <br>You thought you had me uh nana uh nana <br>But you can't fool me uh nana uh nana <br>There's no gentleman here <br><br>My everything is not for fun <br>You‘ve shown me that it's all you want <br>Why can't you settle down? <br>Cause I could love you I swear down <br><br>Don't say any more, hold your tongue <br>I’ve heard it before ？？ it‘s not love <br>You thought you had a plan, act like a gentleman <br>You thought you had it all effortlessly in hand <br>You thought you had me uh nana uh nana <br>But you can't fool me uh nana uh nana <br>There's no gentleman here <br><br>I need a gentleman who holds my hand, won't hide anything from me <br>A gentleman, who understands won't take anything from me <br>But you're a cheat, you're dark and weak <br>And you break everything that you can <br>Can't you see that I can't see no gentleman <br><br>You thought you had a plan, act like a gentleman <br>You thought you had it all effortlessly in hand <br>You thought you had me uh nana uh nana <br>Uh nana uh nana <br>Plan, act like a gentleman <br>You had it all <br>Uh nana uh nana <br>But you can't fool me, uh nana uh nana <br><br>There's no gentleman here]]></content><category term="Anne Pe" label="Anne Pe"/><category term="Feuerfuchs" label="Feuerfuchs"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brian_Reitzell/St_James_Infirmary_Blues_Feat_Mark_Lanegan_From_American_Gods_Soundtrack/</id><title>Brian Reitzell - St. James Infirmary Blues (Feat. Mark Lanegan) (From `American Gods` Soundtrack) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:00:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:00:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brian_Reitzell/St_James_Infirmary_Blues_Feat_Mark_Lanegan_From_American_Gods_Soundtrack/" title="Brian Reitzell - St. James Infirmary Blues (Feat. Mark Lanegan) (From `American Gods` Soundtrack) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[i went down to st.james infirmary <br>i heard my baby moan, <br>and i felt so broken hearted <br><br>she used to be my, my very own. <br><br>i went up to see the doctor, <br>she's very low he said <br>i went back to see my baby <br>good god, she's lying there dead. <br><br>but she's gone, she's gone and may god bless her, wherever she maybe. <br>she can search the whole world over, <br>she'll never find another man like me x2 <br>end]]></content><category term="Brian Reitzell" label="Brian Reitzell"/><category term="St. James Infirmary Blues (Feat. Mark Lanegan) (From `American Gods` Soundtrack)" label="St. James Infirmary Blues (Feat. Mark Lanegan) (From `American Gods` Soundtrack)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eric_Belucca/What_Is_Love_Feat_Philly_K/</id><title>Eric Belucca - What Is Love (Feat. Philly K) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:00:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:00:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eric_Belucca/What_Is_Love_Feat_Philly_K/" title="Eric Belucca - What Is Love (Feat. Philly K) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ohh Ohh, Ohh Ohh, Ohh Ohh, Ohh Ohh <br><br>[Verse 1] <br>I would tell you that I love you tonight <br>But I know that I’ve got time on my side <br>Where you goin'? Why you leavin' so soon? <br>Is there somewhere else that’s better for you? <br><br>[Chorus 1] <br>What is love if you’re not here with me? <br>What is love if it’s not guaranteed? <br>What is love if it just ups and leaves? <br>What is love if you're not here no more? <br>What is love if you’re not really sure? <br>What is love? What is love? <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>Tell myself I wouldn't cry when you're gone <br>But I know it's easier said than done <br>Look at me, look at me choked up now <br>Try to tell you but it won't come out <br><br>[Chorus 2] <br>What is love if you’re not here with me? <br>What is love if it’s not guaranteed? <br>What is love if it just ups and leaves? <br>What is love if you're not here no more? <br>What is love if you’re not really sure? <br>What is love if it just ups and goes? <br><br><br>[Bridge] <br>I can’t live without ya (I can’t live without ya) <br>I can’t live with ya (I can’t live with ya) <br>What goes around will come right back around <br>You won't know 'til it hit ya <br>We were supposed to be <br>We were supposed to be <br>We were supposed to be an empire <br><br>[Chorus 2] <br>What is love if you’re not here with me? <br>What is love if it’s not guaranteed? <br>What is love if it just ups and leaves? <br>What is love <br>What is love if you’re not really sure? <br>What is love if it just ups]]></content><category term="Eric Belucca" label="Eric Belucca"/><category term="What Is Love (Feat. Philly K)" label="What Is Love (Feat. Philly K)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소향/한숨_노래9단_흥부자댁/</id><title>소향 - 한숨 (노래9단 흥부자댁) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:01:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:01:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%ED%96%A5/%ED%95%9C%EC%88%A8_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%989%EB%8B%A8_%ED%9D%A5%EB%B6%80%EC%9E%90%EB%8C%81/" title="소향 - 한숨 (노래9단 흥부자댁) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[숨을 크게 쉬어봐요 <br>당신의 가슴 양쪽이 저리게 <br>조금은 아파올 때까지 <br>숨을 더 뱉어봐요 <br>당신의 안에 남은 게 없다고 <br>느껴질 때까지 <br>숨이 벅차올라도 괜찮아요 <br>아무도 그댈 탓하진 않아 <br>가끔은 실수해도 돼 <br>누구든 그랬으니까 <br>괜찮다는 말 <br>말뿐인 위로지만 <br>누군가의 한숨 <br>그 무거운 숨을 <br>내가 어떻게 <br>헤아릴 수가 있을까요 <br>당신의 한숨 <br>그 깊일 이해할 순 없겠지만 <br>괜찮아요 <br>내가 안아줄게요 <br>숨이 벅차올라도 괜찮아요 <br>아무도 그댈 탓하진 않아 <br>가끔은 실수해도 돼 <br>누구든 그랬으니까 <br>괜찮다는 말 <br>말뿐인 위로지만 <br>누군가의 한숨 <br>그 무거운 숨을 <br>내가 어떻게 <br>헤아릴 수가 있을까요 <br>당신의 한숨 <br>그 깊일 이해할 순 없겠지만 <br>괜찮아요 <br>내가 안아줄게요 <br>남들 눈엔 힘 빠지는 <br>한숨으로 보일진 몰라도 <br>나는 알고 있죠 <br>작은 한숨 내뱉기도 어려운 <br>하루를 보냈단 걸 <br>이제 다른 생각은 마요 <br>깊이 숨을 쉬어봐요 <br>그대로 내뱉어요 <br>누군가의 한숨 <br>그 무거운 숨을 <br>내가 어떻게 <br>헤아릴 수가 있을까요 <br>당신의 한숨 <br>그 깊일 이해할 순 없겠지만 <br>괜찮아요 괜찮아요 괜찮아요 <br>내가 안아줄게요 <br>정말 수고했어요 <br>]]></content><category term="소향" label="소향"/><category term="한숨 (노래9단 흥부자댁)" label="한숨 (노래9단 흥부자댁)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박혜나/그런일은_한놈_두시기_석삼_너구리/</id><title>박혜나 - 그런일은 (한놈 두시기 석삼 너구리) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:01:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:01:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%98%9C%EB%82%98/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%B0%EC%9D%BC%EC%9D%80_%ED%95%9C%EB%86%88_%EB%91%90%EC%8B%9C%EA%B8%B0_%EC%84%9D%EC%82%BC_%EB%84%88%EA%B5%AC%EB%A6%AC/" title="박혜나 - 그런일은 (한놈 두시기 석삼 너구리) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너무나 멀어보여요 <br>이렇게 가까이 있는데도 <br>언제나 나를 안아주던 <br>따스한 인사도 잊은건가요 <br>내가 뭘 잘못했나요 <br>혹시 나 미워졌나요 <br>아니죠 떠나려는건 아니죠 <br>그런일은 절대로 <br>없을거라 나는 믿을게요 <br>오늘은 안돼요 <br>내 사랑이 이대로는 <br>이별을 감당하긴 어려운걸요 <br>많은 약속을 다 지울순 없잖아요 <br>아직도 해드릴게 참 많이 있는데 <br>그리곤 다시 예전처럼 <br>다가와 웃으며 안아줄거죠 <br>정말 날 좋아했는데 <br>정말 날 아꼈었는데 <br>아니죠 그대를 다시 못보는 <br>그런일은 절대로 없는거죠 <br>나는 믿을게요 <br>오늘은 안돼요 내 사랑이 <br>이대로는 <br>이별을 감당하긴 어려운걸요 <br>많은 약속을 다 지울순 <br>없잖아요 <br>아직도 해드릴게 참 많은걸요 <br>내일 아침엔 더 힘들어 <br>질거예요 <br>어쩌면 며칠밤을 <br>지새우겠죠 <br>언제까지나 곁에 <br>있기로 했잖아요 <br>그대가 아니라면 난 혼자인걸요 <br>그대가 아니라면 난 혼자인걸요 <br>]]></content><category term="박혜나" label="박혜나"/><category term="그런일은 (한놈 두시기 석삼 너구리)" label="그런일은 (한놈 두시기 석삼 너구리)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/길미/넌_is_뭔들_인터넷_서핑마니아_서핑걸/</id><title>길미 - 넌 is 뭔들 (인터넷 서핑마니아 서핑걸) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:01:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:01:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%B8%EB%AF%B8/%EB%84%8C_is_%EB%AD%94%EB%93%A4_%EC%9D%B8%ED%84%B0%EB%84%B7_%EC%84%9C%ED%95%91%EB%A7%88%EB%8B%88%EC%95%84_%EC%84%9C%ED%95%91%EA%B1%B8/" title="길미 - 넌 is 뭔들 (인터넷 서핑마니아 서핑걸) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come on Hey Mommy <br>Come on Hey Daddy <br>이리와서 얘들 좀 봐 <br>Come on Hey Sister <br>Come on Hey Brother <br>누가 얘들 좀 말려줘 <br>귀여운 척 섹시한 척 <br>이쁜 척 그런 거 안해도 <br>날 알아보는 너 <br>센스매너 말투표정 <br>행동 하나까지 섬세한 <br>널 알아보는 나 <br>우리 둘 사이 딱 한 뼘 사이 <br>매일 아침 난 너의 <br>목소리로 눈을 뜨고 <br>우리 둘 사이 딱 맞는 타입 <br>Come on 거기 미스터 <br>Come on 이리와 봐 <br>천천히 아주 조금씩 <br>Hey 거기 미소가 예쁜 남자 <br>바로 너 <br>너어어어 아아아아 <br>날 미치게 하는 그런 남자 <br>몸매도 얼굴도 시선강탈 <br>Hey Mr. 생각이 멋진 남자 <br>바로 너 <br>너어어어 아아아아 <br>나 지금 너 땜에 혼란스러 <br>제발 누가 나 좀 말려줘 <br>월화수목금토일 <br>난 매일매일 너를 생각해 <br>넌 나를 생각해 <br>Word up Moon star <br>A형 B형 AB O형 <br>플러스 마이너스 상관없어 <br>S극과 N극처럼 <br>어떤 공식이든 끌려 <br>단지 그냥 너라서 <br>우리 둘 사이 딱 한 뼘 사이 <br>매일 밤마다 <br>너의 자장가로 잠이 들고 <br>우리 둘 사이 딱 맞는 타입 <br>Come on 거기 미스터 <br>Come on 이리와 봐 <br>조용히 속삭여줄래 <br>Hey 거기 미소가 예쁜 남자 바로 너 <br>너어어어 아아아아 <br>날 미치게 하는 그런 남자 <br>몸매도 얼굴도 시선강탈 <br>Hey Mr. 생각이 멋진 남자 바로 너 <br>너어어어 아아아아 <br>나 지금 너 땜에 혼란스러 <br>제발 누가 나 좀 말려줘 <br>입술을 꽉 깨물어 Your Lips <br>너의 두 눈이 스칠 때면 Two Eyes <br>숨막히는 이끌림이 <br>날 어지럽게 해 <br>나 너만의 영원한 소녀 팬 <br>is 뭔들 모든 게 <br>넌 is 뭔들 완벽해 <br>That's right That's right <br>우리 사이 <br>자꾸 떠오르네 문득 <br>너라면 난 is 뭔들 <br>24시간 1분 1초가 <br>조마조마해 조금이라도 <br>널 놓칠까 봐 <br>24시간 지금 이순간 <br>Come on 나를 봐봐 <br>Come on 넌 is 뭔들 <br>이젠 우릴 말리지마 <br>Hey Hey Hey Yeah <br>Hey 거기 미소가 <br>예쁜 남자 바로 너 <br>너어어어 아아아아 <br>날 미치게 하는 그런 남자 <br>몸매도 얼굴도 시선강탈 <br>Hey Mr. 애매모호 <br>피아노 맨 바로 너 <br>너어어어 아아아아 <br>나 지금 너 땜에 혼란스러 <br>제발 누가 나 좀 말려줘 <br>Come on 넌 is 뭔들 <br>]]></content><category term="길미" label="길미"/><category term="넌 is 뭔들 (인터넷 서핑마니아 서핑걸)" label="넌 is 뭔들 (인터넷 서핑마니아 서핑걸)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lorde/Perfect_Places/</id><title>Lorde - Perfect Places - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:01:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:01:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lorde/Perfect_Places/" title="Lorde - Perfect Places - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Every night I live and die <br>Feel the party to my bones <br>Watch the wasters blow the speakers <br>Spill my guts <br>beneath the outdoor light <br>It's just another graceless night <br>I hate the headlines and the weather <br>I'm 19 and I'm on fire <br>But when we're dancing I'm alright <br>It's just another graceless night <br>Are you lost enough <br>Have another drink get lost in us <br>This is how we get notorious oh <br>'Cause I don't know <br>If they keep tellin' me where to go <br>I'll blow my brains <br>out to the radio oh <br>All of the things we're taking <br>'Cause we are young <br>and we're ashamed <br>Send us to perfect places <br>All of our heroes fading <br>Now I can't stand to be alone <br>Let's go to perfect places <br>Every night I live and die <br>Meet somebody take 'em home <br>Let's kiss and then <br>take off our clothes <br>It's just another graceless night <br>All of the things we're taking <br>'Cause we are young <br>and we're ashamed <br>Send us to perfect places <br>All of our heroes fading <br>Now I can't stand to be alone <br>Let's go to perfect places <br>All the nights spent off our faces <br>Trying to find these perfect places <br>What the fuck are <br>perfect places anyway <br>All the nights spent off our faces <br>Trying to find these perfect places <br>What the fuck are <br>perfect places anyway <br>All the nights spent off our faces <br>Trying to find these perfect places <br>What the fuck are <br>perfect places anyway <br>]]></content><category term="Lorde" label="Lorde"/><category term="Perfect Places" label="Perfect Places"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍준보/강남_사나이/</id><title>홍준보 - 강남 사나이 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:04:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:04:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%A4%80%EB%B3%B4/%EA%B0%95%EB%82%A8_%EC%82%AC%EB%82%98%EC%9D%B4/" title="홍준보 - 강남 사나이 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사나이 아픈 가슴을 안고 <br>술잔을 비우고 또 비워도 <br>삐뚤어진 넥타이만 <br>목을 안고 흐느끼네 <br>너무나도 사랑했기에 <br>그 사람을 잊을 수 없어 <br>사랑에 거리 강남에서 <br>술잔을 비웁니다 <br>이별의 아픈 가슴을 안고 <br>술잔을 비우고 또 비워도 <br>슬픈 유행가 노래 가사만 <br>내 마음을 대신하네 <br>너무나도 사랑했기에 <br>그 사람을 잊을 수 없어 <br>사랑에 거리 강남에서 <br> 술잔을 비웁니다 <br>너와 함께 부르던 노래 <br>이제 다시 부를 수 없어 <br>사랑에 거리 강남에서 <br>술잔을 비웁니다 <br>]]></content><category term="홍준보" label="홍준보"/><category term="강남 사나이" label="강남 사나이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍준보/무소유_행복/</id><title>홍준보 - 무소유 행복 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:04:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:04:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%A4%80%EB%B3%B4/%EB%AC%B4%EC%86%8C%EC%9C%A0_%ED%96%89%EB%B3%B5/" title="홍준보 - 무소유 행복 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세상에 올 때도 무소유 <br>우우우우 <br>세상을 떠날 때도 무소유 <br>우우우우 <br>바람처럼 구름처럼 살고 싶어도 <br>날 때부터 죄 많은 인생이라 <br>험하고 험한 세상 그 길에 서서 <br>하루도 근심걱정 떠날 날 없네 <br>작은 행복에 만족을 못하고 <br>더 큰 행복을 찾는지도 몰라 <br>있어도 걱정 없어도 걱정 <br>숨쉴 수가 없네 <br>무소유 행복이 진정한 행복인데 <br>의미 있는 삶을 위해 한두 번쯤은 <br>꿈을 향해 무작정 뛰고 싶어 <br>험하고 험한 세상 그 길에 서서 <br>내 젊음 하나 믿고 도전해보네 <br>작은 행복에 만족을 못하고 <br>더 큰 행복을 찾는지도 몰라 <br>있어도 걱정 없어도 걱정 <br>숨쉴 수가 없네 <br>무소유 행복이 진정한 행복인데 <br>무소유 행복이 진정한 행복인데 <br>]]></content><category term="홍준보" label="홍준보"/><category term="무소유 행복" label="무소유 행복"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍준보/산소_같은_여자야/</id><title>홍준보 - 산소 같은 여자야 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:04:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:04:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%A4%80%EB%B3%B4/%EC%82%B0%EC%86%8C_%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EC%97%AC%EC%9E%90%EC%95%BC/" title="홍준보 - 산소 같은 여자야 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꽃보다 아름다운 사랑스런 내 여자야 <br>바라만 보아도 좋은 <br>너는 나의 여자야 <br>산소 같은 여자 여자 여자야 <br>가끔은 투덜대며 잔소리 하지만 <br>너는 나의 여자야 여자야 <br>매사에 완벽한 여자 여자 여자라면 <br>숨쉴 수도 없을 거야 푼수래도 <br>내 사랑이 나는 좋아 <br>하지만 눈치 없어 <br>내 마음도 몰라주네 <br>예쁜 입술 여자 여자가 <br>꽃보다 아름다운 사랑스런 내 여자야 <br>화내는 모습도 예쁜 <br>눈물 많은 여자야 <br>산소 같은 여자 여자 여자야 <br>싫으면 싫다하고 좋으면 좋다는 <br>톡톡 쏘는 여자야 여자야 <br>매사에 완벽한 여자 여자 여자라면 <br>섹시해도 매력 없어 푼수래도 <br>내 사랑이 나는 좋아 <br>하지만 눈치 없어 <br>내 마음도 몰라주네 <br>예쁜 입술 여자 여자가 <br>매사에 완벽한 여자 여자 여자라면 <br>숨쉴 수도 없을 거야 푼수래도 <br>내 사랑이 나는 좋아 <br>하지만 눈치 없어 <br>내 마음도 몰라주네 <br>예쁜 입술 여자 여자가 <br>]]></content><category term="홍준보" label="홍준보"/><category term="산소 같은 여자야" label="산소 같은 여자야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍준보/물음표만_남기고/</id><title>홍준보 - 물음표만 남기고 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:04:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:04:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%A4%80%EB%B3%B4/%EB%AC%BC%EC%9D%8C%ED%91%9C%EB%A7%8C_%EB%82%A8%EA%B8%B0%EA%B3%A0/" title="홍준보 - 물음표만 남기고 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[물음표만 남기고 그 사람 가네 <br>잊어야 하는지 기다려야 하는지 <br>아무런 말없이 눈물 짓고 떠나네 <br>물음표만 남기고 가네 <br>바람 같은 추억만 차창에 그려 놓고 <br>비마저 내리는 밤에 <br>빗소리 너머로 사라져간 그 사람 <br>내 마음을 알고 갔을까 <br>기적소리 남기고 그 사람 가네 <br>물음표만 남기고 가네 <br>물음표만 남기고 그 사람 가네 <br>보내야 하는지 붙잡아야 하는지 <br>아무 말 못하고 뒷모습만 보았네 <br>물음표만 남겨둔 채로 <br>바람 같은 사랑만 가슴에 남겨놓고 <br>비마저 내리는 밤에 <br>빗소리 너머로 사라져간 그 사람 <br>내 마음을 알고 갔을까 <br>기적소리 남기고 그 사람 가네 <br>물음표만 남기고 가네 <br>물음표만 남기고 가네 <br>]]></content><category term="홍준보" label="홍준보"/><category term="물음표만 남기고" label="물음표만 남기고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/내가_저지른_사랑/</id><title>임창정 - 내가 저지른 사랑 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:04:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:04:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EB%82%B4%EA%B0%80_%EC%A0%80%EC%A7%80%EB%A5%B8_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="임창정 - 내가 저지른 사랑 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[떠나거든 내 소식이 들려오면 <br>이제는 모른다고 해줘 <br>언제나 내 맘속에서 <br>커져만 갔던 너를 <br>조금씩 나도 지우려 해 <br>사랑해 라고 말하고 싶었지만 <br>늘 미안하다고만 했던 나 <br>잊고 잊혀지고 지우고 <br>처음 만난 그때가 그리워진 사람 <br>다시 못 올 몇 번의 그 계절 <br>떠나버린 너의 모습을 <br>지우고 버리고 비워도 <br>어느 새 가득 차버린 내사랑 <br>안 된다고 사랑하면 안 된다고 <br>하지만 우린 함께했지 <br>언제나 내 마음이라 <br>사랑하던 맘이라 <br>그리 아파할 줄 몰랐어 <br>미안해 라고 안아주고 싶지만 <br>점이 돼버린 그 뒷모습 <br>잊고 잊혀지고 지우고 <br>처음 만난 그때가 그리워진 사람 <br>다시 못 올 몇 번의 그 계절 <br>떠나버린 너의 모습을 <br>지우고 버리고 비워도 <br>어느 새 가득 차버린 내사랑 <br>모든 게 나 때문인데 <br>왜 네가 더 힘들어 <br>네가 왜 내 맘을 위로해 <br>왜 <br>잊고 잊혀지고 지우고 <br>처음 만난 그때가 그리워진 사람 <br>다시 못 올 몇 번의 그 계절 <br>떠나버린 너의 모습을 <br>지우고 버리고 비워도 <br>어느 새 가득 차버린 내사랑 <br>잊고 잊혀지고 지우고 <br>처음 만난 그때가 그리워진 사람 <br>다시 못 올 몇 번의 그 계절 <br>떠나버린 너의 모습을 <br>지우고 버리고 비워도 <br>어느 새 가득 차버린 내사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="내가 저지른 사랑" label="내가 저지른 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/또_다시_사랑/</id><title>임창정 - 또 다시 사랑 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:04:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:04:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EB%98%90_%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="임창정 - 또 다시 사랑 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아픔이 좀 더 작아질까 <br>의미 없는 만남을 하다가 <br>어느 날 그대가 흘린 눈물 <br>왠지 나와 같다 느껴서 <br>이렇게 그대를 지키는가 봐요 <br>행복하고 싶었던 그대를 <br>몰랐던 누군 갈 또 알아가면서 <br>분명 행복할 걸 알겠지만 <br>내가 그대를 만났다는 건 <br>어쩌면 흘러가는 흔한 <br>인연이란 것 일진 모르지만 <br>오늘도 다시 또 다시 사랑해요 <br>사랑 언제나 이번이 마지막이라며 <br>처음인 듯 찾아오니까 <br>어느 날 그대가 숨긴 눈물 <br>왠지 나와 같다 느껴서 <br>이렇게 그대를 지키는 가 봐요 <br>행복하고 싶었던 그대를 <br>몰랐던 누군 갈 또 알아가는 게 <br>혹시 두렵기도 하겠지만 <br>내가 그대를 만났다는 건 <br>어쩌면 흘러가는 흔한 <br>인연이란 것일지 모르지만 <br>오늘도 다시 또 다시 사랑해요 <br>사랑 언제나 이번이 마지막이라며 <br>처음인 듯 찾아오니까 <br>절대 우리 작은 다툼 조차 하지 마요 <br>이별 후엔 서운함만 가슴속에 남으니 <br>사소한 그 표현이 그 말들이 <br>언제나 나에겐 참 고마울 거예요 <br>내가 그대를 만났다는 건 <br>어쩌면 흘러가는 흔한 <br>인연이란 것 일진 모르지만 <br>오늘도 다시 또 다시 사랑해요 <br>사랑 언제나 이번이 마지막이라며 <br>처음인 듯 찾아오니까 <br>사랑 언제나 이번이 마지막이라며 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="또 다시 사랑" label="또 다시 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/소주_한_잔/</id><title>임창정 - 소주 한 잔 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:04:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:04:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EC%86%8C%EC%A3%BC_%ED%95%9C_%EC%9E%94/" title="임창정 - 소주 한 잔 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[술이 한잔 생각나는 밤 <br>같이 있는 것 같아요 <br>그 좋았던 시절들 <br>이젠 모두 한숨만 되네요 <br>떠나는 그대 얼굴이 <br>혹시 울지나 않을까 <br>나 먼저 돌아섰죠 <br>그때부터 그리워요 <br>사람이 변하는걸요 <br>다시 전보다 그댈 원해요 <br>이렇게 취할 때 면 <br>꺼져버린 전화를 붙잡고 <br>여보세요 나야 거기 잘 지내니 <br>여보세요 왜 말 안 하니 <br>울고 있니 내가 오랜만이라서 <br>사랑하는 사람이라서 <br>그대 소중한 마음 밀쳐낸 <br>이기적인 그때에 나에게 <br>그대를 다시 불러오라고 <br>미친 듯이 외쳤어 <br>떠나는 그대 얼굴이 <br>마치 처음과 같아서 <br>나 눈물이 났어요 <br>그때부터 그리워요 <br>사랑이 변하는걸요 <br>다시 전보다 그댈 원해요 <br>이렇게 취할 때면 <br>바뀌어버린 전화번호 누르고 <br>여보세요 나야 거기 잘 지내니 <br>오랜만이야 내 사랑아 <br>그대를 다시 불러오라고 <br>미친 듯이 울었어 <br>여보세요 나야 정말 미안해 <br>이기적인 그때에 나에게 <br>그대를 다시 불러오라고 <br>미친 듯이 외쳤어 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="소주 한 잔" label="소주 한 잔"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/이해할_수_있니/</id><title>임창정 - 이해할 수 있니 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EC%9D%B4%ED%95%B4%ED%95%A0_%EC%88%98_%EC%9E%88%EB%8B%88/" title="임창정 - 이해할 수 있니 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 늘 내 안에 머무는 <br>사랑이라 말하고 싶어 <br>언제나 입 속을 맴돌던 <br>너를 사랑할거란 그 말을 <br>하지만 네 목소리에 <br>난 아무 말 할 수가 없어 <br>항상 그랬듯이 오늘도 <br>짧은 인사와 어색함인데 <br>그렇게 넌 언제나 내게 <br>너무나 먼 곳에 있기에 <br>너를 향한 그리움 <br>이렇게 아픈 거야 <br>이런 날 모르는지 <br>이해할 수 있니 <br>난 눈물 나는 날에는 <br>네 목소리 그리워진다는 걸 <br>하지만 나는 <br>아무 표현할 수가 없었어 <br>너에게 내 맘이 부담될까 봐 <br>너를 잃을까 그게 너무 두려워 <br>아무 말도 할 수가 없었어 <br>그렇게 넌 언제나 내게 <br>너무나 먼 곳에 있기에 <br>너를 향한 그리움 <br>이렇게 아픈 거야 <br>이런 날 모르는지 <br>이해할 수 있니 <br>난 눈물 나는 날에는 <br>네 목소리 그리워진다는 걸 <br>하지만 나는 <br>아무 표현할 수가 없었어 <br>너에게 내 맘이 부담될까 봐 <br>너를 잃을까 그게 너무 두려워 <br>아무 말도 할 수가 없었어 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="이해할 수 있니" label="이해할 수 있니"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/기다리는_이유/</id><title>임창정 - 기다리는 이유 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EA%B8%B0%EB%8B%A4%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_%EC%9D%B4%EC%9C%A0/" title="임창정 - 기다리는 이유 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대 보내도 되나요 <br>처음으로 되돌아 갈 수 있나요 <br>나 없인 안 된다던 그대가 <br>혼자 가기엔 먼 길이 될 텐데 <br>눈물 보이면 되는지 <br>잘 살라고 손 잡아 주면 되는지 <br>어떻게 헤어져야 하는 지 <br>내가 배운 건 사랑이 전분데 <br>울지 말아요 <br>그대 맘을 채우지 못했던 날 탓해요 <br>이별은 혼자서도 할 수 있나요 오 <br>내 허락이 없이도 끝을 향해 가겠죠 <br>미안해요 나의 곁에서 <br>더 힘들었을 거라고 <br>차라리 믿을게요 아파도 <br>그대 내게 준 것처럼 <br>나 받은걸 모두 주면 되는지 <br>추억도 이젠 짐이 되나요 <br>내게 남은 건 그 하나뿐인데 <br>울지 말아요 <br>그대 맘을 채우지 못했던 날 탓해요 <br>이별은 혼자서도 할 수 있나요 오 <br>내 허락이 없이도 끝을 향해 가겠죠 <br>미안해요 나의 곁에서 <br>더 힘들었을 거라고 <br>차라리 믿을게요 아파도 <br>이 세상에겐 비밀로 해요 <br>함께 해왔던 그날처럼 늘 이대로 <br>사랑은 혼자서도 할 수 있겠죠 오 <br>그대 상관 없이도 잊지 못할 나니까 <br>괜찮아요 영원한 슬픔에 <br>끝내 살아간대도 <br>내 기다릴 이윤 그댈 테니 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="기다리는 이유" label="기다리는 이유"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/위로/</id><title>임창정 - 위로 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EC%9C%84%EB%A1%9C/" title="임창정 - 위로 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑한단 말 기다리란 말 <br>그 눈물로 대신 했나요 <br>함께 한 사람 그대였기에 <br>나 오늘 하루 견딜 수 있죠 <br>그대 머물던 너무나 <br>아름다운 기억에 <br>난 가끔 서글픈 그리움조차 <br>위로가 되죠 <br>그대 너무 멀어지진 말아요 <br>나의 사랑 느껴 질 수 없어요 <br>마주할 수는 없지만 <br>이별은 아니죠 <br>잠시 멈춰있을 뿐이죠 <br>곁에 없지만 그댄 언제나 내게 <br>가장 큰 위로가 되죠 <br>볼 수 없을 뿐 하늘의 별도 <br>늘 그 자리에 있는 것처럼 <br>그대 머물던 너무나 <br>아름다운 기억에 <br>난 가끔 서글픈 그리움조차 <br>위로가 되죠 <br>그대 너무 멀어지진 말아요 <br>나의 사랑 느껴 질 수 없어요 <br>마주할 수는 없지만 <br>이별은 아니죠 <br>잠시 멈춰있을 뿐이죠 <br>떠난 그대는 괜찮은 건지 <br>내 하루는 여전히 그대일 텐데 <br>함께 한 기억들만이 <br>내 전분 것처럼 자꾸 되돌려 져요 <br>그대 먼 곳에서 돌아오겠죠 <br>슬픈 세상 끝을 보고 있나요 <br>내게로 돌아 올 사람 <br>나 기다리는 일 <br>내게는 행복할 뿐이죠 <br>행복한 눈물일 뿐이죠 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="위로" label="위로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/나란_놈이란/</id><title>임창정 - 나란 놈이란 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EB%82%98%EB%9E%80_%EB%86%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%9E%80/" title="임창정 - 나란 놈이란 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대를 잊는다는 건 <br>지금의 나로선 좀 힘들 거 같아 <br>아무리 원망을 해도 <br>어느새 흐르는 눈물 나도 모르게 <br>그리워 그 목소리 <br>보고 싶어 일어설 수도 없어 <br>시간은 잊으라 하는데 <br>오히려 선명해진 얼굴 <br>그 날은 그대 모습이 <br>떠난다는 말을 하려던 것 같아 <br>초라한 나의 어깨에 <br>차마 말을 못 했었나봐 그랬나봐 <br>그리워 그 목소리 <br>가끔은 힘들던 잔소리마저 <br>잔인한 이별이 있던 날 <br>그 날조차 이젠 그리워 <br>잘 지내라는 행복하라는 <br>그 흔한 이별의 <br>위로마저도 없이 <br>마지막 인사도 못했던 <br>우리의 이별 <br>나를 떠난 그 이유마저 <br>그대가 두고 떠난 <br>그대 인생의 절반은 나란 말 <br>이제는 잊어야 할텐데 <br>오히려 선명해진 그 말 <br>여전히 선명한 목소리 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="나란 놈이란" label="나란 놈이란"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/이미_나에게로/</id><title>임창정 - 이미 나에게로 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EC%9D%B4%EB%AF%B8_%EB%82%98%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C%EB%A1%9C/" title="임창정 - 이미 나에게로 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 꿈이 멎어버린 순간에 <br>난 깨닫고 널 생각해 <br>어쩜 난 너의 힘겨움을 <br>함께 짊어지고 갈 수 있어 <br>할말이 많기도 하고 <br>목소리도 그리워 전화를 했어 <br>씁쓸한 목소리가 들리고 <br>난 미안함에 당황도 했어 <br>난 너무 힘들어서 <br>그런 이유로 만나기 미안해 <br>둘이 할 때는 <br>너만을 생각하려 했는데 <br>문득 어떤 고민에 <br>널 앞에 두고 뭐가 그리 힘들어 <br>내 미래의 완성 속에 있는 너인데 <br>이미 나에게로 하여 <br>집착하게 만든 넌 <br>방황에 지쳐 쓰러져 버린 내가 <br>다시 일어서는 모습 생각하며 <br>날 찾을 수 있니 <br>이미 나에게로 하여 <br>집착하게 만든 넌 <br>실패에 주저앉은 처참한 날 본 후 <br>다시 용기 얻는 모습 생각하며 <br>날 사랑해 줄 수 있겠니 <br>낙엽이 진 나무 위로 <br>하얀 서리가 내린 새벽 <br>내가 이 세상을 보았을 때 <br>얌전하고 고요하게 <br>내 곁에 있어준 너를 생각하며 <br>난 너무 힘들어서 <br>그런 이유로 만나기 미안해 <br>둘이 할 때는 <br>너만을 생각하려 했는데 <br>문득 어떤 고민에 <br>널 앞에 두고 뭐가 그리 힘들어 <br>내 미래의 완성 속에 있는 너인데 <br>이미 나에게로 하여 <br>집착하게 만든 넌 <br>방황에 지쳐 쓰러져 버린 내가 <br>다시 일어서는 모습 생각하며 <br>날 찾을 수 있니 <br>이미 나에게로 하여 <br>집착하게 만든 넌 <br>실패에 주저앉은 처참한 날 본 후 <br>다시 용기 얻는 모습 생각하며 <br>날 사랑해 줄 수 있겠니 <br>이미 나에게로 하여 <br>집착하게 만든 넌 <br>방황에 지쳐 쓰러져 버린 내가 <br>다시 일어서는 모습 생각하며 <br>날 찾을 수 있니 <br>이미 나에게로 하여 <br>집착하게 만든 넌 <br>실패에 주저앉은 처참한 날 본 후 <br>다시 용기 얻는 모습 생각하며 <br>날 사랑해 줄 수 있겠니 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="이미 나에게로" label="이미 나에게로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/그대도_여기에/</id><title>임창정 - 그대도 여기에 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%8F%84_%EC%97%AC%EA%B8%B0%EC%97%90/" title="임창정 - 그대도 여기에 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한참을 바라보았죠 <br>그대와 함께 거닐던 그 길을 <br>바보처럼 눈물이 내려와 <br>내 메마른 입술 위에 번지면 <br>멍하니 서있게 되죠 <br>그대를 처음 만났던 이 길에 <br>뭐 하나도 변한 게 없는데 <br>미소를 잃어가는 <br>나만이 여기에 남았죠 <br>날 보고 있나요 그대도 여기에 <br>오늘을 위해서 날 찾아왔겠죠 <br>우리 만날 날이 이 하루 밖엔 <br>허락이 안되나 봐요 <br>그저 단 하루 밖엔 <br>돌아서 가려고 했죠 <br>이젠 그대를 지우려 하죠 난 <br>일년 후에 다시 또 이 곳에 <br>찾아올 그대를 <br>기다리겠죠 난 영원히 <br>난 여기 있어요 항상 이 자리에 <br>그대도 여기에 날 찾아왔겠죠 <br>우리 만날 날이 이 하루 밖엔 <br>허락이 안되나 봐요 <br>오늘 이 하루뿐이죠 <br>우리 만날 날이 이 하루 밖엔 <br>우리 만날 날이 이 하루 밖엔 <br>허락이 안되나 봐요 <br>그저 단 하루 밖엔 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="그대도 여기에" label="그대도 여기에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/결혼해줘/</id><title>임창정 - 결혼해줘 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EA%B2%B0%ED%98%BC%ED%95%B4%EC%A4%98/" title="임창정 - 결혼해줘 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그럴지도 몰라 널 만나기 위해 <br>많은 날들을 아픔 속에서 <br>눈물 속에서 <br>보내야만 했었었는지 <br>왜 웃기만 하니 뭐라고 말해봐 <br>너도 나처럼 기다렸다고 <br>날 사랑한다고 <br>다시 슬픈 이별은 없다고 <br>혼자이면 언제나 <br>끝도 없는 그리움이 밀려와 <br>무엇 하나 시작할 수 없던 날들 <br>내 곁에 머물러 주렴 <br>내가 다시 꿈을 꿀 수 있게 <br>그래도 가끔은 그 언젠가처럼 <br>다시 이별이 찾아올까 봐 <br>난 두렵기도 해 <br>슬픈 내 눈빛 이해하겠니 <br>이것만 기억해줘 <br>너의 마지막 사랑이라는 걸 <br>많은 시간 지나 모두 변한대도 <br>지금 이 설레임들을 <br>아름답게 간직하는 거야 <br>사랑해 지금처럼 영원히 <br>환한 네 미소 이제 내가 지켜줄게 <br>혼자이면 언제나 <br>끝도 없는 그리움이 밀려와 <br>무엇 하나 시작할 수 없던 날들 <br>너를 만난 이후 다시 꿈꿀 수 있어 <br>이것만 기억해줘 <br>너의 마지막 사랑이라는 걸 <br>많은 시간 지나 모두 변한대도 <br>지금 이 설레임들을 <br>아름답게 간직하는 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="결혼해줘" label="결혼해줘"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/노래_한번_할게요/</id><title>임창정 - 노래 한번 할게요 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98_%ED%95%9C%EB%B2%88_%ED%95%A0%EA%B2%8C%EC%9A%94/" title="임창정 - 노래 한번 할게요 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[노래 한번 할게요 <br>굉장히 좋은 노래 <br>후렴이 듣기 좋아서 <br>마음 아려지는 그런 노래 <br>라라라라라 <br>한 여자가 주인공인 <br>이제는 듣는 사람이 없는 노래 <br>이 노랠 부르면 <br>네가 내 옆으로 와주니까 <br>어깨에 기대어 <br>목소리 좋다고 말해주니까 <br>또 난 좋아서 이 노래의 번호를 눌러 <br>노래를 불러 너를 불러 <br>여기까지만 할래요 <br>나 혼자 하는 노랜 <br>아무리 불러도 계속 불러도 <br>넌 들을 수가 없잖아 <br>이 노랠 부르면 <br>네가 내 옆으로 와주니까 <br>어깨에 기대어 <br>목소리 좋다고 말해주니까 <br>또 난 좋아서 이 노래의 번호를 눌러 <br>노래를 불러 너를 불러 <br>노래가 끝나고 <br>이 노래가 불러준 <br>너도 떠나고 나면 <br>모든 게 돌아와 제자리로 <br>난 어떡해야 할지를 몰라 <br>이 노랠 들으면 <br>너도 내 생각이 나긴 할까 <br>많이 좋아하던 <br>목소리 잊어버린 건 아닐까 <br>또 난 오늘도 이 노래의 번호를 눌러 <br>노래를 불러 너를 불러 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="노래 한번 할게요" label="노래 한번 할게요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/조언/</id><title>임창정 - 조언 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EC%A1%B0%EC%96%B8/" title="임창정 - 조언 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무 말도 하지 않고 <br>창문만 바라보다 <br>불쑥 뱉는 남자의 한숨 소리는 <br>무슨 의미이냐고 <br>며칠 동안 연락이 <br>안 되는 건 왜 그런지 <br>날 붙잡고 하소연하는 그대를 <br>사랑하고 있어 난 <br>비 오던 밤 또 다시 <br>울음 섞인 그녀 목소리 <br>물어 볼 말이 있어 전화했다고 <br>도저히 이해 안가는 <br>남자를 설명해달라면서 <br>나에게 뭐라고 말 해달라는 건지 <br>왜 그대에게 난 여기까진지 <br>남잔 이유 없이 늘 그런 거라고 <br>느긋하게 기다리면 <br>다시 사랑할 수 있다고 <br>비 오던 밤 전화해 <br>울먹이는 그녀 목소리 <br>이런 걸 물어봐도 괜찮겠냐고 <br>도저히 이해 안가는 <br>남자를 설명해달라면서 <br>나에게 뭐라고 말 해달라는 건지 <br>솔직히 나도 이해할 수 없어 <br>진짜 사랑한다면 정말 소중하다면 <br>누구보다 행복하게 <br>그댈 아껴야 그게 맞는 거잖아 <br>나에게 뭐라고 말 해달라는 건지 <br>왜 그대에게 난 여기까진지 <br>남잔 이유 없이 늘 그런 거라고 <br>느긋하게 기다리면 <br>다시 사랑할 수 있다고 <br>나의 슬픈 조언이라고 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="조언" label="조언"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/Smile_Again/</id><title>임창정 - Smile Again - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/Smile_Again/" title="임창정 - Smile Again - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[또 울고 있었군요 <br>이젠 그만 나를 놓아요 <br>커다란 그대 사랑 안고서 <br>맘 편히 쉴 수 있게 <br>긴 세월이 흐른 후 <br>그대 좋은 사람 만나서 <br>행복한 모습 볼 수 있도록 <br>나 그댈 지킬게요 <br>우리 함께 한 많은 날들이 <br>너무나 소중해 <br>그래도 웃을 수 있죠 <br>혼자인 게 서러울 땐 <br>그댈 아프게 한 내 모습만 <br>떠올리며 살아요 <br>긴 그대의 한숨을 <br>모두 가져갈 수 없다면 <br>차라리 그대 그림자 되어 <br>나 항상 그대 곁에 <br>우리 함께 한 많은 날들이 <br>너무나 소중해 <br>그래도 웃을 수 있죠 <br>혼자인 게 서러울 땐 <br>그댈 아프게 한 내 모습만 <br>기억해봐요 그대 <br>세상에 홀로 남겨진 그대를 <br>잠시라도 만날 수 있다면 <br>단 하루라도 <br>야위어 가는 그댈 위해 <br>날 닮은 사람 보내줄게요 <br>그에게서 날 봐요 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="Smile Again" label="Smile Again"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/날_닮은_너/</id><title>임창정 - 날 닮은 너 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EB%82%A0_%EB%8B%AE%EC%9D%80_%EB%84%88/" title="임창정 - 날 닮은 너 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날 닮은 너를 부족한 너를 <br>그저 바라보기엔 <br>후회로 물든 내 지난날이 <br>너무 많이 다쳤어 <br>나의 과거와 너의 지금과 <br>너무도 같기에 두려워 겁이나 <br>내게 마지막이어야 할 사람 <br>너의 방황을 돌릴 수 있게 <br>날 이렇게 뿌리친대도 <br>너의 손을 놓진 않을거야 <br>잠시도 너는 불안한 모습 <br>감출수가 없었니 음 <br>내가 아녀도 지친 니 맘을 <br>위로 받을수 있니 <br>나의 과거와 너의 지금과 <br>너무도 같기에 두려워 겁이나 <br>내게 마지막이어야 할 사람 <br>너의 방황을 돌릴 수 있게 <br>날 이렇게 뿌리친대도 <br>너의 손을 놓진 않을거야 <br>나 역시 너 같았어 <br>너처럼 어두웠어 니가 지내온 <br>또 다른 시간도 더 있을 고통도 <br>난 감당할거야 워 <br>마지막이어야 할사람 <br>너의 미래를 지킬 수 있게 <br>날 이렇게 뿌리친대도 <br>너의 손을 놓진 않을거야 <br>마지막이어야 할 사람 <br>너의 미래를 지킬수 있게 <br>날 이렇게 뿌리친대도 <br>너의 손을 놓진 않을거야 <br>너의 손을 놓진 않을거야 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="날 닮은 너" label="날 닮은 너"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/그때_또_다시/</id><title>임창정 - 그때 또 다시 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EA%B7%B8%EB%95%8C_%EB%98%90_%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C/" title="임창정 - 그때 또 다시 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[네가 없는데도 해는 뜨고 또 지고 <br>창 넘어 세상은 하나 변한 게 없어 <br>삼켰었던 내 슬픔이 갑자기 터져왔어 <br>내가 살고 싶던 삶이란 이게 아닌 걸 <br>아마도 운명이 나를 잘 몰랐기에 <br>우리의 인연을 엇갈리게 했나 봐 <br>이 세상에서 나에게 <br>허락되지 않은 건 <br>함께 있고 싶은 사람과 함께 있는 것 <br>하지만 난 사랑했잖아 <br>살아있었던 거야 <br>네 곁에서 함께 했던 날 동안 <br>그걸로 됐어 나를 완전히 태울 수 <br>있었던 축복을 내게 줬으니 <br>참아 볼게 잊어도 볼게 <br>널 위해서라면 <br>허나 그래도 안되면 기다릴게 <br>그때 또 다시 <br>온몸에 품어도 바람은 흘러가고 <br>밤새워 지켜도 꽃은 시들겠지만 <br>하늘 아래 네가 있어 <br>오늘도 난 눈부셔 <br>널 향한 마음엔 시작만 있는 이유로 <br>하지만 난 사랑했잖아 <br>살아있었던 거야 <br>네 곁에서 함께 했던 날 동안 <br>그걸로 됐어 나를 완전히 태울 수 <br>있었던 축복을 내게 줬으니 <br>참아 볼게 잊어도 볼게 <br>널 위해서라면 <br>허나 그래도 안되면 기다릴게 <br>그때 또 다시 <br>나를 떠나도 그걸로 됐어 <br>나를 완전히 <br>태울 수 있었던 축복을 내게 줬으니 <br>참아 볼게 잊어도 볼게 <br>널 위해서라면 <br>허나 그래도 안되면 기다릴게 <br>그때 또 다시 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="그때 또 다시" label="그때 또 다시"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/나의_연인/</id><title>임창정 - 나의 연인 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%97%B0%EC%9D%B8/" title="임창정 - 나의 연인 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너를 알기 전에 나 어떻게 <br>혼자 살아왔을까 너 없는 세상 <br>이렇게도 내게 눈물 나는 <br>행복 기다릴 줄은 몰랐어 <br>너에게 모두 줄 거야 <br>너를 위한 건 무엇이든 <br>제발 언제나 처음 내게 오던 날처럼 <br>기쁨으로 내게 있어줘 <br>이젠 나보다 너를 사랑 한다는 그 말 <br>모두 이해해 너무 사랑 하니까 <br>네가 웃음지을 때 난 더 크게 웃고 <br>너 아플 땐 난 더 아파 <br>내 삶과 세상 모두가 <br>밝게만 빛나 보여 <br>힘든 하루도 너를 보면 견딜 수 있어 <br>너에게는 웃는 나이길 <br>내겐 아무도 없어 오직 너만이 <br>나를 살게 해 널 사랑한 뒤 <br>너를 느낄 때 난 살아있어 <br>너는 내 행복의 전부니까 <br>제발 언제나 처음 내게 오던 날처럼 <br>기쁨으로 내게 있어줘 <br>이젠 나보다 너를 사랑 한다는 그 말 <br>모두 이해해 너무 사랑하니까 <br>제발 언제나 처음 내게 오던 날처럼 <br>기쁨으로 내게 있어줘 <br>이젠 나보다 너를 사랑한다는 그 말 <br>너에게 하고 싶어 너를 너무 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="나의 연인" label="나의 연인"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/Love_Affair/</id><title>임창정 - Love Affair - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/Love_Affair/" title="임창정 - Love Affair - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지금쯤 올 때도 됐는데 <br>이제는 잊을 때도 됐는데 <br>내게 올 수 없는 건 그댈 향한 <br>나처럼 어쩔 수 없는지 <br>보고파 눈물이 흘러도 <br>그 얼굴 그토록 그리워도 <br>내가 할 수 있는 건 <br>우두커니 그대를 기다리는 일 <br>자꾸만 흐르는 나의 눈물이 <br>행복한 그댈 힘들게 하나요 <br>우린 단 한 번 스쳐가는 인연으로 <br>끝난 건가요 사랑은 했었나요 <br>무언가 이유가 있겠죠 <br>무언지 말할 수가 없겠죠 <br>기다리는 나보다 올 수 없는 <br>마음이 더 힘들겠죠 <br>세상에 또 다시 태어났을 땐 <br>엇갈림 없이 잘할 수 있겠죠 <br>그땐 처음 본 그대 모습 기억해서 <br>또 지금처럼 놓치지 않을게요 <br>내 사랑 쉽게만 보였었는지 <br>모두 주기엔 불안했었는지 <br>제발 내게로 돌아오는 길이라면 <br>느낄 수 있게 지치기 전에 <br>나 또 다시 태어났을 땐 <br>엇갈림 없이 잘할 수 있겠죠 <br>그땐 처음 본 그대 모습 기억해서 <br>또 지금처럼 놓치지 않을게요 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="Love Affair" label="Love Affair"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/슬픈_혼잣말/</id><title>임창정 - 슬픈 혼잣말 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EC%8A%AC%ED%94%88_%ED%98%BC%EC%9E%A3%EB%A7%90/" title="임창정 - 슬픈 혼잣말 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[많이 울었나 봐요 <br>긴 머리 사이 젖은 눈동자 <br>나를 찾아 온 그 이유를 알아요 <br>많이 힘든가요 <br>정말 미안하다고 <br>사랑할 인연은 아니라고 <br>떠나라 해도 난 친구로 남아서 <br>여기 있잖아요 <br>울지 말아요 그대는 이제 내게 <br>남이라 난 안아 줄 수 없잖아 <br>그게 얼마나 가슴 아픈 일인지 <br>말해도 애원해봐도 <br>안될 거잖아요 내게 돌아오는 건 <br>많이 밝아졌네요 그 전화 안에 <br>그가 있나요 <br>그댄 웃는데 나도 좋아야 하는데 <br>자꾸 서글퍼요 <br>이젠 가서는 제발 힘들지 말고 <br>지내요 그래야 나도 살아요 <br>울던 그대를 금방 웃게 하는 건 <br>난 이제 안 된다는 걸 <br>사랑한단 말도 이젠 안 되는 거죠 <br>그 뛰어가는 뒷모습에 <br>또 무너지는 서러운 가슴 <br>터질듯한 벅찬 사랑 우리 얘기 <br>내게만 남길 건가요 그대 <br>울던 그대를 금방 웃게 하는 건 <br>난 이제 안된 다는걸 <br>사랑한단 말도 이젠 혼잣말이죠 <br>한땐 사랑으로 그대 곁에 <br>내가 살았었는데 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="슬픈 혼잣말" label="슬픈 혼잣말"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/오랜만이야/</id><title>임창정 - 오랜만이야 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EC%98%A4%EB%9E%9C%EB%A7%8C%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC/" title="임창정 - 오랜만이야 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[참 오랜만이란 말로 <br>웃으며 인사 하는 너 <br>처음 널 만날 때처럼 <br>내 가슴이 철없이 또 뛰어 <br>꼭 행복 하라는 말로 <br>울면서 보내줬는데 <br>그 말이 무색할 만큼 <br>너 왜 이렇게 많이 야위었어 <br>무슨 일 있었던 거니 <br>세상을 다 줄 것 같은 그 사람과 <br>오래 오래 잘 사는 게 <br>행복하는게 그렇게 힘이 들었니 <br>붙잡을 걸 그랬나 봐 <br>내가 더 사랑한다 말할 걸 <br>가진 게 너무 없어 줄 게 <br>너무 없어 안 되는 줄 알았어 <br>기다릴 걸 그랬나 봐 <br>네가 돌아올 줄 알았다면 <br>혼자가 아닌 나라 널 잡을 수 없어 <br>바보 같지만 미안해 <br>나 다시 널 보낼게 <br>좀 일찍 오지 그랬어 <br>너 때문에 힘들었는데 <br>죽을 것 같았던 나를 <br>그녀가 겨우 구해줬는데 <br>난 왜 이렇게 못 됐니 <br>네 작은 어깨를 꼭 안고 싶어져 <br>자꾸만 후회되는 게 미치겠는게 <br>아프게 너를 또 원해 <br>붙잡을 걸 그랬나 봐 <br>내가 더 사랑한다 말할 걸 <br>가진 게 너무 없어 <br>줄 게 너무 없어 안 되는 줄 알았어 <br>기다릴 걸 그랬나 봐 <br>네가 돌아올 줄 알았다면 <br>혼자가 아닌 나라 널 잡을 수 없어 <br>바보 같지만 미안해 <br>나 다시 널 보낼게 <br>몰라볼 걸 그랬나 봐 <br>널 닮은 사람이지 그랬어 <br>내 앞에 있는 너를 애써 웃는 너를 <br>안아줄 수도 없는데 <br>스쳐갈 걸 그랬나 봐 <br>고개 돌리지 말 걸 그랬어 <br>멀어져 가는 너를 난 잡을 수 없어 <br>다시 한번 더 부탁해 <br>나보다 더 행복해 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="오랜만이야" label="오랜만이야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임창정/어느_하루가/</id><title>임창정 - 어느 하루가 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%B0%BD%EC%A0%95/%EC%96%B4%EB%8A%90_%ED%95%98%EB%A3%A8%EA%B0%80/" title="임창정 - 어느 하루가 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[후회하지 말아요 날 떠난걸 <br>우리의 지난날을 <br>어느 하루가 갑자기 날 떠올려도 <br>쓴 술에 혹시나 날 찾지 마요 <br>좀 더 오래 그댈 지켜주고 <br>싶었었던 내 욕심이 <br>힘들었었던 그대 떠올라서 <br>차마 그리워 할 수 없었죠 <br>우리 좀 더 아름다운 기억 <br>먼저 지워요 <br>그래야만 하루가 수월해져 <br>또 다른 세월에 <br>우리를 다시 떠올린다 해도 살아요 <br>후회하지 말아요 날 떠난걸 <br>우리의 지난날을 <br>후회 말아요 냉정히 날 떠난 것을 <br>그대는 이제 행복하겠죠 <br>좀 더 오래 그댈 안아주지 <br>못했었던 내 한숨이 <br>어리석었던 그때를 원망하며 <br>오늘도 그리워야 했어요 <br>우리 좀 더 오래된 추억을 <br>먼저 지워요 <br>그래야만 아픔이 수월해져 <br>지나는 바람에 <br>가슴을 들켜 눈물 흐른대도 사니까 <br>그대 모질게 날 떠난 걸 <br>절대 후회 말아요 <br>좀 더 오래 그댈 지켜주고 <br>싶었었던 내 욕심이 <br>힘들었었던 그대 떠올라서 <br>차마 그리워 할 수 없었죠 <br>우리 좀 더 아름다운 기억 <br>먼저 지워요 <br>그래야만 하루가 수월해져 <br>또 다른 세월에 우리가 <br>다시 떠오른다 해도 살아요 <br>]]></content><category term="임창정" label="임창정"/><category term="어느 하루가" label="어느 하루가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radiohead/I_Promise/</id><title>Radiohead - I Promise - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:05:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:05:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radiohead/I_Promise/" title="Radiohead - I Promise - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I won't run away no more, I promise <br>Even when I get bored, I promise <br>Even when you lock me out, I promise <br>I say my prayers every night, I promise <br><br>I don't wish that I'm spread, I promise <br>The tantrums and the chilling chats, I promise <br><br>Even when the ship is wrecked, I promise <br>Tie me to the rotten deck, I promise <br><br>I won't run away no more, I promise <br>Even when I get bored, I promise <br><br>Even when the ship is wrecked, I promise <br>Tie me to the rotten deck, I promise <br><br>I won't run away no more, I promise]]></content><category term="Radiohead" label="Radiohead"/><category term="I Promise" label="I Promise"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서달달/그_자리에서/</id><title>서달달 - 그 자리에서 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:06:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:06:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EB%8B%AC%EB%8B%AC/%EA%B7%B8_%EC%9E%90%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C/" title="서달달 - 그 자리에서 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 눈 내 귀 내 입 속에 <br>너의 흔적이 너무나 짙어 <br>그 자리에서 <br>흘려버린 내 마음에 <br>너의 기억이 너무나 깊어 <br>그 자리에서 <br>야 거봐 헤어져 그 세 음절 <br>이미 건조해져 버린 입술 <br>사이에서 흘리는 건 <br>2초도 안 걸려 <br>대신 미세하게 떨렸던 음정 <br>분주해져 복잡한 머릿속은 <br>당장 무슨 말과 어떤 제스처 <br>드라마 속 연인들은 눈물을 짜 <br>혹은 쿨한 척 <br>당당한 걸음으로 걸어가 <br>현실 속 난 그저 머리만 긁적 <br>어눌하지만 최대한 담담한 척 <br>잘 가 행복했어 <br>기다렸다는 듯 기계적인 반응 <br>이상하게도 발걸음이 <br>그다지 무겁지가 않아 <br>불과 몇 시간 전만 해도 <br>어느 연인들 부럽지가 않아 <br>사랑해 입술을 부딪쳤는데 <br>신기하게도 이젠 <br>남이 돼 둘이 돼 <br>어떡해 분명 우리였는데 <br>너나 나나 이젠 자유야 <br>길어질 줄 알았던 오늘 하루가 <br>빨리도 끝나 밤이 깊어오니 <br>난 살 수가 없을 듯 숨이 막혀 <br>널 처음 봤던 그날보다 더 <br>당장 내일 눈을 뜨면 어떻게 버텨 <br>이젠 길어질 것 같아 매일 하루가 <br>내 눈 내 귀 내 입 속에 <br>너의 흔적이 너무나 짙어 <br>그 자리에서 <br>흘려버린 내 마음에 <br>너의 기억이 너무나 깊어 <br>그 자리에서 <br>생각보다 긴 하루는 일주일 정도 <br>어쩌면 미리 했나 봐 <br>맘의 정리정돈 <br>요즘 좀 지겨워 <br>매일 반복되는 바쁜 척 <br>지루한 시간 즐긴 척 <br>잘 지낸 척 <br>insta 웃는 셀카로 도배 <br>하루를 보내 <br>너도 같아 우린 서로를 속여 속네 <br>모르겠어 서로의 속내 <br>실수로 누른 듯해 빨간 heart <br>쉽게 예상돼 확신해 <br>며칠 안에 연락 와 <br>만나자마자 확인해 <br>여전히 따뜻한 서로의 체온 <br>그리웠어 서로에게 <br>묻어있던 흔적을 다시 채워 <br>깨워 서로 외웠던 <br>둘만의 언어 다시 또 배워 <br>끝나면 쓸모 없을 <br>둘만 알아볼 수 있는 <br>은밀한 표정들을 <br>이것도 예상했어 <br>진해진 흔적 <br>무표정하게 씻어내 <br>감정을 간직한 채 <br>이러는 건 서로에게 <br>쓸모 없는 낭비 <br>어쩌면 서롤 외면해 <br>저지른 마음의 반칙 <br>예상했듯 화려한 축제 뒤는 <br>더러워 문제 <br>또 연락해 <br>그래 이게 네가 원한 우리 관계 <br>난 서 있어 그 자리에서 <br>]]></content><category term="서달달" label="서달달"/><category term="그 자리에서" label="그 자리에서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/랩혼_Raphorn/Love_Feat_LQ/</id><title>랩혼 (Raphorn) - Love (Feat. LQ) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:06:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:06:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9E%A9%ED%98%BC_Raphorn/Love_Feat_LQ/" title="랩혼 (Raphorn) - Love (Feat. LQ) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love 사랑 했었다면 변치않는 마음을 <br>Love 흔들리지 않는 사람이란 <br>세상에 없는 걸 <br>Love 세상 어디에도 <br>니가 없는 곳은 없어 <br>Love 너의 눈빛속에 나는 없네 <br>난 아직도 철들지 못했나봐 <br>아주 잠시 잠깐 아프면 모든게 <br>이해 될꺼라 던 너의 말을 듣던 순간 <br>그 이후로 시간이 흘러가지 않네 <br>이 랩을 들어봐 그때와 <br>똑같은 스타일 <br>똑같은 가사 똑같은 너 <br>벗어나질 못해 <br>이젠 눈을 뜰 때마다 <br>너의 생각에 괴롭진 않지만 <br>멈춘 시계에 먼지가 내려 앉듯이 <br>내 마음이 보이지 않아 <br>무척이나 이쁘고 상냥했던 <br>그녀들이 다가왔었지만 <br>난 나를 감추고 <br>아무런 느낌을 느끼지 못하고 <br>감정을 느끼지 못하는 사이코패스 <br>그렇게 너라는 고통을 잊었네 <br>Love 사랑 했었다면 변치않는 마음을 <br>Love 너의 눈빛속에 <br>나는 더이상 없네 <br>너만 없으면 내 모든게 perfect <br>금방 sunrise 올줄 알았던 sunset <br>근데 계속해서 난 어둠에서 정체 <br>말하기도 우울해져 기나긴 공백 <br>여자친구랑 가는 맛집과 모텔 <br>서른 넘어서도 <br>전혀 되지 않아 update <br>쉽지 않아 남친 신분으로의 컴백 <br>남의 연애 얘기 나올때면 바로 정색 <br>겨우 너 같은게 <br>마지막이라 꿈에 나오는 <br>애인이 너 밖에 없어 <br>가끔은 분해하네 <br>그리운 마음은 1도 없어 <br>최신 버전이 너일뿐 <br>차라리 그 전에 만난 애가 더 보고픔 <br>랩혼형이 하자고 한 주제 덕분에 <br>괜히 널 끄집어내 썼는데 <br>기분 별로네 <br>이제 내 가사에서 널 볼 일은 없어 <br>아 better man은 <br>이거보다 전에 만들었어 <br>이젠 나도 몰라 <br>너에게 이끌려 온 내 감정 뭔지 <br>어쩌면 너도 몰라 <br>너의 어장속 녹조 라떼 웬지 <br>이젠 나도 몰라 <br>너에게 이끌려 온 내 감정 뭔지 <br>어쩌면 너도 몰라 <br>너의 어장속 녹조 라떼 웬지 <br>]]></content><category term="랩혼 (Raphorn)" label="랩혼 (Raphorn)"/><category term="Love (Feat. LQ)" label="Love (Feat. LQ)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bryson_Tiller/Set_It_Off/</id><title>Bryson Tiller - Set It Off - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:06:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:06:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bryson_Tiller/Set_It_Off/" title="Bryson Tiller - Set It Off - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro: Faith Evans &amp; Bryson Tiller] <br>Oh, my inspiration comes from you, oh <br>So you think you got what it takes <br>To be my ride or die? <br>Okay <br>We shall see <br><br>[Verse 1] <br>Ayy, I been out here soul searchin' <br>Ayy, say you still got it, girl, what makes you so certain? <br>Hit it, quit it, then went cold turkey <br>You been committed through this whole journey <br>Got a girl that don't expect as much from me <br>That's why she gets so much love from me <br>She just might be the one for me <br>Ain't no need to question, down bitch <br><br>[Chorus] <br>She 'a pull the gun for me <br>Pop 2, she 'a take one for me <br>Set it off, if a bitch come for me <br>Set if off, if a nigga come for me <br>She 'a pull the gun for me <br>Pop 2, she 'a take one for me <br>Set it off, if a bitch come for me <br>Set it off, if a nigga come <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>Do you remember them days, I would cut school and come to you <br>Ma' was cool so I got comfortable <br>Sleeping on the couch, sneak up to your room, ayy <br>I found out you was a freak too soon, ayy <br>Your family thought we had baby too soon, phh <br>I told your family not to speak too soon, ayy <br>Three years later, I'm on TV <br>Now your brother, he envy me <br>I don't know what the fuck he be on, ayy <br>Cool with me cool, we was never friends <br>He put your mama under stress, I put her in a Benz <br>Even though she put me in the streets, she made amends <br>Watchin' over my baby's nigga <br>'Case her son wanna go back to his ways and be a street nigga <br>Plus my girl just copped the heat, nigga <br>And she gon' kill almost any nigga <br>Including me, nigga <br>Ain't nobody who could be with her, 'cept for me <br>That's my down bitch <br><br>[Chorus] <br>She 'a pull the gun for me <br>Pop two, she 'a take one for me <br>Set it off, if a bitch come for me <br>Set it off, if a nigga come for me <br>She 'a pull the gun for me <br>Pop two, she 'a take one for me <br>Set it off, if a bitch come for me <br>Set it off, if a nigga come for me <br><br>[Outro: Bryson Tiller &amp; Unknown] <br>Ooh, yeah <br>Yeah, yeah <br>Ayy, think she'll fuck with this song? <br>Yeah, I hope so nigga <br>She ain't call me back for some reason <br>Oh well, I love her]]></content><category term="Bryson Tiller" label="Bryson Tiller"/><category term="Set It Off" label="Set It Off"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bryson_Tiller/Self-Made/</id><title>Bryson Tiller - Self-Made - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-06T23:06:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-06T23:06:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bryson_Tiller/Self-Made/" title="Bryson Tiller - Self-Made - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro] <br>Woo, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>You already know <br>Young Tiller <br>Let's go <br><br>[Bridge] <br>Gucci on my belt <br>Bought a necklace for myself <br>Bought Giuseppe for myself <br>Spent them blessings on myself <br>Donatello, that's that killa, I smoke purple out the shell <br>She want Birkin, she want Gucci purse, she want Chanel, got it <br><br>[Verse 1] <br>I spend that cause I earned it for myself <br>Got my shawty out the way and now I'm splurging on myself <br>You should worry 'bout yourself <br>I've been working on myself <br>I've been balling like I'm Curry, need a jersey for myself <br>(I need a jersey for myself) <br>What's next? I'm nervous for myself <br>If I changed, I became a better version of myself <br>Bought a chain, bought 2 more, yeah, I deserve that for myself <br>And my neighbors look at me like "How he purchase that himself?" <br><br><br>[Hook] <br>Cause I'm a seven-figure <br>Self-made nigga <br>Blow the money, get it back the next day, nigga <br>(Made it back, yeah) <br>Wow, what the check say, nigga? <br>I'm getting paid, nigga <br>Need a chef and maid, nigga <br><br>[Bridge] <br>And a Gucci on my belt <br>Bought a necklace for myself <br>Bought Giuseppe for myself <br>Spent them blessings on myself <br>Donatello, that's that killa, I smoke purple out the shell <br>She want Birkin, she want Gucci purse, she want Chanel, got it <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>Must've heard a hundred niggas say they made me <br>("I made that, nigga!") <br>So, which one you niggas made me? <br>Don't know who you talking to, not me, oh no, you can't be <br>They wan' be my fam but my crew is sucker-lame free (Lame free) <br>I just want a yacht and a jet-ski <br>Pull up on your block, Icy Hot, Wayne Gretzkey <br>(I pull up, pull up) <br>Fucking con artist, boy, you sketchy <br>Pretty but she messy <br>Only wanna sex me <br><br><br>[Hook] <br>Cause I'm a seven-figure <br>Self-made nigga <br>Blow the money, get it back the next day, nigga <br>(Made it back, yeah) <br>Wow, what the check say, nigga? <br>I'm getting paid, nigga <br>Need a chef and maid, nigga <br><br>[Verse 3] <br>Count that mula with my thumb <br>502, that's where I'm from <br>Used to stay on Hazelwood <br>You see trouble then you run (Run) <br>Word to Joker, no, but we don't do this shit for fun <br>Hundred million, then I'm done <br>Poochie laid out in the sun <br>Like I want <br><br>[Bridge] <br>Gucci on my belt <br>Bought a necklace for myself <br>Bought Giuseppe for myself <br>Spent them blessings on myself <br>Donatello, that's that killa, I smoke purple out the shell <br>She want Birkin, she want Gucci purse, she want Chanel <br><br>[Outro] <br>Yeah, yeah, Gucci on my belt <br>Yeah, she want Gucci on her belt <br>Gucci on her purse <br>Gucci on that <br>Yeah]]></content><category term="Bryson Tiller" label="Bryson Tiller"/><category term="Self-Made" label="Self-Made"/></entry></feed>