<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:19:26+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TP_RETRO_타디스_프로젝트舊/오늘도_그대만_Feat_정동원/</id><title>TP_RETRO_타디스_프로젝트舊 - 오늘도 그대만 (Feat. 정동원) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:47:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:47:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TP_RETRO_%ED%83%80%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4_%ED%94%84%EB%A1%9C%EC%A0%9D%ED%8A%B8%E8%88%8A/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98%EB%8F%84_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%A7%8C_Feat_%EC%A0%95%EB%8F%99%EC%9B%90/" title="TP_RETRO_타디스_프로젝트舊 - 오늘도 그대만 (Feat. 정동원) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[봄날처럼 몰래 <br>다가왔던 나의 그대 <br>여름 같이 뜨거웠던 <br>우리의 시간들 <br>어느덧 찾아온 시린 겨울 <br>혹시 그대 아프진 않을까 <br>걱정돼요 <br>그대에게 부족한 나라서 <br>나 그렇게 그댈 붙잡지 못했죠 <br>소리 없이 울먹이던 그대 <br>그만하자는 그 말 다 거짓말이죠 <br>오지 않는 전화를 붙잡고 <br>후회만 하는 참 바보 같은 나 <br>그땐 뭐가 그렇게 어려웠던 건지 <br>조용히 그대 마음 안아줄 걸 <br>우연처럼 다시 와줘요 <br>내 품에 머물던 <br>그대 온기 남았는데 <br>그댈 사랑한 만큼 <br>하루하루 겨우 버텨봐도 <br>너무 아파 <br>매일 그대 생각에 살아요 <br>빗방울이 떨어지던 그 밤 <br>우산처럼 기울던 그대와 나는 <br>하염없이 눈물만 흘렸죠 <br>돌아온다는 그 말 다 거짓말이죠 <br>오지 않는 전화를 붙잡고 <br>후회만 하고 있는 <br>참 바보 같은 내가 <br>그댈 사랑한 만큼 <br>하루하루 겨우 버텨봐도 <br>너무 아파 <br>매일 그대 생각에 살아요 <br>오늘도 술에 취해 그댈 부르고 <br>후회만 하고 있는 <br>참 이기적인 내가 <br>우리 사랑한 만큼 <br>지우기엔 너무 아픈 그대 이름 <br>매일 그대 생각에 울어요 <br>다시 내게 와줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="T.P RETRO (타디스 프로젝트舊)" label="T.P RETRO (타디스 프로젝트舊)"/><category term="오늘도 그대만 (Feat. 정동원)" label="오늘도 그대만 (Feat. 정동원)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코창/타이밍_Inst/</id><title>코창 - 타이밍 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:47:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:47:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EC%B0%BD/%ED%83%80%EC%9D%B4%EB%B0%8D_Inst/" title="코창 - 타이밍 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[네가 없이 뭐 그닥 <br>잘 지내고 있다가 <br>지금 와서 뭐야 <br>네가 생각나 <br>오늘따라 내 마음이 <br>왜 너를 생각하는지 <br>나도 모르게 왠지 <br>밤새 든 네 생각 <br>왜 너는 한 템포 늦어 <br>내가 매일 듣던 말 <br>여자 마음을 몰라 stop <br>조금 늦는 것 뿐이야 <br>다들 왜 그래 되게 <br>열심히 나를 움직이는데 <br>늘 one tempo <br>늘 one tempo <br>네가 말하던 타이밍 <br>으으음 타이밍 을 <br>이제는 알 것 같아 <br>다시 기회가 올까 <br>네가 말하던 타이밍 <br>으으음 타이밍 을 <br>나는 아직도 많이 <br>늦는 것 같아 <br>마음을 먹은 건 to date <br>연락하는 건 too late <br>하필 지금 눈치란게 생겨서 <br>나를 밀어낼까봐 <br>다가가면 싫어할까봐 <br>그렇게 한 번 더 또 <br>너를 보내고 있어 <br>왜 너는 한 템포 늦어 <br>내가 매일 듣던 말 <br>여자 마음을 몰라 stop <br>조금 늦는 것 뿐이야 <br>다들 왜 그래 뭐가 <br>어때서 자꾸 헷갈리게 해 <br>늘 one tempo <br>늘 one tempo <br>네가 말하던 타이밍 <br>으으음 타이밍 을 <br>이제는 알 것 같아 <br>다시 기회가 올까 <br>네가 말하던 타이밍 <br>으으음 타이밍 을 <br>나는 아직도 많이 <br>늦는 것 같아 <br>다시 한 번 더 <br>내게 타이밍을 줘 <br>나를 보여줄 수 <br>있게 말이야 <br>다시 한 번 더 <br>내게 타이밍을 줘 <br>날 조금 늦춰 <br>네 발에 맞출게 <br>Now I know what to do <br>but i spent all all my chance <br>이제 없다는 걸 <br>잘 알고 있지만 <br>그때 그 내 타이밍 <br>이제 알 것만 같아 <br>이제야 조금은 알 것만 같아 <br>]]></content><category term="코창" label="코창"/><category term="타이밍 (Inst.)" label="타이밍 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코창/타이밍/</id><title>코창 - 타이밍 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:47:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:47:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EC%B0%BD/%ED%83%80%EC%9D%B4%EB%B0%8D/" title="코창 - 타이밍 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[네가 없이 뭐 그닥 <br>잘 지내고 있다가 <br>지금 와서 뭐야 <br>네가 생각나 <br>오늘따라 내 마음이 <br>왜 너를 생각하는지 <br>나도 모르게 왠지 <br>밤새 든 네 생각 <br>왜 너는 한 템포 늦어 <br>내가 매일 듣던 말 <br>여자 마음을 몰라 stop <br>조금 늦는 것 뿐이야 <br>다들 왜 그래 되게 <br>열심히 나를 움직이는데 <br>늘 one tempo <br>늘 one tempo <br>네가 말하던 타이밍 <br>으으음 타이밍 을 <br>이제는 알 것 같아 <br>다시 기회가 올까 <br>네가 말하던 타이밍 <br>으으음 타이밍 을 <br>나는 아직도 많이 <br>늦는 것 같아 <br>마음을 먹은 건 to date <br>연락하는 건 too late <br>하필 지금 눈치란게 생겨서 <br>나를 밀어낼까봐 <br>다가가면 싫어할까봐 <br>그렇게 한 번 더 또 <br>너를 보내고 있어 <br>왜 너는 한 템포 늦어 <br>내가 매일 듣던 말 <br>여자 마음을 몰라 stop <br>조금 늦는 것 뿐이야 <br>다들 왜 그래 뭐가 <br>어때서 자꾸 헷갈리게 해 <br>늘 one tempo <br>늘 one tempo <br>네가 말하던 타이밍 <br>으으음 타이밍 을 <br>이제는 알 것 같아 <br>다시 기회가 올까 <br>네가 말하던 타이밍 <br>으으음 타이밍 을 <br>나는 아직도 많이 <br>늦는 것 같아 <br>다시 한 번 더 <br>내게 타이밍을 줘 <br>나를 보여줄 수 <br>있게 말이야 <br>다시 한 번 더 <br>내게 타이밍을 줘 <br>날 조금 늦춰 <br>네 발에 맞출게 <br>Now I know what to do <br>but i spent all all my chance <br>이제 없다는 걸 <br>잘 알고 있지만 <br>그때 그 내 타이밍 <br>이제 알 것만 같아 <br>이제야 조금은 알 것만 같아 <br>]]></content><category term="코창" label="코창"/><category term="타이밍" label="타이밍"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/연희다방/콧수염/</id><title>연희다방 - 콧수염 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:47:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:47:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%B0%ED%9D%AC%EB%8B%A4%EB%B0%A9/%EC%BD%A7%EC%88%98%EC%97%BC/" title="연희다방 - 콧수염 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘도 니카톡은 답장이 없고 <br>1자는 사라진지 오래인 <br>대화방을 들락날락 <br>자존심 같은건 버린지 오랜데 <br>난 몰라 열번찍어 안 넘어 가는 <br>나무 여기있네 <br>알아 바보같은거 니가 보면 <br>다 니얘긴걸 안다면 <br>싸이콘가 아니면 또라인가 <br>하겠지 uh <br>미쳐서 그래 아니 나 뭐래 <br>온종일 니생각만 자꾸 나잖아 <br>반해버렸잖아 놓치기 싫어 <br>하루종일 랄라랄라랄라 <br>생각나는 니 콧수염 <br>Nanananana <br>nanananana <br>nanananananana <br>nanananana <br>Nanananana <br>nanananana <br>nanananananana <br>알아 별로라는거 내가 봐도 <br>거울을 보며혼자서 <br>뚱뚱한가 아니면 못생겼나 <br>한다고 uh <br>미쳐서 그래 아니 나 뭐래 <br>노래도 니 노래만 자꾸 쓰잖아 <br>반해버렸잖아 놓치기 싫어 <br>하루종일 랄라랄라랄라 <br>생각나는 니 콧수염 <br>Nanananana <br>nanananana <br>nanananananana <br>nanananana <br>Nanananana <br>nanananana <br>nanananananana <br>열번찍어 안 넘어가는 나무 없다고 <br>남자는 들이대는 여잔 다 좋다고 <br>도데체 누가그런 헛소리 했냐고 <br>남자를 만나본적 있어야 알지 <br>미쳐서 그래 아니나 뭐래 <br>이것도 니 얘긴거 너도 알잖아 <br>계속말했잖아 이상형이라고 <br>이정도 했으면 됐잖아 <br>둔탱이다 둔탱이야 <br>Nanananana <br>nanananana <br>nanananananana <br>nanananana <br>Nanananana <br>nanananana <br>nanananananana <br>콧수염 <br>]]></content><category term="연희다방" label="연희다방"/><category term="콧수염" label="콧수염"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/연희다방/유성/</id><title>연희다방 - 유성 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:47:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:47:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%B0%ED%9D%AC%EB%8B%A4%EB%B0%A9/%EC%9C%A0%EC%84%B1/" title="연희다방 - 유성 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하늘에 별이 떨어져 <br>저 별은 유성이라고 부르죠 <br>잠시면 사라지는 저 별똥별은 <br>내 소원을 들어줄까 <br>반짝 스쳐가는 사랑일까 <br>내게로 날아와 줄까 <br>한눈에 반해버린 사랑처럼 <br>내 눈에 박혀버릴까 <br>소원을 들어줘 별아 <br>내가 꿈꿔왔던 그런 별이야 <br>내 사랑을 이뤄줘 별아 <br>그토록 찾던 이상형이야 <br>Falling star <br>다시는 만나지 못 할 까봐 <br>이토록 좋아할 사람 <br>하늘에 떨어지는 유성에게 <br>한 없이 기도 하곤 해 <br>소원을 들어줘 별아 <br>내가 꿈꿔왔던 그런 별이야 <br>내 사랑을 이뤄줘 별아 <br>그토록 찾던 이상형이야 <br>Falling star <br>손 내밀면 사라질 까봐 <br>바라만 보고 서있죠 <br>손 모아 하늘을 보며 <br>오늘밤 유성이 떨어지길 빌어 <br>소원을 들어줘 별아 <br>내가 꿈꿔왔던 그런 별이야 <br>내 사랑을 이뤄줘 별아 <br>그토록 찾던 이상형이야 <br>Falling star <br>Falling star <br>Falling star <br>]]></content><category term="연희다방" label="연희다방"/><category term="유성" label="유성"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/연희다방/동동/</id><title>연희다방 - 동동 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:47:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:47:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%B0%ED%9D%AC%EB%8B%A4%EB%B0%A9/%EB%8F%99%EB%8F%99/" title="연희다방 - 동동 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[동동 떠가는 구름처럼 <br>알게 모르게 항상 있었지 <br>동동 내 맘이 왜 이럴까 <br>I'm in love and you make me smile <br>갑자기 니 존재가 크게만 느껴져 <br>당연히 곁에 있던 너였는데 <br>서로를 좀 더 <br>알아가는 게 좋은데도 <br>또 한편 상처받을까 두려워 <br>동동이 동동love 동동이 동동love <br>마음이 가라앉지 않아 어떡해 <br>내 맘을 채워줘 내 손을 잡아줘 <br>녹여줘 얼어붙은 내 가슴도 <br>rala rala lalarala lala <br>지금 내 기분은 동동 <br>rala rala lalarala lala <br>자꾸만 가슴이 동동 <br>미칠 듯 두근대는 <br>나 좀 어떻게 해줘 <br>당연히 곁에 있던 너였는데 <br>예전엔 눈에 차지 않던 <br>니 행동들도 <br>이제는 내 심장을 설레게 하네 <br>동동이 동동love 동동이 동동love <br>마음이 가라앉지 않아 어떡해 <br>내 맘을 채워줘 내 손을 잡아줘 <br>녹여줘 얼어붙은 내 가슴도 <br>rala rala lalarala lala <br>지금 내 기분은 동동 <br>rala rala lalarala lala <br>자꾸만 가슴이 동동 <br>한 걸음씩 또 한 걸음씩 <br>조금씩 가까이 가볼까 <br>One step two step <br>and hello my baby <br>이제는 연애 좀 해볼까 <br>동동이 동동love 동동이 동동love <br>마음이 가라앉지 않아 어떡해 <br>내 맘을 채워줘 내 손을 잡아줘 <br>녹여줘 얼어붙은 내 가슴도 <br>동동이 동동love 동동이 동동love <br>마음이 가라앉지 않아 어떡해 <br>내 맘을 채워줘 내 손을 잡아줘 <br>녹여줘 얼어붙은 내 가슴도 <br>rala rala lalarala lala <br>지금 내 기분은 동동 <br>rala rala lalarala lala <br>자꾸만 가슴이 동동 <br>널 보면 가슴이 동동 <br>]]></content><category term="연희다방" label="연희다방"/><category term="동동" label="동동"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/연희다방/야설_夜雪/</id><title>연희다방 - 야설 (夜雪) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:47:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:47:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%B0%ED%9D%AC%EB%8B%A4%EB%B0%A9/%EC%95%BC%EC%84%A4_%E5%A4%9C%E9%9B%AA/" title="연희다방 - 야설 (夜雪) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈이 너무 예쁘게 내렸어 <br>아무것도 할 수가 없어 <br>할 일이 진짜 많았는데 <br>그냥 창 밖만 바라봤어 <br>눈발에 조용해진 세상 <br>그 조용함에 귀 기울이고 <br>차가운 하얀 냄새에 <br>가만히 눈을 감아봐 <br>창 밖이 너무 예뻐서 <br>아무것도 할 수가 없어 <br>가로등 불에 비친 금빛눈발 탓에 <br>나 잠도 자긴 글렀구나 <br>눈발에 조용해진 세상 <br>그 조용함에 귀 기울이고 <br>차가운 하얀 냄새에 <br>가만히 눈을 감아봐 <br>창 밖이 너무 예뻐서 <br>아무것도 할 수가 없어 <br>가로등 불에 비친 금빛눈발 탓에 <br>나 잠도 자긴 글렀구나 <br>눈이 너무 예쁘게 내렸어 <br>아무것도 할 수가 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="연희다방" label="연희다방"/><category term="야설 (夜雪)" label="야설 (夜雪)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/연희다방/창밖_좀_볼래/</id><title>연희다방 - 창밖 좀 볼래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:47:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:47:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%B0%ED%9D%AC%EB%8B%A4%EB%B0%A9/%EC%B0%BD%EB%B0%96_%EC%A2%80_%EB%B3%BC%EB%9E%98/" title="연희다방 - 창밖 좀 볼래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여보세요 지금 뭐해 <br>혹시 지금 안바쁘면 <br>창밖 좀 볼래 <br>It's snowing outside now <br>너에게 제일 먼저 <br>말해주고 싶었어 <br>It's snowing outside now <br>오늘 저녁에 잠깐 나와 <br>흰 눈을 맞으며 걸어요 <br>스치는 어깨가 짜릿해요 <br>그대 옆 모습이 좋아요 <br>올 해 겨울은 참 좋아요 <br>It's snowing outside now <br>너에게 제일 먼저 <br>말해주고 싶었어 <br>It's snowing outside now <br>오늘 저녁에 잠깐 나오라니까 <br>흰 눈을 맞으며 걸어요 <br>스치는 어깨가 짜릿해요 <br>그대 옆 모습이 좋아요 <br>올 해 겨울은 참 좋아요 <br>너도 시려운 손 잡아줄 <br>누군가 필요하지 않니 <br>이제 내 손을 꼭 잡아봐 <br>우리는 <br>흰 눈을 맞으며 걸어요 <br>스치는 어깨가 짜릿해요 <br>그대 옆 모습이 좋아요 <br>올 해 겨울은 참 좋아요 <br>여보세요 지금 뭐해 <br>혹시 지금 안 바쁘면 <br>창밖 좀 볼래 <br>]]></content><category term="연희다방" label="연희다방"/><category term="창밖 좀 볼래" label="창밖 좀 볼래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍창우/Perfect_Game_Feat_ARTEe/</id><title>홍창우 - Perfect Game (Feat. ARTEe) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:48:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:48:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%B0%BD%EC%9A%B0/Perfect_Game_Feat_ARTEe/" title="홍창우 - Perfect Game (Feat. ARTEe) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[각자의 제각기 다른 목표 <br>비슷한 수준에선 결국 한 통속 <br>옳고 그름 서로의 다른 온도 <br>그 차이가 불러 온 다툼 <br>물어뜯는 손톱 <br>비슷하게 사는 듯 해 모두 <br>사람 사는 거 다 똑같애 <br>악전고투 <br>걸음마를 맞추거나 <br>혹은 밀려나거나 <br>빠르게 벗어나 다른 <br>살아 낼 궁릴 찾던가 <br>난 좀 달라 <br>모든 흐름을 나에게로 <br>철 마다 바꿔대는 컬러 <br>나는 카멜레온 <br>누가 반대해도 <br>상관 안 해 전혀 <br>그 여론에는 여태는 <br>한 번도 안 꺾어 <br>내 손에 쥐고 있는 패가 <br>아직 많아 <br>결국 방해가 된 밤잠 <br>놓을 수 않는 창작 <br>이 와중에 불가능하지 <br>않은 앞가림 <br>내 의지로 시작 한 게임 <br>켠 김에 왕까지 <br>It's Okay 내려놔 <br>안 당연해 하나도 <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>It's all good 날 믿어 <br>충분해 지금도 <br>Yeah Yeah <br>내 삶의 모토 이게 <br>진짜 정확한 단어 <br>나에 대해선 아무것도 <br>모르고 나를 까던 <br>그들도 불안정한 상태지 <br>안정을 원해 <br>담배 몇 모금으로 <br>달래기엔 끔찍한 권태 <br>내가 배팅한 20대 땐 <br>나도 악전고투 <br>했던 걸 알아 유난히도 <br>많이 맞았던 뒤통수 <br>갚아주지 않았어 <br>그러기 싫었거든 <br>시간이 가고 UPGRADE가 <br>된 듯이 어느덧 서른 <br>게임 이야기가 아직 <br>재미있는 내 동네 친구 <br>난 정반대 음악을 다뤄 <br>그게 내 존재 이유 <br>그렇게 취기가 오른 <br>상태로 날은 밝고 <br>서로가 서로에게 지지 <br>않지 한 글자도 <br>근데 나랑은 안 맞아 <br>겁내는 게 <br>내겐 승률 9할 그 이상 <br>Perfect Game <br>승부 조작 의혹 없이도 <br>매일이 Birthday <br>주머니에 있던 건 먼지 <br>더미와 코인 몇 개 <br>It's Okay 내려놔 <br>안 당연해 하나도 <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>It's all good 날 믿어 <br>충분해 지금도 <br>Yeah Yeah <br>나름의 사연들 남들처럼 <br>살아 내는 게 <br>요즘 청춘의 화두 <br>감정의 샌드백 <br>하고 싶은 걸 쫓아가 <br>늦지 않았어 <br>몇 번의 기회가 남았던 <br>어차피 인생은 마라톤 <br>주머니에 있던 건 먼지 <br>더미와 코인 몇 개 <br>얼마가 남았건 상관 안 해 <br>충실하지 현재에 <br>딱히 다를 바 없는 결론 <br>답이 나온 상황 <br>사실 다들 손에 쥐고 있는 패가 <br>아직 많아 <br>It's Okay 내려놔 <br>안 당연해 하나도 <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>Yeah Yeah <br>It's all good 날 믿어 <br>충분해 지금도 <br>충분해 지금도 <br>Yeah <br>]]></content><category term="홍창우" label="홍창우"/><category term="Perfect Game (Feat. ARTEe)" label="Perfect Game (Feat. ARTEe)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍창우/Breathe_Feat_XenomiX/</id><title>홍창우 - Breathe (Feat. XenomiX) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:48:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:48:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%B0%BD%EC%9A%B0/Breathe_Feat_XenomiX/" title="홍창우 - Breathe (Feat. XenomiX) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My brotha let me breathe Yeah <br>My Sista let me breathe <br>꿈을 꿀 수 있는 게 <br>너무도 당연해 <br>내겐 숨을 쉬듯 자연스럽네 <br>걱정 그만해 날 <br>그들과 섞지 말아 <br>아무렴 뒤 떨어질 수 없는 <br>현실 감각 <br>기억 안나 과하게 <br>욕심을 내 본 적 <br>가진 적 없던 것들이 <br>결국 더 괴롭혀 <br>더 외로워 지기 전에 <br>따라가 꿈을 꿔 <br>이미 꺼졌던 장작 <br>난 다시 불을 피워 <br>내 삶의 목표 자체는 <br>그리 크지 않아 <br>유명한 누가 말 했듯 <br>돈이 다가 아냐 <br>나 눈 감는 때가 오면 <br>목소리가 남아 <br>작은 방 누군가의 <br>이어폰에서 흘렀다가 <br>누군가에 행복을 <br>나눠 줄 수만 있다면 <br>아님 슬픔을 만지는 <br>그럴 수만 있다면 <br>난 만족해 지금 내 노력이 <br>누군가에 가슴에 <br>닿을 때야 나 홀연히 <br>Let me Breathe <br>My brotha let me breathe Yeah <br>Believe me <br>한 숨 돌리고 가게 <br>My Sista let me breathe Yeah <br>Believe me <br>조금 쉬었다 가게 <br>My brotha let me breathe <br>My Sista let me breathe <br>Just believe me <br>이제 어느덧 서른 <br>견고해진 자의식 <br>웬만한 고민들은 다 <br>겪어왔을 나이지 <br>아직 이룰 게 많아 <br>여태는 단지 걸음마 <br>내 고집 못 꺾어 <br>절대 이건 아냐 성급함 <br>후회 하고 싶지 않아 <br>판을 크게 벌려 <br>하고 싶음 해 <br>선천적인 성격 <br>숨쉬는 것도 불편해 <br>의식하는 순간 <br>끌고 가던지 다 내려놔 <br>그렇담 나는 후자 <br>잠깐 한 숨 한 번 쉬고 <br>둘러본 내 주위 <br>환경들은 완벽해 <br>무리 안 해도 굳이 <br>여전히 작업해 <br>그런 무의미한 질문 <br>내게는 묻지 말아 <br>그건 너에게나 치부 <br>어디로 가고 있어 지금 <br>막연한 네 질문에 <br>미리 답할게 Me too <br>내 손에 쥔 꿈이란 게 <br>자꾸 내 눈 앞에 밟혀 <br>그래서 다시 말 할게 <br>난 앞만 보고 달려 <br>Yeah <br>Let me breathe <br>You know how i feel <br>how i live how i spit <br>My brotha let me breathe <br>Yeah just Give me few second <br>모든 게 다 겪어가는 과정 <br>어제도 내일도 <br>책임은 내게 있지 <br>어떤 선택도 책임도 <br>지금 행복 뒤에 <br>내 무덤 내가 파놓고 <br>홀가분히 떠날 수 <br>있을 것만 같거든 다 놓고 <br>나도 참 단순해 <br>쓸 데 없이 고집 <br>부리던 순간을 웃으면서 <br>얘기하는 걸 보니 <br>진심으로 내 주변 모두 <br>행복 했음 해 <br>예전엔 절대 하지 <br>못 했을 고백 <br>My brotha let me breathe Yeah <br>My Sista let me breathe Yeah <br>Just believe me <br>]]></content><category term="홍창우" label="홍창우"/><category term="Breathe (Feat. XenomiX)" label="Breathe (Feat. XenomiX)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍창우/All_Day_Feat_FAMERZ/</id><title>홍창우 - All Day (Feat. FAMERZ) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:48:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:48:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%B0%BD%EC%9A%B0/All_Day_Feat_FAMERZ/" title="홍창우 - All Day (Feat. FAMERZ) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다 담아두고 있지 <br>버텨내야 하는 이유 <br>이름 뒤에 걸린 배역이 <br>몇 개 저마다의 직급 <br>멍하니 보낸 시간은 <br>세 볼 수가 없어 <br>정신과 시간의 방 <br>그 때 방 한 칸은 벙커 <br>그 곳을 벗어난 뒤 <br>새로운 나를 발견 <br>한 듯이 몸을 굴려댔어 <br>게으름을 감춰 <br>많은 사람들을 만났고 <br>그 놈들은 온통 <br>술판 깔아놓고 레퍼토리는 <br>창작의 고통 <br>음 이건 늘 본 듯 한 비슷한 장면 <br>Fxxk it 나도 백날 <br>뱉을 수 있어 시간 나면 <br>맨날 해 봐야 적자야 <br>그래 뭘 냈다 쳐봐 <br>밑밥 잔뜩 깔고 <br>가오 잡아봤자 병 맛 <br>안 겪어봐도 알지 <br>난 필요 없는 훈계 <br>머리 빠개지게 풀어봐 <br>니들만의 숙제 <br>내 과거의 흔적은 남았지 <br>모든 곳곳에 <br>그래서 절대 지칠 수 없지 ALL DAY <br>내가 가는 길이 답이었네 <br>시간 낭비는 않기로 해 <br>지건 이기건 더 후회 하기 전에 <br>Do it Again <br>Do it all day <br>Yeah I do it all day <br>내가 가는 길이 답이었네 <br>시간 낭비는 않기로 해 <br>지건 이기건 더 후회 하기 전에 <br>Do it Again <br>Do it all day <br>Yeah I do it all day <br>천천히 줄여나간 체지방 <br>내 말투와 행동은 예술이 될 시간 <br>내 Wannabe는 <br>내가 되고 싶은 책임감 <br>결국에는 먹이사슬의 <br>맨 위가 내 자리지 <br>정수리들 내 발바닥만 <br>빤히 쳐다보게 <br>더 높아져야 되는 이유 <br>배가 고파졌네 <br>이미 성격이 급하지만 <br>난 천천히 끝까지 갈 생각으로 <br>비를 맞지 재미 있는 건 <br>이불 밖에 다 모여 <br>있다는 사실이 날 움직이게 하지 <br>오랜 고민이 가져다 준 건 <br>재능의 확신 <br>날 버티게 한 건 <br>어떤 기도도 아니고 <br>정 감사할 대상을 찾으면 <br>내가 내 마니또 <br>내 꿈이 너무 작대 <br>그럴 수 밖에 내 성공은 <br>너네 시야 보다 멀리 자리 잡았고 <br>난 그걸 정조준 <br>하는 중 내년에 연봉을 <br>어림 잡아보고 높여 속도를 <br>내가 가는 길이 답이었네 <br>시간 낭비는 않기로 해 <br>지건 이기건 더 후회 하기 전에 <br>Do it Again <br>Do it all day <br>Yeah I do it all day <br>내가 가는 길이 답이었네 <br>시간 낭비는 않기로 해 <br>지건 이기건 더 후회 하기 전에 <br>Do it Again <br>Do it all day <br>Yeah I do it all day <br>총대 메고 뱉던 말들 <br>다 주워담느라고 가는 시간 <br>아주 가끔 생각해 <br>근데 여전한 내 태도 <br>Yeah I won't lose <br>you lazy ass yo <br>난 지칠 수 없지 All day <br>변명이 아닌 이유가 많은 놈 <br>좀 DOPE해 <br>Okay 누구든 인간은 변해 <br>그건 네가 생각하는 것보다 <br>훨씬 당연해 <br>내가 가는 길이 답이었네 <br>시간 낭비는 않기로 해 <br>지건 이기건 더 후회 하기 전에 <br>Do it Again <br>Do it all day <br>Yeah I do it all day <br>내가 가는 길이 답이었네 <br>시간 낭비는 않기로 해 <br>지건 이기건 더 후회 하기 전에 <br>Do it Again <br>Do it all day <br>Yeah I do it all day <br>]]></content><category term="홍창우" label="홍창우"/><category term="All Day (Feat. FAMERZ)" label="All Day (Feat. FAMERZ)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍창우/Respect_Me_Feat_XenomiX_DJ_ROWBOW/</id><title>홍창우 - Respect Me (Feat. XenomiX, DJ ROWBOW) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:48:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:48:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%B0%BD%EC%9A%B0/Respect_Me_Feat_XenomiX_DJ_ROWBOW/" title="홍창우 - Respect Me (Feat. XenomiX, DJ ROWBOW) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[누군가에겐 간절해도 <br>올 수가 없을 내일 <br>그 시간에 술에 쩌들어 <br>겨우 내는 Mixtape <br>머리는 복잡해 <br>보상 받는 날이 올까 <br>음 덕분에 할 일이 <br>많아지는 KOMCA <br>이 판은 왕좌의 게임 <br>공존은 없지 <br>다른 누군가의 패인은 <br>너에겐 좋은 안주거리가 돼 <br>될만한 놈들 틈에서 <br>너도 같이 다이빙 <br>이미 놓쳤어 결정을 <br>봐야 하는 타이밍 <br>부끄러운 손 떼 <br>몇 번을 말 해봐도 <br>꾸준히 걸쳐 <br>네 열정 억지로 매달고 <br>네 딴에서의 청사진 <br>무리하게 펼쳐도 <br>살아지고 있지 <br>살아가네 억지로 <br>변해도 돼 괜찮아 <br>넌 그래야 해 <br>이대로라면 10년 후에도 <br>넌 술래만 해 <br>행인3 역할 정도에 <br>지나지 않은 배역 안 <br>얼토당토 않은 VERSE는 <br>이제 그만 채워가 <br>악취가 진동하는 곳 어쩜 아직 <br>진행 중이겠지 <br>앞이 밝진 않으니까 사실 <br>넌 따져 어쩌네 저쩌네 <br>미쳐 버릴 때까지 <br>난 차라리 편해 <br>여태 길던 거릴 재놨기에 <br>힘들게 살아왔대 <br>내가 보기엔 고작 덤벨 <br>그렇게 쭉 똑같은 컨셉의 <br>시건방을 떠네 <br>Yo 난 필요 없어 조언 너 따위가 <br>건드릴 Navigation은 없지 <br>내 자체가 나침반 <br>왜 나한테 찾나 몰라 <br>네 실패의 이유를 <br>성공의 이유를 늘려가도 <br>시작점은 질투 <br>그딴 새끼들의 말 따윈 <br>쌩까 귀를 닫어 <br>패배자들 입방정 뒤엔 <br>꽤나 값나가는 반전 <br>그래 그래서 지금 넌 <br>바닥만 치고 있어 <br>노력은 귀찮고 <br>입방정만 떨면 보여 비전 <br>제발 그만 좀 해 <br>그 어린애 같은 투정 <br>이쯤 발 걸치고 있던 것도 <br>괜찮은 추억 <br>]]></content><category term="홍창우" label="홍창우"/><category term="Respect Me (Feat. XenomiX, DJ ROWBOW)" label="Respect Me (Feat. XenomiX, DJ ROWBOW)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍창우/Hurricane_Feat_ARTEe/</id><title>홍창우 - Hurricane (Feat. ARTEe) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:48:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:48:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%B0%BD%EC%9A%B0/Hurricane_Feat_ARTEe/" title="홍창우 - Hurricane (Feat. ARTEe) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[더 어지럽게 해 <br>No more silence <br>Make it hot 불처럼 <br>울려 사이렌 <br>All world 퍼져나가 <br>나의 바이러스 <br>Make chaos yo <br>Like a hurricane <br>Time is tickin' 바쁜 시침 <br>그 보다 못한 본새 <br>그 놈의 칠린 <br>음악 하는 척 <br>인스타에서나 자주 비침 <br>결국 없는 결과물 <br>아무도 안 빠는 위치 <br>인맥이 어쩌고 Trend가 <br>어쩌고 핑계들의 대합실 <br>아니 다 떼놓고 봐도 <br>결국 넌 없잖아 배짱이 <br>그 놈의 HIPHOP IS DEAD <br>고만 좀 죽여 <br>저스틴 비버 간지 <br>넌 잘 몰랐잖아 뜨또 <br>손에 쥘 수록 겸허하게 <br>You never know <br>그래서 누가 널 깔 봐도 <br>말도 못해 대놓고 <br>너랑 다르게 잘 봐 <br>난 내 미래 천하태평 <br>정답이 있는 거였다면 <br>난 안 했어 당연 200% <br>더 어지럽게 해 <br>No more silence <br>Make it hot 불처럼 <br>울려 사이렌 <br>All world 퍼져나가 <br>나의 바이러스 <br>Make chaos yo hurricane <br>더 어지럽게 해 <br>No more silence <br>Make it hot 불처럼 <br>울려 사이렌 <br>All world 퍼져나가 <br>나의 바이러스 <br>Make chaos yo <br>like a hurricane <br>Make chaos yo <br>like a hurricane <br>Make chaos yo <br>like a hurricane <br>Make chaos yo <br>like a hurricane <br>점점 더 밀어 <br>넣어 술 없이 <br>내 손으로 끊는 필름 <br>가끔 이런 날이 <br>나에겐 필요해 <br>간만에 취한 듯 <br>생각이 뻗는 대로 내버려 둬 <br>무의식 속에 자아 <br>그러다 보면 <br>결국 뻔한 레퍼토리 <br>많이 봤어 아니 잠깐 <br>나는 역사를 만드는 것엔 <br>관심 하나도 없어 <br>그저 날 잡아 끄는 곳 <br>순간 거기에 관심을 던져 <br>날 데려다 줘 <br>끊어 줬음 해 <br>초심의 탯줄 <br>그렇게 할 배짱 없다면 <br>내 내 선생이 돼줘 <br>악담 일 수 없지 <br>지금 VERSE 똑바로 들어놔 <br>네가 입에 달고 살던 <br>그 새낀 최고가 아냐 <br>다 물어봐 <br>걔도 지금 지가 뭘 하는 지 <br>하나도 없을 거라고 아는 바가 <br>잘 생각 해 봐 그런 놈들이 <br>빼 먹지 않고 남 탓은 많아 <br>더 어지럽게 해 <br>No more silence <br>Make it hot 불처럼 <br>울려 사이렌 <br>All world 퍼져나가 <br>나의 바이러스 <br>Make chaos yo hurricane <br>더 어지럽게 해 <br>No more silence <br>Make it hot 불처럼 <br>울려 사이렌 <br>All world 퍼져나가 <br>나의 바이러스 <br>Make chaos yo <br>like a hurricane <br>Make chaos yo <br>like a hurricane <br>Make chaos yo <br>like a hurricane <br>Make chaos yo <br>like a hurricane <br>Like like a Hurricane <br>]]></content><category term="홍창우" label="홍창우"/><category term="Hurricane (Feat. ARTEe)" label="Hurricane (Feat. ARTEe)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍창우/Reign_On_Me/</id><title>홍창우 - Reign On Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:48:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:48:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%B0%BD%EC%9A%B0/Reign_On_Me/" title="홍창우 - Reign On Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[게임과 바둑에 미쳐 <br>살았던 아이 <br>시간 개념 없이 <br>유일하게 부렸던 사치 <br>그 관심은 음악으로 <br>급했던 걸음마 <br>장르 안 가리고 발매 된 <br>앨범은 벌써 12장 <br>내 하루 시작과 끝 <br>전부가 아마도 <br>이어폰을 달고 살지 <br>지겹지 않아 하나도 <br>아쉬움이 많던 <br>재능을 다 엎었지 기회로 <br>슬럼프에 빠진 너와 다르게 <br>나는 없어 믹테도 <br>When i woke up <br>졸려도 Call up XENO <br>잠꼬대처럼 앨범에 <br>대한 생각을 뱉어 <br>난 하고 싶은 게 많아 <br>밑 그림을 그려줘 <br>그 때 오는 해방감 <br>난 모든 걸 누려 본 채로 <br>그 때 감정을 <br>말해주고 싶어 <br>망설이지 않아도 돼 <br>내 경험을 빌려 <br>스트레스가 아예 <br>없진 않지 나 역시 <br>단지 음악과 함께라면 <br>몇 배는 가볍지 <br>스트레스가 아예 <br>없진 않지 나 역시 <br>단지 음악과 함께라면 <br>몇 배는 가볍지 <br>스트레스가 아예 <br>없진 않지 나 역시 <br>단지 음악과 함께라면 <br>몇 배는 가볍지 <br>그런 생각에 잠기곤 해 <br>내가 나에 대해 <br>많이 모를 때 <br>그 때 마주쳤던 <br>영감들은 과연 <br>지금의 작법이나 <br>가사에 얼마나 참견을 <br>하고 있을지에 <br>대해 말이야 <br>아마도 있겠지 <br>아님 얼마나 <br>비껴 갔을지 <br>분명 한 건 모든 <br>순간들은 나에게 <br>만족을 주고 있고 <br>영감은 아직 사방에 <br>흘러 넘쳐 <br>내게는 삶의 원동력 <br>겪어 본 적 없는 월요병 <br>날씨만 다를 뿐 <br>똑같이 주어지는 하루 <br>나와의 대화이기에 <br>필요가 없는 아부 <br>천천히 걷자 그저 <br>이렇게 꾸준히 <br>그럼 자연스레 <br>알게 돼 내가 누군지 <br>서두르지 않아도 돼 <br>내 판단을 믿어 <br>새내기 같은 기분 <br>처음처럼 불을 지펴 <br>서두르지 않아도 돼 <br>내 판단을 믿어 <br>새내기 같은 기분 <br>처음처럼 불을 지펴 <br>서두르지 않아도 돼 <br>내 판단을 믿어 <br>새내기 같은 기분 <br>처음처럼 불을 지펴 <br>천천히 걷자 <br>그저 이렇게 꾸준히 <br>그럼 자연스레 <br>알게 돼 내가 누군지 <br>서두르지 않아도 돼 <br>내 판단을 믿어 <br>새내기 같은 기분 <br>처음처럼 불을 지펴 <br>그 때 감정을 <br>말해주고 싶어 <br>망설이지 않아도 돼 <br>내 경험을 빌려 <br>스트레스가 아예 <br>없진 않지 나 역시 <br>단지 음악과 함께라면 <br>몇 배는 가볍지 <br>]]></content><category term="홍창우" label="홍창우"/><category term="Reign On Me" label="Reign On Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유애포/홍대_뱃노래/</id><title>유애포 - 홍대 뱃노래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:48:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:48:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EC%95%A0%ED%8F%AC/%ED%99%8D%EB%8C%80_%EB%B1%83%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="유애포 - 홍대 뱃노래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[노 저어가세 노 저어가 <br>나의 꿈 향해 노 저어가 <br>높은 파도에 휩쓸려도 <br>노 저어가야지 <br>어기야 디여차 어기야 디여차 <br>어기야 디여 어기여차 <br>뱃놀이 가잔다 <br>반짝반짝 빛이 나던 <br>나의 눈빛은 사라지고 <br>눈에 넣어도 안 아프던 <br>내 님은 떠나갔네 <br>그래도 가야지 노 저어가야지 <br>저기 고지가 코 앞인데 <br>무감각해진 나의 팔아 조금만 더 <br>해금아 가자 <br>어기야 디여차 어기야 디여차 <br>어기야 디여차 어기야 디여차 <br>아 오늘도 나의 뱃놀이 시작됐네 <br>꿈아 나를 버리지 말아라 <br>너밖에 없다 너밖에 없다 <br>어기야 디여차 어기야 디여차 <br>어기야 디여차 어기야 디여차 <br>아 오늘도 홍대 뱃노래 시작됐네 <br>울려 퍼져라 울려 퍼져라 <br>이 노래가 네게 닿을 때까지 <br>어기야 디여차 어기야 디여차 <br>어기야 디여차 어기야 디여차 <br>내 사랑아 나의 꿈아 <br>내 사랑아 나의 꿈아 <br>노 저어가세 노 저어가 <br>노 저어가세 노 저어가 <br>노 저어가세 노 저어가 <br>노 저어가세 노 저어가 <br>어기야 디여차 어기야 디여차 <br>어기야 디여차 어기야 디여차 <br>어기야 디여차 어기야 디여차 <br>어기야 디여 어기여차 <br>뱃놀이 가잔다 <br>어기야 디여 어기여차 <br>홍대 뱃놀이 가잔다 <br>]]></content><category term="유애포" label="유애포"/><category term="홍대 뱃노래" label="홍대 뱃노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김도환/서로_다른_이별/</id><title>김도환 - 서로 다른 이별 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:48:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:48:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%8F%84%ED%99%98/%EC%84%9C%EB%A1%9C_%EB%8B%A4%EB%A5%B8_%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84/" title="김도환 - 서로 다른 이별 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마지막이었을까 우리 만남이 <br>너라는 모든 모습이 낯설어 <br>나와 이별을 준비하는 <br>너의 모습이 <br>내 가슴을 미어지게 하더라 <br>떠나지 말라며 <br>수천 번을 외쳐봐도 <br>슬픈 눈으로 날 떠나가잖아 <br>행복했던 우리 추억들도 <br>아무 일도 없었던 것처럼 <br>모든 게 다 그리워서 <br>하염없이 눈물만 흘리는데 <br>한번쯤은 하고 싶었던 말 <br>나보다 더 행복 하란 아픈 말 <br>고마웠어 나와 함께 해줘서 <br>떠나지 말라며 <br>수천 번을 외쳐봐도 <br>슬픈 눈으로 날 떠나가잖아 <br>행복했던 우리 추억들도 <br>아무 일도 없었던 것처럼 <br>모든 게 다 그리워서 <br>하염없이 눈물만 흘리는데 <br>한번쯤은 하고 싶었던 말 <br>나보다 더 행복 하란 아픈 말 <br>고마웠어 나와 함께 해줘서 <br>서로 다른 이별 앞에 <br>마주선 우리 <br>모르는 척하며 지내는 게 <br>알면서도 나 <br>다 알면서도 너를 떠나려 해 <br>힘들다는 너의 눈빛에서 <br>내가 해줄 말이 없다는 게 <br>너무나도 미안해서 <br>하염없이 눈물만 흘리는데 <br>한번쯤은 하고 싶었던 말 <br>나보다 더 행복 하란 아픈 말 <br>고마웠어 나와 함께 해줘서 <br>]]></content><category term="김도환" label="김도환"/><category term="서로 다른 이별" label="서로 다른 이별"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노진규/서울역/</id><title>노진규 - 서울역 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:49:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:49:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EC%A7%84%EA%B7%9C/%EC%84%9C%EC%9A%B8%EC%97%AD/" title="노진규 - 서울역 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마지막 떠나는 <br>서울역 밤열차 <br>차창에 말없이 <br>기대앉아 <br>울리는 기적에 <br>하얀 손수건 적시며 <br>떠나가는 여인아 <br>수많은 그 추억에 <br>쏟아지는 눈물 <br>멈추지 못하고 <br>허공만 바라보네 <br>우리 행복했던 그날 <br>예감도 못한 이별에 <br>영화 속의 주인공처럼 <br>내가 울고 섰네 <br>마지막 떠나는 <br>서울역 밤열차 <br>차창에 말없이 <br>기대앉아 <br>울리는 기적에 <br>우린 이렇게 헤어져 <br>떠나가는 여인아 <br>행복한 그 시절은 <br>모두 꿈이었나 <br>붙잡지 못하고 <br>눈물만 글썽이네 <br>우리 행복했던 그날 <br>예감도 못한 이별에 <br>영화 속의 주인공처럼 <br>내가 울고 섰네 <br>]]></content><category term="노진규" label="노진규"/><category term="서울역" label="서울역"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노진규/포항으로_오세요/</id><title>노진규 - 포항으로 오세요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:49:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:49:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EC%A7%84%EA%B7%9C/%ED%8F%AC%ED%95%AD%EC%9C%BC%EB%A1%9C_%EC%98%A4%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94/" title="노진규 - 포항으로 오세요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[포항으로 오세요 <br>구경 한번 오세요 <br>볼거리와 먹거리는 <br>너무 많아 탈이죠 <br>풍성한 바다축제 <br>구경하시고 <br>구룡포 과메기도 <br>즐겨보세요 <br>초록빛 동해바다 <br>수평선 바라보며 <br>연인과 거닐면서 <br>좋은 추억 만드세요 <br>포항으로 오세요 <br>구경 한번 오세요 <br>포항으로 오세요 <br>구경 한번 오세요 <br>대보등대 해맞이는 <br>정말 장관이구요 <br>세계제일 포스코도 <br>직접보시고 <br>죽도시장 싱싱한회 <br>들고가세요 <br>영일만 푸른파도 <br>갈매기 울음소리 <br>누구나 한번 오면 <br>정이 들어 살고 싶은 <br>포항으로 오세요 <br>구경 한번 오세요 <br>풍성한 바다축제 <br>구경하시고 <br>구룡포 과메기도 <br>즐겨보세요 <br>초록빛 동해바다 <br>수평선 바라보며 <br>연인과 거닐면서 <br>좋은 추억 만드세요 <br>포항으로 오세요 <br>구경한번 오세요 <br>]]></content><category term="노진규" label="노진규"/><category term="포항으로 오세요" label="포항으로 오세요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노진규/아내의_기도/</id><title>노진규 - 아내의 기도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:49:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:49:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EC%A7%84%EA%B7%9C/%EC%95%84%EB%82%B4%EC%9D%98_%EA%B8%B0%EB%8F%84/" title="노진규 - 아내의 기도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 힘들어 할 때 <br>너무나 안타까워서 <br>나 몰래 흘린 눈물 강이 <br>되어 넘쳤으리라 <br>하지만 원망 <br>한번 하지 않고 <br>나를 위하여 두 손 모아 <br>기도하는 그 모습 <br>그려만 봐도 <br>커다란 힘이 됩니다 <br>아내의 기도 <br>내가 괴로워할 때 <br>너무나 안타까워서 <br>그 가슴 나보다도 <br>수십만 배 태웠으리라 <br>하지만 후회 <br>한번 하지 않고 <br>나를 위하여 <br>무릎 꿇고 <br>기도하는 그 모습 <br>생각만해도 저절로 <br>힘이 납니다 <br>아내의 기도 <br>]]></content><category term="노진규" label="노진규"/><category term="아내의 기도" label="아내의 기도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/방가레/다시_만난다면_Inst/</id><title>방가레 - 다시 만난다면 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:50:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:50:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%A9%EA%B0%80%EB%A0%88/%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C_%EB%A7%8C%EB%82%9C%EB%8B%A4%EB%A9%B4_Inst/" title="방가레 - 다시 만난다면 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그댄 어디 있는지 <br>뭘 하고 있는지 <br>하루에도 몇 번씩 <br>생각하곤 해 <br>너무 커져버린 내 맘을 <br>가만히 바라보다 <br>또 멍하니 <br>하루가 흘러가 <br>아픈 생각들로 <br>먹먹한 건 혼자만일까 <br>마음 허전함에 답답한 건 <br>나 혼자만일까 <br>이런 조급한 맘 달래는 날 <br>그댄 알고 있는지 <br>매일 그대 곁에 <br>있고 싶은데 <br>우리 다시 만나길 <br>두 눈이 마주치길 <br>그댈 기다리며 <br>길을 빙빙 돌아봐요 <br>우연히 만난다면 <br>두 눈 꼭 감고 <br>그댈 기다리고 <br>기다렸다 말할 거예요 <br>눈길 닿는 어느 곳에 <br>그대 있을까 <br>내린 빗물 따라 <br>걷다 보면 그대가 있을까 <br>이런 바보 같은 <br>생각하는 나를 아는지 <br>이미 그댈 많이 <br>좋아하는데 <br>우리 다시 만나길 <br>두 눈이 마주치길 <br>그댈 기다리며 <br>길을 빙빙 돌아봐요 <br>우연히 만난다면 <br>두 눈 꼭 감고 <br>그댈 기다리고 <br>기다렸다 말할 거예요 <br>나를 생각하고 있는지 <br>아님 관심조차 없는지 <br>물어보고 싶은 말이 많은데 <br>그대에게 <br>그대 다가와 줘요 <br>내 앞에 멈춰줘요 <br>하루하루 내겐 <br>힘겨웠단 말이에요 <br>내 손잡아 준다면 <br>두 눈 꼭 감고 <br>그댈 매일매일 <br>좋아했다 할 거예요 <br>바라보는 눈빛 <br>하나로 날 알아줘요 <br>떨리는 마음 향해 <br>눈을 맞춰주면 <br>이 순간을 기다렸다고 <br>말할 거예요 <br>]]></content><category term="방가레" label="방가레"/><category term="다시 만난다면 (Inst.)" label="다시 만난다면 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/방가레/다시_만난다면_Vocal_원은지/</id><title>방가레 - 다시 만난다면 (Vocal 원은지) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:50:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:50:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%A9%EA%B0%80%EB%A0%88/%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C_%EB%A7%8C%EB%82%9C%EB%8B%A4%EB%A9%B4_Vocal_%EC%9B%90%EC%9D%80%EC%A7%80/" title="방가레 - 다시 만난다면 (Vocal 원은지) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그댄 어디 있는지 <br>뭘 하고 있는지 <br>하루에도 몇 번씩 <br>생각하곤 해 <br>너무 커져버린 내 맘을 <br>가만히 바라보다 <br>또 멍하니 <br>하루가 흘러가 <br>아픈 생각들로 <br>먹먹한 건 혼자만일까 <br>마음 허전함에 답답한 건 <br>나 혼자만일까 <br>이런 조급한 맘 달래는 날 <br>그댄 알고 있는지 <br>매일 그대 곁에 <br>있고 싶은데 <br>우리 다시 만나길 <br>두 눈이 마주치길 <br>그댈 기다리며 <br>길을 빙빙 돌아봐요 <br>우연히 만난다면 <br>두 눈 꼭 감고 <br>그댈 기다리고 <br>기다렸다 말할 거예요 <br>눈길 닿는 어느 곳에 <br>그대 있을까 <br>내린 빗물 따라 <br>걷다 보면 그대가 있을까 <br>이런 바보 같은 <br>생각하는 나를 아는지 <br>이미 그댈 많이 <br>좋아하는데 <br>우리 다시 만나길 <br>두 눈이 마주치길 <br>그댈 기다리며 <br>길을 빙빙 돌아봐요 <br>우연히 만난다면 <br>두 눈 꼭 감고 <br>그댈 기다리고 <br>기다렸다 말할 거예요 <br>나를 생각하고 있는지 <br>아님 관심조차 없는지 <br>물어보고 싶은 말이 많은데 <br>그대에게 <br>그대 다가와 줘요 <br>내 앞에 멈춰줘요 <br>하루하루 내겐 <br>힘겨웠단 말이에요 <br>내 손잡아 준다면 <br>두 눈 꼭 감고 <br>그댈 매일매일 <br>좋아했다 할 거예요 <br>바라보는 눈빛 <br>하나로 날 알아줘요 <br>떨리는 마음 향해 <br>눈을 맞춰주면 <br>이 순간을 기다렸다고 <br>말할 거예요 <br>]]></content><category term="방가레" label="방가레"/><category term="다시 만난다면 (Vocal 원은지)" label="다시 만난다면 (Vocal 원은지)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GUIN/안락의_끝_Feat_Vixy/</id><title>GUIN - 안락의 끝 (Feat. Vixy) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:50:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:50:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GUIN/%EC%95%88%EB%9D%BD%EC%9D%98_%EB%81%9D_Feat_Vixy/" title="GUIN - 안락의 끝 (Feat. Vixy) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날 감싼 패배감이 곧 내게 <br>달아나게 되겠지 그 다음은 <br>끝내러 가 그 분노로 가득 차 <br>꿈틀거리던 밤을 <br>그리고 나가는 거야 <br>방에서 날 받지 못하는 세상으로 <br>그래 난 나를 가둔 거야 <br>여긴 내리쬐는 빛이 너무 가늘어 <br>발을 뻗지 못하면 결국 아무것도 <br>안 바뀌어 난 겪어왔거든 <br>화가 났지 탓할 게 나 뿐 <br>I CAN'T MAKE IT POSSIBLE <br>실패 또 반복을 몇 년간을 하고 <br>나도 이 아픔은 <br>익숙함과는 거리 멀어 <br>절대 아물지 않아 덧이 날 뿐 <br>I CURSED MY LIFE <br>제 인생을 걸지 않아도 <br>되는 이들이 빈 말이나 하고 <br>난 좋다고 거짓말하고 <br>가오 부렸지만 <br>I'M STUCKED IN PERSONAL PROBLEMS <br>노력해봐야 성공 못하면 <br>그게 표시가 나던 <br>물음표를 던지고 있지 <br>난 언제 웃을 수 있는지 <br>나 자신을 믿는 짓은 <br>소년만화에나 있는 일이야 <br>난 살아가고 있는지 <br>살아지고 있는지 <br>아님 사라지고 있는지 <br>이 지옥 같은 안락에 끝이 있기를 <br>OH GOD PLEASE <br>그냥 아무런 일 없이 <br>행복하길 바랬지 <br>난 굴곡 아닌 <br>내리막길 속에 있었으니 <br>고개를 들고 겨우 마주한 벽은 <br>상상이 안가는 기럭지 <br>그리고 돌이켜보니까 <br>다름 아닌 바로 내가 <br>나를 벼랑으로 밀었지 <br>WHEN MY DREAMS AND SKIES ARE HIDIN' <br>MOVE TO TINY LIGHT <br>GOOD VIBE GOOD VIBE GOOD VIBE <br>GOOD VIBE GOOD VIBE GOOD VIBE <br>IF YOU AIN'T STOP TRYIN' TO FLY <br>이 밤도 지나갈 거야 <br>GOOD NIGHT GOOD NIGHT GOOD NIGHT <br>GOOD NIGHT GOOD NIGHT GOOD NIGHT <br>담배연길 물고 욕을 뱉어 <br>낭만적인 단어 대신 <br>내가 패배자 같아 도태된 느낌 <br>땜에 쓴 부정의 시 <br>남을 헐뜯고 나니까 것보다 <br>못한 자신을 발견했지 <br>그런 밤이 계속 됐고 <br>꽤나 오랫동안 날 괴롭혀댔지 <br>내 모든 걸 바쳤는데도 <br>텅 빈 시간만 흘러갔네 <br>날 앞서간 남을 인정 못하니까 <br>난 피해자여야만 해 <br>나도 나쁘진 않았다고 <br>날 몰라본 세상 탓이라고 <br>합리화하고 나면 <br>더 큰 자괴가 기다리고 있어 <br>왜 나만 이래야 해 <br>전혀 공감이 가지 않는 <br>유명인의 책 <br>발버둥 치는 청춘에게 <br>쏟아지는 명언 도전을 <br>말하는 강연들을 저주했네 <br>침은 거울 속 얼굴에 뱉고 <br>다른 이들을 상처 입히던 <br>그 입으로 기도했지 <br>이 지옥 같은 안락에 끝이 있기를 <br>이 지옥 같은 안락의 끝 <br>뛸 수 없어서 그저 누워있다면 <br>바쁘지 못해서 한가하다면 <br>성공을 못해서 편하다면 <br>I swear I'll burn myself <br>and take from them everythin' <br>저 과거형의 문장들에 <br>마침표를 찍게 될 때 <br>WHEN MY DREAMS AND SKIES ARE HIDIN' <br>MOVE TO TINY LIGHT <br>GOOD VIBE GOOD VIBE GOOD VIBE <br>GOOD VIBE GOOD VIBE GOOD VIBE <br>IF YOU AIN'T STOP TRYIN' TO FLY <br>이 밤도 지나갈 거야 <br>GOOD NIGHT GOOD NIGHT GOOD NIGHT <br>GOOD NIGHT GOOD NIGHT GOOD NIGHT <br>날 감싼 패배감이 곧 내게 <br>달아나게 되겠지 그 다음은 <br>끝내러 가 분노로 가득 차 <br>꿈틀거리던 밤을 <br>끝내러 가 숨 쉬듯이 <br>자살을 말하던 나를 <br>끝내러 가 내게 도움 안 되는 <br>감정을 잡던 습관을 <br>날 감싼 패배감이 곧 내게 <br>달아나게 되겠지 그 다음은 <br>끝내러 가 분노로 가득 차 <br>꿈틀거리던 밤을 <br>끝내러 가 숨 쉬듯이 <br>자살을 말하던 나를 <br>끝내러 가 내게 도움 안 되는 <br>감정을 잡던 습관을 <br>WHEN MY DREAMS AND SKIES ARE HIDIN' <br>MOVE TO TINY LIGHT <br>GOOD VIBE GOOD VIBE GOOD VIBE <br>GOOD VIBE GOOD VIBE GOOD VIBE <br>IF YOU AIN'T STOP TRYIN' TO FLY <br>이 밤도 지나갈 거야 <br>GOOD NIGHT GOOD NIGHT GOOD NIGHT <br>GOOD NIGHT GOOD NIGHT GOOD NIGHT <br>날 감싼 패배감이 곧 내게 <br>달아나게 되겠지 그 다음은 <br>끝내러 가 분노로 가득 차 <br>꿈틀거리던 밤을 <br>이건 전처럼 염세에 쩌든 <br>부정의 노래가 아냐 <br>그 반대지 네가 이 가사의 <br>의미를 안다면 말야 <br>GOOD VIBES GOOD VIBES GOOD VIBES <br>GOOD VIBES GOOD VIBES GOOD VIBES <br>GOOD VIBES GOOD VIBES GOOD VIBES <br>GOOD VIBES GOOD VIBES GOOD VIBES <br>]]></content><category term="GUIN" label="GUIN"/><category term="안락의 끝 (Feat. Vixy)" label="안락의 끝 (Feat. Vixy)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Naughty_Boys/숨바꼭질_inst/</id><title>Naughty_Boys - 숨바꼭질 (inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:50:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:50:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Naughty_Boys/%EC%88%A8%EB%B0%94%EA%BC%AD%EC%A7%88_inst/" title="Naughty_Boys - 숨바꼭질 (inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밖에서도 안에서도 <br>내가 맘 편히 쉴 곳은 하나 없고 <br>오늘은 유달리 더 지치는 날인데 <br>목까지 차오르는 <br>욕을 뱉을 곳도 없고 <br>여기라도 시원하게 <br>막 뱉어대야지 <br>유일하게 진짜 <br>내가 되는 이곳에서 <br>목마른 사슴이 <br>시냇물을 찾아 헤매듯이 <br>뭐가 있겠어 <br>과거와 현재는 <br>멈춰있어 다 부서진 <br>통장도 업데이트하면 <br>싸이월드처럼 <br>여기서 저기서 퍼가요 <br>퍼가요 퍼가요 퍼가요 퍼가요 <br>그래 다 가져가 뭐든 뭐든 <br>내 맘이든 몸이든 <br>돈이 될만한 건 뭐든 <br>하루하루 연명하듯 <br>살아가는 내가 <br>세상엔 내 생각보다 <br>더 많은 듯한데 What U Think <br>녹슬은 차 Pride 타고 가도 <br>늘 자랑스런 울 엄마 <br>사소한 것에 소중함이 우러나 <br>그때부터 뭐만 보면 항상 울었나 <br>남자답지 못하다며 <br>내 뺨을 내가 때리고 <br>강해 보여야 한다며 <br>건달바지 빼 입고 <br>진짜 건달 보이면 <br>뒷골목으로 내빼고 <br>조금만 Good Boy였으면 <br>지금 나는 아마도 <br>그저 그런 의미 없고 재미없는 <br>내가 뭘 하고 있었을 라나 그때 그 <br>철없던 시절의 교훈이 오히려 <br>내겐 삶의 나침반이 됐는데 <br>어떡하라고 <br>어차피 이래나 저래나 <br>나는 나인데 <br>이제는 앞뒤 생각하고 <br>살아야 하는 나이네 <br>그런 쓸데없는 말로 <br>꼰대 되는 나인데 <br>변하지 않는 건 <br>넌 여깄고 저긴 나있네 <br>어릴 적에 생각하던 <br>장래희망도 <br>영원할 줄 알았던 <br>할머니 할아버지도 <br>군대를 안 갈 것만 <br>같았던 내 자신도 <br>내가 생각했던 것들은 <br>현실과 하나도 <br>같은 게 없네 하나씩 <br>부서져 가고 있네 조금씩 <br>난 지금 뭐하고 있지 <br>다 보이는 데서 숨바꼭질 <br>어릴 적에 생각하던 <br>장래희망도 <br>영원할 줄 알았던 <br>할머니 할아버지도 <br>군대를 안 갈 것만 <br>같았던 내 자신도 <br>내가 생각했던 것들은 <br>현실과 하나도 <br>같은 게 없네 하나씩 <br>부서져 가고 있네 조금씩 <br>난 지금 뭐하고 있지 <br>다 보이는 데서 숨바꼭질 <br>땅거미 지고 <br>어둠이 찾아와 도시 위 <br>각자의 빛을 내며 <br>어디론가 향하고 있지 <br>살짝 내려간 바지는 여전히 <br>근데 너의 기억은 <br>이젠 잊혀져 가고 있지 <br>뻔한 결말은 재미없어 <br>지금 이순간은 <br>나에게 해방감을 줘 <br>난 보스 그지 같은 일은 너나 해 <br>난 할말을 써 던졌음 던졌지 <br>핑계나 수작 부리지 않어 <br>내 주위엔 보이지 않던데 <br>인스타그램엔 이쁜 애들 <br>왜 이렇게 많아 <br>다 제 눈에 안경 <br>그래 원 없게 먹은 술에 <br>거울 속 내 모습 <br>얼굴은 아주 팅팅 시부럴 <br>콩팥이 안 좋아 라고 중얼거리던 <br>그녀는 시바 존나 이뻤지 <br>하루 종일 그녀 생각에 <br>잠 못 드는데 그녀를 탓해 <br>오늘은 꿈 얘길 <br>빌미로 전화해야지 <br>야 나 기싱꿈 꿨다 시부럴 <br>난 널 꼭 이뤄 <br>유치한 건 난 너무나 싫어 <br>내 마음대로 별을 따다 줄게 <br>떠나 같이 우주로 <br>어릴 적에 생각하던 <br>장래희망도 <br>영원할 줄 알았던 <br>할머니 할아버지도 <br>군대를 안 갈 것만 <br>같았던 내 자신도 <br>내가 생각했던 것들은 <br>현실과 하나도 <br>같은 게 없네 하나씩 <br>부서져 가고 있네 조금씩 <br>난 지금 뭐하고 있지 <br>다 보이는 데서 숨바꼭질 <br>어릴 적에 생각하던 <br>장래희망도 <br>영원할 줄 알았던 <br>할머니 할아버지도 <br>군대를 안 갈 것만 <br>같았던 내 자신도 <br>내가 생각했던 것들은 <br>현실과 하나도 <br>같은 게 없네 하나씩 <br>부서져 가고 있네 조금씩 <br>난 지금 뭐하고 있지 <br>다 보이는 데서 숨바꼭질 <br>어릴 적에 생각하던 <br>장래희망도 <br>영원할 줄 알았던 <br>할머니 할아버지도 <br>군대를 안 갈 것만 <br>같았던 내 자신도 <br>내가 생각했던 것들은 <br>현실과 하나도 <br>같은 게 없네 하나씩 <br>부서져 가고 있네 조금씩 <br>난 지금 뭐하고 있지 <br>다 보이는 데서 숨바꼭질 <br>어릴 적에 생각하던 <br>장래희망도 <br>영원할 줄 알았던 <br>할머니 할아버지도 <br>군대를 안 갈 것만 <br>같았던 내 자신도 <br>내가 생각했던 것들은 <br>현실과 하나도 <br>같은 게 없네 하나씩 <br>부서져 가고 있네 조금씩 <br>난 지금 뭐하고 있지 <br>다 보이는 데서 숨바꼭질 <br>]]></content><category term="Naughty Boys" label="Naughty Boys"/><category term="숨바꼭질 (inst.)" label="숨바꼭질 (inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Naughty_Boys/숨바꼭질/</id><title>Naughty_Boys - 숨바꼭질 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:50:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:50:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Naughty_Boys/%EC%88%A8%EB%B0%94%EA%BC%AD%EC%A7%88/" title="Naughty_Boys - 숨바꼭질 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밖에서도 안에서도 <br>내가 맘 편히 쉴 곳은 하나 없고 <br>오늘은 유달리 더 지치는 날인데 <br>목까지 차오르는 <br>욕을 뱉을 곳도 없고 <br>여기라도 시원하게 <br>막 뱉어대야지 <br>유일하게 진짜 <br>내가 되는 이곳에서 <br>목마른 사슴이 <br>시냇물을 찾아 헤매듯이 <br>뭐가 있겠어 <br>과거와 현재는 <br>멈춰있어 다 부서진 <br>통장도 업데이트하면 <br>싸이월드처럼 <br>여기서 저기서 퍼가요 <br>퍼가요 퍼가요 퍼가요 퍼가요 <br>그래 다 가져가 뭐든 뭐든 <br>내 맘이든 몸이든 <br>돈이 될만한 건 뭐든 <br>하루하루 연명하듯 <br>살아가는 내가 <br>세상엔 내 생각보다 <br>더 많은 듯한데 What U Think <br>녹슬은 차 Pride 타고 가도 <br>늘 자랑스런 울 엄마 <br>사소한 것에 소중함이 우러나 <br>그때부터 뭐만 보면 항상 울었나 <br>남자답지 못하다며 <br>내 뺨을 내가 때리고 <br>강해 보여야 한다며 <br>건달바지 빼 입고 <br>진짜 건달 보이면 <br>뒷골목으로 내빼고 <br>조금만 Good Boy였으면 <br>지금 나는 아마도 <br>그저 그런 의미 없고 재미없는 <br>내가 뭘 하고 있었을 라나 그때 그 <br>철없던 시절의 교훈이 오히려 <br>내겐 삶의 나침반이 됐는데 <br>어떡하라고 <br>어차피 이래나 저래나 <br>나는 나인데 <br>이제는 앞뒤 생각하고 <br>살아야 하는 나이네 <br>그런 쓸데없는 말로 <br>꼰대 되는 나인데 <br>변하지 않는 건 <br>넌 여깄고 저긴 나있네 <br>어릴 적에 생각하던 <br>장래희망도 <br>영원할 줄 알았던 <br>할머니 할아버지도 <br>군대를 안 갈 것만 <br>같았던 내 자신도 <br>내가 생각했던 것들은 <br>현실과 하나도 <br>같은 게 없네 하나씩 <br>부서져 가고 있네 조금씩 <br>난 지금 뭐하고 있지 <br>다 보이는 데서 숨바꼭질 <br>어릴 적에 생각하던 <br>장래희망도 <br>영원할 줄 알았던 <br>할머니 할아버지도 <br>군대를 안 갈 것만 <br>같았던 내 자신도 <br>내가 생각했던 것들은 <br>현실과 하나도 <br>같은 게 없네 하나씩 <br>부서져 가고 있네 조금씩 <br>난 지금 뭐하고 있지 <br>다 보이는 데서 숨바꼭질 <br>땅거미 지고 <br>어둠이 찾아와 도시 위 <br>각자의 빛을 내며 <br>어디론가 향하고 있지 <br>살짝 내려간 바지는 여전히 <br>근데 너의 기억은 <br>이젠 잊혀져 가고 있지 <br>뻔한 결말은 재미없어 <br>지금 이순간은 <br>나에게 해방감을 줘 <br>난 보스 그지 같은 일은 너나 해 <br>난 할말을 써 던졌음 던졌지 <br>핑계나 수작 부리지 않어 <br>내 주위엔 보이지 않던데 <br>인스타그램엔 이쁜 애들 <br>왜 이렇게 많아 <br>다 제 눈에 안경 <br>그래 원 없게 먹은 술에 <br>거울 속 내 모습 <br>얼굴은 아주 팅팅 시부럴 <br>콩팥이 안 좋아 라고 중얼거리던 <br>그녀는 시바 존나 이뻤지 <br>하루 종일 그녀 생각에 <br>잠 못 드는데 그녀를 탓해 <br>오늘은 꿈 얘길 <br>빌미로 전화해야지 <br>야 나 기싱꿈 꿨다 시부럴 <br>난 널 꼭 이뤄 <br>유치한 건 난 너무나 싫어 <br>내 마음대로 별을 따다 줄게 <br>떠나 같이 우주로 <br>어릴 적에 생각하던 <br>장래희망도 <br>영원할 줄 알았던 <br>할머니 할아버지도 <br>군대를 안 갈 것만 <br>같았던 내 자신도 <br>내가 생각했던 것들은 <br>현실과 하나도 <br>같은 게 없네 하나씩 <br>부서져 가고 있네 조금씩 <br>난 지금 뭐하고 있지 <br>다 보이는 데서 숨바꼭질 <br>어릴 적에 생각하던 <br>장래희망도 <br>영원할 줄 알았던 <br>할머니 할아버지도 <br>군대를 안 갈 것만 <br>같았던 내 자신도 <br>내가 생각했던 것들은 <br>현실과 하나도 <br>같은 게 없네 하나씩 <br>부서져 가고 있네 조금씩 <br>난 지금 뭐하고 있지 <br>다 보이는 데서 숨바꼭질 <br>어릴 적에 생각하던 <br>장래희망도 <br>영원할 줄 알았던 <br>할머니 할아버지도 <br>군대를 안 갈 것만 <br>같았던 내 자신도 <br>내가 생각했던 것들은 <br>현실과 하나도 <br>같은 게 없네 하나씩 <br>부서져 가고 있네 조금씩 <br>난 지금 뭐하고 있지 <br>다 보이는 데서 숨바꼭질 <br>어릴 적에 생각하던 <br>장래희망도 <br>영원할 줄 알았던 <br>할머니 할아버지도 <br>군대를 안 갈 것만 <br>같았던 내 자신도 <br>내가 생각했던 것들은 <br>현실과 하나도 <br>같은 게 없네 하나씩 <br>부서져 가고 있네 조금씩 <br>난 지금 뭐하고 있지 <br>다 보이는 데서 숨바꼭질 <br>]]></content><category term="Naughty Boys" label="Naughty Boys"/><category term="숨바꼭질" label="숨바꼭질"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/개미/IMI/</id><title>개미 - I.M.I - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:50:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:50:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%9C%EB%AF%B8/IMI/" title="개미 - I.M.I - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[차디찬 바람에 날려 <br>악몽과 같은 시간이 <br>다 지나가리라 하지만 <br>끝이 없어 <br>원한 건 다 할 수 있어 <br>거짓을 가르쳐왔어 <br>아무도 믿을 수 없게 됐어 <br>내던져버려 <br>그들이 말하는 <br>가치는 믿을 수 없어 <br>나는 나일 뿐이야 <br>뿌리쳐버려 <br>그들이 원하는 <br>모습이 되려 하지마 <br>너는 너일 뿐이야 <br>사리사욕에 가득 찬 <br>TV속 어른 분들의 <br>시나리오만 따라 <br>놀아나는가 <br>내던져버려 <br>그들이 말하는 <br>가치는 믿을 수 없어 <br>나는 나일 뿐이야 <br>뿌리쳐버려 <br>그들이 원하는 <br>모습이 되려 하지마 <br>너는 너일 뿐이야 <br>내던져버려 <br>그들이 말하는 <br>가치는 믿을 수 없어 <br>나는 나일 뿐이야 <br>뿌리쳐버려 <br>그들이 원하는 <br>모습이 되려 하지마 <br>너는 너일 뿐이야 <br>내던져버려 <br>그들이 말하는 <br>가치는 믿을 수 없어 <br>나는 나일 뿐이야 <br>뿌리쳐버려 <br>그들이 원하는 <br>모습이 되려 하지마 <br>너는 너일 뿐이야 <br>]]></content><category term="개미" label="개미"/><category term="I.M.I" label="I.M.I"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/개미/The_Darkest_One/</id><title>개미 - The Darkest One - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:50:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:50:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%9C%EB%AF%B8/The_Darkest_One/" title="개미 - The Darkest One - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What's all the reason <br>behind this <br>You got to tell me <br>Somebody tell me <br>So much innocent <br>souls drowned away <br>front of unseen greed <br>Does your honor matter <br>Front of 295 &amp; 9 <br>We may need <br>somebody to blame <br>That is why we had <br>all gone mad <br>I scream for <br>The life has gone cold <br>I feel the lack <br>Being left alone <br>The heart of <br>The life unseen <br>I will be your <br>The Darkest One <br>The echoes are surrounding <br>around my brain <br>Telling something <br>I can't fully understand <br>The people are so obsessed <br>with the success <br>While they do not have <br>the eyes to see their selves <br>So does it matter <br>They never cared once <br>about what should be done <br>The selfishness overflows <br>They should get <br>what they deserve <br>I scream for <br>The life has gone cold <br>I feel the lack <br>Being left alone <br>The heart of <br>The life unseen <br>I will be your <br>The Darkest One <br>I scream for <br>The life has gone cold <br>I feel the lack <br>Being left alone <br>The heart of <br>The life unseen <br>I will be your <br>The Darkest One <br>We must live through <br>this painful life <br>We must not forget <br>what's been done <br>We must live through <br>this painful life <br>We must not forget <br>what's been done <br>]]></content><category term="개미" label="개미"/><category term="The Darkest One" label="The Darkest One"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리노_Lino/누군갈_사랑하고_있다면_Inst/</id><title>리노_Lino - 누군갈 사랑하고 있다면 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:51:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:51:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%85%B8_Lino/%EB%88%84%EA%B5%B0%EA%B0%88_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%98%EA%B3%A0_%EC%9E%88%EB%8B%A4%EB%A9%B4_Inst/" title="리노_Lino - 누군갈 사랑하고 있다면 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[누군갈 좋아하는 마음이 <br>이렇게 힘이 드는 건가요 <br>작은 순간 하나하나에 <br>내 모습 초라해져 가네요 <br>혹시라도 한 번쯤 <br>내게 눈길이라도 닿을 땐 <br>세상 무엇보다도 <br>더한 행복함을 느끼죠 <br>사랑이란 게 누굴 좋아한단 게 <br>참 어렵고 어려운 일이네요 <br>어떻게 해야 내가 그대 마음에 <br>드는 사람이 될 수 있을까요 <br>누군갈 사랑하고 있다면 <br>너무 아파하진 마요 <br>그건 슬픈 일이 아니니 <br>그댄 눈물 흘리지 말고 <br>더는 외로워하지 마요 <br>가끔씩은 마음이 <br>불안해지기도 하다가 <br>보고 싶은 마음에 설레죠 <br>사랑이란 게 혼자 할 수 있다면 <br>이렇게 힘이 들진 않았을 테죠 <br>어떻게 해야 내가 그대 마음을 <br>움직일 수가 있을까요 <br>누군갈 사랑하고 있다면 <br>너무 아파하진 마요 <br>그건 슬픈 일이 아니니 <br>그댄 눈물 흘리지 말고 <br>더는 외로워하지 마요 <br>사랑 앞에 누구든 <br>뒤로 숨지 말아요 <br>사랑은 꼭 이뤄지지 않아도 <br>아름다우니까 <br>먼 훗날 이 시절이 <br>가슴에 기억되도록 <br>그저 사랑해 <br>누군갈 사랑하고 있다면 <br>너무 아파하진 마요 <br>그건 슬픈 일이 아니니 <br>그댄 눈물 흘리지 말고 <br>더는 외로워하지 마요 <br>]]></content><category term="리노 (Lino)" label="리노 (Lino)"/><category term="누군갈 사랑하고 있다면 (Inst.)" label="누군갈 사랑하고 있다면 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리노_Lino/누군갈_사랑하고_있다면/</id><title>리노_Lino - 누군갈 사랑하고 있다면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:51:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:51:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%85%B8_Lino/%EB%88%84%EA%B5%B0%EA%B0%88_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%98%EA%B3%A0_%EC%9E%88%EB%8B%A4%EB%A9%B4/" title="리노_Lino - 누군갈 사랑하고 있다면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[누군갈 좋아하는 마음이 <br>이렇게 힘이 드는 건가요 <br>작은 순간 하나하나에 <br>내 모습 초라해져 가네요 <br>혹시라도 한 번쯤 <br>내게 눈길이라도 닿을 땐 <br>세상 무엇보다도 <br>더한 행복함을 느끼죠 <br>사랑이란 게 누굴 좋아한단 게 <br>참 어렵고 어려운 일이네요 <br>어떻게 해야 내가 그대 마음에 <br>드는 사람이 될 수 있을까요 <br>누군갈 사랑하고 있다면 <br>너무 아파하진 마요 <br>그건 슬픈 일이 아니니 <br>그댄 눈물 흘리지 말고 <br>더는 외로워하지 마요 <br>가끔씩은 마음이 <br>불안해지기도 하다가 <br>보고 싶은 마음에 설레죠 <br>사랑이란 게 혼자 할 수 있다면 <br>이렇게 힘이 들진 않았을 테죠 <br>어떻게 해야 내가 그대 마음을 <br>움직일 수가 있을까요 <br>누군갈 사랑하고 있다면 <br>너무 아파하진 마요 <br>그건 슬픈 일이 아니니 <br>그댄 눈물 흘리지 말고 <br>더는 외로워하지 마요 <br>사랑 앞에 누구든 <br>뒤로 숨지 말아요 <br>사랑은 꼭 이뤄지지 않아도 <br>아름다우니까 <br>먼 훗날 이 시절이 <br>가슴에 기억되도록 <br>그저 사랑해 <br>누군갈 사랑하고 있다면 <br>너무 아파하진 마요 <br>그건 슬픈 일이 아니니 <br>그댄 눈물 흘리지 말고 <br>더는 외로워하지 마요 <br>]]></content><category term="리노 (Lino)" label="리노 (Lino)"/><category term="누군갈 사랑하고 있다면" label="누군갈 사랑하고 있다면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이나연/선톡_Inst/</id><title>이나연 - 선톡 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:51:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:51:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%82%98%EC%97%B0/%EC%84%A0%ED%86%A1_Inst/" title="이나연 - 선톡 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[문 틈새 스친 옷깃 달콤한 향기 <br>코 끝에 스쳐간 짧은 체리 향기 <br>나도 모르게 마냥 따라간 시선 <br>두 눈에 들어 온 아이 같은 미소 <br>눈치도 없이 계속 늘어간 관심 <br>하루에 열두 번 그대 생각이 나 <br>문잘 보낼까 좀 더 기다려볼까 <br>어제도 오늘도 내일도 니 생각만 <br>수소문해서 알아낸 연락처 <br>들킬까봐 마음 졸이면서 <br>연락해볼까 기다려볼까 <br>그때 꿈같이 울린 <br>카톡 왔어요 <br>문자 왔어요 찾아온 연락 <br>간절한 내 마음 알아 준 걸까요 <br>답장 보내요 애교스런 문자 <br>내가 쓴 글자에 오타는 없었는지 <br>답장 왔어요 섬세한 말투 <br>두 볼을 꼬집죠 꿈이 아닌가요 <br>답장 보내요 조심스럽게 <br>혹시 망설이면 끊길지도 몰라 <br>오늘 만나요 홍대 앞 카페 <br>정말로 좋지만 티는 안 낼래요 <br>내일도 만나 삼청동 거리 <br>내일은 차가운 내 손 잡아줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="이나연" label="이나연"/><category term="선톡 (Inst.)" label="선톡 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이나연/선톡/</id><title>이나연 - 선톡 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:51:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:51:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%82%98%EC%97%B0/%EC%84%A0%ED%86%A1/" title="이나연 - 선톡 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[문 틈새 스친 옷깃 달콤한 향기 <br>코 끝에 스쳐간 짧은 체리 향기 <br>나도 모르게 마냥 따라간 시선 <br>두 눈에 들어 온 아이 같은 미소 <br>눈치도 없이 계속 늘어간 관심 <br>하루에 열두 번 그대 생각이 나 <br>문잘 보낼까 좀 더 기다려볼까 <br>어제도 오늘도 내일도 니 생각만 <br>수소문해서 알아낸 연락처 <br>들킬까봐 마음 졸이면서 <br>연락해볼까 기다려볼까 <br>그때 꿈같이 울린 <br>카톡 왔어요 <br>문자 왔어요 찾아온 연락 <br>간절한 내 마음 알아 준 걸까요 <br>답장 보내요 애교스런 문자 <br>내가 쓴 글자에 오타는 없었는지 <br>답장 왔어요 섬세한 말투 <br>두 볼을 꼬집죠 꿈이 아닌가요 <br>답장 보내요 조심스럽게 <br>혹시 망설이면 끊길지도 몰라 <br>오늘 만나요 홍대 앞 카페 <br>정말로 좋지만 티는 안 낼래요 <br>내일도 만나 삼청동 거리 <br>내일은 차가운 내 손 잡아줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="이나연" label="이나연"/><category term="선톡" label="선톡"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엄재/욕심때문이야/</id><title>엄재 - 욕심때문이야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:51:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:51:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%84%EC%9E%AC/%EC%9A%95%EC%8B%AC%EB%95%8C%EB%AC%B8%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC/" title="엄재 - 욕심때문이야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[생각해봤어 사람은 언제부터 <br>불행한 감정을 느끼는지 말야 <br>그것은 말야 사람의 욕심이 <br>생기고 나서 부터인것 같아 <br>별이 되고픈 달 <br>밤하늘 달빛이 <br>얼마나 이쁜지 모르고 <br>슬픔에 눈물이 <br>아픔에 비되어 <br>그대가 부러워 내렸다 <br>욕심 때문이야 <br>욕심 때문에 <br>그날에 우리가 다투던 이유도 <br>욕심 때문이야 <br>욕심 때문에 <br>그 때의 아픔을 지우려 <br>애썼던 이유도 <br>생각해봤어 사람은 언제부터 <br>이별의 아픔을 느끼는지 말야 <br>그것은 말야 사랑에 욕심이 <br>생기고 나서 부터인것 같아 <br>메마른 땅위에 <br>예쁜꽃 피어도 <br>행복이 오는줄 모르고 <br>사랑에 추억이 <br>아픔에 비되어 <br>그때가 그리워 내렸다 <br>욕심 때문이야 <br>욕심 때문에 <br>그날에 우리가 다투던 이유도 <br>욕심 때문이야 <br>욕심 때문에 <br>그 때의 아픔을 지우려 <br>애썼던 이유도 <br>욕심 때문이야 <br>욕심 때문에 <br>그날에 우리가 다투던 이유도 <br>욕심 때문이야 <br>욕심 때문에 <br>그 때의 아픔을 지우려 <br>애썼던 이유도 <br>욕심 때문이야 <br>욕심 때문에 <br>그날에 우리가 다투던 이유도 <br>욕심 때문이야 <br>욕심 때문에 <br>그 때의 아픔을 지우려 <br>애썼던 이유도 <br>]]></content><category term="엄재" label="엄재"/><category term="욕심때문이야" label="욕심때문이야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송란/송이꽃_MR/</id><title>송란 - 송이꽃 (MR) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:51:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:51:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EB%9E%80/%EC%86%A1%EC%9D%B4%EA%BD%83_MR/" title="송란 - 송이꽃 (MR) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 나는 꽃이야 송이꽃이야 <br>내 향기가 약이 되는 꽃 <br>산바람도 들바람도 <br>내 향기를 원하고 있어 <br>나도 나도 여자야 천상여자야 <br>내 입술이 빨개지는 날 <br>그대 맘을 다 비우고 <br>내 향기를 채워 보세요 <br>내 순정에 꽃향기 꽃 <br>다 모아 모아 모아서 <br>아롱 아롱 아롱 취하게 <br>내사랑 다 줄 수 있어 <br>송이 꽃은 기다렸어요 <br>그대 같은 멋진 남자를 <br>긴 세월로 아껴둔 사랑 <br>둥기당기 다 주고 싶어 <br>나는 나는 꽃이야 송이꽃이야 <br>내 향기가 약이 되는 꽃 <br>산바람도 들바람도 <br>내 향기를 원하고 있어 <br>나도 나도 여자야 천상여자야 <br>내 입술이 빨개지는 날 <br>그대 맘을 다 비우고 <br>내 향기를 채워 보세요 <br>이 세상에 있는 행복 <br>다 모아 모아 모아서 <br>딸랑 딸랑 딸랑 애교로 <br>그 마음 녹여드릴게 <br>송이꽃은 기도합니다 <br>내 향기가 약이 되어서 <br>나 그대랑 건강하면서 <br>둥기 당기 사랑하자고 <br>이 세상에 있는 행복 <br>다 모아 모아 모아서 <br>딸랑 딸랑 딸랑 애교로 <br>그 마음 녹여드릴게 <br>송이꽃은 기도합니다 <br>내 향기가 약이 되어서 <br>나 그대랑 건강하면서 <br>둥기 당기 사랑하자고 <br>둥기 당기 사랑하자고 <br>]]></content><category term="송란" label="송란"/><category term="송이꽃 (MR)" label="송이꽃 (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송란/송이꽃/</id><title>송란 - 송이꽃 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:52:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:52:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EB%9E%80/%EC%86%A1%EC%9D%B4%EA%BD%83/" title="송란 - 송이꽃 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 나는 꽃이야 송이꽃이야 <br>내 향기가 약이 되는 꽃 <br>산바람도 들바람도 <br>내 향기를 원하고 있어 <br>나도 나도 여자야 천상여자야 <br>내 입술이 빨개지는 날 <br>그대 맘을 다 비우고 <br>내 향기를 채워 보세요 <br>내 순정에 꽃향기 꽃 <br>다 모아 모아 모아서 <br>아롱 아롱 아롱 취하게 <br>내사랑 다 줄 수 있어 <br>송이 꽃은 기다렸어요 <br>그대 같은 멋진 남자를 <br>긴 세월로 아껴둔 사랑 <br>둥기당기 다 주고 싶어 <br>나는 나는 꽃이야 송이꽃이야 <br>내 향기가 약이 되는 꽃 <br>산바람도 들바람도 <br>내 향기를 원하고 있어 <br>나도 나도 여자야 천상여자야 <br>내 입술이 빨개지는 날 <br>그대 맘을 다 비우고 <br>내 향기를 채워 보세요 <br>이 세상에 있는 행복 <br>다 모아 모아 모아서 <br>딸랑 딸랑 딸랑 애교로 <br>그 마음 녹여드릴게 <br>송이꽃은 기도합니다 <br>내 향기가 약이 되어서 <br>나 그대랑 건강하면서 <br>둥기 당기 사랑하자고 <br>이 세상에 있는 행복 <br>다 모아 모아 모아서 <br>딸랑 딸랑 딸랑 애교로 <br>그 마음 녹여드릴게 <br>송이꽃은 기도합니다 <br>내 향기가 약이 되어서 <br>나 그대랑 건강하면서 <br>둥기 당기 사랑하자고 <br>둥기 당기 사랑하자고 <br>]]></content><category term="송란" label="송란"/><category term="송이꽃" label="송이꽃"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이아랑/RE랑_Inst/</id><title>이아랑 - R.E.랑 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:52:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:52:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%84%EB%9E%91/RE%EB%9E%91_Inst/" title="이아랑 - R.E.랑 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑은 했었는지 <br>내 님은 떠나가고 <br>홀로 남은 나는 <br>눈물만 주르르르륵 <br>기다리다 지쳐 <br>내 님이 그리워 <br>다시 내 눈은 <br>주르르르륵 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아라리요 <br>아리랑 고개를 넘어간다 <br>나를 버리고 가시는 님은 <br>십리도 못 가서 발병난다 <br>사랑은 했었는지 <br>내 님은 떠나가고 <br>홀로 남은 나는 <br>눈물만 주르르르륵 <br>기다리다 지쳐 <br>내 님이 그리워 <br>다시 내 눈은 <br>주르르르륵 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아라리요 <br>아리랑 고개를 넘어간다 <br>나를 버리고 가시는 님은 <br>십리도 못 가서 발병난다 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아라리요 <br>아리랑 고개를 넘어간다 <br>나를 버리고 가시는 님은 <br>십리도 못 가서 발병난다 <br>]]></content><category term="이아랑" label="이아랑"/><category term="R.E.랑 (Inst.)" label="R.E.랑 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이아랑/RE랑/</id><title>이아랑 - R.E.랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:52:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:52:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%84%EB%9E%91/RE%EB%9E%91/" title="이아랑 - R.E.랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑은 했었는지 <br>내 님은 떠나가고 <br>홀로 남은 나는 <br>눈물만 주르르르륵 <br>기다리다 지쳐 <br>내 님이 그리워 <br>다시 내 눈은 <br>주르르르륵 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아라리요 <br>아리랑 고개를 넘어간다 <br>나를 버리고 가시는 님은 <br>십리도 못 가서 발병난다 <br>사랑은 했었는지 <br>내 님은 떠나가고 <br>홀로 남은 나는 <br>눈물만 주르르르륵 <br>기다리다 지쳐 <br>내 님이 그리워 <br>다시 내 눈은 <br>주르르르륵 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아라리요 <br>아리랑 고개를 넘어간다 <br>나를 버리고 가시는 님은 <br>십리도 못 가서 발병난다 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아라리요 <br>아리랑 고개를 넘어간다 <br>나를 버리고 가시는 님은 <br>십리도 못 가서 발병난다 <br>]]></content><category term="이아랑" label="이아랑"/><category term="R.E.랑" label="R.E.랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nashville_Cast/A_Life_Thats_Good_Feat_Charles_Esten__Lennon__Maisy/</id><title>Nashville_Cast - A Life That`s Good (Feat. Charles Esten &amp; Lennon &amp; Maisy) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:52:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:52:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nashville_Cast/A_Life_Thats_Good_Feat_Charles_Esten__Lennon__Maisy/" title="Nashville_Cast - A Life That`s Good (Feat. Charles Esten &amp; Lennon &amp; Maisy) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sittin' here tonight <br>By the fire light <br>It reminds me I already have more than I should <br>I don't need fame, no one to know my name <br>At the end of the day <br>Lord I pray, I have a life that's good <br><br>Two arms around me, heaven to ground me <br>And a family that always calls me home <br>Four wheels to get there, enough love to share <br>And a sweet sweet sweet song <br>At the end of the day <br>Lord I pray <br>I have a life that's good <br><br>Sometimes I'm hard on me <br>When dreams don't come easy <br>I wanna look back and say <br>I did all that I could <br>Yeah at the end of the day, Lord I pray <br>I have a life that's good <br><br>Two arms around me, heaven to ground me <br>And a family that always calls me home <br>Four wheels to get there, enough love to share <br>And a sweet sweet sweet song <br><br>At the end of the day, Lord I pray <br>I have a life that's good <br>At the end of the day, Lord I pray <br>I have a life that's good]]></content><category term="Nashville Cast" label="Nashville Cast"/><category term="A Life That`s Good (Feat. Charles Esten &amp; Lennon &amp; Maisy)" label="A Life That`s Good (Feat. Charles Esten &amp; Lennon &amp; Maisy)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루브/그대라면_Inst/</id><title>루브 - 그대라면 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:53:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:53:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%EB%B8%8C/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%9D%BC%EB%A9%B4_Inst/" title="루브 - 그대라면 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나 둘 셋 넷 <br>어디쯤일까 혼자가 익숙해져 <br>하루 또 하루 일년 <br>언제부턴가 습관처럼 <br>닫혀진 내 맘 속 빈자리 <br>망가진 추억 속 <br>시린 단어로 <br>남겨진 내 이야기 <br>남아있던 온기조차 <br>모조리 빼앗아 가듯 <br>빠져나가던 숨 <br>살며시 감싸며 다가와 <br>차갑게 쌓인 눈 위에 꽃잎이 <br>어디에서 왔는지 <br>그 고요함이 날 <br>돌돌돌 사뿐히 내려 앉으면 <br>어두운 물가 위로 <br>흐르는 따스함 <br>어디론가 날 데려가 <br>다시 하나 둘 셋 <br>어디쯤 일까 또 다시 나 <br>여기서 멍하니 서 있어 <br>마지막 사랑인 듯 <br>속삭임이 반복될 까 두려워 <br>숨 쉬는 법을 잊은 <br>바보가 되는 시간 올까봐 <br>차갑게 쌓인 눈 위에 <br>꽃잎이 어디에서 왔는지 <br>그 고요함이 날 <br>돌돌돌 사뿐히 내려 앉으면 <br>어두운 물가 위로 흐르는 <br>온기에 매달려 어디론가 <br>어디쯤 인가 모를 <br>나 여기 서있어 <br>차갑게 쌓인 하얀 눈 위에 <br>다가온 그대 나 <br>어디에서 왔는지 <br>그 고요함이 날 살며시 <br>다가와 감싸 안으면 <br>어느새 내 맘속 가득히 <br>차오르는 그대의 따스한 온기 <br>]]></content><category term="루브" label="루브"/><category term="그대라면 (Inst.)" label="그대라면 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루브/그대라면/</id><title>루브 - 그대라면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:53:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:53:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%EB%B8%8C/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%9D%BC%EB%A9%B4/" title="루브 - 그대라면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나 둘 셋 넷 <br>어디쯤일까 혼자가 익숙해져 <br>하루 또 하루 일년 <br>언제부턴가 습관처럼 <br>닫혀진 내 맘 속 빈자리 <br>망가진 추억 속 <br>시린 단어로 <br>남겨진 내 이야기 <br>남아있던 온기조차 <br>모조리 빼앗아 가듯 <br>빠져나가던 숨 <br>살며시 감싸며 다가와 <br>차갑게 쌓인 눈 위에 꽃잎이 <br>어디에서 왔는지 <br>그 고요함이 날 <br>돌돌돌 사뿐히 내려 앉으면 <br>어두운 물가 위로 <br>흐르는 따스함 <br>어디론가 날 데려가 <br>다시 하나 둘 셋 <br>어디쯤 일까 또 다시 나 <br>여기서 멍하니 서 있어 <br>마지막 사랑인 듯 <br>속삭임이 반복될 까 두려워 <br>숨 쉬는 법을 잊은 <br>바보가 되는 시간 올까봐 <br>차갑게 쌓인 눈 위에 <br>꽃잎이 어디에서 왔는지 <br>그 고요함이 날 <br>돌돌돌 사뿐히 내려 앉으면 <br>어두운 물가 위로 흐르는 <br>온기에 매달려 어디론가 <br>어디쯤 인가 모를 <br>나 여기 서있어 <br>차갑게 쌓인 하얀 눈 위에 <br>다가온 그대 나 <br>어디에서 왔는지 <br>그 고요함이 날 살며시 <br>다가와 감싸 안으면 <br>어느새 내 맘속 가득히 <br>차오르는 그대의 따스한 온기 <br>]]></content><category term="루브" label="루브"/><category term="그대라면" label="그대라면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/못잊을_사랑/</id><title>왕소연 - 못잊을 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:53:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:53:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EB%AA%BB%EC%9E%8A%EC%9D%84_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="왕소연 - 못잊을 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 나를 잊었나 벌써 잊었나 아직도 사랑은 <br>가슴에 남아있는데 잊으려 지우려 아무리 <br>애를 써 봐도 자꾸만 커 가는 그리움 <br>이토록 못 잊을사람 왜 내가 보냈나 <br>떠나지마 가지마 애원 할걸 붙잡지도 못하고 <br>떠나지마 가지마 매달릴 걸 후회하는 바보 <br>돌아와요 웃으며 와줘요 내게는 너하나 뿐이야 <br><br>2. 이토록 못 잊을 사람 왜 내가 보냈나 <br>떠나지마 가지마 애원 할 걸 붙잡지도 못하고 <br>떠나지마 가지마 매달릴 걸 후회 하는 바보 <br>돌아와요 웃으며 와 줘요 내게는 너 하나 뿐이야]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="못잊을 사랑" label="못잊을 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/첫사랑/</id><title>왕소연 - 첫사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:53:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:53:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EC%B2%AB%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="왕소연 - 첫사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 그대를 처음 본 순간 내 가슴 너무 떨렸어요 <br>그때 이미 예감했죠 사랑에 빠질 것을 <br>그대의 몸짓 그대의 미소 다정스런 그대 목소리 <br>나 어떡해요 숨이 멎을 것 같아 그대에게 빠져버렸어요 <br>하루 온 종일 그대 생각 뿐이죠 내일 역시도 그리 보낼 거예요 <br>손 내밀어 잡아주세요 이런 내 사랑 받아 주세요 <br><br>2. 그대의 몸짓 그대의 미소 다정스런 그대 목소리 <br>나 어떡해요 숨이 멎을 것 같아 그대에게 빠져버렸어요 <br>하루 온종일 그대 생각뿐이죠 내일 역시도 그리 보낼 거예요 <br>손 내밀어 잡아주세요 이런 내 사랑 받아 주세요 <br>이런 내 사랑 받아 주세요]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="첫사랑" label="첫사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/가지마/</id><title>왕소연 - 가지마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:53:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:53:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EA%B0%80%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88/" title="왕소연 - 가지마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 꽃바람 타고 떠나 간데요 나를 두고 떠나 간데요 <br>우리 인연은 여기 까지가 끝이라 하네요 <br>울지도 마요 잡지도 마요 마음 편히 가게 해줘요 <br>부탁 하네요 애원 못하게 미련도 갖지 못하게 <br>아무말 없이 뒷모습 보며 보내야만 하는 내가 너무 싫지만 <br>어쩔수 없는 내가 미워요 내가 잘못 했으니까요 <br>사랑 했지만 너무도 소홀 했던나 그래서 나를 떠나는 이유를 알기에 <br>가지마 날 떠나가지 말라고 애원도 못 한답니다. <br><br>2. 울지도 마요 잡지도 마요 마음 편히 가게 해줘요 <br>부탁 하네요 애원 못하게 미련도 갖지 못하게 <br>아무말 없이 뒷모습 보며 보내야만 하는 내가 너무 싫지만 <br>어쩔수 없는 내가 미워요 내가 잘못 했으니까요 <br>사랑 했지만 너무도 소홀 했던나 그래서 나를 떠나는 이유를 알기에 <br>가지마 날 떠나가지 말라고 애원도 못 한답니다.]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="가지마" label="가지마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/초대/</id><title>왕소연 - 초대 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:53:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:53:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EC%B4%88%EB%8C%80/" title="왕소연 - 초대 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 언제나 머물고 싶은 이 마음 그대 아나요 <br>눈부신 사랑 앞에 소중한 당신 당신을 초대합니다 <br>애타는 마음으로 그리워질 때 간절한 소망 하나로 <br>가득찬 사랑의 맹세를 하고 당신의 손을 잡고 <br>영원히 머물던 자리 세월의 그 빈자리로 <br>남겨진 추억의 문을 열고 당신을 초대합니다 <br><br>2. 애타는 마음으로 그리워질 때 간절한 소망 하나로 <br>가득찬 사랑의 맹세를 하고 당신의 손을 잡고 <br>영원히 머물던 자리 세월의 그 빈자리로 <br>남겨진 추억의 문을 열고 당신을 초대합니다 <br>당신을 초대합니다]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="초대" label="초대"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/만약에/</id><title>왕소연 - 만약에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:53:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:53:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EB%A7%8C%EC%95%BD%EC%97%90/" title="왕소연 - 만약에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 만약에 당신이 그 누구와 사랑에 빠지면 <br>그 사람을 위해서 무얼 할 수 있나 <br>텅 빈 세상 살아가는 이유가 만약에 너라면 어떡하겠니 <br>사는 동안 단 한 번의 사랑이 만약에 너라면 허락하겠니 <br>얼마나 더 많이 외로워해야 널 끌어안고서 울어볼까 <br>이제는 더 이상 지칠 몸조차 비워둘 마음조차 없는데 <br>또 다른 이유로 널 못 본다면 나 살아가는 의미도 없지 <br>만약에 널 위해 나 죽을 수 있다면 날 받아주겠니 <br><br>2. 텅 빈 세상 살아가는 이유가 만약에 너라면 어떡하겠니 <br>사는 동안 단 한 번의 사랑이 만약에 너라면 허락하겠니 <br>얼마나 더 많이 외로워해야 널 끌어안고서 울어볼까 <br>이제는 더 이상 지칠 몸조차 비워둘 마음조차 없는데 <br>또 다른 이유로 널 못 본다면 나 살아가는 의미도 없지 <br>만약에 널 위해 나 죽을 수 있다면 날 받아주겠니]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="만약에" label="만약에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/잠자는_공주/</id><title>왕소연 - 잠자는 공주 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:53:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:53:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EC%9E%A0%EC%9E%90%EB%8A%94_%EA%B3%B5%EC%A3%BC/" title="왕소연 - 잠자는 공주 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 세상이 미워졌나요 누군가 잊어야만 하나 <br>날마다 쓰러지고 또 다시 일어서지만 달라진건 없는가요 <br>세상길 걷다가 보면 삥 돌아 가는 길도 있어 <br>하루를 울었으면 하루는 웃어야 해요 그래야만 견딜 수 있어 <br>앵두 빛 그 고운 두 볼에 살며시 키스를 해주면 <br>그대는 잠에서 깨어나 나에게 하얀 미소 지을까 <br>그대여 어서 일어나 차가운 가슴을 녹여요 <br>또다시 시작되는 아침을 걸어봐요 그대 곁에 나 있을게 <br><br>2. 앵두 빛 그 고운 두 볼에 살며시 키스를 해주면 <br>그대는 잠에서 깨어나 나에게 하얀 미소 지을까 <br>그대여 어서 일어나 차가운 가슴을 녹여요 <br>또다시 시작되는 아침을 걸어봐요 그대 곁에 나 있을게 <br>또다시 시작되는 아침을 걸어봐요]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="잠자는 공주" label="잠자는 공주"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/벤취/</id><title>왕소연 - 벤취 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:53:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:53:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EB%B2%A4%EC%B7%A8/" title="왕소연 - 벤취 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 내 무릎 에 털석 앉아봐 <br>언제나 너의 벤치로 살 거야 <br>아무 때 라도 허전 하면 <br>내 가슴 에다 기대봐 <br>가다가 길 가다가 <br>피곤해 지면 내게 와 <br>너만이 나의 주인이 잖아 너만 쉬어 가도록 <br>너 올때 까지 기다릴께 비를 맞고 와도 돼 <br>술 취해서 와도 돼 나는야 너의 벤치야 <br><br>2. 내 무릎 에 털석 앉아봐 언제나 너의 벤치로 살 거야 <br>아무 때 라도 허전 하면 내 가슴 에다 기대봐 <br>가다가 길 가 다가 피곤해 지면 내게 와 <br>너만이 나의 주인이 잖아 너만 쉬어 가도록 <br>너올때 까지 기다릴께 아침 일찍 와도 돼 <br>저녁 늦게 와도 돼 나는야 너의 벤치야 <br>비를 맞고 와도 돼 술 취해서 와도 돼 나는야 너의 벤치야]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="벤취" label="벤취"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/거짓말/</id><title>왕소연 - 거짓말 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:53:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:53:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EA%B1%B0%EC%A7%93%EB%A7%90/" title="왕소연 - 거짓말 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 돌아온다던 그 말도 거짓말 <br>세상의 모든 거짓말 다 해놓고 <br>행여 나를 찾아와 있을 <br>너의 그 마음도 다칠까 <br>너의 자리를 난 또 비워둔다 <br>이젠 더 이상 속아선 안되지 <br>이젠 더 이상 믿어선 안되지 <br>하지만 그게 말처럼 쉽지 않아 <br>다시 한번만 더 나 너를 <br>다시 한번만 더 너에게 나를 <br>사랑할 기횔 주어본다 <br>어떤 사랑으로 나의 용서에 답하련지 <br>또 잠시 날 사랑하다 떠날 건지 <br>마치 처음 날 사랑하듯 <br>가슴 뜨겁게 와 있지만 <br>난 왠지 그 사랑이 두려워 <br>오직 나만을 위한 그 약속과 <br>내 곁에서 날 지켜준다는 말 <br>이번만큼은 제발 변치않길 <br><br>2. 어떤 사랑으로 나의 용서에 답하련지 <br>또 잠시 날 사랑하다 떠날 건지 <br>마치 처음 날 사랑하듯 <br>가슴 뜨겁게 와 있지만 <br>난 왠지 그 사랑이 두려워 <br>오직 나만을 위한 그 약속과 <br>내 곁에서 날 지켜준다는 말 <br>이번만큼은 제발 변치않길 <br>오직 나만을 위한 그 약속과 <br>내 곁에서 날 지켜준다는 말 <br>이번만큼은 제발 변치않길]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="거짓말" label="거짓말"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/너에게로_또다시/</id><title>왕소연 - 너에게로 또다시 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:53:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:53:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EB%84%88%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C%EB%A1%9C_%EB%98%90%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C/" title="왕소연 - 너에게로 또다시 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 그 얼마나 오랜 시간을 짙은 어둠에서 서성거렸나 <br>내 마음을 닫아 둔채로 헤매이다 흘러간 시간 <br>잊고 싶던 모든 일들은 때론 잊은 듯이 생각됐지만 <br>고개 저어도 떠오르는건 나를 보던 젖은 그 얼굴 <br>아무런 말없이 떠나버려도 때로는 모진 말로 멍들이며 울려도 <br>내 깊은 방황을 변함없이 따뜻한 눈으로 지켜보던 너 <br>너에게로 또다시 돌아오기까지가 왜 이리 힘들었을까 <br>이제 나는 알았어 내가 죽는날까지 널 떠날 수 없다는 걸 <br><br>2. 아무런 말없이 떠나버려도 때로는 모진 말로 멍들이며 울려도 <br>내 깊은 방황을 변함없이 따뜻한 눈으로 지켜보던 너 <br>너에게로 또다시 돌아오기까지가 왜 이리 힘들었을까 <br>이제 나는 알았어 내가 죽는날까지 널 떠날 수 없다는 걸]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="너에게로 또다시" label="너에게로 또다시"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/마이웨이/</id><title>왕소연 - 마이웨이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:53:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:53:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B4%EC%9B%A8%EC%9D%B4/" title="왕소연 - 마이웨이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 아주 멀리 왔다고 생각했는데 돌아다 볼 곳 없네 <br>정말 높이 올랐다 느꼈었는데 내려다 볼 곳 없네 <br>처음에는 나에게도 두려움 없었지만 어느새 겁 많은 놈으로 변해 있었어 <br>누구나 한번쯤은 넘어질 수 있어 이제와 주저앉아 있을 수는 없어 <br>내가 가야 하는 이 길에 지쳐 쓰러지는 날까지 일어나 한번 더 부딪혀 보는거야 <br>때론 큰 산 앞에서 무릎 꿇고서 포기도 하려 했어 <br>처음처럼 또다시 돌아가려고 무작정 찾으려 했어 <br>처음에는 나에게도 두려움 없었지만 어느새 겁 많은 놈으로 변해 있었어 <br>누구나 한번쯤은 넘어질 수 있어 이제와 주저앉아 있을 수는 없어 <br>내가 가야하는 이 길에 지쳐 쓰러지는 날까지 일어나 한번 더 부딪혀 보는거야 <br>마이웨이 <br><br>2. 처음에는 나에게도 두려움 없었지만 어느새 겁 많은 놈으로 변해 있었어 <br>누구나 한번쯤은 넘어질 수 있어 이제와 주저앉아 있을 수는 없어 <br>내가 가야 하는 이 길에 지쳐 쓰러지는 날까지 일어나 한번 더 부딪쳐 보는거야 <br>누구나 한번쯤은 넘어질 수 있어 이제와 주저앉아 있을 수는 없어 <br>내가 가야하는 이 길에 지쳐 쓰러지는 날까지 일어나 한번 더 부딪혀 보는거야 <br>마이웨이]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="마이웨이" label="마이웨이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/광화문연가/</id><title>왕소연 - 광화문연가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:53:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:53:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EA%B4%91%ED%99%94%EB%AC%B8%EC%97%B0%EA%B0%80/" title="왕소연 - 광화문연가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 이젠 모두 세월 따라 흔적도 없이 변하였지만 <br>덕수궁 돌담길에 아직 남아 있어요 다정히 걸어가는 연인들 <br>언젠가는 우리 모두 세월을 따라 떠나가지만 <br>언덕 밑 정동길에 아직 남아 있어요 눈 덮인 조그만 교회당 <br>향긋한 오월의 꽃향기가 가슴 깊이 그리워지면 <br>눈 내린 광화문 네거리 이곳에 이렇게 다시 찾아와요 <br>언젠가는 우리 모두 세월을 따라 떠나가지만 <br>언덕 밑 정동길에 아직 남아있어요 눈 덮인 조그만 교회당 <br><br>2. 향긋한 오월의 꽃향기가 가슴 깊이 그리워지면 <br>눈 내린 광화문 네거리 이곳에 이렇게 다시 찾아와요 <br>언젠가는 우리 모두 세월을 따라 떠나가지만 <br>언덕 밑 정동길에 아직 남아있어요 눈 덮인 조그만 교회당]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="광화문연가" label="광화문연가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/사랑이여_영원히/</id><title>왕소연 - 사랑이여 영원히 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:53:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:53:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4%EC%97%AC_%EC%98%81%EC%9B%90%ED%9E%88/" title="왕소연 - 사랑이여 영원히 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 이 세상에 태어나서 나 그대를 사랑하게 됐고 <br>똑똑하게 사랑하겠다던 마음이 그대 앞에선 사라지고 <br>아무 때나 찾아오는 보고픔에 젖은 그리움이 <br>내 나이가 지나서 시간이 흘러도 변하지 않을 것 같아 <br>속상해요 가는 시간이 속상해요 또 오는 세월이 <br>가시 같은 현실의 강을 건너가도 난 니가 있어 괜찮아 <br>얼마동안 사랑하고 얼마동안 너를 보게 될까 <br>미치도록 보고 싶어 가슴 아픈 날이 많았는데 <br>아무리 힘든 날이 와도 난 니 손을 놓지 않겠다 <br><br>2. 그대 앞에 있는 내가 때론 작게 느껴지더라도 <br>세상에서 누굴 사랑 하냐고 물으면 그대라고 말할 나에요 <br>운이 좋아 널 만났다고 요즘 들어 생각을 하게 돼 <br>다시 한번 세상에 태어날 수 있다면 그때도 너였으면 해 <br>얼마동안 사랑하고 얼마동안 너를 보게 될까 <br>미치도록 보고 싶어 가슴 아픈 날이 많았는데 <br>아무리 힘든 날이 와도 난 니 손을 놓지 않겠다 <br>난 니 손을 놓지 않겠다]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="사랑이여 영원히" label="사랑이여 영원히"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/그사람/</id><title>왕소연 - 그사람 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:54:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:54:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EA%B7%B8%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C/" title="왕소연 - 그사람 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 그 사람 날 웃게한 사람 그 사람 날 울게한 사람 <br>그 사람 따뜻한 입술로 내게 내 심장을 찾아 준 사람 <br>그 사랑 지을수 없는데 그 사랑 잊을수 없는데 <br>그 사람 내 숨같은 사람 우 그런 사람이 떠나가네요 <br>그 사람아 사랑아 아픈 가슴아 아무것도 모르는 사람아 <br>사랑했고 또 사랑해서 보낼 수 밖에 없는 사람아 내 사랑아 <br><br>2. 내 가슴 너덜 거린데도 그 추억 날을 세워 찔러도 <br>그 사람 흘릴 눈물이 나를 더욱더 아프게 하네요 <br>그 사람아 사랑아 아픈 가슴아 아무것도 모르는 사람아 <br>눈물 대신 슬픔 대신 나를 잊고 행복하게 살아줘 내 사랑아 <br>우리 삶이 다해서 우리 두눈 감을때 그때 한번 기억해 <br>그 사람아 사랑아 아픈 가슴아 아무것도 모르는 사람아 <br>사랑했고 또 사랑해서 보낼 수 밖에 없는 사람아 <br>내 사랑아 내 사랑아 우후후]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="그사람" label="그사람"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/숨어우는_바람소리/</id><title>왕소연 - 숨어우는 바람소리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:54:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:54:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EC%88%A8%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%B0%EB%8A%94_%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC/" title="왕소연 - 숨어우는 바람소리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 갈대밭이 보이는 언덕 통나무집 창가에 <br>길 떠난 소녀같이 하얗게 밤을새우네 <br>김이나는 차 한잔을 마주 하고 앉으면 <br>그 사람 목소린가 숨어우는 바람소리 <br>둘이서 걷던 갈대밭 길에 달은지고있는데 <br>잊는다 하고 무슨 이유로 눈물이 날까요 <br>아 아 아 길잃은 사슴처럼 그리움이 돌아오면 <br>쓸쓸한 갈대숲에 숨어우는 바람소리 <br><br>2. 둘이서 걷던 갈대밭 길에 달은지고있는데 <br>잊는다 하고 무슨 이유로 눈물이 날까요 <br>아 아 아 길잃은 사슴처럼 그리움이 돌아오면 <br>쓸쓸한 갈대숲에 숨어우는 바람소리 숨어우는 바람소리]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="숨어우는 바람소리" label="숨어우는 바람소리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/사랑이_남아_있을때/</id><title>왕소연 - 사랑이 남아 있을때 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:54:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:54:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4_%EB%82%A8%EC%95%84_%EC%9E%88%EC%9D%84%EB%95%8C/" title="왕소연 - 사랑이 남아 있을때 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 잡지도 못하고 보내야 했어요 마음은 너무나 아프지만 <br>잊어야 한다는 그말은 말아줘요 너무나 사랑했어요 <br>사랑이 남아 있을때 돌아서야 덜 아프다고 누군가 나에게 말을 했지요 <br>나보다 더좋은 사람 만날수가 있을거예요 그동안 내게 했던 것 처럼만 하세요 <br>이별마저 사랑하며 원점으로 당신을 아주 보내줄게요 <br><br>2. 울지도 못하고 돌아서 왔어요 당신을 너무도 아꼈기에 <br>날 잊어 달라는 그말은 말아줘요 너무나 가슴 아파요 <br>미련이 남아 있을때 보내야지 덜 아프다고 누군가 내게 말을 했지요 <br>나보다 더 좋은사람 찾을수가 있을거예요 그동안 내게 했던 것 처럼만 하세요 <br>미련마저 간직하며 원점으로 당신을 아주 보내줄게요]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="사랑이 남아 있을때" label="사랑이 남아 있을때"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왕소연/모란동백/</id><title>왕소연 - 모란동백 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:54:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:54:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%95%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EB%AA%A8%EB%9E%80%EB%8F%99%EB%B0%B1/" title="왕소연 - 모란동백 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1. 모란은 벌써 지고 없는데 먼 산에 뻐꾸기 울면 <br>상냥한 얼굴 모란 아가씨 꿈 속에 웃고 오네 <br>세상은 바람 불고 고달파라 나 어느 변방에 떠돌다 떠돌다 <br>어느 나무 그늘에 고요히 고요히 잠든다 해도 <br>또 한 번 모란이 필 때까지 나를 잊지 마세요 <br><br>2. 동백은 벌써 지고 없는데 먼 산에 눈이 내리면 <br>상냥한 얼굴 동백 아가씨 웃으며 봄이 오네 <br>세상은 바람 불고 덧없어라 나 어느 바다에 떠돌다 떠돌다 <br>어느 모랫벌에 외로이 외로이 잠든다 해도 <br>또 한 번 동백이 필 때까지 나를 잊지 마세요 <br>또 한 번 모란이 필 때까지 나를 잊지 말아요]]></content><category term="왕소연" label="왕소연"/><category term="모란동백" label="모란동백"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1carat/Lets_Go/</id><title>1carat - Let`s Go - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T22:58:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T22:58:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/1carat/Lets_Go/" title="1carat - Let`s Go - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Boom Boom 들어봐 <br>느껴봐 느껴봐 <br>Hey Boom Boom <br>Boom Boom <br>Boom Boom 음악에 <br>빠져봐 빠져봐 <br>Let's Dance Dance <br>Dance Dance <br>가슴 터지게 <br>우리 모두 달려봐 <br>Let's go go <br>Let's go go <br>가슴 터지게 <br>우리 한번 놀아봐 <br>Let's Play Play <br>Hey Play Play <br>노답 미스는 꺼지고 <br>백퍼 진짜만 모여봐 <br>우리 매력에 빠져봐 <br>이제 모두 다같이 시작해 <br>Let's Go <br>Let's Go <br>Let's Go <br>Let's Go <br>Boom Boom 쏟아봐 <br>채워봐 채워봐 <br>Hey Boom Boom <br>Boom Boom <br>Boom Boom 심장이 <br>터지게 더 쎄게 <br>Let's Play Play <br>Hey Play Play <br>가슴 터지게 <br>우리 모두 뛰어봐 <br>Everybody <br>Jump <br>가슴 터지게 <br>모두 소리 질러봐 <br>Everybody <br>Scream <br>노답 미스는 꺼지고 <br>백퍼 진짜만 모여봐 <br>우리 매력에 빠져봐 <br>이제 모두 다같이 시작해 <br>Let's Go <br>Let's Go <br>Let's Go <br>Let's Go <br>Let's Go <br>]]></content><category term="1carat" label="1carat"/><category term="Let`s Go" label="Let`s Go"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mac_Demarco/Go_Easy/</id><title>Mac_Demarco - Go Easy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:02:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:02:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mac_Demarco/Go_Easy/" title="Mac_Demarco - Go Easy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pack it up and leave it, leave it all behind you <br>Starting fresh in someone else's town <br>And though we may be leaving, I'll be right beside you <br>To pick you up until you come around <br><br>So please, go easy with my baby <br>Please, go easy <br>Please, go easy with my baby <br>Please, go easy <br><br>Honey it can be tough, without your friends beside you <br>You built it up, just to knock it down <br>So when you're feeling rough, I'll be right behind you <br>To pick you up until you come around <br><br>So please, go easy with my baby <br>Please, go easy <br>Please, go easy with my baby <br>Please, go easy x2]]></content><category term="Mac Demarco" label="Mac Demarco"/><category term="Go Easy" label="Go Easy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mac_Demarco/Brother/</id><title>Mac_Demarco - Brother - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:02:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:02:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mac_Demarco/Brother/" title="Mac_Demarco - Brother - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're no better off, living your life and dreaming at night <br>This much is true, but it's still up to you to take my advice <br><br>To take it slowly, brother <br>Let it go now, brother <br>Take it slowly, brother <br>Let it go <br><br>Go home x4 <br><br>You're better off dead, when your mind's been set from nine until five <br>How could it be true, well it's happened to you, so take my advice <br><br>And take it slowly, brother <br>Let it go now, brother <br>Take it slowly, brother <br>Let it go <br><br>Go home x8]]></content><category term="Mac Demarco" label="Mac Demarco"/><category term="Brother" label="Brother"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mac_Demarco/Let_My_Baby_Stay/</id><title>Mac_Demarco - Let My Baby Stay - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:02:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:02:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mac_Demarco/Let_My_Baby_Stay/" title="Mac_Demarco - Let My Baby Stay - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was made to love her, been working at it <br>Half of my life, I've been an addict <br><br>And she's been good to me <br>Far as I can tell she's happy, livin' with her Macky <br><br>So please don't take my love away <br>Let my baby stay, let my baby stay <br><br>Please don't take my love away <br>Let my baby stay, let my baby stay <br><br>And where would I be, feeling lonely <br>Separated from my one and only <br><br>And what's there left to say <br>Far as I can tell that day could be on its way <br><br>So please don't take my love away <br>Let my baby stay, let my baby stay <br><br>Please don't take my love away <br>Let my baby stay, let my baby stay]]></content><category term="Mac Demarco" label="Mac Demarco"/><category term="Let My Baby Stay" label="Let My Baby Stay"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mac_Demarco/Passing_Out_Pieces_Of_Me/</id><title>Mac_Demarco - Passing Out Pieces Of Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:02:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:02:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mac_Demarco/Passing_Out_Pieces_Of_Me/" title="Mac_Demarco - Passing Out Pieces Of Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Watching my life, passing right in front of my eyes <br>Hell of a story, oh is it boring <br>Can't claim to care, never been reluctant to share <br>Passing out pieces of me, don't you know nothing comes free <br><br>What mom don't know has taken its toll on me <br>It's all I've seen that can't be wiped clean <br>It's hard to believe what it's made of me <br><br>Passing my life, living it out in her sight <br>Listening closely, hearing her mostly <br>Can't shake concern, seems that every time that I turn <br>I'm passing out pieces of me, don't you know nothing comes free <br><br>What mom don't know has taken its toll on me <br>It's all I've seen that can't be wiped clean <br>It's hard to believe what it's made of me]]></content><category term="Mac Demarco" label="Mac Demarco"/><category term="Passing Out Pieces Of Me" label="Passing Out Pieces Of Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mac_Demarco/Salad_Days/</id><title>Mac_Demarco - Salad Days - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:02:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:02:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mac_Demarco/Salad_Days/" title="Mac_Demarco - Salad Days - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[As I'm getting older, chip up on my shoulder <br>Rolling through life, to roll over and die <br><br>Missing hippy Jon, salad days are gone <br>Remembering things just to tell 'em so long <br><br>Oh mama, actin' like my life's already over <br>Oh dear, act your age and try another year <br><br>Always feeling tired, smiling when required <br>Write another year off and kindly resign <br><br>Salad days are gone, missing hippy Jon <br>Remember the days just to tell 'em so long <br><br>Oh mama, actin' like my life's already over <br>Oh dear, act your age and try another year x2]]></content><category term="Mac Demarco" label="Mac Demarco"/><category term="Salad Days" label="Salad Days"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mac_Demarco/Goodbye_Weekend/</id><title>Mac_Demarco - Goodbye Weekend - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:02:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:02:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mac_Demarco/Goodbye_Weekend/" title="Mac_Demarco - Goodbye Weekend - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye weekend, so long darling <br>Macky's been a bad bad boy <br>And when their preaching is sure to change me <br>Should rearrange me or so they thought <br><br>So don't go telling me how this boy should be leading his own life <br>Sometimes rough, but generally speaking I'm fine <br>If you don't agree with the things that go on within in my life <br>Well honey that's fine just know that you're wasting your time <br><br>Sort me, place me, give me a sign <br>Repeat the mantra when you're stepping out of line <br>Give me a number, something to be <br>May help out the country boy but it won't work out on me <br><br>x2 <br>So don't go telling me how this boy should be leading his own life <br>Sometimes rough but generally speaking I'm fine <br>If you don't agree with the things that go on within in my life <br>Well honey that's fine just know that you're wasting your time]]></content><category term="Mac Demarco" label="Mac Demarco"/><category term="Goodbye Weekend" label="Goodbye Weekend"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시온의_이슬/이끌림_Inst/</id><title>시온의_이슬 - 이끌림 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:02:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:02:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EC%98%A8%EC%9D%98_%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%AC/%EC%9D%B4%EB%81%8C%EB%A6%BC_Inst/" title="시온의_이슬 - 이끌림 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어렵게 지내온 날들 <br>그 고통의 시간 내맘에 <br>이젠 되돌릴 수 없는 <br>내안의 작은 소망들을 <br>이길을 걸어요 점점 <br>더 가까워 지는 어둠에 <br>이젠 알것같기에 <br>날 향한 아버지의 뜻을 <br>믿을수 없는 일이 <br>나에게 온다해도 <br>날향한 주의 뜻이 <br>이렇게 날 이끄시네 <br>언제나 함께 계셔 <br>날 위로 하시는 주 <br>이렇게도 낮고 낮은 날 위해 <br>동행 하시는 주 <br>언제나 함께 계셔 <br>날 위로 하시는 주 <br>이렇게도 낮고 낮은 날 위해 <br>언제나 동행 하네 <br>그사랑 참 감사해 <br>주 사랑이 큰 사랑이 <br>우리의 죄 대신 했네 <br>믿을 수 없는 일이 <br>나에게 온다해도 <br>날 향한 주의 뜻이 <br>이렇게 날 이끄시네 <br>언제나 함께 계셔 <br>날 위로 하시는 주 <br>이렇게도 낮고 낮은 날 위해 <br>동행 하시는 주 <br>언제나 함께 계셔 <br>날 위로 하시는 주 <br>이렇게도 낮고 낮은 날 위해 <br>언제나 동행 하네 <br>그사랑 참 감사해 <br>]]></content><category term="시온의 이슬" label="시온의 이슬"/><category term="이끌림 (Inst.)" label="이끌림 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시온의_이슬/이끌림/</id><title>시온의_이슬 - 이끌림 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:02:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:02:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EC%98%A8%EC%9D%98_%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%AC/%EC%9D%B4%EB%81%8C%EB%A6%BC/" title="시온의_이슬 - 이끌림 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어렵게 지내온 날들 <br>그 고통의 시간 내맘에 <br>이젠 되돌릴 수 없는 <br>내안의 작은 소망들을 <br>이길을 걸어요 점점 <br>더 가까워 지는 어둠에 <br>이젠 알것같기에 <br>날 향한 아버지의 뜻을 <br>믿을수 없는 일이 <br>나에게 온다해도 <br>날향한 주의 뜻이 <br>이렇게 날 이끄시네 <br>언제나 함께 계셔 <br>날 위로 하시는 주 <br>이렇게도 낮고 낮은 날 위해 <br>동행 하시는 주 <br>언제나 함께 계셔 <br>날 위로 하시는 주 <br>이렇게도 낮고 낮은 날 위해 <br>언제나 동행 하네 <br>그사랑 참 감사해 <br>주 사랑이 큰 사랑이 <br>우리의 죄 대신 했네 <br>믿을 수 없는 일이 <br>나에게 온다해도 <br>날 향한 주의 뜻이 <br>이렇게 날 이끄시네 <br>언제나 함께 계셔 <br>날 위로 하시는 주 <br>이렇게도 낮고 낮은 날 위해 <br>동행 하시는 주 <br>언제나 함께 계셔 <br>날 위로 하시는 주 <br>이렇게도 낮고 낮은 날 위해 <br>언제나 동행 하네 <br>그사랑 참 감사해 <br>]]></content><category term="시온의 이슬" label="시온의 이슬"/><category term="이끌림" label="이끌림"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/데니스프로젝트/그대를_잊은적_없다_Inst/</id><title>데니스프로젝트 - 그대를 잊은적 없다 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:03:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:03:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%B0%EB%8B%88%EC%8A%A4%ED%94%84%EB%A1%9C%EC%A0%9D%ED%8A%B8/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9E%8A%EC%9D%80%EC%A0%81_%EC%97%86%EB%8B%A4_Inst/" title="데니스프로젝트 - 그대를 잊은적 없다 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그리워 너의 향기 마저 <br>날 위해 이제 돌아와줘 <br>널 보낼 수 없어 널 잊은 적 없어 Baby <br>I Want It 너의 모든 것 <br>아직도 남아있는 <br>너의 향기에 난 취해 <br>근데 꿈속에선 <br>도망쳐 날 계속 피해 <br>실감이 안나 <br>나 혼자 눈을 뜨는 아침 <br>내가 만진 너의 머리는 이제 없지 <br>어색해진 발걸음 <br>내 옆에는 빈자리 <br>불러주던 애칭도 <br>이제 들리지 않지 <br>실수라도 내게 전화 <br>해줬으면 좋겠어 <br>헛된 바램인걸 <br>나도 알고 있어 <br>처음 만난 그날부터 <br>입맞춘 순간까지 <br>너에 대해 아무것도 <br>나는 잊은 게 없어 <br>네가 날 어떻게 <br>생각할진 몰라도 <br>처음부터 지금까지 <br>난 변한 것은 없어 <br>술 먹고 늦지 말란 <br>잔소리가 그리워 <br>아침에 깨워주던 <br>목소리가 듣고 싶어 <br>잘해주지 못한 날이 <br>미안해 지는데 <br>니가 그려주던 꽃까지 <br>시든 것 같네 <br>그리워 너의 향기 마저 <br>날 위해 이제 돌아와줘 <br>널 보낼 수 없어 널 잊은 적 없어 Baby <br>I Want It 너의 모든 것 <br>알아줘 나의 이런 맘 <br>너 아니면 안 해 이런 말 <br>좀 어색하지 이런 나 <br>다시 시작 할 수는 없을까 <br>그리워 너의 향기 마저 <br>날 위해 이제 돌아와줘 <br>널 보낼 수 없어 널 잊은 적 없어 Baby <br>I Want It 너의 모든 것 <br>그대를 잊은 적이 없어 단 한번도 <br>너와 헤어지고 나선 없어 <br>날 반겨 주는 <br>사람이 그리워 너와의 사랑이 <br>이런 이기적인 <br>나에겐 없어 할말이 <br>네가 좋아하던 음식은 <br>이제 맛이 없어 <br>배 고프지 않아서 <br>잘 차려 먹지 않아 <br>가로등의 불빛처럼 <br>희미해지겠지 내가 <br>너로 인해 힘들다고 <br>소리 지르니까 <br>보고 싶다고 이젠 볼 수 없는데 <br>가고 싶어도 이젠 갈 수 없는데 <br>수 백 번이고 찾아가고 싶어 <br>너의 집 앞 <br>매번 반복되는 첫 페이지 <br>넌 마치 집합 <br>처럼 새까맣게 변해버린 내 맘 <br>추억의 메모리는 <br>복구가 불가능해 <br>정말로 너 말고는 싫어 다른 애 <br>취하고 싶어 널 안주 삼아 <br>술잔을 따르네 <br>그리워 너의 향기 마저 <br>날 위해 이제 돌아와줘 <br>널 보낼 수 없어 널 잊은 적 없어 Baby <br>I Want It 너의 모든 것 <br>그리워 너의 향기 마저 <br>날 위해 이제 돌아와줘 <br>널 보낼 수 없어 널 잊은 적 없어 Baby <br>I Want It 너의 모든 것 <br>]]></content><category term="데니스프로젝트" label="데니스프로젝트"/><category term="그대를 잊은적 없다 (Inst.)" label="그대를 잊은적 없다 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/데니스프로젝트/그대를_잊은적_없다_Feat_노훈/</id><title>데니스프로젝트 - 그대를 잊은적 없다 (Feat. 노훈) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:03:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:03:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%B0%EB%8B%88%EC%8A%A4%ED%94%84%EB%A1%9C%EC%A0%9D%ED%8A%B8/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9E%8A%EC%9D%80%EC%A0%81_%EC%97%86%EB%8B%A4_Feat_%EB%85%B8%ED%9B%88/" title="데니스프로젝트 - 그대를 잊은적 없다 (Feat. 노훈) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그리워 너의 향기 마저 <br>날 위해 이제 돌아와줘 <br>널 보낼 수 없어 널 잊은 적 없어 Baby <br>I Want It 너의 모든 것 <br>아직도 남아있는 <br>너의 향기에 난 취해 <br>근데 꿈속에선 <br>도망쳐 날 계속 피해 <br>실감이 안나 <br>나 혼자 눈을 뜨는 아침 <br>내가 만진 너의 머리는 이제 없지 <br>어색해진 발걸음 <br>내 옆에는 빈자리 <br>불러주던 애칭도 <br>이제 들리지 않지 <br>실수라도 내게 전화 <br>해줬으면 좋겠어 <br>헛된 바램인걸 <br>나도 알고 있어 <br>처음 만난 그날부터 <br>입맞춘 순간까지 <br>너에 대해 아무것도 <br>나는 잊은 게 없어 <br>네가 날 어떻게 <br>생각할진 몰라도 <br>처음부터 지금까지 <br>난 변한 것은 없어 <br>술 먹고 늦지 말란 <br>잔소리가 그리워 <br>아침에 깨워주던 <br>목소리가 듣고 싶어 <br>잘해주지 못한 날이 <br>미안해 지는데 <br>니가 그려주던 꽃까지 <br>시든 것 같네 <br>그리워 너의 향기 마저 <br>날 위해 이제 돌아와줘 <br>널 보낼 수 없어 널 잊은 적 없어 Baby <br>I Want It 너의 모든 것 <br>알아줘 나의 이런 맘 <br>너 아니면 안 해 이런 말 <br>좀 어색하지 이런 나 <br>다시 시작 할 수는 없을까 <br>그리워 너의 향기 마저 <br>날 위해 이제 돌아와줘 <br>널 보낼 수 없어 널 잊은 적 없어 Baby <br>I Want It 너의 모든 것 <br>그대를 잊은 적이 없어 단 한번도 <br>너와 헤어지고 나선 없어 <br>날 반겨 주는 <br>사람이 그리워 너와의 사랑이 <br>이런 이기적인 <br>나에겐 없어 할말이 <br>네가 좋아하던 음식은 <br>이제 맛이 없어 <br>배 고프지 않아서 <br>잘 차려 먹지 않아 <br>가로등의 불빛처럼 <br>희미해지겠지 내가 <br>너로 인해 힘들다고 <br>소리 지르니까 <br>보고 싶다고 이젠 볼 수 없는데 <br>가고 싶어도 이젠 갈 수 없는데 <br>수 백 번이고 찾아가고 싶어 <br>너의 집 앞 <br>매번 반복되는 첫 페이지 <br>넌 마치 집합 <br>처럼 새까맣게 변해버린 내 맘 <br>추억의 메모리는 <br>복구가 불가능해 <br>정말로 너 말고는 싫어 다른 애 <br>취하고 싶어 널 안주 삼아 <br>술잔을 따르네 <br>그리워 너의 향기 마저 <br>날 위해 이제 돌아와줘 <br>널 보낼 수 없어 널 잊은 적 없어 Baby <br>I Want It 너의 모든 것 <br>그리워 너의 향기 마저 <br>날 위해 이제 돌아와줘 <br>널 보낼 수 없어 널 잊은 적 없어 Baby <br>I Want It 너의 모든 것 <br>]]></content><category term="데니스프로젝트" label="데니스프로젝트"/><category term="그대를 잊은적 없다 (Feat. 노훈)" label="그대를 잊은적 없다 (Feat. 노훈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zuna/Wieso_/</id><title>Zuna - Wieso? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:03:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:03:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zuna/Wieso_/" title="Zuna - Wieso? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lalalala, lalalala lalalala <br>Lalalalala <br>Lalalalala <br>Lalalala <br>Lalalalalalala <br>Scurr, scurr, scurr <br><br>Sag an allen deinen Jungs, die von Weitem Welle schieben <br>Ich bin da Kugeln fliegen, schiessen scharf KMN ist die Macht, Diggi <br>In der Nacht Batzen stapeln im Vollrausch <br>Links, rechts Knockout, mit Bitches aus Moskau <br>Baby, aus dem Weg, weil die Gage ist hoch <br>Zehn Mille bar auf dem Weg zur Million'n <br>AMG auf Kickdown, die Augen sind gross <br>Roli am Arm 15er Statussymbol <br>Willkomm'n im Milieu, willkomm'n im Kartell <br>Wo Junkies zustechen nur fur paar Cent <br>Ich scheiss' auf dein Gold, nachstes Jahr Platin <br>Ein falsches Wort, Pisser, lass' Kugeln hageln <br>Alles auf Kopf in der Louis V <br>Hab' Mille genug, Geld, mon ami <br>Keiner toppt KMN Family <br>Seit Tag eins in HD Quality <br><br>Brrraaa Bruder, wieso <br>Wieso, wieso, wieso <br>Machst du Film, Kino, Kino <br>Chaye, wo dein Benz und Munition <br>Brrraaa Bruder, wieso <br>Wieso, wieso, wieso <br>Machst du Film, Kino, Kino <br>Chaye, wo dein Benz und Munition <br><br>Bruder, wieso machst du auf Mann, Film <br>Aber zitterst schon bei Kurse verhandeln <br>Geb' dir Schell'n, so als war' ich dein Onkel <br>Seit Tag eins Original mit der Bande <br>Kurzhaarschnitt Benzema <br>Auf Strasse mein Name bekannt <br>Du findest, mein Verhalten ist falsch <br>Weil ich auf Alk deine Frau knall' <br>Mache kein Halt, mach die Flaschen auf Tisch, Mamacita <br>Heut geht alles auf mich, Taxi iz da <br>ubernacht' in Prasidentsuite <br>KMN ist die Gang, geh, verpiss dich, du Pic <br>Du platzt, weil du von Weitem zusiehst <br>Zund' Blunt an in der Q7 <br>Sonne scheint immer Juli <br>Heute Strand, geh beiseite, Habibi <br><br>Brrraaa Bruder, wieso <br>Wieso, wieso, wieso <br>Machst du Film, Kino, Kino <br>Chaye, wo dein Benz und Munition <br>Brrraaa Bruder, wieso <br>Wieso, wieso, wieso <br>Machst du Film, Kino, Kino <br>Chaye, wo dein Benz und Munition <br><br>Lalalalalala, lalalalalala <br>Lalalalalala <br><br>Brrraaa Bruder, wieso <br>Wieso, wieso, wieso <br>Machst du Film, Kino, Kino <br>Chaye, wo dein Benz und Munition <br>Brrraaa Bruder, wieso <br>Wieso, wieso, wieso <br>Machst du Film, Kino, Kino <br>Chaye, wo dein Benz und Munition]]></content><category term="Zuna" label="Zuna"/><category term="Wieso?" label="Wieso?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_M_Machine/Voyeur/</id><title>The_M_Machine - Voyeur - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:07:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:07:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_M_Machine/Voyeur/" title="The_M_Machine - Voyeur - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't worry girl <br>I follow you wherever you're going <br>I promise you love <br>You'll never be alone <br>I can tell you're dreaming <br>Are you dreaming of me <br>You forgot this kiss <br>I hope you left it behind on purpose <br><br>Carry on <br>When you're dreaming <br>Carry on <br>I'll be watching you <br>Carry on <br>It's almost time to wake up girl <br>Now open your eyes <br><br>Don't cry my love <br>You're eyes stay dry like mine <br>Wrapped up in fire <br>The world belongs to us tonight <br>And i can tell you're dreaming <br>Are you dreaming of me <br>You forgot this kiss love <br>I hope you left it behind on purpose <br><br>Carry on <br>When you're dreaming <br>Carry on <br>I'll be watching you <br>Carry on <br>It's almost time to wake up girl <br>Now open your eyes <br><br>Are you dreaming <br>Are you dreaming now <br>Are you dreaming <br>Are you dreaming of me <br><br>Carry on <br>When you're dreaming <br>Carry on <br>I'll be watching you <br>Carry on <br>It's almost time to wake up girl <br>Now open your eyes]]></content><category term="The M Machine" label="The M Machine"/><category term="Voyeur" label="Voyeur"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yonii/Mama/</id><title>Yonii - Mama - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:07:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:07:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yonii/Mama/" title="Yonii - Mama - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh Mama <br><br>Mama safi sifini <br>Enti dima kat bghini <br>Je prefere 7yati jdida <br>Je m'eloigne mel mafia w el gangsta <br>Mama safi sifini <br>Enti dima kat bghini <br>Je prefere 7yati jdida <br>Je m'eloigne mel mafia w el gangsta <br><br>L3azhm riski w nghamer <br>Pour my mother <br>L7lem yji nhar, tcha3l fih el anwar <br>Nerja3 lik ya yommima bel 3az, lham w chan <br>Nkhorjou bel lil, n7aws bik f'limousine <br>Rabbi y7fedk mel 3in <br>Ya rou7 ibnek l7nin, 3ini bel khir <br>Rani mgharreb finin <br>Tbedlat 3liya l7ouma, desole khellitek mehmouma <br>Ch7al men 7bab mchaw ma chefnahoum <br>Ma oud3ouna, ma oud3anahoum <br>Ghir fel foto chefnahoum w fel mekbara zernahoum <br>Hada taman ghorba l9asia <br>Hada l7ayat ghada machia <br>Men li 7essit b denya da7katliya lkhedma jatli tab3ini gha hiya <br>L7ayat gharbiya lmabiya khallatni n3eych wa7da li bla insaniya <br><br>Mama safi sifini <br>Enti dima kat bghini <br>Je prefere 7yati jdida <br>Je m'eloigne mel mafia w el gangsta <br>Mama safi sifini <br>Enti dima kat bghini <br>Je prefere 7yati jdida <br>Je m'eloigne mel mafia w el gangsta <br><br>Mama safi sifini <br>Ana ma 3azhlt 7yati <br>Ta7t fel gharourani, mchit fih <br>Khabdeni denya, mantlo9 fih <br> w gelt 3lach <br>Tba3t klam nass <br>Lakin el youm ntfa3l w ngoul <br>Rabbi karim ya sri l2oumoun <br><br>Mama safi sifini <br>Enti dima kat bghini <br>Je prefere 7yati jdida <br>Je m'eloigne mel mafia w el gangsta <br>Mama safi sifini <br>Enti dima kat bghini <br>Je prefere 7yati jdida <br>Je m'eloigne mel mafia w el gangsta]]></content><category term="Yonii" label="Yonii"/><category term="Mama" label="Mama"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yonii/Attention/</id><title>Yonii - Attention - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:07:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:07:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yonii/Attention/" title="Yonii - Attention - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Soufri <br>Integration <br>Attention <br>Attention <br><br>Wasch hada maghrebi <br>Passport france <br>Jazairi oula tunsie <br>Lybie oula masri3 <br>Iraqi oula syrie <br>Senegale oula Mali <br>Somali Mauretane <br>Ana kabri mana de el boldan <br><br>Mara la bas <br>Ou mara XXX <br>Rabi 7asbini fl foun <br>XXX <br>Rabouni, chebouni, kabrouni, 7almounie, ta7li ouldi <br>7didi, 7aschdouni, kar7ouni, seftouni, teb7ouni <br><br>Migration, Integration, Attention <br>Choya goul lia kifasch XXX <br>Munition, Kalaschnikow, Attention <br>Dakschi choya li mabarit <br>Migration, Integration, Attention <br>Choya goul lia kifasch fl blad <br>Munition, Kalaschnikow, Attention <br>Dakschi choya li mabarit <br><br>Galbi <br>Bain hada ma bra i f7am <br>Rabi khleck nsan <br>Y 7aml ki hayavan <br>Khodi oula 7yan <br>Je pas rifi oula ba khelini n schroub ou nschi oun dya hyati <br>Fl dounya dial mouschkil XXX rabi khfer tomobil <br><br>Migration, Integration, Attention <br>Choya goul lia kifasch XXX <br>Munition, Kalaschnikow, Attention <br>Dakschi choya li mabarit <br>Migration, Integration, Attention <br>Choya goul lia kifasch fl blad <br>Munition, Kalaschnikow, Attention <br>Dakschi choya li mabarit <br>Migration, Integration, Attention <br>Choya goul lia kifasch XXX <br>Munition, Kalaschnikow, Attention <br>Dakschi choya li mabarit <br>Migration, Integration, Attention <br>Choya goul lia kifasch fl blad <br>Munition, Kalaschnikow, Attention <br>Dakschi choya li mabarit]]></content><category term="Yonii" label="Yonii"/><category term="Attention" label="Attention"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Androp/BGM/</id><title>Androp - BGM - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:07:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:07:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Androp/BGM/" title="Androp - BGM - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가사를 입력해 주세요.笑ったこと忘れないように <br>(와랏-타코토 와스레나이요-니) <br>웃었던 적 잊지 않도록 <br><br>そっと思い出はポケットに <br>(솟-토 오모이데와 포켓-토니) <br>살며시 추억은 주머니에 <br><br>悲しみも拭えるように <br>(카나시미모 누구에루요-니) <br>슬픔도 씻어낼 수 있도록 <br><br>君の指を握っておこう <br>(키미노유비오 니깃-테오코-) <br>너의 손을 꼭 잡고 있을래 <br><br>似た者どうしの僕らは <br>(니타모노도-시노 보쿠라와) <br>서로 꼭 닮은 우리는 <br><br>大事な言葉は言えないまま <br>(다이지나코토바와 이에나이마마) <br>해야 할 말은 하지 못한 채 <br><br>無理にはしゃいで？がるから <br>(무리니하샤이데 츠요가루카라) <br>애써 밝은 척 하면서 <br><br>君に？づかれないようにしよう <br>(키미니키즈카레나이요-니시요-) <br>너에게 들키지 않게 할래 <br><br>今日は空が？いから <br>(쿄-와소라가아오이카라) <br>오늘은 날씨가 좋으니까 <br><br>まだ行ってない場所に行こう <br>(마다잇-테나이바쇼니이코-) <br>아직 가보지 않은 곳에 가보자 <br><br>たとえ？れなくなっても <br>(타토에카에레나쿠낫-테모) <br>돌아올 수 없게 되더라도 <br><br>君といるからどこへでも <br>(키미토이루카라 도코에데모) <br>너와 있으니까 어디라도 좋아 <br><br>そっと想いが <br>(솟-토 오모이가) <br>살며시 추억이 <br><br>ずっと消えないように <br>(즛-토 키에나이요-니) <br>언제까지나 사라지지 않게끔 <br><br>そっと伸ばす手に <br>(솟-토 노바스테니) <br>살며시 내민 손에서 <br><br>君の熱を感じた <br>(키미노네츠오칸-지타) <br>너의 따듯함을 느꼈어 <br><br>巡って 巡って <br>(메굿-테 메굿-테) <br>돌고 돌아 <br><br>今となりに君がいる <br>(이마토나리니 키미가이루) <br>지금 내 옆엔 네가 있고 <br><br>響いて 響いて <br>(히비이테 히비이테) <br>울려퍼지고 울려퍼져 <br><br>世界は光溢れる <br>(세카이와히카리 아후레루) <br>세상은 빛이 흘러 넘쳐 <br><br>突然の雨に降られても <br>(토츠젠-노아메니 후라레테모) <br>갑자기 비가 쏟아져도 <br><br>語り合うBGMにしよう <br>(카타리아우 비지에무니시요-) <br>우리 이야기의 BGM으로 삼자 <br><br>曇って凍えた心に <br>(쿠못-테 코고에타코코로니) <br>어둡고 얼어붙은 마음에 <br><br>君の笑顔が虹を架ける <br>(키미노에가오가 니지오카케루) <br>네 미소가 무지개를 만들어 <br><br>時計の針は進んでも <br>(토케이노하리와 스슨-데모) <br>시곗바늘은 앞으로 가더라도 <br><br>やっと想いを？えても <br>(얏-토 오모이오츠타에테모) <br>겨우 마음을 전했어도 <br><br>やっぱり僕は僕だし <br>(얏-빠리 보쿠와보쿠다시) <br>여전히 나는 나이고 <br><br>君は君のままだから <br>(키미와키미노 마마다카라) <br>너는 너인 채니까 <br><br>きっと想いは <br>(킷-토 오모이와) <br>분명 그 마음은 <br><br>ずっと消えないまま <br>(즛-토 키에나이마마) <br>언제까지나 사라지지 않아 <br><br>遠く離れても <br>(토-쿠 하나레테모) <br>멀리 떨어져 있어도 <br><br>君の熱を感じた <br>(키미노네츠오칸-지타) <br>너의 따듯함이 느껴져 <br><br>？いて ？いて <br>(토도이테 토도이테) <br>닿아라 닿아라 <br><br>この空には君がいる <br>(코노소라니와 키미가이루) <br>이 하늘에는 네가 있고 <br><br>輝き？けて <br>(카가야키 츠즈케테) <br>반짝이는 <br><br>未？に今？がる <br>(미라이니 이마츠나가루) <br>미래에 지금 다가갈 테니 <br><br>巡って 巡って <br>(메굿-테 메굿-테) <br>돌고 돌아 <br><br>僕の中には君がいる <br>(보쿠노나카니와 키미가이루) <br>나의 한가운데엔 네가 있고 <br><br>響いて 響いて <br>(히비이테 히비이테) <br>울려퍼지고 울려퍼져 <br><br>世界は光溢れる <br>(세카이와히카리 아후레루) <br>세상은 빛이 흘러 넘쳐 <br>]]></content><category term="Androp" label="Androp"/><category term="BGM" label="BGM"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Super_Whatevr/Will_Work_For_Food/</id><title>Super_Whatevr - Will Work For Food - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:07:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:07:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Super_Whatevr/Will_Work_For_Food/" title="Super_Whatevr - Will Work For Food - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[He woke up <br>Shrapnel scars across the top of his head <br>His children at the edge of his bed <br>Not sure if this really happened <br><br>He sits up <br>Just standing but he falls to the floor <br>Pleading that he's still fit for war <br>He's cursing at his purple heart <br><br>Suit and Tie <br>Sits and waits and stares at the clock <br>Wondering about what time he got up <br>Struggling with his lungs filled with tar <br><br>Interview <br>Says it seems to me you're unfit <br>Doesn't match the job description <br>Cause no ones cares he's a veteran <br><br>As he looks for savior <br>In the back of the paper <br>He thinks he's willing and able <br>Why can't I be like the rest <br><br>Nobody seems to draw nearer <br>This questions never looked clearer <br>Life starts to feel like a mirror <br>His bottle clung to his chest <br><br>No more use <br>Resorting to a life of abuse <br>This love affair has tied up his noose <br>He didn't get the option to choose <br><br>Oh god why me <br>I thought this was the land of the free <br>A life of fame without pedigree <br>Cause freedom costs unfortunately <br><br>Oh god you're not waking up <br>Please wake up <br>Oh my love <br>Wake up <br><br>Oh god you're not waking up <br>Please wake up <br>Oh my love <br>Wake up]]></content><category term="Super Whatevr" label="Super Whatevr"/><category term="Will Work For Food" label="Will Work For Food"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Super_Whatevr/Someone_Somewhere_Somehow/</id><title>Super_Whatevr - Someone Somewhere Somehow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:07:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:07:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Super_Whatevr/Someone_Somewhere_Somehow/" title="Super_Whatevr - Someone Somewhere Somehow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I asked you how he's doing the day before he died <br>you said he's doing fine we're all just doing fine <br>About a week ago I watched his body lowered down <br>Now no one's doing fine and I am less and less around <br>I'm sick to death and scared that I might actually be the culprit <br>I didn't spend much time with him and no one seemed to notice <br>His lust for life was squandered when he lost his loving friends <br>believe he actually was a corpse before his life had ended <br>The final letter seemed despondent as if he wasn't there <br>one more summer and you could have been amongst the world you feared <br><br>You were happy Don't understand how it could all be fake <br>Your smile glowing but your eyes reflected shame <br>Sorrowful and somber filled your family didn't help <br>Your sister was the one with issues that they had to deal with now <br>Now life is but a memory and death is in full swing <br>Your skin that held together bone is promptly decaying <br>Family gathered round to see an issue unresolved <br>Why couldn't you have told a friend that might've helped it all <br>Identify the body the father pleaded so <br>All that laid was flesh no longer occupied a soul <br><br>Delicate and calm the father witnessed his son's fate <br>The bullet hole that entered had an exit just the same <br><br>I've been wrapping these tragedies in plastic <br>and throwing them away amidst the trash that I inhabit <br><br>It's madness, it's tragic <br>I'm clogging up my feelings with this sickness that is sadness <br><br>and I asked you how he's doing the day before he died <br>you said he's doing fine we're all just doing fine]]></content><category term="Super Whatevr" label="Super Whatevr"/><category term="Someone Somewhere Somehow" label="Someone Somewhere Somehow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Super_Whatevr/Good_Luck/</id><title>Super_Whatevr - Good Luck - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:08:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:08:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Super_Whatevr/Good_Luck/" title="Super_Whatevr - Good Luck - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All of my days have been mapped out for me and <br>All of my love has left no room to breathe <br>But I won't let you go <br><br>I didn't want to end up quite like this <br>But you didn't care if I still gave a shit <br>But I won't let you go <br><br>Oh my god you are so messed up in the head and darling I am too <br><br>So I would like to know if you would like to go to my humble abode to stay no wait you hate me darling hate me <br><br>All of my life I thought I had it made <br>But then you showed up and ruined my whole day <br>Oh I won't let you go <br><br>Guess I'm a fool believing all your lies <br>But no one can say that I didn't try <br>Oh I won't let you go <br><br>Oh my god you are so messed up in the head but darling I am too <br><br>So I would like to know if you would like to go to my humble abode to stay no wait you hate me darling hate me x2 <br><br>Good luck good luck to you love x2 <br><br>There's so much I could tell you but you're still gonna leave <br>So good luck to you darling and maybe one day we'll speak <br>The last time I remember will be the last time I forget <br>The scars upon your thighs or the freckles down your neck <br><br>So good luck good luck to you love x3 <br>Good luck, good luck]]></content><category term="Super Whatevr" label="Super Whatevr"/><category term="Good Luck" label="Good Luck"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Woodes/Byron/</id><title>Woodes - Byron - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:08:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:08:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Woodes/Byron/" title="Woodes - Byron - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I stand in the ocean <br>And I can see my toes <br>Rocks on the horizon <br>Where in the deep the sharks creep <br>You stand in the ocean <br>Waves break on your chest <br>Salty eyes, wide open, in the deep in the deep now <br><br>I stand in the ocean <br>And I can see my toes <br>Rocks on the horizon <br>Where in the deep the sharks creep <br>You stand in the ocean <br>Waves break on your chest <br>Salty eyes, wide open, in the deep in the deep now <br><br>Fully submerged in your love <br>Waves wash over me <br>Caught in a current in your love and I'm swimming deep]]></content><category term="Woodes" label="Woodes"/><category term="Byron" label="Byron"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Woodes/Bonfire/</id><title>Woodes - Bonfire - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:08:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:08:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Woodes/Bonfire/" title="Woodes - Bonfire - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I see this place went wild <br>Trees they all grew up <br>Try to find the one I'd climb <br>That reached out <br>Spiraled out <br><br>Still run like that child <br>Though now, it's overgrown <br>Branches whip my face <br>No trace, of home <br><br>I was afraid of monsters <br>Not on bonfire nights <br>I emerge from the darkness <br>Skin hot from the light <br><br>I was a afraid of monsters <br>Not on bonfire nights <br>Rise up from the darkness <br>Skin hot from the light <br><br>I'll go first, come what may <br>We're fearless again <br>Burst burst burst into flames <br>We're fearless again <br><br>I feel you by my side <br>We're never growing up <br>Climbing branch by branch <br>Straight up <br>To the top <br><br>Luminescent smile <br>Stare out at the flames <br>Dirt marks on my face <br>We're back again <br><br>Still running like a child <br>Running like a child <br>Still dreaming like a child <br>Dreaming like a child <br>Flames grow wild <br>Keep me warm inside]]></content><category term="Woodes" label="Woodes"/><category term="Bonfire" label="Bonfire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Woodes/Daggers__Knives/</id><title>Woodes - Daggers &amp; Knives - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:08:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:08:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Woodes/Daggers__Knives/" title="Woodes - Daggers &amp; Knives - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[At arms length you keep her <br>Say I need you, she'll be there <br>At arms length you keep me <br>You know my ways, try to read me <br><br>Soon enough 'though this balancing act has been fun <br>You'll decide, you'll decide on the one <br>Soon enough, 'though this road has been long <br>It's easy with her and I'm not the one <br><br>Oh oh oh <br>Daggers and knives <br>Subtle but simple <br>Effectively lies <br>Oh oh oh <br>But see this crown <br>I reign here still <br>I'm the queen of this town <br><br>Falling back into place <br>Twisted words, that shake <br>Through my bones <br>In my mouth <br>It's on the tip of my tongue <br>But no words come out <br><br>Soon enough though this balancing act has been fun <br>You'll decide, you'll decide on the on <br>Soon enough through this road has been long <br>It's easy with her and I'm not the one <br><br>Oh oh oh <br>Daggers and knives <br>Subtle but simple <br>Effectively lies <br>Oh oh oh <br>But see this crown <br>I reign here still <br>I'm the queen of this town <br><br>And I'll be fine <br>I'll be fine on my own <br>Though I love you you know <br>I can do it on my own <br>And I'll be fine <br>I'll be fine on my own <br>Though I love you you know <br>I can do this on my own <br><br>Oh oh oh <br>Daggers and knives <br>Subtle but simple <br>Effectively lies <br>Oh oh oh <br>But see this crown <br>I reign here still <br>I'm the queen of this town]]></content><category term="Woodes" label="Woodes"/><category term="Daggers &amp; Knives" label="Daggers &amp; Knives"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Woodes/Poison/</id><title>Woodes - Poison - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:08:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:08:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Woodes/Poison/" title="Woodes - Poison - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning round <br>Neat pirouettes <br>Eyes locked on the constant <br>Til I forget <br><br>Hold it <br>Deep breath <br>In and out until there's nothing left <br><br>Did I just drink poison <br>Is this a trick <br>Is your hand on the trigger <br>Is this it <br><br>Slowing down <br>I placed my bets <br>Thought I lost it <br>Well, I forget <br><br>Hold it <br>Deep breath <br>In and out til there's nothing left <br><br>Did I just drink poison <br>Is this a trick <br>Is your hand on the trigger <br>Is this it <br><br>Out of sight <br>Look what I made <br>I thought about it <br>Put it away <br><br>Locked in <br>Deep breath <br>No excuses, got nothing left <br><br>Did I just drink poison <br>No more tricks <br>My band's on the trigger <br>This is it]]></content><category term="Woodes" label="Woodes"/><category term="Poison" label="Poison"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Woodes/The_Thaw/</id><title>Woodes - The Thaw - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:08:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:08:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Woodes/The_Thaw/" title="Woodes - The Thaw - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[River flow <br>Takes me back <br>Deeper and deeper <br>Fresh coat of snow, broken sheet of ice <br>We move further and further apart <br><br>Longest time waiting for the light <br>The thaw <br>Shortest time drifting <br>A sudden night <br>It's early evening and I'm <br><br>Watching it fall, each flake <br>I watch it fall, should we walk away <br>Snow fall <br>The words I can't say <br>You hold me close <br>And I melt away <br><br>I think I know <br>You take me back <br>Deeper and deeper <br>This was a home <br>It's growing' dark <br>We move further and further apart <br><br>Longest time waiting for the light <br>The thaw <br>Shortest time drifting <br>A sudden night <br>It's early evening and I'm <br><br>Watching it fall, each flake <br>I watch it fall, should we walk away <br>Snow fall <br>The words I can't say <br>You hold me close <br>And I melt away <br><br>Flakes of snow fall on my nose <br>I mistook you for my love <br>Ghostly as your figure glows <br>Watch me as I turn and run <br><br>Flakes of snow fall on my nose <br>I mistook you for my love <br>Ghostly as your figure glows <br>Watch me as I turn and run <br><br>Watching it fall, each flake <br>I watch it fall, should we walk away <br>Snow fall <br>The words I can't say <br>You hold me close <br>And I melt away <br><br>Watching it fall, each flake <br>I watch it fall, should we walk away <br>Snow fall <br>The words I can't say <br>You hold me close <br>And I melt away <br><br>Watching, watching it fall <br>Watching, watching it fall <br>Watching, watching it fall <br>Watching, watching it fall <br>Watching, watching it fall <br>Watching, watching it fall <br>Watching, watching it fall <br>Watching, watching it fall]]></content><category term="Woodes" label="Woodes"/><category term="The Thaw" label="The Thaw"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Woodes/Rise/</id><title>Woodes - Rise - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:08:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:08:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Woodes/Rise/" title="Woodes - Rise - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One eye open <br>No rock left unturned <br>Like a drop in the ocean <br>I rise <br><br>And they say it might be witchcraft <br>When they saw her strength <br>Invisible armour to keep his words away <br><br>Oh oh, arms rise up she wakes <br>Oh oh, moves through the water and changes <br>Oh oh, arms rise up she stands <br>Oh oh, holding the fire in her hands <br><br>Both eyes open <br>She watches woodland burn <br>White cliffs against the ocean <br>It's high tide <br><br>And they say it might be witchcraft <br>When they heard the roar <br>Of the flames licking the fortress <br>Of love that stands no more <br><br>Oh oh, arms rise up she wakes <br>Oh oh, moves through the water and changes <br>Oh oh, arms rise up she stands <br>Oh oh, holding the fire in her hands <br><br>Oh oh, arms rise up she wakes <br>Oh oh, moves through the water and changes <br>Oh oh, arms rise up she stands <br>Oh oh, holding the fire in her hands <br><br>Rise up <br>She starts to rise up <br>She's going to rise up <br>She's going to rise up <br><br>As she dives into the water <br>Whispers of the flame <br>And they weight for her return <br>Oh but will she stay <br><br>Rise up <br>She starts to rise up <br>She's going to rise up <br>She starts to rise up <br><br>Rise up <br>She starts to rise up <br>She's going to rise up <br>She starts to rise up <br><br>Rise up <br>She starts to rise up]]></content><category term="Woodes" label="Woodes"/><category term="Rise" label="Rise"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아이동요/숫자_노래/</id><title>아이동요 - 숫자 노래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:10:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:10:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/%EC%88%AB%EC%9E%90_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="아이동요 - 숫자 노래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모두 모여서 선생님이랑 숫자놀이 다 함께 해보자 <br>일 이 삼 사 오 육 칠 팔 구 십 숫자놀이 정말로 재밌다 <br><br>손가락을 접으면서 세어보자 하나 둘 셋 넷 다섯 여섯 <br>일곱 여덟 아홉 열 재미있는 숫자 노래를 부르자]]></content><category term="아이동요" label="아이동요"/><category term="숫자 노래" label="숫자 노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/These_Words_Are_Everything/</id><title>Jon_Wayne - These Words Are Everything - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:11:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:11:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/These_Words_Are_Everything/" title="Jon_Wayne - These Words Are Everything - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1996 <br>It was raining, drops were cutting through the mist <br>I'm in the kitchen like a good kid <br>Hot chocolate <br>Drawing booklets for profit <br>Grandad had some quarters for my project <br>Ever since I had an honest audience I swore to God that I would body shit <br>Life is too short for modesty <br>I was telling myself, upon that balcony <br>My legs went through the bars steady swinging 'til the splinters came <br>Im aiming for the top <br>Whenever I'm dropping, mom even the mockups are hot <br>This shit is better than friendship <br>They never understand when I begin shit <br>I walk the lower field until the bell hits the wind <br>It's clicking like these groups of little kids when they get it in <br>But I don't need to play pretend when I play to win <br>Word to Benjamins <br>Word to everything, these words are everything <br>Or maybe words are just my only thing <br><br>2006 <br>Dilla died and I was living off his gift <br>I just heard Donuts at the Borders on the corner in La Habra I was over all these people tryna tell me my aspirations were goners <br>I wrote my poems so I could stay in my zone <br>Thinking Why go to church if I feel God in my home <br>Maybe, I write because I'm feeling odd in my bones <br>And when I exorcise this demon I'm not thinking of those <br>It's 2010 <br>I got some shows and I'm finally making friends <br>I'm on the cusp of something big and I can feel it <br>Everything has been building up to this moment I can steal it <br>I'm just a aphid in the crib speaking major <br>Lip service paid for <br>Showed the whole city what this Wayniac is great for <br>Word to the Kev machine <br>Word to everything, these words are everything <br>Or maybe words are just my only thing <br><br>2016 <br>I spent the last 2 years fucking up big dreams <br>You never know what you want until you get it <br>The future ain't set sometimes it's the little things winning over these checks <br>I had the chance to sell out and I told them 'bout <br>How words are everything, much bigger than gold clouds <br>If I'm a shell of a man my words are empty <br>Ringing through the halls of my bones for near a century <br>Don't lecture me <br>I see that selling soul get better things <br>And maybe its just fear that's keeping me from better scenes <br>But i'm here, one piece <br>An uncle and a beast <br>When they hit play they know that 'imma feast so rest in peace <br><br>Married to the game, but it's complicated <br>I know just how it works if I was smart I'd get hella cake <br>Like if I throw a hook upon this beat it'd get hella plays <br>If I just said yes to all these fools I'd get hella paid <br>If only I could keep my mouth shut no enemies <br>But I don't see the point in knowing truth and not set it free <br>I can't both express myself then play the game <br>If you just can't handle what I say then don't say my name <br>Keep it out your mouth like a foot <br>Rappers babble like a young adult book <br>Look, my trifocal looks could kill some dumb occult crooks <br>Burn a skull, cook <br>If I come out retirement, I got em all shook <br>Let me shake em then <br>Paperless, stirring up emotions with my paper pen <br>If you getting this for free what you pay for then <br>Word to friends and them <br>Word to everything <br>But when I die, I know my words will be my only thing]]></content><category term="Jon Wayne" label="Jon Wayne"/><category term="These Words Are Everything" label="These Words Are Everything"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Hills_Feat_Zeroh/</id><title>Jon_Wayne - Hills (Feat. Zeroh) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:11:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:11:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Hills_Feat_Zeroh/" title="Jon_Wayne - Hills (Feat. Zeroh) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I be running up the hill now <br>Digging my heels into this wheelbarrow <br>Trying to build house for my famil, yo <br>Before I peel out the hill, I push it real loud <br>Feel love, it was so much, we didn't have to say it though <br><br>I be running up the hill now <br>Digging my heels into this wheelbarrow <br>Just trying to build house for my famil, yo <br>I peel out the hill, I push it real loud <br>Feel love, it was so much, we didn't have to say it though <br>Though, though, though]]></content><category term="Jon Wayne" label="Jon Wayne"/><category term="Hills (Feat. Zeroh)" label="Hills (Feat. Zeroh)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Blue_Green_Feat_Low_Leaf/</id><title>Jon_Wayne - Blue Green (Feat. Low Leaf) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:12:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:12:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Blue_Green_Feat_Low_Leaf/" title="Jon_Wayne - Blue Green (Feat. Low Leaf) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I just cancelled my tour <br>I just woke up in bed <br>I had last nights dinner on the sheets <br>I had a burning in my throat I couldn't swallow <br>I had shuffled to the mirror and saw death over my head <br>If i was sleeping on my back I would've died <br>Jameson in my blood <br>Jameson in my eyes <br>Jameson on my mind <br>I know I need to stop <br>But if I'm flying, it's Jameson on the ride <br>This how I'm making money but a cost to my life <br>Digging in my arms over turbulent flights <br>Walking down the aisle blood from where I scratched <br>Stewardess looking worried but she's too afraid to ask <br>So if you find me in the state please give me two <br>Its just me slipping through these greens and these blues <br>I know that sounds foolish but who knew thatI'd be living the life <br>I barely knew but always dreamed of <br>And you sweep anything under these rugs to let 'em all know your name that's a dangerous drug <br>Runnin' a marathon but with batons and get gone when your asked to pass it on <br>Pass it on <br><br>I awaken to a new day <br>I create who I'm becoming <br>Connect to something <br>A journey through the desert <br>City and the tales they're running through these hills, now <br>I be running through these hills now <br>I be running through these hills now]]></content><category term="Jon Wayne" label="Jon Wayne"/><category term="Blue Green (Feat. Low Leaf)" label="Blue Green (Feat. Low Leaf)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Afraid_Of_Us_Feat_Zeroh/</id><title>Jon_Wayne - Afraid Of Us (Feat. Zeroh) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:12:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:12:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Afraid_Of_Us_Feat_Zeroh/" title="Jon_Wayne - Afraid Of Us (Feat. Zeroh) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was sitting in Japan when my nephew was born <br>Broke my damn heart when I wasn't there for him <br>It made me think about my life <br>And my order of operations <br>I was drunk at a show and fucked my boy's set up <br>It was a blessing when he checked me at the check in <br>I ain't never been the same and I'll never forget it <br>I've been the burden of my people <br>And alienating fans <br>Just thinking they would never understand <br>Really it's wavelength bringing us together in a way <br>So really I should be more open to two way <br>And if I ever did you something dirty, I do pray <br>I get another chance but this karma catching up in a true way <br>I've been so caught up in the lack of acceptance <br>I never focused on the man to accept <br>And if it's too late for a formal apology, I accept it x2 <br>You think of me less than I am but maybe that's a blessing <br>I just hope that I can spread my message <br>A to Z passing off to zeroh <br><br>Shit, all I want to say is put it down <br>Your position been compromised <br>Everything has a beginning and an end <br>I know glory'll take you dead or alive <br>In ruts fucked up off such and such <br>Is thus just because <br>You're afraid of us <br>Ya <br>So put it down <br>Put it down <br>x2 <br><br>All my life I was looking for love <br>Found it in Florida under the too hot sun <br>Took it for granted <br>Started to run <br>Became the man or a gun <br>But now I'm looking down the barrel of one <br>On my knees when I heard she could see my skin was empty <br>Please wake me when the self hatred is done <br>And I try but she reminds me of what I've become <br>Thought i knew myself but that knowing is done <br>I just hope that she still sees my love <br>And for that I just hope these old songs take off <br>I need a house <br>And a rack <br>For every leaf of grass on my big ass lawn <br>And as I see my family progress all I want is a daughter or son <br>Been around the world playing rapper is dumb <br>Fulfilling fantasies of a teenage me <br>And in the end it's my people bringing joy to the room <br>Some advice don't lose sight about where you're from <br>A to Z <br><br>Shit, all I want to say is put it down <br>Your position been compromised <br>Everything has a beginning and an end <br>I know glory'll take you dead or alive <br>In ruts fucked up off such and such <br>Is thus just because <br>You're afraid of us <br>Ya <br>So put it down <br>Put it down <br>x2 <br><br>Yo, look at these people <br>Counting on me when I can't even count on myself <br>Look at these homies <br>So sure of me when I'm not so sure of myself <br>I need help <br>But I'm too damn proud to stop the progress now <br>I need to slow down <br>But I need a good friend to come and tell me how <br>x6 <br><br>Shit, all I want to say is put it down <br>Your position been compromised <br>Everything has a beginning and an end <br>I know glory'll take you dead or alive <br>In ruts fucked up off such and such <br>Is thus just because <br>You're afraid of us <br>Ya <br>So put it down <br>Put it down <br>x2]]></content><category term="Jon Wayne" label="Jon Wayne"/><category term="Afraid Of Us (Feat. Zeroh)" label="Afraid Of Us (Feat. Zeroh)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Rainbow_Feat_Danny_Watts/</id><title>Jon_Wayne - Rainbow (Feat. Danny Watts) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:12:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:12:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Rainbow_Feat_Danny_Watts/" title="Jon_Wayne - Rainbow (Feat. Danny Watts) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yo, I've undersold what I'm going through <br>I'm pointing you and shedding light on what I'm coming to <br>The colors press me to the grayer states <br>Erasing the vigor I used to have <br>I figure if I do the math I grew for <br>Pressure existing in regions I never knew existed <br>I'm finding reasons to be submissive to new conditions <br>Maybe I was born for a regular life <br>My heart is like sediments sled in a bed of my plights <br>Let the rain fall down on top my feelings <br>I'm feeling like I should sliver inside a hole and quiver <br>Picture a plant that's at the bed of a river <br>Swaying to the flow but dying under a stigma <br>That it has to be a certain way <br>People plugging at its petals cause it's tucked away <br>I'm just pressing on the gas, running back until I crash <br>Inside the tunnel I molded for men to pass]]></content><category term="Jon Wayne" label="Jon Wayne"/><category term="Rainbow (Feat. Danny Watts)" label="Rainbow (Feat. Danny Watts)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/City_Lights/</id><title>Jon_Wayne - City Lights - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:12:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:12:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/City_Lights/" title="Jon_Wayne - City Lights - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I see my past highlighted by these city lights <br>I take the alleyways, grabbing on this battered mic <br>The dark shedded light <br>My peers after mine <br>I'm just hoping that they also love the afterlife <br>Either that or whatever is creeping after life <br>See, I'm a man tonight <br>I see these boys looking joyful with their toys <br>While I'm grabbing on my Samsonite <br>The smell of leather lingers <br>As I watch these calendars slip through my fingers <br>I don't wanna meet my maker, just make my meters <br>And keep them burning <br>And every day I have I hope they keep me learning <br>Reading these books, getting lost, feel at home like the search is my cause <br>And the music is my God speaking sermon after sermon <br>I see them all saluting, thank me for my service, I did it for me <br>But it keeps me going on and you can see what I see <br>Know an adolescent out there wanna be what I be <br>There's a price to a young'un <br>You most likely don't invite the kind of vices we brung in <br>Be it poison of the body or the kind you can't see cause it's creeping up behind <br>And if they don't have footing they can slip right in their mind <br>Torn apart by anxiety and ripples of ill <br>See I'm seeing it still <br>And I struggle with the deep end <br>Drowning in my thoughts but my body's breathing 'cause my nephew's still teething and I'd like to see him frequent <br>Dusting cobwebs on my way to speak to Jesus <br>That's who we pray to when our young mind was feening for a reason to the season <br>But the wind is blowing harsh tonight <br>Do I even need to tell you that it's raining <br>Or can you feel it <br>'Cause I can feel it <br><br>Verse 2 <br><br>It might as well be the blood of the Earth <br>And if it is then it's flooded my entity <br>These rivers got me caught between infinities <br>I feel the cold dirt cover every inch of me <br>Open my mouth and these demons are creeping into me <br>My lungs are full of sin <br>It felt better when I had this belly full of gin <br>It felt better when I couldn't wait for life to end <br>We had our moments, G <br>We never speak about the time we saw the end of things <br>We had a dryer in our hands and we missed the tub <br>I'm thankful every day <br>I thank our family who kept us going every way <br>Before the scene they helped me blossom to this fiend <br>I can taste the first sweat on my lips <br>To the time I had the first girl's head in my grip <br>Wasn't calling out the father <br>Thinking I'm a man, I'm a man <br>Little did you know that was never part of the plan <br>You ain't a man till you traveled through these sands in the hourglass <br>So listen close I need to tell you something deep]]></content><category term="Jon Wayne" label="Jon Wayne"/><category term="City Lights" label="City Lights"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Paper_Feat_Shango/</id><title>Jon_Wayne - Paper (Feat. Shango) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:12:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:12:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Paper_Feat_Shango/" title="Jon_Wayne - Paper (Feat. Shango) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[exhales <br><br>When I die, I wanna grow into a tree <br>I want 'em to bury me <br>Mixed in with soil and leaves <br>And when I'm stretched 'cross the land <br>And your son cuts me down <br>I wanna be the book your grandchildren read aloud <br>With the tape on my spine <br>I'm still proud <br>I want 'em to hand me down <br>And give me to Goodwill <br>And price me for a dollar <br>Still get shoplifted, hell <br>Torn open just to give a man shelter, shit <br>That's the world of my wishes <br>This paper my motivation <br>Money the sole witness <br>Bones are just branches saplings <br>Twisting, matching <br>Everything I had to live with <br>When the flower blooms <br>It's whatever I'm in tune with <br>That's what I hope you take pictures of <br>The line between misery and living breathing is thin enough <br>I struggle to be <br>The seed that I love <br>But <br>When the time comes <br><br>Rooted in the purpose and the prose <br>We hope whatever grows <br>Mirrors all the seeds you ever sowed <br>All the blessings, all the blessings, all the blessings <br>So when the time comes <br>And your vines run <br>And the mind numbs <br>The will define sums <br>In the divine Sun <br>That's filling my lungs <br>When the time comes <br><br>Look at these paper mache people <br>Construction paper skies <br>Newspaper brains <br>With the Moleskine eyes <br>All I need is one match to make 'em dance <br>Stick your hands in <br>They're just waiting for a chance to be candid <br>Maybe go up in flames like ya mans did <br>They don't know what they want <br>They're just asking <br>And still trying to act like they ran shit <br>Ok now maybe if you sketched out your body <br>You wouldn't have to declare yourself sorry <br>Don't put it on me <br>Not my fault I didn't shove you in the copy <br>I had to write my own book I did it sloppy <br><br>And if you fall on the ground, I ain't picking you up <br>And if you bury yourself, I ain't digging you up <br>And when you turn into dust, I ain't kicking you up <br>And when you get in my way, I'm just ripping you up <br>When the time comes <br><br>Rooted in the purpose and the prose <br>We hope whatever grows <br>Mirrors all the seeds you ever sowed <br>All the blessings, all the blessings, all the blessings <br>So when the time comes <br>And your vines run <br>And the mind numbs <br>The will define sums <br>In the divine Sun <br>That's filling my lungs <br>When the time comes]]></content><category term="Jon Wayne" label="Jon Wayne"/><category term="Paper (Feat. Shango)" label="Paper (Feat. Shango)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/The_Single/</id><title>Jon_Wayne - The Single - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:12:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:12:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/The_Single/" title="Jon_Wayne - The Single - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm on my Kool G hitting loosies in a Coogi in the booth <br>Don't sleep on me or suck this pillow and the piece <br>Don't speak on <br><br>fffffffff <br><br>Yo, you ready <br><br>Yup <br><br>Yo <br>I'm on my Kool G hitting loosies in a Coogi in the booth <br>Don't sleep on me or suck this pillow and the piece <br>Don't speak on me or what I be <br>You know I'm coming for these rings <br>I'm the w <br><br>fuck cut <br><br>I'm on my Kool G hitting loosies in a Coogi in the booth <br>Don't sleep on me or suck this pillow and the piece <br>Don't speak on me or what I be <br>You know I'm coming for these rings <br>I'm the <br><br>FUCK <br><br>Hey, you good man <br><br>Yup, yep, let's just keep it going]]></content><category term="Jon Wayne" label="Jon Wayne"/><category term="The Single" label="The Single"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Out_Of_Sight/</id><title>Jon_Wayne - Out Of Sight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:12:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:12:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Out_Of_Sight/" title="Jon_Wayne - Out Of Sight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My momma always told me I was never in the here and now <br>My head in the past, my feet in the future <br>My life, hang my head like a necklace <br>In the blink, no sheet <br>Next scene I'm just eating my breakfast <br>Isolation slowly feeling like it's house arrest <br>Bound from the scene that made me see what my credit gets <br>Puttin' health before career just to steer ahead <br>and burn a few bridges just to keep the ends mirrored <br>And in the end this mirrors getting strange <br>I'd never thought I'd ever see a change <br>Nobody pickin' up the phone <br>Makes me question if I ever did 'em wrong <br>Steady lying but I'd better be alone <br>And if I did I'd have to own up <br>Little did I know the cognac was keeping me from growing up <br>And my fear of flying keeping me from going up <br>And musical meditation is spiritually glowin' up <br><br>This is my work but it was just a diversion <br>When I was kicking the curb <br>Feels like I'm sinning when I be seeing the light <br>Cause now I'm working on this living just to rap about life <br>That's some backwards commitment <br>And on the way I know I gave away some friends <br>And every day I wish that we could speak again <br>But every time I wanna make it right I freeze up <br>and the visions of the shadows of my demons who went out of sight <br><br>They went out of sight <br>Until now <br><br>Sometimes <br>When you end a build you end up destroying things <br>The kind you hate so much you end up enjoying things <br>Like how we break it up to keep it moving forward when we sit inside the new box but think about the older things <br>I'm just a man playing god with my thoughts <br>Over pans and pots <br>He scotch rocks and acting like Novocaine <br>Might as well fix the grill spill the spray until the day that my brains cold <br>That's what I told the rain <br>Pre apocalyptic LA everyday <br>Yeah, I keep myself company on the motorway <br>Like the hunchback of notre dame <br>Ringing dead radio waves <br>Still feel this weight from the barricade <br>Tryna feel like a human among these animals <br>Tryna feel some community in this solitude <br>And as I hit the nuke button once again I can see that <br>I don't have a single friend <br><br>This is my work but it was just a diversion <br>When I was kicking the curb <br>Feels like I'm sinning when I be seeing the light <br>Cause now I'm working on this living just to rap about life <br>That's some backwards commitment <br>And on the way I know I gave away some friends <br>And every day I wish that we could speak again <br>But every time I wanna make it right I freeze up <br>and the visions of the shadows of my demons who went out of sight <br><br>Until now <br>They went out of sight <br>Until now <br>They went out of sight]]></content><category term="Jon Wayne" label="Jon Wayne"/><category term="Out Of Sight" label="Out Of Sight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Human_Condition/</id><title>Jon_Wayne - Human Condition - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:12:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:12:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Human_Condition/" title="Jon_Wayne - Human Condition - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Put my mind in my head <br>And my head in my hands <br>And my hands on this body <br>And my body on land <br>And this land on this earth <br>And this earth in the system <br>And the system in my thoughts <br>And my thoughts into wishes <br>And this wishes are just dreams <br>These dreams are just goals <br>These goals <br>Make a man wanna be more than that <br>And the ghosts just laugh <br>And hope that I don't pass <br>This is an ode to my opposition <br>I know my flow's full of contradiction <br>And good luck getting the right brain to play with the left <br>But hand over breast <br>I'm gonna try as long as plant life's sustaining my breath <br>The very same God used for badminton with Death <br>That hot smog riddled Los Angeles breath <br>That hard, heavy hitting old Anakin breath <br>And opposition get that old mannequin rest <br>Cause after this they know there's no more expanding their chest <br>Like <br><br>Watch me hang to the rim as these people feel the grim <br>My people kicking buckets like sighs <br>And that's a fine commitment to the human condition <br>You say committing sin <br>But I say stupid decisions <br>You'll throw tomato in the face of bravado <br>Not my fault that the Model T is parked in the pothole <br>Get out my grotto <br>Before I get out the bottle <br>Get out my face <br>I don't wanna see a doctor or hospital <br>I'm fine and this age is just a number <br>I'm seeing triple digits, no wonder <br>My eyesight is shit <br>My mind is asunder <br>My hands are in the cup <br>And my body is under <br>A lot of pressure with this poisonous flask <br>No measure when I take off the mask <br>Keep my soul under glass <br>The devil's shopping through the window <br>Since I was hanging loose with these lame ass kiddos <br>It's foggy through the Grey Goose and Gray Gas indo <br>For real]]></content><category term="Jon Wayne" label="Jon Wayne"/><category term="Human Condition" label="Human Condition"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Live_From_The_Fuck_You/</id><title>Jon_Wayne - Live From The Fuck You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:12:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:12:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Live_From_The_Fuck_You/" title="Jon_Wayne - Live From The Fuck You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yo man, um, are you Jonwayne bro Are you Jonwayne <br>Yeah <br>Oh shit man, what's up <br>Look, I don't know who you are, bro, but I'm with this girl <br>she says she knows who you are, I think she's a big fan <br>But, um, she says you rap and I'm not really seeing it dog <br>Um, yeah, no I don't really look like a rapper but yeah I do <br>So you rap <br>I do rap Yeah, I make rap music, yeah <br>Really <br>Yeah <br>Really <br>Yeah It's not that great but it's it's cool I'm glad she likes it <br>Alright man I mean, I'm not really seeing it but uh <br>It's ok I mean, you know, you can YouTube it later if you want, you know <br>Alright man, well look, it's her birthday <br>You know, I'm in the club, she's a fan, so <br>it would mean a lot to me and I know it would mean a lot to her <br>I understand, and I'm kinda aw man <br>I'm with my friends and I don't wanna do this right now <br>If you spit a rap for her real quick <br>No I don't want to, like, it's a thing <br>Like, what do you do for a living Office <br>I work at Radio Shack, bro <br>You work at RadioShack <br>Well, go get me some cables right now You see what I mean <br>Look bro, I don't want it to be like that, yo <br>I'm not trying to like come at you I just, I'm just saying like <br>You're not going to leave me alone, are you <br>I mean it's her birthday, dog I'm just saying <br>I'm with my boys right now <br>I see the boys, and look I'm not trying to break it up <br><br>Ok, ok, alright alright, check check <br>I'm coming to you live from the <br>Don't ask me for nothing <br>I'm bout to kill this mic with the <br>You need to stop frontin <br>Coming to you live from the <br>I could put your future in my duffle <br>And still shoot you off some classics in the scuffle <br><br>Live from the fuck you <br>Live from the <br>Jon, you know we never really loved you <br>We're just touching base for the hook up <br>Looking for some daps like a piece to the puzzle <br>Get in the huddle <br>I'm about to bust this verse <br>So here's a little story bout the way I make it hurt <br>The way I make you learn how not to approach a man <br>Who's suffering for his work <br>Like a monkey in the circus <br>Force in his power make a rapper short circuit <br>I'm not the favor for this party but fuck it yo <br><br>It's live from the <br>I'll crush this mic with the <br>yeah <br>Just admire me from afar <br>Dap with the <br>I appreciate your love and support <br>But keep it moving before I ruin me for you <br>One love and all that, I just humored you <br>Now let me get back <br>Ok, peace, thank you <br><br>That was fucking ill, dude What the fuck <br>Alright man, I gotta go Peace Yeah, alright man, peace <br>What the fuck Yo, did you guys hear that man Yo, Jonwayne]]></content><category term="Jon Wayne" label="Jon Wayne"/><category term="Live From The Fuck You" label="Live From The Fuck You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Ted_Talk/</id><title>Jon_Wayne - Ted Talk - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:12:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:12:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jon_Wayne/Ted_Talk/" title="Jon_Wayne - Ted Talk - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You never seen a man so calm in your life <br>They afraid of this might <br>And I got the type of mind to grind into that white light <br>I rock the mic inside the china shop and spit that bull shit, this ain't no bullshit <br>It's eating past after the stomach full shit <br>No eating ass, no groceries, I ate at restaurants <br>They serve me well since I'm a baby of the Kant renaissance <br>You may recall my marvelous reconnaissance <br>I never forget, like elephants on 4chan <br>Remember I'm a poor man, but got a fucking kingdom up in here <br>Where the beer flows like memes, seeded without a peer <br>See I had it up to here, all these doubters in my ear <br>Tryna tell me I don't have the whole world up on my spear what you do <br>I Van Gogh 'em, pretend I don't know 'em <br>Too busy showboatin' to roast 'em, the flames floatin' <br>No jokes, see my quotes remain potent <br>Even in the casket, I'll be one to close it <br>I'm a poet and I know it, see I could do some good <br>But these demons in my ear make me feel misunderstood <br>Lord knows, my intentions are hood <br>And I rub it in a little bit more than I should <br>But what would you do if you were great and you knew it <br>I put up a page, I get in my range <br>I open up a vein and let a river run through it <br>You call it music <br>that's close enough <br><br>Hoe, one two 'til my voice is hoarse <br>Hoe, one two 'til my voice is hoarse <br>Hoe, one two 'til my voice is hoarse <br>Guaranteed to rock, rock, rock the mic <br>Hoe, one two 'til my voice is hoarse <br>Hoe, one two 'til my voice is hoarse <br>Hoe, one two 'til my voice is hoarse <br>Then take a pause <br><br>I get my dinner on from intercom psalms and scratch an itching inner palm <br>Give a Ted Talk about shitting on 'em and spitting on and on <br>They wonder what arithmetic I'm riffing on <br>They wonder what this written on <br>since when he get his Merv Griffin on <br>I wonder who I'm pissing off <br>Bump missives in the whip, run crystals for the glisten <br>Dump crystal down the sink up in the kitchen <br>I run missiles in my whistler <br>Children for my pisser <br>When these women call me Mr J know I came to slay like a gay man <br>Shade like a Ray Ban, you know I'm here to stay <br>You can find me 'round the way like a waistband <br>Writing 'bout my stay on some 'how to be a man when you hate man' <br>LA, the home of human spray tan <br>Heard it from the grapevine in that gray van, with many a gray band <br>I give a damn on some frankly my dear, whoever made me had some great ideas <br>My parents built me, yeah I'm straight IKEA <br>Had this voice to God since I was five feet uh <br>Drinking wine, eating divine pita <br>Kissing that cross, now they kissing my crosshairs <br>When I rap on beats that sound like a video game boss lair shit <br>In my pauses I hear Ric Flair trippin' <br>Yeah my quips could carry trips like some big bear visions <br>Yeah these words are so sharp I give some thin air stitches <br>Got a hole in space time where I state my business <br><br>Hoe, one two 'til my voice is hoarse <br>Hoe, one two 'til my voice is hoarse <br>Hoe, one two 'til my voice is hoarse <br>Guaranteed to rock, rock, rock the mic <br>Hoe, one two 'til my voice is hoarse <br>Hoe, one two 'til my voice is hoarse <br>Hoe, one two 'til my voice is hoarse <br>Then take a pause, and you know, of course]]></content><category term="Jon Wayne" label="Jon Wayne"/><category term="Ted Talk" label="Ted Talk"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Funeral_Advantage/Lakewood_Mausoleum/</id><title>Funeral_Advantage - Lakewood Mausoleum - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:14:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:14:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Funeral_Advantage/Lakewood_Mausoleum/" title="Funeral_Advantage - Lakewood Mausoleum - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Underneath the saw <br>You don't have to make love so hard <br>This used to be a sacred place for us <br>You could lose them <br>Oh but I'd never know that I threw it all away <br>I've had enough cocaine <br>Here at the fire field <br>But at The Lakewood Mausoleum <br>You can know them <br><br>So what's the point in all this <br>There isn't point in us living again <br>How lucky I was to have had something <br>that made saying goodbye so quick <br><br>I don't know why you think hell is so far <br>She used to whisper ancient things to us <br>I couldn't control myself, she knew I was afraid <br>She asked me do you know them <br><br>I'd like to know it all <br>I guess I'll see you when I see you all down there <br>If you look closely you can see them all <br><br>Do you think that you deserve it <br>Down at The Lakewood Mausoleum]]></content><category term="Funeral Advantage" label="Funeral Advantage"/><category term="Lakewood Mausoleum" label="Lakewood Mausoleum"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Funeral_Advantage/We_Lost_Our_Home/</id><title>Funeral_Advantage - We Lost Our Home - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:15:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:15:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Funeral_Advantage/We_Lost_Our_Home/" title="Funeral_Advantage - We Lost Our Home - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't want you <br>It's no fair that I can't bring you <br>If I could go across I'd keep it inside <br>This was the last lie <br>You swore this was the last time <br>But the first half was so hard <br><br>So I'll melt again <br>I had a feeling I'd felt again <br>I had this reason to know that I'd slowly choose to walk away again <br><br>I'm mad as hell <br>I'm standing at your back door and I'm waiting for you to come out <br>What do you need, for me to get clean <br>And for the cuts on all your fingers to melt <br>Yeah you'll get them back <br><br>I don't get you <br>How could they fucking like you <br>You talk about the safety of being alone <br>I wish that you'd talk more about coming home again <br><br>Yeah, we'll get them back]]></content><category term="Funeral Advantage" label="Funeral Advantage"/><category term="We Lost Our Home" label="We Lost Our Home"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Funeral_Advantage/Shining/</id><title>Funeral_Advantage - Shining - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:15:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:15:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Funeral_Advantage/Shining/" title="Funeral_Advantage - Shining - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A Delight in your bed <br>And to think that I would leave you here <br>I'll think back to all the moments in those places you won't go near <br><br>Too young we're amateurs <br>Too stupid to know we were <br>Too drunk to know I was still alive <br>Too young we're amateurs <br>Too stupid to know we were <br>Too young to know we were terrified so I risked you out the back door <br><br>Do you still think it's immature <br>Would you still stay with fuck the thought of her <br>Would you still stay always and forever tonight <br><br>So let me take you out tonight]]></content><category term="Funeral Advantage" label="Funeral Advantage"/><category term="Shining" label="Shining"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Funeral_Advantage/The_Hanging_Cage/</id><title>Funeral_Advantage - The Hanging Cage - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:15:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:15:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Funeral_Advantage/The_Hanging_Cage/" title="Funeral_Advantage - The Hanging Cage - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My eyes were on you before, there was no anyone else <br>I think that someone might have disappointed your heart in your formative years <br>And I was only trying, calmly, to explain it to you <br>I swear you died when I was 16 but now you're right here <br><br>Holding me up, yeah you keep holding me then running away <br>I searched the whole world trying to find you, I wasted all my time to remind you <br>That I was making it up, control is under us and floating away <br>How many minutes underwater do you think it would take <br><br>I'd like to go back before we ever had a chance <br>You opened your heart wide but I was standing there, stupid <br>And I was using under pretext of illusion to prove <br>That I could use the heating in this house to make a fire out of you]]></content><category term="Funeral Advantage" label="Funeral Advantage"/><category term="The Hanging Cage" label="The Hanging Cage"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Funeral_Advantage/CEOT7K/</id><title>Funeral_Advantage - C.E.O.T.7.K. - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:15:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:15:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Funeral_Advantage/CEOT7K/" title="Funeral_Advantage - C.E.O.T.7.K. - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Is it impossible to pretend you're not alone <br>Or is it harder because I don't try <br>Beside you, I've reduced to <br>An amputee, dead, always here but never again <br>I am at rest now trying desperately and still hoping to fit in <br><br>Bury me in earth's hands <br>The birds told me something that I don't understand <br>Nothing has changed, we're still on track <br>This world gave me nothing, so I'll give nothing back <br><br>Is it a problem to abstain from relief for so long <br>You said I made you feel sick so I swallowed <br>Inside you, I felt used too <br>And if you see Dan tell him that I'm looking for him <br>He is a ghost now trying desperately and is longing to fit in <br><br>Bury me in earth's hands <br>The birds told me something that I don't understand <br>God please show me anything, 'cause I'm your punching bag <br>This world gave me nothing, so I'll give nothing back]]></content><category term="Funeral Advantage" label="Funeral Advantage"/><category term="C.E.O.T.7.K." label="C.E.O.T.7.K."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Funeral_Advantage/Please_Help_Me/</id><title>Funeral_Advantage - Please Help Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:15:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:15:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Funeral_Advantage/Please_Help_Me/" title="Funeral_Advantage - Please Help Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It was starting to go wrong <br>I saw you can't be alone <br>So I bought some flowers without you <br>The realtor's showing the house <br>Do you need help moving things out <br>I'd like to be there just so you could choose <br>You said I made you feel alone <br>I thought something real was shown <br>I found an apartment near by <br>So maybe we could still try <br>I don't deserve it but I caught a glimpse <br>And it's my fault because I ruined this <br><br>There was never another <br>And since the time that you asked me <br>Do the dead hate the living <br>It was supposed to be a safe place <br>No matter what they should say <br>It's sad that she's still getting followed around <br>I looked into your heart <br>Said you were scared to have kids because the place you grew up in <br>She said you don't understand some things don't work out as planned <br>This place was sacred, now we'll bury it <br><br>So is it too much for me to ask <br>But I miss those days when you gave back <br>And I thank god that I'm still alive]]></content><category term="Funeral Advantage" label="Funeral Advantage"/><category term="Please Help Me" label="Please Help Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Manse/Rising_Sun_Feat_Chris_Jones_Radio_Edit/</id><title>Manse - Rising Sun (Feat. Chris Jones) (Radio Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:17:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:17:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Manse/Rising_Sun_Feat_Chris_Jones_Radio_Edit/" title="Manse - Rising Sun (Feat. Chris Jones) (Radio Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When light fades <br>When hearts break <br>Just hold your tears, life will still go on <br><br>Let's dream away <br>Turn our world around <br><br>It's our time <br>To break free <br>And runaway from this world we know <br>It's time for change <br>Leave your fears behind <br><br>The rising sun will guide us <br>lighting up the place <br>Where we are as one <br>All day long <br>Are you down with us in the rising sun <br>Are you down with us in the rising sun <br><br>Are you down with us in the rising sun <br>Are you down with us in the rising sun <br>Are you down with us in the rising sun <br><br>When night fades <br>When stars shade <br>We find a way to survive this way <br>Just walk away <br>Live for here and now <br>It's our time <br>To break free <br>And runaway from this world we know <br>It's time for change <br>Leave your fears behind <br><br>The rising sun will guide us <br>lighting up the place <br>Where we are as one <br>All day long <br>Are you down with us in the rising sun <br>Are you down with us in the rising sun <br><br>Are you down with us in the rising sun <br>Are you down with us in the rising sun <br>Are you down with us in the rising sun]]></content><category term="Manse" label="Manse"/><category term="Rising Sun (Feat. Chris Jones) (Radio Edit)" label="Rising Sun (Feat. Chris Jones) (Radio Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임재웅/겁이나_Feat_사라/</id><title>임재웅 - 겁이나 (Feat. 사라) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T23:19:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T23:19:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9E%AC%EC%9B%85/%EA%B2%81%EC%9D%B4%EB%82%98_Feat_%EC%82%AC%EB%9D%BC/" title="임재웅 - 겁이나 (Feat. 사라) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가끔 겁이나 <br>너로 시작해 너로 끝나는 <br>내 하루에 네가 없어진다면 <br>난 어떨까 <br>하루하루를 의미 없이 <br>보내진 않을까 <br>나를 아껴주는 <br>나를 생각하는 너의 진심들이 <br>불안한 마음을 <br>나의 마음 안엔 <br>이미 온통 너로 가득해져 버려서 <br>무의미 해져 <br>그래서 겁이나 <br>이런 사랑 <br>다시는 하지 않겠다고 <br>다짐했었는데 <br>나를 아껴주는 <br>나를 생각하는 너의 진심들이 <br>불안한 마음을 <br>나의 마음 안엔 <br>이미 온통 너로 가득해져 버려서 <br>무의미 해져 <br>그래서 겁이나 <br>그렇게 상처받고 <br>아파했으면서도 <br>너라면 다시 한번 온전히 <br>나의 마음을 드러내도 <br>괜찮을 것 같다는 그런 생각이 <br>매일매일 들곤 해 <br>너의 마지막이 <br>나의 마지막이 <br>너의 마지막이 나의 마지막이 <br>서로였으면 해 <br>그대를 사랑해 <br>마지막 바람은 <br>우리란 단어가 <br>영원했으면 해 <br>우리란 단어가 <br>영원했으면 해 <br>]]></content><category term="임재웅" label="임재웅"/><category term="겁이나 (Feat. 사라)" label="겁이나 (Feat. 사라)"/></entry></feed>