<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:49+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amy_Shark/Blood_Brothers/</id><title>Amy Shark - Blood Brothers - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:12:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:12:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amy_Shark/Blood_Brothers/" title="Amy Shark - Blood Brothers - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We see eye to eye <br>Happy to jump the line <br>See you in 3D <br>Cut my hand gently <br>Helping you make your bed <br>Waiting inside your head <br>You're giving away the ending <br>We should stop pretending <br><br>Doc says, Girl, take one pill <br>And you whisper double that, double that <br>What was I like before you <br>Well I can't answer that, answer that <br>Wrap me up in secrets <br>And one day, we'll let it out, let it out <br>I can kiss you for free now <br>For free now <br><br>Why, why, why I feel like a million dollar bill <br>Hanging off your arm so chill <br>Hell no, I'm not like the others <br>We're the only blood brothers <br>Why, why, why I feel like a million dollar bill <br>Hanging off your arm so chill <br>How might we tell your mother <br>That I'm your little blood brother <br><br>You sit in my car <br>Like some superstar <br>On the count of 3 <br>Lean in, check to listen <br>To the woods, it's me and you <br>And you like my uniform <br>I start work at 1PM <br>So we just fuck around 'til then <br><br>Doc says, Girl, take one pill <br>And you whisper double that, double that <br>What was I like before you <br>Well I can't answer that, answer that <br>Wrap me up in secrets <br>And one day, we'll let it out, let it out <br>I can kiss you for free now <br>For free now <br><br>Why, why, why I feel like a million dollar bill <br>Hanging off your arm so chill <br>Hell no, I'm not like the others <br>We're the only blood brothers <br>Why, why, why I feel like a million dollar bill <br>Hanging off your arm so chill <br>How might we tell your mother <br>That I'm your little blood brother <br><br>All you are, all I said <br>Couldn't break apart and you're a little more dead <br>I feel my words won't work now, it's all I have <br>I want it, I want it, I want it more <br><br>Why, why, why I feel like a million dollar bill <br>Hanging off your arm so chill <br>Hell no, I'm not like the others <br>We're the only blood brothers <br>Why, why, why I feel like a million dollar bill <br>Hanging off your arm so chill <br>How might we tell your mother <br>That I'm your little blood brother <br>That I'm your little blood brother <br>That I'm your little blood brother]]></content><category term="Amy Shark" label="Amy Shark"/><category term="Blood Brothers" label="Blood Brothers"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amy_Shark/Weekends/</id><title>Amy Shark - Weekends - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:12:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:12:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amy_Shark/Weekends/" title="Amy Shark - Weekends - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You ban me from sleeping pills and codeine <br>I'm at my best, just even knowing <br>You're coming around, you're coming around <br>You switch from vodka, lime and soda <br>And I hate every girl that's ever known ya <br>And you know a lot about me, it's more than I can stand <br><br>Only on weekends we feel the love <br>Only on weekends this happens to us <br>Only on weekends I have no room for anyone else, but you <br><br>And I took your number quicker than my next breath <br>I call your house phone just to listen, to hear what your life might sound like <br>What your life might sound like <br><br>Only on weekends we feel the love <br>Only on weekends this happens to us <br>Only on weekends I have no room for anyone else, but you <br>Only on weekends we feel the same <br>Only on weekends is what we do <br>Only on weekends I have no room for anyone else, but you <br><br>There's a place for us <br>There's a tiny little room for two <br>And it's crystallised in my mind, that tiny little room <br>With you <br>Only on weekends <br><br>Only on weekends we feel the love <br>Only on weekends this happens to us <br>Only on weekends I have no room for anyone else, but you <br>For anyone else, but you <br>Only on weekends <br>Only on weekends <br>On weekends I have no room for anyone else, but you]]></content><category term="Amy Shark" label="Amy Shark"/><category term="Weekends" label="Weekends"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amy_Shark/Adore/</id><title>Amy Shark - Adore - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:12:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:12:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amy_Shark/Adore/" title="Amy Shark - Adore - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm just gonna stand with my bag hanging off my left arm <br>I'm just gonna walk home kicking stones at parked cars <br>But I had a great night, 'cause you kept rubbing against my arm <br>I'm just gonna stand with my bag hanging off my left arm <br><br>Get me a drink, I get drunk off one sip, just so I can adore you <br>I want the entire street out of town just so I can be alone with you <br>Now go when you're ready <br>My head's getting heavy, pressed against your arm <br>I adore you <br><br>All of my money is spent on these nights, just so we can hang out <br>Squeezing in and out of these dresses, I wanna be found by you <br>Found by you <br><br>Get me a drink, I get drunk off one sip, just so I can adore you <br>I want the entire street out of town just so I can be alone with you <br>Now go when you're ready <br>My head's getting heavy, pressed against your arm <br>I adore you, I adore you <br><br>I kick the gutter in tight shorts, basketball courts <br>Watch me, watch him talk to girls <br>I'm known as a right hand slugger <br>Anybody else wanna touch my lover <br><br>Get me a drink, I get drunk off one sip, just so I can adore you <br>I want the entire street out of town just so I can be alone with you <br>Now go when you're ready <br>My head's getting heavy, pressed against your arm <br>Just to adore you, I adore you]]></content><category term="Amy Shark" label="Amy Shark"/><category term="Adore" label="Adore"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amy_Shark/Drive_You_Mad/</id><title>Amy Shark - Drive You Mad - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:12:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:12:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amy_Shark/Drive_You_Mad/" title="Amy Shark - Drive You Mad - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Running away <br>How i felt like this yesterday <br>And if there's a problem, you'd want to know <br>Losing my shadow <br><br>Even though you say you won't lie down <br>I'll ask every night to wear you out <br>Make me believe one day i'll be great <br>Keep me in your heart for old times sake <br><br>I need love <br>I'm enough, i'm enough <br>I'm enough to drive you mad <br>In your arms, in your arms <br>In your arms i needed that <br>Believe me <br><br>Sleep on the grass <br>You take me hand i take you way too fast <br>You said you feel like there's nothing you can't say <br>And i felt that yesterday <br><br>Even though you say you won't lie down <br>I'll ask every night to wear you out <br>Make me believe one day i'll be great <br>Keep me in your heart for old times sake <br><br>I need love <br>I'm enough, i'm enough <br>I'm enough to drive you mad <br>In your arms, in your arms <br>In your arms i needed that <br>Believe me <br><br>Running away <br>How i felt like this yesterday <br><br>We stole your love <br>I'm enough, i'm enough <br>I'm enough to drive you mad <br>In your arms, in your arms <br>In your arms i needed that <br>Oooh believe me <br><br>I'm enough, i'm enough <br>I'm enough to drive you mad <br>I'm enough, i'm enough <br>I'm enough to drive you mad <br>Oooh believe me]]></content><category term="Amy Shark" label="Amy Shark"/><category term="Drive You Mad" label="Drive You Mad"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/Let_Me_Love_You_More/</id><title>Misty Edwards - Let Me Love You More - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:13:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:13:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/Let_Me_Love_You_More/" title="Misty Edwards - Let Me Love You More - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm in love with a Man <br>I'm in love with a Stranger <br>I'm in love with my Maker <br>Whom I have never seen <br>I'm in love with a Lamb <br>I'm in love with a Lion <br>I'm in love with my Savior <br>Whom I have yet to know <br><br>Oh, won't You let me love You more? <br>This is all that I desire <br>Won't You let me love You more <br>This is all that I require <br>Won't You let me love You more <br>This is my deepest heart's desire <br>Won't You let me love You more <br>Still more and more <br><br>For You could give to me the gift of walking on water <br>And maybe, maybe I will raise the dead <br>But I have one life to live <br>And all I have to give to You is love <br>I have one life to live <br>And all I have to give to You is love <br><br>And if I never walk on water <br>If I never see the miracles <br>If I never hear your voice so loud <br>Just knowing that You love me <br>Is enough to keep me here <br>Just hearing those words is enough <br>Is enough to satisfy <br><br><br><br>You do, You do <br>You satisfy <br>I couldn't leave even if a tried <br>I must have You <br>I must have You <br>I must have You <br><br>Oh, won't You let me love You more? <br>This is all that I desire <br>Won't You let me love You more <br>This is all that I require <br>Won't You let me love You more <br>This is my deepest heart's desire <br>Won't You let me love You more <br>Still more and more <br><br>When it's all been said <br>And when it's all been done <br>When the race is run <br>Well, it all comes down to love, love, love]]></content><category term="Misty Edwards" label="Misty Edwards"/><category term="Let Me Love You More" label="Let Me Love You More"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/I_Will_Waste_My_Life/</id><title>Misty Edwards - I Will Waste My Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:13:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:13:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/I_Will_Waste_My_Life/" title="Misty Edwards - I Will Waste My Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I will waste my life <br>I'll be tested and tried <br>With no regrets inside of me <br>Just to find I'm at your feet <br>Let me find I'm at your feet <br><br>I leave my father's house, and <br>I leave my Mother <br>I leave all I have known, and <br>I'll have no other <br><br>For I am in love with you <br>And there is no cost <br>I am in love with you <br>And there is no loss <br>I am in love with you <br>I want to take your name <br>I am in love with you <br>I want to cling to you, Jesus <br>Just let me cling to you, Jesus <br><br>I say goodbye to my father, my mother <br>I turn my back on every other lover, and I <br>Press on, yes I press on <br>I say goodbye to my father, my mother <br>I turn my back on every other lover, and I press on, yes I press on <br><br>For I am in love with you <br>And there is no cost <br>I am in love with you <br>And there is no loss <br>I am in love with you <br>I want to take your name <br>I am in love with you <br>I want to cling to you, Jesus <br>Just let me cling to you, Jesus <br>I want to cling to you...]]></content><category term="Misty Edwards" label="Misty Edwards"/><category term="I Will Waste My Life" label="I Will Waste My Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/My_Confession_I_Will_Follow_The_Lamb/</id><title>Misty Edwards - My Confession (I Will Follow The Lamb) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:13:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:13:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/My_Confession_I_Will_Follow_The_Lamb/" title="Misty Edwards - My Confession (I Will Follow The Lamb) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I will follow the Lamb wherever He goes <br>Wherever He goes I will follow Him <br><br>There's only one way to the Father <br>There's only one truth <br>There's only one light in the darkness <br><br>He's not just a teacher <br>He's not one of many <br>He's the very Son of God <br>And I will follow Him <br><br>(I'll go down with Him)]]></content><category term="Misty Edwards" label="Misty Edwards"/><category term="My Confession (I Will Follow The Lamb)" label="My Confession (I Will Follow The Lamb)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/People_Get_Ready/</id><title>Misty Edwards - People Get Ready - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:13:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:13:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/People_Get_Ready/" title="Misty Edwards - People Get Ready - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can hear the rhythm <br>Of the Lion of the tribe of Judah <br><br>He's doing a new thing <br>So we're singing a new song <br><br>He's not a baby in a manger anymore <br>He's not a broken man on a cross <br>He didn't stay in the grave <br>And He's not staying in heaven forever! <br><br>He's alive <br>He's alive <br>He's alive <br>He's alive! <br><br>People get ready! <br>Jesus is coming! <br><br>We join in the song of the ages <br>It's a new song <br>It's a new song <br>It's a new song <br><br>We say to the One who was slain <br>"You have proven Your love <br>And You have shown us, shown us <br>That You can be trusted." <br><br>So take the scroll and open <br>And open, and open the seals <br>We trust You, Jesus <br>And we want you to come back <br>So take the scroll and open the seals <br>So take the scroll and open the seals <br><br>I can hear the rhythm <br>Of the Lion of the tribe of Judah <br><br>He's doing a new thing <br>So we're singing a new song <br><br>He's not a baby in a manger anymore <br>He's not a broken man on a cross <br>He didn't stay in the grave <br>And He's not staying in heaven forever! <br><br>He's alive <br>He's alive <br>He's alive <br>He's alive! <br><br>People get ready! <br>Jesus is coming! <br><br>People walking around <br>With their fingers in the their ears <br>Singing, "Da da da da da." <br>"I don't want to hear the sound of the coming King." <br><br>But He says, he says <br>"Well, I have held my peace for <br>A long, long, long, long time <br>And in my silence you thought <br>That i was all together like you <br>And in your heart you were settled in complacency <br>You said, 'He won't even respond.' <br>You said, 'He's not interested." <br>You said, 'He's dead and gone." <br>But I've been silent for such <br>A long, long, long, long time <br>But I'm about to gasp, to pant <br>To cry out, to cry out <br>I'm going to shout!" <br><br>Once again I'm going to shake <br>Everything that can be shaken <br>Once again I'm going to break <br>Everything that can be broken <br><br>Are you ready? <br>Are you ready for this? <br><br>Are you ready? <br>Are you ready? <br><br>People get ready! <br>Jesus is coming! <br><br>He's coming! <br>He's coming! <br>He's coming! <br>He's coming!!!]]></content><category term="Misty Edwards" label="Misty Edwards"/><category term="People Get Ready" label="People Get Ready"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/Between_The_Cherubim/</id><title>Misty Edwards - Between The Cherubim - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:13:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:13:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/Between_The_Cherubim/" title="Misty Edwards - Between The Cherubim - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We will awaken the dawn <br>With a song in the night <br>For a new day will come <br>Just as sure as the sun will rise <br><br>Though deep darkness prevail <br>For the night weeping endures <br>Yet Your light will not fail <br>You won't rest until our righteousness shines <br><br>You who dwell between the cherubim <br>To You we cry <br>Oh, Shepherd of Israel <br>Restore and cause Your face to shine <br>Don't remember our former sin <br>Let Your mercy speedily come <br>Oh, Shepherd of Israel <br>Restore and cause Your face to shine <br><br>Though we're feasting on the bread of affliction <br>And the water of tears is our wine <br>We won't draw back <br>We will run to You <br>For we know it's just a matter of time <br>You will answer the cry of Your people <br>And Your ear is attentive to their sighs <br>So we lift up our voice to You <br>And we sing in the dawning light <br><br>For the glory of Your name <br>For Your glory and your fame <br>Though the earth be removed <br>We lift our hands to only You <br><br>For the glory of Your name <br>For Your glory and Your fame <br>Though the nations rage toward You <br>Let our love remain true]]></content><category term="Misty Edwards" label="Misty Edwards"/><category term="Between The Cherubim" label="Between The Cherubim"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/All-Consuming_Fire/</id><title>Misty Edwards - All-Consuming Fire - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:13:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:13:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/All-Consuming_Fire/" title="Misty Edwards - All-Consuming Fire - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[O Lord bless me and keep me <br>Cause Your face to shine on me <br>Lord be gracious <br>Lift the light of Your countenance <br>Give me peace <br><br>For I live only to see Your face <br>So shine on me <br>For I live only to see Your face <br>So shine on me <br><br>Let the light of Your face <br>Shine down on my heart <br>And let me feel it]]></content><category term="Misty Edwards" label="Misty Edwards"/><category term="All-Consuming Fire" label="All-Consuming Fire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/You_Wont_Relent_Seal/</id><title>Misty Edwards - You Wont Relent (Seal) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:13:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:13:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/You_Wont_Relent_Seal/" title="Misty Edwards - You Wont Relent (Seal) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You won't relent until you have it all <br>My heart is yours <br>You won't relent until you have it all <br>My heart is yours <br><br>I'll set you as a seal upon my heart <br>As a seal upon my arm <br>For there is love that is as strong as death <br>Jealousy, demanding as the grave <br>Many waters cannot quench this love <br><br>You won't relent until you have it all <br>My heart is yours <br>You won't relent until you have it all <br>My heart is yours <br><br>I'll set you as a seal upon my heart <br>As a seal upon my arm <br>For there is love that is as strong as death <br>Jealousy, demanding as the grave <br>Many waters cannot quench this love <br><br>Waters cannot quench this love <br>You won't relent until you have it all <br>My heart is yours <br>Waters cannot quench this love <br>You won't relent until you have it all <br>My heart is yours <br><br>Come be the fire inside of me <br>Come be the flame upon my heart <br>Come be the fire inside of me <br>Until you and I are one]]></content><category term="Misty Edwards" label="Misty Edwards"/><category term="You Wont Relent (Seal)" label="You Wont Relent (Seal)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/My_Soul_Longs_For_You/</id><title>Misty Edwards - My Soul Longs For You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:13:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:13:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/My_Soul_Longs_For_You/" title="Misty Edwards - My Soul Longs For You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My soul longs for You <br>My soul longs for you <br>And Nothin' else will do <br>Nothin' else will do <br><br>My soul longs for You <br>My soul longs for you <br>And Nothin' else will do <br>Nothin' else will do <br><br>My soul longs for You <br>My soul longs for you <br>And Nothin' else will do <br>Nothin' else will do <br><br>My soul longs for You <br>My soul longs for you <br>And Nothin' else will do <br>Nothin' else will do <br><br>I believe You will come like the rain <br>I believe You will come like the rain (I believe it) <br>I believe You will come like the rain yeah <br>And I believe You will come like the rain <br><br>You'll come like the rain <br>You'll come like the rain <br>You'll come like the rain <br>You'll come like the rain <br><br>My soul longs for You <br>My soul longs for you <br>And Nothin' else will do <br>Nothin' else will do <br><br>My soul longs for You <br>My soul longs for you <br>And Nothin' else will do <br>Nothin' else will do <br><br>I believe You will come like the rain <br>I believe You will come like the rain <br><br>You'll come like the rain <br>You'll come like the rain <br>You'll come like the rain <br>You'll come like the rain <br><br>So let it rain, let it rain, let it rain , let it rain <br>So let it rain, let it rain, let it rain , let it rain <br>So let it rain, let it rain, let it rain , let it rain <br>So let it rain, let it rain, let it rain <br><br>Hallelujah, Halleljujah <br>You'll make all things new, all things new yeah <br>Hallelujah, Halleljujah <br>You'll make all things new, all things new <br><br>It's just a matter of time that <br>Gonna turn it all around, yeah <br><br>(make all things new) Time, time, time <br><br>Hallelujah, Halleljujah <br>You'll make all things new, all things new <br><br>So let it rain, let it rain, let it rain , let it rain <br>So let it rain, let it rain, let it rain , let it rain <br>So let it rain, let it rain, let it rain , let it rain <br>So let it rain, let it rain, let it rain <br><br>Hallelujah, Halleljujah <br>You'll make all things new, all things new <br>Hallelujah, Halleljujah <br>You'll make all things new, all things new <br>Hallelujah, Halleljujah <br>You'll make all things new, all things new <br>Hallelujah, Halleljujah <br>You'll make all things new, all things new]]></content><category term="Misty Edwards" label="Misty Edwards"/><category term="My Soul Longs For You" label="My Soul Longs For You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/Finally_I_Surrender/</id><title>Misty Edwards - Finally I Surrender - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:13:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:13:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Misty_Edwards/Finally_I_Surrender/" title="Misty Edwards - Finally I Surrender - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All I want is You to have Your way <br>You are the Potter and I am the clay <br><br>All I need is You to have Your way <br>You are Creator and I am what You made <br><br>Finally I surrender <br>Finally I surrender <br><br>You are God, I am man <br>You are sovereign]]></content><category term="Misty Edwards" label="Misty Edwards"/><category term="Finally I Surrender" label="Finally I Surrender"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박준호/True_Love/</id><title>박준호 - True Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:13:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:13:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A4%80%ED%98%B8/True_Love/" title="박준호 - True Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑 나 원하는 것보다 <br>사랑 그가 원하는 것 <br>사랑 나 꿈꾸는 것보다 <br>사랑 그가 꿈꾸게 하는 것 <br>친구를 위해 목숨 버리는 것 <br>골고다의 길을 홀로 걷는 것 <br>모두 다 주고도 생명까지 주고도 <br>더 주고 싶은 것 늘 기도하는 것 <br>사랑 인간으로 오신 <br>사랑 하나님의 아들 <br>사랑 단 한 번의 제사 <br>사랑 희생의 섬김 <br>친구를 위해 목숨 버리는 것 <br>골고다의 길을 홀로 걷는 것 <br>모두 다 주고도 생명까지 주고도 <br>더 주고 싶은 것 사랑 <br>친구를 위해 목숨 버리는 것 <br>골고다의 길을 홀로 걷는 것 <br>모두 다 주고도 생명까지 주고도 <br>더 주고 싶은 것 늘 기도하는 것 <br>]]></content><category term="박준호" label="박준호"/><category term="True Love" label="True Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시우_XIU/귤이의_피크닉/</id><title>시우 (XIU) - 귤이의 피크닉 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:13:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:13:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EC%9A%B0_XIU/%EA%B7%A4%EC%9D%B4%EC%9D%98_%ED%94%BC%ED%81%AC%EB%8B%89/" title="시우 (XIU) - 귤이의 피크닉 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한 발짝 두 발짝 폴짝 창문 넘어 <br>세 발짝 네 발짝 폴짝 담을 넘어 <br>꽃길을 따라 랄라 노랠 부르며 <br>오 한 발짝 두 발짝 폴짝 언덕 넘어 <br>세 발짝 네 발짝 폴짝 강을 넘어 <br>시냇물 따라 랄라 노랠 부르며 <br>넌 나의 선물 <br>내 통조림보다 니가 더 좋아 <br>My darling <br>매일 이 순간을 기다려 <br>막 설레 사랑스러워 <br>눈뜨면 꿈일까 봐 겁이 나 <br>막 숨이 가빠 올라 <br>널 만나 여긴 paradise <br>눈부신 shiny day <br>한 발짝 두 발짝 폴짝 강을 넘어 <br>세 발짝 네 발짝 폴짝 언덕 넘어 <br>시냇물 따라 랄라 노랠 부르며 <br>오 한 발짝 두 발짝 폴짝 담을 넘어 <br>세 발짝 네 발짝 폴짝 창문 넘어 <br>의자에 앉아 랄라 노랠 부르며 <br>넌 나의 보물 <br>내 캣타워보다 니가 더 좋아 <br>My darling <br>내일이 오기만 기다려 <br>막 설레 잠이 안 와 <br>눈뜨면 꿈일까 봐 겁이 나 <br>막 볼이 달아올라 <br>널 만나 여긴 paradise <br>눈부신 shiny day <br>]]></content><category term="시우 (XIU)" label="시우 (XIU)"/><category term="귤이의 피크닉" label="귤이의 피크닉"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공휘/어땠을까/</id><title>공휘 - 어땠을까 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:13:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:13:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%ED%9C%98/%EC%96%B4%EB%95%A0%EC%9D%84%EA%B9%8C/" title="공휘 - 어땠을까 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어쩌면 한번쯤 <br>다시 만날꺼란 <br>그런 생각에 웃곤 해 <br>맘에 없던 그 말 <br>밀어 냈던 그 날 <br>후회만하는 내 모습 <br>한번만 내게 돌아와 준다면 <br>한번만 나를 봐준다면 <br>차갑던 맘도 아픈 기억들도 <br>멈출텐데 <br>너와 나 그때 그랬으면 어땠을까 <br>그때 그랬다면 어땠을까 우리 <br>그랬으면 어땠을까 <br>지나버린 모든 시간들이 <br>가슴에 남아 마주친다면 우리 <br>어디에 있니 하고픈 말 있어 <br>가슴 속 담아 두었던 그 말 <br>사랑한다고 혼자 연습했던 그 말 <br>너와 나 그때 그랬으면 어땠을까 <br>그때 그랬다면 어땠을까 우리 <br>그랬으면 어땠을까 <br>다시 그때로 돌아간다면 <br>그랬었다면 우리 어땠을까 <br>나 다시 돌아가면 말했을까 <br>그때 그랬다면 어땠을까 우리 <br>그랬으면 어땠을까 <br>지나버린 모든 시간들이 <br>가슴에 남아 아파하겠지 나는 <br>]]></content><category term="공휘" label="공휘"/><category term="어땠을까" label="어땠을까"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/히즈윌_HisWill/愛し合いましょう_서로_사랑하자/</id><title>히즈윌 (HisWill) - 愛し合いましょう (서로 사랑하자) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9E%88%EC%A6%88%EC%9C%8C_HisWill/%E6%84%9B%E3%81%97%E5%90%88%E3%81%84%E3%81%BE%E3%81%97%E3%82%87%E3%81%86_%EC%84%9C%EB%A1%9C_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%98%EC%9E%90/" title="히즈윌 (HisWill) - 愛し合いましょう (서로 사랑하자) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[闇を越えて主の光きた <br>君のために？の光きた <br><br>憎む思いで迷う心は <br>主の光が見えない <br><br>すべての罪を <br>十字架で覆い <br>ただひとつだけ <br>愛しなさい <br><br>愛しなさい <br>愛しなさい <br><br>わが主の愛を忘れずに？えます <br><br>愛して <br>愛しなさい <br>愛し合いましょう <br><br>愛しなさい <br>愛しなさい <br><br>わが主の？み忘れずに？えます <br><br>愛して <br>愛しなさい <br>愛し合いましょう <br><br>愛しなさい <br>愛しなさい <br>愛し合いましょう]]></content><category term="히즈윌 (HisWill)" label="히즈윌 (HisWill)"/><category term="愛し合いましょう (서로 사랑하자)" label="愛し合いましょう (서로 사랑하자)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/히즈윌_HisWill/日日の全て_모든_삶의_순간/</id><title>히즈윌 (HisWill) - 日日の全て (모든 삶의 순간) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9E%88%EC%A6%88%EC%9C%8C_HisWill/%E6%97%A5%E6%97%A5%E3%81%AE%E5%85%A8%E3%81%A6_%EB%AA%A8%EB%93%A0_%EC%82%B6%EC%9D%98_%EC%88%9C%EA%B0%84/" title="히즈윌 (HisWill) - 日日の全て (모든 삶의 순간) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[命？きる日 霧のように去るとき <br>限りない？光 主に捧げ <br><br>美しい世界　我がため作られ <br>新たな日？を 主は？えられる <br><br>ときには春のように <br>ときには？しい冬も <br><br>ときには 感動も <br>ときには？？え <br><br>日？の全てが　主の贈り物　 <br>一番 良いものを　 <br>わたしに 合わせ？え]]></content><category term="히즈윌 (HisWill)" label="히즈윌 (HisWill)"/><category term="日日の全て (모든 삶의 순간)" label="日日の全て (모든 삶의 순간)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/히즈윌_HisWill/愛_사랑/</id><title>히즈윌 (HisWill) - 愛 (사랑) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9E%88%EC%A6%88%EC%9C%8C_HisWill/%E6%84%9B_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="히즈윌 (HisWill) - 愛 (사랑) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[たとえ天使の言葉　話せても <br>愛なければ無になり <br>すべての知識が分かっても <br>愛なくては無に等しい <br><br>たとえわが手にあるものと <br>わが身のすべてを <br>燃やし？えても <br>愛がなければ何でもないよ <br><br>愛は優しく <br>情け深く <br>愛は妬むことしない <br>不作法せず <br>利益求めず <br>すべてが忍ばれる <br><br>信仰と希望とまた愛とは <br>永久にあること、 <br>大いなるもの 愛である　 <br>大いなるもの愛 <br>大いなるもの愛]]></content><category term="히즈윌 (HisWill)" label="히즈윌 (HisWill)"/><category term="愛 (사랑)" label="愛 (사랑)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/히즈윌_HisWill/主の愛_사랑으로/</id><title>히즈윌 (HisWill) - 主の愛 (사랑으로) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9E%88%EC%A6%88%EC%9C%8C_HisWill/%E4%B8%BB%E3%81%AE%E6%84%9B_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9C%BC%EB%A1%9C/" title="히즈윌 (HisWill) - 主の愛 (사랑으로) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[任せられた多くのことで <br>自分を下ろし？牲が要るとき <br><br>乾いた心　 <br>それを持ち　 <br>主の前に行きます <br><br>主の愛　 <br>主の愛にて　 <br>私を？たしてください <br><br>十字架の血潮で <br>私に主の愛が流れるように <br><br>どんな言葉も　 <br>どんな業でも　 <br>愛がなければ何の意味もない <br><br>愛のない熱心　 <br>愛のない知識　 <br>どんな花をも？かせられない <br><br>主の愛　 <br>主の愛にて <br>我らを？たしてください <br><br>十字架の血潮で <br>我らに主の愛が <br><br>主の愛　 <br>主の愛にて <br>我らを？たしてください <br><br>十字架の血潮で <br>我らに主の愛が <br>流れるように <br>流れるように <br>流れるように]]></content><category term="히즈윌 (HisWill)" label="히즈윌 (HisWill)"/><category term="主の愛 (사랑으로)" label="主の愛 (사랑으로)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/히즈윌_HisWill/わたしも_そうなりたい_나도_바보처럼_살래요/</id><title>히즈윌 (HisWill) - わたしも そうなりたい (나도 바보처럼 살래요) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9E%88%EC%A6%88%EC%9C%8C_HisWill/%E3%82%8F%E3%81%9F%E3%81%97%E3%82%82_%E3%81%9D%E3%81%86%E3%81%AA%E3%82%8A%E3%81%9F%E3%81%84_%EB%82%98%EB%8F%84_%EB%B0%94%EB%B3%B4%EC%B2%98%EB%9F%BC_%EC%82%B4%EB%9E%98%EC%9A%94/" title="히즈윌 (HisWill) - わたしも そうなりたい (나도 바보처럼 살래요) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[人里から離れ船作るノ？ア <br>君は愚かです <br>君は愚かです <br>なぜ晴れた日に　 <br>山の上で作るの <br>君は愚かです <br>君は愚かです <br><br>空の陽を見て <br>雨のこと忘れてもいいのに <br>人があざわらう諦めてもいいのに <br><br>どうしてその道を？けられる <br>どうやってその場を <br>守っていたんです <br>どうしてその道を？けられる <br>どうやってその場を <br>守っていたんですか <br><br>君は 愚かです <br>君は 愚かです <br>君は 愚かです <br>私も そうなりたい]]></content><category term="히즈윌 (HisWill)" label="히즈윌 (HisWill)"/><category term="わたしも そうなりたい (나도 바보처럼 살래요)" label="わたしも そうなりたい (나도 바보처럼 살래요)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/히즈윌_HisWill/我が人生_삶으로/</id><title>히즈윌 (HisWill) - 我が人生 (삶으로) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9E%88%EC%A6%88%EC%9C%8C_HisWill/%E6%88%91%E3%81%8C%E4%BA%BA%E7%94%9F_%EC%82%B6%EC%9C%BC%EB%A1%9C/" title="히즈윌 (HisWill) - 我が人生 (삶으로) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[世の富みも世での名も誇りも <br>すべて下ろして <br><br>十字架の愛 <br>その血潮 <br>主の？み思い巡らす <br><br>我が全てただ主に <br>？えられたもの <br>我が人生？みで？たしてくれた <br><br>我がすべてただ主に <br>？えられたもの <br><br>我が人生主の前今捧げます <br><br>主を歌う <br>我が？みの中で <br>用いてください <br>主を褒めます <br><br>主を崇め <br>我が？みの中で <br>用いてください <br>光として <br><br>用いてください <br>光として]]></content><category term="히즈윌 (HisWill)" label="히즈윌 (HisWill)"/><category term="我が人生 (삶으로)" label="我が人生 (삶으로)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/히즈윌_HisWill/主の惠み_그_은혜로만/</id><title>히즈윌 (HisWill) - 主の惠み (그 은혜로만) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9E%88%EC%A6%88%EC%9C%8C_HisWill/%E4%B8%BB%E3%81%AE%E6%83%A0%E3%81%BF_%EA%B7%B8_%EC%9D%80%ED%98%9C%EB%A1%9C%EB%A7%8C/" title="히즈윌 (HisWill) - 主の惠み (그 은혜로만) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[私があるのは主の？み <br>私がしたことはありません <br>私があるのは主の？み <br>なに一つ私がしたことはない <br><br>ただ主の？みだけが私にあふれ <br>神の？みによって私は生きる <br><br>主の？み ？みで <br>その中で私に？みが？くように <br>　 <br>主の？み　？みで <br>その中で いつでも生きる]]></content><category term="히즈윌 (HisWill)" label="히즈윌 (HisWill)"/><category term="主の惠み (그 은혜로만)" label="主の惠み (그 은혜로만)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/히즈윌_HisWill/荒野をとおって_광야를_지나며/</id><title>히즈윌 (HisWill) - 荒野をとおって (광야를 지나며) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9E%88%EC%A6%88%EC%9C%8C_HisWill/%E8%8D%92%E9%87%8E%E3%82%92%E3%81%A8%E3%81%8A%E3%81%A3%E3%81%A6_%EA%B4%91%EC%95%BC%EB%A5%BC_%EC%A7%80%EB%82%98%EB%A9%B0/" title="히즈윌 (HisWill) - 荒野をとおって (광야를 지나며) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[なぜ闇のなかに、深き闇みに <br>一人で捨てられたのか <br>私はなぜ寂しくなり、低くなり、 <br>？りなくなったのか <br>荒野、荒野にいる <br><br>主だけ助けになり、 <br>主だけ光になり、 <br>主だけ友になれる荒野 <br><br>主を離れて、 <br>とても生きられない荒野 <br>荒野にいる <br><br>なぜ闇のなかに、深き闇みに <br>一人で捨てられたのか <br>私はなぜ寂しくなり、低くなり、 <br>？りなくなったのか <br>荒野、荒野にいる <br><br>主だけ助けになり、 <br>主だけ光になり、 <br>主だけ友になれる荒野 <br><br>主を離れて、 <br>とても生きられない荒野 <br>荒野、荒野 <br><br>主に用いられるように、 <br>？められるように、 <br>主に送られた所　荒野 <br><br>御？によって、 <br>生まれ？えられる <br>荒野 <br>荒野にいる <br><br>こころを明け渡して、華やかな夢も <br>主の手に捧げる <br>主の御旨が我が主だけが <br>私に現れるように　 <br>荒野を通って]]></content><category term="히즈윌 (HisWill)" label="히즈윌 (HisWill)"/><category term="荒野をとおって (광야를 지나며)" label="荒野をとおって (광야를 지나며)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/히즈윌_HisWill/橫目_곁눈질/</id><title>히즈윌 (HisWill) - 橫目 (곁눈질) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9E%88%EC%A6%88%EC%9C%8C_HisWill/%E6%A9%AB%E7%9B%AE_%EA%B3%81%EB%88%88%EC%A7%88/" title="히즈윌 (HisWill) - 橫目 (곁눈질) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[今はここ立っていても <br>明日は主に？えますよ <br>なぜ遠くにいるように <br>主を離れ何を見るの <br><br>今にでも？かしい <br>わが主に？えるように <br>欲もなく未練もなく <br>ありがたく生きたいです <br><br>今はここ立っていても <br>明日は主に？えますよ <br>なぜ遠くにいるように <br>主を離れ何を見るの <br><br>明日には主が呼んだら <br>？められるように <br>イエスの道 <br>？い道 <br>？理の道 <br>行きたいです <br><br>今はここ立っていても <br>明日は主に？えますよ <br>なぜ遠くにいるように <br>主を離れ何を見るの <br><br>今はここ立っていても <br>明日は主に？えますよ <br>キリストの花嫁として <br>いつまでも生きたいです <br>何を見るの]]></content><category term="히즈윌 (HisWill)" label="히즈윌 (HisWill)"/><category term="橫目 (곁눈질)" label="橫目 (곁눈질)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/히즈윌_HisWill/眞の光_참빛/</id><title>히즈윌 (HisWill) - 眞の光 (참빛) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9E%88%EC%A6%88%EC%9C%8C_HisWill/%E7%9C%9E%E3%81%AE%E5%85%89_%EC%B0%B8%EB%B9%9B/" title="히즈윌 (HisWill) - 眞の光 (참빛) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[？の光が？た、 <br>イエスの光が？た <br>君を照らしている <br>君には命の光 <br><br>暗いところ光が？て <br>天が開いて、天使も歌う <br>闇に迷う君のために <br>？の光のイエスが？た <br><br>愛を探して、？理を求める <br>寂しく、苦しむ <br>君のために <br><br>暗闇越えて、命下さる <br>光のイエスが？た <br><br>？の光が？た、 <br>イエスの光が？た <br>君を照らしている <br>君には命の光 <br><br>暗いところ光が？て <br>天が開いて、天使も歌う <br>闇に迷う君のために <br>？の光のイエスが？た <br><br>愛を探して、？理を求める <br>寂しく、苦しむ <br>君のために <br><br>暗闇越えて、命くださる <br>光のイエスが？た <br><br>愛を探して、？理を求める <br>寂しく、苦しむ <br>君のために <br><br>暗闇越えて、命くださる <br>光のイエスが？た <br>光のイエスが？た <br>光のイエスが？た]]></content><category term="히즈윌 (HisWill)" label="히즈윌 (HisWill)"/><category term="眞の光 (참빛)" label="眞の光 (참빛)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/히즈윌_HisWill/君のため_널_위해/</id><title>히즈윌 (HisWill) - 君のため (널 위해) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9E%88%EC%A6%88%EC%9C%8C_HisWill/%E5%90%9B%E3%81%AE%E3%81%9F%E3%82%81_%EB%84%90_%EC%9C%84%ED%95%B4/" title="히즈윌 (HisWill) - 君のため (널 위해) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[朝日は誰のために昇る <br>風は誰のために吹くの <br>？い空と綺麗な海は <br>誰のためにあるの <br><br>小鳥は何を歌うのだろう <br>？れる木の葉は何を？くの <br>夜の星は誰のため煌めいてるの <br><br>全ては君への贈り物 <br>全ては君への愛の歌 <br>主は君に全て作られ <br>君に愛を？える <br><br>目に見えない主の愛が <br>いつも君を包む <br>昇る朝日のように <br>？わらない主の愛が <br><br>全ては君への贈り物 <br>全ては君への愛の歌 <br>主は君に全て作られ <br>君に愛を？える <br><br>目に見えない主の愛が <br>いつも君を包む <br>昇る朝日のように <br>？わらない主の愛が <br><br>昇る朝日のように <br>？わらない主の愛が]]></content><category term="히즈윌 (HisWill)" label="히즈윌 (HisWill)"/><category term="君のため (널 위해)" label="君のため (널 위해)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/히즈윌_HisWill/一日（하루）/</id><title>히즈윌 (HisWill) - 一日（하루） - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9E%88%EC%A6%88%EC%9C%8C_HisWill/%E4%B8%80%E6%97%A5%EF%BC%88%ED%95%98%EB%A3%A8%EF%BC%89/" title="히즈윌 (HisWill) - 一日（하루） - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[今日も一日というプレゼント <br>いつものような新たな日 <br>ワクワク？持ちで？き出す <br>今日は何が待っているんだろう <br>何も起こらない平和な日 <br>夢が？う　サプライズデ？ <br>そこで踏み出した愛の？みに <br>幸せが？く <br><br>今日も一日というプレゼント <br>いつものような新たな日 <br>ワクワク？持ちで？き出す <br>今日は何が待っているんだろう <br>何も起こらない平和な日 <br>夢が？う　サプライズデ？ <br>そこで踏み出した愛の？みに <br>幸せが？く <br><br>何も起こらない平和な日 <br>夢が？う　サプライズデ？ <br>そこで踏み出した愛の？みに <br>幸せが？く <br><br>振り向くと長い旅だったな <br>この先分からないけれど <br>主と？く一日が <br>私をきっと笑わせるだろう <br><br>今日も一日というプレゼント <br>いつものような新たな日 <br>ワクワク？持ちで？き出す <br>今日は何が待っているんだろう]]></content><category term="히즈윌 (HisWill)" label="히즈윌 (HisWill)"/><category term="一日（하루）" label="一日（하루）"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lil_Yachty/Peek_A_Boo_Feat_Migos/</id><title>Lil Yachty - Peek A Boo (Feat. Migos) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lil_Yachty/Peek_A_Boo_Feat_Migos/" title="Lil Yachty - Peek A Boo (Feat. Migos) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ricky Racks <br>Peek a boo woo <br>Peek a boo <br>Uh uh play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that money like <br>peek a boo ooh <br>Play with these bitches like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Broke ass bitch ass nigga <br>I'm not finna' play with you <br>that's what these rappers do <br>Peek a boo peek a boo <br>peek a boo peek a boo <br>Peek a boo peek a boo bitch <br>Peek a boo peek a boo <br>peek a boo peek a boo <br>Peek a boo bitch <br>Peek a boo peek a boo <br>peek a boo peek a boo <br>Peek a boo peek a boo bitch <br>Peek a boo peek a boo <br>peek a boo <br>Lil Boat <br>I'm not finna' play with you <br>that's what these rappers do <br>Red dot red dot red dot <br>red dot red dot <br>On his nose like Rudolph <br>Pull up to the scene <br>all white with the roof off <br>Take that lil' bitch <br>to the Ruth Chris <br>Fuck her then fuck on her sister <br>I'm ruthless <br>Chill on the 6 <br>when I'm fuckin' on poochie <br>That bitch was ugly <br>but pussy on smoothie wet <br>Play with that kitty like hello <br>Took a step back then I bust it <br>I bust it I bust it like Melo <br>Aiming at you and your fellows <br>My new bitch yellow <br>She blow that dick like a cello <br>Fuck her then send that <br>bitch home on the metro <br>Ooh young nigga fly like a pigeon <br>Versace frames <br>they be hidin' my vision <br>Make sure all my niggas eat <br>that's the mission <br>Emotion I'ma go get it <br>go get it I got it <br>Uh uh play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that money like <br>peek a boo ooh <br>Play with these bitches like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Broke ass bitch ass nigga <br>I'm not finna' play with you <br>that's what these rappers do <br>Peek a boo peek a boo <br>peek a boo peek a boo <br>Peek a boo peek a boo bitch <br>Peek a boo peek a boo <br>peek a boo peek a boo <br>Peek a boo bitch <br>Peek a boo peek a boo <br>peek a boo peek a boo <br>Peek a boo peek a boo bitch <br>Peek a boo peek a boo <br>peek a boo <br>I'm not finna' play with you <br>that's what these rappers do <br>Open your eyes <br>bitch you see all this money <br>Made that lil' bitch <br>tape a brick to her stomach <br>You not the gang <br>we don't kick it or punt it <br>Just bought the Wraith <br>and I revved it tectonic <br>Look at the numbers <br>mechanics ain't frontin' <br>I came from the lint went to jail <br>I got punished ooh <br>Pourin' a four <br>Freddy Kreuger wow <br>My niggas turn barracuda <br>You cappin' <br>I came from trappin' <br>I used to have the dope <br>stashed in the cabinet dope <br>Mama couldn't tell me shit <br>where was my daddy Mom <br>Look at my Patek I'm flexin' <br>I'm petty I'm petty <br>I fucked the pussy <br>the first time I met it <br>Won't give you no credit <br>you ate it spaghetti <br>I cook the brick <br>cut the brick with machetes <br>Married the money <br>the bitch wasn't ready uh uh <br>Uh uh play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that money like <br>peek a boo ooh <br>Play with these bitches like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Broke ass bitch ass nigga <br>I'm not finna' play with you <br>that's what these rappers do <br>Peek a boo peek a boo <br>peek a boo peek a boo <br>Peek a boo peek a boo bitch <br>Peek a boo peek a boo <br>peek a boo peek a boo <br>Peek a boo bitch <br>Peek a boo peek a boo <br>peek a boo peek a boo <br>Peek a boo peek a boo bitch <br>Peek a boo peek a boo <br>peek a boo <br>I'm not finna' play with you <br>that's what these rappers do <br>New grey drop top Audi 2013 yeah <br>White coco butterfly wings 2k17 <br>Ice ice came out the machine ice <br>Came out the machine ice baby <br>Draco Uzi Tommy gun <br>SK Tommy gun all machines <br>brrrt <br>Yeah hey pull up on the side of 'em <br>skrrt <br>Let the clip ride on 'em <br>Ayy fuck 12 <br>open fire on 'em fuck 12 <br>Open up fire on 'em fuck 12 <br>Yeah don't tuck in my chain nah <br>I'm with the gang gang <br>hit you with range <br>Scattering showers <br>here come the rain <br>Icy Hot sleeve these <br>niggas in pain hey <br>Uh uh play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that pussy like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Play with that money like <br>peek a boo ooh <br>Play with these bitches like <br>peek a boo uh <br>Broke ass bitch ass nigga <br>I'm not finna' play with you <br>that's what these rappers do <br>Left wrist white <br>it's the Patek Philippe <br>Bad white bitch with a fatty unique <br>Smokin' on cookies <br>from granny trees <br>Pocket rocket <br>go go gadget go go <br>I make a play Madden John <br>I know it was some speculation <br>'bout who the one <br>But we invented the dabbin' dab <br>Fuck it <br>we just let 'em have it have it <br>Draco for niggas with static <br>brrt static <br>I can do magic and make me a rabbit <br>With usin' my karats ice woah <br>Just like the package <br>I'm drinkin' on Actavis <br>expensive habits Actavis mud <br>Yellow bitch Pikachu bitch <br>Cameltoe peekin' at you look at you <br>Peek a boo <br>Peek a boo peek a boo <br>]]></content><category term="Lil Yachty" label="Lil Yachty"/><category term="Peek A Boo (Feat. Migos)" label="Peek A Boo (Feat. Migos)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전자양/사스콰치/</id><title>전자양 - 사스콰치 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%9E%90%EC%96%91/%EC%82%AC%EC%8A%A4%EC%BD%B0%EC%B9%98/" title="전자양 - 사스콰치 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사스콰치 <br>가자 사스콰치 <br>털복숭이라는 건 뭘까 <br>뛰자 사슴같이 <br>사람은 널 노리는 맹수 <br>가자 소년소녀 <br>젊음이라는 것은 뭘까 <br>타자 타임머신 <br>시간은 널 노리는 맹수 <br>타임머신 타임머신 아인슈타인 <br>너도 어른이 되고 털이 자라면 <br>다른 나의 모습을 증오를 할까 <br>같아도 똑같지 않을수 있는 <br>달라도 다르지 않은게 있어 <br>얼렁뚱땅 넘기고 넘기다 <br>내이럴줄 알았지 <br>갈팡질팡 어쩔줄 모르다 <br>내이럴줄 알았지 <br>널 그냥 잡아먹을 걸 <br>널 그냥 구워먹을 걸 <br>널 그냥 삼켜버릴 걸 <br>널 그냥 구워먹을 걸 <br>너와 나의 꿈동산은 폐허 <br>어쩔 수 없다 하겠지 <br>이성적인 질문을 해봐도 <br>이상적이라 하겠지 <br>널 그냥 잡아먹을 걸 <br>널 그냥 구워먹을 걸 <br>널 그냥 삼켜버릴 걸 <br>모두다 하나가 될 걸 <br>]]></content><category term="전자양" label="전자양"/><category term="사스콰치" label="사스콰치"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전자양/스티커/</id><title>전자양 - 스티커 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%9E%90%EC%96%91/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B0%EC%BB%A4/" title="전자양 - 스티커 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[전부 터널을 보고 있었어 <br>안개 낀 숲으로 가는 <br>춥고 무서워 더럽고 가려워 <br>피가 튄 하얀 티셔츠 <br>광채를 내뿜은 초록색 해골은 <br>우리를 조롱하고 <br>왜 저주받을 실수는 언제나 <br>하찮은 장난에서 시작할까 <br>첨부터 너를 보고 있었어 <br>목걸이를 깨물고 있는 <br>덥고 우스워 따갑고 마려워 <br>낡은 카디건 보풀 <br>룸미러 아래 흔들리는 숲속향은 <br>뇌를 주물럭 거려 <br>부끄러운 트로피들의 무덤은 <br>달처럼 불룩하게 불러와 <br>구원은 이제 싫어 <br>도덕은 삶을 도둑질하네 <br>희귀한 금속 메달 <br>신비한 힘 깃들어있는 <br>그대만이 우주를 깨우리 <br>그대만이 지옥을 구하리 <br>그대만이 천국에 오줌누고 <br>그대만이 우릴 구원하리 <br>지금 이 순간을 즐겨 <br>걱정해도 빚은 줄지않아 <br>첨지어보는 표정 <br>어색해도 넌 아름다워 <br>그대만이 우주를 깨우리 <br>그대만이 지옥을 구하리 <br>그대만이 천국에 오줌누고 <br>그대만이 우릴 구원하리 <br>]]></content><category term="전자양" label="전자양"/><category term="스티커" label="스티커"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이어스_Ears/비밀/</id><title>이어스 (Ears) - 비밀 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:14:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:14:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%96%B4%EC%8A%A4_Ears/%EB%B9%84%EB%B0%80/" title="이어스 (Ears) - 비밀 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그때 넌 눈으로 이미 <br>말하고 있었어 <br>너무 힘든 일이니 이제 <br>그만하자고 <br>지쳐 보이는 네 모습과 <br>다른 내 마음에 <br>니가 아플 걸 알면서도 <br>멈추지 못 하네 <br>너에게 늘 특별한 사람이고 싶어 난 <br>혹시 예전 그대로 돌아 <br>갈 수 있을까 <br>네 환한 미소와 내가 준 <br>목걸이까지 <br>지금 이대로 널 보내면 <br>안될 것 같아서 <br>니가 아플 걸 알면서도 <br>그만하자 못해 <br>너에게 늘 특별한 사람이고 싶어 난 <br>그만하자 말 못해 <br>]]></content><category term="이어스 (Ears)" label="이어스 (Ears)"/><category term="비밀" label="비밀"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이어스_Ears/Take_Me/</id><title>이어스 (Ears) - Take Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:15:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:15:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%96%B4%EC%8A%A4_Ears/Take_Me/" title="이어스 (Ears) - Take Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모른 척 외면해도 <br>거울을 보는 이 기분 <br>어디가 같은 건지 <br>생각이나 말투가 말야 <br>같은 곳에 있을 때 <br>같은 말에 웃을 때 <br>서로의 머릿속에 <br>스쳐 가지 말라고 말해 <br>그 말은 아직 남겨둔 채로 <br>아직 우린 서로 바라만 보는 게 <br>I feel alive <br>I don't care if it hurts <br>No one understand <br>how I feel right now <br>Take me <br>Take on me <br>Take on me <br>Take on me <br>너와 날 연결시킨 <br>그 고리의 이음새와 <br>네가 보여줄 곳의 <br>따듯함이 날 반기겠지 <br>같은 곳에 있을 때 <br>같은 말에 웃을 때 <br>서로의 가슴속은 <br>스쳐 가지 말라고 말해 <br>그 말은 아직 남겨둔 채로 <br>아직 우린 서로 바라만 보는 게 <br>I feel alive <br>I don't care if it hurts <br>No one understand <br>how I feel right now <br>Take me <br>Take on me <br>Take on me <br>Take on me <br>]]></content><category term="이어스 (Ears)" label="이어스 (Ears)"/><category term="Take Me" label="Take Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이어스_Ears/Not_Your_Fault/</id><title>이어스 (Ears) - Not Your Fault - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:15:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:15:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%96%B4%EC%8A%A4_Ears/Not_Your_Fault/" title="이어스 (Ears) - Not Your Fault - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[추억 하나가 떠내려가 <br>끝이 안 보이는 <br>저기 먼 곳으로 가나 봐 <br>난 손을 흔들어 <br>그것에게 작별을 고하고 <br>뒤돌아 눈물을 훔쳐내 <br>그 오랜 시간 간직해왔던 <br>그 수 많은 <br>너에 관한 이야기들까지 <br>웃음으로 애써 <br>내 속으로 널 숨겨놓고서 <br>잘 가란 인사를 건넸지 <br>It's not your fault <br>어쩔 수 없었다는 거 알아 <br>너와 난 이해하잖아 <br>It's not your fault <br>아프지 말고 더 잘 살아 <br>아니 조금은 아파도 돼 <br>가슴에 피어난 그 멍들은 <br>보라색의 물감처럼 <br>물들어 버렸나 <br>돌이킬 수가 없이 <br>언제부턴가 뜨겁지 않은 <br>그런 사람이 돼 버렸나 봐 <br>그 오랜 시간 간직해왔던 <br>그 수 많은 <br>너에 관한 이야기들까지 <br>웃음으로 애써 <br>내 속으로 널 숨겨놓고서 <br>잘 가란 인사를 건넸지 <br>It's not your fault <br>어쩔 수 없었다는 거 알아 <br>너와 난 이해하잖아 <br>It's not your fault <br>아프지 말고 더 잘 살아 <br>아니 조금은 아파도 돼 <br>]]></content><category term="이어스 (Ears)" label="이어스 (Ears)"/><category term="Not Your Fault" label="Not Your Fault"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이어스_Ears/Petals/</id><title>이어스 (Ears) - Petals - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:15:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:15:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%96%B4%EC%8A%A4_Ears/Petals/" title="이어스 (Ears) - Petals - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너무 큰 바람일까 <br>나를 위한다는 건 <br>너에게 갇혀있어 <br>내가 아닌 무언가 <br>너무 멀리 왔을까 <br>애써 외면해 <br>나를 잊어가 <br>방황하던 날이 <br>떨어지는 꽃잎처럼 <br>나는 바래져 <br>힘들었던 날이 <br>날개 잃은 새들처럼 <br>너무 큰 욕심일까 <br>아이처럼 사는 게 <br>너에게 갇혀있어 <br>내가 아닌 무언가 <br>나를 잊어가 <br>방황하던 날이 <br>떨어지는 꽃잎처럼 <br>나는 바래져 <br>힘들었던 날이 <br>날개 잃은 새들처럼 <br>너무 멀리 왔을까 <br>애써 외면해 <br>]]></content><category term="이어스 (Ears)" label="이어스 (Ears)"/><category term="Petals" label="Petals"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이어스_Ears/The_Day/</id><title>이어스 (Ears) - The Day - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:15:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:15:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%96%B4%EC%8A%A4_Ears/The_Day/" title="이어스 (Ears) - The Day - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우연치곤 제법 <br>떨려오는 그 미소 속에 <br>내 마음을 흔들어놓고 갔지 <br>다시 보게 될까 <br>몇 번이고 만나게 되면 <br>그땐 꼭 잡겠다 생각했어 <br>빠져드는 신비한 <br>네 그 불빛과는 다른 내 모습에 <br>망설임도 설레여서 <br>웃는 내 모습 들켜버렸어 <br>Oh Please Tell Me You Love Me Now <br>I Just Can't Wait Anymore <br>Oh Please Tell Me You Love Me Now <br>And I Will Never Let A Day Go By <br>그 날 그 장소에 <br>너와 내가 없었더라면 <br>내 텅빈 마음은 누가 채울까 <br>사랑한다는 말 <br>정성스레 잘 포장해선 <br>내 마음 전하려고 애썼지 <br>빠져드는 신비한 <br>네 그 불빛과는 다른 내 모습에 <br>망설임도 설레여서 <br>웃는 내 모습 들켜버렸어 <br>Oh Please Tell Me You Love Me Now <br>I Just Can't Wait Anymore <br>Oh Please Tell Me You Love Me Now <br>And I Will Never Let A Day Go By <br>]]></content><category term="이어스 (Ears)" label="이어스 (Ears)"/><category term="The Day" label="The Day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/uju_우주/Outfit/</id><title>uju (우주) - #Outfit - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:15:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:15:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/uju_%EC%9A%B0%EC%A3%BC/Outfit/" title="uju (우주) - #Outfit - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지나가는 사람들 <br>모두 똑같은 옷차림에 <br>똑같은 눈으로 걸어가고 있네 <br>흘러가는 시간은 <br>아직 우리가 늦었다고 <br>말하지 않는데 걸음을 재촉해 <br>우린 유행하는 옷을 입고 <br>당당하게 걷고 있지 <br>하지만 색깔 없는 사람들 <br>우린 각자의 색으로 살고 있지 <br>She's walking out <br>and gonna do it like you babe <br>like you babe <br>She's walking out <br>and gonna do it like you babe <br>like you babe <br>like you babe <br>like you babe <br>like you babe <br>like you babe <br>지루하게 흐르는 오늘 하루는 <br>무엇이든 하고만 싶어져 <br>들뜨게 하는데 <br>희미하게 들리는 <br>나의 마음속 한자리엔 <br>단순하게 살라고 <br>나를 다그치는데 <br>우린 지나버린 시간으로 <br>돌아가고 싶은 걸까 <br>하지만 대답 없는 사람들 <br>우린 각자의 답으로 살고 있지 <br>나는 꿈꿔왔던 내 모습에 <br>가까워져 가고 있는 걸까 <br>너도 무엇이든 될 것만 같았던 <br>그런 꿈을 꿨을까 <br>나는 꿈꿔왔던 내 모습에 <br>가까워져 가고 있는 걸까 <br>너도 무엇이든 될 것만 같았던 <br>그런 꿈을 꿨을까 <br>She's walking out <br>and gonna do it like you babe <br>like you babe <br>She's walking out <br>and gonna do it like you babe <br>like you babe <br>like you babe <br>like you babe <br>like you babe <br>like you babe <br>]]></content><category term="uju (우주)" label="uju (우주)"/><category term="#Outfit" label="#Outfit"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CHAPLYNN/그래_왜_Cause_Of_You/</id><title>CHAPLYNN - 그래 왜 (Cause Of You) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:15:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:15:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CHAPLYNN/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%98_%EC%99%9C_Cause_Of_You/" title="CHAPLYNN - 그래 왜 (Cause Of You) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어쩌다 너와 눈을 맞출 때 <br>어쩌다 니가 나를 부를 때 <br>막 어지럽고 이상하게 숨이 막혀 <br>oh 요즘 나 <br>널 보면 숨을 쉴 수 없어 그래 왜 <br>그렇게 니가 날 쳐다보면 <br>그렇게 니가 웃어버리면 아마 <br>심장이 뛰다 터져버려 죽을 거야 <br>oh 요즘 나 <br>너 땜에 미칠 것만 같아 그래 왜 <br>그래 왜 그래 왜 uh 그래 왜 <br>널 보면 숨을 쉴 수 없어 그래 왜 <br>그래 왜 그래 왜 uh 그래 왜 <br>너 땜에 미칠 것만 같아 <br>우연히 손끝이라도 닿아버리면 <br>그러다 빨개진 얼굴 들켜버리면 <br>그때는 나도 이상하게 변할지 몰라 <br>oh 요즘 나 <br>나도 날 어쩔 수가 없어 그래 왜 <br>숨이 가빠와 말이 안 나와 <br>그저 땅만 봐 <br>내가 왜 너를 왜 그게 왜 <br>숨이 가빠와 말이 안 나와 <br>그저 땅만 봐 <br>그래 왜 그래 왜 oh 그래 왜 <br>널 보면 숨을 쉴 수 없어 그래 왜 <br>그래 왜 그래 왜 oh 그래 왜 <br>너 땜에 미칠 것만 같아 그래 왜 <br>나를 보던 눈빛들과 내게 짓던 <br>표정들 내게 하던 그 말들 <br>모두 가지고 싶어 <br>나를 보던 눈빛들과 내게 짓던 <br>표정들 내게 하던 그 말들 <br>나만 가지고 싶어 <br>너를 보던 눈빛 내게 짓던 표정 <br>숨을 쉴 수 없어 <br>나를 보던 눈빛 내게 짓던 표정 <br>너 땜에 미칠 것만 같아 <br>그래 왜 그래 왜 oh 그래 왜 <br>널 보면 숨을 쉴 수 없어 그래 왜 <br>그래 왜 그래 왜 oh 그래 왜 <br>너 땜에 미칠 것만 같아 그래 왜 <br>너 땜에 숨을 쉴 수 없어 <br>나를 보던 눈빛 내게 짓던 표정 <br>내게 하던 그 말 <br>나를 보던 눈빛 내게 짓던 표정 <br>내게 하던 그 말 <br>]]></content><category term="CHAPLYNN" label="CHAPLYNN"/><category term="그래 왜 (Cause Of You)" label="그래 왜 (Cause Of You)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/주님의_흔적/하나님_이_나라_이_민족_Feat_김지원/</id><title>주님의 흔적 - 하나님 이 나라 이 민족 (Feat. 김지원) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:15:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:15:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%98_%ED%9D%94%EC%A0%81/%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EB%8B%98_%EC%9D%B4_%EB%82%98%EB%9D%BC_%EC%9D%B4_%EB%AF%BC%EC%A1%B1_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%80%EC%9B%90/" title="주님의 흔적 - 하나님 이 나라 이 민족 (Feat. 김지원) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나님 이 나라 이 민족 <br>주의 말씀을 간직하게 하소서 <br>하나님 이 나라 모든 세대 <br>주의 말씀을 경외하게 하소서 <br>우리의 귀를 지혜에 <br>우리의 마음 명철에 두어 <br>공의 정의 정직 <br>모든 선한 길을 알게 하소서 <br>하나님을 경외할 때 <br>하나님 알게 되리니 <br>우리를 선한 자의 길로 <br>행하게 하시며 <br>우리로 의인의 길을 <br>지키게 하리라 <br>우리가 소리치오니 주여 <br>말씀의 지혜 주시옵소서 <br>악한 자의 길과 패역한 자에게서 <br>건져내시옵소서 <br>하나님을 경외할 때 <br>하나님 알게 되리니 <br>우리를 선한 자의 길로 <br>행하게 하시며 <br>우리로 의인의 길을 <br>지키게 하리라 <br>우리가 회개하오니 <br>우리를 불쌍히 여기소서 <br>주 앞에 엎드리오니 주여 <br>긍휼히 여겨주시옵소서 주여 <br>하나님을 경외할 때 <br>하나님 알게 되리니 <br>우리를 선한 자의 길로 <br>행하게 하시며 <br>우리로 의인의 길을 <br>지키게 하리라 <br>하나님 이 나라 이 민족 <br>주의 말씀을 간직하게 하소서 <br>하나님 이 나라 모든 세대 <br>주의 말씀을 경외하게 하소서 <br>]]></content><category term="주님의 흔적" label="주님의 흔적"/><category term="하나님 이 나라 이 민족 (Feat. 김지원)" label="하나님 이 나라 이 민족 (Feat. 김지원)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/If_It_Is_Love/</id><title>Hollerado - If It Is Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:18:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:18:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/If_It_Is_Love/" title="Hollerado - If It Is Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Over the mountains high <br>Stretches the dark, knit, sober sky <br>Oh how I long to rest my feet <br>Oh how I long to rest with thee <br><br>If it is love you love the most <br>If it is love that you love the most <br>If it is love that you love the most <br>Know I will please you Lord <br>Know I will please you Lord <br><br>I must keep walking down <br>Across the river and into town <br>On through the dark and narrow streets <br>I look for a place to rest my feet <br>I look for a place to rest from thee <br><br>If it is love you love the most <br>If it is love that you love the most <br>If it is love that you love the most <br>Know I will please you Lord <br>Know I will please you Lord <br><br>If it is love you love the most <br>If it is love that you love the most <br>If it is love that you love the most <br>Know I will please you Lord <br>Oh I'll please you Lord <br>I will please you Lord <br>I will please you Lord <br>I will please you Lord <br>I will please you, I'll please you Lord <br><br>If it is love you love the most <br>If it is love that you love the most <br>If it is love that you love the most <br>Know I will please you Lord <br>Know I will please you Lord <br><br>If it is love you love the most <br>Know I will please you Lord]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="If It Is Love" label="If It Is Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Age_Of_Communication/</id><title>Hollerado - Age Of Communication - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:18:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:18:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Age_Of_Communication/" title="Hollerado - Age Of Communication - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was awoken <br>Like a gasping for air in the night <br>Nothing was broken <br>I did not scream out loud in fright <br>I came for forgiveness, I came for forgiveness <br>If you could concede this, I'd go back to sleeping alright <br><br>I wish for water <br>Like a blind man alone in the street <br>Been to the river <br>You're holding your cup out for me <br>I came for forgiveness, I came for forgiveness <br>I came for forgiveness, oh, I don't talk so well <br><br>In this age of communication <br>I don't speak so well <br><br>I came for forgiveness, oh, I don't talk so well <br><br>In this age of communication <br>I don't speak so well <br>This age of communication <br>I don't speak so well <br>In this age of communication <br>I don't speak so well]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="Age Of Communication" label="Age Of Communication"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Eloise/</id><title>Hollerado - Eloise - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:18:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:18:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Eloise/" title="Hollerado - Eloise - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The first time I saw you crawling there <br>You're such a mess on the floor <br>You were, a million miles from reality <br>And I, I couldn't envy you more <br>Saw you, you took another sip from that bottle <br>And, you looked right into my soul <br>You had the, fresh face of a black and white movie star <br>Who's never gonna grow old <br><br>Eloise, please don't fuck it up like me <br>Take a day at a time, you'll see <br>Everything's gold, everything, everything <br><br>There's a business man with a black, leather jacket, yeah <br>You got him paying your bills <br>And your, mother's marrying a millionaire now <br>She's who gives you those pills, I know how it goes <br>They said you got eyes like your father but <br>He still entitled to admit <br>Yeah and you just love to watch the world pass by <br>But you're, you're too young for regret <br><br>Eloise, please don't fuck it up like me <br>Take a day at a time, you'll see <br>Everything's gold, everything, everything <br>Eloise, please don't fuck it up like me <br>Take a day at a time, you'll see <br>Everything's gold, everything, everything <br><br>I've seen the morning come up from the other side <br>I've been the belle of the ball, but <br>When the carnival's packed up and left you go <br>What is left of it all <br>And, you don't have a bedtime, no <br>You barely even got a bed, but <br>Only you can teach yourself to walk <br>You gotta long road, long road ahead <br>Oh Eloise <br><br>Eloise, please don't fuck it up like me <br>Take a day at a time, you'll see <br>Everything's gold <br>Eloise, please don't fuck it up like me <br>Take a day at a time, you'll see <br>Everything's gold]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="Eloise" label="Eloise"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Sorry_Youre_Alright/</id><title>Hollerado - Sorry You`re Alright - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:18:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:18:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Sorry_Youre_Alright/" title="Hollerado - Sorry You`re Alright - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes I feel old, then I lose my mind <br>Then I lose control, and then there I go <br>Where I never wanted to go, can't explain those grooves <br>We're all meant to live, that's called being alive <br>I'm sorry you're alright, sorry it's not blind <br>But I can't help you see, and you can't help me breathe <br>And make me feel alright <br><br>I'll never be your king <br>I'll never be fine <br>Never in my mind <br>As long as you are here <br>And you're by my side <br>Then I'll feel alright <br><br>Sometimes I sleep too much, and then stay up late <br>And then I lose control, and then there I go <br>Where I never wanted to go, where you're shady and she chills <br>We're all meant to live, that's from getting high <br>I'm sorry you're alright, sorry if you're blind <br>But I can't help you see, you can't help me breathe <br>And make me feel alright <br><br>I'll never be your king <br>I'll never be fine <br>Never in my mind <br>As long as you are here <br>And you're by my side <br>Then I'll feel alright <br><br>I'll never be your king <br>I'll never be fine <br>Never in my mind <br>As long as you are here <br>And you're by my side <br>Then I'll feel alright <br>As long as you are here <br>And you're by my side <br>Then I'll feel alright]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="Sorry You`re Alright" label="Sorry You`re Alright"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Rollerskater/</id><title>Hollerado - Rollerskater - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:18:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:18:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Rollerskater/" title="Hollerado - Rollerskater - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[He got a little bit of a grass <br>He got a smile on his face <br>He got a little bit of sass <br>He got a red headband, like the Dire Straits man <br>Are you a here all alone, ah you feel all alone <br><br>Do you notice the stairs <br>There's a group of teenage girls takin' pictures with their phones <br><br>Rollerskater with your head in the clouds <br>You move your body like there's no one around <br>People are poison, their life you'd have poured gin <br>Wish I could care about nothing like you <br>Wish I could care about nothing like you <br><br>I got trouble with my nerves <br>I'm a little neurotic, well a lot of neurotic <br>Started doubling my words doublin' <br>I got sweat, wet hands like a nervous Spiderman <br>And I'm here all alone, and I'm here all alone <br><br>And I'm watching you twirl <br>And the laughing kids are joking how you never kissed a girl <br><br>Rollerskater with your head in the clouds <br>You move your body like there's no one around <br>People are poison, their life you'd have poured gin <br>Wish I could care about nothing like you <br>Rollerskater, rollerskater <br>Wish I could care about nothing like you <br><br>And I wish I knew how, not to worry about <br>When the people are laughing and thinking out loud <br>You got it all figured out, I wish I didn't care about <br>What the corny people think about the way I <br><br>Rollerskater you got no one to please <br>Got you socks pulled up to the cuts on your knees <br><br>Rollerskater with your head in the clouds <br>You move your body like there's no one around <br>People are poison, their life you'd have poured gin <br>Wish I could care about nothing like you <br>Rollerskater, rollerskater <br>Wish I could care about nothing like you <br>Rollerskater, rollerskater <br>Wish I could care about nothing like you <br>Wish I could care about nothing like you]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="Rollerskater" label="Rollerskater"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/I_Got_You/</id><title>Hollerado - I Got You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:18:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:18:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/I_Got_You/" title="Hollerado - I Got You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Rich kids, make it look easy <br>They got me worrying what I'm doing with my life <br>I try, I barely get by then I don't make him wait 'till he dies <br><br>Ooh, rich kids Making the world spin <br>Ooh, rich kids London time <br>Rich kids Posted pictures from paradise <br>I'm just trying to keep my head above the poverty line <br><br>I got something they don't <br>I got you <br>I got you <br>I got something they don't <br>I got you <br>I got you <br><br>Magazines, I just can't read them <br>Make it seem like you're barely a man <br>It's just wrong to have nothing in common with the princes and queens who wear the <br><br>Ooh, rich kids Making the world spin <br>Ooh, rich kids Calvin Klein <br>Rich kids Got me staring at my sneakers <br>Singing, even the news is <br><br>I got something they don't <br>I got you <br>I got you <br>I got something they don't <br>I got you <br>I got you <br><br>You are my fast car, my trust fund <br>My priceless Matisse <br>I love your company, like they love their companies <br><br>I got something they don't <br>I got you <br>I got you <br>I got something they don't <br>I got you <br>I got you]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="I Got You" label="I Got You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Grief_Money/</id><title>Hollerado - Grief Money - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:18:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:18:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Grief_Money/" title="Hollerado - Grief Money - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Our water's black and our pockets are filthy <br>Let's cut another blank check to the wealthiest man <br>Adjust for inflation, turn dollars into dopamine <br>Dollars into dopamine <br>Dopamine <br>Dopamine <br>Dopamine <br><br>I want more, I want more <br>Grief money <br>I want more, I want more <br>Grief money <br><br>Politicians campaigning how they love mother nature <br>Tax rooms to distract you but in back rooms they rape her <br>It's a white man's world, fuck education <br>Keep the kids down while the grown ups settle accounts <br>Accounts <br>Accounts <br>Settle accounts <br><br>I want more, I want more <br>Grief money <br>I want more, I want more <br>Grief money <br>I want more, I want more <br>Grief <br><br>Don't let the sun go down on your empire <br>Until every last dollar's delivered <br>If half the worlds starves on water and rice <br>There'll be more for us, oh, wouldn't that be nice <br>I want more, I want more, I want home <br><br>I want more, I want more <br>Grief money <br>I want more, I want more <br>Grief money <br>I want more, I want more <br>Grief]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="Grief Money" label="Grief Money"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Brick_Wall/</id><title>Hollerado - Brick Wall - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:18:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:18:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Brick_Wall/" title="Hollerado - Brick Wall - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Daddy has a farm down in Mexcio <br>Mommy does a raindance at the town strip show <br>Oh the cops they call me monkey man, but I'm reading a book <br>Well daddy's got a farm where the same cops don't look <br><br>I'm walk alone, the desert at night <br>And I follow lights towards the border, and I say <br>Hey, what's a brick wall doing in my way <br><br>Daddy has a farm on the shady side of town <br>Mommy's on the porch she's always sliding down <br>For me there's nothing here, if I don't wanna be a crook <br>And daddy has a farm where the cops don't look <br><br>I'm walk alone, the desert at night <br>And I follow lights towards the border, and I say <br>Hey, what's a brick wall doing in my way <br>Hey, what's a brick wall doing in my way <br><br>I walk at night <br>I walk at night <br>I walk at night all alone <br>Follow the lights <br>Follow the lights <br>Follow the lights take me home <br><br>I dug a hole when my daddy died <br>So I hid behind the shed held my shovel and cried <br>I walk the desert at night <br>And I follow lights towards the border, and I say <br>Hey, what's a brick wall doing in my way <br>What's a brick wall doing in my way <br>What's a brick wall doing in my way <br>What's a brick wall doing in my way What do you always gotta be a <br>Brick wall standing in my way]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="Brick Wall" label="Brick Wall"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Dont_Shake/</id><title>Hollerado - Don`t Shake - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:18:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:18:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Dont_Shake/" title="Hollerado - Don`t Shake - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you find somebody to love <br>And they give you the strength to go on <br>Be prepared for the day, when they need you <br><br>You were driving through a wintery cold <br>With a hand so sure of the road <br>Through a fear, that you fear, but you can't show <br><br>Don't shake <br>Right now it's your turn to pretend <br>Everything will be right in the end <br>This passenger your driving depends <br>On your steady hand <br>On your steady hand <br><br>It may rain, and it may snow <br>But your passenger don't even know <br>While they sleep, you will keep total control <br><br>Don't shake <br>Right now it's your turn to pretend <br>Everything will be right in the end <br>This passenger your driving depends <br>On your steady hand <br>On your steady hand <br>On your steady hand <br><br>And when they wake <br>You will be right there beside them <br>Make them believe <br>There's no fear inside you <br>Don't shake <br><br>Don't shake <br>Right now it's your turn to pretend <br>Everything will be right in the end <br>This passenger your driving depends <br>So don't shake <br>Don't shake <br>Your steady hand <br>Your steady hand <br>Your steady hand]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="Don`t Shake" label="Don`t Shake"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Born_Yesterday/</id><title>Hollerado - Born Yesterday - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:18:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:18:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Born_Yesterday/" title="Hollerado - Born Yesterday - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I had my head, kicked in by a wild love <br>And it drained, the colour outta my blood <br>I'd smell her sweat, on every man that I'd see <br>And I'd wake up sick from drugging myself to sleep <br><br>For you make me feel <br>Like I was born yesterday <br>Like I've never been broken <br>Never been broken <br>You make me feel <br>Like I was born yesterday <br>Like I've never been broken <br>Never been broken <br><br>I was jagged glass, deep underwater <br>Till I washed up, soft on your shore <br>Your healing eyes, they shine like Orion <br>And I am the first human to look upwards in the night <br><br>You make me feel <br>Like I was born yesterday <br>Like I've never been broken <br>Never been broken <br>You make me feel <br>Like I was born yesterday <br>Like I've never been broken <br>Never been broken <br><br>Oh don't let go <br>I won't let go <br>So don't let go <br><br>You make me feel <br>Like I was born yesterday <br>Like I've never been broken <br>Never been broken <br>You make me feel <br>Like I was born yesterday <br>Like I've never been broken <br>Never been broken <br><br>You make me go <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>You make me go <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>You make me go <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>You make me go <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>You make me go yeah]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="Born Yesterday" label="Born Yesterday"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lil_Yachty/Harley/</id><title>Lil Yachty - Harley - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:18:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:18:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lil_Yachty/Harley/" title="Lil Yachty - Harley - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's Lil Boat, all my diamonds go bling, blang, blaow <br>Lil Boat <br><br>Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley <br>Ridin' like a Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley <br>My new bitch a bot <br>My new bitch a Barbie <br>And I'm balling hard <br>Can't nobody guard me, no, no <br>Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley <br>Ridin' like a Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley <br>My new bitch a bot <br>My new bitch a barbie <br>And I'm balling so damn hard <br>Can't nobody guard me, no, no <br><br>Late night with the report like Colbert, aye <br>Love her iced out like a Kid Cuisine <br>Lil Boat in the magazine <br>Big bro keep the magazines <br>Charged up like an Alkaline <br>Bet she feel dick in her spine <br><br>Oh, ridin' like a Harley <br>My bitch a Barbie <br>Can't no one guard Boat <br><br>Harley Harley Harley Harley Harley <br>Ridin' like a Harley Harley Harley Harley Harley <br>My new bitch a bot <br>My new bitch a Barbie <br>And I'm balling hard <br>Can't nobody guard me, no, no <br>Harley Harley Harley Harley Harley <br>Ridin' like a Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley, aye <br>My new bitch a bot <br>My new bitch a Barbie <br>And I'm balling so damn hard <br>Can't nobody guard me, no, no <br><br>Ain't nobody flexing like me <br>Ain't no nigga flexing like me <br>18, got the brand new AMG <br>Yo baby daddy tryna ride front seat, no <br>Stop hating on a young nigga 'cause I'm getting cake <br>Right wrist so dipped look like a Frosted Flake <br>Top of the building, athletes be my neighbours <br>These niggas soft like Life Savers <br>These niggas be bitches <br>Most of these niggas be hoes <br>Guess that that's just how it goes <br><br>Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley <br>Ridin' like a Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley <br>My new bitch a bot <br>My new bitch a Barbie <br>And I'm balling hard <br>Can't nobody guard me, no, no <br>Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley <br>Ridin' like a Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley, Harley <br>My new bitch a bot <br>My new bitch a Barbie <br>And I'm balling so damn hard <br>Can't nobody guard me, no, no <br><br>Oh, like a Harley <br>Can't no one guard me <br>Can't no one fuck with Boat]]></content><category term="Lil Yachty" label="Lil Yachty"/><category term="Harley" label="Harley"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이현/Mom/</id><title>이현 - Mom - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:18:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:18:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%98%84/Mom/" title="이현 - Mom - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그동안 얼마나 힘들었나요 <br>당신의 이름이 어색해지기까지 <br>얼마나 수없이 아파했었나요 <br>같은 곳을 봐도 서로 달랐던 말들로 <br>아직 다 알진 못해요 <br>그대가 마음에 <br>담고 사는 슬픔을 <br>하지만 이젠 알아요 <br>그대의 마음에 <br>담고 사는 사람 나란걸 <br>매일 그대가 <br>눈물로 보낸 하늘의 기도를 <br>절대로 잊지 못해요 <br>조금은 느려진 걸음 <br>이젠 내가 함께 할게요 <br>매일 감사해요 <br>나보다 나를 <br>사랑해준 사람 <br>언제나 내 곁을 지켜준 <br>불러도 부르고 싶은 <br>이름 <br>mom <br>그동안 얼마나 아파했나요 <br>당신의 마음에 묻어버린 상처로 <br>가끔은 말없이 주저앉은 채 <br>한참동안 소리없이 흐르던 눈물 <br>매일 그대가 <br>눈물로 보낸 하늘의 기도를 <br>절대로 잊지 못해요 <br>조금은 느려진 걸음 <br>이젠 내가 함께 할게요 <br>매일 감사해요 <br>나보다 나를 <br>사랑해준 사람 <br>언제나 나를 지켜준 <br>변하지 않는 그 사랑 <br>그대 <br>사랑합니다 <br>빛나는 그대 잊지 못해요 <br>불러도 부르고 싶은 <br>말로다 표현 못하는 <br>이름 <br>mom <br>]]></content><category term="이현" label="이현"/><category term="Mom" label="Mom"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/봄바람_등을_타고_제8회_MBC_창작동요제_1990/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 봄바람 등을 타고 (제8회 MBC 창작동요제, 1990) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:18:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:18:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%B4%84%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C_%EB%93%B1%EC%9D%84_%ED%83%80%EA%B3%A0_%EC%A0%9C8%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1990/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 봄바람 등을 타고 (제8회 MBC 창작동요제, 1990) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[초록 바람이 불어와 <br>나뭇잎을 물들이고 <br>노란 바람이 불어와 <br>개나리꽃 물들이지 <br>곱게 머리 빗은 보슬비도 <br>봄바람 등을 타고 <br>라라라 콧노래 부르며 <br>소올솔 내려오지 <br><br>꿈 빛 바람이 불어와 <br>아지랑이 펴오르고 <br>남빛 바람이 불어와 <br>호로로롱 산새 날지 <br>곱게 단장한 봄 아씨도 <br>봄바람 등을 타고 <br>라라라 콧노래 부르며 <br>사알살 다가오지]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="봄바람 등을 타고 (제8회 MBC 창작동요제, 1990)" label="봄바람 등을 타고 (제8회 MBC 창작동요제, 1990)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/새싹들이다_제1회_MBC_창작동요제_1983/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 새싹들이다 (제1회 MBC 창작동요제, 1983) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%83%88%EC%8B%B9%EB%93%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%A4_%EC%A0%9C1%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1983/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 새싹들이다 (제1회 MBC 창작동요제, 1983) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마음을 열어 하늘을 보라 <br>넓고 높고 푸른 하늘 <br>가슴을 펴고 소리쳐보자 <br>우리들은 새싹들이다 <br>푸른 꿈이 자란다 곱고 고운 꿈 <br>두리둥실 떠간다 구름이 되어 <br>너른 벌판을 달려나가자 <br>씩씩하게 나가자 <br>어깨를 걸고 함께 나가자 <br>발맞춰 나가자 <br><br>마음을 열어 하늘을 보라 <br>넓고 높고 푸른 하늘 <br>가슴을 펴고 소리쳐보자 <br>우리들은 새싹들이다 <br>해님 되자 달님 되자 별님이 되자 <br>너른 세상 불을 밝힐 큰 빛이 되자 <br>무지개 빛깔 아름다운 꿈 <br>모두 우리 차지다 <br>너와 나 함께 우리가 되어 <br>힘차게 나가자]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="새싹들이다 (제1회 MBC 창작동요제, 1983)" label="새싹들이다 (제1회 MBC 창작동요제, 1983)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/봄_제8회_MBC_창작동요제_1990/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 봄 (제8회 MBC 창작동요제, 1990) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%B4%84_%EC%A0%9C8%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1990/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 봄 (제8회 MBC 창작동요제, 1990) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니나니 나니나 니나니나 <br>버들피리 소리가 들려온다 <br>니나니 나니나 니나니나 <br>버들피리 소리가 들려온다 <br>니나니 나니나 니나니나 <br>시내에 얼음이 다 풀렸다 <br>니나니 나니나 니나니나 <br>잔디가 파랗게 돋아난다 <br>니나니 나니나 니나니나 <br>산나물 캐러들 올라간다 <br>니나니 나니나 니나니나 <br>제비가 물차고 날아든다 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="봄 (제8회 MBC 창작동요제, 1990)" label="봄 (제8회 MBC 창작동요제, 1990)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/아빠_힘내세요_제15회_MBC_창작동요제_1997/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 아빠 힘내세요 (제15회 MBC 창작동요제, 1997) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%95%84%EB%B9%A0_%ED%9E%98%EB%82%B4%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94_%EC%A0%9C15%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1997/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 아빠 힘내세요 (제15회 MBC 창작동요제, 1997) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[딩동댕 초인종 소리에 <br>얼른 문을 열었더니 <br>그토록 기다리던 아빠가 <br>문 앞에 서계셨죠 <br>너무나 반가워 웃으며 <br>아빠하고 불렀는데 <br>어쩐지 오늘 아빠의 얼굴이 <br>우울해 보이네요 <br>무슨 일이 생겼나요 <br>무슨 걱정 있나요 <br>마음대로 안 되는 일 <br>오늘 있었나요 <br>아빠 힘내세요! <br>우리가 있잖아요 <br>아빠 힘내세요! 우리가 있어요 <br><br>딩동댕 초인종 소리에 <br>얼른 문을 열었더니 <br>그토록 기다리던 아빠가 <br>문 앞에 서계셨죠 <br>너무나 반가워 웃으며 <br>아빠하고 불렀는데 <br>어쩐지 오늘 아빠의 얼굴이 <br>우울해 보이네요 <br>무슨 일이 생겼나요 <br>무슨 걱정 있나요 <br>마음대로 안 되는 일 <br>오늘 있었나요 <br>아빠 힘내세요! <br>우리가 있잖아요 <br>아빠 힘내세요! 우리가 있어요 <br>힘내세요~ 아빠!]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="아빠 힘내세요 (제15회 MBC 창작동요제, 1997)" label="아빠 힘내세요 (제15회 MBC 창작동요제, 1997)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/산마루에서_제4회_MBC_창작동요제_1986/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 산마루에서 (제4회 MBC 창작동요제, 1986) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%82%B0%EB%A7%88%EB%A3%A8%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C_%EC%A0%9C4%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1986/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 산마루에서 (제4회 MBC 창작동요제, 1986) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[산마루에서 외쳐보자 <br>야호 야호 야하호 <br>나무들이 노래한다 <br>야호 야호 야하호 <br>새소리 물소리가 골짜기에 차고 <br>바람에 푸른 잎이 깃발이 되네 <br>산마루에서 외쳐보자 <br>야호 야호 야하호 <br>나무들이 노래한다 <br>야호 야호 야하호 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="산마루에서 (제4회 MBC 창작동요제, 1986)" label="산마루에서 (제4회 MBC 창작동요제, 1986)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/새봄_제10회_MBC_창작동요제_1992/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 새봄 (제10회 MBC 창작동요제, 1992) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%83%88%EB%B4%84_%EC%A0%9C10%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1992/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 새봄 (제10회 MBC 창작동요제, 1992) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새파란 봄 하늘에 <br>아지랑이 꿈꾸고 <br>풀피리 소리에 눈꽃 뜨고 <br>나비는 즐겁네 <br>꽃바람 살랑 불면 <br>진달래 손을 잡고 <br>날아라 산새야 <br>꿈을 싣고 새봄 노래하자 <br><br>새파란 봄 하늘에 <br>버들가지 춤추고 <br>여울물 소리에 장단 맞춰 <br>나비는 춤추네 <br>꽃바람 살랑 불면 <br>개나리 손을 잡고 <br>날아라 산새야 꿈을 엮어 <br>새봄 얘기하자]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="새봄 (제10회 MBC 창작동요제, 1992)" label="새봄 (제10회 MBC 창작동요제, 1992)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/가보고_싶다_제18회_MBC_창작동요제_2000/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 가보고 싶다 (제18회 MBC 창작동요제, 2000) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EA%B0%80%EB%B3%B4%EA%B3%A0_%EC%8B%B6%EB%8B%A4_%EC%A0%9C18%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_2000/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 가보고 싶다 (제18회 MBC 창작동요제, 2000) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[진달래 동산에서 즐겁게 놀다가 <br>살며시 눈을 감고 <br>너의 모습 그린다 <br>낙동강 강가에 오고 싶지 <br>압록강 두만강에 가고 싶다 <br>햇볕이 쨍쨍 째는 무더운 여름날 <br>송사리 잡으면서 깜둥이가 되자 <br><br>단풍잎 곱게 물든 가을 언덕에서 <br>동화책 펼쳐놓고 <br>너의 모습 그린다 <br>한라산 설악산이 보고 싶지 <br>백두산 금강산이 보고 싶다 <br>흰 눈이 오는 날엔 흰 눈을 맞으며 <br>두 손을 마주 잡고 <br>기쁜 노래 부르자]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="가보고 싶다 (제18회 MBC 창작동요제, 2000)" label="가보고 싶다 (제18회 MBC 창작동요제, 2000)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/아기_다람쥐_또미_제14회_MBC_창작동요제_1996/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 아기 다람쥐 또미 (제14회 MBC 창작동요제, 1996) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%95%84%EA%B8%B0_%EB%8B%A4%EB%9E%8C%EC%A5%90_%EB%98%90%EB%AF%B8_%EC%A0%9C14%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1996/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 아기 다람쥐 또미 (제14회 MBC 창작동요제, 1996) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쪼로로롱 산새가 <br>노래하는 숲 속에 <br>예쁜 아기 다람쥐가 <br>살고 있었어요 <br>울창한 숲 속 푸른 나무 위에서 <br>아기다람쥐 또미가 <br>살고 있었어요 <br>야호! 랄라 노래 부르자 <br>야호! 숲 속의 아침을 <br>야호! 트랄라 귀여운 <br>아기다람쥐 또미! <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="아기 다람쥐 또미 (제14회 MBC 창작동요제, 1996)" label="아기 다람쥐 또미 (제14회 MBC 창작동요제, 1996)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/푸른_꿈을_키워가요_제2회_MBC_창작동요제_1984/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 푸른 꿈을 키워가요 (제2회 MBC 창작동요제, 1984) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%ED%91%B8%EB%A5%B8_%EA%BF%88%EC%9D%84_%ED%82%A4%EC%9B%8C%EA%B0%80%EC%9A%94_%EC%A0%9C2%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1984/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 푸른 꿈을 키워가요 (제2회 MBC 창작동요제, 1984) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[움츠렸던 날개 펴고 <br>저 하늘을 날아봐요 <br>이 세상이 넓은 줄은 <br>이제까지 몰랐어요 <br>망망한 저 바다엔 <br>우리의 희망 가득 <br>높고 푸른 저 숲속엔 <br>힘찬 기상 서려 있네 <br>닫혀있던 마음의 창 <br>하늘 향해 활짝 열고 <br>새싹들의 푸른 꿈을 <br>싱그럽게 키워가요 <br><br>가슴속에 감추어진 <br>넓은 세계 바라봐요 <br>티 없이 밝은 마음 <br>가득하게 차 있어요 <br>아름다운 가슴속에 <br>뜨거운 사랑 가득 <br>미소 짓는 내 얼굴엔 <br>참된 평화 서려 있네 <br>닫혀있던 마음의 창 <br>하늘 향해 활짝 열고 <br>새싹들의 푸른 꿈을 <br>싱그럽게 키워가요]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="푸른 꿈을 키워가요 (제2회 MBC 창작동요제, 1984)" label="푸른 꿈을 키워가요 (제2회 MBC 창작동요제, 1984)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/봄을_그리는_색연필_제2회_KBS_창작동요대회_1990/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 봄을 그리는 색연필 (제2회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1990) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%B4%84%EC%9D%84_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_%EC%83%89%EC%97%B0%ED%95%84_%EC%A0%9C2%ED%9A%8C_KBS_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EB%8C%80%ED%9A%8C_1990/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 봄을 그리는 색연필 (제2회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1990) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[파란 남청 색연필로 <br>파란 하늘 그리고 <br>하양 초록 색연필로 <br>정성 들여 칠하면 <br>토끼 구름 솜구름 <br>산 위에 피어나고 <br>졸졸졸 흘러가는 <br>골짜기 맑은 냇물 <br>보리밭 푸른 물결 <br>출렁이는 도화지에 <br>종달새 날아와 즐겁게 노래하네 <br><br>초록 연두 색연필로 <br>나뭇가지 그리고 <br>노랑 분홍 색연필로 <br>정성 들여 칠하면 <br>높은 산 넓은 들에 <br>새싹들이 돋아나고 <br>하르르 피어나는 <br>살구꽃 진달래꽃 <br>꽃다지 민들레꽃 <br>수를 놓은 도화지에 <br>노랑나비 날아와 <br>즐겁게 춤을 추네]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="봄을 그리는 색연필 (제2회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1990)" label="봄을 그리는 색연필 (제2회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1990)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/참_좋은_말_제25회_MBC_창작동요제_2007/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 참 좋은 말 (제25회 MBC 창작동요제, 2007) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%B0%B8_%EC%A2%8B%EC%9D%80_%EB%A7%90_%EC%A0%9C25%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_2007/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 참 좋은 말 (제25회 MBC 창작동요제, 2007) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑해요 이 한마디 참 좋은 말 <br>우리 식구 자고 나면 주고받는 말 <br>사랑해요 이 한마디 참 좋은 말 <br>엄마 아빠 일터 갈 때 주고받는 말 <br>이 말이 좋아서 온종일 신이 나지요 <br>이 말이 좋아서 온종일 일 맛나지요 <br>이 말이 좋아서 온종일 <br>가슴이 콩닥콩닥 뛴데요 <br>사랑해요 이 한마디 참 좋은 말 <br>나는 나는 이 한마디가 정말 좋아요 <br>나는 나는 이 한마디가 정말 좋아요 <br>(반복) <br>사랑 사랑해요]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="참 좋은 말 (제25회 MBC 창작동요제, 2007)" label="참 좋은 말 (제25회 MBC 창작동요제, 2007)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/반딧불이_제22회_MBC_창작동요제_2004/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 반딧불이 (제22회 MBC 창작동요제, 2004) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%B0%98%EB%94%A7%EB%B6%88%EC%9D%B4_%EC%A0%9C22%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_2004/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 반딧불이 (제22회 MBC 창작동요제, 2004) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[해님이 서산으로 그 모습 감추면 <br>땅거미 하늘하늘 온 세상 내리고 <br>까만 하늘에 별들이 총총 <br>땅에는 반디가 깜빡 <br>손에 손마다 작은 불 밝히고 <br>반디야 너 어디 가니 <br>맑은 바람 살랑 부는 <br>고향 마을 찾아간다 <br><br>달님이 동산으로 둥실 떠오면 <br>온 세상 찰방찰방 <br>은빛 물결 넘치고 <br>까만 하늘에 별들이 총총 <br>땅에는 반디가 깜박 <br>손에 손마다 작은 초롱 들고 <br>반디야 너 어디 가니 <br>냇물소리 장단 맞춰 <br>살랑살랑 춤을 추니]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="반딧불이 (제22회 MBC 창작동요제, 2004)" label="반딧불이 (제22회 MBC 창작동요제, 2004)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/그림_그리고_싶은_날_제2회_KBS_창작동요대회_1990/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 그림 그리고 싶은 날 (제2회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1990) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%BC_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EA%B3%A0_%EC%8B%B6%EC%9D%80_%EB%82%A0_%EC%A0%9C2%ED%9A%8C_KBS_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EB%8C%80%ED%9A%8C_1990/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 그림 그리고 싶은 날 (제2회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1990) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하얀 종이 위에다 <br>아빠 얼굴 그려 보고 <br>하얀 종이 위에다 <br>엄마 얼굴 그려 보네 <br>나를 위해 고생하신 <br>부모님의 깊은 사랑 <br>그림 그리고 싶은 날 <br>제일 먼저 그려 봅니다 <br>그림 그리고 싶은 날 <br>제일 먼저 그려 봅니다 <br><br>하얀 종이 위에다 <br>학교 교정 그려 보고 <br>하얀 종이 위에다 <br>선생님을 얼굴 그려 보네 <br>나를 위해 수고하신 <br>선생님의 고마움을 <br>그림 그리고 싶은 날 <br>제일 먼저 그려 봅니다 <br>그림 그리고 싶은 날 <br>제일 먼저 그려 봅니다]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="그림 그리고 싶은 날 (제2회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1990)" label="그림 그리고 싶은 날 (제2회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1990)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/별과_꽃_제11회_MBC_창작동요제_1993/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 별과 꽃 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%B3%84%EA%B3%BC_%EA%BD%83_%EC%A0%9C11%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1993/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 별과 꽃 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[담 밑에 앉아서 쳐다보면 <br>별도 뵈고 꽃도 뵈고 <br>수많은 별들은 하늘의 꽃 <br>꽃들은 이 땅의 별 <br>꽃들은 예뻐서 별들은 안자요 <br>별들도 예뻐서 꽃들도 안자요 <br>초승달이 넘어가네 <br>밤새들도 잠들었네 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="별과 꽃 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993)" label="별과 꽃 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/꿀벌의_여행_제12회_MBC_창작동요제_1994/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 꿀벌의 여행 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EA%BF%80%EB%B2%8C%EC%9D%98_%EC%97%AC%ED%96%89_%EC%A0%9C12%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1994/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 꿀벌의 여행 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[윙윙 거칠고 험한 산을 날아가지요 <br>윙윙 머나먼 나라까지 꽃을 찾아서 <br>윙윙 조그만 날개 고단하여 <br>너무 지쳤지마는 <br>쉬지 않고 날아가지요 <br>윙윙 거칠고 험한 산을 날아가지요 <br>윙윙 머나먼 나라까지 꽃을 찾아서 <br>야! 야! 야! <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="꿀벌의 여행 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994)" label="꿀벌의 여행 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/이슬_제6회_MBC_창작동요제_1988/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 이슬 (제6회 MBC 창작동요제, 1988) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%AC_%EC%A0%9C6%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1988/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 이슬 (제6회 MBC 창작동요제, 1988) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[호롱 호롱 호롱 산새 소리에 <br>잠 깨어 뜰로 나가니 <br>풀잎마다 송송이 <br>맺힌 이슬 아름다워 <br>은쟁반에 가득 담아 <br>아가 옷 지어볼까 <br>색실에 곱게 끼워 <br>엄마 목걸이 만들까 <br>호롱 호롱 호롱 산새 소리에 <br>잠 깨어 뜰로 나가니 <br>풀잎마다 송송이 <br>맺힌 이슬 아름다워 <br><br>호롱 호롱 호롱 산새 소리에 <br>잠 깨어 뜰로 나가니 <br>꽃잎마다 송송이 <br>맺힌 이슬 아름다워 <br>편지 속에 가득 넣어 <br>해님께 보내볼까 <br>햇살에 곱게 달아 <br>구름에 메어 띄어 볼까 <br>호롱 호롱 호롱 산새 소리에 <br>잠 깨어 뜰로 나가니 <br>꽃잎마다 송송이 <br>맺힌 이슬 아름다워]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="이슬 (제6회 MBC 창작동요제, 1988)" label="이슬 (제6회 MBC 창작동요제, 1988)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/내가_제일_좋아하는_말_제13회_MBC_창작동요제_1995/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 내가 제일 좋아하는 말 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%82%B4%EA%B0%80_%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%BC_%EC%A2%8B%EC%95%84%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%A7%90_%EC%A0%9C13%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1995/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 내가 제일 좋아하는 말 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[몇천 번을 불러도 <br>더 부르고 싶은 말 <br>내가 제일 좋아하는 <br>그런 말이 하나 있죠 <br>어머니를 부를 때마다 <br>다가선 어머니 얼굴 <br>나에게 사랑으로 가르치시네 <br>몇천 번을 불러도 <br>더 부르고 싶은 말 <br>내가 제일 좋아하는 <br>어머니 내 어머니 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="내가 제일 좋아하는 말 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995)" label="내가 제일 좋아하는 말 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/숲속을_걸어요_제4회_MBC_창작동요제_1986/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 숲속을 걸어요 (제4회 MBC 창작동요제, 1986) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%88%B2%EC%86%8D%EC%9D%84_%EA%B1%B8%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94_%EC%A0%9C4%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1986/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 숲속을 걸어요 (제4회 MBC 창작동요제, 1986) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[숲속을 걸어요 <br>산새들이 속삭이는 길 <br>숲속을 걸어요 <br>꽃향기가 그윽한 길 <br>해님도 쉬었다 가는 길 <br>다람쥐가 넘나드는 길 <br>정다운 얼굴로 <br>우리 모두 숲속을 걸어요 <br><br>숲속을 걸어요 <br>맑은 바람 솔바람 이는 <br>숲속을 걸어요 <br>도랑물이 노래하는 길 <br>달님도 쉬었다 가는 길 <br>산노루가 넘나드는 길 <br>웃음 띤 얼굴로 <br>우리 모두 숲속을 걸어요]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="숲속을 걸어요 (제4회 MBC 창작동요제, 1986)" label="숲속을 걸어요 (제4회 MBC 창작동요제, 1986)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/기차를_타고_제1회_KBS_창작동요대회_1989/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 기차를 타고 (제1회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1989) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EA%B8%B0%EC%B0%A8%EB%A5%BC_%ED%83%80%EA%B3%A0_%EC%A0%9C1%ED%9A%8C_KBS_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EB%8C%80%ED%9A%8C_1989/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 기차를 타고 (제1회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1989) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기차 타고 신나게 달려가 보자 <br>높은 산도 지나고 <br>넓은 들도 지나고 <br>푸른 산을 지날 땐 산새를 찾고 <br>넓은 바다 지날 땐 물새와 놀고 <br>설레임을 가득 안고 달려가 보자 <br>새로운 세상이 자꾸자꾸 보인다 <br><br>기차 타고 신나게 달려가 보자 <br>높은 산도 지나고 <br>넓은 들도 지나고 <br>따뜻한 마음을 서로 나누면 <br>처음 만난 옆 사람도 정다운 이웃 <br>즐거움을 가득 안고 달려가 보자 <br>아름다운 세상이 자꾸자꾸 보인다]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="기차를 타고 (제1회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1989)" label="기차를 타고 (제1회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1989)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/왜_이렇게_덥지__제28회_MBC_창작동요제_2010/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 왜 이렇게 덥지? (제28회 MBC 창작동요제, 2010) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%99%9C_%EC%9D%B4%EB%A0%87%EA%B2%8C_%EB%8D%A5%EC%A7%80__%EC%A0%9C28%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_2010/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 왜 이렇게 덥지? (제28회 MBC 창작동요제, 2010) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아이스크림 좋아 <br>냉장고 자꾸 열면 <br>빙하가 녹잖아 펭귄이 싫어해 <br>무심코 켜놓은 컴퓨터 때문에 <br>지구가 아파 울고 있어 <br>물놀이 좋아 수도꼭지 자꾸 틀면 <br>바다가 더워져 고래가 싫어해 <br>무심코 켜놓은 형광등 때문에 <br>지구가 점점 더워 더워 더워지네 <br>지구는 벗을 옷도 없는데 <br>자꾸만 덥게 하면 안 되는데 <br>자전거 타고서 달려보자 <br>우리 지구 시원하게 <br>지구는 벗을 옷도 없는데 <br>자꾸만 덥게 하면 안 되는데 <br>나무 한 그루 심어보자 <br>우리 지구 시원하게 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="왜 이렇게 덥지? (제28회 MBC 창작동요제, 2010)" label="왜 이렇게 덥지? (제28회 MBC 창작동요제, 2010)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/내_동생_참새래요_제25회_MBC_창작동요제_2007/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 내 동생 참새래요 (제25회 MBC 창작동요제, 2007) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%82%B4_%EB%8F%99%EC%83%9D_%EC%B0%B8%EC%83%88%EB%9E%98%EC%9A%94_%EC%A0%9C25%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_2007/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 내 동생 참새래요 (제25회 MBC 창작동요제, 2007) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 동생 참새래요 짹짹짹짹 <br>잠시도 쉬지 않고 짹짹짹짹 <br>입술은 오물조물 눈은 동글 <br>안으면 조용할까요 <br>난 숙제도 해야 하는데 <br>난 노래도 하고 싶은데 <br>나만 따라다니는 동생 <br>놀자고 짹짹 랄랄랄라 <br>그래도 엄마 아빠 귀엽다고요 <br>짹짹짹짹짹 노래하래요 <br>조금은 얄밉고 시끄럽지만 <br>귀여운 내 동생이죠 <br><br>내 동생 참새래요 짹짹짹짹 <br>입도 안 아픈가 봐 짹짹짹짹 <br>폴짝 쿵 저만 혼자 신이 났죠 <br>잠들면 조용할까요 <br>난 만화도 보고 싶은데 <br>난 친구랑 놀고 싶은데 <br>나만 따라다니는 동생 <br>싫어도 짹짹 랄랄랄라 <br>엄마는 큰 딸이라 예쁘다면서 <br>짹짹짹 노래하는 동생만 봐요 <br>가끔은 심술 나 돌아서지만 <br>귀여운 내 동생이죠]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="내 동생 참새래요 (제25회 MBC 창작동요제, 2007)" label="내 동생 참새래요 (제25회 MBC 창작동요제, 2007)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/연날리기_제7회_MBC_창작동요제_1989/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 연날리기 (제7회 MBC 창작동요제, 1989) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%97%B0%EB%82%A0%EB%A6%AC%EA%B8%B0_%EC%A0%9C7%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1989/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 연날리기 (제7회 MBC 창작동요제, 1989) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[에헤야 디야 바람 분다 <br>연을 날려 보자 <br>에헤야 디야 잘도 난다 <br>저 하늘 높이 난다 <br>무지개 옷을 입고 저 하늘에 <br>꼬리를 흔들며 <br>모두 다 어울려서 친구 된다 <br>두둥실 춤을 춘다 <br>에헤야 디야 바람 분다 <br>연을 날려 보자 <br>에헤야 디야 잘도 난다 <br>우리의 꿈을 싣고 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="연날리기 (제7회 MBC 창작동요제, 1989)" label="연날리기 (제7회 MBC 창작동요제, 1989)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/수건돌리기_제8회_MBC_창작동요제_1990/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 수건돌리기 (제8회 MBC 창작동요제, 1990) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%88%98%EA%B1%B4%EB%8F%8C%EB%A6%AC%EA%B8%B0_%EC%A0%9C8%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1990/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 수건돌리기 (제8회 MBC 창작동요제, 1990) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람 솔솔 불어오는 산에 올라가 <br>파란 하늘 노란 들판 내려다보며 <br>잔디밭에 옹기종기 모여 앉아서 <br>수건 돌리기를 해보자 <br>손잡고 동그랗게 모이자 <br>모두 모이자 <br>랄랄라 누가 누가 술래냐 <br>가위 바위 보 <br>빙글빙글 돌아간다 술래가 돈다 <br>우리 모두 손뼉 치며 노래 부르자 <br>파란 하늘 높이높이 올라가도록 <br>소리 높여 노래 부르자 <br><br>시냇물이 흘러가는 들판에 나가 <br>하얀 구름 푸른 산을 바라다보며 <br>모래밭에 옹기종기 모여 앉아서 <br>수건 돌리기를 해보자 <br>손잡고 동그랗게 모이자 <br>모두 모이자 <br>랄랄라 누가 누가 술래냐 <br>가위 바위 보 <br>빙글빙글 돌아간다 술래가 돈다 <br>누구 뒤에 놓았는지 알려 주지 마 <br>수철이가 붙잡혔다 노래 불러라 <br>손뼉 치며 따라 부르자]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="수건돌리기 (제8회 MBC 창작동요제, 1990)" label="수건돌리기 (제8회 MBC 창작동요제, 1990)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/아이들은_제7회_MBC_창작동요제_1989/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 아이들은 (제7회 MBC 창작동요제, 1989) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EB%93%A4%EC%9D%80_%EC%A0%9C7%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1989/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 아이들은 (제7회 MBC 창작동요제, 1989) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세상이 이렇게 밝은 것은 <br>즐거운 노래로 가득 찬 것은 <br>집집마다 어린 해가 <br>자라고 있어서다 <br>그 해가 노래이기 때문이다 <br>어른들은 모를 거야 <br>아이들이 해인 것을 <br>하지만 금방이라도 <br>알 수 있지 알 수 있어 <br>아이들이 잠시 없다면 <br>아이들이 잠시 없다면 <br>나나나 나나나나 낮도 밤인 것을 <br>노랫소리 들리지 않는 것을 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="아이들은 (제7회 MBC 창작동요제, 1989)" label="아이들은 (제7회 MBC 창작동요제, 1989)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/종이접기_제4회_MBC_창작동요제_1986/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 종이접기 (제4회 MBC 창작동요제, 1986) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:19:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:19:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%A2%85%EC%9D%B4%EC%A0%91%EA%B8%B0_%EC%A0%9C4%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1986/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 종이접기 (제4회 MBC 창작동요제, 1986) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[색종이를 곱게 접어서 <br>물감으로 예쁘게 색칠하고 <br>알록달록 오색실 꼬리 달아 <br>비행기를 만들자 <br>솔솔 바람 부는 뒷동산에 <br>동네 친구 모두 모여서 <br>파란 하늘 향해 날리면 <br>새처럼 날아간다 <br>하늘 끝까지 날아라 <br>높이 더 높이 <br><br>도화지를 곱게 접어서 <br>색연필로 예쁘게 색칠하고 <br>노랑 파랑 은행잎 돛대 달아 <br>종이배를 만들자 <br>졸졸 노래하는 시냇가에 <br>동네 친구 모두 모여서 <br>파란 시냇물에 띄우면 <br>물 따라 흘러간다 <br>동해바다까지 흘러라 <br>멀리 더 멀리]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="종이접기 (제4회 MBC 창작동요제, 1986)" label="종이접기 (제4회 MBC 창작동요제, 1986)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/노을_제2회_MBC_창작동요제_1984/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 노을 (제2회 MBC 창작동요제, 1984) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%85%B8%EC%9D%84_%EC%A0%9C2%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1984/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 노을 (제2회 MBC 창작동요제, 1984) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람이 머물다 간 들판에 <br>모락모락 피어나는 저녁연기 <br>색동옷 갈아입은 가을 언덕에 <br>빨갛게 노을이 타고 있어요 <br>허수아비 팔 벌려 웃음 짓고 <br>초가지붕 둥근 박 꿈꿀 때 <br>고개 숙인 논밭의 열매 <br>노랗게 익어만 가는 <br>가을바람 머물다 간 들판에 <br>모락모락 피어나는 저녁연기 <br>색동옷 갈아입은 가을 언덕에 <br>붉게 물들어 타는 저녁놀 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="노을 (제2회 MBC 창작동요제, 1984)" label="노을 (제2회 MBC 창작동요제, 1984)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/네_잎_클로버_제14회_MBC_창작동요제_1996/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 네 잎 클로버 (제14회 MBC 창작동요제, 1996) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%84%A4_%EC%9E%8E_%ED%81%B4%EB%A1%9C%EB%B2%84_%EC%A0%9C14%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1996/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 네 잎 클로버 (제14회 MBC 창작동요제, 1996) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[깊고 작은 산골짜기 사이로 <br>맑은 물 흐르는 작은 샘터에 <br>예쁜 꽃들 사이에 살짝 숨겨진 <br>이슬 먹고 피어난 네 잎 클로버 <br>랄랄라 한 잎 랄랄라 두 잎 <br>랄랄라 세 잎 랄랄라 네 잎 <br>행운을 가져다 준다는 <br>수줍은 얼굴의 미소 <br>한줄기의 따스한 햇살 받으며 <br>희망으로 가득한 나의 친구야 <br>빛처럼 밝은 맘으로 <br>너를 닮고 싶어 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="네 잎 클로버 (제14회 MBC 창작동요제, 1996)" label="네 잎 클로버 (제14회 MBC 창작동요제, 1996)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/별_내리는_들_길에서_제13회_MBC_창작동요제_1995/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 별 내리는 들 길에서 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%B3%84_%EB%82%B4%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_%EB%93%A4_%EA%B8%B8%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C_%EC%A0%9C13%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1995/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 별 내리는 들 길에서 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[초저녁별 곱게 뿌린 들길을 <br>아빠하고 손을 잡고 <br>다정하게 걸어가는 길 위로 <br>은모래 빛깔 별이 내려요 <br>쪼롱 쪼로롱 짹짹짹 산새 소리에 <br>아기별들 눈 뜨고 <br>초승달님 내게 살며시 다가와 <br>별님처럼 살아가래요 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="별 내리는 들 길에서 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995)" label="별 내리는 들 길에서 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/시골_여행_제13회_MBC_창작동요제_1995/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 시골 여행 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B3%A8_%EC%97%AC%ED%96%89_%EC%A0%9C13%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1995/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 시골 여행 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[버스를 타고 가면 <br>눈을 감고 있어도 <br>어디 어딜 지나는지 나는야 알지 <br>향긋한 풀 내음 두 볼을 간질이면 <br>어디긴 어디야 탁 트인 들녘이지 <br><br>버스를 타고 가면 <br>바라보지 않아도 <br>어디 어딜 지나는지 나는야 알지 <br>솔바람 불어와 귓가에 살랑대면 <br>어디긴 어디야 우거진 숲 동네지]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="시골 여행 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995)" label="시골 여행 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/노을_지는_풍경_제1회_KBS_창작동요대회_1989/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 노을 지는 풍경 (제1회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1989) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%85%B8%EC%9D%84_%EC%A7%80%EB%8A%94_%ED%92%8D%EA%B2%BD_%EC%A0%9C1%ED%9A%8C_KBS_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EB%8C%80%ED%9A%8C_1989/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 노을 지는 풍경 (제1회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1989) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[노을 지는 풍경이 너무 아름다워 <br>노을 속에 잠겨 예쁜 꿈을 꾼다 <br>높은 하늘이 되어 작은 새와 함께 <br>노을 주위를 돌며 날아가는 꿈을 <br>노을 지는 풍경이 너무 아름다워 <br>노을 속에 잠겨 예쁜 꿈을 꾼다 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="노을 지는 풍경 (제1회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1989)" label="노을 지는 풍경 (제1회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1989)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/아기염소_제9회_MBC_창작동요제_1991/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 아기염소 (제9회 MBC 창작동요제, 1991) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%95%84%EA%B8%B0%EC%97%BC%EC%86%8C_%EC%A0%9C9%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1991/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 아기염소 (제9회 MBC 창작동요제, 1991) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[파란 하늘 파란 하늘 꿈이 <br>드리운 푸른 언덕에 <br>아기염소 여럿이 <br>풀을 뜯고 놀아요 <br>해처럼 밝은 얼굴로 <br>빗방울이 뚝뚝뚝뚝 <br>떨어지는 날에는 <br>잔뜩 찡그린 얼굴로 <br>엄마 찾아 음~메 아빠 찾아 음~메 <br>울상을 짓다가 <br>해가 번쩍 곧게 피어나면 <br>너무나 기다렸나 봐 <br>홀짝홀짝 콩콩콩 <br>흔들흔들 콩콩콩 <br>신나는 아기 염소들 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="아기염소 (제9회 MBC 창작동요제, 1991)" label="아기염소 (제9회 MBC 창작동요제, 1991)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/예쁜_아기곰_제13회_MBC_창작동요제_1995/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 예쁜 아기곰 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%98%88%EC%81%9C_%EC%95%84%EA%B8%B0%EA%B3%B0_%EC%A0%9C13%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1995/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 예쁜 아기곰 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[동그란 눈에 까만 작은 코 <br>하얀 털옷을 입은 예쁜 아기곰 <br>언제나 너를 바라보면서 <br>작은 소망 얘기하지 <br>너의 곁에 있으면 나는 행복해 <br>어떤 비밀이라도 말할 수 있어 <br>까만 작은 코에 입을 맞추면 <br>수줍어 얼굴을 붉히는 예쁜 아기곰 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="예쁜 아기곰 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995)" label="예쁜 아기곰 (제13회 MBC 창작동요제, 1995)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/가을_들녘길_제3회_KBS_창작동요대회_1991/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 가을 들녘길 (제3회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1991) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EA%B0%80%EC%9D%84_%EB%93%A4%EB%85%98%EA%B8%B8_%EC%A0%9C3%ED%9A%8C_KBS_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EB%8C%80%ED%9A%8C_1991/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 가을 들녘길 (제3회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1991) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[파란 가을 하늘에는 <br>고추잠자리 뱅뱅 돌고 <br>고추잠자리 쫓는 아이들 <br>흥겹게 따라 돈다 <br>노을빛 물든 얼굴에 <br>맺힌 땀방울 <br>땅거미 따라 <br>돌아오는 길 <br>가을 들녘 길 <br><br>노란 가을 들녘에는 <br>양팔 벌린 허수아비 <br>참새떼 쫓는 아이들이 <br>들길로 달려간다 <br>노을빛 물든 얼굴에 <br>맺힌 땀방울 <br>땅거미 따라 <br>돌아오는 길 <br>가을 들녘 길]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="가을 들녘길 (제3회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1991)" label="가을 들녘길 (제3회 KBS 창작동요대회, 1991)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/미술_시간_제12회_MBC_창작동요제_1994/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 미술 시간 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%AF%B8%EC%88%A0_%EC%8B%9C%EA%B0%84_%EC%A0%9C12%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1994/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 미술 시간 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하하 호호 시끌벅적 <br>미술 시간 시끄럽긴 하지만 <br>하하 호호 시끌벅적 <br>미술 시간 재미있어요 <br>빨주노초파남보 <br>아름다운 무지개 생기고 <br>탐스러운 빨간 사과 <br>주렁주렁 열리네 <br>하하 호호 시끌벅적 <br>미술 시간 우리들은 마술사 <br>하하 호호 시끌벅적 <br>미술 시간 우리들 세상 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="미술 시간 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994)" label="미술 시간 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/나의_친구_제12회_MBC_창작동요제_1994/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 나의 친구 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC_%EC%A0%9C12%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1994/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 나의 친구 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[물새 우는 바닷가에서 <br>밀려오는 파도를 보며 <br>멀리 떠난 나의 친구를 <br>모래 위에 그려봅니다 <br>소라 껍질 주어 모으며 <br>속삭이던 친구 목소리 <br>조약돌을 주어 세다가 <br>글썽이던 친구 얼굴이 <br>물새 우는 바닷가에서 <br>가슴속에 밀려오는데 <br>아직까지 소식이 없어 <br>그리움만 출렁입니다 <br><br>바람 부는 언덕에 올라 <br>흘러가는 흰 구름 보며 <br>멀리 떠난 나의 친구를 <br>하늘 속에 그려봅니다 <br>이름 없는 풀꽃 만지며 <br>속삭이던 친구 목소리 <br>참새들의 노래 듣다가 <br>글썽이던 친구 얼굴이 <br>바람 부는 언덕에 서면 <br>바람 타고 달려오는데 <br>편지 한 장 소식이 없어 <br>그리움만 흘러갑니다]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="나의 친구 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994)" label="나의 친구 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/높임말_친구_제19회_KBS_창작동요대회_2007/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 높임말 친구 (제19회 KBS 창작동요대회, 2007) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%86%92%EC%9E%84%EB%A7%90_%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC_%EC%A0%9C19%ED%9A%8C_KBS_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EB%8C%80%ED%9A%8C_2007/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 높임말 친구 (제19회 KBS 창작동요대회, 2007) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리들이 하는 말은 이상해 <br>어른들은 말을 올리래요 <br>어떻게 올려야지 <br>하늘높이 올라서 당겨볼까 <br>우리들이 하는 말은 이상해 <br>어른들은 말을 높이래요 <br>어떻게 높여야지 <br>두 팔 벌려 쭈욱 밀어볼까 <br>요구르트의 요는 달콤하고 <br>요술의 요는 신기한데 <br>내 말 뒤에 따라오던 요는 <br>자꾸만 깜빡 깜빡 사라져 <br>하하하하 웃고 싶을 때에도 <br>요요요요 하고 붙일까요 <br>잉잉잉 울을 때도 올려주고 <br>높여줘야 하나요 <br>우리들이 하는말은 이상해 <br>어른들이 올리라고 하시는 말 <br>밀어보고 당겨보자 <br>가장 친한 친구 만들어보자 <br><br>하하하하 웃고 싶을 때에도 <br>요요요요 하고 붙일까요 <br>잉잉잉 울을 때도 올려주고 <br>높여줘야 하나요 <br>우리들이 하는 말은 이상해 <br>어른들이 올리라고 하시는 말 <br>밀어보고 당겨보자 <br>가장 친한 친구 만들어보자 <br>랄라라랄라 랄라라랄랄라 <br>랄라라랄라 랄랄랄라 <br>랄라라랄라 랄랄라 <br>가장 친한 친구 만들어보자]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="높임말 친구 (제19회 KBS 창작동요대회, 2007)" label="높임말 친구 (제19회 KBS 창작동요대회, 2007)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/이렇게_살아가래요_제10회_MBC_창작동요제_1992/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 이렇게 살아가래요 (제10회 MBC 창작동요제, 1992) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%9D%B4%EB%A0%87%EA%B2%8C_%EC%82%B4%EC%95%84%EA%B0%80%EB%9E%98%EC%9A%94_%EC%A0%9C10%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1992/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 이렇게 살아가래요 (제10회 MBC 창작동요제, 1992) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나비 등을 타고 꽃밭에 갔더니 <br>내게 꽃처럼 살아가래요 <br>산새 등을 타고 숲속에 갔더니 <br>내게 산처럼 살아가래요 <br>그윽한 향기 뿌리고 <br>방긋이 웃음 띄우며 <br>무겁게 앉아 멀리 바라보고 <br>푸르게 살아가래요 <br>나비 등을 타고 꽃밭에 갔더니 <br>내게 꽃처럼 살아가래요 <br>산새 등을 타고 숲속에 갔더니 <br>내게 산처럼 살아가래요 <br>랄랄라라 랄라 랄랄라라 랄라 <br>랄라 랄랄라랄랄라라라 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="이렇게 살아가래요 (제10회 MBC 창작동요제, 1992)" label="이렇게 살아가래요 (제10회 MBC 창작동요제, 1992)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/궁금이_제19회_MBC_창작동요제_2001/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 궁금이 (제19회 MBC 창작동요제, 2001) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EA%B6%81%EA%B8%88%EC%9D%B4_%EC%A0%9C19%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_2001/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 궁금이 (제19회 MBC 창작동요제, 2001) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[창문 앞에 미루나무는 <br>왜 키가 길쭉 큰 걸까 <br>눈이 부신 여름 해님은 <br>왜 잠이 없는 것일까 <br>새벽 달님 쳐다 보면은 <br>왜 슬퍼지는 걸까 <br>푸른 바다 바라보면은 <br>왜 가슴이 넓어질까 <br>이 세상은 온통 모르는 것 투성이 <br>이 세상은 온통 알고픈 것 투성이 <br>이 세상은 온통 궁금한 것 투성이 <br>그래서 내 별명은 궁금이 <br>창문 앞에 미루나무는 <br>왜 키가 길쭉 큰 걸까 <br>눈이 부신 여름 해님은 <br>왜 잠이 없는 것일까 <br><br>어딘가가 아플 때에는 <br>왜 엄마 생각날까 <br>우리 아빠 나를 부를 때 <br>왜 내 강아지 내 강아지 하실까 <br>이 세상은 온통 모르는 것 투성이 <br>이 세상은 온통 알고픈 것 투성이 <br>이 세상은 온통 궁금한 것 투성이 <br>그래서 내 별명은 <br>그래서 내 별명은 궁금이]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="궁금이 (제19회 MBC 창작동요제, 2001)" label="궁금이 (제19회 MBC 창작동요제, 2001)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/봄비_제11회_MBC_창작동요제_1993/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 봄비 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%B4%84%EB%B9%84_%EC%A0%9C11%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1993/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 봄비 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[소록소록 봄비가 내리는 들에 <br>방글방글 새싹들이 얼굴 내밀고 <br>온 세상의 어린이 예뻐지라고 <br>봄바람이 사르르르 뿌리고 가요 <br>진달래 수줍어 얼굴 붉히고 <br>개나리꽃 노랗게 활짝 웃으면 <br>종달새, 벌, 나비 모두 일어나 <br>노래하며 춤을 추네 <br>소록소록 봄비가 내려온 뒤에 <br>선녀들이 무지개를 타고 내려와 <br>온 세상의 어린이 밝아지라고 <br>일곱 빛깔 웃음꽃을 뿌리고 가요 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="봄비 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993)" label="봄비 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/하늘나라_동화_제9회_MBC_창작동요제_1991/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 하늘나라 동화 (제9회 MBC 창작동요제, 1991) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98%EB%82%98%EB%9D%BC_%EB%8F%99%ED%99%94_%EC%A0%9C9%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1991/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 하늘나라 동화 (제9회 MBC 창작동요제, 1991) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[동산 위에 올라서서 <br>파란 하늘 바라보며 <br>천사 얼굴 선녀 얼굴 <br>마음속에 그려봅니다 <br>하늘 끝까지 올라 <br>실바람을 끌어안고 <br>날개 달린 천사들과 <br>속삭이고 싶어라 <br><br>동산 위에 올라서서 <br>파란 하늘 바라보며 <br>천사 얼굴 선녀 얼굴 <br>마음속에 그려봅니다 <br>하늘 끝까지 올라 <br>실바람을 끌어안고 <br>아름다운 선녀들과 <br>뛰어 놀고 싶어라]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="하늘나라 동화 (제9회 MBC 창작동요제, 1991)" label="하늘나라 동화 (제9회 MBC 창작동요제, 1991)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/소낙비_친구_제25회_MBC_창작동요제_2007/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 소낙비 친구 (제25회 MBC 창작동요제, 2007) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%86%8C%EB%82%99%EB%B9%84_%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC_%EC%A0%9C25%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_2007/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 소낙비 친구 (제25회 MBC 창작동요제, 2007) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[개나리 노란 꽃 뚝뚝 떨어지던 날 <br>수업 끝 종소리와 함께 <br>쏟아지던 소낙비 <br>친구들 하나 둘 엄마와 집으로 가고 <br>내 마음 기다림은 텅 빈 운동장 <br>가만히 서서 비 그치기 기다릴 때 <br>환한 웃음으로 다가와 <br>우산 전해 주던 너 <br>그렇게 우린 친구가 됐어 <br>언제나 함께 하는 소낙비 친구 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="소낙비 친구 (제25회 MBC 창작동요제, 2007)" label="소낙비 친구 (제25회 MBC 창작동요제, 2007)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/시골_하루_제12회_MBC_창작동요제_1994/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 시골 하루 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B3%A8_%ED%95%98%EB%A3%A8_%EC%A0%9C12%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1994/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 시골 하루 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뽀오얀 안개가 산무등을 타고 <br>닭소리에 잠을 깨면 <br>초가집 굴뚝에 흰 연기 오르니 <br>시골 하루 시작된다 <br>산비둘기 모여 구구 <br>풀을 뜯는 염소 음매 <br>한가롭게 강아지 놀고 <br>소를 모는 농부 이랴 <br>빨래하는 소리 뚝딱 <br>물레방아 빙글 잘도 돈다 <br>살며시 초생달 서산에 걸리고 <br>귀뚜라미 자장가에 <br>칭얼대던 아기의 두 눈이 감기면 <br>들려오는 멍멍 소리 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="시골 하루 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994)" label="시골 하루 (제12회 MBC 창작동요제, 1994)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/바람개비_제11회_MBC_창작동요제_1993/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 바람개비 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C%EA%B0%9C%EB%B9%84_%EC%A0%9C11%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1993/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 바람개비 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[파란 색종이 위에 <br>무지갯빛 색칠하고 <br>곱게 접어서 만든 <br>아주 예쁜 바람개비 <br>빙글빙글 빙글빙글 빙그르르 <br>손으로 돌려보고 <br>빙글빙글 빙글빙글 빙그르르 <br>골목길 달려간다 <br>빙글 빙그르 도는 <br>무지갯빛 날개 위로 <br>우리 고운 꿈 달고 <br>빙글빙글 돌아간다 <br><br>노란 색종이 위에 <br>오색나비 색칠하고 <br>곱게 접어서 만든 <br>아주 예쁜 바람개비 <br>빙글빙글 빙글빙글 빙그르르 <br>입으로 불어보고 <br>빙글빙글 빙글빙글 빙그르르 <br>파란 들 달려간다 <br>빙글 빙그르 도는 <br>오색빛깔 날개 위로 <br>우리 고운 꿈 달고 <br>빙글빙글 돌아간다]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="바람개비 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993)" label="바람개비 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/푸른_세상_만들기_제15회_MBC_창작동요제_1997/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 푸른 세상 만들기 (제15회 MBC 창작동요제, 1997) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%ED%91%B8%EB%A5%B8_%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81_%EB%A7%8C%EB%93%A4%EA%B8%B0_%EC%A0%9C15%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1997/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 푸른 세상 만들기 (제15회 MBC 창작동요제, 1997) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[푸른 하늘을 만들어줘요 <br>새하얀 뭉게구름 두둥실 <br>예쁜 새 모여 노래 부르는 <br>저 파란 숲속 나라도 만들어줘요 <br>아빠가 만들어 주시나요 <br>엄마가 만들어 주실까 <br>아니야 우리가 해야 하죠 <br>아름다운 푸른 세상 만들기 <br>우리가 푸른 씨앗 되어 <br>푸른 숲을 만들어보자 <br>우리가 푸른 바람 되어 <br>저 하늘보다 푸르게 하자 <br><br>아빠가 만들어 주시나요 <br>엄마가 만들어 주실까 <br>아니야 우리가 해야 하죠 <br>아름다운 푸른 세상 만들기 <br>우리가 푸른 씨앗 되어 <br>푸른 숲을 만들어보자 <br>우리가 푸른 바람 되어 <br>저 하늘보다 푸르게 하자]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="푸른 세상 만들기 (제15회 MBC 창작동요제, 1997)" label="푸른 세상 만들기 (제15회 MBC 창작동요제, 1997)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/도토리의_꿈_제10회_KBS부산_창작동요대회_2003/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 도토리의 꿈 (제10회 KBS부산 창작동요대회, 2003) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%8F%84%ED%86%A0%EB%A6%AC%EC%9D%98_%EA%BF%88_%EC%A0%9C10%ED%9A%8C_KBS%EB%B6%80%EC%82%B0_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EB%8C%80%ED%9A%8C_2003/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 도토리의 꿈 (제10회 KBS부산 창작동요대회, 2003) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아름다운 숲속에 <br>작고 예쁜 도토리 <br>풀잎에 가려서 보이지 않지만 <br>바람에 실려 오는 산새 노래에 <br>멋진 참나무 되는 꿈을 꾼다네 <br>저 하늘 날다가 쉬고 싶을 때면 <br>커다란 가지도 내어 주고 <br>시원한 나뭇잎 그늘 만들어 <br>마음껏 노래하게 해 <br>도토리의 작은 꿈 아름다워서 <br>내 마음까지 행복해져 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="도토리의 꿈 (제10회 KBS부산 창작동요대회, 2003)" label="도토리의 꿈 (제10회 KBS부산 창작동요대회, 2003)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/화가_제10회_MBC_창작동요제_1992/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 화가 (제10회 MBC 창작동요제, 1992) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%ED%99%94%EA%B0%80_%EC%A0%9C10%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1992/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 화가 (제10회 MBC 창작동요제, 1992) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[맑게 개인 공원에서 <br>턱수염 난 화가 아저씨 <br>나비가 훨훨 날아가고 <br>꽃들이 웃고 있는 모습을 <br>랄랄랄랄랄라 랄랄랄랄랄라 <br>콧노래를 불러가며 <br>아주 예쁘고 그리고 있었어요 <br>맑고 푸른 동심을 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="화가 (제10회 MBC 창작동요제, 1992)" label="화가 (제10회 MBC 창작동요제, 1992)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/아빠_사랑해요_제27회_MBC_창작동요제_2009/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 아빠 사랑해요 (제27회 MBC 창작동요제, 2009) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%95%84%EB%B9%A0_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4%EC%9A%94_%EC%A0%9C27%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_2009/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 아빠 사랑해요 (제27회 MBC 창작동요제, 2009) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밤하늘 별빛 반짝일 때면 <br>문득 생각이 나요 <br>내가 힘이 들 때 손잡아주시던 <br>따스한 그 손길이 <br>아무 말 하지는 않아도 <br>눈빛 속에서 느껴져요 <br>나를 사랑하시는 그 마음이 <br>자꾸자꾸 생각나 울 것 같아요 <br>밤하늘을 보던 나의 눈 속에 <br>별빛이 흔들려요 <br>이젠 나도 알죠 아빠 마음을 <br>아빠 사랑해요]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="아빠 사랑해요 (제27회 MBC 창작동요제, 2009)" label="아빠 사랑해요 (제27회 MBC 창작동요제, 2009)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/섬마을_제5회_MBC_창작동요제_1987/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 섬마을 (제5회 MBC 창작동요제, 1987) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EC%84%AC%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%84_%EC%A0%9C5%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1987/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 섬마을 (제5회 MBC 창작동요제, 1987) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[노을이 젖어 드는 둥근 섬마을 <br>금 물결 파도 위에 갈매기 날고 <br>노을 실은 고깃배가 오색실 달아 <br>뚜뚜뚜와 고동 소리 크게 울린다 <br>에헤야 기를 올려라 <br>에헤 에헤 에헤야 노를 잡아라 <br>에헤야 돛을 내려라 <br>에헤 에헤 에헤야 닻을 매어라 <br>(반복)]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="섬마을 (제5회 MBC 창작동요제, 1987)" label="섬마을 (제5회 MBC 창작동요제, 1987)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성을_자극하는_창작동요_베스트/바람새_제11회_MBC_창작동요제_1993/</id><title>감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 바람새 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T17:20:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T17:20:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%90%EA%B7%B9%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EB%B2%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C%EC%83%88_%EC%A0%9C11%ED%9A%8C_MBC_%EC%B0%BD%EC%9E%91%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%A0%9C_1993/" title="감성을 자극하는 창작동요 베스트 - 바람새 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다가올까 사라질까 <br>보이지는 않아도 <br>나는 바람새를 알아요 <br>저 파란 풀밭 위에 <br>나래깃을 부비며 <br>다가오는 바람새를 <br>동동 동동동동 비눗방울을 <br>하늘에 날려 보내면 <br>어느샌가 다가와서 <br>방울방울 쪼아 먹어요 <br><br>다가올까 사라질까 <br>보이지는 않아도 <br>나는 바람새를 알아요 <br>저 파란 풀밭 위에 <br>나래깃을 부비며 <br>다가오는 바람새를 <br>동동 동동동동 빨간 풍선을 <br>하늘에 날려 보내면 <br>어느샌가 다가와서 <br>두리둥실 갖고 놀아요]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="바람새 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993)" label="바람새 (제11회 MBC 창작동요제, 1993)"/></entry></feed>