<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:57:33+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안녕의_온도/늪이라_하여도_Feat_박준하_Remastered/</id><title>안녕의_온도 - 늪이라 하여도 (Feat. 박준하) (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:14:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:14:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EB%85%95%EC%9D%98_%EC%98%A8%EB%8F%84/%EB%8A%AA%EC%9D%B4%EB%9D%BC_%ED%95%98%EC%97%AC%EB%8F%84_Feat_%EB%B0%95%EC%A4%80%ED%95%98_Remastered/" title="안녕의_온도 - 늪이라 하여도 (Feat. 박준하) (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[찰나에 흔한 독백이 <br>순간의 거짓을 감추고 <br>어둠 속 홀로 보았던 <br>애매한 마음의 경계가 <br>찰나에 선한 말들이 <br>어두운 마음을 흔들 때 <br>가끔은 그리워했던 <br>메마른 감정의 굴레가 <br>내 마음이 늪이라 하여도 <br>어둠을 헤어 나올 <br>생각이 없네 <br>마음이 늪이라 하여도 <br>슬픔을 헤어 나올 <br>생각이 없는 순간 <br>내 마음이 늪이라 하여도 <br>어둠을 헤어 나올 <br>생각이 없네 <br>마음이 늪이라 하여도 <br>슬픔을 헤어 나올 <br>생각이 없는 순간에 <br>늪이라 하여도 <br>어둠을 헤어 나올 <br>생각이 없네 <br>마음이 늪이라 하여도 <br>슬픔을 헤어 나올 <br>생각이 없는 순간 <br>]]></content><category term="안녕의 온도" label="안녕의 온도"/><category term="늪이라 하여도 (Feat. 박준하) (Remastered)" label="늪이라 하여도 (Feat. 박준하) (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안녕의_온도/짝사랑_Feat_Grace_New_Ver/</id><title>안녕의_온도 - 짝사랑 (Feat. Grace) (New Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:14:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:14:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EB%85%95%EC%9D%98_%EC%98%A8%EB%8F%84/%EC%A7%9D%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_Feat_Grace_New_Ver/" title="안녕의_온도 - 짝사랑 (Feat. Grace) (New Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아니 이게 무슨 일이야 <br>어젯밤 잠들기 전 <br>겨우 진정시킨 내 맘이 <br>너무 빨리 뛰잖아 <br>날 보고 웃지 말아 줘 <br>백 번은 넘게 본 <br>나만 아는 너의 사진에 <br>얼굴 빨개지잖아 <br>내 마음이 내 심장이 <br>자꾸만 한 템포씩 <br>빨라져 너무 힘들어 <br>내 맘을 말해 버릴까 <br>고민도 해 봤어 <br>어떻게 말해야 내 마음이 <br>조금은 전해질까 <br>니가 좋단 뻔한 말보다 <br>더 괜찮은 말이 <br>있을 거라 고민해 봤어 <br>하지만 딱 하나야 <br>내 마음이 내 심장이 <br>자꾸만 한 템포씩 <br>빨라져 너무 힘들어 <br>내 맘 알게 된다면 <br>흩어져 버릴까 봐 <br>너무 두려워 모르겠니 <br>내 맘 정말 알아주길 바래 <br>내 마음이 내 심장이 <br>자꾸만 두근두근 떨려와 <br>너밖에 몰라 <br>]]></content><category term="안녕의 온도" label="안녕의 온도"/><category term="짝사랑 (Feat. Grace) (New Ver.)" label="짝사랑 (Feat. Grace) (New Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안녕의_온도/겨울로_가기위해_사는_밤_Feat_노티스노트_Remastered/</id><title>안녕의_온도 - 겨울로 가기위해 사는 밤 (Feat. 노티스노트) (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:14:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:14:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EB%85%95%EC%9D%98_%EC%98%A8%EB%8F%84/%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8%EB%A1%9C_%EA%B0%80%EA%B8%B0%EC%9C%84%ED%95%B4_%EC%82%AC%EB%8A%94_%EB%B0%A4_Feat_%EB%85%B8%ED%8B%B0%EC%8A%A4%EB%85%B8%ED%8A%B8_Remastered/" title="안녕의_온도 - 겨울로 가기위해 사는 밤 (Feat. 노티스노트) (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지쳐 잠 못 드는 <br>이 밤 누가 알까 <br>공기도 내 맘을 <br>주체 못하는 밤 <br>텁텁한 내 말이 <br>벽에 닿지 못해 <br>사람이 지겨운 <br>어둠뿐인 이 밤 <br>삶은 가볍고 <br>순간적인데 <br>하루는 길고 <br>너무 무겁다 <br>갑갑한 마음이 <br>모여 꿈을 꾸다 <br>짙은 색 밤들이 <br>모여 겨울이다 <br>겨울은 봄을 꿈꾸며 <br>꽃필 날을 보다 <br>어느덧 내 삶은 <br>겨울뿐이더라 <br>겨울로 가기 위해 <br>사는 밤 <br>겨울로 가기 위해 <br>사는 밤 <br>늘 기다린 봄에 <br>그 시간을 잊다 <br>눈물로 또다시 <br>마주하는 이 밤 <br>갑갑한 마음이 <br>모여 꿈을 꾸다 <br>짙은 색 밤들이 <br>모여 겨울이다 <br>]]></content><category term="안녕의 온도" label="안녕의 온도"/><category term="겨울로 가기위해 사는 밤 (Feat. 노티스노트) (Remastered)" label="겨울로 가기위해 사는 밤 (Feat. 노티스노트) (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안녕의_온도/어쩌면_좋을까_Feat_지언/</id><title>안녕의_온도 - 어쩌면 좋을까 (Feat. 지언) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:14:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:14:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EB%85%95%EC%9D%98_%EC%98%A8%EB%8F%84/%EC%96%B4%EC%A9%8C%EB%A9%B4_%EC%A2%8B%EC%9D%84%EA%B9%8C_Feat_%EC%A7%80%EC%96%B8/" title="안녕의_온도 - 어쩌면 좋을까 (Feat. 지언) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어젯밤 날 걱정하는 <br>니 말에 괜히 화가나 <br>서둘러 잘 거라며 <br>전활 끊고 한숨 못 잤어 <br>아침이 되어서야 <br>좀 풀린 맘에 집을 나섰어 <br>이 맘을 좀 정리하고 싶어 <br>그래야만 해 <br>나 정말 니가 좋은 걸까 <br>나 정말 너를 <br>좋아하게 된 걸까 <br>친구란 이름에 화가 나 <br>이런 내가 나도 미워 <br>집 앞에 거의 다 와가는 <br>길에 연락이 왔어 <br>오늘도 날씨가 정말 <br>좋다며 어디 있냐고 <br>떨리는 내 맘 맞는 걸까 <br>나 정말 너를 <br>좋아하게 된 걸까 <br>내 맘을 어쩌면 좋을까 <br>이런 내가 나도 싫어 <br>요즘 난 너와 <br>주고받던 얘기는 <br>다 외운단 말이야 <br>집에 간다고 <br>나 먼저 일어나서 <br>너희 집 앞이란 말이야 <br>친구이긴 싫어 <br>매일보고 싶은 내 맘을 <br>어쩜 좋을까 <br>지금에 당장은 <br>뭐라 말 못해도 <br>매일 널 이렇게 <br>바라만 보아도 <br>언제가 너에게 <br>꼭 하고 싶은 말 <br>좋아해 내 맘 <br>모두 주고 싶어 <br>]]></content><category term="안녕의 온도" label="안녕의 온도"/><category term="어쩌면 좋을까 (Feat. 지언)" label="어쩌면 좋을까 (Feat. 지언)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안녕의_온도/잔인해_윤석철_Of_안녕의_온도/</id><title>안녕의_온도 - 잔인해 (윤석철 Of 안녕의 온도) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:14:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:14:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EB%85%95%EC%9D%98_%EC%98%A8%EB%8F%84/%EC%9E%94%EC%9D%B8%ED%95%B4_%EC%9C%A4%EC%84%9D%EC%B2%A0_Of_%EC%95%88%EB%85%95%EC%9D%98_%EC%98%A8%EB%8F%84/" title="안녕의_온도 - 잔인해 (윤석철 Of 안녕의 온도) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뒤돌아 서서 <br>한참을 멍하니 봤어 <br>대체 난 왜 <br>여깄는 건지 정말 <br>알 수 없다는 <br>생각에 사로잡혀서 <br>한발도 떼지 못한 채 <br>한편의 잔인한 영화가 <br>금세 또 끝난 거라고 <br>고갤 들어 <br>내 눈앞에 펼쳐진 <br>대답 없는 수많은 <br>길을 보았어 <br>확실하게 혼자라는 걸 <br>알아버렸지 <br>지금을 말하는 게 아니야 <br>너와 있을 때 <br>난 가끔 더 외로웠어 <br>사랑이 이런 거라고 <br>내 맘을 달래 <br>보아도 잔인해 <br>고갤 들어 내 <br>눈앞에 펼쳐진 <br>지나버린 우리의 <br>길을 보았어 <br>확실하게 끝이라는 걸 <br>알아버렸지 <br>사랑은 잔인하게 끝나버렸어 <br>고갤 들어 내 눈앞에 펼쳐진 <br>대답 없는 수많은 <br>길을 보았어 <br>확실하게 혼자라는 걸 <br>알아 버렸지 <br>지금을 말하는 게 아니야 <br>너와 있을 때 <br>난 가끔 더 외로웠어 <br>사랑이 이런 거라고 <br>내 맘을 달래 <br>보아도 잔인해 <br>]]></content><category term="안녕의 온도" label="안녕의 온도"/><category term="잔인해 (윤석철 Of 안녕의 온도)" label="잔인해 (윤석철 Of 안녕의 온도)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안녕의_온도/사랑의_한가운데_Feat_선우정아_Remastered/</id><title>안녕의_온도 - 사랑의 한가운데 (Feat. 선우정아) (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:14:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:14:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EB%85%95%EC%9D%98_%EC%98%A8%EB%8F%84/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%98_%ED%95%9C%EA%B0%80%EC%9A%B4%EB%8D%B0_Feat_%EC%84%A0%EC%9A%B0%EC%A0%95%EC%95%84_Remastered/" title="안녕의_온도 - 사랑의 한가운데 (Feat. 선우정아) (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[평소엔 잘 <br>내키지 않는데도 <br>밖에 나간 채로 <br>침대에 누웠어 <br>그래 어제와 <br>같은 날이야 <br>모든 게 귀찮고 <br>정말 모르겠어 <br>눈을 감으니 <br>뜨거운 내 맘이 <br>눈물을 참으며 <br>내게 어디냐고 <br>돌릴 수 없다는 걸 <br>난 잘 알아 <br>이젠 끝이라고 <br>내게 말해줄래 <br>사랑의 한가운데 <br>꺼지지 않는 빛을 찾아 <br>사랑의 한가운데 희미해 <br>깜깜한 내 맘에 <br>빛을 보내 <br>꺼져간 빛으로 <br>너를 찾아갈게 <br>어두운 내 맘에 <br>빛을 보여줘 <br>너에게 마지막 <br>인사를 보낼게 <br>평소엔 잘 <br>내키지 않는데도 <br>밖에 나간 채로 <br>침대에 누웠어 <br>그래 어제와 <br>같은 날이야 <br>모든 게 귀찮고 <br>정말 모르겠어 <br>사랑의 한가운데 <br>꺼지지 않는 빛을 찾아 <br>사랑의 한가운데 희미해 <br>깜깜한 내 맘에 <br>빛을 보내 <br>꺼져간 빛으로 <br>너를 찾아갈게 <br>어두운 내 맘에 <br>빛을 보여줘 <br>너에게 마지막 <br>인사를 보낼게 <br>깜깜한 내 맘에 <br>빛을 보내 <br>꺼져간 빛으로 <br>너를 찾아갈게 <br>어두운 내 맘에 <br>빛을 보여줘 <br>너에게 마지막 <br>인사를 보낼게 <br>]]></content><category term="안녕의 온도" label="안녕의 온도"/><category term="사랑의 한가운데 (Feat. 선우정아) (Remastered)" label="사랑의 한가운데 (Feat. 선우정아) (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안녕의_온도/평생_겨울_일_것만_같아_Feat_Grace/</id><title>안녕의_온도 - 평생 겨울 일 것만 같아 (Feat. Grace) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:14:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:14:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EB%85%95%EC%9D%98_%EC%98%A8%EB%8F%84/%ED%8F%89%EC%83%9D_%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8_%EC%9D%BC_%EA%B2%83%EB%A7%8C_%EA%B0%99%EC%95%84_Feat_Grace/" title="안녕의_온도 - 평생 겨울 일 것만 같아 (Feat. Grace) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[봄 자주 가던 <br>근처 운동장에 <br>여름 그 나무 <br>기억할까 <br>가을낙엽 떨어지던 <br>그 자리에 <br>겨울 내내 <br>두 손 꼭 잡고 <br>살아갈 이유 없는 <br>나를 보며 <br>넌 내게 말했었지 <br>무너진 나를 <br>애써 도망쳐 <br>사라지지 말고 <br>내 손을 꼭 <br>잡아보겠냐고 <br>그림 같은 니가 <br>내게 펼쳐지고 <br>너 말곤 모든 게 흩어져 <br>흩날리는 눈이 <br>만약 내 맘이라면 <br>평생 겨울 일 것만 같아 <br>언제가 너는 <br>내게 말했었지 <br>사랑은 영원한 걸까 <br>널 알고부터 <br>줄 곧 나는 그래 <br>쓸쓸히 웃는 너를 봤지 <br>세상에 익숙해진 <br>나를 보며 넌 <br>내게 말했었지 <br>무뎌진 나를 <br>변하지 않는 <br>사랑이라는 건 <br>세상에 있기는 한 거냐고 <br>돌아서는 니가 <br>내게 펼쳐지고 <br>너 말곤 모든 게 흩어져 <br>흩날리는 눈이 <br>만약 내 맘이라면 <br>평생 겨울 일 것만 같아 <br>다시 돌아가 그때 그대로가 <br>네게 돌아가 그때 그대로가 <br>니가 가버린 내 삶은 <br>숨이 멎은 것 같아 <br>돌아서는 니가 <br>내게 펼쳐지고 <br>이 세상 모든 게 <br>흩어 사라졌어 <br>흩날리는 눈이 <br>만약 내 맘이라면 <br>평생 겨울 일 것만 같아 <br>돌아서는 니가 <br>내게 펼쳐지고 <br>이 세상 모든 게 흩어져 <br>흩날리는 눈이 <br>만약 내 맘이라면 <br>평생 겨울일 것만 같아 <br>]]></content><category term="안녕의 온도" label="안녕의 온도"/><category term="평생 겨울 일 것만 같아 (Feat. Grace)" label="평생 겨울 일 것만 같아 (Feat. Grace)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/덤덤라디오/돌아보다/</id><title>덤덤라디오 - 돌아보다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:14:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:14:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%A4%EB%8D%A4%EB%9D%BC%EB%94%94%EC%98%A4/%EB%8F%8C%EC%95%84%EB%B3%B4%EB%8B%A4/" title="덤덤라디오 - 돌아보다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[해가 지는 언덕을 지날 때쯤 <br>달이 뜨는 언덕을 지날 때쯤 <br>그 아이는 어떻게 지내고 있을까 <br>그 아이는 어떤 꿈을 꾸고 있을까 <br>좋아한다는 말 보고 싶다는 말 <br>그립다는 말 보고 싶다는 말 <br>우후후 우후후 우후후 우후후 <br>돌아보다 흐느끼는 뒷모습 <br>초라한 나의 모습 <br>그땐 그럴 수 밖에 없었다며 <br>돌아보며 스스로 위로해도 <br>웃고 있는 네 모습 <br>웃는데 흐르는 너의 눈물 <br>좋아한다는 말 보고 싶다는 말 <br>그립다는 말 보고 싶다는 말 <br>우후후 우후후 우후후 우후후 <br>돌아보다 흐느끼는 뒷모습 <br>초라한 나의 모습 <br>그땐 그럴 수 밖에 없었다며 <br>돌아보며 스스로 위로해도 <br>웃고 있는 네 모습 <br>웃는데 흐르는 너의 눈물 <br>돌아보다 흐느끼는 뒷모습 <br>초라한 나의 모습 <br>그땐 그럴 수 밖에 없었다며 <br>돌아보며 스스로 위로해도 <br>웃고 있는 네 모습 <br>웃는데 흐르는 너의 눈물 <br>워우우 워어 너의 눈물 <br>해가 지는 언덕을 지날 때쯤 <br>달이 뜨는 언덕을 지날 때쯤 <br>]]></content><category term="덤덤라디오" label="덤덤라디오"/><category term="돌아보다" label="돌아보다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zara_Larsson/So_Good_Feat_Ty_Dolla_ign/</id><title>Zara_Larsson - So Good (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:15:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:15:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zara_Larsson/So_Good_Feat_Ty_Dolla_ign/" title="Zara_Larsson - So Good (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So good so good so good so good <br>You know my love is <br>So good so good so good so good <br>You know my love is <br>My love is more potent <br>than anything in the cup <br>that you're holdin' <br>One little taste will have you open <br>Aye I know you want some <br>you want some <br>Too strong no limits <br>It's not official <br>so take your time with it <br>It go straight to your head <br>control your mind with it <br>Aye I know you want some <br>you want some <br>You know that I'm the only one that <br>gets you higher <br>Gets you higher babe <br>And you ain't gotta worry <br>'cause you know I got it <br>Know I got it babe <br>You be stuck on it <br>'cause my love so good <br>So you keep comin' back to <br>get some more <br>Got you in your feelings <br>all emotional <br>My love my love <br>So good so good so good so good <br>You know my love is <br>So good so good so good so good <br>You know my love is <br>My love ain't running out <br>Got a endless supply <br>there'll never be a drought <br>I put you to sleep <br>you'll never leave your house <br>Aye I know you want <br>know you want some <br>You know that I'm the only one that <br>gets you higher <br>Gets you higher babe <br>And you ain't gotta worry <br>'cause you know I got it <br>Know I got it babe <br>You be stuck on it <br>'cause my love so good <br>So you keep comin' back to <br>get some more <br>Got you in your feelings <br>all emotional <br>My love my love <br>So good so good so good so good <br>You know my love is <br>So good so good so good so good <br>You know my love is <br>Girl your love so good girl <br>Got me comin' back for seconds <br>what's good girl <br>Got me clearin' out my schedule <br>tryna link up <br>Girl you know <br>you 'bout to get that thang <br>beat up <br>When I pull up <br>you know what I came for <br>Dolla lay the pipe <br>keep some dope D for you <br>Put your body straight to sleep <br>I got you wakin' up thankin' me <br>You be stuck on it <br>'cause my love so good <br>So you keep comin' back to <br>get some more <br>Got you in your feelings <br>all emotional <br>My love my love <br>So good so good so good so good <br>You know my love is <br>So good so good so good so good <br>You know my love is <br>]]></content><category term="Zara Larsson" label="Zara Larsson"/><category term="So Good (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign)" label="So Good (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/2ski/오늘의_나/</id><title>2ski - 오늘의 나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:15:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:15:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/2ski/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98%EC%9D%98_%EB%82%98/" title="2ski - 오늘의 나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 매일매일 달라지고 <br>있음이 느껴져 <br>하루하루 늘어가는 <br>엄마의 주름살도 다 보여 <br>i can't believe it <br>어른이 된 거 <br>아직도 난 철 들지 않았는데 <br>내게 이래라 저래라 말하지마 <br>do not talk about my life <br>내 갈 길은 오로지 <br>가지 못한 길뿐야 <br>나는 그냥 나 <br>Me myself &amp; i <br>나는 그냥 나 <br>yesterday's me and today i i <br>yesterday's me and today i i <br>어제의 나 그리고 오늘의 나 <br>어제보다 더 나아진 오늘의 나 <br>yesterday's me and today i i <br>난 그냥 분명한걸 믿어 <br>You don't have to believe that <br>겨울이 지나면 <br>봄이 오는 그딴 뻔한 거 <br>내 눈앞에 네가 <br>너무나도 예쁘다는 거 <br>so beautiful <br>네 기준에 날 맞추려 하지마 절대 <br>난 변하지 않아 절대 믿어도 돼 <br>나는 그냥 나 <br>Me myself &amp; I <br>나는 그냥 나 <br>yesterday's me and today i i <br>yesterday's me and today i i <br>어제의 나 그리고 오늘의 나 <br>어제보다 더 나아진 오늘의 나 <br>yesterday's me and today i i <br>thx to my brother <br>Moneytree &amp; 2ski <br>그 둘이 있어 올라가 <br>나의 존재가치 <br>그 믿음에 감사해 <br>내가 지칠 수 없게 만들어 <br>나 올라가 네가 더 볼 수도 없게 <br>날 버리고 떠난걸 <br>후회하게 만들어줄게 <br>그게 바로 나 <br>Me myself &amp; i <br>보여줄게 나 <br>yesterday's me and today i i <br>yesterday's me and today i i <br>어제의 나 그리고 오늘의 나 <br>어제보다 더 나아진 오늘의 나 <br>yesterday's me and today i i <br>]]></content><category term="2ski" label="2ski"/><category term="오늘의 나" label="오늘의 나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신성진/I_Am/</id><title>신성진 - I Am - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:15:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:15:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%84%B1%EC%A7%84/I_Am/" title="신성진 - I Am - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이렇게 끝나버릴 <br>줄은 몰랐어 <br>영원할 것만 같던 <br>너와의 사랑이 <br>니 맘이 쉽게 정리 될 <br>줄은 몰랐어 <br>언제나 서로만 생각할 것 <br>같던 우리 <br>그 맘이 멀어질 줄은 <br>정말 몰랐어 <br>니가 날 어떻게 떠나 <br>사랑하는데 어떻게 잊어 <br>잊어 yeah <br>내가 널 사랑하는데 어떻게 <br>니가 다른 사람 만나 <br>행복하길 바래 Oh Oh <br>그게 무슨 말도 안 되는 소리야 <br>도저히 난 <br>너는 지금 내가 이기적이라 <br>말하지만 <br>나는 지금 너를 이렇게라도 <br>붙잡고 싶어 <br>다시 돌아와줘 정말 후회가 돼 <br>Oh Oh <br>그러니까 한번만 <br>사랑하는데 어떻게 떠나 <br>떠나 yeah <br>내가 널 사랑하는데 사실은 <br>니가 다른 사람 만나 <br>불행하길 바래 <br>지금 이게 나의 솔직한 맘이야 <br>지금도 난 <br>끝내 너는 나를 떠나가겠지만 <br>oh <br>다시 돌아오지 않을 것도 <br>알지만 난 <br>사랑하는데 어떻게 잊어 <br>잊어 <br>내가 널 사랑하는데 아직은 <br>나는 다른 사람 만나 <br>행복하긴 싫어 <br>Oh Oh <br>지금 니가 너무 원망스러워 <br>오늘도 난 <br>지금도 난 oh oh <br>여전히 난 <br>Oh Oh 아직도 난 <br>]]></content><category term="신성진" label="신성진"/><category term="I Am" label="I Am"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shawn_Mendes/Mercy_Acoustic_Guitar/</id><title>Shawn_Mendes - Mercy (Acoustic Guitar) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:15:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:15:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shawn_Mendes/Mercy_Acoustic_Guitar/" title="Shawn_Mendes - Mercy (Acoustic Guitar) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You've got a hold of me <br>Don't even know your power <br>I stand a hundred feet <br>But I fall when I'm around ya <br>Show me an open door <br>Then you go and slam it on me <br>I can't take anymore <br>I'm saying baby <br>Please have mercy on me <br>Take it easy on my heart <br>Even though <br>you don't mean to hurt me <br>You keep tearing me apart <br>Would you please have mercy <br>mercy on my heart <br>Would you please have mercy <br>mercy on my heart <br>I'd drive through the night <br>Just to be near you baby <br>Heart open testify <br>Tell me that I'm not crazy <br>I'm not asking for a lot <br>Just that you're honest with me <br>My pride is all I got <br>I'm saying baby <br>Please have mercy on me <br>Take it easy on my heart <br>Even though <br>you don't mean to hurt me <br>You keep tearing me apart <br>Would you please have mercy on me <br>I'm a puppet on your strings <br>And even though <br>you got good intentions <br>I need you to set me free <br>Would you please have mercy <br>mercy on my heart <br>Would you please have mercy <br>mercy on my heart <br>Consuming all the air <br>inside my lungs <br>Ripping all the skin <br>from off my bones <br>I'm prepared to sacrifice my life <br>I would gladly do it twice <br>Consuming all the air <br>inside my lungs <br>Ripping all the skin <br>from off my bones <br>I'm prepared to sacrifice my life <br>I would gladly do it twice <br>Oh please have mercy on me <br>Take it easy on my heart <br>Even though <br>you don't mean to hurt me <br>You keep tearing me apart <br>Would you please have mercy on me <br>I'm a puppet on your string <br>And even though <br>you got good intentions <br>I need you to set me free <br>I'm begging you for mercy <br>mercy <br>I'm begging you <br>begging you please baby <br>I'm begging you for mercy <br>mercy <br>Oh I'm begging you <br>I'm begging you yeah <br>]]></content><category term="Shawn Mendes" label="Shawn Mendes"/><category term="Mercy (Acoustic Guitar)" label="Mercy (Acoustic Guitar)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서울문_Seoulmoon/언제까지나/</id><title>서울문_Seoulmoon - 언제까지나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:15:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:15:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EC%9A%B8%EB%AC%B8_Seoulmoon/%EC%96%B8%EC%A0%9C%EA%B9%8C%EC%A7%80%EB%82%98/" title="서울문_Seoulmoon - 언제까지나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밤이 깊어져 외로운 거리 <br>나에게만 들리는 목소리 <br>이 빛 사이로 불빛 사이로 <br>들어와 내 옆에 있어주겠니 <br>운명처럼 넌 <br>운명처럼 내 <br>마음을 가득 채워가고 있어 <br>운명 같은 넌 <br>운명 같은 내 <br>세상을 완전히 바꿔놨어 <br>밤이 깊어져 어두운 거리 <br>나에게만 빛나는 네 모습 <br>이 빛 사이로 그 빛 사이로 <br>들어가 네 옆에 내가 있을게 <br>운명처럼 넌 운명처럼 내 <br>마음을 가득 채워가고 있어 <br>운명 같은 넌 운명 같은 내 <br>세상을 완전히 바꿔놨어 <br>언제까지나 <br>너의 곁에 항상 <br>내가 있어 줄게 <br>언제까지나 <br>나의 마음 항상 <br>너를 지켜 줄게 <br>언제까지나 <br>너의 곁에 항상 <br>내가 있어 줄게 <br>언제까지나 <br>나의 마음 항상 <br>너를 지켜 줄게 <br>잊지 않아 너와 나의 만남 <br>거짓말 같은 우연처럼 <br>놓지 마 너와 나의 인연 <br>끝나지 않을 운명처럼 <br>언제까지나 <br>너의 곁에 항상 <br>내가 있어 줄게 <br>언제까지나 <br>나의 마음 항상 <br>너를 지켜 줄게 <br>언제까지나 <br>너의 곁에 항상 <br>내가 있어 줄게 <br>언제까지나 <br>나의 마음 항상 <br>너를 지켜 줄게 <br>]]></content><category term="서울문 (Seoulmoon)" label="서울문 (Seoulmoon)"/><category term="언제까지나" label="언제까지나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/사리사/오_마이_갓/</id><title>사리사 - 오 마이 갓 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:15:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:15:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%82%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%82%AC/%EC%98%A4_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B0%93/" title="사리사 - 오 마이 갓 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사실 잘생긴 건 아냐 <br>정말 딱 이상형 그 반대 <br>근데 정말 이상하지 <br>자꾸 눈이 가잖아 <br>내가 먼저 들이대볼까 <br>아니야 기다려볼래 <br>너는 관심도 없나 봐 <br>눈도 안 마주치네 <br>아 진짜 완전 짜증 나잖아 <br>내가 왜 이러고 있지 <br>아 진짜 내 스타일 아닌데 <br>네가 왜 내 맘에 들어와 <br>내가 먼저 들이대볼까 <br>아니야 기다려볼래 <br>너는 관심도 없나 봐 <br>눈도 안 마주치네 <br>오 마이 갓 <br>나 어떡해 네가 너무 좋은데 <br>오 마이 갓 <br>나 어떡해 너를 사랑하나 봐 <br>아 진짜 완전 짜증 나잖아 <br>내가 왜 이러고 있지 <br>아 진짜 내 스타일 아닌데 <br>네가 왜 내 맘에 들어와 <br>아 진짜 완전 자존심 상해 <br>내가 왜 이러고 있지 <br>아 진짜 이건 아닌 것 같아 <br>네가 왜 내 맘에 들어와 <br>]]></content><category term="사리사" label="사리사"/><category term="오 마이 갓" label="오 마이 갓"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서나인_Sunine/Igloo_Feat_RIWOO/</id><title>서나인_Sunine - Igloo (Feat. RIWOO) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:15:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:15:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EB%82%98%EC%9D%B8_Sunine/Igloo_Feat_RIWOO/" title="서나인_Sunine - Igloo (Feat. RIWOO) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[에스키모처럼 꽁꽁 싸매고 <br>얼굴색을 허옇게 <br>질린 듯 위장해도 <br>숨길 수 없는 피부 속 안의 붉은 피 <br>몸 속에서 마치 와인처럼 흐르지 <br>우린 취한 것 같애 이 분위기에 <br>너와 나는 남이 아닌 우리기에 <br>자린 넓어도 좀 더 붙어 <br>앉자고 말했지 <br>작은 감정들을 <br>피부에 닿게 누리기엔 <br>우리 사이는 너무 먼 것 같아 <br>코에 코가 닿을 듯 내 곁에 앉아 <br>여긴 이글루니까 <br>일단 한잔하고 나서 <br>에스키모 식으로 인사하자 <br>겉은 차가워 보여도 <br>생각보단 따듯해 <br>그래 어쩌면 여긴 <br>다른 곳보다는 따분해 <br>보여도 계속 있다 보면 <br>기분 좋게 나른해 <br>입 꼬리가 올라갈 때 <br>난 한 잔을 더 따를게 <br>시간이 갈수록 자꾸만 나 <br>너에 대한 모습에 애가 타 <br>대화를 나눌 때나 <br>눈을 맞출 때나 <br>점점 깊어지는 걸 <br>겉은 차가워 보여도 <br>안은 아주 많이 따뜻한 걸 <br>매일 너랑 있고 싶어 <br>둘만의 이글루에 <br>이글루에 이글루에서 <br>한 잔을 따른 뒤에 너의 눈을 봐 <br>초점이 약간 흐려진 듯해 <br>넌 누굴 봐 <br>앞에 앉아있던 <br>내 친구를 부른 담 <br>에 한댈 태우겠다면서 <br>핑곌 대고 데려가 <br>그렇게 그 친구는 <br>급한 일이 생겼고 <br>난 그 친구를 챙겼고 <br>둘만의 시간이 생겼어 <br>어색한 기운은 돌고 <br>우린 술로 그걸 치워 <br>주고 받는 말들은 <br>서로 눈에 콩깍지를 씌워 <br>yeah I really wanna <br>spend time with u <br>시간은 두실 넘어가는 게 <br>이 말을 하는 이유 <br>꼭 오늘이 아니어도 돼 <br>내일도 보고 싶어 <br>빈말이 아냐 <br>네 작은 손도 잡고 싶어 <br>이 말들은 맘속에 두고 <br>잔을 비웠네 <br>근데 네 손은 차 있는 <br>잔 대신 내 손 등 위에 <br>머릿속은 하얘지고 얼어버렸네 <br>때마침 창문은 <br>blind처럼 김이 서렸네 <br>시간이 갈수록 자꾸만 나 <br>너에 대한 모습에 애가 타 <br>대화를 나눌 때나 <br>눈을 맞출 때나 <br>점점 깊어지는 걸 <br>겉은 차가워 보여도 <br>안은 아주 많이 따뜻한 걸 <br>매일 너랑 있고 싶어 <br>둘만의 이글루에 <br>이글루에 이글루에서 <br>얼음벽돌을 쌓아 원하는 만큼 <br>저 별들이 날 몰라볼 만큼 <br>stack n hide stack n hide <br>stack n hide stack n hide <br>얼음벽돌을 쌓아 원하는 만큼 <br>저 별들이 날 몰라볼 만큼 <br>stack n hide stack n hide <br>stack n hide stack n hide <br>시간이 갈수록 자꾸만 나 <br>너에 대한 모습에 애가 타 <br>대화를 나눌 때나 <br>눈을 맞출 때나 <br>점점 깊어지는 걸 <br>겉은 차가워 보여도 <br>안은 아주 많이 따뜻한 걸 <br>매일 너랑 있고 싶어 <br>둘만의 이글루에 <br>이글루에 이글루에서 <br>]]></content><category term="서나인 (Sunine)" label="서나인 (Sunine)"/><category term="Igloo (Feat. RIWOO)" label="Igloo (Feat. RIWOO)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소연/그런_날_그런_너에게/</id><title>소연 - 그런 날, 그런 너에게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:15:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:15:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%EC%97%B0/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%B0_%EB%82%A0_%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%B0_%EB%84%88%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C/" title="소연 - 그런 날, 그런 너에게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그런 날이 누구에게나 <br>한번쯤 있지 <br>결국 내 것은 없음을 <br>깨닫는 순간 <br>오로지 나만 <br>혼자인 것 만같은 그런 <br>외로움에 소용돌이가 <br>몰아칠 때 <br>I'm by your side <br>I'm by your side <br>그런 생각에 <br>슬퍼질 때 슬퍼질때 <br>조용히 따뜻한 <br>온기를 온기를 <br>내게 나눠주는 <br>네가 있음에 <br>난 행복할 수 있어 <br>그런 생각에 <br>슬퍼질 때 슬퍼질때 <br>조용히 따뜻한 <br>온기를 온기를 <br>네게 나눠줄게 <br>나의 작음 마음 <br>일지라도 난 <br>I'm by your side <br>I'm by your side <br>그런 생각에 <br>슬퍼질 때 슬퍼질때 <br>조용히 따뜻한 <br>온기를 온기를 <br>내게 나눠주는 <br>네가 있음에 <br>난 행복할 수 있어 <br>그런 생각에 <br>슬퍼질 때 슬퍼질때 <br>조용히 따뜻한 <br>온기를 온기를 <br>네게 나눠줄게 <br>나의 작음 마음 <br>일지라도 난 <br>그런 생각에 슬퍼질 때 <br>조용히 따뜻한 <br>내맘 줄게 난 <br>]]></content><category term="소연" label="소연"/><category term="그런 날, 그런 너에게" label="그런 날, 그런 너에게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAX_학스/Knock_It_Off/</id><title>HAX_학스 - Knock It Off - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:16:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:16:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HAX_%ED%95%99%EC%8A%A4/Knock_It_Off/" title="HAX_학스 - Knock It Off - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우린 우릴 잘 알아 <br>달라도 너무 달라 <br>그래 우린 ice skate 탄 듯 <br>너무 많이 돌고 돌아 <br>더 돌아 <br>사실 좀 지루해 too long <br>난 널 힘들게 해서 <br>넌 날 만족 못해서 <br>사실 난 always not alone <br>하나도 안 고마워 <br>넌 너무 이기적이야 안 아까워 <br>그냥 이제는 혼자 갈래 <br>Knock it off Knock it off <br>Do you love me always you said <br>Knock it off Knock it off <br>Never never you can’t comeback <br>Knock it off Knock it off <br>Knock it off Knock it off <br>Knock it off Knock it off <br>Oh no no no <br>널 너무도 잘 알아 <br>딱 하난 우린 맞아 <br>그래 우린 마치 꼬마 아이처럼 <br>고집이 너무 많아 <br>너무 많아 <br>점점 지쳐가 on and on <br>웃음을 점점 잃어 가 <br>널 보는 나의 미소가 yeah <br>사실 좀 미워했어 널 <br>근데 하나도 난 이해가 <br>안 되는 게 아직 많아 <br>그냥 이제는 혼자 갈래 <br>Knock it off Knock it off <br>Do you love me always you said <br>Knock it off Knock it off <br>Never never you can’t comeback <br>Knock it off Knock it off <br>Knock it off Knock it off <br>Knock it off Knock it off <br>Oh no no no <br>You know I don’t never love you <br>두 번 다신 <br>I don’t think about you oh no <br>Knock it off Knock it off <br>Do you love me always you said <br>Knock it off Knock it off <br>Never never you can’t comeback <br>Knock it off Knock it off <br>Knock it off Knock it off <br>Knock it off Knock it off <br>Oh no no no <br>]]></content><category term="HAX (학스)" label="HAX (학스)"/><category term="Knock It Off" label="Knock It Off"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/류정필/당신모습/</id><title>류정필 - 당신모습 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:16:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:16:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A5%98%EC%A0%95%ED%95%84/%EB%8B%B9%EC%8B%A0%EB%AA%A8%EC%8A%B5/" title="류정필 - 당신모습 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[당신 생각하면 마냥 즐겁고 <br>당신 생각하면 너무 행복하고 <br>당신의 맑은 그 미소에 <br>모든 근심 사라지고 말죠 <br>무지개를 꿈꾸지도 않아요 <br>판타지를 바라지도 않아요 <br>당신의 맑은 그 순수한 <br>눈짓 있으면 되요 <br>눈송이처럼 하얀 당신 마음 <br>꽃송이처럼 환한 당신의 얼굴 <br>햇살인 듯 당신 모습 같을까요 <br>햇살인 듯 당신 모습 같을까요 <br>바람소리는 그대의 향기 <br>빗방울 소리는 그대의 음성 <br>당신의 맑은 그 순수한 <br>영혼이겠지요 <br>눈송이처럼 하얀 당신 마음 <br>꽃송이처럼 환한 당신의 얼굴 <br>햇살인 듯 당신 모습 같을까요 <br>햇살인 듯 당신 모습 같을까요 <br>눈송이처럼 하얀 당신 마음 <br>꽃송이처럼 환한 당신의 얼굴 <br>햇살인 듯 당신 모습 같을까요 <br>햇살인 듯 당신 모습 같을까요 <br>바람소리는 그대의 향기 <br>빗방울 소리는 그대의 음성 <br>당신의 맑은 그 순수한 <br>영혼이겠지요 영혼이겠지요 <br>]]></content><category term="류정필" label="류정필"/><category term="당신모습" label="당신모습"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김연은/여호와는_나의_목자/</id><title>김연은 - 여호와는 나의 목자 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:16:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:16:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%97%B0%EC%9D%80/%EC%97%AC%ED%98%B8%EC%99%80%EB%8A%94_%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EB%AA%A9%EC%9E%90/" title="김연은 - 여호와는 나의 목자 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여호와는 나의 목자 되시오니 <br>부족함이 내게 없으리로다 <br>여호와는 나의 목자 되시오니 <br>부족함이 내게 없으리로다 <br>나를 푸른 풀밭과 쉴만한 <br>물가로 인도하여주시고 <br>내 영혼 소생시키시고 <br>의의 길로 인도하여주시네 <br>여호와는 나의 목자 되시오니 <br>부족함이 내게 없으리로다 <br>여호와는 나의 목자 되시오니 <br>부족함이 내게 없으리로다 <br>사망의 음침한 골짜기라도 <br>해가 두렵지 않음은 <br>주께서 함께 하시며 <br>항상 나를 안위하여 주시네 <br>여호와는 나의 목자 되시오니 <br>부족함이 내게 없으리로다 <br>주께서 내게 상을 차려주시고 <br>기름을 머리에 부으셨으니 <br>내 잔이 넘치나이다 <br>내 평생에 선하심과 인자하심이 <br>반드시 나를 따르리니 <br>내가 여호와의 집에 <br>영원히 살리로다 <br>여호와는 나의 목자 되시오니 <br>부족함이 내게 없으리로다 <br>여호와는 나의 목자 되시오니 <br>부족함이 내게 없으리로다 <br>여호와는 나의 목자 되시오니 <br>부족함이 내게 없으리로다 <br>여호와는 나의 목자 되시오니 <br>부족함이 내게 없으리로다 <br>]]></content><category term="김연은" label="김연은"/><category term="여호와는 나의 목자" label="여호와는 나의 목자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/경민혁/날_위한_크리스마스/</id><title>경민혁 - 날 위한 크리스마스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:16:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:16:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B2%BD%EB%AF%BC%ED%98%81/%EB%82%A0_%EC%9C%84%ED%95%9C_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%A4%EB%A7%88%EC%8A%A4/" title="경민혁 - 날 위한 크리스마스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[추운 고요한 밤 <br>눈 내리는 밤 <br>나의 작은 집은 <br>두근거리고 있어 <br>차가운 겨울이 <br>따스해 너와 함께라 <br>이런 겨울이 <br>영원했으면 좋겠어 <br>하얀 눈 바람 불어와 <br>눈꽃송이 휘날리고 <br>크리스마스 종소리가 <br>울려 퍼지면 <br>작은 파티가 시작 돼 <br>현관문 앞 니가 나타나면 <br>뛰어가서 폭 안길 거야 <br>흥겨운 노랫소리 맞춰서 <br>꼭 안고 춤도 추면서 <br>준비한 선물 <br>풀어보면 놀라서 <br>나를 숨막히게 안을걸 <br>널 위한 크리스마스 <br>공연도 기대해 <br>오늘 밤 시작해 <br>너는 날 웃게 해 <br>내가 만든 <br>이상한 스웨터 입고 <br>집까지 왔어 <br>포장해서 익힌 요리와 <br>세일한 와인 <br>이런 작은 기쁨 <br>영원했음 좋겠어 <br>하얀 눈 바람 불어와 <br>눈꽃송이 휘날리고 <br>크리스마스 종소리가 <br>울려 퍼지면 <br>작은 파티가 시작 돼 <br>현관문 앞 니가 나타나면 <br>뛰어가서 폭 안길 거야 <br>흥겨운 노랫소리 맞춰서 <br>꼭 안고 춤도 추면서 <br>준비한 선물 <br>풀어보면 놀라서 <br>나를 숨막히게 안을 걸 <br>널 위한 크리스마스 <br>공연도 기대해 <br>오늘 밤 시작해 <br>따스하게 나를 바라보며 <br>니 품 속에 날 안아줄래 <br>가슴이 두근거려 <br>날 안고 춤추는 <br>니가 좋아서 <br>니가 준 선물 <br>풀어보고 놀라서 <br>눈물을 멈출 수 없었어 <br>날 위한 크리스마스 인가 봐 <br>사랑해 너를 영원히 <br>조그만 크리스마스트리에 <br>빛나는 별들 <br>희한한 마법 같았어 <br>달콤한 너와의 시간 <br>]]></content><category term="경민혁" label="경민혁"/><category term="날 위한 크리스마스" label="날 위한 크리스마스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/경민혁/오빠_요리_잘해요/</id><title>경민혁 - 오빠 요리 잘해요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:16:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:16:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B2%BD%EB%AF%BC%ED%98%81/%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%A0_%EC%9A%94%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9E%98%ED%95%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="경민혁 - 오빠 요리 잘해요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[냠냠 냠냠 냠냠 냠냠 <br>냠냠 냠 냠냠 냠냠 <br>냠냠 냠 냠냠 냠냠 <br>냠냠 냠 냠냠 냠 <br>오빠 요리 잘해요 <br>내 부엌으로 초대할게 <br>맛있는 거 해줘요 <br>맛있는 거 원해요 <br>내 예민한 미각이 <br>오빠 요릴 원하고 있어 <br>설레는 맛 황홀한 맛 <br>기절할 듯한 그런 맛 <br>오빤 요리할 때가 <br>너무 섹시해 <br>날카론 칼놀림 <br>가슴이 두근 <br>펜을 튕기는 <br>굵은 오빠의 팔뚝 <br>화려한 불꽃에 <br>떨리는 마음 <br>매콤하고 쌉쌀해 <br>담백하고 상큼해 <br>오빠 요리 잘해요 <br>내 부엌으로 초대할게 <br>맛있는 거 해줘요 <br>맛있는 거 원해요 <br>내 예민한 미각이 <br>오빠 요릴 원하고 있어 <br>설레는 맛 황홀한 맛 <br>기절할 듯한 그런 맛 <br>어떤 맛 집에서도 <br>맛 볼 수 없는 <br>나 만의 요리 오빠의 요리 <br>착한 사랑에 굶어 <br>앙상했었던 나의 마음이 <br>통통해져 가 <br>새콤하고 달콤해 <br>고소하고 짭쪼름해 <br>오빠 요리 잘해요 <br>내 부엌으로 초대할게 <br>맛있는 거 해줘요 <br>맛있는 거 원해요 <br>내 예민한 미각이 <br>오빠 요릴 원하고 있어 <br>설레는 맛 황홀한 맛 <br>기절할 듯한 그런 맛 <br>달콤한 간장소스 <br>부드런 크림소스 <br>내 입맛에 딱 맞아 <br>날 만족시켜 <br>디저트는 내가 준비할게 <br>오빠 요리 잘해요 <br>내 부엌으로 초대할게 <br>맛있는 거 해줘요 <br>맛있는 거 원해요 <br>내 예민한 미각이 <br>오빠 요릴 원하고 있어 <br>설레는 맛 황홀한 맛 <br>기절할 듯한 그런 맛 <br>설레는 맛 황홀한 맛 <br>기절할 듯한 그런 맛 <br>설거지는 내가 할게 <br>뒤에서 날 꼭 안아줘 <br>]]></content><category term="경민혁" label="경민혁"/><category term="오빠 요리 잘해요" label="오빠 요리 잘해요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/경민혁/달밤/</id><title>경민혁 - 달밤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:16:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:16:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B2%BD%EB%AF%BC%ED%98%81/%EB%8B%AC%EB%B0%A4/" title="경민혁 - 달밤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대를 떠난 지 <br>여러 해가 지나갔어 <br>밝은 달 <br>떠오른 밤이면 <br>그대가 생각나네 <br>나 떠나 힘들었던 <br>그대가 웃는다니 <br>그 미소 말갛던 얼굴을 <br>어루만지고 싶어 <br>운명에 벽 앞에 <br>초라해지고 <br>약해질 뿐인 <br>나지만 <br>그대를 위해 <br>버티고 있어 <br>다시 만날 그날 <br>위해서 <br>밤바람 타고 날아온 <br>그대의 모습들이 <br>그리움 가득한 <br>그 고운 웃음 <br>다시 만날 수 있을까 <br>그대는 어디에서 <br>내 생각 하고 있나 <br>부드런 그대에 살결에 <br>쉬고픈 밤이라네 <br>기약 없는 기다림 <br>흐르는 시간 <br>쓰러져 버리고 <br>싶을 땐 <br>그대의 마음이 <br>날 잡아주길 <br>날 다시 일으켜 세우길 <br>밤바람 타고 날아온 <br>그대의 모습들이 <br>그리움 가득한 <br>그 고운 웃음 <br>다시 만날 수 있을까 <br>이렇게 오래 <br>떠나 있을 줄 알았다면 <br>내 품 속에 조금 더 <br>안고 있을걸 <br>그대와 함께 <br>행복하게 살고 싶어서 <br>시작한 이 여정 <br>언제 끝날 지 <br>알 수가 없어 <br>웃으며 나를 보내던 <br>그대의 눈동자엔 <br>눈물이 가득해 <br>품에 안고서 <br>돌아오겠다 했는데 <br>밤바람 타고 날아온 <br>그대의 모습들이 <br>그리움 가득한 <br>그 고운 웃음 <br>다시 만날 수 있을까 <br>]]></content><category term="경민혁" label="경민혁"/><category term="달밤" label="달밤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/경민혁/들키지_않게/</id><title>경민혁 - 들키지 않게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:16:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:16:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B2%BD%EB%AF%BC%ED%98%81/%EB%93%A4%ED%82%A4%EC%A7%80_%EC%95%8A%EA%B2%8C/" title="경민혁 - 들키지 않게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너를 보면 내 마음이 <br>두근대 <br>이 마음을 너는 아는지 <br>바보야 <br>내가 먼저 너의 얼굴 <br>보면서 이렇게 말해 <br>친구들 몰래 <br>나랑 만날래 <br>으흐흐 <br>이 바보야 몰랐겠지 <br>나도 널 <br>좋아하고 있었다는 걸 <br>친구들을 주말마다 <br>부른 건 오 사실은 <br>너의 얼굴 <br>보고 싶어서 <br>친구들 몰래 <br>너와나 단둘이 우리 <br>만나서 설레는 <br>데이트를 해 <br>노노노 우리 이제 <br>친구 아냐 망설이지마 <br>아무도 모르게 <br>들키지 않게 <br>맑은 하늘 아래에서 <br>너와나 <br>둘이 함께 <br>손을 잡고 걷고 싶었어 <br>너의 부드러운 손을 <br>내 옆에서 향기로운 봄처럼 <br>봄 하늘 바람처럼 <br>웃는 너를 여름처럼 <br>사랑해줄게 <br>언제부터 나를 <br>좋아한 거니 <br>나는 예전에 <br>너를 만났을 때 <br>너의 이쁜 눈에 <br>반해버려 좋아했었어 <br>수줍음 많던 내가 <br>너에게 용기 내서 <br>한 발짝 다가갔으니 <br>두 발짝 니가 다가와 <br>친구들 몰래 <br>나와서 <br>너와나 단둘이 우리 <br>만나서 설레는 <br>데이트를 해 <br>노노노 걸리지마 <br>부끄럽잖아 <br>멀리 <br>우리 동네 밖에 나가서 <br>아무도 모르게 <br>들키지 않게 <br>맑은 하늘 아래에서 <br>너와나 <br>둘이 함께 <br>손을 잡고 걷고 싶었어 <br>너의 부드러운 손을 <br>내 옆에서 향기로운 봄처럼 <br>봄 하늘 바람처럼 <br>웃는 너를 <br>친구들 몰래 <br>뜨거운 여름처럼 <br>사랑해줄게요 <br>아 <br>들켰네 <br>]]></content><category term="경민혁" label="경민혁"/><category term="들키지 않게" label="들키지 않게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/경민혁/어제_오늘_내일/</id><title>경민혁 - 어제 오늘 내일 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:16:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:16:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B2%BD%EB%AF%BC%ED%98%81/%EC%96%B4%EC%A0%9C_%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98_%EB%82%B4%EC%9D%BC/" title="경민혁 - 어제 오늘 내일 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[걱정 말아요 모두 <br>나 잘 지내고 있어 <br>그런 표정 말아요 <br>일상에 지쳐서 <br>사랑은 잠시 안녕 <br>괜찮아요 <br>오늘 슬픈 하루 <br>내일 태양은 뜨겠죠 <br>오늘 살다가 보면 <br>내일 사랑이 오겠죠 <br>어제 그대 떠나 <br>오늘 나 힘들지만 <br>내일 웃고 살 거야 <br>슬픈 사랑 보다 <br>즐거운 하루 <br>더 좋은 어른 아이 <br>이야기할 때 <br>나의 눈치보지 말아요 <br>이대로 괜찮아요 <br>바쁜 일상에 치여 <br>사랑은 잠시 안녕 <br>괜찮아요 <br>오늘 슬픈 하루 <br>내일 태양은 뜨겠죠 <br>오늘 살다가 보면 <br>내일 사랑이 오겠죠 <br>어제 그대 떠나 <br>오늘 나 힘들지만 <br>내일 웃고 살 거야 <br>무엇이 행복인가요 <br>나는 잘 모르겠어 <br>사랑이 행복인가요 <br>당신은 행복한가요 <br>어릴 적엔 지금 <br>나의 나이 되면 <br>인생을 알 줄 <br>알았었는데 <br>괜찮아요 <br>오늘 슬픈 하루 <br>내일 태양은 뜨겠죠 <br>오늘 살다가 보면 <br>내일 사랑이 오겠죠 <br>어제 그대 떠나 <br>오늘 나 힘들지만 <br>내일 웃고 살 거야 <br>걱정을 말아요 <br>괜찮아요 <br>사랑을 쉰다고 <br>슬퍼 마요 <br>하루 이틀 살다 보면 <br>나도 다시 사랑하겠죠 <br>지금 내게 필요한 것은 <br>야근 없는 행복한 일상들 <br>]]></content><category term="경민혁" label="경민혁"/><category term="어제 오늘 내일" label="어제 오늘 내일"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/경민혁/웃는_니가_좋아/</id><title>경민혁 - 웃는 니가 좋아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:16:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:16:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B2%BD%EB%AF%BC%ED%98%81/%EC%9B%83%EB%8A%94_%EB%8B%88%EA%B0%80_%EC%A2%8B%EC%95%84/" title="경민혁 - 웃는 니가 좋아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[환하게 웃는 니가 좋아 <br>아무 걱정 없는 것 같아 <br>너의 웃음 사로잡아서 <br>내 것으로 하고 싶어 <br>비가 내려와 가슴속에 <br>맑았던 날이 하루 있었는지 <br>편안해져 비가 내리면 <br>고요해져 모든 것이 <br>거울 속에서 슬프게 <br>나를 보는 표정 없는 자 <br>누구인 건지 <br>나를 왜 숨막히게 <br>비참하게 만들어 <br>비가 내려와 어둠 속에 <br>널 생각하며 기다리고 있어 <br>편안해져 비가 내리면 <br>고요해져 모든 것이 <br>거울 속에서 슬프게 <br>나를 보는 표정 없는 자 <br>누구인 건지 <br>나를 왜 숨막히게 <br>비참하게 해 <br>나 미칠 것 같아 <br>불안이 밀려들어 <br>시린 너의 숨결이 <br>독처럼 파고들어 <br>너의 치명적인 한 마디가 <br>나를 더 어둠으로 밀어 <br>텅 빈 눈동자 <br>멍하니 나를 보는 <br>새하얀 얼굴 <br>일그러진 니 표정이 <br>날 웃게 해 <br>입맞추고 싶어져 <br>미칠 것 같아 <br>내 안에 사는 니가 <br>망가져 버린 멈춰진 심장 <br>이제는 쉬고 싶어 <br>이 세상에서 영원히 <br>]]></content><category term="경민혁" label="경민혁"/><category term="웃는 니가 좋아" label="웃는 니가 좋아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/후아유/Sweet_My_Love/</id><title>후아유 - Sweet My Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:16:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:16:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9B%84%EC%95%84%EC%9C%A0/Sweet_My_Love/" title="후아유 - Sweet My Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sweet My Love <br>그대를 사랑하는 내 맘이 <br>그대만 바라보는 내 맘이 <br>달콤한 러브 라떼 <br>fall in love falling in love <br>Love is you <br>시간이 흘러도 내 마음에 <br>변하지 않는 사랑이란 걸 <br>그대만 모르죠 <br>without you <br>without your love can't live <br>이렇게 내게 <br>사랑을 알려준 너 <br>놀라게 변해가 <br>세상이 변해만 가 <br>혼자 걷는 내 모습 <br>어딘지 어색해도 <br>입가엔 미소가 번지고 <br>발걸음 가벼워 <br>Sweet My Love <br>그대를 사랑하는 내 맘이 <br>그대만 바라보는 내 맘이 <br>달콤한 러브 라떼 <br>fall in love falling in love <br>Love is you <br>시간이 흘러도 <br>내 마음에 변하지 않는 <br>사랑이란 걸 <br>그대만 모르죠 <br>without you <br>without your love can't live <br>감출 수 없어 <br>니 모습 바라보면 <br>우울했던 기분 <br>한순간 사라져가 <br>내가 알던 사랑은 <br>사랑이 아니었어 <br>모든 게 새롭고 놀라워 <br>니 곁에 있으면 <br>Sweet My Love <br>그대를 사랑하는 내 맘이 <br>그대만 바라보는 내 맘이 <br>달콤한 러브 라떼 <br>fall in love falling in love <br>Love is you <br>시간이 흘러도 <br>내 마음에 변하지 않는 <br>사랑이란 걸 <br>그대만 모르죠 <br>without you <br>without your love can't live <br>이별이란 없겠죠 <br>가야 할 이 길 위에 <br>그냥 이대로 영원히 <br>함께 어디든 <br>Sweet My Love <br>그대를 사랑하는 내 맘이 <br>그대만 바라보는 내 맘이 <br>달콤한 러브 라떼 <br>fall in love falling in love <br>Love is you <br>시간이 흘러도 <br>내 마음에 변하지 않는 <br>사랑이란 걸 <br>그대만 모르죠 <br>without you <br>without your love can't live <br>]]></content><category term="후아유" label="후아유"/><category term="Sweet My Love" label="Sweet My Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/공휘/나에게_빠져들어_With_홍나영/</id><title>공휘 - 나에게 빠져들어 (With 홍나영) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:17:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:17:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%B5%ED%9C%98/%EB%82%98%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_%EB%B9%A0%EC%A0%B8%EB%93%A4%EC%96%B4_With_%ED%99%8D%EB%82%98%EC%98%81/" title="공휘 - 나에게 빠져들어 (With 홍나영) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[안녕 거울보며 <br>내게 인사해 <br>시작은 늘 홧팅 <br>힘찬 발걸음 룰루랄라 <br>행복한 일 가득 <br>마음속에 담아두고 <br>하루종일 뱅뱅 <br>머리속이 복잡해져 <br>웃어볼까 <br>나에게 점점 빠져 들거야 <br>당당한 내 모습 가장 나답게 <br>어떠한 어려움이 내게와도 <br>한번더 웃어봐 <br>힘을내 나처럼 <br>모두다 빠져들어 <br>나에게 빠져들어 <br>오늘 하루 혼자 <br>이겨냈다 위로하고 <br>마무린 늘 퍼펙하게 <br>나를 사랑하며 <br>웃어볼까 <br>나에게 점점 빠져 들거야 <br>당당한 내모습 가장 나답게 <br>어떠한 어려움이 내게 와도 <br>한번 더 웃어봐 <br>힘을내 나처럼 <br>모두다 빠져들어 <br>모두가 내게 빠져 들거야 <br>외로워 슬퍼도 울지 않을래 <br>어떠한 어려움이 내게 와도 <br>한번더 웃어봐 <br>힘을내 나처럼 <br>모두 다 빠져들어 <br>나에게 빠져들어 <br>]]></content><category term="공휘" label="공휘"/><category term="나에게 빠져들어 (With 홍나영)" label="나에게 빠져들어 (With 홍나영)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/03소1059/없네_Feat_박준하/</id><title>03소1059 - 없네 (Feat. 박준하) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:17:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:17:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/03%EC%86%8C1059/%EC%97%86%EB%84%A4_Feat_%EB%B0%95%EC%A4%80%ED%95%98/" title="03소1059 - 없네 (Feat. 박준하) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[술에 취해 비틀거리던 밤 <br>집으로 가는 골목길에서 <br>나는 길을 잃었네 <br>여기가 어디쯤인지 <br>잠시 담벼락에 기대앉아 <br>조용한 밤하늘을 올려다본 <br>나는 그리워졌네 <br>어느새 눈물이 흘러내리네 <br>흐르는 눈물을 닦아내고 <br>한참을 내려간 전화번호들 <br>나는 찾지 못했네 <br>어느새 눈물이 흘러내리네 <br>없네 없네 연락할 사람 없네 <br>아무리 찾아보아도 <br>없네 없네 연락할 사람 없네 <br>아무리 찾아보아도 <br>그 많은 얼굴들 전화번호들 <br>그리 많아도 <br>내 전화 받아줄 사람은 <br>그 많은 사람들 전화번호들 <br>그리 많아도 <br>내 전화 받아줄 사람은 <br>없네 없네 연락할 사람 없네 <br>아무리 찾아보아도 <br>없네 없네 연락할 사람 없네 <br>아무리 찾아보아도 <br>]]></content><category term="03소1059" label="03소1059"/><category term="없네 (Feat. 박준하)" label="없네 (Feat. 박준하)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/심보준/내_모습_그대로/</id><title>심보준 - 내 모습 그대로 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:17:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:17:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%AC%EB%B3%B4%EC%A4%80/%EB%82%B4_%EB%AA%A8%EC%8A%B5_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%A1%9C/" title="심보준 - 내 모습 그대로 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주는 토기장이 <br>나는 그의 진흙 <br>그의 형상대로 <br>날 빚으셨네 <br>주님 보시기에 <br>참 좋은 작품 <br>주는 내 아버지 <br>나는 그의 아들 <br>그의 형상 닮아 <br>나 태어났네 <br>주님 보시기에 <br>참 좋은 아들 <br>내 모습 그대로 <br>나를 빚으신 주님 <br>내 모습 그대로 <br>나를 낳으신 주님 <br>내 모습 그대로 <br>나를 사용하실 주님 <br>당신의 두 손에 <br>내 삶을 맡겨드립니다 <br>주는 내 아버지 <br>나는 그의 아들 <br>그의 형상 닮아 <br>나 태어났네 <br>주님 보시기에 <br>참 좋은 아들 <br>내 모습 그대로 <br>나를 빚으신 주님 <br>내 모습 그대로 <br>나를 낳으신 주님 <br>내 모습 그대로 <br>나를 사용하실 주님 <br>당신의 두 손에 <br>내 삶을 맡겨드립니다 <br>한 발도 나갈 수 없어 <br>어둔 방에 홀로 있을 때 <br>날 만드신 손이 <br>날 위해 못 박으신 손이 <br>그 손이 나를 이끄셨네 <br>내 모습 그대로 <br>내 모습 그대로 <br>나를 빚으신 주님 <br>내 모습 그대로 <br>나를 낳으신 주님 <br>내 모습 그대로 <br>나를 사용하실 주님 <br>당신의 두 손에 <br>내 삶을 맡겨드립니다 <br>주님 보시기에 <br>참 좋은 작품 <br>]]></content><category term="심보준" label="심보준"/><category term="내 모습 그대로" label="내 모습 그대로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정경/어메이징_아리랑_Amazing_Arirang/</id><title>정경 - 어메이징 아리랑 (Amazing Arirang) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:17:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:17:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B2%BD/%EC%96%B4%EB%A9%94%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%95_%EC%95%84%EB%A6%AC%EB%9E%91_Amazing_Arirang/" title="정경 - 어메이징 아리랑 (Amazing Arirang) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Amazing grace <br>how sweet the sound <br>That saved a wretch like me <br>I once was lost <br>but now I'm found <br>Was blind but now I see <br>Amazing grace <br>how sweet the sound <br>That saved a wretch like me <br>I once was lost <br>but now I'm found <br>Was blind but now I see <br>아리랑 아리랑 아라리요 <br>아리랑 고개로 넘어간다 <br>나를 버리고 가시는 님은 <br>십 리도 못 가서 발병 난다 <br>아리랑 아리랑 아라리요 <br>아리랑 고개로 넘어간다 <br>나를 버리고 가시는 님은 <br>십 리도 못 가서 발병 난다 <br>나를 버리고서 가시는 님은 <br>십 리도 못 가서 발병 난다 <br>십 리도 못 가서 발병 난다 <br>]]></content><category term="정경" label="정경"/><category term="어메이징 아리랑 (Amazing Arirang)" label="어메이징 아리랑 (Amazing Arirang)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정경/그녀에게_To_My_Love/</id><title>정경 - 그녀에게 (To My Love) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:17:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:17:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B2%BD/%EA%B7%B8%EB%85%80%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_To_My_Love/" title="정경 - 그녀에게 (To My Love) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[달아나듯 흘러간 <br>저 세월의 무게 앞에 눌려 <br>수많은 걸 버려왔지 <br>너와의 날들 마저 <br>이제서야 돌아 보네 <br>홀로 남겨진 너에게 <br>해줄 게 하나 없는 무력함에 <br>스스로 작아져 가는 <br>주저앉은 날 <br>잡아 끄는 소리가 들려 <br>일어나 그녀에게로 가 <br>마지막인 것처럼 쉼 없이 달려가 <br>그녈 안고 온 힘을 다해서 <br>조금은 어색 하더라도 <br>이렇게 말을 해 <br>미안해 너의 소중함을 <br>지켜내지 못했던 철없던 어림을 <br>조금만 더 지켜봐 줘 <br>내 생에 남은 날들과 <br>함께할 모습을 <br>일어나 그녀에게로 가 <br>마지막인 것처럼 쉼 없이 달려가 <br>그녈 안고 온 힘을 다해서 <br>조금은 어색 하더라도 <br>이렇게 말을 해 <br>미안해 너의 소중함을 <br>지켜내지 못했던 철없던 어림을 <br>조금만 더 지켜봐 줘 <br>내 생에 남은 날들과 <br>]]></content><category term="정경" label="정경"/><category term="그녀에게 (To My Love)" label="그녀에게 (To My Love)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정경/남촌_Southern_Countryside/</id><title>정경 - 남촌 (Southern Countryside) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:17:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:17:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B2%BD/%EB%82%A8%EC%B4%8C_Southern_Countryside/" title="정경 - 남촌 (Southern Countryside) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[산 너머 남촌에는 누가 살길래 <br>해마다 봄바람이 남으로 오네 <br>꽃이 피는 사월이면 진달래향기 <br>밀 익는 오월이면 보리 내음새 <br>어느 것 한가진들 실어 안 오리 <br>남촌서 남풍 불 때 나는 좋대나 <br>산 너머 남촌에는 누가 살길래 <br>저 하늘 저 빛깔이 그리 고울까 <br>금잔디 넓은 벌엔 호랑 나비떼 <br>버들가지 실개천엔 종달새 노래 <br>어느 것 한가진들 실어 안 오리 <br>남촌서 남풍 불 때 나는 좋대나 <br>]]></content><category term="정경" label="정경"/><category term="남촌 (Southern Countryside)" label="남촌 (Southern Countryside)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정경/산촌_Mountain_Village/</id><title>정경 - 산촌 (Mountain Village) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:17:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:17:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B2%BD/%EC%82%B0%EC%B4%8C_Mountain_Village/" title="정경 - 산촌 (Mountain Village) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[달구지 가는 소리는 <br>산령을 도는데 <br>물긷는 아가씨 모습이 <br>꽃인 양 곱구나 <br>사립문 떠밀어 열고 <br>들판을 바라보면 <br>눈부신 아침 햇빛에 <br>오곡이 넘치네 <br>아아 박꽃 향내 <br>흐르는 마을 <br>천년 만년 누려 본 들 <br>싫다 손 늬하랴 <br>망아지 우는 소리는 <br>언덕을 넘는데 <br>흐르는 시냇물 사이로 <br>구름은 말없네 <br>농주는 알맞게 익어 <br>풍년을 바라보고 <br>땀 배인 얼굴마다 <br>웃음이 넘치네 <br>아아 박꽃 향내 <br>흐르는 마을 <br>천년 만년 누려 본 들 <br>싫다 손 늬하랴 <br>]]></content><category term="정경" label="정경"/><category term="산촌 (Mountain Village)" label="산촌 (Mountain Village)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정경/제주해녀_-_바다를_담은_소녀_Jeju_Haenyeo_-_The_deep_sea_inside_a_girl/</id><title>정경 - 제주해녀 - 바다를 담은 소녀 (Jeju Haenyeo - The deep sea inside a girl) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:17:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:17:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B2%BD/%EC%A0%9C%EC%A3%BC%ED%95%B4%EB%85%80_-_%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%A4%EB%A5%BC_%EB%8B%B4%EC%9D%80_%EC%86%8C%EB%85%80_Jeju_Haenyeo_-_The_deep_sea_inside_a_girl/" title="정경 - 제주해녀 - 바다를 담은 소녀 (Jeju Haenyeo - The deep sea inside a girl) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아직은 가녀린 몸 위로 <br>속곳을 걸치고 <br>좁고 너른 모퉁이 <br>돌아 올레길 지나 <br>언덕 넘어 보이는 <br>하늘을 담은 <br>또 다른 하늘이 <br>소녈 기다리네 <br>소녀의 손끝이 <br>바다를 가르며 <br>지나온 세월의 <br>파도 마시며 <br>수면 위를 수놓는 <br>숨비 소리가 <br>주름에 새겨지듯 <br>깊어가는 바다 <br>바다를 담은 소녀 <br>그 두 손으로 <br>하늘 가르며 꿈을 꾸어요 <br>바다를 담은 소녀 <br>그 두 눈으로 <br>세상 만지며 꿈을 나눠요 <br>소녀의 손끝이 <br>바다를 가르며 <br>지나온 세월의 <br>파도 마시며 <br>수면 위를 수놓는 <br>숨비 소리가 <br>주름에 새겨지듯 <br>깊어가는 바다 <br>바다를 담은 소녀 <br>그 두 손으로 <br>하늘 가르며 꿈을 꾸어요 <br>바다를 담은 소녀 <br>그 두 눈으로 <br>세상 만지며 꿈을 나눠요 <br>바다를 담은 소녀 <br>그 두 손으로 <br>하늘 가르며 꿈을 꾸어요 <br>바다를 담은 소녀 <br>그 두 눈으로 <br>세상 만지며 꿈을 나눠요 <br>꿈을 꾸어요 <br>꿈을 나눠요 <br>]]></content><category term="정경" label="정경"/><category term="제주해녀 - 바다를 담은 소녀 (Jeju Haenyeo - The deep sea inside a girl)" label="제주해녀 - 바다를 담은 소녀 (Jeju Haenyeo - The deep sea inside a girl)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정경/Mozart___Le_Nozze_Di_Figaro_K492_-_Hai_Gia_Vinta_La_Causa_모차르트___피가로의_결혼_-_넌_벌써_승리를_가졌다/</id><title>정경 - Mozart : Le Nozze Di Figaro K.492 - Hai Gia Vinta La Causa (모차르트 : 피가로의 결혼 - 넌 벌써 승리를 가졌다) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:17:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:17:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B2%BD/Mozart___Le_Nozze_Di_Figaro_K492_-_Hai_Gia_Vinta_La_Causa_%EB%AA%A8%EC%B0%A8%EB%A5%B4%ED%8A%B8___%ED%94%BC%EA%B0%80%EB%A1%9C%EC%9D%98_%EA%B2%B0%ED%98%BC_-_%EB%84%8C_%EB%B2%8C%EC%8D%A8_%EC%8A%B9%EB%A6%AC%EB%A5%BC_%EA%B0%80%EC%A1%8C%EB%8B%A4/" title="정경 - Mozart : Le Nozze Di Figaro K.492 - Hai Gia Vinta La Causa (모차르트 : 피가로의 결혼 - 넌 벌써 승리를 가졌다) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hai gia vinta la causa <br>Cosa sento <br>In qual laccio io cadea <br>Perfidi Io voglio <br>Di tal modo punirvi <br>A piacer mio <br>La sentenza sara <br>Ma s'ei pagasse <br>La vecchia pretendente <br>Pagarla In qual maniera <br>E poi v'e Antonio <br>Che a un incognito <br>Figaro ricusa Di dare <br>una nipote in matrimonio <br>Coltivando l'orgoglio <br>Di questo mentecatto <br>Tutto giova a un raggiro <br>Il colpo e fatto <br>Vedro mentre io sospiro <br>Felice un servo mio <br>E un ben ch'invan desio <br>Ei posseder dovra <br>Vedro per man d'amore <br>Unita a un vile oggetto <br>Chi in me desto un affetto <br>Che per me poi non ha <br>Che per me poi non ha <br>Vedro mentre io sospiro <br>Felice un servo mio <br>E un ben ch'invan desio <br>Ei posseder dovra <br>Vedro per man d'amore <br>Unita a un vile oggetto <br>Chi in me desto un affetto <br>Che per me poi non ha <br>Che per me poi non ha <br>Vedro Vedro Vedro Vedro <br>Ah no lasciarti in pace <br>Non vo' questo contento <br>Tu non nascesti audace <br>Tu non nascesti audace <br>Per dare a me tormento <br>E forse ancor per ridere <br>per ridere <br>Di mia infelicita <br>Gia la speranza sola <br>Delle vendette mie <br>Quest'anima consola <br>E giubilar mi fa <br>E giubilar <br>E giubilar mi fa <br>Ah no lasciarti in pace <br>Non vo' questo contento <br>Tu non nascesti audace <br>Per dare a me tormento <br>E forse ancor per ridere <br>per ridere <br>Di mia infelicita <br>Gia la speranza sola <br>Delle vendette mie <br>Quest'anima consola <br>E giubilar mi fa <br>E giubilar <br>E giubilar mi fa <br>E giubilar <br>E giubilar mi fa <br>E giubilar mi fa <br>E giubilar mi fa <br>]]></content><category term="정경" label="정경"/><category term="Mozart : Le Nozze Di Figaro K.492 - Hai Gia Vinta La Causa (모차르트 : 피가로의 결혼 - 넌 벌써 승리를 가졌다)" label="Mozart : Le Nozze Di Figaro K.492 - Hai Gia Vinta La Causa (모차르트 : 피가로의 결혼 - 넌 벌써 승리를 가졌다)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정경/Respighi___Nebbie_레스피기___안개/</id><title>정경 - Respighi : Nebbie (레스피기 : 안개) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:17:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:17:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B2%BD/Respighi___Nebbie_%EB%A0%88%EC%8A%A4%ED%94%BC%EA%B8%B0___%EC%95%88%EA%B0%9C/" title="정경 - Respighi : Nebbie (레스피기 : 안개) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Soffro Lontan lontano <br>Le nebbie sonnolente <br>Salgono dal tacente Piano <br>Alto gracchiando i corvi <br>Fidati all'ali nere <br>Traversan le brughiere Torvi <br>Dell'aere ai morsi crudi <br>Gli addolorati tronchi <br>Offron pregando <br>i bronchi Nudi <br>Come ho freddo <br>Son solo <br>Pel grigio ciel sospinto <br>Un gemito d'estinto Vola <br>E mi ripete Vieni <br>E buia la vallata <br>O triste o disamata <br>Vieni Vieni <br>]]></content><category term="정경" label="정경"/><category term="Respighi : Nebbie (레스피기 : 안개)" label="Respighi : Nebbie (레스피기 : 안개)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정경/Leoncavallo___Mattinata_레온카발로___아침의_노래/</id><title>정경 - Leoncavallo : Mattinata (레온카발로 : 아침의 노래) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:18:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:18:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B2%BD/Leoncavallo___Mattinata_%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A8%EC%B9%B4%EB%B0%9C%EB%A1%9C___%EC%95%84%EC%B9%A8%EC%9D%98_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="정경 - Leoncavallo : Mattinata (레온카발로 : 아침의 노래) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[L'aurora di bianco vestita <br>Gia l'uscio dischiude al gran sol <br>Di gia con le rosee sue dita <br>Carezza de' fiori lo stuol <br>Commosso da un fremito <br>arcano Intorno il creato <br>E tu non ti desti ed invano <br>Mi sto qui dolente a cantar <br>Metti anche tu la veste Bianca <br>E schiudi l'uscio al tuo cantor <br>Ove non sei la luce manc <br>Ove tu sei nasce l'amor <br>Ove non sei la luce manc <br>Ove tu sei <br>Ove tu sei nasce l'amor <br>]]></content><category term="정경" label="정경"/><category term="Leoncavallo : Mattinata (레온카발로 : 아침의 노래)" label="Leoncavallo : Mattinata (레온카발로 : 아침의 노래)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정경/RStrauss___8_Lieder_Aus_Letzte_Blatter_Op10_-_I_Zueignung_리하르트_슈트라우스___8개의_가곡_작품번호_10_-_1번_헌정/</id><title>정경 - R.Strauss : 8 Lieder Aus Letzte Blatter Op.10 - I. Zueignung (리하르트 슈트라우스 : 8개의 가곡 작품번호 10 - 1번. 헌정) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:18:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:18:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B2%BD/RStrauss___8_Lieder_Aus_Letzte_Blatter_Op10_-_I_Zueignung_%EB%A6%AC%ED%95%98%EB%A5%B4%ED%8A%B8_%EC%8A%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B0%EC%8A%A4___8%EA%B0%9C%EC%9D%98_%EA%B0%80%EA%B3%A1_%EC%9E%91%ED%92%88%EB%B2%88%ED%98%B8_10_-_1%EB%B2%88_%ED%97%8C%EC%A0%95/" title="정경 - R.Strauss : 8 Lieder Aus Letzte Blatter Op.10 - I. Zueignung (리하르트 슈트라우스 : 8개의 가곡 작품번호 10 - 1번. 헌정) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ja du weisst es teure Seele <br>Dass ich fern von dir mich quale <br>Liebe macht die Herzen krank <br>Habe Dank <br>Einst hielt ich der Freiheit <br>Zecher <br>Hoch den Amethysten Becher <br>Und du segnetest den Trank <br>Habe Dank <br>Und beschworst darin die Bosen <br>Bis ich was ich nie gewesen <br>Heilig heilig an's Herz dir sank <br>Habe Dank <br>]]></content><category term="정경" label="정경"/><category term="R.Strauss : 8 Lieder Aus Letzte Blatter Op.10 - I. Zueignung (리하르트 슈트라우스 : 8개의 가곡 작품번호 10 - 1번. 헌정)" label="R.Strauss : 8 Lieder Aus Letzte Blatter Op.10 - I. Zueignung (리하르트 슈트라우스 : 8개의 가곡 작품번호 10 - 1번. 헌정)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정경/Schubert___Der_Erlkonig_Op1_D328_슈베르트___마왕_작품번호_1/</id><title>정경 - Schubert : Der Erlkonig Op.1 D.328 (슈베르트 : 마왕 작품번호 1) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:18:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:18:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B2%BD/Schubert___Der_Erlkonig_Op1_D328_%EC%8A%88%EB%B2%A0%EB%A5%B4%ED%8A%B8___%EB%A7%88%EC%99%95_%EC%9E%91%ED%92%88%EB%B2%88%ED%98%B8_1/" title="정경 - Schubert : Der Erlkonig Op.1 D.328 (슈베르트 : 마왕 작품번호 1) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wer reitet so spat durch <br>Nacht und Wind <br>Es ist der Vater mit seinem Kind <br>Er hat den Knaben wohl in dem Arm <br>Er fabt ihn sicher er halt ihn <br>warm <br>Mein Sohn was birgst du <br>so bang dein Gesicht <br>Siehst Vater <br>du den Erlkonig nicht <br>Den Erlenkonig mit Kron <br>und Schwief <br>Mein Sohn es ist ein Nebelstreif <br>Du liebes Kind komm <br>geh mit mir <br>Gar schone Spiele spiel <br>ich mit dir Manch bunte <br>Blumen sind an dem Strand <br>Meine Mutter hat manch <br>gulden Gewand <br>Mein Vater mein Vater <br>und horest du nicht <br>Was Erlenkonig mir <br>leise verspricht <br>Sei ruhig bleibe ruhig <br>mein Kind <br>In durren Blattern <br>sauselt der Wind <br>Willst feiner Knabe <br>du mit mir gehn Meine <br>Tochter sollen dich <br>warten schon <br>Meine Tochter fuhren <br>den nachtlichen Reihn <br>Und wiegen und tanzen <br>und singen dich ein <br>Sie wiegen und tanzen <br>und singen dich ein <br>Mein Vater mein Vater <br>und siehst du nicht <br>dort Erlkonigs Tochter <br>am dustern Ort <br>Mein Sohn mein Sohn <br>ich seh es genau Es <br>scheinen die alten <br>Weiden so grau <br>Ich liebe dich <br>mich reizt deine schone Gestalt <br>Und bist du nicht willig <br>so brauch ich Gewalt <br>Mein Vater mein Vater <br>jetzt fabt er mich an <br>Erlkonig hat mir ein Leids getan <br>Dem Vater grauset's er reitet <br>geschwind Er halt in Armen <br>das achzende Kind <br>Erreicht den Hof mit Muh' und Not <br>In seinen Armen das Kind war tot <br>]]></content><category term="정경" label="정경"/><category term="Schubert : Der Erlkonig Op.1 D.328 (슈베르트 : 마왕 작품번호 1)" label="Schubert : Der Erlkonig Op.1 D.328 (슈베르트 : 마왕 작품번호 1)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정경/Beethoven___Ich_Liebe_Dich_WoO123_베토벤___그대를_사랑해/</id><title>정경 - Beethoven : Ich Liebe Dich WoO.123 (베토벤 : 그대를 사랑해) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:18:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:18:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B2%BD/Beethoven___Ich_Liebe_Dich_WoO123_%EB%B2%A0%ED%86%A0%EB%B2%A4___%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%A5%BC_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4/" title="정경 - Beethoven : Ich Liebe Dich WoO.123 (베토벤 : 그대를 사랑해) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ich liebe dich so wie du mich <br>am Abend und am Morgen <br>Noch war kein Tag wo du und <br>ich nicht teilten unsre Sorgen <br>Auch waren sie <br>fur dich und mich geteilt <br>Leicht zu ertragen <br>Du trostetest im Kummer mich <br>ich weint' in deine Klagen <br>in deine Klagen <br>Drum Gottes Segen uber dir <br>du meines Lebens Freude <br>Gott schutze dich <br>erhalt' dich mir <br>schutz' und erhalt' uns beide <br>Gott schutze dich <br>erhalt' dich mir <br>schutz' und erhalt' uns beide <br>Erhalt' erhalt' uns beide <br>erhalt' uns beide <br>]]></content><category term="정경" label="정경"/><category term="Beethoven : Ich Liebe Dich WoO.123 (베토벤 : 그대를 사랑해)" label="Beethoven : Ich Liebe Dich WoO.123 (베토벤 : 그대를 사랑해)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/케이/난_말야/</id><title>케이 - 난 말야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:18:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:18:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4/%EB%82%9C_%EB%A7%90%EC%95%BC/" title="케이 - 난 말야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[길에 서서 <br>미소를 띄며 바라보는 <br>그 눈빛 좋아 <br>나도 따라 웃게 돼 <br>너를 보면 한없이 좋아 <br>저기에서 손을 흔들며 <br>날 반기는 따뜻한 너를 <br>내겐 큰 선물 같아 <br>내 인생의 특별한 너 <br>난 말야 니가 참 좋아 <br>잠들 때까지 생각이 나는걸 <br>하루가 온통 너로 가득해 <br>내 맘도 똑같은 걸 <br>내 안에 모두 너야 <br>어느 순간 갑자기 <br>들어온거야 <br>아침부터 생각나는 <br>너 눈만 뜨면 전화하게 돼 <br>온통 내 하루 속에 <br>너로 가득해 행복하게 <br>아침부터 나를 깨우는 <br>니 목소리 듣는 게 좋아 <br>나를 아껴주는 너 <br>선물 같은 너란 사람 <br>난 말야 니가 참 좋아 <br>잠들 때까지 생각이 나는걸 <br>하루가 온통 너로 가득해 <br>내 맘도 똑같은 걸 <br>내 안에 모두 너야 <br>어느 순간 갑자기 <br>들어온거야 <br>왜 이렇게 늦게 <br>우리 만나 <br>이런 행복 이제서야 <br>알게 된 것일까 <br>난 말야 니가 참 좋아 <br>잠들 때까지 생각이 나는걸 <br>하루가 온통 너로 가득해 <br>내 맘도 똑같은 걸 <br>내 안에 모두 너야 <br>어느 순간 갑자기 <br>들어온거야 <br>어느 순간 갑자기 <br>들어온거야 <br>]]></content><category term="케이" label="케이"/><category term="난 말야" label="난 말야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/모기/타투_TaTtoo/</id><title>모기 - 타투 (TaT)too - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:18:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:18:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AA%A8%EA%B8%B0/%ED%83%80%ED%88%AC_TaTtoo/" title="모기 - 타투 (TaT)too - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그땐 매일 함께 했던 <br>그 조그만 카페 <br>이젠 나 홀로 앉아 <br>두 눈 가득 널 담아 <br>요즘 노래 흘러 가고 <br>분주한 사람들 <br>컵에 비친 내 눈 속은 <br>그때로 돌아가 있어 <br>너와 눈을 맞추고 <br>니 얘기에 귀 기울이면 <br>다른 무엇도 보이지 않았어 <br>너를 만나 사랑을 하고 <br>너를 만나 이별을 해도 <br>내 눈 속에 새겨진 니 모습이 <br>누군가와 사랑을 하고 <br>누군가와 이별을 해도 <br>문신처럼 지워지지 않아 <br>너라는 타투 <br>그땐 매일 함께 걷던 <br>이 거리를 혼자 걸어 <br>너와 자주 간 옷집도 <br>그대로 인데 <br>문득 비친 거울 속엔 <br>너만 내 곁에 없어 <br>너와 옷을 맞추고 <br>니 손을 잡고 걸으면 <br>다른 무엇도 보이지 않았어 <br>너를 만나 사랑을 하고 <br>너를 만나 이별을 해도 <br>내 눈 속에 새겨진 니 모습이 <br>누군가와 사랑을 하고 <br>누군가와 이별을 해도 <br>문신처럼 지워지지 않아 <br>너라는 타투 <br>우 우 <br>내 눈 속에 새겨진 니 모습이 <br>우 우 <br>문신처럼 지워지지 않아 <br>그땐 매일 함께 했던 <br>이 카페에 앉아 <br>낡은 악보 한 장에 <br>널 이렇게 그려 <br>]]></content><category term="모기" label="모기"/><category term="타투 (TaT)too" label="타투 (TaT)too"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/K2_김성면/사랑한다는_그_말이_Inst/</id><title>K2_김성면 - 사랑한다는 그 말이 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:18:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:18:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/K2_%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%A9%B4/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%9C%EB%8B%A4%EB%8A%94_%EA%B7%B8_%EB%A7%90%EC%9D%B4_Inst/" title="K2_김성면 - 사랑한다는 그 말이 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대와 함께 거닐던 <br>거리에 서 있어요 <br>세월의 흔적 속에 아련해진 <br>추억을 따라 걸으며 <br>서툴기만 했던 우리 사랑이 <br>길 곳곳에 남아 <br>스치는 사람 마치 그대인 듯 <br>자꾸 멈추는데 <br>사랑한다는 그 말이 <br>왜 그리 힘들었는지 <br>지금은 혼잣말이 되어버린 <br>사랑한다는 그 말이 <br>이젠 <br>생각만해도 어느새 두 눈은 <br>그대를 흘리고 <br>채워지지 않을 네 빈자리에 <br>대신 고이는데 <br>사랑한다는 그 말이 <br>왜 그리 힘들었는지 <br>지금은 혼잣말이 되어버린 <br>사랑한다는 그 말이 <br>이제는 눈물이 되고 <br>다시 돌릴 수 없는데 <br>사랑한다는 그 말이 <br>왜 그리 힘들었는지 <br>이제는 습관처럼 되어버린 <br>사랑한다는 그 말이 <br>이젠 <br>]]></content><category term="K2 김성면" label="K2 김성면"/><category term="사랑한다는 그 말이 (Inst.)" label="사랑한다는 그 말이 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/K2_김성면/사랑한다는_그_말이/</id><title>K2_김성면 - 사랑한다는 그 말이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:18:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:18:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/K2_%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%EB%A9%B4/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%9C%EB%8B%A4%EB%8A%94_%EA%B7%B8_%EB%A7%90%EC%9D%B4/" title="K2_김성면 - 사랑한다는 그 말이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대와 함께 거닐던 <br>거리에 서 있어요 <br>세월의 흔적 속에 아련해진 <br>추억을 따라 걸으며 <br>서툴기만 했던 우리 사랑이 <br>길 곳곳에 남아 <br>스치는 사람 마치 그대인 듯 <br>자꾸 멈추는데 <br>사랑한다는 그 말이 <br>왜 그리 힘들었는지 <br>지금은 혼잣말이 되어버린 <br>사랑한다는 그 말이 <br>이젠 <br>생각만해도 어느새 두 눈은 <br>그대를 흘리고 <br>채워지지 않을 네 빈자리에 <br>대신 고이는데 <br>사랑한다는 그 말이 <br>왜 그리 힘들었는지 <br>지금은 혼잣말이 되어버린 <br>사랑한다는 그 말이 <br>이제는 눈물이 되고 <br>다시 돌릴 수 없는데 <br>사랑한다는 그 말이 <br>왜 그리 힘들었는지 <br>이제는 습관처럼 되어버린 <br>사랑한다는 그 말이 <br>이젠 <br>]]></content><category term="K2 김성면" label="K2 김성면"/><category term="사랑한다는 그 말이" label="사랑한다는 그 말이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유진/스물하나/</id><title>유진 - 스물하나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:18:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:18:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EC%A7%84/%EC%8A%A4%EB%AC%BC%ED%95%98%EB%82%98/" title="유진 - 스물하나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘도 어김없이 <br>찾아온 아침 <br>바쁘게 준비를 하고 <br>문을 나서던 그때 <br>고양이 한 마리가 <br>나에게 다가와 <br>가만히 무릎 위에 <br>앉히고 둘러본 동네 <br>하얗게 피어난 구름 하늘 <br>내 맘 속에 가득 담고 <br>겁 많고 여리던 그 아이는 <br>이제 스물하나 <br>늦은 저녁 지는 노을 아래 <br>동그랗게 비친 얼굴 <br>아직도 걱정이 많은 너는 <br>이제 스물하나 <br>지금 겨우 나 어른이 <br>돼가고 있는 것 같은데 <br>옳은 방향으로 <br>가고 있는 걸까 <br>하얗게 피어난 구름 하늘 <br>내 맘 속에 가득 담고 <br>겁 많고 여리고 <br>걱정이 넘치던 그 아이는 <br>지금 노래하네 <br>]]></content><category term="유진" label="유진"/><category term="스물하나" label="스물하나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Sign/</id><title>Porter_Nickerson - Sign - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:22:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:22:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Sign/" title="Porter_Nickerson - Sign - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All these habits, creatures they keep <br>We're all slaves to potions, slaves to sleep <br>When I wake up, I'm going to dance a jig <br>Uncork the poison and take a swig <br>If it's love you want, I'll give you some <br>But don't take it girl, then turn and run <br>Because the morning light against your face <br>Is the prettiest sign I've seen of grace <br>You're the prettiest sign I've seen of grace <br>Help me out, I'm falling <br>Pick me up, the wild wind's calling <br>There's still time to feel something, that's true <br>All these fables and all these facts <br>I try to run, but they pull me back <br>Though the lines across my face are real <br>I got a brand new heart going to crack the seal <br>Help me out, I'm falling <br>Pick me up, the wild wind's calling <br>There's still time to feel something, that's true <br>Honey I do, I do, I do believe in you <br>I do, I do believe <br>I do believe in you, I do I do, I do believe <br>Oh Whippoorwill, don't let go of me <br>I feel your song across the breeze <br>Few have seen, but I believe <br>You'll show yourself to me help me out, I'm falling <br>Pick me up, the wild wind's calling <br>There's still time to feel something, that's true <br>Honey I do, I do, I do believe in you <br>I do, I do believe I do believe in you, I do In you]]></content><category term="Porter Nickerson" label="Porter Nickerson"/><category term="Sign" label="Sign"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/If_You_Stay/</id><title>Porter_Nickerson - If You Stay - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:22:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:22:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/If_You_Stay/" title="Porter_Nickerson - If You Stay - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Summer had gone, she put leaves in the gutter <br>and an old car out on the front lawn <br>I watched you move in with your bike and your boxes <br>I dropped the tray when you answered your door <br>Such a long road all the way from Ohio <br>I caught the outline of your face in the window <br>I don't think my heart can beat any faster <br>There's no way I can't see you now <br>Watching the sun rise and fall <br>from your window <br>Baklava in a four poster bed <br>The moon keeping time with <br>your body and mine <br>I remember every word that you said <br>Why did you go to her <br>I don't know why <br>You pushed me away <br>Biggest mistake of my life <br>It took years for me to trust myself <br>When you left me here for someone else <br>It takes more then words to make this girl believe <br>Are you ok I can't hide that from you <br>Can't hide that from you <br>Does she still have a hold <br>No, we're through <br>I remember when I was the only one <br>It's been a long night, I've come a long way <br>I think it's all right if you still wanna stay <br>I think it's all right if you stay <br>Why did you take so long]]></content><category term="Porter Nickerson" label="Porter Nickerson"/><category term="If You Stay" label="If You Stay"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Earthquake/</id><title>Porter_Nickerson - Earthquake - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:22:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:22:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Earthquake/" title="Porter_Nickerson - Earthquake - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You don't want my whole heart <br>Just the easy part <br>You say let's keep it easy just for a while <br>You say it with a smile <br>And I'm ok for a while <br>Sooner or later the truth has got to come out <br>I should've seen through you <br>Should've been wide awake <br>Before you hit I should've felt the earthquake <br>Because you don't want my whole heart <br>Don't want the damaged part <br>You're no mechanic <br>You're not going to make no repairs <br>You want to drive it off the lot <br>You want the part that revs and runs hot <br>You want to lay in the tall grass, I guess that's ok baby <br>But hey <br>I Should have seen through you <br>Should've seen the faults and all the breaks <br>Before you hit I should've felt the earthquake <br>Let's burn baby burn baby all night long <br>Come on burn baby burn baby all night long <br>I want to burn rubber baby to the light of dawn <br>Because I Know you don't want my whole heart <br>I should have seen through you <br>I should have seen the faults and all of the breaks <br>I should've known better than that <br>Oh well, what can I say <br>You don't want my whole heart, just the easy part <br>You don't want my whole heart <br>Just the part that revs and runs hot <br>Everything'll be fine, don't want to hear about it <br>Ain't got time for that now, don't want to hear about it <br>I just want to feel good, don't want to care about it <br>You don't want my whole heart <br>I ain't got time for that now]]></content><category term="Porter Nickerson" label="Porter Nickerson"/><category term="Earthquake" label="Earthquake"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Loving_On_Her_Mind/</id><title>Porter_Nickerson - Loving On Her Mind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:22:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:22:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Loving_On_Her_Mind/" title="Porter_Nickerson - Loving On Her Mind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She says she loves you, her eyes are warm but tired Like she's been <br>walking on a wire and talking to the sky As far as I can see, you act like <br>you don't care Like some strip club millionaire, but a woman like her is rare <br>We both know she's not the cheating kind She's tired of this roller coaster ride <br>She's got loving on her mind <br>Loving on her mind Her eyes are walking all over this bar Loving on her mind <br>She's flirting on the dance floor <br>Sara left with the car You better show up, she's starting to unwind <br>She's got loving on her mind <br>I know you're hurting, you'll get another job but you'll never break free Sleeping 'til noon smoking weed <br>living in the land of make believe What are you afraid of]]></content><category term="Porter Nickerson" label="Porter Nickerson"/><category term="Loving On Her Mind" label="Loving On Her Mind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/In_Bloom/</id><title>Porter_Nickerson - In Bloom - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:22:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:22:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/In_Bloom/" title="Porter_Nickerson - In Bloom - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Like mud on God's feet, a heart leaves no trace <br>Heart knows no boundaries of time or space <br>A lost poet soldier alone in the field <br>My heart will keep on fighting <br>no gun and no shield <br>My heart won't be denied <br>No my heart won't be denied tonight <br>In the face of danger <br>in the wake of regret <br>Heart flows unabated <br>drinking this breath <br>Everything your body does <br>my heart wants to feel <br>My mind can't deny <br>what my heart knows is real <br>My heart won't be denied <br>No my heart won't be denied tonight <br>Heart will build a castle, heart will tear it down <br>Heart's a broken compass lying on the ground <br>All of the things I thought I knew <br>They only prove that I'm a fool <br>My heart is trying to see this through <br>But in my mind I haven't got a clue <br>It's all in season it's all in bloom <br>You walk into the room, there's a buzz in my ear <br>Up high in a frequency only dogs can hear <br>Everything your body does, my heart wants to feel <br>My mind can't deny what my heart knows is real <br>All of the things I thought I knew <br>They only prove that I'm a fool <br>Everything's different around you <br>My heart is trying to see this through <br>But in my mind I haven't got a clue <br>It's all in season it's all in bloom <br>It's all in bloom]]></content><category term="Porter Nickerson" label="Porter Nickerson"/><category term="In Bloom" label="In Bloom"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Wasting_Time/</id><title>Porter_Nickerson - Wasting Time - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:22:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:22:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Wasting_Time/" title="Porter_Nickerson - Wasting Time - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Reach for the window <br>Open the good in yourself <br>See diamonds around you <br>In everyone else <br>Sometimes you can hear it <br>Silence of wings on the wind <br>Withdraw your resistance <br>And let my love in <br>Sometimes we're all lazy and crazy and tired <br>But you're wasting time, Trying to find <br>A sweet summer mystic <br>To help you forget the past <br>You'll shed your old skin once again <br>But the healing won't last <br>Passion burns quickly from bonfire to ash <br>When you're wasting time Looking behind <br>Sometimes I wonder how far you can bend <br>Before you break <br>Look me in the eye darling you know <br>I'll be here as long as it takes <br>Wind in the wires <br>Sings as it sighs <br>Reminds us of lovers we knew <br>They never told you that you were a star <br>So stop wasting time <br>Learning your lines <br>So stop wasting time <br>Maybe it's crazy, I still want to try]]></content><category term="Porter Nickerson" label="Porter Nickerson"/><category term="Wasting Time" label="Wasting Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Echo_Of_Love/</id><title>Porter_Nickerson - Echo Of Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:22:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:22:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Echo_Of_Love/" title="Porter_Nickerson - Echo Of Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm skating by myself staring down through the clear <br>Laying down and waiting for the stars to appear <br>You seem to want to be everywhere but here <br>How could so little love hurt so much <br>I've been wounded angry at the slow speed of grace <br>I screamed in the mirror at my own reflected face <br>Tried to take credit for my role in this play <br>But our little run on Broadway is a bust <br>Oh I can't explain what became of us <br>14 dollar flowers in a vase by the door <br>Dry gone grey petals are scattered on the floor <br>We both walk by not seeing, not hearing anymore <br>Someone has to bend to pick them up <br>Maybe I should be the one to stand up and say <br>When the dream was broken <br>I left the pieces where they lay <br>But my voice has been stolen <br>And my hands feel like clay <br>When silence is all I can offer up <br>I can't explain what became <br>I can't explain what became of us <br>I want to reach across this room <br>but my hands are tied <br>I hear the echo of love in the back of my mind <br>I took a walk down today to our secret place <br>I thought I saw the ghost of love <br>I thought I saw your face <br>In the long willow branches as they bent in the breeze <br>Made my heart feel so full of rust <br>If this illusion ever lets me go <br>I'll forgive myself as the sun melts the snow <br>There is no absolution in the echo of love <br>Just freedom from shadows in the dusk <br>I can't explain what became of us]]></content><category term="Porter Nickerson" label="Porter Nickerson"/><category term="Echo Of Love" label="Echo Of Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Living_Proof/</id><title>Porter_Nickerson - Living Proof - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:22:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:22:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Living_Proof/" title="Porter_Nickerson - Living Proof - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[He came home from Korea, left his boots outside the door <br>A soldier changes clothes, but he can't wash off the war <br>If he had his demons, he kept them to himself <br>Farming 18 hour days to put food up on our shelves <br>So don't say it can't be done <br>Because I know that isn't true <br>My father didn't give up <br>and I am living proof <br>My brothers all played football <br>After their chores and homework <br>Mama kept the books at the grain exchange <br>and we all sang in church <br>I don't know how she did it <br>Cooked three meals and raised 6 kids <br>People think the world owes them something <br>My mama never did <br>So don't say it can't be done <br>Because I know that isn't true <br>My father didn't give up <br>and I am living proof <br>Sister, I'll leave a light on for you <br>Brother, don't let them bury your truth <br>The Northern Lights keep shining down even when <br>I can't see through <br>I know you'll never give up <br>And I'll never give up on you <br>We are living proof <br>Living proof that love sustains us <br>Living proof that love survives <br>That we'll find safe passage <br>Through the darkness in our lives <br>It takes more than me and you <br>These sweet fields of St Ansgar <br>Hold the seeds of my soul <br>I see my sister in the kitchen <br>As she pulls the window closed <br>My father smiles and waves <br>Parks the tractor for the night <br>Tomorrow they'll do it all again <br>Be up before first light <br>So don't say it can't be done <br>The sun is rising soon <br>You're not the only one <br>I'm right here with you <br>So don't say it can't be done <br>Because I know that isn't true <br>Those before us didn't give up <br>And we are living proof]]></content><category term="Porter Nickerson" label="Porter Nickerson"/><category term="Living Proof" label="Living Proof"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/I_Need_You/</id><title>Porter_Nickerson - I Need You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:22:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:22:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/I_Need_You/" title="Porter_Nickerson - I Need You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been dreaming and the dream never lets me down <br>The air feels heavy when I awake like the angel won't come around <br>Where should I go <br>With this heart that won't keep time on its own <br>This kick drum needs a bass line <br>I need you <br>There's a river that flows from everywhere <br>If I listen I can see it electric on the air <br>You see it all <br>To you it all makes sense trust is the only option <br>The one true covenant <br>I Need You <br>Need your smile to look forward to bridge the miles, to pull me through <br>When all is lost in the weeds you have all the light that I need]]></content><category term="Porter Nickerson" label="Porter Nickerson"/><category term="I Need You" label="I Need You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Plant_A_Garden/</id><title>Porter_Nickerson - Plant A Garden - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:22:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:22:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Plant_A_Garden/" title="Porter_Nickerson - Plant A Garden - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We all live in a big dome <br>Fuzzy little creatures set out to roam <br>We dance around like puppets who won't cut the string <br>Like cancer kills the host, we destroy everything <br>I wanna plant a garden in the sun <br>Wheels keep spinning and spinning around <br>But there's a better way I've found <br>I'm gonna take these seeds and plant them in the ground <br>And stop spinning and spinning around <br>You can modify, but love still wins <br>You can change the form, but Mother Nature steps in <br>After all the trees are gone and there are no birds in the sky <br>Your granddaughter's gonna take your hand and <br>Look you in the eye and say <br>I wanna plant a garden <br>When the water covers this land again <br>We'll climb aboard the garbage scow <br>The flotilla of trash we've thrown away <br>That'll be our new home now <br>Like Noah sailed for 40 days <br>We'll climb on two by two <br>There won't be any animals left <br>It'll just be me and you]]></content><category term="Porter Nickerson" label="Porter Nickerson"/><category term="Plant A Garden" label="Plant A Garden"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Old_Red_Barn/</id><title>Porter_Nickerson - Old Red Barn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:22:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:22:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Porter_Nickerson/Old_Red_Barn/" title="Porter_Nickerson - Old Red Barn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I smell the earth and the scent lingers <br>Feel the midday sun on my skin <br>Glass is sweating between your fingers <br>Come on baby, you're reeling me in <br>Paint's going to peel on the old red barn <br>Sirens will moan, sound the alarm <br>Your hand brushes up against my arm <br>Nothing in the world could do me harm <br>I see your face and all the tension goes slack <br>When you reach for the sun, it reaches right back <br>When you reach for the sun, it reaches right back <br>There's an invisible hand, at the helm <br>Leaning into the shade of this old Dutch elm <br>Taking a nap, to the sound of your heart <br>There's plenty of time darling, before it gets dark <br>Paint's going to peel <br>Pull down the shades before it gets too hot <br>Paint's going to peel on the old red barn <br>Sirens will moan, sound the alarm <br>your hand brushes up against my arm <br>nothing in the world could do me harm <br>I see your face and all the tension goes slack <br>When you reach for the sun it reaches right back <br>When you reach for the sun <br>Come on reach for the sun <br>I want to reach for the sun <br>It reaches right back]]></content><category term="Porter Nickerson" label="Porter Nickerson"/><category term="Old Red Barn" label="Old Red Barn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nature_Set/The_Engineer/</id><title>Nature_Set - The Engineer - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:23:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:23:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nature_Set/The_Engineer/" title="Nature_Set - The Engineer - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I sing the body electric <br>You cut the meat from the bone <br>I peeled back layers of static <br>And now I just can't be alone <br><br>I am the body electric <br>I am the meat and the bone <br>I am this fear fantastic <br>You will never be alone <br><br>You bring me scraps from the table <br>I was once an engineer <br>You regard me with a steady gaze <br>I don't know why I come here <br><br>You take the scraps so grateful <br>I am now the engineer <br>Avert your eyes while I sleep so fitful <br>Feel my hand, feel your fear <br><br>I wring my hands with the feeling <br>You are sleeping like a dog <br>I keep watch while you are resting <br><br>Eyes, eye fringes, iris of the eye, eye brows <br>And the waking or sleeping of the lids <br>Mouth, tongue, lips, teeth, roof of the mouth jaws <br><br>Jaw hinges <br>Eye fringes <br>Jaw hinges <br><br>I sing the body electric <br>You cut the meat from the bone <br>I peeled back layers of static <br>And now I just can't be alone <br><br>I am the body electric <br>I am the meat and the bone <br>I am this fear fantastic <br>You will never be alone <br><br>Eyes, eye fringes, iris of the eye, eye brows <br>And the waking or sleeping of the lids <br>Mouth, tongue, lips, teeth, roof of the mouth jaws]]></content><category term="Nature Set" label="Nature Set"/><category term="The Engineer" label="The Engineer"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nature_Set/At_Least_Not_Today/</id><title>Nature_Set - At Least Not Today - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:23:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:23:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nature_Set/At_Least_Not_Today/" title="Nature_Set - At Least Not Today - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We're serious, you won't make us laugh <br>You're jealous, but that phase will pass <br>Don't smoke dona't drink don't steal don't want to <br> At least not today <br><br>We're serious, well trying to be <br>You're friends with us That's most unlikely <br>Don't smile dona't laugh don't cry don't want to <br> At least not today <br><br>Spend time with us, we'll make it quick <br>You'll find out just what makes us tick <br>Don't think that we won't make an impact <br>When we get raw <br><br>Come see us and walk in our shoes <br>We're the future of yesterday's news <br>Someone to try us, occupy us <br>Is what we're looking for <br><br>We took a wrong turn a few pages back <br>Now there's us and there's you, an unfortunate fact <br>So just keep on walking, don't show us the light <br>Wea're happy in here not getting it quite right <br><br>We took a wrong turn a few pages back <br>Now there's us and there's you and still no friendship pact <br>So just keep on walking don't show us the light <br>We're happy in here not getting it quite right]]></content><category term="Nature Set" label="Nature Set"/><category term="At Least Not Today" label="At Least Not Today"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nature_Set/You_Or_Nobody/</id><title>Nature_Set - You Or Nobody - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:23:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:23:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nature_Set/You_Or_Nobody/" title="Nature_Set - You Or Nobody - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I just saw you walking <br>I fell for you in record time <br>You were only talking <br>But I was picking up the sign <br>I saw the line <br><br>I know that you've been hurting <br>Is it fair to take it out on me <br>I'm the one who has been helping <br>But things have turned out differently <br>We'll make it you'll see <br><br>I'm not sure you realise <br>I'm not playing round this time <br>This is really it for me <br>It's either you or nobody <br>Nobody <br><br>Another Friday evening <br>And soon the weekend will be gone <br>We did a lot of sleeping <br>But not a whole lot else was done <br>Now Monday's begun <br><br>I'm not sure you realise <br>I'm not playing round this time <br>This is really it for me <br>It's either you or nobody <br><br>Tell me what is on your mind <br>I couldn't stand it if you lied <br>I wanna make the most of this <br>I'm just so lucky to have found your kiss <br>I found your kiss]]></content><category term="Nature Set" label="Nature Set"/><category term="You Or Nobody" label="You Or Nobody"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nature_Set/Enough_Is_Enough/</id><title>Nature_Set - Enough Is Enough - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:23:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:23:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nature_Set/Enough_Is_Enough/" title="Nature_Set - Enough Is Enough - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We are a joke, we are a joke <br>And this is our play, this is our play <br>Presented to you, presented to you <br>My bed is my stage <br>We pick out the soundtrack, out the soundtrack <br>We fix you a drink, fix you a drink <br>We fetch you a high back chair <br>We dress up in pink <br><br>We just don't know when enough is enough <br>We just don't know when enough is enough <br><br>We are a talk, we are a talk <br>And we got something to say, something to say <br>Lie after lie, Lie after lie <br>Page after page <br>And we keep on going <br>We've been here all along <br>Your house in on fire, your children are gone <br><br>We just don't know when enough is enough <br>We just don't know when enough is enough <br><br>We line up pairs of shoes <br>So we can play shop <br>The windows are open <br>We're in the stocks <br>We paint on our whiskers <br>and wind back my watch <br>I kick off my shoes yeah, I switch the light off <br>We wanna feel real, we wanna free wheel <br>We just don't know when enough is enough <br>We wanna go down, we wanna go drown <br>We just wanna get you off <br>Enough is enough, enough is enough <br>Enough is enough, enough is enough <br>Enough is enough, enough is enough <br>Enough is enough, enough is enough <br>Enough is enough, enough is enough]]></content><category term="Nature Set" label="Nature Set"/><category term="Enough Is Enough" label="Enough Is Enough"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jebroer/Deal_Met_De_Rave_Feat_Rich_Cutillo/</id><title>Jebroer - Deal Met De Rave (Feat. Rich Cutillo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:23:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:23:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jebroer/Deal_Met_De_Rave_Feat_Rich_Cutillo/" title="Jebroer - Deal Met De Rave (Feat. Rich Cutillo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[De zon is onder <br>Deze avond is van mij <br>De hele week ging me als een flits voorbij <br>Dus meisje pak je koffers in en stap maar achterin <br>Want wij gaan hoger dan de wolken <br>En dieper dan de zee <br>Verder dan de horizon met mensen om ons heen <br>En ik laat je nooit alleen <br>Je bent m'n tijger in de rain <br>Ik heb een deal met, met de rave <br>Ik laat je nooit alleen <br>Ik heb een deal met, met de rave <br>En als ik opa ben zeg ik dat ik heb geleefd <br>Met de rave <br>Ik laat je nooit alleen <br>Ik heb een deal met, met de rave <br>En als ik opa ben zeg ik dat ik heb geleefd <br><br>Ik ben op een level, als een auto moeten tanken <br>Mijn gedachte op die centen, heb genoeg van al die sletten <br>Vechten in de stad, politie ziet me liever vast <br>Veel boetes op de mat ben aan het spinnen in de club <br>Drugs maken moe, word soms wakker op de stoep <br>Gooi een L in de lucht, 't is m'n city wat ik roep <br>Young boy in de streets, trek een wheelie op m'n fiets <br>Motherfuck the police <br>Man, ik hou van al die haat <br>Want jij kan zien ho 't met me gaat <br>Wil me geld, ik ben verslaafd <br>Heb het nooit genoeg gemaakt <br>Ik hou van Polluk als me bro <br>Weet nog zo waar het rolt <br>Maar nu wordt er mee gegooid <br>Pak m'n diamond en ik maak je dood <br>Lach me dood en voor me lui sta bij de Duivel in het krijt <br>Ben aan het oogsten, heb gezaaid <br>Luister bitch, je wordt genaaid <br>Meer money op m'n mind <br>Niks, alles op z'n tijd <br>Ik heb geen tijd, tijd dus squap en ik maak alles af <br><br>De zon is onder <br>Deze avond is van mij <br>De hele week ging me als een flits voorbij <br>Dus meisje pak je koffers in en stap maar achterin <br>Want wij gaan hoger dan de wolken <br>En dieper dan de zee <br>Verder dan de horizon met mensen om ons heen <br>En ik laat je nooit alleen <br>Je bent m'n tijger in de rain <br>Ik heb een deal met, met de rave <br>Ik laat je nooit alleen <br>Ik heb een deal met, met de rave <br>En als ik opa ben zeg ik dat ik heb geleefd <br>Met de rave <br>Ik laat je nooit alleen <br>Ik heb een deal met, met de rave <br>En als ik opa ben zeg ik dat ik heb geleefd <br><br>Zuip me vaak zat klem <br>Ben een fan van al m'n fans <br>En ik ben gewoon mens van een <br>Vergeet nooit waar het begon <br>Slimme jongen was dom <br>Tegenwoordig kom ik rond en zijn de rollen andersom <br>Kan niet stunten op mij <br>Genoeg armoed gezaaid <br>Zeg het verleden Bye, bye <br>Als ik met m'n geld zwaai <br>En ik geef echt geen fock <br>Met mezelf, ben in love <br>Al die liefde is tof <br>Tijd is geld, kijk me klok <br>Geen seconde verspild <br>Ben pas chill met een mill <br>Geef me moeder een deel <br>Jullie weten de deel <br>Vier shows in de week <br>'t is een droom wat ik leef <br>Ik ben een groot probleem <br>Voor die boys in de game <br>Sta langer in brand <br>Vuur en vlam <br>Heb de wereld in m'n hand <br>Ik ben een diamant <br>Mijn liefde is puur <br>In m'n maag is het zuur <br>Ik ben daar in de buurt tot het laatste uur <br><br>Want wij gaan hoger dan de wolken <br>En dieper dan de zee <br>Verder dan de horizon met mensen om ons heen <br>En ik laat je nooit alleen <br>Je bent m'n tijger in de rain <br>Ik heb een deal met, met de rave <br>Ik laat je nooit alleen <br>Ik heb een deal met, met de rave <br>En als ik opa ben zeg ik dat ik heb geleefd <br>Met de rave <br>Ik laat je nooit alleen <br>Ik heb een deal met, met de rave <br>En als ik opa ben zeg ik dat ik heb geleefd]]></content><category term="Jebroer" label="Jebroer"/><category term="Deal Met De Rave (Feat. Rich Cutillo)" label="Deal Met De Rave (Feat. Rich Cutillo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stepherd/Killin_It/</id><title>Stepherd - Killin It - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:23:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:23:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stepherd/Killin_It/" title="Stepherd - Killin It - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Drie uur bij de bushalte <br>Vier uur, check je Twitter op je phone <br>Schat je moet je niet druk maken <br>Binnenkort zijn we all alone <br>Ik heb foto's, foto's in m'n kamer <br>Foto's voor later van jou <br>Ik heb foto's, foto's in m'n kamer <br>Foto's voor later van jou <br><br>Want ze killed me softly <br>Killed me softly Killed me softly <br>Killed me softly <br>Killin' it Killin' it Killin' it Killin' it <br>Killin' softly <br>Want ze killed me softly <br>Killed me softly Killed me softly <br>Killed me softly <br>Killin' it Killin' it Killin' it Killin' it <br>Killin' softly <br><br>Meisje ik vind je dope <br>Dit is niet gewoon <br>Ho ik achter je loop <br>Schat je bent zo dope <br>Geef me je autograph, op m'n rug, in m'n nek <br>Schatje ik heb geen pen <br>Maar ik vind je dede <br>Meisje vindt je het erg <br>Als ik je foto heb <br>Staat daar boven m'n bed <br>Ik haal 'm voor niemand weg <br>Schrijf je naam in 't zand <br>En maak er een foto van <br><br>Want ze killed me softly <br>Killed me softly Killed me softly <br>Killed me softly <br>Killin' it Killin' it Killin' it Killin' it <br>Killin' softly <br><br>Want ze killed me softly <br>Killed me softly Killed me softly <br>Killed me softly <br>Killin' it Killin' it Killin' it Killin' it <br>Killin' softly <br><br>Ik ben in struiken of in een steegje <br>Van jou word ik verlegen <br>De boy die je kent, vind ik vervelend <br>Binnenkort heb ik met hem afgerekend <br>Een foto van je <br>Ik wil hem halen, als een tattoo op m'n schouder <br>Trouwen en van je houden <br>Yeah, lotta mercy <br>Ik ken je roepnaam en m'n achternaam <br>'t Zal je goed staan <br>Roep maar en ik ben daar <br>Drie keer, als de Candyman <br>Ik ben de man die je dansend chant <br>In de hoop dat ik rampetamp <br>Ik wil alleen jou <br>En ga aan de wand <br>Jij zet mij in vuur en vlam <br><br>Drie uur bij de bushalte <br>Vier uur, check je Twitter op je phone <br>Schat je moet je niet druk maken <br>Binnenkort zijn we all alone <br>Ik heb foto's, foto's in m'n kamer <br>Foto's voor later van jou <br>Ik heb foto's, foto's in m'n kamer <br>Foto's voor later van jou <br><br>Want ze killed me softly <br>Killed me softly Killed me softly <br>Killed me softly <br>Killin' it Killin' it Killin' it Killin' it <br>Killin' softly <br>Want ze killed me softly <br>Killed me softly Killed me softly <br>Killed me softly <br>Killin' it Killin' it Killin' it Killin' it <br>Killin' softly]]></content><category term="Stepherd" label="Stepherd"/><category term="Killin It" label="Killin It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Charlie_Boisseau/Jen_Ai_Des_Tas/</id><title>Charlie_Boisseau - J`en Ai Des Tas - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:24:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:24:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Charlie_Boisseau/Jen_Ai_Des_Tas/" title="Charlie_Boisseau - J`en Ai Des Tas - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[J'en ai des tas <br>Des tas de petites journees comme ca <br>Ou je te dessine sur des vitrines <br>Des murs tout autour de moi <br>J'en ai des tas <br>Des tas de petits mots doux comme ceux <br>Que j'avais bien pris le soin de couvrir <br>Pour que tu ne te doutes pas <br>Que dans le tas de rien que je deteste <br>Y'a toujours des tonnes et des tonnes de toi <br>Toi qui t'en vas, moi qui reste <br>ca ne te fait ni chaud ni froid <br><br>J'en ai des tas <br>Des tas de regards desabuses <br>Qui trainent encore quand je me rappelle <br>Que t'as pas voulu essayer <br>J'en ai des tas <br>Des tas de petits reveils brises <br>Ou sans comprendre je me laisse prendre <br>A l'idee que tu dormes a cote <br><br>Car dans le tas de rien que je deteste <br>Y'a toujours des tonnes et des tonnes de toi <br>Toi qui t'en vas, moi qui reste <br>ca ne te fait ni chaud ni froid <br><br>J'en ai des tas <br><br>Des tas de saisons que j'ai loupe <br>En cherchant toujours ton printemps <br>Pourtant perdu a tout jamais <br>J'en ai des tas <br>Des tas d'amours qui auraient pu vivre <br>Et a qui j'ai ferme la porte <br>Apres mettre retrouve ivre <br><br>Car dans le tas de rien que je deteste <br>Y'a toujours des tonnes et des tonnes de toi <br>Toi qui t'en vas et moi qui reste <br>ca ne te fait ni chaud ni froid <br><br>J'en ai des tas <br>Des tonnes de jeux qui ne se jouent <br>Qu'avec toi, qu'avec <br>J'en ai des tonnes, des tonnes de jeux <br>Meme qui volent en eclats <br><br>Car dans le tas de rien que je deteste <br>Y'a toujours des tonnes et des tonnes de toi <br>Toi qui t'en vas et moi qui reste <br>ca ne te fait ni chaud ni froid <br><br>Car dans le tas de rien que je deteste <br>Y'a toujours des tonnes et des tonnes de toi <br>Le tas d'amour que je t'adresse <br>ca ne te fait ni chaud ni froid]]></content><category term="Charlie Boisseau" label="Charlie Boisseau"/><category term="J`en Ai Des Tas" label="J`en Ai Des Tas"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/Nandemonaiya_movie_ver/</id><title>Radwimps - Nandemonaiya (movie ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:25:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:25:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/Nandemonaiya_movie_ver/" title="Radwimps - Nandemonaiya (movie ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[二人の間 通り過ぎた風は <br>후타리노아이다 토오리스기타 카제와 <br><br>どこから寂しさを運んできたの <br>도코카라 사비시사오 하콘데키타노 <br>？ <br>泣いたりしたそのあとの空は <br>나이타리시타 소노아토노 소라와 <br><br>やけに透き通っていたりしたんだ <br>야케니 스키톳테이타리시탄다 <br>？ <br>いつもは尖ってた父の言葉が <br>이츠모와 토갓테타 치치노 코토바가 <br>？ <br>今日は暖かく感じました <br>쿄-와 아타타카쿠 칸지마시타 <br>？ <br>優しさも笑顔も夢の語り方も <br>야사시사모 에가오모 유메노카타리카타모 <br><br>知らなくて全部 君を？似たよ <br>시라나쿠테 젠부 키미오 마네타요 <br>？ <br>もう少しだけでいいあと少しだけでいい <br>모- 스코시다케데이이 아토스코시다케데이이 <br>？ <br>もう少しだけでいいから <br>모- 스코시다케데이이카라 <br>？ <br>もう少しだけでいいあと少しだけでいい <br>모- 스코시다케데이이 아토스코시다케데이이 <br><br>もう少しだけ くっついていようか <br>모- 스코시다케 쿳츠이테이요-카 <br>？ <br>僕らタイムフライヤ？時を？け上がるクライマ？ <br>보쿠라 타이무후라이야- 토키오 카케아가루 쿠라이마- <br>？ <br>時のかくれんぼ はぐれっこはもういやなんだ <br>토키노카쿠렌보 하구렛코와 모- 이야난다 <br>？ <br>嬉しくて泣くのは 悲しくて笑うのは <br>우레시쿠테나쿠노와 카나시쿠테와라우노와 <br>？ <br>君の心が 君を追い越したんだよ <br>키미노 코코로가 키미오 오이코시탄다요 <br>？ <br>星にまで願って 手にいれたオモチャも <br>호시니마데 네갓테 테니이레타 오모챠모 <br>？ <br>部屋の隅っこに今 ？がってる <br>헤야노스밋코니 이마 코로갓테루 <br>？ <br>？えたい夢も 今日で100個できたよ <br>카나에타이유메모 쿄-데 햣코데키타요 <br>？ <br>たった一つといつか 交換こしよう <br>탓타 히토츠토 이츠카 코-칸 코시요- <br>？ <br>いつもは？らないあの子に今日は <br>이츠모와 샤베라나이 아노코니 쿄-와 <br>？ <br>放課後「また明日」と？をかけた <br>호-카고 마타아시타토 코에오카케타 <br>？ <br>慣れないこともたまにならいいね <br>나레나이코토모 타마니나라이이네 <br>？ <br>特にあなたが 隣にいたら <br>토쿠니 아나타가 토나리니이타라 <br><br>もう少しだけでいいあと少しだけでいい <br>모- 스코시다케데이이 아토스코시다케데이이 <br>？ <br>もう少しだけでいいから <br>모- 스코시다케데이이카라 <br>？ <br>もう少しだけでいいあと少しだけでいい <br>모- 스코시다케데이이 아토스코시다케데이이 <br><br>もう少しだけ くっついていようよ <br>모- 스코시다케 쿳츠이테이요-요 <br>？ <br>僕らタイムフライヤ？君を知っていたんだ <br>보쿠라 타이무후라이야- 키미오 싯테이탄다 <br><br>僕が 僕の名前を？えるよりずっと前に <br>보쿠가 보쿠노나마에오 오보에루요리 즛토마에니 <br>？ <br>君のいない 世界にも何かの意味はきっとあって <br>키미노이나이 세카이니모 나니카노 이미와 킷토앗테 <br>？ <br>でも君のいない世界など <br>데모 키미노이나이 세카이나도 <br><br>夏休みのない八月のよう <br>나츠야스미노나이 하치가츠노요- <br><br>？君のいない 世界など笑うことない サンタのよう <br>키미노이나이 세카이나도 와라우코토나이 산타노요- <br>？ <br>君のいない 世界など <br>키미노이나이 세카이나도 <br>？ <br>僕らタイムフライヤ？時を？け上がるクライマ？ <br>보쿠라 타이무후라이야- 토키오 카케아가루 쿠라이마- <br>？ <br>時のかくれんぼ はぐれっこはもういやなんだ <br>토키노카쿠렌보 하구렛코와 모- 이야난다 <br><br>なんでもないや やっぱりなんでもないや <br>난데모나이야 얏파리 난데모나이야 <br><br>今から行くよ <br>이마카라 이쿠요 <br>？ <br>僕らタイムフライヤ？時を？け上がるクライマ？ <br>보쿠라 타이무후라이야- 토키오 카케아가루 쿠라이마- <br>？ <br>時のかくれんぼ はぐれっこはもういいよ <br>토키노카쿠렌보 하구렛코와 모- 이이요 <br><br>君は派手なクライヤ？ <br>키미와 하데나 쿠라이야- <br>？ <br>その？ 止めてみたいな <br>소노나미다 토메테 미타이나 <br>？ <br>だけど君は拒んだ <br>다케도 키미와 코반다 <br>？ <br>零れるままの？を見てわかった <br>코보레루마마노 나미다오미테 와캇타 <br>？ <br>嬉しくて泣くのは悲しくて笑うのは <br>우레시쿠테 나쿠노와 카나시쿠테 와라우노와 <br>？ <br>僕の心が 僕を追い越したんだよ <br>보쿠노 코코로가 보쿠오 오이코시탄다요]]></content><category term="Radwimps" label="Radwimps"/><category term="Nandemonaiya (movie ver.)" label="Nandemonaiya (movie ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/Sparkle_movie_ver/</id><title>Radwimps - Sparkle (movie ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:25:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:25:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/Sparkle_movie_ver/" title="Radwimps - Sparkle (movie ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마다 코노 세카이와 <br>보쿠오 카이나라 시테이타이 미타이다 <br>노조미 도리다로 <br>우츠쿠시쿠 모카우요 <br>타카이노 스나도케이 <br>나가메나라가 키스오시요요 <br>사요나라카라 이치반 토오이 <br>바쇼데 마치아와세오 <br>지쇼니 아루 코토바데 <br>데키아갓타 세카이오 니쿤다 <br>만게쿄-노 나카데 <br>하츠가츠노 아루 아사 <br>키미와 보쿠노 마에데 <br>하니칸데와 스마시테 미세타 <br>코노 세카이노 쿄카쇼노 <br>요나 에가오데 <br>츠이니 토키와 키타 <br>키노 마데와 죠쇼노 죠쇼데 <br>토바시 요미데 이이카라 <br>콧카라가 보쿠다요 <br>케-켄토 치시키토 <br>카비노 하에카캇타 유-키오 못테 <br>이마다 카츠데 나이 스피-도데 <br>키미노 모토에 다이부오 <br>마도로미노 나카데 나마누루이 코-라니 <br>코코데 나이 돗카오 유메미타요 <br>쿄-시츠노 마도니 소토니 <br>덴샤니 유라레 하코바레루 아사니 <br>아이시 카타사에모 <br>키미노 니오이가 시타 <br>아루키 카타사에모 <br>소노 와라이 코에가 시타 <br>이츠카 키에테 나쿠나루 <br>키미노 스베테오 <br>코노 메니 야키츠케테오쿠 코토와 <br>모- 켄리난카쟈 나이 <br>키무다토 오모운다 <br>운메-다토카 미라이톳카 테 코토바가 <br>도레다케 테오 노바소-토 <br>토도카 나이 <br>바쇼데 보쿠라 코이우 스루 <br>토케이노 하리모 후타리오 <br>요코메니 미나가라 스스무 <br>손나 세카이오 후타리데 <br>잇쇼 이야, 난쇼 데모 <br>이키누이테 이코-]]></content><category term="Radwimps" label="Radwimps"/><category term="Sparkle (movie ver.)" label="Sparkle (movie ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/Zenzenzense_movie_ver/</id><title>Radwimps - Zenzenzense (movie ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:25:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:25:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/Zenzenzense_movie_ver/" title="Radwimps - Zenzenzense (movie ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[얏토 메오 사마시타카이 <br>소레나노니 나제 메모 <br>아와세야 시나인다이 <br>오소이요 토 오코루 키미 <br>코레데모 야레루다케 <br>토바시테 키탄다요 <br>코코로가 카라다오 <br>오이코시테 키탄다요 <br>키미노 카미야 히토미다케데 <br>무네가 이타이요 <br>오나지 토키오 스이콘데 <br>하나시타쿠 나이요 <br>하루카 무카시카라 시루 소노 코에니 <br>우마레테 하지메테 <br>나니오 이에바 이이 <br>키미노 젠젠젠세카라 <br>보쿠와 키미오 사가시 하지메타요 <br>소노 부킷쵸나 와라이카타오 <br>메가케테 얏테 키탄다요 <br>키미가 젠젠젠부 나쿠낫테 <br>치리지리니 낫탓테 <br>모오 마요와나이 마타 이치카라 <br>사가시 하지메루사 <br>무시로 제로카라 마타 우츄오 <br>하지메테 미요우카 <br>돗카라 하나스카나 <br>키미가 네뭇테이타 아이다노 스토리 <br>난오쿠 난코넨 분노 <br>모노가타리오 카타리니 키탄다요 <br>케도 이자 소노 스가타 <br>코노 메니 우츠스토 <br>키미모 시라누 키미토 <br>쟈레테 타와무레 타이요 <br>키미노 키에누 이타미마데 <br>아이시테미타이요 <br>긴카 난코분카노 하테니 데아에타 <br>소노 테오 코와사즈 도오 니깃타 나라이이 <br>키미노 젠젠젠세카라 <br>보쿠와 키미오 사가시 하지메타요 <br>소노 사와가시이 코에토 나미다오 <br>메가케 얏테키탄다요 <br>손나 카쿠메이 젠야노 보쿠라오 <br>다레가 토메루토 유운다로오 <br>모오 마요와나이 키미노 <br>하토니 하타오 타테루요 <br>키미가 보쿠카라 아키라메 <br>카타오 우바이톳타노 <br>젠젠젠세카라 보쿠와 키미오 <br>사가시 하지메타요 <br>소노 부킷쵸나 와라이카타오 메가케테 <br>얏테 키탄다요 <br>키미가 젠젠젠부 나쿠낫테 <br>치리지리니 낫탓테 <br>모오 마요와나이 마타 이치카라 <br>사가시 하지메루사 <br>난코넨데모 코노 우타오 <br>쿠치즈사미나가라]]></content><category term="Radwimps" label="Radwimps"/><category term="Zenzenzense (movie ver.)" label="Zenzenzense (movie ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/Nandemonaiya_English_Movie_ver/</id><title>Radwimps - Nandemonaiya (English Movie ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:25:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:25:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/Nandemonaiya_English_Movie_ver/" title="Radwimps - Nandemonaiya (English Movie ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The sorrowful gust of <br>wind that blew <br>right between you and me <br>Where did it find the loneliness <br>it carried on the breeze <br>Looking up at the sky <br>after shedding a stream of tears <br>I could see for miles of blue <br>it's never been so clear <br>Speeches that my father <br>gave me would <br>always make me despair <br>Somehow <br>I feel a warmth and <br>comfort today <br>Your ever kind heart <br>the way you smile <br>and even how you <br>find your dreams <br>I knew nothing <br>so honestly <br>I've always copied you <br>Now just a little more <br>Only just a little more <br>Let's stay here a little <br>longer now <br>Now just a little more <br>Only just a little more <br>Let's stick together <br>just a little bit longer <br>Oh yes we are time flyers <br>Scaling the walls of time climber <br>Tired of playing hide and <br>seek with time and <br>always coming just short <br>Crying even <br>when you're happy <br>Smiling even <br>when you're feeling lonely <br>It's because the part of you <br>Has made it <br>here before the rest has <br>I used to wish upon the stars <br>the toys that I once adored <br>Forgotten now <br>are rolling 'round <br>the corners of the floor <br>Finally <br>my dreams have counted <br>up to hundred today <br>Someday <br>I'll trade them all <br>for just the very one <br>Girl that I have seen in school <br>that never have told hello <br>After class today <br>I waved and said <br>See you tomorrow <br>It's not really that bad <br>trying something <br>new every once in a while <br>Especially if I can do it <br>with you by my side <br>Now just a little more <br>Only just a little more <br>Let's stay here a little <br>longer now <br>Just a little more <br>Only just a little more <br>Let's stick together <br>just a little bit longer <br>Oh yes we are time flyers <br>so and I <br>I knew who you were <br>way before <br>Way before I even knew <br>my own name <br>There's no clue <br>but I'm sure I swear <br>Even if you're not around <br>in this wide world <br>Of course it surely <br>would have some <br>kind of meaning <br>But if when you're not around <br>in this crazy world <br>Would be like the month of <br>August without summer break <br>And if you're not around <br>in this great world <br>Would be like Santa Claus <br>without any glee <br>If you're not around <br>in this wide world <br>Oh yes we are time flyers <br>Scaling the walls of time climber <br>Tired of playing hide and <br>seek with time and <br>always coming just short <br>No never mind that <br>No never mind what I said now <br>Cause I'm on my way to you <br>Oh we are time flyers <br>Dashing up the steps of time now <br>No more playing hide and seek <br>with you and time <br>And always coming just short <br>You're quite a showy crier <br>Want to stop your tears <br>see your eyes drier <br>But when I went to wipe <br>your tears dry <br>You refused but I <br>saw them pouring <br>down your face I knew why <br>Crying even when I'm happy <br>Smiling even <br>when I'm feeling lonely <br>It's because the heart of mine <br>Has made it <br>here before my body <br>]]></content><category term="Radwimps" label="Radwimps"/><category term="Nandemonaiya (English Movie ver.)" label="Nandemonaiya (English Movie ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/Sparkle_English_ver/</id><title>Radwimps - Sparkle (English ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:25:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:25:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/Sparkle_English_ver/" title="Radwimps - Sparkle (English ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Caught in a never-ending game <br>Seems like the world's still <br>trying to tame me <br>If that's the way I will obey <br>Beautifully struggle everyday <br>Should we have a little kiss <br>while seeing both of our <br>hourglasses <br>Let’s make a plan to meet somewhere <br>that is most far from goodbye <br>Finally the time has come <br>Everything up ‘til yesterday <br>was a prologue <br>Skimming through the days of old <br>It’s my turn to bear the load <br>My experience and my skill <br>And all the courage I had <br>let start to mildew <br>At an unprecedented speed <br>I will dive right into you <br>And when I dozed off into <br>a lukewarm can of soda <br>I dreamed of a world <br>so far from here <br>that's not on the map <br>Searching outside <br>of the classroom window <br>or in summer morning <br>that's brought <br>from the commuting train <br>Words like tomorrow <br>or future or fate <br>no matter how far <br>they extend their hands <br>We breathe we dream <br>we raise our love <br>in a timeless land <br>that is far out of reach <br>Even the second <br>hour hands of the clock <br>they look at us sideways <br>as they tick and tock <br>How I hope to have <br>forever to spend <br>This life no <br>all future lives <br>right here in this world with you <br>Let's put away them far ahead <br>How do you do's and all the <br>Nice to meet you's <br>and breathe over a 1000-year <br>cycle in a single day <br>How I hated lifeless world <br>that's made up entirely of <br>dictionary words that <br>I saw through my kaleidoscope <br>on a monotonous August morn <br>When you appeared in front of me <br>you acted shy but I didn't <br>miss your grinning face like <br>If it's the textbook of this world <br>of how to make your smile on your face <br>I've been looking for incredible’s <br>the meaning of unbelievable <br>I even hope for tragedies <br>if it goes with the thrill <br>But then you were standing <br>in a front of my door <br>with every piece in your hand <br>that I could ask for <br>Words like tomorrow <br>or future or fate <br>no matter how far <br>they extend their hands <br>Let's breathe and dream <br>we play together <br>in this place <br>What do you say <br>Even the way that you loved <br>I swear I could smell <br>the scent of yours <br>And in the way that you walked <br>I could hear that <br>bright laughter of yours <br>Since one day you will disappear <br>I’ll keep every part of you <br>Make sure that it's burned <br>into the back of my eyes <br>It’s not a right that I’m due <br>my duty that is must have been kept <br>Words like tomorrow <br>or future or fate <br>no matter how far <br>they extend their hands <br>We breathe we dream <br>we raise our love <br>in a timeless land <br>that is far out of reach <br>Even the second <br>hour hands of the clock <br>they look at us sideways <br>as they tick and tock <br>How I hope to have <br>forever to spend <br>This life no <br>all future lives <br>right here in this world with you <br>]]></content><category term="Radwimps" label="Radwimps"/><category term="Sparkle (English ver.)" label="Sparkle (English ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/Zenzenzense_English_ver/</id><title>Radwimps - Zenzenzense (English ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:26:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:26:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/Zenzenzense_English_ver/" title="Radwimps - Zenzenzense (English ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[At last <br>hello you’ve opened your eyes <br>But why won't you even look me <br>in the eyes <br>what's wrong with you <br>You angrily tell me that I’m late <br>Well I'm sorry <br>but I did my best and running <br>at my fastest pace <br>My heart overtook my body <br>as it flew to find you <br>in this place <br>Seeing your hair flowing <br>and your bright eyes glowing <br>aches my very core <br>Wish I could breathe <br>in the same dimension <br>I don’t want to let it go <br>Now that I am finally faced <br>with the voice <br>I’ve known for so long <br>I don’t know <br>what the words should be <br>the very first I say to you <br>Back in the Zenzenzense <br>‘til this day been lookin <br>everywhere for you <br>I followed the sound <br>of your innocent laughter <br>and it guided me <br>in the right way <br>Even if every piece <br>of you disappeared <br>and if it scattered everywhere <br>No I wouldn’t waver <br>I would start back <br>at one look <br>for you all over again <br>Or maybe instead <br>I’ll take the whole universe <br>right back to zero again <br>Where should I start <br>How should I explain <br>Wanna tell you everything <br>that happened <br>while you were <br>in a long long dream <br>I flew through dozens of skies <br>to tell you adventures <br>I've been through hundreds <br>of millions of light years’ worth <br>But now I'm here <br>finally seeing you reflected <br>in my eyes <br>I just want to know you <br>play around and show you <br>who it is that you can be <br>I just want to love you <br>every fragment of you right down <br>to the pain you feel <br>Now that we have finally met <br>at many galaxies’ end <br>I don’t know <br>how to hold your hand <br>so that I don’t break it <br>Back in the Zenzenzense <br>‘til this day been looking <br>everywhere for you Oh <br>I let the sound <br>of your unfettered voice <br>and the shedding <br>of tears lead me this way <br>So tell me <br>who will ever gonna stop us <br>on this the eve of our revolution <br>No more hesitation <br>I will put up a flag <br>to stake my claim <br>on your heart tonight <br>‘Cause you took away <br>from me the will to give up <br>so clearly and awkwardly <br>I wonder if we can push <br>our way through <br>The countless barriers <br>that's waiting in the future <br>just beyond our view <br>Side by side <br>no way we can lose <br>We’ll beat destiny <br>at its own game <br>and make it follow our own rules <br>and there isn’t any weapon <br>besides you <br>that I need to use <br>Zenzenzense <br>‘til this day been looking <br>everywhere for you <br>I followed the sound <br>of your innocent laughter <br>and it guided me <br>in the right way <br>Even if every piece <br>of you disappeared <br>and if it scattered everywhere <br>No I wouldn’t waver <br>I would start back <br>at one look for you <br>all over again <br>For millions of light years <br>yet to come <br>with a verse on my lips <br>that will never end <br>]]></content><category term="Radwimps" label="Radwimps"/><category term="Zenzenzense (English ver.)" label="Zenzenzense (English ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/Dream_lantern_English_ver/</id><title>Radwimps - Dream lantern (English ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:26:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:26:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Radwimps/Dream_lantern_English_ver/" title="Radwimps - Dream lantern (English ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ah if only our voices <br>speak at night <br>could ever reach <br>the very edge of this world <br>and the time <br>Instead of fading <br>into air and dust <br>Then what will the words <br>could ever be <br>farthest words from probably <br>Let's make a promise <br>that will never fade <br>Let's say it together <br>in count of three oh <br>Ah I'm told that some part <br>of every wish will be heard <br>But lately I lost sight <br>of the truth in those words <br>I can't even remember <br>when I gave up believing <br>What could have <br>been the reason <br>Ah the very moment <br>that the rain will stop <br>And the place rainbow born <br>and dies <br>And where the end <br>of this life lies <br>I've always been insisting <br>there was something <br>that I've longing for <br>One day we'll reach to emotions <br>unexplored unprecedented <br>We'll high five love <br>we've yet to discover <br>and give a kiss to time <br>The five dimensions keep <br>on teasing me <br>But I will keep on looking <br>at you dear <br>Let's make a sign for <br>when we say nice <br>to meet you again <br>I'm on my way to you <br>chasing after your name <br>]]></content><category term="Radwimps" label="Radwimps"/><category term="Dream lantern (English ver.)" label="Dream lantern (English ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alivor/Vorace/</id><title>Alivor - Vorace - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:26:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:26:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alivor/Vorace/" title="Alivor - Vorace - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[J'mors pas a la main qui m'nourrit <br>J'fais pas d'auto mutilation <br>J'torture la ptite souris elle passait pour mes ptites rations <br>Le grand pere au premier rang dans l'champs d'bataille s'fait du mal <br>Petit fils au dernier rang dans l'fond d'la classe fait du sale <br>Nos soldats morts dans la justice <br>J'ai l'petard j'fete pas l'armistice <br>Un pour tous tous pour le bif' <br>Nous on bouge que pour nos mif' <br>Nos avant d'etre esclave jadis <br>Sourd et muet j'parles pas j'agis <br>Fouad ou est la rage a vie <br>Savoir habile j'ai la carabine <br>Des batons dans les roues des dos d'ane on m'dis fait belek retrograde <br>Ils peuvent pas m'ge bou comme Erdogan mes soldats VOR Sont al <br>Charbonnage pour comble le vide <br>Charognard pour compte l'fric <br>J'voulais celebrite mais j'suis connu qu'dans le service des flics <br><br>Ding Dong <br>L'huissiers coriace police et coriace <br>Ping pong <br>Les balles se renvoient bastos se renvoient <br>King Kong <br>Frappes sur le thorax tappes sur le thorax <br>Feroce est la jeun <br>Feroce est la jeun <br>Tous le monde est vorace <br>En dessous des droits au dessus des lois <br>Tous le monde est vorace <br>En dessous des droits au dessus des lois <br>Tous le monde est vorace <br>Predateur ne veut plus etre proie <br>Vorace <br>Serviteur veux fumee l'roi <br>Vorace <br><br>J'suis dans l'bidonville <br>Ou est mon empire <br>J'vois qu'des bidons vides <br>Et l'feux qui s'empire <br>Chemins maudits <br>On a peine <br>Voyous penible <br>On m'as dis choisis <br>Sois t'es bene soit t'es benis <br>Levres cousus pas d'poukhi non <br>On aura tous vu t'as tout dis ouai <br>La rue c'est road tah Poutine <br>J'tourne en rond dans l'sale du sang sur la toupille <br>La vie tient qu'a un bout d'fil pas solide <br>L'avenir tient qu'a un coup d'fil anonyme <br>Mes kho be tom prison <br>Reseaux piston pilon <br>Chemin du million est long <br>Bonheur vite au filon <br><br>Ding Dong <br>L'huissiers coriace police et coriace <br>Ping pong <br>Les balles se renvoient bastos se renvoient <br>King Kong <br>Frappes sur le thorax tappes sur le thorax <br>Feroce est la jeun <br>Feroce est la jeun <br>Tous le monde est vorace <br>En dessous des droits au dessus des lois <br>Tous le monde est vorace <br>En dessous des droits au dessus des lois <br>Tous le monde est vorace <br>Predateur ne veut plus etre proie <br>Vorace <br>Serviteur veux fumee l'roi <br>Vorace]]></content><category term="Alivor" label="Alivor"/><category term="Vorace" label="Vorace"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sam_Ock/Fallin/</id><title>Sam_Ock - Fallin` - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:27:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:27:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sam_Ock/Fallin/" title="Sam_Ock - Fallin` - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I'm ice when I'm daze <br>I hear your tune <br>Let the music relax and unwind <br>Shade got me hot like a <br>supernova light <br>Don't let me fall for my lies <br>Just take one look at me <br>See the frayin' of my heart <br>I'll let your love <br>pull me through <br>Brought to my knees <br>I wanna feel at ease <br>Please help me now to move <br>Help me to move <br>Every time I listen to your voice <br>When I'm fallin' <br>Every single night <br>and every morning <br>You're my song and rhyme <br>You're my perfect time <br>I will trust you and I'll hope <br>Pride got me hot like a <br>goose feather down <br>Blaze knead my heart <br>flour dough golden bell <br>Shade under ya balcony <br>Lovin' got me coolin' see <br>Currency affirmation <br>planted in humility <br>Ability is weakenin' <br>but love my caffeine <br>Drip cup americano <br>hit em with the steam <br>Yea we the dream team <br>trottin' all around <br>the Globe Going for them threes <br>you and me free throw whoa <br>Just take one look at me <br>See the frayin' of my heart <br>I'll let your love <br>pull me through <br>Brought to my knees <br>I wanna feel at ease <br>Please help me now to move <br>Help me to move <br>Every time I listen to your voice <br>When I'm fallin' <br>Every single night <br>and every morning <br>You're my song and rhyme <br>You're my perfect time <br>I will trust you and I'll hope <br>Even if I'm blind <br>I'll listen to your song <br>How can I know beauty <br>Without knowing you <br>I need Your love <br>Every time I listen to your voice <br>When I'm fallin' <br>Every single night <br>and every morning <br>You're my song and rhyme <br>You're my perfect time <br>I will trust you and I'll hope <br>]]></content><category term="Sam Ock" label="Sam Ock"/><category term="Fallin`" label="Fallin`"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shigga_Shay/In_My_Hand/</id><title>Shigga_Shay - In My Hand - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:29:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:29:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shigga_Shay/In_My_Hand/" title="Shigga_Shay - In My Hand - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Memories are just where you laid them <br>Dragging the waters til the depths give up their dead <br>What did you expect to find <br>Was it something you left behind <br>Don't you remember anything I said when I said <br><br>Don't fall away and leave me to myself <br>Don't fall away and leave love bleeding in my hands, in my hands again <br>And leave love bleeding in my hands, in my hands <br>Love lies bleeding <br><br>Oh hold me now I feel contagious <br>Am I the only place that you've left to go <br>She cries her life is like <br>Some movie in black and white <br>Dead actors faking lines, over and over and over again she cries <br><br>And I watched as you turned away <br>You don't remember, but I do <br>You never even tried <br><br>Don't fall away and leave me to myself <br>Don't fall away and leave love bleeding in my hands, in my hands again <br>Leave love bleeding in my hands, in my hands again <br>Leave love bleeding in my hands, in my hands again, oh]]></content><category term="Shigga Shay" label="Shigga Shay"/><category term="In My Hand" label="In My Hand"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caknow/임홍선/</id><title>Caknow - 임홍선 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:29:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:29:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caknow/%EC%9E%84%ED%99%8D%EC%84%A0/" title="Caknow - 임홍선 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[hey 엄마 그래 <br>난 그저 웃고싶어 <br>좆같은 새끼들 밟으며 <br>겉모습이 아닌 마음으로 <br>난 그저 웃고싶어 <br>예 엄마 난 빛나고 싶어 <br>병신들 다 태워 버리게 <br>추운겨울이 와도 <br>엄마의 마음이 <br>얼지 않도록 <br>엄마 우리 약속 했던것 <br>부끄럼 없이 사는건 <br>그저 낭만적인 말이 었는걸 <br>정의라는게 항상 <br>속고 뺏기는 거라면 <br>이젠 장난감으로 <br>지구를 지키던 <br>아들은 없어진 지도 <br>닳도록 올리는 기도 <br>좆같어 이제 비는것도 <br>이젠 창조가 됐는지 <br>내가 원숭이 새낀지 <br>나도 헷갈려 <br>허나 엄마의 희망이기에 <br>있어야돼 하나님 <br>꺼지면 안되는 불씨기에 <br>있어야지 하나님 <br>아들아 저 하늘위는 <br>너가 보지못한 곳이있어 <br>고통도 가난도 없는 <br>낭만적인 도시로 <br>가자 그래 <br>우리 기도 하자 <br>가자 응 엄마 <br>우리 기도 하자 <br>아들아 저 하늘위는 <br>눈물이 없는 도시래 <br>우린 눈물이 말랐어도 <br>저 아름다운 도시로 <br>가자 그래 <br>우리 기도 하자 <br>가자 응 엄마 <br>우리 기도 하자 <br>엄마는 소녀 <br>장미꽃을 안다가 <br>가시가 박힌걸 <br>아름다움은 결국 <br>상처를 만들어 <br>사계절 꽃이 필 수 있는건 <br>따뜻한 맘보단 <br>따뜻한 온실속 <br>결국 영원한 사랑도 <br>돈 안에서 행복하단걸 <br>속쓰려 <br>욱욱 컥 거리는 속 <br>헛구역 질을 계속 해도 <br>내속은 비어있어 <br>난 웃음이 많은 사람이니 <br>웃을게 하하하하 <br>그래 하늘아 <br>내 얼굴을 봐줘 <br>시발놈들아 내 <br>몰골을 보라고 <br>엄마의 품안에선 <br>아름다웠던 것들이 <br>이제는 내 목을 조르며 <br>흥분한듯 떨리는 진동 <br>두려워 엄마는 <br>참 강인한 존재인걸 <br>난 두려워 엄마는 <br>참 여린 존재 였잖어 <br>아들아 저 하늘위는 <br>너가 보지못한 곳이있어 <br>고통도 가난도 없는 <br>낭만적인 도시로 <br>가자 그래 <br>우리 기도 하자 <br>가자 응 엄마 <br>우리 기도 하자 <br>아들아 저 하늘위는 <br>눈물이 없는 도시래 <br>우린 눈물이 말랐어도 <br>저 아름다운 도시로 <br>가자 그래 <br>우리 기도 하자 <br>가자 응 엄마 <br>우리 기도 하자 <br>]]></content><category term="Caknow" label="Caknow"/><category term="임홍선" label="임홍선"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caknow/거꾸로_탄_우산/</id><title>Caknow - 거꾸로 탄 우산 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:29:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:29:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Caknow/%EA%B1%B0%EA%BE%B8%EB%A1%9C_%ED%83%84_%EC%9A%B0%EC%82%B0/" title="Caknow - 거꾸로 탄 우산 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[파도의 눈물은 <br>더 깊게 빠지게 해 <br>나의 시체 <br>비내리는 바다 속에 <br>빨려 들어가고 있네 <br>내 영혼은 그저 <br>바라 보고 있어 <br>잘가 내 인생아 <br>잘가 내 사랑아 <br>잘가 버려 모든 <br>내 기억의 조각들아 <br>허나 엉덩이 묻은 <br>모래를 털지 못해 <br>물 위에 다시 날 띄워 <br>우산을 타고서 <br>surf surf surf <br>어딨니 나의 행복들은 <br>전부 어딨니 <br>surf surf surf <br>이 슬픔안에 <br>나는 어디 있니 <br>노를 저어봐 저어봐 <br>저어봐 또 저어봐도 <br>넓은 바다는 <br>나의 행복을 숨겨 <br>노를 저어봐 저어봐 <br>저어봐 또 저어봐 <br>이 눈물위에 내 우산이 <br>가라 앉지 않기를 <br>난 외로운 항해사 <br>외로운 어두운 바다 <br>어디에 잠겨있는걸까 <br>조용한 파도안에 <br>내 감정은 익사 <br>껍데기만 덩그러니 <br>떠다니는 기분 <br>누가 이곳에 <br>있긴 할까 추운건 싫어 <br>등 넓은 고래야 <br>날 꽉 안아줘 <br>어서 날 꽉 안아줘 <br>파래진 입술이 <br>너의 온기로 <br>가득찰 수있게 <br>어서 날 꽉 안아줘 <br>어서 날 꽉 안아줘 <br>이 무서운 슬픔에 <br>빠지지 않도록 <br>니가 날 좀 안아줘 <br>surf surf surf <br>어딨니 나의 행복들은 <br>전부 어딨니 <br>surf surf surf <br>이 슬픔안에 <br>나는 어디 있니 <br>노를 저어봐 저어봐 <br>저어봐 또 저어봐도 <br>넓은 바다는 <br>나의 행복을 숨겨 <br>노를 저어봐 저어봐 <br>저어봐 또 저어봐 <br>이 눈물위에 내 우산이 <br>가라 앉지 않기를 <br>]]></content><category term="Caknow" label="Caknow"/><category term="거꾸로 탄 우산" label="거꾸로 탄 우산"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/율/어디라도_가고싶어/</id><title>율 - 어디라도 가고싶어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:29:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:29:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A8/%EC%96%B4%EB%94%94%EB%9D%BC%EB%8F%84_%EA%B0%80%EA%B3%A0%EC%8B%B6%EC%96%B4/" title="율 - 어디라도 가고싶어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[따스한 아침햇살에 <br>나도 모르게 <br>잠에서 깨어 일어나 <br>창문을 열었을 때 <br>포근하게 날 비추는 <br>저 햇살이 <br>날 오라하네 손짓하네 <br>날 부르네 <br>많은 게 필요하진 않아 <br>교통카드 한 장 들고 <br>가까운 곳 <br>어디라도 가고싶어 <br>굳이 멀리가지 않더라도 <br>가까운 곳 어디라도 <br>다른 마음 다른 <br>기분으로 가면 <br>그 동안 아무렇지 않게 <br>지나쳤던 많은 것들 <br>보이겠지 들리겠지 <br>느껴지겠지 <br>혼자보단 둘인 게 <br>더 좋겠지 <br>함께 떠들며 함께 <br>걸으며 웃음짓네 <br>다른 게 필요하진 않아 <br>함께하는 이 순간에 <br>가까운 곳 <br>어디라도 가고싶어 <br>굳이 멀리가지 않더라도 <br>가까운 곳 어디라도 <br>다른 마음 다른 <br>기분으로 가면 <br>그 동안 아무렇지 않게 <br>지나쳤던 많은 것들 <br>보이겠지 들리겠지 <br>느껴지겠지 <br>영화처럼 멋진 곳은 <br>아닐지라도 <br>마음 닿는 대로 <br>어디라도 가고싶어 <br>굳이 멀리가지 않더라도 <br>가까운 곳 어디라도 <br>그 동안에 아무렇지 않게 <br>지나쳤던 많은 것들 <br>보이겠지 들리겠지 <br>느껴지겠지 <br>어디라도 가고싶어 <br>]]></content><category term="율" label="율"/><category term="어디라도 가고싶어" label="어디라도 가고싶어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정상수/긍정_바이브/</id><title>정상수 - 긍정 바이브 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:31:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:31:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%83%81%EC%88%98/%EA%B8%8D%EC%A0%95_%EB%B0%94%EC%9D%B4%EB%B8%8C/" title="정상수 - 긍정 바이브 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여실히 열심히 하니깐 <br>결실을 맺네 <br>다시 또 자신을 <br>돌아보고서는 뱉네 <br>다 한때지 난 빡세지 <br>내 장래를 향해 밤새지 <br>난 달리지 더 not easy <br>Ready to the challenge <br>이제 내 지게 속의 <br>무게를 덜어내고 <br>고개를 넘어가 뭐 <br>고생은 하겠지 <br>한 단계 성장해 <br>도전해 더 발전해 <br>미랠 향해 진전해 <br>멈추지는 않아 절대 <br>Bibbidi bob the bbidi boo <br>수많은 압박 속에서도 <br>오로지 끈기를 끝까지 믿고 <br>주변사람들을 다 속여서도 <br>불태우네 날 깨우네 <br>개운해 한수 배우네 <br>곡때문에 애태우네 <br>다시 또 가사를 때우네 <br>매일매일 funnyday <br>내일은 다시 <br>Holiday <br>E-mail을 보내 <br>main character <br>상수형과 saturday <br>Better than yesterday <br>어제보다 <br>더 나은 내일을 원해 <br>계속 노력해 <br>난 준비됐어 a better day <br>긍정 Vibe 우린 이렇게 살아 <br>힘들고 어려워도 <br>웃으며 높이 날아 <br>긍정 vibe 우린 이렇게 살아 <br>어떤 일도 결국 <br>해낸다는 것을 알아 <br>긍정 vibe 우린 이렇게 살아 <br>리듬 안에서 <br>믿음과 확신이 자라 <br>긍정 vibe 우린 이렇게 살아 <br>우린 뭐든 할 수 <br>있다는 걸 깨달아 <br>긍정 바이브 <br>해볼래 하이 파이브 <br>힙합 더 다이브 <br>힙합 이즈 얼라이브 <br>포지티브 마인드 <br>아임 소 파인 <br>저스트 킵 트라이 <br>베이비 돈 크라이 <br>눈 부신 선샤인처럼 <br>빛나는 싸인 <br>시도해 올 카인드 <br>한 길로만 그라인드 <br>전설은 영원히 남지 <br>네버 다이 <br>요즘엔 너 나 할 것 없이 <br>터프 가이 <br>행동이 없다면 <br>너의 rap은 라이 <br>안 좋은 습관에 <br>세이 굿 바이 <br>도전과 시도가 <br>만들어내는 차이 <br>무엇이든 이루어낼 <br>수 있는 나이 <br>이 구역은 믿음과 <br>확신의 와이파이 <br>강한 신념으로 <br>싸우는 무에타이 <br>생긴 대로 너와 내 <br>멋대로 에픽하이 <br>나팔바지 입고 <br>걸어가는 거야 싸이 <br>긍정 Vibe 우린 이렇게 살아 <br>힘들고 어려워도 <br>웃으며 높이 날아 <br>긍정 vibe 우린 이렇게 살아 <br>어떤 일도 결국 <br>해낸다는 것을 알아 <br>긍정 vibe 우린 이렇게 살아 <br>리듬 안에서 <br>믿음과 확신이 자라 <br>긍정 vibe 우린 이렇게 살아 <br>우린 뭐든 할 수 <br>있다는 걸 깨달아 <br>긍정 바이브 <br>일단 해보는 타입 <br>꿈 꾸는 라이프 <br>미래가 흐르는 파이프 <br>내 인생은 지금부터가 <br>하이라이트 <br>내 안에 잠 든 거인을 <br>리얼라이즈 <br>인생의 신호등 들어왔어 <br>그린 라이트 <br>최자 개코가 놀라는 <br>다이너마이트 <br>내 가사 롸임 데이터는 <br>수천 테라 바이트 <br>내 머릿 속은 전 세계 <br>최대 웹 사이트 <br>긍정 Vibe 우린 이렇게 살아 <br>힘들고 어려워도 <br>웃으며 높이 날아 <br>긍정 vibe 우린 이렇게 살아 <br>어떤 일도 결국 <br>해낸다는 것을 알아 <br>긍정 vibe 우린 이렇게 살아 <br>리듬 안에서 <br>믿음과 확신이 자라 <br>긍정 vibe 우린 이렇게 살아 <br>우린 뭐든 할 수 <br>있다는 걸 깨달아 <br>]]></content><category term="정상수" label="정상수"/><category term="긍정 바이브" label="긍정 바이브"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김시형/친구_With_김동현/</id><title>김시형 - 친구 (With 김동현) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:32:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:32:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%8B%9C%ED%98%95/%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC_With_%EA%B9%80%EB%8F%99%ED%98%84/" title="김시형 - 친구 (With 김동현) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언제라도 나에게 <br>지켜주는 그 이름 <br>그저 부를 수 있다면 <br>단 한 사람 나의 친구야 <br>지쳐 있는 나에게 <br>너는 항상 말하지 <br>생각보다 괜찮다고 <br>힘든 마음 덜어주네 <br>오래된 사진 속에는 <br>당연한 듯한 내 옆에 있는 모습 <br>빠르게 변해가는 우리 <br>아쉬워하며 지나간다 <br>항상 지켜왔던 우리 약속 <br>세월 속에 그 자리에 있고 <br>너와 함께했던 우리 추억 <br>잊지 않고 나의 마음속에 있네 <br>내 삶 속에 있어준 <br>하나뿐인 나의 친구야 <br>술 한 잔과 함께한 <br>마주 했던 그 시간 <br>변할 수 없는 우리 우정 <br>맞잡은 손 꺾이지 않네 <br>오래된 사진 속에는 <br>당연한 듯한 내 옆에 있는 모습 <br>빠르게 변해가는 우리 <br>아쉬워하며 지나간다 <br>항상 지켜왔던 우리 약속 <br>세월 속에 그 자리에 있고 <br>너와 함께했던 우리 추억 <br>잊지 않고 나의 마음속에 있네 <br>내 삶 속에 있어준 <br>하나뿐인 나의 친구야 <br>하나뿐인 나의 친구야 <br>]]></content><category term="김시형" label="김시형"/><category term="친구 (With 김동현)" label="친구 (With 김동현)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김유식_KIM_YU_SIK/여호와_이레_Vocal_Feat_김_찬/</id><title>김유식_KIM_YU_SIK - 여호와 이레 (Vocal Feat. 김 찬) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:32:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:32:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9C%A0%EC%8B%9D_KIM_YU_SIK/%EC%97%AC%ED%98%B8%EC%99%80_%EC%9D%B4%EB%A0%88_Vocal_Feat_%EA%B9%80_%EC%B0%AC/" title="김유식_KIM_YU_SIK - 여호와 이레 (Vocal Feat. 김 찬) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[들에 백합화 그 누가 가꾸나 <br>이른 비 늦은 비 내리니 꽃이 피네 <br>공중에 새들은 그 누가 키우나 <br>철 따라 주께서 준비 하시네 <br>무엇을 먹을까 염려 마오 <br>창조주 여호와 계시니 <br>무엇을 입을까 근심 마오 <br>우리 하나님 아버지 준비 하시네 <br>여호와 이레 준비 하시고 <br>여호와 이레 허락 하시네 <br>우리 모든 삶 <br>주님께 내어 맡기며 <br>주 여호와 하나님 <br>우리 주만 따를 때 <br>모든 걱정 모든 근심 <br>물러가리 <br>우리 모든 삶 <br>주님께 내어 맡기며 <br>주 여호와 하나님 <br>우리 주만 따를 때 <br>모든 걱정 모든 근심 <br>물러가리 <br>여호와 이레 <br>여호와 이레 <br>여호와 이레 <br>여호와 이레 <br>]]></content><category term="김유식 (KIM YU SIK)" label="김유식 (KIM YU SIK)"/><category term="여호와 이레 (Vocal Feat. 김 찬)" label="여호와 이레 (Vocal Feat. 김 찬)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김유식_KIM_YU_SIK/모든_영광_주님께_Vocal_Feat_김_찬/</id><title>김유식_KIM_YU_SIK - 모든 영광 주님께 (Vocal Feat. 김 찬) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:32:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:32:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9C%A0%EC%8B%9D_KIM_YU_SIK/%EB%AA%A8%EB%93%A0_%EC%98%81%EA%B4%91_%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98%EA%BB%98_Vocal_Feat_%EA%B9%80_%EC%B0%AC/" title="김유식_KIM_YU_SIK - 모든 영광 주님께 (Vocal Feat. 김 찬) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언제부터인가 나의 마음속에 <br>살며시 들어와 계시는 주님 <br>나의 모든 생각 감찰 하시며 <br>모든 묵상과 간구 응답 하시네 <br>나 호흡 있는 날까지 <br>받은 은혜 감사 드리며 <br>주신 응답 온 세상 증거하리라 <br>모든 영광 주님께 돌리리라 <br>나 호흡 있는 날까지 <br>받은 은혜 감사 드리며 <br>주신 응답 온 세상 증거하리라 <br>모든 영광 주님께 돌리리라 <br>모든 영광 주님께 돌리리라 <br>모든 영광 주님께 돌리리라 <br>]]></content><category term="김유식 (KIM YU SIK)" label="김유식 (KIM YU SIK)"/><category term="모든 영광 주님께 (Vocal Feat. 김 찬)" label="모든 영광 주님께 (Vocal Feat. 김 찬)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김유식_KIM_YU_SIK/내_안에_나의_영혼아_Vocal_Feat_김_찬/</id><title>김유식_KIM_YU_SIK - 내 안에 나의 영혼아 (Vocal Feat. 김 찬) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:32:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:32:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9C%A0%EC%8B%9D_KIM_YU_SIK/%EB%82%B4_%EC%95%88%EC%97%90_%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%98%81%ED%98%BC%EC%95%84_Vocal_Feat_%EA%B9%80_%EC%B0%AC/" title="김유식_KIM_YU_SIK - 내 안에 나의 영혼아 (Vocal Feat. 김 찬) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 안에 나의 영혼아 <br>너 낙망 치를 말아라 <br>나의 방패 나의 반석 되신 <br>구원의 주 널 지키시리 <br>시험 환란 닥쳐 와도 <br>너 흔들리지 말아라 <br>우리 구주 우리 예수님이 <br>항상 너 함께 동행 하네 <br>오호라 주 여호와여 <br>내 안에 영혼 안위 하소서 <br>오호라 주 여호와여 <br>주의 얼굴 내게 비추소서 <br>시험 환란 닥쳐 와도 <br>너 흔들리지 말아라 <br>우리 구주 우리 예수님이 <br>항상 너 함께 동행 하네 <br>오호라 주 여호와여 <br>내 안에 영혼 안위 하소서 <br>오호라 주 여호와여 <br>내 안에 영혼 안위 하소서 <br>오호라 주 여호와여 <br>주의 얼굴 내게 비추소서 <br>오호라 주 여호와여 <br>주의 얼굴 내게 비추소서 <br>]]></content><category term="김유식 (KIM YU SIK)" label="김유식 (KIM YU SIK)"/><category term="내 안에 나의 영혼아 (Vocal Feat. 김 찬)" label="내 안에 나의 영혼아 (Vocal Feat. 김 찬)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/magnic/Finish/</id><title>magnic - Finish - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:32:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:32:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/magnic/Finish/" title="magnic - Finish - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[길게도 끌었어 <br>날 떠나줘 멀었어 <br>하지만 오늘 다 끝나 <br>니네가 틀렸어 <br>난 절대 안 틀렸어 <br>alright it's all over tonight <br>all over tonight <br>tonight <br>all over tonight <br>tonight <br>오늘 밤 모든 게 끝나 <br>난 내가 이 정도까지 큰 다음 <br>어리고 어른스럽게 굴다 <br>포기하길 바랬지만 still alive <br>삶은 쉽게 끝나지 않았지만 <br>내가 하는 것들은 고비를 지나 <br>또 새로운 산을 오르고 있어 지난 <br>발자국들은 안 봐도 느껴지지 다 <br>멍청이들은 다 못 알아봤지 <br>내 영혼이 지니고 있는 빛깔을 <br>천천히 들어 난 올려다 본 뒤 <br>마구 흘리고 다닐 거야 <br>황금빛 가루 <br>목걸이와 금니 또 여덟 개의 링 <br>Ride around ma town <br>원할 때 바로 <br>쉽지 않겠지만 당연한 거지 <br>니가 다 알어 <br>나 나는 알어 나를 알어 <br>끝나길 바라며 또 안 끝나길 <br>순간의 영원을 즐기며 하품하지 <br>popin champagne <br>일러 맥주 한입 <br>걱정은 안해 내 꾸준한 입 <br>오늘 밤 모든 게 끝나 <br>모두에게 인사를 goodnight <br>새론 아침이 올 거야 다음날 <br>모두에게 인사를 goodnight <br>길게도 끌었어 <br>날 떠나줘 멀었어 <br>하지만 오늘 다 끝나 <br>니네가 틀렸어 <br>난 절대 안 틀렸어 <br>alright it's all over tonight <br>all over tonight <br>tonight <br>all over tonight <br>tonight <br>오늘 밤 모든 게 끝나 <br>늘 하던 대로 약을 삼킨 다음 <br>오늘따라 유난히 긴 달 <br>을 바라보며 I'm so fuckin high <br>뭐든 이룰 수 있을 것 같애 <br>날 괴롭히던 것들 어차피 내 안에 <br>존재하던 것 들일뿐 <br>어떤 일이든 <br>난 바라보는 눈이 <br>달라졌어 미리 끝 <br>까지 다 바라보고 온 듯이 <br>초연한 눈빛으로 본 도시 <br>맘껏 정신을 잃고 다녀 <br>바로 오늘 큰 돈을 번 듯이 <br>반드시 될 거라 난 믿었지 <br>내일 입을 셔츠를 다려 반듯이 <br>다른 놈들은 못 보는 걸 보지 <br>운명의 베일이 <br>가리는 것도 난 투시 <br>뱅뱅 돌아온 길 매일매일 <br>생각하던 걸 다 가진 채로 play back <br>후회 없지 마지막 가사 뒤에 마침 <br>표를 찍고 나서 이제 맞이 할 아침 <br>오늘 밤 모든 게 끝나 <br>모두에게 인사를 goodnight <br>이제 기회가 없을지도 몰라 <br>늦기 전에 인사해둬 goodnight <br>all over tonight <br>늦기 전에 인사해둬 goodnight <br>all over tonight <br>BLUE Blue blu 너무 새파란 밤 <br>all over tonight <br>늦기 전에 인사해둬 goodnight <br>all over tonight <br>BLUE Blue blu 너무 새파란 밤 <br>]]></content><category term="!magnic!" label="!magnic!"/><category term="Finish" label="Finish"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/magnic/Purple_Cloud/</id><title>magnic - Purple Cloud - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:32:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:32:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/magnic/Purple_Cloud/" title="magnic - Purple Cloud - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[두통 자주 있는 일 <br>눈을 질끈 감았다 뜨고 <br>흐르는 헛 눈물을 훔쳐 <br>온도는 생각보단 뜨거워 <br>니가 더 뜨고 내가 못 뜨고 <br>별 잡 생각이 다 들어 <br>보라색 구름 안에 갇힌 기분 <br>복잡한 생각들이 들어 <br>purple cloud <br>purple cloud <br>purple cloud <br>purple cloud <br>welcome 고민월드 <br>계절 따라 바뀌어 가네 <br>우리도 <br>뒤로 가지만 않으면 장땡이지 뭐 <br>걸어가는 법은 알어 <br>take it easy 워 <br>그대로 봐 그대로 노력해 <br>손을 놓아도 그대로 내 옆에 <br>있디 말디 뭔 상관이여 <br>이젠 괴롭게 <br>생각하고 싶지 않어요 왜 이렇게 <br>질처억대 바이바이 <br>사바세계 난 부처가 되어 <br>세상을 바라 보고 싶어 <br>이 반복을 수십 번 수백 번 <br>수천 번 수만 번 계속 하더라도 <br>벗어 날 수 있다면 내게 불 한번 <br>또 붙여보지 <br>꺼지고 상처 입더라도 <br>불 한번 또 붙여보지 <br>아직 철부지 이건 노래에서만 <br>난 계속 구름을 통해서 봐 <br>purple cloud <br>purple cloud <br>purple cloud <br>purple cloud <br>헤집고 헤엄 <br>뭉게뭉게 연기 속 <br>해지고 해 떠 <br>나는 자연의 섭리 속 <br>헤집고 헤엄 <br>뭉게뭉게 연기 속 <br>해지고 해 떠 <br>우린 자연의 섭리 속 <br>헤집고 헤엄 <br>뭉게뭉게 연기 속 <br>해지고 해 떠 <br>나는 자연의 섭리 속 <br>헤집고 헤엄 <br>뭉게뭉게 연기 속 <br>해지고 해 떠 <br>우린 자연의 섭리 속 <br>]]></content><category term="!magnic!" label="!magnic!"/><category term="Purple Cloud" label="Purple Cloud"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/magnic/So_Icey_Feat_Icey_Blouie/</id><title>magnic - So Icey (Feat. Icey Blouie) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:32:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:32:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/magnic/So_Icey_Feat_Icey_Blouie/" title="magnic - So Icey (Feat. Icey Blouie) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So icey <br>너무 얼음같애 <br>넌 난 눈물흘려 몰래 <br>So icey <br>너무 얼음같애 <br>넌 난 차가워져 가네 <br>So icey So icey <br>so icey so icey <br>So icey <br>너무 얼음같애 <br>넌 난 눈물흘려 몰래 <br>여긴 눈은 잘 오지 않아도 <br>난 느낄 수 있어 <br>이 차가움은 여름에도 <br>날 더울 수 없게 해 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>보냈던 시간은 <br>다 얼어서 정지한 듯 해 <br>나 홀로 섬 <br>에 같인 듯한 기분 <br>여긴 무인도 <br>내가 좋아하는 <br>다듀의 노래처럼 <br>난 이 도실 떠날 생각이었어 <br>너와 함께 라면 <br>너무 길어서 끊어지지 <br>않을 것 같던 끈은 비로소 <br>부숴져 버렸지 <br>이 온도는 끔찍해 <br>우리가 자주 갔었던 그 집엔 <br>쓸데없는 기억들이 <br>가득해서 난 잘 못 지내 <br>병들어선 몸을 떨고있기에 <br>so please <br>다시한번 따뜻하게 <br>나를 안아준다면 <br>모든 봄이 내게 올텐데 <br>이걸 알아준다면 <br>뭐든 좋으니 <br>내게 연락해 베이베 <br>하지만 그럴 일은 없지 <br>그저 견디는 중이야 <br>이 냉랭한 한기 <br>Fuck 니 향기 차라리 <br>영영 사라졌음 하지만 <br>it ain't easy <br>So icey <br>너무 얼음같애 <br>넌 난 눈물흘려 몰래 <br>So icey <br>너무 얼음같애 <br>넌 난 차가워져 가네 <br>So icey So icey <br>so icey so icey <br>So icey <br>너무 얼음같애 <br>넌 난 눈물흘려 몰래 <br>Baby I'm so icey <br>너를 담을 수 없어 <br>난 냉동실 <br>숨이 너무 막히는 <br>차가운 냉기 <br>날 식혀줘 난 필요해 소화기 <br>우리둘 사이엔 이미 <br>쳐져있는 커다란 벽 <br>널 볼일은 없겠지 영영 <br>너는 내 가슴을 크게 찢어놓고 <br>내게 연락하지마 다신 <br>괜찮다는 말들 전부 가식 <br>I got too many bitches <br>I got too many bitches <br>요즘 내 옷 프레드 페리 <br>디자이너 청바지에 은니 <br>Bitch I'm ballin ballin ballin <br>Bitch I'm ballin ballin ballin <br>나는 원래 차가워 <br>머리를 비우고 싶어 텅텅 <br>널 잊고 싶어 난 평생토록 <br>니 번호도 이미 난 지웠어 <br>딴 여자랑 자고 나면 난 공허 <br>잊고 싶어 우리 둘의 추억 <br>전부 지우고 싶어 내 기억 <br>에 im so icey <br>So icey <br>너무 얼음같애 <br>넌 난 눈물흘려 몰래 <br>So icey <br>너무 얼음같애 <br>넌 난 차가워져 가네 <br>So icey So icey <br>so icey so icey <br>So icey <br>너무 얼음같애 <br>넌 난 눈물흘려 몰래 <br>]]></content><category term="!magnic!" label="!magnic!"/><category term="So Icey (Feat. Icey Blouie)" label="So Icey (Feat. Icey Blouie)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/magnic/Y3_Feat_TSUN/</id><title>magnic - Y3 (Feat. TSUN) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:32:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:32:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/magnic/Y3_Feat_TSUN/" title="magnic - Y3 (Feat. TSUN) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 어젯 밤에 <br>새론 신발을 <br>알게 됐지 요걸 지를까 <br>말까 들뜬 마음 <br>Y3 니가 좋아졌어 다이스키 <br>I love it 이젠 질렸어 Nike <br>Yoji Yamamoto와 <br>Adidas의 합작 <br>nice kicks <br>조던은 너무 <br>많이들 신어 역시 <br>유행은 뭐든 재미 없지 <br>사진들을 보면 <br>볼수록 갖고싶어져 <br>이런걸 참으면 <br>병되지 가끔씩 사던 <br>신발이란 걸 <br>오늘은 지를 때야 <br>라고 맘을 먹으며 <br>클릭을 하네 <br>같은 짓 반복 <br>아이콘을 몇번을 눌렀어 <br>조금 늦게 뜨네 <br>뒤늦게 다음창으로 <br>넘어가 보여 내 눈에 <br>i really wanna that shit <br>Y3 나랑 안어울리게 <br>so hype hype hype hype <br>난 매일 봐 <br>여러 사이트들과 <br>인스타그램 속의 타임라인 <br>또 둘러보기 안 <br>나랑 전혀 접점이 하나 <br>도 없을 것 같지만 <br>열등감을 주는 사람 <br>들이 올린 잘 꾸며진 <br>사진속의 그 허탈함 <br>니들은 몰라 내게 꽤 큰 <br>의미의 상대적 박탈감 <br>못난 모습 이걸 <br>누군가 안다면 난 탈락 <br>다들 팔로워가 많은 <br>해쉬태그갱들 나도 당장 <br>비싸고 잘나가는 삶을 <br>게시 하고파서 안달 <br>나있지만 하나도 <br>난 지금 그럴 껀덕지가 없지 <br>cash rules everything <br>around me 예예 역시 <br>난 사람 수 많은 욕심 위에 <br>엎드려 잠을 자는 도시 <br>또 사하라 안에서 <br>다른 척 하며 같은 것을 좇지 <br>i really wanna that shit <br>Y3 나랑 안어울리게 <br>so hype hype hype hype <br>나랑 안어울리게 <br>so hype so hype so hype <br>Y3 Y3 Y3 <br>난 계속 바라봐 <br>멍하니 유리창안을 <br>쇼윈도에 비친 <br>너무나 파란하늘 <br>난 계속 바라봐 <br>멍하니 유리창안을 <br>쇼윈도에 비친 <br>너무나 파란하늘 <br>]]></content><category term="!magnic!" label="!magnic!"/><category term="Y3 (Feat. TSUN)" label="Y3 (Feat. TSUN)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/magnic/Lexapro/</id><title>magnic - Lexapro - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:32:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:32:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/magnic/Lexapro/" title="magnic - Lexapro - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[MGNC stay blue <br>MGNC stay blue <br>stay blue <br>stay blue <br>stay blue again <br>기분은 최저 <br>땅을 뚫고 내려가 <br>고개를 숙여 <br>근처도 못간 paradise <br>날 아는 척 마 <br>니 기분도 달아나 <br>세상에 혼자인 기분 <br>나 혼자 달나라 <br>내뱉는 한숨 <br>삼키는 알약 한줌 <br>내뱉는 한숨 <br>삼키는 알약 한줌 <br>내뱉는 한숨 <br>삼키는 알약 한줌 <br>내뱉는 한숨 <br>삼키는 알약 한줌 <br>이미 내 머릿속은 <br>엉망 미쳐버리곤 <br>머리를 쥐어뜯고 <br>망가져버린 내모든 ego <br>누군간 쉽게 공감 <br>누군간 나를 버리고 <br>새로운 길을 가려 하네 <br>그래 나를 내비둬 <br>I wanna go hard <br>그러나 힘이 없어 <br>차라리 눈을 감고싶어 <br>세상이 희미해서 <br>침대 위에 하루종일 누워 <br>내가 의미했던 <br>가치들이 점점 <br>사라져 가는 기분이야 <br>뭘 위해서 <br>숨을 쉬는가 <br>나는 비는가 <br>아니 빌었던가 <br>헛갈리기까지 해 <br>난 뭔가를 잃었던가 <br>확실한게 있다면 <br>그건 내게 빌어먹을 돈과 <br>많은 문제들이 있단거지 <br>어서 삼켜야겠어 <br>처방받은 약을 몇가지 <br>기분은 최저 <br>땅을 뚫고 내려가 <br>고개를 숙여 <br>근처도 못간 paradise <br>날 아는 척 마 <br>니 기분도 달아나 <br>세상에 혼자인 기분 <br>나 혼자 달나라 <br>내뱉는 한숨 <br>삼키는 알약 한줌 <br>내뱉는 한숨 <br>삼키는 알약 한줌 <br>내뱉는 한숨 <br>삼키는 알약 한줌 <br>내뱉는 한숨 <br>삼키는 알약 한줌 <br>이미 내 머릿속은 <br>엉망 잊어버리곤 <br>예전처럼 살고 싶어 <br>습관적인 피곤 <br>을 달고 사는 내게 <br>밤하늘은 새파란 빛 <br>shit 그래 젊음을 낭비 <br>처방을 받은 약이 <br>몇 개 나 남았는지 <br>세어보며 다음 병원에 <br>갈 날을 난 계산하지 <br>축 처진 어깨 <br>힘이 없는 발걸음 <br>에이 뭐 어때하는 <br>친구들의 말들은 <br>미안하지만 전혀 <br>힘이 되지 않아 <br>그래 나도 알아 내가 <br>할 수 있는 건 지금 하나 <br>그냥 방구석에 쳐박힌 채로 <br>우울한 생각 꼬리 물기 <br>멈출 수 없이 계속 <br>구김이 생겨가는 내 맘엔 <br>그냥 약이 필요하단 걸 알아 <br>기분은 최저 <br>땅을 뚫고 내려가 <br>고개를 숙여 <br>근처도 못간 paradise <br>날 아는 척 마 <br>니 기분도 달아나 <br>세상에 혼자인 기분 <br>나 혼자 달나라 <br>내뱉는 한숨 <br>삼키는 알약 한줌 <br>내뱉는 한숨 <br>삼키는 알약 한줌 <br>내뱉는 한숨 <br>삼키는 알약 한줌 <br>내뱉는 한숨 <br>삼키는 알약 한줌 <br>]]></content><category term="!magnic!" label="!magnic!"/><category term="Lexapro" label="Lexapro"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/얼베인_레코즈_Urbane_Records/Right_Here/</id><title>얼베인_레코즈_Urbane_Records - Right Here - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:32:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:32:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%BC%EB%B2%A0%EC%9D%B8_%EB%A0%88%EC%BD%94%EC%A6%88_Urbane_Records/Right_Here/" title="얼베인_레코즈_Urbane_Records - Right Here - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Urbane의 Party <br>잘 들어왔어 <br>전부 shake yo <br>body everybody <br>우리 팀은 사기 <br>I mean everybody <br>Finna build a mountain <br>우리 만에 질서 <br>무리없이 Maintain <br>fuck a vacay <br>쉴 틈없이 달려 <br>기다리지 큰 pay day <br>Fuck 메이저 소속사 <br>Industry real shady <br>자수성가 가 목표 <br>Like real slim shAdy <br>But can we make it <br>Of course we can <br>다른건 몰라도 <br>랩은 개 잘해 <br>이 바닥을 여자라고 <br>치고 우린 다 갖지 <br>이건 게임이 될 듯해 <br>yea 땅따먹기 <br>Esquil levodopa <br>jermaine we killin <br>다 죽인 다음 비트 <br>위에서 chillin <br>이정도 들어봤으면 <br>확 오잖아 감이 <br>전부 우리한테 걸면 돼 <br>다 좆까고 UB <br>UB records right here <br>We right here <br>내게 뭘 원하는지 <br>난 너무 잘 알아 <br>Yeah i'm fuckin right here <br>right here We doin right here <br>가야돼 전부 담어 <br>a lot of trophies out there <br>U want real homie <br>우릴 따라와 배워 <br>허락은 길형이 <br>We going to the top <br>Ain't gonna stop <br>내 맘대로 뺏어 Yeah right <br>몇명의 groupies out there <br>60억의 가능성 중에 <br>하날 고를래 <br>음악이라는 것 <br>돌팔이 아님 정신병자들 <br>정모엔 관심없어 <br>아예 눈을 감았어 <br>URBANE 가족들에게는 반성 <br>약판다고 핑계대며 <br>가살 안써 <br>하지만 이게 내가 <br>차별되는 이유 <br>돈이 성공의 기준이라면 <br>이미 이뤘어 <br>got a lisence <br>다음엔 힙합씬의 <br>과대평가된 엑스트라들 <br>돈과 명예 타령하며 <br>랩스타 놀이 할 때 <br>URBANE 우린 그냥 즐기며 <br>너넬 사냥해 <br>I am right here <br>우리 팀은 안 움직여 <br>너네가 와 이리로 <br>URBANE의 party는 이 바닥에 <br>새길 마지막 이름 <br>UB records right here <br>We right here <br>내게 뭘 원하는지 <br>난 너무 잘 알아 <br>Yeah i'm fuckin right here <br>right here We doin right here <br>가야 돼 전부 담어 <br>a lot of trophies out there <br>U want real homie <br>우릴 따라와 배워 <br>허락은 길형이 <br>We going to the top <br>Ain't gonna stop <br>내 맘대로 뺏어 Yeah right <br>몇명의 groupies out there <br>I can not stop urbane groove <br>니안에 모든 <br>감각들을 터트려봐 <br>Sure to 원해 fucking with us <br>나의 목소리가 <br>니 귀에 파고들 때 <br>너는 like oh oh oh <br>시간은 많아 보여줄 때 <br>넌 yes sir <br>내가 feel을 줄게 <br>넌 내게 real one night <br>일단 지금은 <br>그냥 다 feeling <br>어찌할 수 없는 <br>나의 grooving <br>리듬과 난 <br>언제나 soulmate <br>좀 더 알고 싶다면 <br>네게 선물을 줄게 <br>Right here in lose control <br>진지하게 임해왔네 <br>2015 거쳐 <br>D&amp;D Psycho <br>2 days 의 작은 업적 <br>낮이나 밤이나 우린 <br>항상 깨있어 매일 <br>눈을 뜨고 꾸는 꿈이 <br>만들어 내 컬쳐 <br>U R B A N E를 붙여 <br>그럼 뭐든 씹을 수 있어 <br>wack의 이름부터 <br>랩은 날 더 키워 <br>할 수록 근육 붙어 <br>내가 써내려 갈 <br>profile은 바로 지금부터 <br>시스템을 거부하네 <br>i'm on my way <br>back on my shit <br>나는 real 힙합을 원해 <br>겁이 많지 주류 속에 취한 <br>무리 너희 부류는 갇혀 <br>구류 우린 걸어가지 one way <br>yeah I'm livin' fuckin' dirty city <br>그래도 자리를 지켜 <br>fuckin' dirty city <br>생존의 법칙은 돈이나 <br>주먹이나 귀나 <br>펜이나 입 이야 <br>we still rappin' right here <br>UB records right here <br>We right here <br>내게 뭘 원하는지 <br>난 너무 잘 알아 <br>Yeah i'm fuckin right here <br>right here We doin right here <br>가야돼 전부 담어 <br>a lot of trophies out there <br>U want real homie <br>우릴 따라와 배워 <br>허락은 길형이 <br>We going to the top <br>Ain't gonna stop <br>내맘대로 뺏어 Yeah right <br>몇명의 groupies out there <br>]]></content><category term="얼베인 레코즈 (Urbane Records)" label="얼베인 레코즈 (Urbane Records)"/><category term="Right Here" label="Right Here"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/흐림_hrim/널_데려간_그_버스는_널_내리지_않은_채로_널_그리워하는_나에게/</id><title>흐림_hrim - 널 데려간 그 버스는 널 내리지 않은 채로 널 그리워하는 나에게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:33:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:33:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9D%90%EB%A6%BC_hrim/%EB%84%90_%EB%8D%B0%EB%A0%A4%EA%B0%84_%EA%B7%B8_%EB%B2%84%EC%8A%A4%EB%8A%94_%EB%84%90_%EB%82%B4%EB%A6%AC%EC%A7%80_%EC%95%8A%EC%9D%80_%EC%B1%84%EB%A1%9C_%EB%84%90_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9B%8C%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%82%98%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C/" title="흐림_hrim - 널 데려간 그 버스는 널 내리지 않은 채로 널 그리워하는 나에게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하얀 너를 봤을 때 <br>우린 함께 걸었지 <br>깊은 눈동자를 볼 수 없어 <br>외로운 눈길 주네 <br>그대가 모르게 <br>잊으려고 애를 써도 <br>매일 아침 눈을 떠도 <br>상냥하게 나타나는 너 <br>널 데려간 그 버스는 <br>널 내리지 않은 채로 <br>널 그리워하는 나에게 <br>푸른 저 하늘을 바라보며 <br>슬픈 생각을 떨쳐 <br>처음 너를 봤을 때 <br>그 미소가 구름에 서려 <br>길을 걷는 동안에도 <br>비를 맞는 이 순간도 <br>가슴 속엔 오직 하나만이 <br>길고 길던 어둠 속에 <br>한 줄기의 빛이 내려 <br>너와 나는 춤을 추었어 <br>잊으려고 애를 써도 <br>매일 아침 눈을 떠도 <br>상냥하게 나타나는 너 <br>널 데려간 그 버스는 <br>널 내리지 않은 채로 <br>널 그리워하는 나에게 <br>]]></content><category term="흐림 (hrim)" label="흐림 (hrim)"/><category term="널 데려간 그 버스는 널 내리지 않은 채로 널 그리워하는 나에게" label="널 데려간 그 버스는 널 내리지 않은 채로 널 그리워하는 나에게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/흐림_hrim/또다시_제자리_standstill/</id><title>흐림_hrim - 또다시 제자리 (standstill) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:33:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:33:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9D%90%EB%A6%BC_hrim/%EB%98%90%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C_%EC%A0%9C%EC%9E%90%EB%A6%AC_standstill/" title="흐림_hrim - 또다시 제자리 (standstill) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어제는 기분 좋은 <br>장면을 보며 <br>잠에서 깼어 <br>보라색 옷을 입은 사람이 <br>내게 다가와 속삭이네 <br>내 귓가에 <br>가만히 이끌려 <br>알고 있었지만 <br>중요하지 않았던 <br>그런 사실들 <br>나는 그 순간을 <br>놓칠 이유가 없었고 <br>홀린 듯 그 순간을 <br>본능적 그 감정을 느낀다 <br>차가운 그 목소리 <br>뜨거운 그 표정을 <br>다시 또 이끌려 <br>차가운 그 목소리 <br>뜨거운 그 표정을 <br>다시 또 이끌려 <br>다시 제자리로 <br>다시 제자리로 <br>오늘은 더 기분 좋은 <br>상상을 하며 <br>눈을 감았어 <br>검붉은 옷을 입은 사람이 <br>네게 다가가 속삭이네 <br>니 어둠에 <br>가만히 이끌려 <br>차가운 그 목소리 <br>뜨거운 그 표정을 <br>다시 또 이끌려 <br>차가운 그 목소리 <br>뜨거운 그 표정을 <br>다시 또 이끌려 <br>다시 제자리로 <br>다시 제자리로 <br>]]></content><category term="흐림 (hrim)" label="흐림 (hrim)"/><category term="또다시 제자리 (standstill)" label="또다시 제자리 (standstill)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Willy_Alberti/Omdat_Ik_Zoveel_Van_Je_Hou/</id><title>Willy_Alberti - Omdat Ik Zoveel Van Je Hou - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:53:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:53:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Willy_Alberti/Omdat_Ik_Zoveel_Van_Je_Hou/" title="Willy_Alberti - Omdat Ik Zoveel Van Je Hou - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Je bent niet mooi, je bent geen knappe vrouw <br>Jouw nagels zijn voortdurend in de rouw <br>Toch wil ik van geen ander weten <br>Omdat ik zoveel van je hou <br>Al zit je pak niet altijd eerste klas <br>Toch ben ik danig met jou in mijn sas <br>Wil van een ander nooit iets weten <br>Omdat ik zoveel van je hou <br>Wat verdriet mooi ben je niet <br>Zeker niet als je kijft <br>Ben geen plaat, schoonheid vergaat <br>Alleen de lelijkheid die blijft <br>Daar mot je maar aan wennen <br>Al zijn je kleren dan niet van satijn <br>Al doe je echt niet aan de slanke lijn <br>Toch wil ik van geen ander weten <br>Omdat ik zoveel van je hou <br>Al zijn je haren slecht gepermanent <br>En is het gebruik van zeep jou onbekend <br>Toch zal ik jou niet willen ruilen <br>Omdat ik zoveel van je hou <br>Lief en leed, zoals je weet <br>Deel ik altijd met jou <br>Ik weet heel goed hoe jij dat doet <br>Je geeft de narigheid aan mij <br>Dat heb ik steeds geweten <br>Al ben je dan vaak een rare man <br>Al denk ik soms dat je enkel schelden kan <br>Toch kan slechts Magere Hein ons scheiden <br>Omdat ik zoveel van je hou]]></content><category term="Willy Alberti" label="Willy Alberti"/><category term="Omdat Ik Zoveel Van Je Hou" label="Omdat Ik Zoveel Van Je Hou"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Enca/Love_On_My_Body/</id><title>Enca - Love On My Body - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:56:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:56:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Enca/Love_On_My_Body/" title="Enca - Love On My Body - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby boy you got me thinking about you <br>About you,about you <br>Got me feeling like I can't be without you <br>Without You,Without You <br><br>You're the reason we don't talk to more <br>You don't wanna stay don't wanna go <br>But Im tipsy and emotional <br>I just wanna call to let you know <br><br>I got your love on my body <br>I got your love on my body <br>Got your love on my body <br>I got your love on my body <br><br>Baby no one else can touch me the way you do <br>I need you,right now <br>Baby no one else can make me forget you <br>Forget you, forget you <br><br>Im the reason we don't talk no more <br>I messed up too many times before <br>But Im tipsy and emotional <br>I just wanna call to let you know <br><br>I got your love on my body <br>I got your love on my body <br>Got your love on my body <br>I got your love on my body <br><br>I miss you so bad <br>Miss you like I never missed somebody <br>Just want you to know <br>Still got your loving on my body <br><br>Loving,loving on my body <br>I got you,I got you,I got you with me <br>But you're not with me,you're not with me <br>Loving,loving on my body <br><br>I got your love on my body <br>I got your love on my body <br>Got your love on my body <br>I got your love on my body]]></content><category term="Enca" label="Enca"/><category term="Love On My Body" label="Love On My Body"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제이켠/흠뻑_Feat_Cherry_Coke/</id><title>제이켠 - 흠뻑 (Feat. Cherry Coke) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:56:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:56:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%EC%BC%A0/%ED%9D%A0%EB%BB%91_Feat_Cherry_Coke/" title="제이켠 - 흠뻑 (Feat. Cherry Coke) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby I'm crying <br>No baby I don't cry <br>I'm wet with you <br>You should be my home baby <br>Let me be <br>walk and talk &amp; walk and talk baby <br>나와 걸을 땐 더 딱 붙어 maybe <br>아마 너를 만나지 못했더라면 <br>저기 쟤들과 난 술을 <br>퍼 마시고 있었겠지 right <br>언젠가 난 너를 <br>태우고 달리고 싶어 <br>천장을 열고 올림픽대로 <br>도쿄 하와이 서울 배경 <br>Let's ride baby <br>로켓을 쏴 저 멀리 <br>떠나자 여길 요즘 아이폰에 널린 <br>인스타 피드에 몸매 <br>자랑하는 애들을 <br>창피하게 만드네 <br>팔다리 길이 whoo <br>oh see oh see <br>지성이 묻어있는 말투와 동시에 <br>음악을 사랑하는 몸짓 <br>거기서 난 멈칫 yeah <br>Baby I'm crying <br>No baby I don't cry <br>I'm wet with you <br>You should be my home baby <br>듀스 스냅댄스 <br>옥상 옐로 페인트 <br>두꺼운 입술 립밤은 필요 없지 <br>키스 키스 키스 <br>우리 사이 시놉시스 <br>가난해도 행복하다는 건 거짓말 <br>그래도 우린 멋진 <br>꿈을 꿀 줄 아니까 <br>쉬지 않고 울려대는 전화 마림바 <br>페이스타임 우린 매일 하니까 <br>day all day all <br>중요하게 다뤄 사소한 내용 <br>day all day all day all <br>진짜 고려하고 있어 너를 채용 <br>하려 해 너의 하루에 절반을 <br>내가 전부 다 쓰고 싶으니까 <br>이런 말 싫어하지 넌 이쁘니까 <br>흠뻑 빠져 헤엄해 <br>Baby I'm crying <br>No baby I don't cry <br>I'm wet with you <br>You should be my home baby <br>흠뻑 빠져 흠뻑 yeah <br>흠뻑 빠져 흠뻑 yeah <br>헤엄치고 있어 너의 마음에 <br>원한다면 술을 끊어볼게 <br>Let me know 너 눈떴을 때 <br>우리가 더 많이 <br>닮아있었음 좋겠어 <br>빅웨이브 브로콜리 Let's ride <br>Baby I'm crying <br>No baby I don't cry <br>I'm wet with you <br>You should be my home baby <br>Baby I'm crying <br>No baby I don't cry <br>I'm wet with you <br>You should be my home baby <br>it's okay <br>]]></content><category term="제이켠" label="제이켠"/><category term="흠뻑 (Feat. Cherry Coke)" label="흠뻑 (Feat. Cherry Coke)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joe_Williams/Get_Out_Of_My_Life_Woman/</id><title>Joe_Williams - Get Out Of My Life Woman - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:56:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:56:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joe_Williams/Get_Out_Of_My_Life_Woman/" title="Joe_Williams - Get Out Of My Life Woman - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You don't love me no more <br>Get out my life woman <br>You don't love me no more <br>Get out my life woman <br>You don't love me no more <br><br>Get out my eyes teardrops <br>I got to see my way around <br>Get out my eyes teardrops <br>I got to see my way around <br>Get out my life, heartaches <br>Nothin' but heartaches by the pound <br><br>Get off my ladder, woman <br>I got to climb up to the top <br>Get off my ladder, woman <br>There is nothin that can make me stop <br><br>Get out the way, woman <br>I got to be movin' on <br>Get out the way, woman <br>I got to be movin' on <br>Get out the way, woman <br>I got to be movin' on <br><br>I'm sorry I've got leave you]]></content><category term="Joe Williams" label="Joe Williams"/><category term="Get Out Of My Life Woman" label="Get Out Of My Life Woman"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Donald_Byrd/Fallin_Like_Dominoes/</id><title>Donald_Byrd - (Fallin` Like) Dominoes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:56:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:56:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Donald_Byrd/Fallin_Like_Dominoes/" title="Donald_Byrd - (Fallin` Like) Dominoes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A pretty baby dry your eyes don't you know it can't be that bad <br>Oh, how it hurts me pretty baby when I see you sittin' there so sad <br>No need to worry 'bout tomorrow, and yesterday is gone <br><br>So raise your chin up girl, and we can work our problems out one by one <br><br>Hold me tight Hold me tight <br>Don't let go <br>Turn me loose <br>Never no, no, no <br>We'll stand our problems all in a row <br>Watch them fall, like dominoes <br><br>A pretty baby dry your eyes don't you know it can't be that bad <br>Oh, how it hurts me pretty baby when I see you sittin' there so sad <br>One day you're gonna hear me say, that everything's alright <br>So let's not worry 'bout tomorrow while we got each other here tonight]]></content><category term="Donald Byrd" label="Donald Byrd"/><category term="(Fallin` Like) Dominoes" label="(Fallin` Like) Dominoes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Grant_Green/Down_Here_On_The_Ground_Live/</id><title>Grant_Green - Down Here On The Ground (Live) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:56:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:56:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Grant_Green/Down_Here_On_The_Ground_Live/" title="Grant_Green - Down Here On The Ground (Live) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Down here on the ground <br>It ain't no place for living <br>No, no, no <br>Down here on the ground <br>Watching the sparrows fly high <br><br>I watch the birds <br>As they make their wings <br>Flying solid free <br>How I wish it were me <br><br>But I'm down here on the ground <br>And I'm wanting something better <br>I'm down here on the ground <br>Wanting something more <br><br>One morning soon <br>I will find <br>Some wings on my mind <br>To take me high <br><br>So if you hear a sound <br>From down here on the ground <br>My friends <br>It's only me <br>Trying to fly <br>Trying to fly <br>I would love to fly <br>Because I'm tired of being <br>Down here on the ground <br>I'm tired of being <br>Down here on the ground, yeah <br><br>One morning soon <br>I gotta find <br>Some wings on my mind <br>Wings to take me high <br><br>So if you hear a sound <br>If you hear a sound <br>From down here on the ground <br>I said my friends <br>It's only me <br>I will be trying to fly <br>Trying to fly <br>Live a bird I would love to fly <br>Because I'm tired of being <br>Down here on the ground <br>Yes I'm tired of being <br>Down here on the ground, yeah]]></content><category term="Grant Green" label="Grant Green"/><category term="Down Here On The Ground (Live)" label="Down Here On The Ground (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nancy_Wilson/Son_Of_A_Preacher_Man/</id><title>Nancy_Wilson - Son Of A Preacher Man - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:56:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:56:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nancy_Wilson/Son_Of_A_Preacher_Man/" title="Nancy_Wilson - Son Of A Preacher Man - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Billy Ray was a preacher's son <br>And when his daddy would visit he'd come along <br>When they gathered around and started talking <br>That's when Billy would take me walking <br>Out through the back yard we'd go walking <br>Then he'd look into my eyes <br>Lord knows, to my surprise <br><br>The only one who could ever reach me <br>Was the son of a preacher man <br>The only boy who could ever teach me <br>Was the son of a preacher man <br>Yes he was, he was, ooh, yes he was <br><br>Being good isn't always easy <br>No matter how hard I try <br>When he started sweet talking to me <br>He'd come and tell me Everything is all right <br>He'd kiss and tell me Everything is all right <br>Can I get away again tonight <br><br>The only one who could ever reach me <br>Was the son of a preacher man <br>The only boy who could ever teach me <br><br>Was the son of a preacher man <br>Yes he was, he was, ooh, yes he was yes he was <br><br>How well I remember <br>The look that was in his eyes <br>Stealing kisses from me on the sly <br>Taking time to make time <br>Telling me that he's all mine <br>Learning from each other's knowing <br>Looking to see how much we've grown and <br><br>The only one who could ever reach me <br>Was the son of a preacher man <br>The only boy who could ever teach me <br>Was the son of a preacher man <br>Yes he was, he was, oh yes he was <br><br>The only one who could ever reach me <br>He was the sweet talking son of a preacher man <br>The only boy who could ever teach me <br>Was the son of a preacher man <br><br>The only one who could ever reach me <br>Was the sweet talking son of a preacher man]]></content><category term="Nancy Wilson" label="Nancy Wilson"/><category term="Son Of A Preacher Man" label="Son Of A Preacher Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lou_Rawls/Youve_Made_Me_So_Very_Happy/</id><title>Lou_Rawls - You`ve Made Me So Very Happy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:56:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:56:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lou_Rawls/Youve_Made_Me_So_Very_Happy/" title="Lou_Rawls - You`ve Made Me So Very Happy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I lost at love before <br>Got mad and closed the door <br>But you said try just once more <br>I chose you for the one <br>Now I'm having so much fun <br>You treated me so kind <br>I'm about to lose my mind <br>You made me so very happy <br>I'm so glad you came into my life <br><br>The others were untrue <br>But when it came to lovin' you <br>I'd spend my whole life with you <br>'Cause you came and you took control <br>You touched my very soul <br>You always showed me that <br>Loving you was where it's at <br>You made me so very happy <br>I'm so glad you came into my life <br><br>I love you so much, it seems <br>That you're even in my dreams <br>I hear you calling me <br>I'm so in love with you <br>All I ever want to do is <br>Thank you, baby <br><br>You made me so very happy <br>I'm so glad you came into my life <br>You made me so very happy <br>I'm so glad you came into my life]]></content><category term="Lou Rawls" label="Lou Rawls"/><category term="You`ve Made Me So Very Happy" label="You`ve Made Me So Very Happy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Donald_Byrd/Street_Lady/</id><title>Donald_Byrd - Street Lady - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:57:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:57:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Donald_Byrd/Street_Lady/" title="Donald_Byrd - Street Lady - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey Woman <br>Liberated Lady of today <br>Remember all our childhood days <br>Boy and girl we used to play <br><br>Free now <br>Emancipation is what you've found <br>Legislation put me down <br>What happened to yesterday <br><br>Woman of the world <br>Now that your eyes meet mine <br><br>You're where you want to be <br><br>You've come along way baby <br><br>Hey woman <br>Chauvinism's day is done <br>Now there isn't anyone <br>For you to look up to <br><br>Hey lady <br>If independence is your thing <br>You've got the world on a string <br>Go out and take your turn <br><br>Woman of the world <br>Where would you prefer me now <br>After all we've done together <br>You want to pull away now <br><br>You've come a long way baby]]></content><category term="Donald Byrd" label="Donald Byrd"/><category term="Street Lady" label="Street Lady"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박재정/마법의_성/</id><title>박재정 - 마법의 성 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:57:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:57:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EC%A0%95/%EB%A7%88%EB%B2%95%EC%9D%98_%EC%84%B1/" title="박재정 - 마법의 성 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[믿을 수 있나요 <br>나의 꿈속에서 <br>너는 마법에 빠진 공주란 걸 <br>언제나 너를 향한 몸짓에 <br>수많은 어려움뿐이지만 <br>그러나 언제나 <br>굳은 다짐뿐이죠 <br>다시 너를 구하고 말 거라고 <br>두 손을 모아 기도했죠 <br>끝없는 용기와 지혜 달라고 <br>마법의 성을 지나 늪을 건너 <br>어둠의 동굴 속 <br>멀리 그대가 보여 <br>이제 나의 손을 잡아보아요 <br>우리의 몸이 <br>떠오르는 것을 느끼죠 <br>자유롭게 저 하늘을 <br>날아가도 놀라지 말아요 <br>우리 앞에 펼쳐진 세상이 <br>너무나 소중해 함께라면 <br>마법의 성을 지나 늪을 건너 <br>어둠의 동굴 속 <br>멀리 그대가 보여 <br>이제 나의 손을 잡아 보아요 <br>이제 나의 손을 잡아 보아요 <br>자유롭게 저 하늘을 <br>날아가도 놀라지 말아요 <br>우리 앞에 펼쳐진 세상이 <br>너무나 소중해 함께라면 <br>자유롭게 저 하늘을 <br>날아가도 놀라지 말아요 <br>우리 앞에 펼쳐진 세상이 <br>너무나 소중해 함께라면 <br>너무나 소중해 함께 <br>너무나 소중해 함께 있다면 <br>]]></content><category term="박재정" label="박재정"/><category term="마법의 성" label="마법의 성"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/장윤정/천생연분/</id><title>장윤정 - 천생연분 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T19:57:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T19:57:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%EC%9C%A4%EC%A0%95/%EC%B2%9C%EC%83%9D%EC%97%B0%EB%B6%84/" title="장윤정 - 천생연분 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나를 믿고 있는 너에겐 <br>정말 미안한 마음뿐이야 <br>이번 한 번만 용서해 <br>너무너무 예쁘다고 해도 <br>너를 떠올리며 거절했지만 <br>이번 한 번뿐이라는 걸 맹세해 <br>약속을 정하고 그날이 왔어 <br>신경 써서 옷도 입고 머리도 하고 <br>오랜만에 하는 소개팅에서 <br>무슨 말을 할까 고민도 하고 <br>널 만날 때완 다른 느낌에 <br>설레임을 안고 집을 나섰지 <br>날씨도 좋고 기분도 좋고 <br>아무튼 이래저래 좋았던 거야 <br>나를 믿고 있는 너에겐 <br>정말 미안한 마음뿐이야 <br>이번 한 번만 용서해 <br>십분 정도 먼저 도착해서 <br>어떤 남자일까 상상을 했어 <br>멋졌으면 키도 컸으면 좋겠어 <br>혹시나 하고 주위를 살피고 <br>흐르는 노래를 따라 불렀어 <br>드디어 내 친구의 모습 보이고 <br>난 수줍어 고개를 숙였어 <br>초등학교 동창이란 친구 얘기에 <br>인사를 하려고 고개를 드니 <br>내 앞에 있는 건 다름 아닌 너 <br>황당한 나보다 더 당황하는 너 <br>서로 믿고 있는 너와 나 <br>그냥 맘껏 웃어버렸어 <br>서로 용서해 이번만 <br>이렇게 예쁜 너의 곁엔 <br>이렇게 착한 내가 있었어 <br>우린 결코 헤어질 수 없어 영원히 <br>그렇게 미안해하지 마 <br>예쁜 추억을 만든 것뿐이야 <br>너를 사랑해 난 너를 사랑해 <br>사랑해 <br>사랑해 <br>사랑해 <br>그렇게 미안해하지 마 <br>예쁜 추억을 만든 것뿐이야 <br>너를 사랑해 <br>난 너를 사랑해 <br>난 너를 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="장윤정" label="장윤정"/><category term="천생연분" label="천생연분"/></entry></feed>