<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:28:22+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/웨더/쉬운_Feat_남지/</id><title>웨더 - 쉬운 (Feat. 남지) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:28:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:28:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9B%A8%EB%8D%94/%EC%89%AC%EC%9A%B4_Feat_%EB%82%A8%EC%A7%80/" title="웨더 - 쉬운 (Feat. 남지) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너와 다투며 했던 말 <br>거슬렸는지 <br>한참을 생각하다 <br>지나버린 정류장 <br>여러 번 여러 번 <br>너가 너무 보고 싶은 날 <br>전화를 걸어 <br>데이트 하잔 약속 뒤엔 <br>들려오는 네 말은 <br>나중에 다음에 <br>몰라 며칠 <br>괜찮은가 싶다 <br>또 며칠 덧나고 <br>보고 싶지 않아 <br>뭐 대충 <br>이렇게 잊고 살다 <br>아무일 없듯이 <br>연락 온 너는 <br>내 앞에 나타난 너는 <br>누구세요 누구시나요 <br>이렇게 쉽게 온 너는 <br>세상에 나쁜 너는 <br>누구세요 누구시나요 <br>애써 모른 척 웃어봐도 <br>네 맘대로야 <br>오늘만은 오늘만은 <br>오늘만은 바래다줘 <br>몰라 며칠 <br>괜찮은가 싶다 <br>또 며칠 덧나고 <br>보고 싶지 않아 <br>뭐 대충 <br>이렇게 잊고 살다 <br>아무일 없듯이 <br>연락 온 너는 <br>내 앞에 나타난 너는 <br>누구세요 누구시나요 <br>이렇게 쉽게 온 너는 <br>세상에 나쁜 너는 <br>누구세요 누구시나요 <br>애써 모른 척 웃어봐도 <br>네 맘대로야 <br>누군가 널 만나도 괜찮아 <br>이렇게 쉽게 말해도 <br>아직도 나는 너를 <br>기다릴게 늦어도 괜찮아 <br>몇 번을 다시 말해도 <br>내 맘은 너야 <br>오늘만은 오늘만은 <br>오늘만은 널 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="웨더" label="웨더"/><category term="쉬운 (Feat. 남지)" label="쉬운 (Feat. 남지)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/웨더/겨울_오면/</id><title>웨더 - 겨울 오면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:28:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:28:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9B%A8%EB%8D%94/%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8_%EC%98%A4%EB%A9%B4/" title="웨더 - 겨울 오면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[늦잠 자고 있는 하늘 <br>찌푸리고 있는 구름 <br>오늘은 만나기 어색한 날 <br>자주 가던 너네 집 앞 <br>너네 동네 담벼락 <br>이제는 서로가 익숙한 날 <br>스치는 바람에 <br>외로운 시간 쏟아져 <br>좋았던 추억 닿아도 <br>멀어져 우리 <br>시들어진 꽃처럼 <br>여름이 지난 사랑 <br>아름다운 노을처럼 <br>사라지는 사랑 <br>밤하늘에 별처럼 <br>만질 수 없는 사랑 <br>떨어지는 낙엽처럼 <br>헤어져 겨울 오면 <br>스치는 바람에 <br>외로운 시간 쏟아져 <br>좋았던 추억 닿아도 <br>멀어져 우리 <br>시들어진 꽃처럼 <br>여름이 지난 사랑 <br>아름다운 노을처럼 <br>사라지는 사랑 <br>밤하늘에 별처럼 <br>만질 수 없는 사랑 <br>떨어지는 낙엽처럼 <br>헤어져 겨울 오면 <br>]]></content><category term="웨더" label="웨더"/><category term="겨울 오면" label="겨울 오면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/에네스티/No_Mercy_Prod_By_lad/</id><title>에네스티 - No Mercy (Prod. By !lad) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:28:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:28:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%90%EB%84%A4%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B0/No_Mercy_Prod_By_lad/" title="에네스티 - No Mercy (Prod. By !lad) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지나가는 사람들의 표정을 봐 <br>그댈 보고 다 놀라고들 있잖아 <br>넌 알고 있다는 듯한 <br>표정을 짓고 있지만 <br>그대의 눈 속에 담긴 나를 봐 <br>아무 생각도 못 하고 있잖아 <br>넌 모르는 척 미소를 짓고 있지만 <br>I have no mercy on your body <br>네가 쳐다만 봐도 <br>I have no mercy on your body <br>눈을 뗄 수 없었어 <br>You have no mercy on your body <br>너를 바라만 봐도 <br>You have no mercy on your body <br>손을 뗄 수 없었어 <br>그냥 너와 눈이 마주친 <br>그 순간에 알게 됐지 <br>난 벌써 불안해 <br>난 내가 뭘 원하는지를 <br>명확히 알고 있기 때문에 <br>지금 지나가는 얘기도 <br>그냥 다 돌려 말하는 것뿐이고 <br>내가 정말 네게 하고 싶은 얘기들 <br>하나 둘씩 그 모두를 <br>말하기도 전에 네가 떠날까가 <br>난 정말 두려워 <br>정확히 말하자면 <br>말하지 못할까가 무서워 <br>물론 두 번째 눈이 마주쳤을 때 <br>나는 다른 게 무서워졌지 <br>내가 널 위해서 얼마나 <br>잔인해질 수 있을 지가 보였거든 <br>I have no mercy on your body <br>You have no mercy on your body <br>그냥 천천히 천천히 <br>지나갔지만 <br>또 미안하다는 말도 <br>이제는 필요 없다고 <br>시작도 하지 않았다니까 <br>반의 반도 <br>그래 걔넨 내가 지옥 같대 <br>그래 맞아 내가 지옥 같지 <br>남에게는 차마 <br>말로는 하지도 못할 <br>그런 상상을 오늘 <br>밤새 하고 있지 난 <br>내 눈에서 눈 떼지마 <br>물론 네가 잊지 못할 걸 알고 있지 <br>난 니가 제일 누리고 <br>있단 걸 난 아니까 <br>]]></content><category term="에네스티" label="에네스티"/><category term="No Mercy (Prod. By !lad)" label="No Mercy (Prod. By !lad)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Flo_Morrissey/Sunday_Morning/</id><title>Flo Morrissey - Sunday Morning - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:28:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:28:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Flo_Morrissey/Sunday_Morning/" title="Flo Morrissey - Sunday Morning - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday morning, praise the dawning <br>It's just a restless feeling by my side <br>Early dawning, Sunday morning <br>It's just the wasted years so close behind <br>Watch out, the world's behind you <br>There's always someone around you who will call It's nothing at all <br>Sunday morning and I'm falling <br>I've got a feeling I don't want to know <br>Early dawning, Sunday morning <br>It's all the streets you crossed, not so long ago <br>Watch out, the world's behind you <br>There's always someone around you who will call It's nothing at all <br>Watch out, the world's behind you <br>There's always someone around you who will call It's nothing at all <br>Sunday morning <br>Sunday morning <br>Sunday morning]]></content><category term="Flo Morrissey" label="Flo Morrissey"/><category term="Sunday Morning" label="Sunday Morning"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/담소네공방/잘_지내길_바래요/</id><title>담소네공방 - 잘 지내길 바래요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:28:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:28:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%B4%EC%86%8C%EB%84%A4%EA%B3%B5%EB%B0%A9/%EC%9E%98_%EC%A7%80%EB%82%B4%EA%B8%B8_%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%98%EC%9A%94/" title="담소네공방 - 잘 지내길 바래요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대를 지워야만 한다면 <br>꽃으로 지우고 싶어 <br>시간이 지나도 <br>향기가 남아서 <br>머물게 되도록 <br>그대를 보내야만 한다면 <br>바다로 보내고 싶어 <br>작은 종이배에 <br>내 맘 담아서 <br>흘려 보내도록 <br>꽃과 함께 너를 지운다 <br>바다와 함께 <br>너를 보낸다 <br>잘 지내길 바래요 <br>후회 없이 미련도 없이 <br>나는 참 우습게도 <br>그대가 남기고 간 <br>따뜻한 걱정들로 <br>하루하루 살아갈 테니 <br>잘 지내길 바래요 <br>후회 없이 미련도 없이 <br>나는 정말 우습게도 <br>그대에게 남기고 간 <br>철없던 상처들로 <br>하루하루 살아갈 테니 <br>잘 지내길 바래요 <br>후회 없이 미련도 없이 <br>나는 참 우습게도 <br>그대가 남기고 간 <br>따뜻한 걱정들로 <br>하루하루 살아갈 테니 <br>잘 지내길 바래요 <br>후회 없이 미련도 없이 <br>나는 정말 우습게도 <br>그대에게 남기고 간 <br>철없던 상처들로 <br>하루하루 살아갈 테니 <br>그대를 만나서 <br>난 사랑을 배웠고 <br>마음 다 해 <br>웃는 법도 배웠죠 <br>나보다 나를 더 <br>사랑한 그대여 <br>안녕 <br>]]></content><category term="담소네공방" label="담소네공방"/><category term="잘 지내길 바래요" label="잘 지내길 바래요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/메도우_Meadow/뻐근해/</id><title>메도우 (Meadow) - 뻐근해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:28:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:28:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A9%94%EB%8F%84%EC%9A%B0_Meadow/%EB%BB%90%EA%B7%BC%ED%95%B4/" title="메도우 (Meadow) - 뻐근해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너와 나 사이의 <br>거리감을 묻는다면 <br>아마 난 철창 안에 갇힌 새 같아 <br>하루 종일 떠들어봤자 <br>대답은 고개만 끄덕 끄덕거리네 <br>첨엔 넌 뭐든지 내게 줄듯이 <br>너보다 나에게 모든 걸 맞출 듯이 <br>지금 너와 나의 거리는 <br>시차가 너무나 커 <br>날 마주하는 위치는 반대편 <br>이제 너의 손을 잡기에도 <br>아무 말 없이 안아주기에도 <br>나도 너무 차가워 <br>너에게 줄 온기가 <br>남아있지 않아 <br>어떠한 감정도 아까워 <br>지금 이 순간에도 <br>넌 거짓들을 늘어 뜨려 놓아 <br>난 그걸 줍기에도 벅차 <br>잃어버린 시간 앞에 <br>난 멍하니 서있어 <br>악몽이라면 꿈을 꾸고 싶지 않아 <br>야 조용 조용해 <br>입만 열면 거짓말해 <br>뿐인 너의 말을 듣기에는 <br>이제 온몸이 뻐근해 <br>야 조용 조용해 <br>입만 열면 거짓말해 <br>뿐인 너의 말을 듣기에는 <br>이제 온몸이 뻐근해 <br>삐융 삐융 경찰차 불러 <br>너 같은 얘들 안 잡아가고 <br>뭐하나 몰러 <br>넌 나를 사랑하는 척 사기범에 <br>네 옆에 또 그 옆 옆에 공범이 많어 <br>몇 명이야 대체 나를 상대로 <br>바람난 너네들 <br>눈엔 난 그저 삐에로 <br>미로같이 복잡한 너와 나의 관계 <br>타임머신이 있다면 <br>널 만나기 전으로 갈게 <br>나와 연락이 끊겼던 그때 <br>넌 어디서 뭘 했는지 질문에 답해 <br>날 보며 웃던 너의 미소 속에 <br>주름 하나 없이 얼굴이 참 두껍네 <br>다시 돌아갈 수 없는 이 길의 끝에 <br>너를 밀어내려고 해 <br>거짓은 언젠가 탄로나 <br>진실 앞에 무릎을 꿇어 임마 <br>이제 진짜 사랑을 찾기 바뻐 <br>마치 울 엄마 <br>야 조용 조용해 <br>입만 열면 거짓말해 <br>뿐인 너의 말을 듣기에는 <br>이제 온몸이 뻐근해 <br>야 조용 조용해 <br>입만 열면 거짓말해 <br>뿐인 너의 말을 듣기에는 <br>이제 온몸이 뻐근해 <br>까도 까도 또 나오는 <br>네 껍질 그리고 <br>string cheese 같이 <br>늘어난 네 거짓 그리고 <br>없어진 염치와 눈치 <br>두루 겸비 그리고 <br>또 또 또 또 뭐가 남았어 대체 <br>널 대체할 여자를 원해 난 <br>너가 뭔데 날 떠나지 않으려 해 <br>미안해 이미 난 <br>너를 버린지 오래야 <br>곁에 있어봤자 <br>넌 불 보듯 뻔해 <br>불난 집에 부채질을 권해 <br>온 우주를 동원해도 날 못 구원해 <br>넌 빌고 또 빌어 잃고 또 잃어 <br>난 샤머니즘 같은 관계는 안 믿어 <br>너로 인해 난 책임감을 얻었고 <br>너랑 비슷하기만 해도 <br>절대 선택 안 해 <br>지금이라도 너가 못 된걸 <br>알아서 다행이야 <br>그만둬 날 좀 내비둬 <br>야 조용 조용해 <br>입만 열면 거짓말해 <br>뿐인 너의 말을 듣기에는 <br>이제 온몸이 뻐근해 <br>야 조용 조용해 <br>입만 열면 거짓말해 <br>뿐인 너의 말을 듣기에는 <br>이제 온몸이 뻐근해 <br>]]></content><category term="메도우 (Meadow)" label="메도우 (Meadow)"/><category term="뻐근해" label="뻐근해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/라지스몰/Tonight/</id><title>라지스몰 - Tonight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:28:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:28:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9D%BC%EC%A7%80%EC%8A%A4%EB%AA%B0/Tonight/" title="라지스몰 - Tonight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[좀 더 섹시한 밤을 <br>너와 담고 싶어 <br>오늘밤 너와 난 그저 <br>좀 더 섹시한 밤을 <br>너와 담고 싶어 <br>오늘밤 너와 난 그저 <br>하염없이 걷는 게 좋았어 <br>한마디 작은 손을 잡고서 <br>한없이 덥던 더위도 <br>막을 수 없었지 <br>그렇게 우린 딱 붙어있었어 <br>날씨도 질투 할 만큼 <br>또 우리만의 단어로 <br>채운 사전도 <br>곧 만들어 질 것만큼 <br>같은 채널 똑같은 주파수에 <br>타고 있는 것 같이 <br>우린 잘 통했어 <br>바로 swerving swerving <br>어디든지 좋지 <br>오늘은 운 좋게 <br>엄마의 qm을 <br>딱 몰고 나왔지 <br>무턱대고 떠나고 싶어 <br>맘이 탁 트여있는 바다로 <br>해변가를 단둘이 걷고 싶어 <br>아무도 없는 곳으로 <br>조용해 질 때까지 <br>더 조용해 질 때까지 <br>니 숨소리와 파도 소리만이 <br>귀에 들려왔지 Whoa <br>좀 더 섹시한 밤을 <br>너와 담고 싶어 <br>오늘밤 너와 난 그저 <br>좀 더 섹시한 밤을 <br>너와 담고 싶어 <br>오늘밤 너와 난 그저 <br>단순히 니 옷에 맞췄어 <br>니 색깔을 내 옷에 입혔어 <br>hey 옆에 있어 <br>morning morning <br>끝까지 난 <br>burning burning <br>이 리듬에 흥얼대고 있어 <br>다른 걸 바라진 않아 <br>니말 다 들어 줄 수 있어 <br>난 그런 사람이야 <br>끝까지 들어 줄 수 있어 <br>함께 있을 때 알지 <br>느낌이 좋대 <br>예전부터 알고 있었어 <br>I miss you hey <br>술을 한잔 더 마셔볼까 또 <br>너와 함께 있으면 좋으니까 <br>집에 가지마 오늘 끝났어 <br>I just pull you down <br>함께 있을 때 <br>알지 느낌이 좋대 <br>예전부터 알고 있었어 <br>I miss you hey <br>좀 더 섹시한 밤을 <br>너와 담고 싶어 <br>오늘밤 너와 난 그저 <br>좀 더 섹시한 밤을 <br>너와 담고 싶어 <br>오늘밤 너와 난 그저 <br>단순히 니 옷에 맞췄어 <br>니 색깔을 내 옷에 입혔어 <br>hey <br>옆에 있어 <br>morning morning <br>끝까지 난 <br>burning burning <br>이 리듬에 흥얼대고 있어 <br>]]></content><category term="라지스몰" label="라지스몰"/><category term="Tonight" label="Tonight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김윤진/내_영혼의_그윽히_깊은데서/</id><title>김윤진 - 내 영혼의 그윽히 깊은데서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:29:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:29:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9C%A4%EC%A7%84/%EB%82%B4_%EC%98%81%ED%98%BC%EC%9D%98_%EA%B7%B8%EC%9C%BD%ED%9E%88_%EA%B9%8A%EC%9D%80%EB%8D%B0%EC%84%9C/" title="김윤진 - 내 영혼의 그윽히 깊은데서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 영혼의 그윽히 깊은데서 <br>맑은 가락이 울려 나네 <br>하늘 곡조가 언제나 흘러나와 <br>내 영혼을 고이 싸네 <br>평화 평화로다 <br>하늘 위에서 내려오네 <br>그 사랑의 물결이 영원토록 <br>내 영혼을 덮으소서 <br>내 맘속에 솟아난 이 평화는 <br>깊이 묻히인 보배로다 <br>나의 보화를 캐내어 가져갈 자 <br>그 아무도 없으리라 <br>평화 평화로다 <br>하늘 위에서 내려오네 <br>그 사랑의 물결이 영원토록 <br>내 영혼을 덮으소서 <br>내 영혼에 평화가 넘쳐남은 <br>주의 큰 복을 받음이라 <br>내가 주야로 주님과 함께 있어 <br>내 영혼이 편히 쉬네 <br>이 땅 위의 험한 길 가는 동안 <br>참된 평화가 어디 있나 <br>우리 모두 다 예수를 친구삼아 <br>참 평화를 누리겠네 <br>평화 평화로다 <br>하늘 위에서 내려오네 <br>그 사랑의 물결이 영원토록 <br>내 영혼을 덮으소서 <br>평화 평화로다 <br>하늘 위에서 내려오네 <br>그 사랑의 물결이 영원토록 <br>내 영혼을 덮으소서 <br>평화 평화로다 <br>하늘 위에서 내려오네 <br>그 사랑의 물결이 영원토록 <br>내 영혼을 덮으소서 <br>]]></content><category term="김윤진" label="김윤진"/><category term="내 영혼의 그윽히 깊은데서" label="내 영혼의 그윽히 깊은데서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이연주/Happy_Day/</id><title>이연주 - Happy Day - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:29:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:29:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%97%B0%EC%A3%BC/Happy_Day/" title="이연주 - Happy Day - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기뻤던 날들과 <br>서운했던 날들 <br>끝나지 않을 듯 <br>했던 일들 전부 <br>사라져 없어져 <br>버리고 나니 <br>소중함을 알게 <br>돼버렸어 <br>너가 있던 날들과 <br>없어졌던 날들 <br>끝나지 않을 듯 <br>했던 우린 결국 <br>멀어져 잘라져 <br>버리고 나니 <br>웃음이 사라져 <br>버렸어 <br>나도 날 잘 몰라서 <br>의문이 들지만 <br>시간이 지나면 <br>언젠간 <br>행복해 질 거야 <br>기쁜 척 슬프지 않은 척 <br>해볼까 <br>해피해피 해피데이 <br>바쁜 척 충분히 사는 척 <br>해볼까 <br>해피해피 해피데이 <br>나도 날 잘 몰라서 <br>의문이 들지만 <br>시간이 지나면 <br>언젠간 <br>행복해 질 거야 <br>기쁜 척 슬프지 않은 척 <br>해볼까 <br>해피해피 해피데이 <br>바쁜 척 충분히 사는 척 <br>해볼까 <br>해피해피 해피데이 <br>기뻤던 추억만 <br>생각해두기 <br>슬펐던 생각은 <br>훨훨 털어버리기 <br>앞으로 행복한 기억만 <br>쌓으려는 <br>생각을 해요 <br>해피 해피데이 <br>기쁜 척 슬프지 않은 척 <br>해볼까 <br>해피해피 해피데이 <br>바쁜 척 충분히 사는 척 <br>해볼까 <br>해피해피 해피데이 <br>설레었던 날들과 <br>행복했던 시간 <br>그 시간을 넘어 <br>이제 날려 볼까 <br>이겨내 버텨내 <br>시간 지나가니 <br>이제서야 모두 다 <br>잊었어 <br>]]></content><category term="이연주" label="이연주"/><category term="Happy Day" label="Happy Day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_골드피쉬/커튼쳐/</id><title>Goldfish (골드피쉬) - 커튼쳐 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:29:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:29:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_%EA%B3%A8%EB%93%9C%ED%94%BC%EC%89%AC/%EC%BB%A4%ED%8A%BC%EC%B3%90/" title="Goldfish (골드피쉬) - 커튼쳐 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주황색 오후 너무 나른하지 <br>걷고픈 건 늘어선 <br>빌딩 위의 하늘이지 <br>저긴 도시와 <br>함께이면서도 밖에 있지 <br>색깔은 예쁘지만 <br>어지럽지 그라데이션 <br>지금 나도 저 색깔을 닮아있지 <br>바빴던 하루하루가 쌓여 <br>어지럽게 섞여있어 <br>곧 내릴 저녁 어둠처럼 <br>나를 덮어줄 휴식이 <br>절대로 필요한걸 <br>지금은 음 <br>chillin in the AGT's song <br>닮고 싶어 <br>내가 좋아하는 밴드의 멋 <br>what a liberalist <br>그들이 자유로운 건 <br>피곤하면 쉬는 것처럼 <br>무지 당연한 것에서부터 <br>나온다는 걸 뻔히 알고 있는 나 <br>망설일 것 하나 없이 커튼을 치고 <br>하루라도 멀리 보는 <br>사람들은 알 거야 <br>이건 끝이 아냐 <br>더 좋은 시작의 시작이란 걸 <br>All the people are <br>talkin about sunshine <br>누가 더 눈부실지 그게 다들 겁나 <br>달리기만 하는 거 아니거든 정답 <br>커튼 쳐 baby 커튼 쳐 <br>All the people are <br>talkin about sunshine <br>누가 더 눈부실지 그게 다들 겁나 <br>내일의 정답은 <br>누워서 보는 천장에 <br>커튼 쳐 baby 커튼 쳐 <br>엄마가 해준 미트볼 스파게티 <br>다음 디저트론 <br>네스퀵이 딱이겠지 <br>한동안 못 본 만화영화 타임 <br>말도 안 되는 줄거리도 <br>지금은 말이 되지 <br>아니 그보다 침대 위 시간은 <br>멈춘다던 누구보다 <br>신짱구가 한 수 위지 <br>이런 평화로움도 <br>곧 내 재산이겠지 <br>그리고 내 인생을 <br>하나의 여정이라 쳤을 때 <br>I don't wanna be a car <br>without a fuckin awesome brake <br>put on the brake <br>take a fuckin awesome break <br>쉬는 시간은 꿀맛이지 <br>이 맛은 좀 더 짙어 <br>왜냐 우리가 만든 앨범 <br>뭣보다 진해서 <br>단잠에 빠지고 낼 아침을 맞이 <br>커튼을 걷고 따스한 햇볕을 맞지 <br>복잡했던 머린 투명한 <br>탄산수 글라스 같지 <br>톡톡 터지는 원천은 <br>절대 끝이 없을 거란 걸 <br>All the people are <br>talkin about sunshine <br>누가 더 눈부실지 그게 다들 겁나 <br>달리기만 하는 거 아니거든 정답 <br>커튼 쳐 baby 커튼 쳐 <br>All the people are <br>talkin about sunshine <br>누가 더 눈부실지 그게 다들 겁나 <br>내일의 정답은 <br>누워서 보는 천장에 <br>커튼 쳐 baby 커튼 쳐 <br>]]></content><category term="Goldfish (골드피쉬)" label="Goldfish (골드피쉬)"/><category term="커튼쳐" label="커튼쳐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_골드피쉬/Personal/</id><title>Goldfish (골드피쉬) - Personal - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:30:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:30:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_%EA%B3%A8%EB%93%9C%ED%94%BC%EC%89%AC/Personal/" title="Goldfish (골드피쉬) - Personal - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 노래에선 찾지 말아줘요 <br>어떠한 공감대도 <br>이건 정말 personal track <br>누가 말한 대로 <br>너는 너고 나는 나거든요 <br>굳이 설명하라니까 <br>재미란 게 없네 <br>official officer 힙합퍼 <br>널 피해서 주피터 행 <br>하나같이 다 <br>똑같은 교복을 입고서 <br>등교하는 꼴 말해 뭐해 <br>난 플로우 탈 땐 <br>마치 personal jet <br>캔딛이 준 <br>지극한 personal track <br>하나부터 열까지 다 견고하네 <br>내 brainstorm 위 <br>해가 비추니 무지개 색 <br>and we fit like lego block <br>그 숫자만 세봐도 <br>하루 꼬박 걸릴 걸 수백 개 <br>꽉 막힌 새끼들 손 쫙 펴겠지만 <br>너넨 못 따라와 <br>이 personal gap <br>아 다르고 어 달러 <br>한 마디 조차 다른걸 <br>P E R S O N A L <br>우리 색깔은 진해서 <br>어딜 가도 다 바를 거야 <br>P E R S O N A L <br>]]></content><category term="Goldfish (골드피쉬)" label="Goldfish (골드피쉬)"/><category term="Personal" label="Personal"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_골드피쉬/Candid_Night_Feat_Owen_Ovadoz/</id><title>Goldfish (골드피쉬) - Candid Night (Feat. Owen Ovadoz) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:30:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:30:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_%EA%B3%A8%EB%93%9C%ED%94%BC%EC%89%AC/Candid_Night_Feat_Owen_Ovadoz/" title="Goldfish (골드피쉬) - Candid Night (Feat. Owen Ovadoz) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그림자 자욱하게 <br>덮인 하늘 아래 <br>난 한강을 보며 <br>미소 지었지 <br>모두가 잠든 하루 <br>꿈 꾸거나 밤을 새고 <br>깨 있는 자는 아마 <br>나와 같겠지 <br>아무리 생각해도 <br>난 잘못한 게 없는데 <br>왜 나만 가지고 <br>talking shit <br>걱정마 세네배로 <br>다 갚아줄 테니 <br>제발 신경 써라 <br>너의 앞길 <br>초등학생 때 내 <br>아버지의 부재 <br>어머니도 못 채워줬지 <br>내가 멨어 총대 <br>곱게 못 자라 왜 <br>나는 맞았지 형한테 <br>아 참 맞아 버릇이 <br>없어서 많이 맞았대 <br>look how I became now <br>looking all grown now <br>쓰지 고운 말 가식 아니야 <br>I'm all about <br>not getting upset <br>우리는 행복한 <br>생각만 하고 살지 <br>livin la vida loca <br>no 복잡한 소리나 헛소리 <br>난 내 갈 길을 가 <br>길을 막지는 마 <br>낭비할 시간 없지 <br>이미 난 다 <br>지나간 아쉬움에 <br>부족함을 느끼기보다는 <br>정진해 가 <br>악플러 임마 너희 <br>신경 안 쓴지 오래야 <br>왜 갖추지 못한 게 <br>너의 게으름이 아니야 <br>내 방향을 <br>탁상공론으로 논한다니 <br>funny how you criticize <br>when you a NOBODY <br>오늘 밤 따라 궁금한 게 <br>너무 많은데 <br>모든 것에 끄덕이기엔 <br>누구처럼 많이 크질 않았네 <br>We are candid tonight <br>솔직해 져봐 <br>말처럼 진짜가 <br>되고 싶다면 <br>Just be candid tonight <br>솔직해 제발 <br>조금이나마 더 <br>투명한 태도 음악 해봐 <br>조물조물 나를 <br>빚어내려던 손들 <br>이제 단단해진 <br>내게 대지 조각칼 <br>나 찔리라고 <br>나잇값을 물어내래 <br>근데 어떡해 <br>난 가진 게 코메디 <br>영화값 밖에 없는 걸 <br>자 다 가져가 <br>남 인생까지 <br>설계해주고 쫌 웃겼다 <br>너도 빠듯하잖아 <br>I don't know about <br>빠듯한 삶 <br>허나 빠삭 내가 <br>걸어 갈 방향 <br>Yes I know that <br>당연해 내 가치관도 <br>완전히 객관적일 <br>수는 없겠지 but <br>적어도 난 움직이려 해 <br>평평하고 넓은 곳으로 <br>편협한 예술가는 <br>never never ever ever <br>탐험가가 되어 <br>반나절 할애해봤자 <br>볼 게 아직 너무 많아 <br>밤은 금방 지나가 <br>바보들은 살면서 <br>느낄 수 있는 것의 <br>반을 포기하네 <br>아니 어쩌면 <br>그보다 더 NO <br>오늘 밤 따라 <br>궁금한 게 너무 많은데 <br>모든 것에 끄덕이기엔 <br>누구처럼 많이 크질 않았네 <br>We are candid tonight <br>솔직해 져봐 <br>말처럼 진짜가 <br>되고 싶다면 <br>Just be candid tonight <br>솔직해 제발 <br>조금이나마 더 <br>투명한 태도 음악 해봐 <br>Candid Gang은 <br>여기저기 탐험해 <br>누구 참견 따위 <br>받아주긴 바쁜 밤이네 <br>미래를 그려보지 <br>하늘 가득히 <br>별들은 환하게 빛나지 <br>우린 저게 돼서 <br>보여줄 거야 모두 앞에 <br>오늘 밤 따라 궁금한 게 <br>너무 많은데 <br>모든 것에 끄덕이기엔 <br>누구처럼 많이 크질 않았네 <br>We are candid tonight <br>솔직해 져봐 <br>말처럼 진짜가 <br>되고 싶다면 <br>Just be candid tonight <br>솔직해 제발 <br>조금이나마 더 <br>투명한 태도 <br>음악 해봐 <br>]]></content><category term="Goldfish (골드피쉬)" label="Goldfish (골드피쉬)"/><category term="Candid Night (Feat. Owen Ovadoz)" label="Candid Night (Feat. Owen Ovadoz)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_골드피쉬/Fun_Shop_Feat_Chef/</id><title>Goldfish (골드피쉬) - Fun Shop (Feat. Chef) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:30:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:30:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_%EA%B3%A8%EB%93%9C%ED%94%BC%EC%89%AC/Fun_Shop_Feat_Chef/" title="Goldfish (골드피쉬) - Fun Shop (Feat. Chef) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ladies and gentlemen <br>I welcome you to the newly <br>opened fun shop <br>starring the Queen Beni G <br>and Candid Creation <br>and myself <br>allow me to introduce myself <br>I go by the name <br>of Chef cookin up your <br>cheap ass sensitivity <br>let's go <br>Oh yeah <br>또각또각 부릉부릉 <br>많은 girls and boys <br>음악을 소비하지 <br>아마 보통 비슷하고 <br>뻔한 걸 알아 <br>우린 이쯤에서 <br>재미있는 걸 제시하지 <br>나는 경제학부 나왔지 <br>당시 바닥 쳤던 성적을 <br>증명이나 하듯이 <br>이 앨범은 <br>수요공급원리 무시 <br>그니깐 제한이 없대 <br>both 퀄리티와 크기 <br>언제든 drive or work <br>열정적인 play or love <br>whatever you do <br>we can give you <br>이국적 느낌 <br>맵시 있는 무드 <br>쇼윈도 그 뒤로 <br>새로운 실험을 해 <br>궁금하다면 리스트 위로 <br>tight flow <br>연년생들 모여 <br>make some good fun <br>so everybody buy this <br>we've got the fun <br>Go shopping <br>You've got the fun <br>And buy this <br>we've got the fun <br>Go shopping <br>You've got the fun <br>And buy this <br>we've got the fun <br>Go shopping <br>You've got the fun <br>And buy this <br>we've got the fun <br>Go shopping <br>You've got the fun <br>And buy this <br>buy this music <br>or you gon lose <br>트렌드에 휘둘려 <br>놓친 행복 지수 <br>I go by the name <br>of C H E F <br>내가 밝혀줄게 너희들 미래 <br>주인공이 되고 싶니 <br>duly noted <br>난 박명수와 <br>핀 조명 같은 노릇 <br>이 무대 위로 와 <br>너도 될 수 있거든 <br>20대에 다 해보자 <br>금방 와 서른 <br>hol up slow down <br>나로 말하자면 <br>나왔지 사범대 <br>영어교육과 hola <br>senorita chica bonita <br>잘 생긴 놈도 잘 들어 <br>내 경험담 <br>ain't no education better <br>than 실전 싸움 <br>and a trend's never better <br>than being happy right <br>센 척 하는 <br>여자 래퍼들은 몰라 <br>calling yourself <br>unpretty that's why <br>you rap pity so everybody <br>we've got the fun <br>Go shopping <br>You've got the fun <br>And buy this <br>we've got the fun <br>Go shopping <br>You've got the fun <br>And buy this <br>we've got the fun <br>Go shopping <br>You've got the fun <br>And buy this <br>we've got the fun <br>Go shopping <br>You've got the fun <br>And buy this <br>]]></content><category term="Goldfish (골드피쉬)" label="Goldfish (골드피쉬)"/><category term="Fun Shop (Feat. Chef)" label="Fun Shop (Feat. Chef)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_골드피쉬/Art_Class/</id><title>Goldfish (골드피쉬) - Art Class - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:30:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:30:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_%EA%B3%A8%EB%93%9C%ED%94%BC%EC%89%AC/Art_Class/" title="Goldfish (골드피쉬) - Art Class - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어린이 <br>너라는 도화지는 <br>누구보다 희고 맑아 <br>그림 그리기에 깨끗해 <br>누구든 첨엔 오롯이 백지 <br>허나 피하는게 좋아 <br>어른들이 손을 댈 때 <br>니가 말 안듣는 <br>애가 됐더라도 <br>이제는 함부로 <br>널 쓰지 못해 <br>chart of excel <br>니 손으로 크고 힘 있게 <br>눈앞에 보이는걸 그려 <br>kid life mindmap thing <br>지나치게 여러 번 <br>덧칠한 그림 <br>무겁고 건사하기 <br>어려우니 명심해 <br>잘 골라 니 그림에 <br>어울리는 색 <br>유행하는 크레파스 <br>고집하는 애들 색맹 <br>이제 계속해서 <br>그려 나가면 <br>너라는 커다란 <br>우주가 완성돼지 <br>space space <br>큰 그림 보란 <br>말에 멈추지마 <br>To infinity and beyond <br>더 크게 크게 크게 go <br>니가 그린 큰 우주 그림은 <br>별이 총총 해가 쨍쨍 <br>빛나는 인생 <br>Here's Light here's light <br>here's light here's light <br>니가 그린 큰 우주 그림은 <br>별이 총총 해가 쨍쨍 <br>빛나는 인생 <br>Here's Light here's light <br>here's light here's light <br>So i told ya told ya told ya <br>that I draw my own thing <br>내 말을 비뚜루 들었다면 <br>분명히 묻겠지 <br>내 스케치북은 <br>얼마나 채웠냐고 <br>한 층 더 멍청하다면 <br>베니갱 미술 했나요 <br>자 내 예를 <br>몇 개 들어볼게 <br>내 그림을 망치려면 <br>엄마를 위해 취직하면 돼 <br>반대로 내가 <br>음악을 시작한 건 <br>내 우주 캔버스에 <br>더해줬지 별 다섯개 <br>과거에 난 억지로 <br>볼펜만을 쥐었지만 <br>이젠 멋대로 붓을 들고 <br>획을 그어 휙휙 <br>어떤 어른들은 <br>여백의 미 쓸모 없다지만 <br>나한텐 구름 한 점이 <br>파란 하늘에 딱 이지 <br>y'all know <br>천천히라도 좋아 <br>진하게 그려낸 <br>내 그림들을 이어가 <br>큰 그림 됐다 해도 <br>멈추지 마 <br>To infinity and beyond <br>더 크게 크게 크게 go <br>니가 그린 큰 우주 그림은 <br>별이 총총 해가 쨍쨍 <br>빛나는 인생 <br>Here's Light here's light <br>here's light here's light <br>니가 그린 큰 우주 그림은 <br>별이 총총 해가 쨍쨍 <br>빛나는 인생 <br>Here's Light here's light <br>here's light here's light <br>]]></content><category term="Goldfish (골드피쉬)" label="Goldfish (골드피쉬)"/><category term="Art Class" label="Art Class"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_골드피쉬/봄_꽃_너/</id><title>Goldfish (골드피쉬) - 봄, 꽃, 너 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:30:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:30:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_%EA%B3%A8%EB%93%9C%ED%94%BC%EC%89%AC/%EB%B4%84_%EA%BD%83_%EB%84%88/" title="Goldfish (골드피쉬) - 봄, 꽃, 너 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[봄 꽃 너 oh <br>봄 꽃 너 oh <br>봄 꽃 너 oh <br>봄 꽃 너 oh <br>오늘 우연히 꺼내본 <br>니 편지에는 <br>봄의 향기가 잔뜩 묻었네 <br>내 코는 영리하지 <br>그 자리에서 대번에 <br>우리 어렸을 때 <br>기억을 추려내 <br>너는 은색 목걸이가 <br>달린 향수병을 들고 <br>내 혼이 빠질 <br>때까지 뿌려대 <br>아마 그 때의 향기도 <br>이 편지에 밴 것 같아 <br>오늘 같은 날은 <br>추억 물끄러미 <br>나한테 제일 정확하게 <br>너를 기록하는 방법 <br>너의 냄샌 <br>착하고도 부드럽지 <br>치크칙 내 옷 <br>위로 뿌려두니 <br>친구들이 의심 <br>학교 생활 <br>무슨 스릴러지 <br>이렇게 잊고 <br>있던 느낌들은 <br>학교 운동장과 <br>나무 냄새의 조화 같지 <br>향긴 너를 내 맘 속에 <br>영원히 묻게 해줘 <br>이 관곈 봄처럼 은은하지 <br>이제 피어오잖아 <br>나른한 봄의 향기가 <br>하루 잡고 우릴 <br>회상할 차례야 <br>이제 피어오잖아 <br>나른한 봄의 향기가 <br>우린 봄에 시작해서 <br>지금까지 왔잖아 <br>smells like 봄 꽃 너 oh <br>몽롱하게 흠뻑 <br>봄 꽃 너 oh <br>몽롱하게 흠뻑 <br>학교 끝나고선 <br>놀러갈 데가 많아도 <br>우린 복잡한 덴 <br>다 피해서 가자 <br>한강의 봄바람을 쐬면 <br>일년 간 나눠 느낄 수 있는 <br>따뜻한 뭔 갈 <br>채울 수 있잖아 <br>너랑 걸으니까 <br>난 무지 들떠있어 <br>난 벗꽃나무 기분은 <br>생각 안해 미처 <br>귀에다 꽂고 <br>찍어볼래 사진 <br>넌 날 말려 <br>꺾지말라고 대신 <br>서로가 꽃이 되어주자고 <br>지금까지 널 <br>꽃이라고 생각하는 중 <br>뭐 그럴만도해 <br>너의 향기는 <br>막 피어나는 듯 <br>향기란 건 손에 쥐어 <br>주머니에 꼭꼭 <br>접어 넣어도 <br>가질 수 없기에 <br>난 온 힘으로 <br>지금을 맡는 중 <br>가르쳐준 대로 <br>꺾지 않을래 너란 꽃 <br>바라는 건 내 곁에 <br>오래간 있는 거라고 <br>그거면 돼 <br>봄과 꽃과 너 <br>이렇게 연결되지 <br>매해 봄이 돌아온다면 <br>내게 넌 영원하지 <br>이제 피어오잖아 <br>나른한 봄의 향기가 <br>하루 잡고 우릴 <br>회상할 차례야 <br>이제 피어오잖아 <br>나른한 봄의 향기가 <br>우린 봄에 시작해서 <br>지금까지 왔잖아 <br>smells like 봄 꽃 너 oh <br>몽롱하게 흠뻑 <br>봄 꽃 너 oh <br>몽롱하게 흠뻑 <br>]]></content><category term="Goldfish (골드피쉬)" label="Goldfish (골드피쉬)"/><category term="봄, 꽃, 너" label="봄, 꽃, 너"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_골드피쉬/Full_Time_Job/</id><title>Goldfish (골드피쉬) - Full Time Job - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:30:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:30:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_%EA%B3%A8%EB%93%9C%ED%94%BC%EC%89%AC/Full_Time_Job/" title="Goldfish (골드피쉬) - Full Time Job - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[같잖은 지인이 <br>넌 되게 특이하대 <br>나한텐 물음표가 즐비하대 <br>난 순간 재미난 <br>구경거리라도 된 것처럼 <br>벙쪄 있고 말의 뼈를 <br>발라 음미하네 <br>이 대화가 계속 비뚤어지고 <br>초점을 벗어나는 <br>이유는 정말 괜한 게 아냐 <br>걔가 나란 인간 <br>풀지 못한 건 <br>아마 프레임에 갇힌 <br>두뇌가 체한 것 같아 <br>그 말은 결국 되게 <br>멍청하단 거야 <br>몸을 펼쳐 누워 봤자 <br>네모나게 뻗을 거야 <br>걔 침댄 딱딱하고 <br>불편할거 같아 <br>그니까 걘 꿈이란 게 없고 <br>불평할게 많아 stupid <br>요점은 이거지 <br>난 창의하고 싶고 <br>사고하고 싶고 <br>그 단계를 딛고 있어 <br>여러 번 말했지 <br>돈은 나중이라고 <br>근데 걘 같은 말이 <br>해질 때까지 물어봐 또 <br>Full time job <br>Cause I'm only 26 <br>Why don't you get a full time job <br>Cause I'm so so creative <br>Why don't you get a full time job <br>Cause your stupid job sucks man <br>Oh yeah Full time job <br>Fuck that full time job <br>Vocation is vacation <br>내 천직은 방학 같아 <br>Vocation is vacation <br>그 잘난 full time job 때매 <br>바쁘실 텐데 <br>내 걱정은 왜 또 해가지고 <br>Hey yo man what's up <br>How have you been <br>I do my music so huh <br>How do you do <br>난 작년에 혼자 틈틈이 <br>믹스 테잎 작업했지 <br>니가 준 비트보다 <br>훨씬 더 잘 타고 왔지 <br>후리한 대표님과 <br>음반계약을 맺었고 <br>잘 진행 중이야 <br>친구들과의 좋은 작업도 <br>그래 니가 예상했던 <br>내 스물여섯에 비하면 <br>너무도 잘하고 있어 <br>걱정이 과했던걸 <br>내 번역 공부에 대해 <br>시간이 없다며 <br>매일 충고했지 <br>다시 한번 물어볼게 <br>How do your music do <br>진짜 니 인생 걸어 볼만한 <br>full time job 인지 <br>니 음악 목숨 걸기엔 <br>값이 싸 <br>뻔한 곡들이니 <br>구글링은 하지마 <br>난 좋은 글을 읽고 <br>매 시간 새 발상이야 <br>이 가사 얼마가 될진 <br>아무도 모르겠지 <br>Full time job <br>Cause I'm only 26 <br>Why don't you get a full time job <br>Cause I'm so so creative <br>Why don't you get a full time job <br>Cause your stupid job sucks man <br>Oh yeah Full time job <br>Fuck that full time job <br>Vocation is vacation <br>내 천직은 방학 같아 <br>Vocation is vacation <br>그 잘난 full time job 때매 <br>바쁘실 텐데 <br>내 걱정은 왜 또 해가지고 <br>]]></content><category term="Goldfish (골드피쉬)" label="Goldfish (골드피쉬)"/><category term="Full Time Job" label="Full Time Job"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_골드피쉬/Sneakers_Hiker_Feat_Chef/</id><title>Goldfish (골드피쉬) - Sneakers Hiker (Feat. Chef) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:30:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:30:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_%EA%B3%A8%EB%93%9C%ED%94%BC%EC%89%AC/Sneakers_Hiker_Feat_Chef/" title="Goldfish (골드피쉬) - Sneakers Hiker (Feat. Chef) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey what have you <br>got in you backpack <br>빨간색 스니커즈 <br>check check <br>그리고 초콜릿 SNEAKERS는 <br>반드시 big pack <br>택 뗀 새 티셔츠는 <br>오로지 기분 낼 때 <br>이 여행의 취지는 <br>자유로움이 <br>main theme <br>난 감사해 모든 선생님들 <br>오해는 말고 교수나 <br>주변의 어르신들 <br>배워왔어 뭐든 천천히 <br>음미하는 법을 <br>내 느긋함은 안달 난 <br>지구의 허를 찌름 <br>우리는 눕고 싶으면 <br>눕고 아닐 땐 걸어 <br>떼를 쓰고 싶다면 떼써 <br>또 어제 몇 발짝 걸었는지 <br>얼마나 왔는지 세거나 <br>쟤 뒷꿈치를 쫓을 <br>필요 없어 전혀 <br>저 길가엔 꽃들이 <br>향기 진하게 나부껴 <br>그걸 느꼈지 <br>그래 난 이미 <br>소중한 걸 얻었지 <br>물어볼 테지 <br>얼마나 비싼 델 갔다 왔니 <br>F- Y'ALL 나는 <br>스니커즈 하이커 <br>이 기분이라면 난 <br>물 위도 걷지 <br>어디든 갈 수 있어 <br>sneakers hiker <br>발자국 지구를 덮지 <br>I do what I want cruising <br>down the sun <br>아니면 밤 홍대나 강남 <br>아저씨 가주세요 이태원 <br>like right now <br>맛난 이야기를 전해주는 <br>my time <br>sponsored by <br>under the limelight <br>난 팔고 있지 내 인생사 <br>경험담 from my life <br>히피스러운 만담 <br>그렇다고 까불지마 <br>없다면 깡 나를 만날 <br>이 노래 듣고 <br>다셔라 입맛만 <br>I be at LA downtown <br>공연하지 그리고 <br>그 다음날은 <br>uh uh uh chapter 4 <br>let's write some 역사 <br>계속 떨어왔지 점잔 <br>생색내기 적합한 성격 <br>이제 보여줘 <br>what I'm about <br>Beni G Candid and I <br>최고의 삼인방 <br>oh you didn't know <br>better ask somebody <br>이 기분이라면 난 <br>물 위도 걷지 <br>어디든 갈 수 있어 <br>sneakers hiker <br>발자국 지구를 덮지 <br>]]></content><category term="Goldfish (골드피쉬)" label="Goldfish (골드피쉬)"/><category term="Sneakers Hiker (Feat. Chef)" label="Sneakers Hiker (Feat. Chef)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_골드피쉬/ODD_Feat_Chef/</id><title>Goldfish (골드피쉬) - ODD (Feat. Chef) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:30:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:30:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_%EA%B3%A8%EB%93%9C%ED%94%BC%EC%89%AC/ODD_Feat_Chef/" title="Goldfish (골드피쉬) - ODD (Feat. Chef) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너는 좀 이상해 <br>난 그런 너를 좋아해 <br>왜냐면 지금 세상은 <br>심심하고 또 식상해 <br>나쁜 말로 하면 <br>하나같이 뭐 같애 <br>너와의 대화는 당분간 <br>쟁여놓을 마카롱같애 <br>don't give me 손사래 <br>난 오늘 밤 집요하네 <br>예의가 없었다면 <br>그거에 대해서는 미안해 <br>하지만 알아 둬야 돼 <br>너와 나 사이 <br>odd atmosphere <br>just feel it <br>흔치 않을 거 같애 <br>나는 딴 사람들 처지 <br>걱정 안 해 <br>다 커서 프라이버시 <br>성인으로 앞서 가네 <br>하지만 나 오늘만큼 <br>너하고는 나누고 싶어 <br>좋은 사상과 영감 적당하게 <br>난 가사를 쓰고 <br>음악을 만들어 <br>아마 내일부터는 <br>너와의 눈빛 교환만으로 <br>벌스 열 개를 쓰고 <br>새벽엔 창작욕 활활 태워 <br>이 느낌의 몫을 다 하겠어 <br>오늘 날씨를 묻는다면 <br>odd odd <br>난 별로라고 말하고 싶어 <br>odd atmosphere <br>솔직히 난 벌써 너랑 편해 <br>odd odd <br>날씨보다 다른 할 <br>얘기가 너무 많다고 <br>odd atmosphere <br>Feel this vibe <br>chill this out <br>Make it mine <br>make it yours <br>till we meet ourselves <br>with this freaky jazz tune <br>freaky jazz tune <br>freaky jazz tune <br>넌 너가 마이너인걸 <br>제대로 아는 듯해 <br>근데 그걸 티 내길 <br>절대로 두려워 않네 <br>오늘 내 호기심은 <br>열이 나서 타는 듯해 <br>더 가서 너의 키스씬 <br>궁금해하네 <br>너는 좀 이상해 <br>난 그런 너를 좋아해 <br>왜냐면 지금 세상은 <br>심심하고 또 식상해 <br>나쁜 말로 하면 <br>하나같이 뭐 같애 <br>너와의 대화는 당분간 <br>쟁여놓을 마카롱 같애 <br>chemistry chemistry <br>어떤 공기가 있어 <br>너랑 난 분명 이 기묘한 <br>분위기를 믿어 <br>odd atmosphere <br>그래프 그려낼 <br>도리가 없어 <br>just believe in this <br>look into it deeper <br>오늘 날씨를 묻는다면 <br>odd odd <br>난 별로라고 말하고 싶어 <br>odd atmosphere <br>솔직히 난 벌써 너랑 편해 <br>odd odd <br>날씨보다 다른 할 <br>얘기가 너무 많다고 <br>odd atmosphere <br>I don't know what's wrong <br>아마 우리 사이에는 <br>드럼의 부재 묵직함을 <br>못 줘서 그런 거 같아 <br>반면 아주 편하게 <br>힙합은 부랄 친구인듯한 <br>그런 기분 안에서 <br>with this microphone <br>I draw pictures <br>여기서는 예의를 지켜 <br>알아 난 이상해 <br>혹시 너도 이상한 걸 좋아해 <br>알지 너도 이 세상은 <br>심심하고 식상해 <br>Beni Gang knows it too <br>다른 여자들은 식상해 <br>Beni G understands <br>what it means to ride on <br>D-R-U-M 아마 내가 <br>아름다움을 찾지 못해 <br>헤매고 있을 때 나타난 <br>널 이해하듯 <br>아는듯해 그녀도 <br>대다수 잘 이해 못해 <br>so when I hesitate <br>between you and some girl <br>1분 1초가 아까워 <br>계집은 닿지 못하는 섬 <br>ask me if I give a f- <br>버스는 떠났어 <br>난 벌써 너랑 편해 <br>hip hop that's where I'm from <br>odd odd <br>odd atmosphere <br>odd odd <br>odd atmosphere <br>]]></content><category term="Goldfish (골드피쉬)" label="Goldfish (골드피쉬)"/><category term="ODD (Feat. Chef)" label="ODD (Feat. Chef)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_골드피쉬/Blah_Blah/</id><title>Goldfish (골드피쉬) - Blah Blah - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:30:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:30:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Goldfish_%EA%B3%A8%EB%93%9C%ED%94%BC%EC%89%AC/Blah_Blah/" title="Goldfish (골드피쉬) - Blah Blah - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Feel this vibe <br>chill this out <br>Make it mine <br>make it yours <br>till we meet ourselves <br>with this freaky jazz tune <br>freaky jazz tune <br>freaky jazz tune <br>Feel this vibe <br>chill this out <br>Make it mine <br>make it yours <br>till we meet ourselves <br>with this freaky jazz tune <br>freaky jazz tune <br>freaky jazz tune <br>Feel this vibe <br>chill this out <br>Make it mine <br>make it yours <br>till we meet ourselves <br>with this freaky jazz tune <br>freaky jazz tune <br>freaky jazz tune <br>Feel this vibe <br>chill this out <br>Make it mine <br>make it yours <br>till we meet ourselves <br>with this freaky jazz tune <br>freaky jazz tune <br>freaky jazz tune <br>지나가는 모든 것이 <br>기회가 돼 <br>어떤 단어 위로 <br>내 색깔을 칠해가네 <br>이 모든 process <br>to flow with Candid <br>난 얘랑 만들어가는 <br>중이야 new thang shit <br>I don't wanna cope with <br>불합리한 도시 <br>like 흔해빠진 직딩 <br>스타일 어중간한 용기 <br>so I 내가 느낀걸 <br>죄다 기록해 <br>내 뇌는 쉴새 없이 <br>되새김질 하지 지겹게 <br>blah blah blah <br>blah blah blah <br>blah blah blah <br>Say <br>blah blah blah <br>Say <br>blah blah blah <br>blah blah blah <br>]]></content><category term="Goldfish (골드피쉬)" label="Goldfish (골드피쉬)"/><category term="Blah Blah" label="Blah Blah"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노블레스/다시_또_겨울_Inst/</id><title>노블레스 - 다시 또 겨울 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:32:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:32:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EB%B8%94%EB%A0%88%EC%8A%A4/%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C_%EB%98%90_%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8_Inst/" title="노블레스 - 다시 또 겨울 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[12월의 바람보다 <br>차가운 건 이별인가 봐 <br>사람마음 하나 잡지 못해 <br>여기 혼자 남겨졌나 봐 <br>올해 겨울은 왠지 <br>혼자 있을 것만 같아 lonely <br>올해 겨울도 왠지 <br>널 기다릴 것만 같아 maybe <br>또 돌아왔나 봐 시린 겨울 <br>시간 참 빨라 또 다시 겨울 <br>그리워지네 그때가 <br>그리워지네 그녀가 <br>내게 남긴 많은 기억 그 중에 <br>겨울이 가장 추억할게 많은가 봐 <br>겨울에 가장 좋았던게 많았나 봐 <br>하고 싶은 말이 하지 못한 말이 <br>너무 많이 남았나 봐 <br>그땐 하고 싶은 말도 <br>해야 했던 말도 <br>가슴 안에 묻었나 봐 <br>오늘도 그냥 그렇게 <br>내일도 그저 그렇게 <br>따뜻함 없는 하루가 또 지나겠지 <br>미지근한 내 가슴은 마르겠지 <br>그때 남아 있는 많은 기억 그 중에 <br>겨울이 가장 추억할게 많은가 봐 <br>겨울에 가장 좋았던게 많았나 봐 <br>필요해 필요해 필요해 니가 <br>필요해 필요해 필요해 내겐 <br>필요해 필요해 필요해 누가 <br>필요해 필요해 필요해 니가 <br>니가 필요해 이 겨울이 가기 전에 <br>마지막 따스함을 안겨줬던 니가 <br>마지막 그 순간을 함께했던 니가 <br>12월의 바람보다 <br>차가운 건 이별인가 봐 <br>사람마음 하나 잡지 못해 <br>여기 혼자 남겨졌나 봐 <br>올해 겨울은 왠지 <br>혼자 있을 것만 같아 lonely <br>올해 겨울도 왠지 <br>널 기다릴 것만 같아 maybe <br>하고 싶은 말이 하지 못한 말이 <br>너무 많이 남았나 봐 <br>그땐 하고 싶은 말도 <br>해야 했던 말도 <br>가슴 안에 묻었나 봐 <br>필요해 필요해 필요해 니가 <br>그리워지네 그때가 <br>]]></content><category term="노블레스" label="노블레스"/><category term="다시 또 겨울 (Inst.)" label="다시 또 겨울 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/노블레스/다시_또_겨울/</id><title>노블레스 - 다시 또 겨울 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:33:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:33:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%85%B8%EB%B8%94%EB%A0%88%EC%8A%A4/%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C_%EB%98%90_%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8/" title="노블레스 - 다시 또 겨울 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[12월의 바람보다 <br>차가운 건 이별인가 봐 <br>사람마음 하나 잡지 못해 <br>여기 혼자 남겨졌나 봐 <br>올해 겨울은 왠지 <br>혼자 있을 것만 같아 lonely <br>올해 겨울도 왠지 <br>널 기다릴 것만 같아 maybe <br>또 돌아왔나 봐 시린 겨울 <br>시간 참 빨라 또 다시 겨울 <br>그리워지네 그때가 <br>그리워지네 그녀가 <br>내게 남긴 많은 기억 그 중에 <br>겨울이 가장 추억할게 많은가 봐 <br>겨울에 가장 좋았던게 많았나 봐 <br>하고 싶은 말이 하지 못한 말이 <br>너무 많이 남았나 봐 <br>그땐 하고 싶은 말도 <br>해야 했던 말도 <br>가슴 안에 묻었나 봐 <br>오늘도 그냥 그렇게 <br>내일도 그저 그렇게 <br>따뜻함 없는 하루가 또 지나겠지 <br>미지근한 내 가슴은 마르겠지 <br>그때 남아 있는 많은 기억 그 중에 <br>겨울이 가장 추억할게 많은가 봐 <br>겨울에 가장 좋았던게 많았나 봐 <br>필요해 필요해 필요해 니가 <br>필요해 필요해 필요해 내겐 <br>필요해 필요해 필요해 누가 <br>필요해 필요해 필요해 니가 <br>니가 필요해 이 겨울이 가기 전에 <br>마지막 따스함을 안겨줬던 니가 <br>마지막 그 순간을 함께했던 니가 <br>12월의 바람보다 <br>차가운 건 이별인가 봐 <br>사람마음 하나 잡지 못해 <br>여기 혼자 남겨졌나 봐 <br>올해 겨울은 왠지 <br>혼자 있을 것만 같아 lonely <br>올해 겨울도 왠지 <br>널 기다릴 것만 같아 maybe <br>하고 싶은 말이 하지 못한 말이 <br>너무 많이 남았나 봐 <br>그땐 하고 싶은 말도 <br>해야 했던 말도 <br>가슴 안에 묻었나 봐 <br>필요해 필요해 필요해 니가 <br>그리워지네 그때가 <br>]]></content><category term="노블레스" label="노블레스"/><category term="다시 또 겨울" label="다시 또 겨울"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/달무리/토토에게_온_편지_Vocal_미유_최준호/</id><title>달무리 - 토토에게 온 편지 (Vocal 미유, 최준호) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:33:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:33:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%AC%EB%AC%B4%EB%A6%AC/%ED%86%A0%ED%86%A0%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_%EC%98%A8_%ED%8E%B8%EC%A7%80_Vocal_%EB%AF%B8%EC%9C%A0_%EC%B5%9C%EC%A4%80%ED%98%B8/" title="달무리 - 토토에게 온 편지 (Vocal 미유, 최준호) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[햇볕이 반짝이던 <br>어느 고운 날 <br>왠지 온종일 <br>기분이 좋았어요 <br>작은 상자에 <br>작은 몸을 가득 싣고 <br>긴 여행을 떠났지요 <br>음음음 <br>통통한 볼에 <br>귀여운 까까머리 <br>동그란 안경 <br>날 바라보던 눈빛 <br>우리 처음 만난 날의 <br>당신을 기억해요 <br>너를 만난 건 나에게 <br>기적과 같은 일이었지 <br>말하지 않아도 괜찮아 <br>오늘 밤 꿈속에서 <br>우리 만나자 <br>그 어떤 재롱도 <br>아무 소용없던 날 <br>나의 위로를 <br>그댄 들었을까요 <br>당신이 많이 울던 밤 <br>그 날을 기억해요 <br>너를 만난 건 나에게 <br>기적과 같은 일이었지 <br>말하지 않아도 괜찮아 <br>오늘 밤 꿈속에서 <br>우리 만나자 <br>너를 만난 건 나에게 <br>기적과 같은 일이었지 <br>말하지 않아도 괜찮아 <br>오늘 밤 꿈속에서 <br>우리 만나자 <br>빨간 지붕 그 아래 <br>우리 만나자 <br>어젠 바다에 놀러 갔어요 <br>귀여운 사진도 찍었구요 <br>나를 잊어도 괜찮아요 <br>그래도 난 당신을 사랑해요 <br>여전히 난 당신을 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="달무리" label="달무리"/><category term="토토에게 온 편지 (Vocal 미유, 최준호)" label="토토에게 온 편지 (Vocal 미유, 최준호)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kiesza/Dearly_Beloved/</id><title>Kiesza - Dearly Beloved - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:33:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:33:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kiesza/Dearly_Beloved/" title="Kiesza - Dearly Beloved - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm lost, so lost trying to find a way <br>To you, been so long since you tempted me <br>So sure, the way that I feel <br>Oh, it's got to be for real <br><br>Suffocating love, I need to escape <br>I can barely breathe in this empty space <br>I need you to take me before I fade away <br><br>For you I will fall <br>For you I would lose it all <br>For you great or small <br>Dearly beloved, anything that you want <br>Anything that you want <br><br>Dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>Dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>Dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>Dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br><br>Been rough <br>So rough wondering what you want <br>With me <br>Been so tough everyday that you're gone <br>While I fight the way that I feel <br>Oh it's got to be for real <br><br>Suffocating love, I need to escape <br>I can barely breathe in this empty space <br>I need you to take me before I fade away <br><br>For you I will fall <br>For you I would lose it all <br>For you great or small <br>Dearly beloved anything that you want <br><br>Anything that you want <br>I will make it true <br>Because I'd rather drown in a sea of you <br>Than to drift away in the empty truth <br><br>Dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>Dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>Dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>Dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>Dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br><br>For you I will fall <br>dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>For you I would lose it all <br>dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>For you, great or small <br>dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>Dearly beloved, anything that you want <br>dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>For you <br>dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>Anything that you want, for you <br>dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>dearly beloved, dearly beloved <br>Anything that you want, anything that you want]]></content><category term="Kiesza" label="Kiesza"/><category term="Dearly Beloved" label="Dearly Beloved"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/니드_NEed/넌_그래_Feat_하늘/</id><title>니드 (NEed) - 넌 그래 (Feat. 하늘) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:34:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:34:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%88%EB%93%9C_NEed/%EB%84%8C_%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%98_Feat_%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98/" title="니드 (NEed) - 넌 그래 (Feat. 하늘) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 하루종일 <br>니 얼굴 떠올라 <br>손에 잡히는 일들이 <br>하나도 없어 <br>어쩔 수 없나봐 <br>말해야 하나봐 <br>어느새 나도 <br>모르게 빠진건가봐 <br>차가운 바람도 <br>우릴 입 맞추게 하고 <br>창넘어 들어온 햇살도 <br>우릴 끌어안아 <br>넌 그래 매일 같던 <br>하루를 꿈꾸게 해 <br>요즘 매일같이 <br>니 생각 밀려와 <br>맘에 드는 옷 고르기가 <br>너무 힘들어 <br>어쩔 수 없나봐 <br>설레는 이 맘 <br>어느새 나도 모르게 <br>웃음이 나나봐 <br>어두운 겨울밤 <br>우릴 손잡게 하고 <br>골목에 들어오는 달빛에 <br>우린 따스해져 <br>넌 그래 매일 같던 <br>그 길을 새롭게 해 <br>우아하고 아늑해져 <br>너와 함께 있는 곳엔 <br>넌 그래 <br>아름답고 행복해져 <br>내 곁에 니가 있으면 <br>넌 그래 <br>향기롭고 따스해져 <br>너를 감싸 안을 때면 <br>니가 그래 <br>설레이고 두근거려 <br>내 이름을 부를 때면 <br>너가 그래 <br>눈빛 입술 머릿결 마저 <br>햇살에 비춰 <br>눈부시게 하고 <br>황홀하게 만들어 <br>수줍은 미소를 <br>내게 선물해줄 때면 <br>나 미쳐버릴 것만 같아 <br>우아하고 아늑해져 <br>너와 함께 있는 곳엔 <br>넌 그래 <br>아름답고 행복해져 <br>내 곁에 니가 있으면 <br>넌 그래 <br>향기롭고 따스해져 <br>너를 감싸 안을 때면 <br>니가 그래 <br>설레이고 두근거려 <br>내 이름을 부를 때면 <br>너가 그래 <br>우아하고 아늑해져 <br>너와 함께 있는 곳엔 <br>넌 그래 <br>아름답고 행복해져 <br>내 곁에 니가 있으면 <br>넌 그래 <br>향기롭고 따스해져 <br>너를 감싸 안을 때면 <br>니가 그래 <br>설레이고 두근거려 <br>내 이름을 부를 때면 <br>너가 그래 <br>넌 그래 <br>넌 그래 <br>니가 그래 <br>넌 그래 <br>]]></content><category term="니드 (NEed)" label="니드 (NEed)"/><category term="넌 그래 (Feat. 하늘)" label="넌 그래 (Feat. 하늘)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sianna/Havre_De_Paix/</id><title>Sianna - Havre De Paix - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:34:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:34:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sianna/Havre_De_Paix/" title="Sianna - Havre De Paix - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Appuie sur play mec faut que tu m'ecoutes <br>Des vrais amis y'en a pas beaucoup <br>Il t'appelle frere t'es meme pas son couz' <br>Il encaisse l'argent toi t'encaisses les coups <br>Le temps s'ecoule vite pour la reussite <br>Le chemin est long mais la vie est courte <br>Je vais pas me laisser faire faut rester lucide <br>Face a Lucifer faut s'serrer les coudes <br>Le mal nous tourne autour et nos meres en souffrent <br>En bas de nos tours les petits sont determines <br>A se faire la guerre pour un bout de terrain <br>Sans passer par le notaire <br>C'est fini c'est trop tard dans le tiek's y'a trop d'armes <br>Previens tous tes contacts <br>Sors pas a decouvert <br>Conseille de mon comptable <br>Comme la bac defonce la porte chez toi quand on tape <br><br>Ici il y a pas de repit, noir est le drapeau <br>Doigt sur la detente, seul moyen de repos <br>La vie nous mene en bateau <br>Oui dans le mal je navigue <br>Il est temps de quitter le navire <br>Que je prenne en main ma vie <br><br>Tu crois vivre en enfer <br>C'est que ce n'est pas le paradis <br>Je vois des gens nager dans la merde <br>Et d'autres se noyer dans la tise <br>Y'a pas de valeurs sures sur Terre tout est relatif <br>Pour acheter un havre de paix ou un coin de paradis <br><br>Je suis trop terre a terre <br>Ils l'ont trop ouvert, j'viens faire taire les rappeur <br>J'ai deja tout gagne dis leur que j'ai plus rien a perdre <br>Qu'ils s'excusent c'est meme plus la peine <br>Une fois enterre personne manque a l'appel <br>Demande a Bernie je fais pas de cadeaux meme a Noel <br>C'est la douche froide il pleut des balles <br>Tu t'es mouille t'as pas eu le temps de te ve sau <br>Je te laisse dans ton bain de sang <br>Moi je suis dans mon bendo <br>Mais c'est pas pour autant que je vais me la couler douce <br>Je me demarque des autres <br>Vas y fais moi la passe <br>Je fais tourner le business la concu' se tourne les pouces <br>Je suis venu te prendre ta place, j'tabasse j'tabasse <br><br>Ici il y a pas de repit, noir est le drapeau <br>Doigt sur la detente, seul moyen de repos <br>La vie nous mene en bateau <br>Oui dans le mal je navigue <br>Il est temps de quitter le navire <br>Que je prenne en main ma vie <br><br>Tu crois vivre en enfer <br>C'est que ce n'est pas le paradis <br>Je vois des gens nager dans la merde <br>Et d'autres se noyer dans la tise <br>Y'a pas de valeurs sures sur Terre tout est relatif <br>Pour acheter un havre de paix ou un coin de paradis]]></content><category term="Sianna" label="Sianna"/><category term="Havre De Paix" label="Havre De Paix"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/남수와학스/사랑타령/</id><title>남수와학스 - 사랑타령 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:35:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:35:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%A8%EC%88%98%EC%99%80%ED%95%99%EC%8A%A4/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%83%80%EB%A0%B9/" title="남수와학스 - 사랑타령 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[불안해 하지 않아도 네 곁에 <br>모든 걸 빠짐없이 다 지켜줄게 <br>너는 말 안 해도 돼 <br>우린 천천히 서로를 알아가면 돼 <br>I don't know what you what but <br>전부 다 줄게 <br>I what you be my baby girl <br>넌 아름답게 매일 밤과 <br>나의 모든 꿈을 채워 <br>Will always be together baby <br>My love song moves your <br>body everyday <br>매일매일 보여줄게 <br>My love song moves your <br>body everyday <br>눈을 감아 <br>네 귀에다 속삭일게 <br>너를 위해 불러줄게 <br>매일 밤 네 안에 들어가 <br>사랑의 노래를 불러줄게 <br>세상 모든 게 다 <br>멈춰있길 바라 Baby <br>지금 이 순간은 <br>너를 위한 Party <br>My love song moves your <br>body everyday <br>매일매일 보여줄게 <br>My love song moves your <br>body everyday <br>눈을 감아 <br>네 귀에다 속삭일게 <br>너를 위해 불러줄게 <br>매일 밤 네 안에 들어가 <br>사랑의 노래를 불러줄게 <br>세상 모든 게 다 <br>멈춰있길 바라 Baby <br>지금 이 순간은 <br>너를 위한 Party <br>너는 내 꿈속에 들어와서 <br>하루도 빠짐없이 날 홀리게 해 <br>너는 잘 안 해도 돼 <br>지금처럼 옆에서 숨만 쉬면 돼 <br>I don't know what you what but <br>전부 다 줄게 <br>I what you be my baby girl <br>넌 아름답게 매일 밤과 <br>나의 모든 꿈을 채워 <br>Will always be together baby <br>My love song moves your <br>body everyday <br>매일매일 보여줄게 <br>My love song moves your <br>body everyday <br>눈을 감아 <br>네 귀에다 속삭일게 <br>너를 위해 불러줄게 <br>매일 밤 네 안에 들어가 <br>사랑의 노래를 불러줄게 <br>세상 모든 게 다 <br>멈춰있길 바라 Baby <br>지금 이 순간은 <br>너를 위한 Party <br>나의 전부를 걸어도 돼 <br>you are the only one for me <br>I what you girl don't you know <br>이제부터 마음대로 해도 돼 <br>Girl <br>]]></content><category term="남수와학스" label="남수와학스"/><category term="사랑타령" label="사랑타령"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amy_Macdonald/Dream_On/</id><title>Amy Macdonald - Dream On - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:35:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:35:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amy_Macdonald/Dream_On/" title="Amy Macdonald - Dream On - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ooh, ooh <br>Ooh, ooh <br><br>Never gonna be on my own <br>It's clear as the day <br>Never gonna cast my anchor out <br>I'm a free spirit, torn in a way <br><br>I can't stay here for too long <br>I got to keep on moving on <br>Nothing fades as nothing changes <br>This old place is driving me crazy <br><br>Live on and dream on <br>I'm on top of the world and I'm on the right track <br>I'm on top of the world and I won't look back <br>Live on and dream on <br>I'm on top of the world and I'm on the right track <br>I'm on top of the world and I won't look back <br><br>I was living for the weekend <br>And the drinks are on me <br>Skipping school and cutting out <br>I wish this world would let me be <br><br>Trying to catch a feeling <br>Trying to find myself <br>We ran out into temptations <br>Cause this old place is driving me crazy <br><br>Live on and dream on <br>I'm on top of the world and I'm on the right track <br>I'm on top of the world and I won't look back <br>Live on and dream on <br>I'm on top of the world and I'm on the right track <br>I'm on top of the world and I won't look back <br><br>I miss you when I'm gone <br>I'm still playing the same old songs <br>Dance like we used to do <br>But I'm better without you, better without you <br><br>Live on and dream on <br>I'm on top of the world and I'm on the right track <br>I'm on top of the world and I won't look back <br>Live on and dream on <br>I'm on top of the world and I'm on the right track <br>I'm on top of the world and I won't look back <br><br>The time to listen now, I cast my anchor down <br>I'm on top of the world and I'm on the right track <br>I'm on top of the world and I won't look back <br>The time to listen now, I cast my anchor down <br>I'm on top of the world and I'm on the right track <br>I'm on top of the world and I won't look back <br><br>Na na na na na na na na <br>Na na na na na na na na <br>Ooh, ooh]]></content><category term="Amy Macdonald" label="Amy Macdonald"/><category term="Dream On" label="Dream On"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Emil_Berg/Borde_Kanske_Dra/</id><title>Emil Berg - Borde Kanske Dra - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:35:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:35:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Emil_Berg/Borde_Kanske_Dra/" title="Emil Berg - Borde Kanske Dra - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Vi strckte hnderna mot himlen <br>Sa En dag ska vi n <br>Men vi slutade att vxa <br>Hller andan dr vi str <br>Du fick en notifikation <br>Och tryckte bort den lika fort <br>r det nu du brjat leta <br>Efter andra fina ord <br><br>Fr jag kan inte bara slppa att du ljg igen <br>Och som du sitter dr och himlar med gonen <br>Jag borde kanske dra direkt <br>Nr du sger du var full, det var en engngsgrej <br>r det verkligen s vrt att dumfrklara mig <br>Jag borde kanske dra direkt <br>Borde kanske dra direkt <br><br>Och det gick snett som fan p nyr <br>Fr mycket av allt <br>Tomma ord p tomma sidor <br>Och en blick lika kall <br>Vi ligger under brnda lakan <br>Ett outtalat slut <br>Knner grten smyga nrmre <br>Och brister till slut <br><br>Fr jag kan inte bara slppa att du ljg igen <br>Och som du sitter dr och himlar med gonen <br>Jag borde kanske dra direkt <br>Nr du sger du var full, det var en engngsgrej <br>r det verkligen s vrt att dumfrklara mig <br>Jag borde kanske dra direkt <br>Borde kanske dra direkt <br><br>Jag borde kanske dra direkt <br>Fr jag kan inte bara slppa att du ljg igen <br>Och som du sitter dr och himlar med gonen <br>Jag borde kanske dra direkt <br>Jag borde kanske dra direkt <br>Nr du sger du var full, det var en engngsgrej <br>r det verkligen s vrt att dumfrklara mig <br>Jag borde kanske dra direkt <br>Borde kanske dra direkt]]></content><category term="Emil Berg" label="Emil Berg"/><category term="Borde Kanske Dra" label="Borde Kanske Dra"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강태민과_노란샤스/아재개그/</id><title>강태민과 노란샤스 - 아재개그 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:35:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:35:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%ED%83%9C%EB%AF%BC%EA%B3%BC_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%80%EC%83%A4%EC%8A%A4/%EC%95%84%EC%9E%AC%EA%B0%9C%EA%B7%B8/" title="강태민과 노란샤스 - 아재개그 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 아재개그가 <br>대세 라고 하는데 <br>사실 뭐가 대체 <br>재밌는지 몰라 <br>웃기다고 하기엔 <br>뭔가 쫌 모자라고 <br>감동 있다 하기엔 <br>울리지 않아 <br>언제 시작 됐지 <br>모르겠어 <br>대체 이건 뭐야 <br>재미 없어 <br>말이 안돼 말도 <br>안 된다고 <br>어색한 말투 <br>촌스런 말장난 <br>그런 거 말고 <br>긴장 하지마 들어봐 <br>이게 내 진짜 개그야 <br>내 개그는 진짜야 <br>재밌어 <br>유머러스한 남자 <br>멋있어 <br>내 개그는 진짜 <br>미 미 미 미 미쳤어 <br>도레미 미쳤어 <br>아야어여 오요우유는 <br>고소해 <br>촌스런 개그 하는 <br>사람 많은데 사람 <br>들이 건설한 다리는 <br>구닥다리 <br>어제 빌린 친구 <br>책이 없어지고 말았어 <br>이리저리 둘러봐도 <br>못 찾겠어 <br>이방저방 헤매다 <br>내방 들어왔는데 <br>스탑 이게 내 책임감 <br>내가 하는 말 <br>웃지 않고는 못 버티는 말 <br>긴장 하지마 들어봐 <br>이게 내 진짜 개그야 oh <br>재밌어 <br>유머러스한 남자 <br>멋있어 <br>내 개그는 진짜 <br>미 미 미 미 미쳤어 <br>도레미 미쳤어 <br>아야어여 오요우유는 <br>고소해 <br>도래도래 고개 <br>도래 돌리지마 사람 <br>들 넘어가는 소리 <br>웃음 소리 <br>진짜 개그 <br>진짜 <br>진짜 개그 <br>진짜 <br>내 개그는 진짜야 <br>오 미쳤어 미쳤어 <br>아야어여 오요우유는 <br>고소해 <br>도래도래 고개 <br>도래 돌리지마 사람 <br>들 넘어가는 소리 <br>웃음 소리 <br>미 미 미 미 미쳤어 <br>도레미 미쳤어 미쳤어 <br>아야어여 오요우유는 <br>고소해 <br>촌스런 개그 하는 <br>사람 많은데 <br>사람들이 건설하는 <br>다리는 구닥다리 <br>미 미 미 미 미쳤어 <br>도레미 미쳤어 <br>아야어여 오요우유 <br>고소해 <br>도래도래 고개 <br>도래 돌리지마 사람 <br>들 넘어가는 소리 <br>웃음 소리 <br>]]></content><category term="강태민과 노란샤스" label="강태민과 노란샤스"/><category term="아재개그" label="아재개그"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승모/비정_부루스/</id><title>강승모 - 비정 부루스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:35:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:35:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%EB%AA%A8/%EB%B9%84%EC%A0%95_%EB%B6%80%EB%A3%A8%EC%8A%A4/" title="강승모 - 비정 부루스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지나가겠죠 아프다 보면 <br>떠나갈 사람 붙잡고 <br>매달려도 소용없네 <br>상냥한 말과 해맑은 미소 <br>그게 나에겐 전부였는데 <br>너 정말 가는 거니 <br>슬퍼서 몸부림쳐도 <br>널 향한 마음 뻔히 알면서 <br>미소 지으며 가는구나 <br>웃어지겠죠 울다가 보면 <br>가슴속에는 말없이 <br>가지 말라 애원해도 <br>무표정하게 모른척하며 <br>날 바라보는 너의 모습이 <br>너 정말 가는 거니 <br>다시는 만나지 말자 <br>차라리 내가 너를 보낼게 <br>이게 마지막 내사랑이야 <br>이게 마지막 내사랑이야 <br>]]></content><category term="강승모" label="강승모"/><category term="비정 부루스" label="비정 부루스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승모/잠시/</id><title>강승모 - 잠시 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:35:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:35:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%EB%AA%A8/%EC%9E%A0%EC%8B%9C/" title="강승모 - 잠시 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[살고 싶지 않을 때에도 <br>니가 있어 살 수 있었어 <br>너의 숨결 살아있는 한 <br>내 심장도 뛰고 있을 거야 <br>너만이 나를 살게 해줘 <br>멈추었던 나의 인생을 <br>너만이 나를 숨쉬게 해 <br>더 이상 바랄게 없는 당신 <br>잠시도 잠시도 <br>놓칠까 두려워져 <br>애타게 애타게 <br>기다리는 내 마음이야 <br>지친 가슴 눈물이 달래고 <br>너와 함께 끝내는 내 인생 <br>너만이 나를 살게 해줘 <br>멈추었던 나의 인생을 <br>너만이 나를 숨쉬게 해 <br>더 이상 바랄게 없는 당신 <br>잠시도 잠시도 <br>놓칠까 두려워져 <br>애타게 애타게 <br>기다리는 내 마음이야 <br>지친 가슴 눈물이 달래고 <br>너와 함께 끝내는 내 인생 <br>]]></content><category term="강승모" label="강승모"/><category term="잠시" label="잠시"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승모/아니_된다고/</id><title>강승모 - 아니 된다고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:35:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:35:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%EB%AA%A8/%EC%95%84%EB%8B%88_%EB%90%9C%EB%8B%A4%EA%B3%A0/" title="강승모 - 아니 된다고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그리워도 찾지 않겠어 <br>다시 네겐 가지 않겠어 <br>무너져버린 내 인생 속에 <br>더 이상 당신은 없어요 <br>가슴 치며 울고불고 <br>매달려봤지만 <br>난 정말 몰랐어요 이별할 줄은 <br>그런 당신 다시 내게 돌아온다면 <br>받아줄까 그게 겁이나 <br>아니된다고 아니된다고 <br>이제 그만 당신과 나는 <br>인연이 없다오 <br>가슴 치며 울고불고 <br>매달려봤지만 <br>난 정말 몰랐어요 이별할 줄은 <br>그런 당신 다시 내게 돌아온다면 <br>받아줄까 그게 겁이나 <br>아니된다고 아니된다고 <br>이제 그만 당신과 나는 <br>인연이 없다오 <br>아니된다고 아니된다고 <br>이제 그만 당신과 나는 <br>인연이 없다오 <br>]]></content><category term="강승모" label="강승모"/><category term="아니 된다고" label="아니 된다고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bishop_Briggs/Wild_Horses_Acoustic/</id><title>Bishop Briggs - Wild Horses (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:35:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:35:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bishop_Briggs/Wild_Horses_Acoustic/" title="Bishop Briggs - Wild Horses (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You hold me down in the best way <br>No quarter from these chains that I've <br>Slept on my heart for a feeling <br>Why can't I let my demons out <br><br>Keep screaming into the pillow <br>Cause your taste still gets me stupid high <br>Oh glory, I'm a believer <br>Oh glory, I'm a troubler <br><br>Wild horses, wild horses <br>Wild horses run faster, run faster <br>Run faster <br><br>Wild horses run faster, run faster <br>Run faster <br><br>You call my truth in the worst way <br>Through the dirty lands of a broken smile <br>And I swear I'm not a pretender <br>Sometimes it's love who's the baby's cry <br><br>So, I keep on damning the devil <br>And you keep on saying it's alright <br>Oh glory, I'm a believer <br>Oh Lord, I'm holding tight, but <br><br>Wild horses, wild horses <br>Wild horses run faster, run faster <br>Run faster <br><br>Wild horses run faster, run faster <br>Run faster <br><br>So, I keep on damning the devil <br>And you keep on saying it's alright <br>Oh glory, I'm a believer <br>Oh Lord, I'm holding tight, but]]></content><category term="Bishop Briggs" label="Bishop Briggs"/><category term="Wild Horses (Acoustic)" label="Wild Horses (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Handsome_Ghost/Brand_New_Colony/</id><title>Handsome Ghost - Brand New Colony - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:36:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:36:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Handsome_Ghost/Brand_New_Colony/" title="Handsome Ghost - Brand New Colony - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll be the grapes fermented <br>Bottled and served <br>with the table set <br>in my finest suit <br>Like a perfect gentlemen <br>I'll be the fire escape <br>that's bolted to the ancient brick <br>Where you will sit <br>and contemplate your day <br>I'll be the Water Wings <br>that save you <br>if you start drowning <br>In an open tab <br>when your judgement's <br>on the brink <br>I'll be the phonograph <br>that plays your favorite <br>Albums back <br>as you're lying there <br>drifting off to sleep <br>I'll be the platform shoes <br>and undo what heredity's done <br>to you <br>You won't have to strain <br>to look into my eyes <br>I'll be your winter coat <br>buttoned and zipped straight <br>to the throat <br>With the collar up <br>so you won't catch a cold <br>I I want to take you far <br>from the cynics in this town <br>And kiss you on the mouth <br>We'll cut our bodies free <br>from the tethers of this scene <br>Start a brand new colony <br>Where everything will change <br>We'll give ourselves new names <br>identities erased <br>The sun will heat the grounds <br>Under our bare feet <br>in this brand new colony <br>This brand new colony <br>everything will change <br>everything will change <br>]]></content><category term="Handsome Ghost" label="Handsome Ghost"/><category term="Brand New Colony" label="Brand New Colony"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Barbara_Opsomer/Cette_Nuit-la/</id><title>Barbara Opsomer - Cette Nuit-la - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:36:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:36:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Barbara_Opsomer/Cette_Nuit-la/" title="Barbara Opsomer - Cette Nuit-la - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Je ferme les yeux, je laisse en suspens <br>Le superflu, le jour qui nous reprend <br>Est ce qu'on attendra jusque la <br><br>Cette nuit la, cette nuit la <br>On se regarde, on laisse flotter <br>Entre nos levres, un gout d'inacheve <br>a qui fera le premier pas <br>Cette nuit la, cette nuit la <br><br>Je n'touche plus terre <br>Quand on se perd <br>Elle me devore <br>Cette nuit la, cette nuit la <br><br>Le ciel s'eteint, je suis eblouis <br>Les heures defilent et font place a l'envie <br>Elle brille plus fort a chaque pas <br>Cette nuit la, cette nuit la <br>Je me reveille mais tes bras n'osent plus <br>Le jour se leve, on s'est perdu <br>Elle nous echappe, elle ne reviendra pas <br>Cette nuit la, cette nuit la <br><br>Je n'touche plus terre <br>Quand on se perd <br>Elle me devore <br>Cette nuit la, cette nuit la <br><br>Je n'touche plus terre <br>Quand on se perd <br>Elle me devore <br>Cette nuit la, cette nuit la <br>a coeur ouvert <br>Je la laisse faire <br>Contre ton corps <br>Cette nuit la, cette nuit la]]></content><category term="Barbara Opsomer" label="Barbara Opsomer"/><category term="Cette Nuit-la" label="Cette Nuit-la"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/EGB_밴드/암연/</id><title>E.G.B 밴드 - 암연 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:40:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:40:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/EGB_%EB%B0%B4%EB%93%9C/%EC%95%94%EC%97%B0/" title="E.G.B 밴드 - 암연 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내겐 너무나 슬픈 이별을 말할때 <br>그댄 아니 슬픈 듯 웃음을 보이다 <br>정작 내가 일어나 집으로 가려 할때는 <br>그땐 꼭 잡은 손을 놓지 않았어 <br><br>울음을 참으려고 하늘만 보다가 <br>끝내 참지 못하고 내 품에 안겨와 <br>마주 댄 그대 볼에 눈물이 느껴질때는 <br>나도 참지 못하고 울어버렸어 <br><br>사랑이란 것은 나에게 아픔만 주고 <br>내 마음 속에는 멍울로 다가와 <br>우리가 잡으려 하면 이미 먼 곳에 <br>그땐 때가 너무 늦었다는데 <br><br>차마 어서 가라는 그 말은 못하고 <br>나도 뒤돌아서서 눈물만 흘리다 <br>이젠 갔겠지하고 뒤를 돌아보면 <br>아직도 그대는 그 자리에 <br><br><br>사랑이란 것은 나에게 아픔만 주고 <br>내 마음 속에는 멍울로 다가와 <br>우리가 잡으려 하면 이미 먼 곳에 <br>그땐 때가 너무 늦었다는데 <br><br>차마 어서 가라는 그 말은 못하고 <br>나도 뒤돌아서서 눈물만 흘리다 <br>이젠 갔겠지하고 뒤를 돌아보면 <br>아직도 그대는 그 자리에 <br><br>아직도 그대는 그 자리에..]]></content><category term="E.G.B 밴드" label="E.G.B 밴드"/><category term="암연" label="암연"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SV_김수빈/아름다운_이별/</id><title>SV (김수빈) - 아름다운 이별 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:49:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:49:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SV_%EA%B9%80%EC%88%98%EB%B9%88/%EC%95%84%EB%A6%84%EB%8B%A4%EC%9A%B4_%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84/" title="SV (김수빈) - 아름다운 이별 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 좀 소원했지 <br>날 사랑하긴 하냐며 <br>닦달하는 너의 입버릇 <br>수시로 확인을 바라는 네가 <br>귀찮기도 했지 <br>시간이 갈수록 <br>점점 커지는 <br>너와 나의 틈 사이 <br>네가 처한 환경이 <br>조금은 부담스러워 <br>솔직히 혼자가 되고 싶단 <br>상상도 몇 번 했지 <br>맘 한구석 너와의 <br>이별을 바랬는지도 몰라 <br>그런데 요 며칠 사이 <br>눈치 없는 나도 뭔가 <br>이상한 낌새가 느껴질 법한 <br>너의 달라진 행동 <br>어렴풋이 예상됐지만 <br>다른 남자가 생겼단 <br>그 말을 네가 <br>입에 담을 땐 조금 놀랐어 <br>스스로 놀라울 정도로 <br>덤덤하고 냉정한 나의 반응 <br>오히려 네가 <br>눈물을 흘리며 <br>뻔뻔한 말들을 <br>지껄이는데도 <br>왠지 화내고 싶은 <br>기분도 들지 않아 <br>현실감각을 상실한 <br>상황에 처한 너와 나 <br>행여나 이 모든 것들이 <br>너의 장난이었다고 <br>말하나 싶었지만 <br>그런 반전은 없었다 <br>그래 오늘에야말로 <br>내 인생에 처음으로 <br>신사적인 아름다운 <br>이별의 순간이다 <br>아니 너에 대한 <br>나의 마음도 <br>식은 건 사실이니까 <br>결국 아름답다고 <br>말할 순 없으려나 <br>나의 이성과는 상관없이 <br>공허한 기분은 어쩔 수가 없구나 <br>나의 이성과는 상관없이 <br>공허한 기분은 어쩔 수가 없구나 <br>겨울이라 그런가 <br>건조한 눈이 <br>따갑고 침침해 <br>집에 돌아와 <br>네가 준 인공눈물을 찾기 위해 <br>방을 뒤졌지 <br>가방 안에 몇 달 전 <br>위급상황에 사놓고 깜빡 <br>잊고 있었던 생리대가 나오네 <br>입술을 뜯어먹는 날 <br>위해 네가 준 립밤 <br>여태껏 몇 번 <br>바르지도 않았구나 <br>생각해보니 <br>이것들이 든 가방조차 <br>네가 사준 거잖아 <br>어느새 추억을 공유하는 동안 <br>네가 남긴 것들이 너무나 많아 <br>내 일상 곳곳에 <br>침투해있는 네가 <br>이렇게 간단히 <br>사라져 버릴 수 있다니 <br>지금까지 그리 적지 <br>않은 경험인 것 같은데도 <br>역시나 타격이 <br>전혀 없을 순 없어 <br>네가 그리운 것도 <br>다시 널 보고 싶은 것도 아닌데 <br>어쩔 수는 없네 이런 기분은 <br>나의 이성과는 상관없이 <br>공허한 기분은 어쩔 수가 없구나 <br>나의 이성과는 상관없이 <br>공허한 기분은 어쩔 수가 없구나 <br>몇 해전의 나와 같이 <br>격렬한 분노에 휩싸여 <br>개지랄을 하지 <br>않아서였을까 <br>순순히 별 말 없이 <br>물러나준 게 네가 <br>나에게 고맙다고 한 <br>이유가 될까 <br>여느 때와 다름없이 <br>너의 손을 잡고 집까지 <br>바래다준 뒤 <br>마지막 인사를 하면 <br>너와의 사진 카드비번 <br>모든 게 사라지거나 <br>바뀌어야 돼 뒤돌아서는 지금 <br>나의 이성과는 상관없이 <br>공허한 기분은 어쩔 수가 없구나 <br>나의 이성과는 상관없이 <br>공허한 기분은 어쩔 수가 <br>나의 이성과는 상관없이 <br>공허한 기분은 어쩔 수가 없구나 <br>나의 이성과는 상관없이 <br>아름다운 이별인걸 <br>아름다운 이별이야 <br>추잡한 끝을 보진 않았으니까 <br>나는 폭언을 하지 않았고 <br>너는 맘 편히 갈 수 있었지 <br>]]></content><category term="SV (김수빈)" label="SV (김수빈)"/><category term="아름다운 이별" label="아름다운 이별"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/장은숙/내_마지막_사랑/</id><title>장은숙 - 내 마지막 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:49:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:49:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%EC%9D%80%EC%88%99/%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%88%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%89_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="장은숙 - 내 마지막 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[허름한 술집에 멍하니앉아 <br>눈물로 술잔을 가득 채우고 <br>한잔두잔 마셔봐도 <br>취하질 않아요 <br>어두운 거리를 휘청거리다 <br>쇼윈도 거울에 비친 내 얼굴 <br>울다 웃다 주저 앉아 <br>나 이제 어떡해요 <br>주룩 주룩 주룩 <br>비가 내리네 <br>주룩 주룩 주룩 <br>눈물이 흐르네 <br>나를 떠나버린 사랑 <br>다시는 오지 말아 <br>내가 쓰러지지 않게 <br>다시는 오지 말아 <br>비틀 비틀 비틀 <br>비틀거리네 <br>내 마지막 사랑이 <br>주룩 주룩 주룩 <br>비가 내리네 <br>주룩 주룩 주룩 <br>눈물이 흐르네 <br>나를 떠나버린 사랑 <br>다시는 오지 말아 <br>내가 쓰러지지 않게 <br>다시는 오지 말아 <br>비틀 비틀 비틀 <br>비틀거리네 <br>내 마지막 사랑이 <br>비틀 비틀 비틀 <br>비틀거리네 <br>내 마지막 사랑이 <br>]]></content><category term="장은숙" label="장은숙"/><category term="내 마지막 사랑" label="내 마지막 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Se_Dejaban_Llevar/</id><title>Me Enveneno De Azules - Se Dejaban Llevar - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:49:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:49:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Se_Dejaban_Llevar/" title="Me Enveneno De Azules - Se Dejaban Llevar - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[el creia que todo era real <br>Y se conecto a la red <br>Se electrocuto <br><br>Ellos eran siete amigos y un blues <br>El blues era de amor <br>Ninguno lo consiguio <br><br>No se puede hablar sin voz <br>No se supieron entender <br>Se dejaban llevar <br>Sin preguntarse nada mas <br><br>el jugaba con sus munecas <br>Y ella con su corazon <br>Ella creia que lo haria primero <br><br>Ellos saltaban las lineas <br>Y ellas las pintaban en el suelo <br>Para saltarlas mejor <br><br>Para saltarlas mejor <br>Se necesita voluntad <br>Darle la espalda al sol <br>No es la mejor forma de hablar <br><br>Cual es el precio que hoy <br>Le pones a tu vida <br>Puedes llegar a ser <br>Lo que quieras si tu quieres <br><br>Andemos de cara al sol <br>Sin fachas, sin valores <br>Podemos hacerlo mejor <br>Si creemos en lo que somos <br><br>No se puede hablar sin voz <br>No se pudieron entender <br>Se dejaban llevar <br>Sin preguntarse nada mas]]></content><category term="Me Enveneno De Azules" label="Me Enveneno De Azules"/><category term="Se Dejaban Llevar" label="Se Dejaban Llevar"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Un_Dia_Menos/</id><title>Me Enveneno De Azules - Un Dia Menos - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:49:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:49:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Un_Dia_Menos/" title="Me Enveneno De Azules - Un Dia Menos - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Usa el maquillaje para esconderse <br>Su tiempo estuvo bien <br>Cuenta cosas que a todos nos sorpende <br>Si miente lo hace muy bien <br><br>Lo hace tan bien, que nos transporta <br>Hacia sus dias de gloria <br>Lo hace tan bien, que si es mentira <br>No nos importa <br><br>Usa papel de fumar, para escribirle al aire <br>Ella dice que la quiere <br>Es rockera, es hippy, es pop y siniestra <br>Y dice que vio a los Beatles en Las Ventas <br><br>Y eso esta tan bien que nos transporta <br>Hacia sus dias de gloria <br>Lo hace tan bien, que si es mentira <br>No nos importa <br><br>Le cuesta tanto reconocer que esta cansada <br>Sufre tanto si no estas alli para escucharla <br>Me gusta verla cuando el aire se lleva sus cartas <br>Ver su risa helada cuando acaricia su cara <br><br>Pero sobre todo, me gustan sus palabras, tan largas <br>Y es tan brillante que me ciega, cuando estoy con ella <br>El tiempo no me importa, aunque mienta <br>Y su maquillaje crezca, quiero que sepa <br>Que la creo, que la creo <br><br>Aunque hablas siempre y nunca escuchas <br>Y aunque tu sonrisa hoy sea pintada <br>Puedes contarme todo lo que quieras <br>Hoy solo es un dia menos]]></content><category term="Me Enveneno De Azules" label="Me Enveneno De Azules"/><category term="Un Dia Menos" label="Un Dia Menos"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Imagenes/</id><title>Me Enveneno De Azules - Imagenes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:49:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:49:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Imagenes/" title="Me Enveneno De Azules - Imagenes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Toda la vida corriendo detras <br>Sin poder dibujar el paisaje, sin pasajes <br>Mi condicion de soldado raso <br>Nunca me dio para poder comprar <br>Los pinceles <br><br>Imagenes rondando en mi cabeza <br>Jugando con mi vida cada dia <br><br>Cada manana al despertar <br>Juego con todas las ventanas, a abrir el dia <br><br>Todas las cosas que vienen detras <br>Son robadas con dignidad <br>De que me sirvio <br><br>Imagenes rondando en mi cabeza <br>Paisajes que hicisteis mi vida <br>Comprendo bien el cambio de las cosas <br>La vida puede ser venenosa <br><br>Venenosa la vida es venenosa <br>La la la <br><br>Imagenes rondando en mi cabeza <br>Paisajes que hicisteis mi vida <br>Comprendo bien el cambio de las cosas <br>La vida puede ser venenosa]]></content><category term="Me Enveneno De Azules" label="Me Enveneno De Azules"/><category term="Imagenes" label="Imagenes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Es_Fiel/</id><title>Me Enveneno De Azules - Es Fiel - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:50:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:50:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Es_Fiel/" title="Me Enveneno De Azules - Es Fiel - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Todas las formas de conseguirlo <br>Son suficientes para que sonrias <br>Las pequenas cosas del dia a dia <br>Melancolia, proporcionable a tu manera <br>De querer <br><br>Si es fiel, si es fiel <br>Se que tu alma no es de papel <br>Ni de carton, ni de carton <br>Porque yo oigo latir ese corazon <br><br>Cada manana de cada dia <br>Y cada noche, de cada luna, aunque este escondida <br>Y aunque este escondida <br>No importa, porque los dias <br>Que no han pasado son suficiente para reir <br><br>Y es fiel, y es fiel <br>Tu sabes que mi alma no es de papel <br>Ni de carton, ni de carton <br>Tu oyes latir mi corazon <br>Uh]]></content><category term="Me Enveneno De Azules" label="Me Enveneno De Azules"/><category term="Es Fiel" label="Es Fiel"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Llaves/</id><title>Me Enveneno De Azules - Llaves - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:50:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:50:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Llaves/" title="Me Enveneno De Azules - Llaves - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cada manana se levanta el dia <br>Y me resulta todo tan normal <br>Hay costumbres que son tan cobardes <br>Y cobardes que viven solo por costumbre <br><br>Y a mi me da tanto miedo <br>Mi vida es a veces tan pobre <br>Tan pobre y tan dulce a la vez <br><br>Me resulta facil creer que puedo tropezar <br>Tres veces en la misma piedra <br>Debo ser el ultimo loco con sentido de orientacion <br>Y ya ves, no me encuentro <br>Quiero reaccionar <br><br>Me alejare de todos los moldes <br>Y rompere los dientes al destino <br>Tu y yo valemos mas que todo esto <br>Tu y yo podemos hacer una gran revolucion <br>Y cambiar para siempre <br><br>Para siempre es mucho tiempo <br>Naranara <br>El tiempo es lo que mas me ata <br>Naranara <br>El tiempo se queda detras <br><br>La vida es una puerta cerrada <br>Y cada uno tiene una llave <br>Hay que encontrar la puerta correcta <br>Las llaves abren muchas puertas <br>Si sabes buscar, si sabes buscar <br><br>No le hagas mucho dano <br>Deja que encuentre su llave <br>Dejalo que se equivoque <br>El tiempo es lo que le hace fuerte <br>El tiempo se queda detras]]></content><category term="Me Enveneno De Azules" label="Me Enveneno De Azules"/><category term="Llaves" label="Llaves"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/No_Se_Sabian_Hablar/</id><title>Me Enveneno De Azules - No Se Sabian Hablar - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:50:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:50:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/No_Se_Sabian_Hablar/" title="Me Enveneno De Azules - No Se Sabian Hablar - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[el era el mago <br>De los hombres sin casa <br>Siempre creia en todo lo que hacia <br>Sus manos eran fuertes <br>Porque era fuerte sin corazon <br><br>Ella era la princesa <br>De los cuentos de hadas <br>Su piel era suave, y su sonrisa cuidada <br>Sus pasos eran lentos pero firmes <br>Como su corazon <br><br>No quisieron admitir <br>Que entre los dos hacian <br>Un corazon gigante <br><br>Y el tiempo se pasaba para los dos <br>Y entre los dos hacian <br>Un corazon gigante <br>Un solo corazon <br><br>Hoy se ha levantado <br>Pensando que era el dia <br>Sabia donde estaba <br>La veia todas las mananas <br>Pero siempre la miraba por detras <br>Para no enrojecer <br><br>Y ella sabia <br>A la hora que pasaba <br>Siempre esperaba <br>Para decirle lo que sentia <br>Pero siempre lo miraba por detras <br>Para no enrojecer <br><br>No se sabian hablar <br>Y entre los dos hacian <br>Un corazon gigante <br>Y el tiempo se pasaba para los dos <br>Y entre los dos hacian <br>Un corazon gigante <br><br>No se supieron entender <br>Y entre los dos hacian <br>Un corazon gigante <br>Y el tiempo se pasaba para los dos <br>Y entre los dos hacian <br>Un corazon gigante <br>Un solo corazon]]></content><category term="Me Enveneno De Azules" label="Me Enveneno De Azules"/><category term="No Se Sabian Hablar" label="No Se Sabian Hablar"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Birdy/</id><title>Me Enveneno De Azules - Birdy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:50:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:50:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Birdy/" title="Me Enveneno De Azules - Birdy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[el queria volar <br>Y dormia en una jaula <br>Trabajaba en sus alas <br>En el garaje de su casa <br><br>Esta guerra me partio el corazon <br>Y ahora te encuentro <br>De cuclillas a los pies de esta cama <br>Cuentame porque no quieres hablar <br>Que te ha hecho este mal, soy tu amigo <br><br>Ese impulso con el aire <br>Resbalando por tu cara <br>Si te caias te volvias a levantar <br>Dime cuanto dano te han hecho ya <br>Nunca nos dijeron que esto era asi <br>Mi amigo <br><br>Puedo ver aun levitando con tus manos <br>Persiguiendo aviones y estudiando <br>Aves de colores <br><br>Puedo verte aun en tu primera cita <br>Aquella chica se moria por ti <br>Tu solo tenias ojos para el cielo <br><br>Estoy empezando a echarte de menos <br>Y no puedo verte asi <br>Tendremos que pensar algun plan <br>Mirame y dime que sabes quien soy <br>No nos merecemos estar aqui <br>Sin vida <br><br>Vamos a tirarles mierda a la cara <br>Porque ellos nunca nos dejaron vivir <br>Yo tambien quiero volar <br>Dame tu mano y salta conmigo]]></content><category term="Me Enveneno De Azules" label="Me Enveneno De Azules"/><category term="Birdy" label="Birdy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Super_Heroe/</id><title>Me Enveneno De Azules - Super Heroe - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:50:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:50:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Super_Heroe/" title="Me Enveneno De Azules - Super Heroe - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sabes cual es mi secreto <br>Sabes, siempre sabes <br><br>Soy un super heroe <br>Retirado este verano <br>He perdido el traje <br>Que me dejaron los marcianos <br><br>Vaya contrariedad cruel <br><br>Ya no puedo viajar en el tiempo <br>Sabes, siempre sabes <br><br>Tu te alegras tanto <br>Porque hoy somos iguales <br>No te alegres tanto <br>Porque hoy hay algo que tu no sabes <br>No te lo dire jamas <br><br>Empiezo a estar mejor <br>Ahora que no tengo esa carga <br>Fue lo mejor, quizas <br>Que pudo pasarme <br>Ahora lo tengo claro <br><br>Soy un super heroe <br>Retirado este verano <br>He perdido el traje <br>Que me dejaron los marcianos <br><br>Tu te alegras tanto <br>Porque hoy somos iguales <br>No te alegres tanto <br>Porque hoy hay algo que tu no sabes <br>No te lo dire jamas]]></content><category term="Me Enveneno De Azules" label="Me Enveneno De Azules"/><category term="Super Heroe" label="Super Heroe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Esperando_Un_Milagro/</id><title>Me Enveneno De Azules - Esperando Un Milagro - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:50:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:50:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Esperando_Un_Milagro/" title="Me Enveneno De Azules - Esperando Un Milagro - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Desde hace tiempo <br>La vengo siguiendo <br>Ella todavia no me conoce <br>Me estoy secando por dentro <br><br>Estoy esperando <br>Que pase este invierno <br>Y que vengan cantando <br>Mis sentimientos <br><br>Esperando un milagro <br>Que me ayude a decidirme de una vez <br>Nunca encuentro el momento <br>De poder mirarte a los ojos de una vez <br><br>Realidad virtual <br>No acierto a comprender <br>Mi verdadera locura <br>Este juego nunca se me ha dado bien <br>No encuentro respuestas <br>Me he quedado sin respuesta <br>A tu pregunta, a tu pregunta <br>Como puedo ser tan cobarde <br>Y no decirle nunca nada, de una vez <br><br>Esperando un milagro <br>Que me ayude a decidirme <br>De una vez <br><br>Salalalala <br><br>No encuentro respuestas <br>A tus preguntas <br><br>Salalalalala <br><br>Esperando un milagro]]></content><category term="Me Enveneno De Azules" label="Me Enveneno De Azules"/><category term="Esperando Un Milagro" label="Esperando Un Milagro"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Como_Soy/</id><title>Me Enveneno De Azules - Como Soy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:50:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:50:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Como_Soy/" title="Me Enveneno De Azules - Como Soy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[He tardado tiempo en descubrir <br>lo que a mi me gusta a ella le hace feliz <br>Y he tratado de interpretar <br>pero cuando soy yo todo funciona mejor <br>todo funciona mejor <br>todo funciona mejor <br>He tardado tiempo en descubrir <br>lo que yo queria era poder reir <br>Yo he querido que tu seas mi estrella <br>desde ahora te tendre siempre entre ellas <br>siempre entre ellas <br>siempre entre ellas <br>Todo lo que pido es una oportunidad <br>quiero poder quererme como soy <br>como soy <br>como soy <br>como soy <br>como soy]]></content><category term="Me Enveneno De Azules" label="Me Enveneno De Azules"/><category term="Como Soy" label="Como Soy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Lluvia_En_Mis_Zapatos/</id><title>Me Enveneno De Azules - Lluvia En Mis Zapatos - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:50:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:50:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/Lluvia_En_Mis_Zapatos/" title="Me Enveneno De Azules - Lluvia En Mis Zapatos - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hoy he salido con los zapatos de domingo <br>Y llueve en toda la ciudad <br>Hoy he salido y es viernes <br>Nadando llegare hasta el fondo de algun bar <br><br>Y la lluvia en mis zapatos de charol <br>En mis bolsillos cosidos <br>Cada vez me moja mas <br><br>Hoy quiero pasear <br>Calarme hasta sentirme <br>Frio como antes <br><br>Como antes de ayer <br>Cuando todavia era frio, sin querer <br>Cuando todavia estabamos juntos <br>Cuando todo llegaba tarde <br>Y el presente era ciencia ficcion <br><br>Viernes y llueve en la ciudad <br>Todo un fin de semana <br>Para apagar los fuegos <br><br>Lluvia, disimula mis lagrimas <br>Si vuelve le dire <br>Que no la quiero ver mas <br><br>No, no, no <br><br>Le dire que no la quiero ver mas]]></content><category term="Me Enveneno De Azules" label="Me Enveneno De Azules"/><category term="Lluvia En Mis Zapatos" label="Lluvia En Mis Zapatos"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/A_Veces_Quiero_Estar_Callado/</id><title>Me Enveneno De Azules - A Veces Quiero Estar Callado - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:50:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:50:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Me_Enveneno_De_Azules/A_Veces_Quiero_Estar_Callado/" title="Me Enveneno De Azules - A Veces Quiero Estar Callado - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Mientras hayan palabras que duelan <br>Mientras nadie comprenda este juego <br>Me encerrare en esta caja vacia <br>A esperar que algo pase y me salve <br><br>Siempre he sido un poco cruel <br>Con mi forma de entenderme <br>Se que me avisaste, pero entiende <br>Que mi sangre siempre me pierde, siempre me pierde <br><br>A veces puedo estar callado <br>Y a veces quiero estar callado <br><br>Mientras las palabras duelan <br>Mientras nadie quiera hacerlo <br>Esperare en esta caja vacia <br><br>Siempre ha sido un poco cruel <br>La forma de entenderme <br>Yo confio en ti, pero mi sangre <br>Que es tu sangre, siempre me pierde <br><br>Y es que vienes y vas <br>Y te quedas y te enciendes <br>Y te consumes, te haces vapor <br>Te haces transparente y vuelta a empezar otra vez <br><br>Siempre igual, me haces dano y hago vahos con tu vapor <br>Que siempre se pierde <br>Se hace transparente <br>Me vuelvo a encerrar otra vez <br><br>A veces puedo estar callado <br>Y a veces quiero estar callado]]></content><category term="Me Enveneno De Azules" label="Me Enveneno De Azules"/><category term="A Veces Quiero Estar Callado" label="A Veces Quiero Estar Callado"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Raptools/Galaxy1983/</id><title>Raptools - Galaxy1983 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:51:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:51:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Raptools/Galaxy1983/" title="Raptools - Galaxy1983 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fly so high oh <br>Fly so high oh <br>Fly so high MAMA <br>The first time universe <br>Fly so high oh <br>Fly so high oh <br>Fly so high MAMA <br>falling in the falling <br>I’m falling universe <br>Mama mama <br>Mama mama <br>Mama mama <br>Mama mama <br>난 오르고 또 오르네 <br>드넓은 나의 우주를 <br>My resume에 <br>한 줄을 채웠네 랩 경력자 <br>나를 바라라 <br>Mic 잡고 있는 <br>내게 줘 Like <br>누구도 거부할 수 없어 <br>get ready to go drive <br>이미 결제했어 <br>내 ticket은 <br>벗어 던져 넥타이는 <br>좀만 더 투자해 <br>난 줄였지 자는 시간을 <br>위로 날아갈 일만 남았네 내일 <br>따라와 봐 따라와 봐 <br>숨 쉬고 있어 <br>이 리듬의 배 속에서 <br>내가 풍 하면 덩 <br>헤엄치고 있어 <br>꿈같은 우주 속에서 <br>내가 어 하면 예 <br>넌 들썩이며 달아올라 <br>젖어 들어 녹아내려 <br>내가 우 하면 핫 <br>내 몸을 불태워 <br>뭐가 무서워 그게 나다워 <br>여긴 너무 더워 <br>그래도 옷은 안 벗어 <br>이 모든 걸 잠재워 <br>it's war 우주전쟁 oh <br>다 때려잡아 oh <br>Fly four <br>Fly three <br>Fly two <br>Fly so high oh <br>Mama mama <br>Mama mama <br>Mama mama <br>Mama mama <br>여기는 fantastic <br>느낌은 very classic <br>이것은 랩 우주탐험 <br>완전 색다른 경험 <br>지구부터 화성까지 <br>다 따먹고 갈게 <br>배터지게 먹고 나서 <br>손가락 입에 넣을게 <br>랩으로 토할래 <br>나 또 노래를 부를래 <br>태양까지 직진 전진 oh 또 전진 <br>멈추지 않아 빠져들지 <br>oh like 블랙홀 <br>숨지 않아 다가가지 <br>oh 태양 속으로 <br>올라타 빈자리 <br>얼마 안 남았어 너의 막차 <br>자리 잡아 너 타자마자 <br>출발할게 꽉 잡아 <br>너의 navigation Oh <br>no destination Go <br>My birthday the first day <br>I’m thirties but thirsty <br>Let's get it super star <br>아니라도 상관없어 <br>남들보다 난 빨라 달라 <br>My job ah 아주 많아 <br>빛이 보이기 시작 <br>pitch를 더 높여 <br>날아간다 오늘도 난 <br>랩 탐험을 시작한다 <br>Mama <br>]]></content><category term="Raptools" label="Raptools"/><category term="Galaxy1983" label="Galaxy1983"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Raptools/주인공/</id><title>Raptools - 주인공 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:51:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:51:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Raptools/%EC%A3%BC%EC%9D%B8%EA%B3%B5/" title="Raptools - 주인공 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh 터벅터벅 <br>퇴근길의 발걸음 <br>어깨엔 삶의 무게 한가득 <br>짊어졌거든 근데 <br>우린 젊거든 <br>beat을 줘 마이크 줘 <br>우린 피터 팬 Neverland <br>현실을 이겨낸 Super star <br>행여나 누가 뭐랄까 <br>겁 안 나 멀리 나아가 <br>여기 있는 사람 <br>모두 나랑 같이 feel me <br>Keep it going going <br>느껴봐 재미 <br>여기 있는 사람 <br>모두 나랑 같이 feel me <br>Keep it going going <br>느껴봐 재미 <br>던져버려 가방을 태워버려 <br>넥타이 퇴근하는 순간 <br>숨 막히게 갑갑했던 <br>나이테를 끊어버려 <br>후회 없이 살아간다 <br>후회하며 지나가는 <br>지금을 잡은 후에 <br>희미하게 보인 <br>나를 남김 없이 불태웠지 <br>지금 너를 들여다봐 <br>목욕물은 적당히 따뜻하게 <br>맥주 한 캔 더해주면 <br>여기가 천국 <br>It’s time to go back right now <br>It’s time to go back right now <br>그만해 그만해 <br>It’s time to go back right now <br>It’s time to go back right now <br>그만해 그만해 <br>부숴버려 keyboard <br>망치로 누군가가 <br>인생을 망치려 했으나 <br>퍽이나 그게 먹힐까 <br>벌써 땀이나 <br>돌아봐 다같이 춤춰봐 <br>shake it shake it freestyle로 <br>break it break it <br>금메달 품으로 <br>오늘 주인공 you Bravo <br>달려들어 불나방처럼 <br>물 불 가리지 말고 <br>그대여 뛰어올라 <br>뭘 하든 말든 상관말아 <br>이제부터 벌레처럼 꿈틀 되 <br>단 그냥 밟혀 죽네 <br>새처럼 날아올라 높게 <br>무쇠처럼 강력하게 찍네 <br>Spike spike spike spike spike <br>MIC like my life <br>It's highlight in the bright night <br>여기 있는 사람 <br>모두 나랑 같이 feel me <br>Keep it going going <br>느껴봐 재미 <br>여기 있는 사람 <br>모두 나랑 같이 feel me <br>Keep it going going <br>느껴봐 재미 <br>부숴버려 keyboard <br>망치로 누군가가 <br>인생을 망치려 했었나 <br>퍽이나 그게 먹힐까 <br>벌써 땀이나 <br>돌아봐 다같이 춤춰바 <br>shake it shake it freestyle로 <br>break it break it <br>금메달 품으로 <br>오늘 주인공 you Bravo <br>오늘을 살고 내일을 달려가 <br>똑같은 오늘은 너무 겁이 나 <br>막막해 막상 난 <br>막살지도 못하잖아 <br>잠시만 벗어나 <br>오늘을 살아봐 oh <br>꿈을 꾸며 달려가는 20대들 <br>하루하루 살아가는 30대들 <br>자식놈들 생각하는 40대들 <br>부숴버려 keyboard <br>망치로 누군가가 <br>인생을 망치려 했으나 <br>퍽이나 그게 먹힐까 <br>벌써 땀이나 <br>돌아봐 다같이 춤춰바 <br>shake it shake it freestyle로 <br>break it break it <br>금메달 품으로 <br>오늘 주인공 you Bravo <br>]]></content><category term="Raptools" label="Raptools"/><category term="주인공" label="주인공"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Raptools/랩에_미쳤네/</id><title>Raptools - 랩에 미쳤네 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:51:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:51:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Raptools/%EB%9E%A9%EC%97%90_%EB%AF%B8%EC%B3%A4%EB%84%A4/" title="Raptools - 랩에 미쳤네 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 하루 일을 마치면 <br>어떤이들은 춤을 추고 <br>어떤 이들은 <br>친구 만나 술을 먹고 <br>어떤 이들은 집에 가 <br>가족과의 대화 <br>어떤 이들은 <br>still in 회사 <br>그렇지만 난 <br>headphone microphone <br>공들여온 <br>내 가사들을 되씹으며 <br>랩 게임을 즐기네 <br>내 시간은 늘 부족해 <br>남들보다 더 많은 <br>삶을 살기에 <br>누구보다 더 tight하고 <br>잘게 쪼개네 <br>나의 인생의 박자에 <br>더 많은 음절을 집어넣네 <br>밤새 녹음하고 새벽엔 <br>운동을 땀이 마르지 않아 <br>어차피 불면증이라 <br>잠은 잘 안자 <br>재밌게 그리는 거야 <br>인생의 Canvas <br>여백은 없어 꽉 채워 <br>나의 물감을 짜내 또 짜내 <br>남김 없이 나의 <br>열정을 Glass에 부어 <br>우리 다 같이 짠해 <br>내 일의 내일을 위해 <br>다 같이 다 같이 <br>랩에 미쳤네 나는 <br>나는 랩에 미쳤네 <br>아주 많이 나는 <br>랩에 미쳤네 ah <br>랩에 미쳤네 <br>입에서 나는 단내 <br>무엇보다 달콤해 <br>이것에 중독되어버린 나는 <br>오늘도 꿈을 꾸며 칼을 가는 <br>메모장에 꽉 채운 <br>내 가사는 <br>내가 사는 이유이며 <br>동시에 내가 찾는 <br>가치의 지도 <br>누가 뭐라 해도 <br>멈출 수 없는 나의 기도 <br>도로 아무 타 불이 <br>돼버린 나의 기로 <br>이십 년 소년의 그 길로 <br>랩에 미쳤네 나는 <br>나는 랩에 미쳤네 <br>아주 많이 나는 <br>랩에 미쳤네 ah <br>랩에 미쳤네 <br>새벽 6시 반이면 <br>어김없이 떠지는 <br>내 두 눈을 화장실 <br>거울에 비춰보니 <br>초점이 전혀 없네 <br>어제도 녹음으로 <br>밤을 지세 웠지 <br>꾸겨진 셔츠 쑤셔 넣고 <br>커피 한잔 oh <br>출근 준비 완료 <br>내 삶에 믹스테입은 후달려도 <br>믹스커피는 빠질 수가 없네 <br>맥심 for life <br>라디오를 켜 뉴스쇼채널 <br>이놈에 정치판과 <br>경제판은 흔들리는 <br>내 하루를 더욱 <br>흔들어대네 come on <br>회사주차장 앞 전투 <br>준비완료 마무리는 <br>The game of common <br>one Mic two MC 사회에선 <br>하이에나 그러나 <br>스튜디오에서 랩을 할 땐 <br>한 마리 고독한 늑대 새끼네 <br>그래 난 랩에 미쳐버렸네 <br>그래 나는 랩에 미쳤네 <br>남김 없이 나의 <br>열정을 Glass에 부어 <br>우리 다 같이 짠해 <br>내 일의 내일을 위해 <br>다같이 다같이 <br>oh common <br>랩에 미쳤네 그래 <br>나는 정말 랩에 미쳤네 <br>리듬가락타고 랩에 미쳤네 <br>랩에 미쳤네 <br>호랑이 담배피던 시절 부터 <br>내가 꿈꿔왔던 세상이 <br>지금과는 조금 달랐네 <br>하루하루 살다보니 <br>그놈의 지독히도 지독했던 <br>경쟁과 열등속에 <br>땅끝까지 나를 <br>밀어붙여 달렸네 <br>지난 7여녀간 열정과 <br>경력을 팔았다면 <br>지금은 작은 <br>스튜디오안에 앉아 <br>나는 랩을 팔고있네 <br>랩에 미쳤네 그래 <br>나는 정말 랩에 미쳤네 <br>리듬가락타고 <br>랩에 미쳤네 <br>랩에 미쳤네 <br>]]></content><category term="Raptools" label="Raptools"/><category term="랩에 미쳤네" label="랩에 미쳤네"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Raptools/Go_Home_Feat_JSB/</id><title>Raptools - Go Home (Feat. JSB) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:51:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:51:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Raptools/Go_Home_Feat_JSB/" title="Raptools - Go Home (Feat. JSB) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[국민학교 삼 학년 이름도 <br>기억 안 나는 꼬맹이 <br>친구들과의 작별 인사를 <br>뒤로하고 온 곳 모든 것은 <br>새롭게 바뀌었고 시간의 <br>태엽을 뒤로 감은듯한 도시 <br>따스한 분위기 허름하지만 <br>넓은 이곳의 흙 냄새 <br>그리움을 느끼기도 전에 <br>날 받아준 이 도시 <br>눈을 잠시 감아 <br>그때로 돌아간 난 <br>다시 꿈을 꾼다 <br>원주시 원동 12통 5반 <br>내가 살던 고향 떠난 지 <br>벌써 어느덧 십 수 년 <br>포근한 냄새가 <br>나를 반기던 일산동과 <br>명륜동을 가로지른 <br>언덕 배기쯤 <br>비 올 때면 항상 <br>우산을 들고 엄마가 <br>기다렸지 그 시절 <br>그 기억들이 나를 감싸네 <br>추억팔인 질색인데 <br>어쩔 수 없는 내 뿌리 <br>내 hometown <br>그때 어린 시절 늘 함께 있었지 <br>웃고 떠들며 좋은 꿈을 꾸었지 <br>오랜 시간 지나도 잊지 않았어 <br>그 시절의 약속 늘 소중했었지 <br>천오백 원짜리 안주 <br>너와 나의 집 사이의 <br>소줏집 <br>그곳에서 피워냈던 <br>음악 이야기 <br>십 년은 더 지나서야 <br>이야기해 <br>기억나니 우리 만들었던 노래 <br>to my friends <br>그 랩을 아직 나는 기억해 <br>동시에 그 맘도 나는 간직해 <br>Everyday 바쁘지만 <br>연락해 가끔 <br>Have a good day <br>어제와 내일에 경계가 없는 <br>지금을 살며 낮져밤져의 <br>삶은 지독히도 끝없는 <br>반복과 반복 <br>발악하는 현실 속 <br>남기고 싶은 추억 <br>말뚝박기 스티브 오스틴 <br>라디오헤드 우탱클랜 <br>모든 게 가능했던 그 <br>때 그 장소 <br>너와 나에 의식 속엔 <br>길이 없어 no way <br>끝이 없이 반복되는 <br>내 미래는 no gate <br>이번 명절에 다시 만나 <br>우리같이 go home <br>그때 어린 시절 늘 함께 있었지 <br>웃고 떠들며 좋은 꿈을 꾸었지 <br>오랜 시간 지나도 잊지 않았어 <br>그 시절의 약속 늘 소중했었지 <br>그리운 그 시절 그리운 <br>그 동네 그리워서 <br>머릿속에 그림을 그리네 <br>불러볼게 노래 아니 <br>그냥 끼적이듯 말해 <br>마지막 퍼즐을 <br>맞춰주게 엽우 <br>좋은 옷 좋은 차 좋은 집만 <br>꿈꾸던 그때는 그랬네 <br>철이 없었네 <br>온 동네 누비며 <br>떠들고 다녔었지 <br>I wanna be a rapstar but <br>지금에 난 내 아들의 star <br>]]></content><category term="Raptools" label="Raptools"/><category term="Go Home (Feat. JSB)" label="Go Home (Feat. JSB)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Raptools/푸르리라_Feat_Candice/</id><title>Raptools - 푸르리라 (Feat. Candice) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:51:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:51:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Raptools/%ED%91%B8%EB%A5%B4%EB%A6%AC%EB%9D%BC_Feat_Candice/" title="Raptools - 푸르리라 (Feat. Candice) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘도 난 coffee 한잔을 <br>들고 거리로 나아가 <br>분주히 걷고 있는 이들 <br>사이로 끼어가 <br>정신 없이 앞만 보며 <br>아스팔트 위 누비다 <br>잃어가고 있어 나 <br>끌려가고 있어 나 팔려 <br>틀 속에서 난 살고 있어 <br>강물 속에 휩쓸려 <br>남들처럼 살라고 애써 <br>발버둥치고만 있어 <br>도심 속 moskito <br>같은 인간들 지겨워 <br>Hell Zika virus <br>팍팍 뿌려 F killer <br>잔소리 듣기가 싫지 <br>큰소리쳤으니까 <br>망설일 필요도 없지 <br>가솔린 꽉 채웠으니 <br>Accelerator 밟아 <br>저 기저 언덕 넘어 <br>넓어지는 시야 <br>푸르름 속으로 <br>부릉 부릉 부르릉 <br>삶에 지쳐 힘겨운가요 <br>안아줄게요 <br>더 이상 아프지 말아요 <br>많이들 잊고 살아가요 <br>순수함을 요 <br>그래도 푸르게 <br>푸르게 살아요 <br>갑갑한 현실에서 <br>잠시 눈을 감아 상상해 <br>여기는 걱정 없이 <br>풀 수 있는 3분 30초의 <br>크리넥스 그려냈어 <br>난 너의 판타지 <br>매일 꿈 꾸지 <br>아름다운 제주도의 <br>밤하늘의 별 <br>이 자리에 놀이판이 <br>펼쳐졌으니 마당놀이 <br>신 나게 시작해볼까 <br>나는 난장판에 <br>랩을 하는 마당쇠 <br>시원하게 뽑아줄게 <br>3분 30초의 크리넥스 <br>굿거리장단은 <br>좀 더 구수하게 <br>자진모리장단은 <br>여전히 힘차게 <br>이 비트 위의 장단은 <br>내 맘대로 갈게 <br>배트를 휘둘러봐 홈런 <br>삶에 지쳐 힘겨운가요 <br>안아줄게요 <br>더 이상 아프지 말아요 <br>많이들 잊고 살아가요 <br>순수함을 요 <br>그래도 푸르게 <br>푸르게 살아요 <br>Throw your hands in the air yo <br>Come on MIC check <br>with my fellow yo <br>그대여 이리 와요 <br>lets do it do it do it do it do it <br>Let me hear saying yeah <br>Ah yeah Baby come on <br>Ah yeah Ah yeah <br>푸르푸르 아 게 아게 <br>Everybody say Ah Ah yeah <br>]]></content><category term="Raptools" label="Raptools"/><category term="푸르리라 (Feat. Candice)" label="푸르리라 (Feat. Candice)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sikstyn/KingFish_Remix_Ver/</id><title>Sikstyn - KingFish (Remix Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:53:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:53:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sikstyn/KingFish_Remix_Ver/" title="Sikstyn - KingFish (Remix Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[루비콘 강을 건넜네 <br>젊을 때 엎지른 물 수심 <br>심히 높아져가네 <br>누군 팻말 글자 루비콘 <br>고치래 요단으로 <br>넌 뭐가 그리 걱정돼 <br>챙기기나 해 서핑보드 <br>등 떠밀린 책임도 <br>뜬 햇빛보단 안 따가워 <br>난반사가 된 파도 <br>물결 찰랑이는 머리결 <br>그녀의 한숨도 <br>물방울처럼 터질걸 <br>억 소리 준비해 <br>왜냐면 내 꼬챙이에 Ugh <br>King fish <br>낚싯대 챙겨와 <br>그물도 big size <br>오늘 좀 큰 거 땡기자 <br>조던 신발끈 묶듯 <br>밧줄도 단단히 매듭짓고 <br>놈이 아무리 커도 <br>결국엔 생선 작살 찍어 <br>King fish <br>King fish <br>King fish <br>i wish <br>i wish <br>King fish <br>King fish <br>i wish <br>i wish <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>회 뜰 때까지 <br>스피커 베이스처럼 <br>출렁이는 물결 <br>낚시는 쉽지 <br>손가락 질 쯤 Like 키보드 <br>마이크 잡은 어부 <br>예수님 만난 베드로 <br>지국총 어사와 <br>그물을 당겨 힘껏 <br>저 먼 바다 깊이 <br>기포 오르는 잔잔한 곳 <br>배고파 부글부글 대는 <br>놈의 욕망이 발효 <br>난 미끼 하나 던지고 <br>저기 숨다 나와 산호 <br>난 확신해 오늘은 <br>꼭 잡을게 큰 살코기 <br>산 좋고 물 좋아 <br>오늘 밤엔 떴네 <br>탱탱하고 육덕진 보름달 <br>니 굶주린 배를 채워줄게 <br>어서 잔치 벌이자 <br>적신호도 없이 달려 <br>우린 이제 외제차야 <br>king fish <br>살어리 얄라리 <br>인생 뭐 있냐 <br>로또 처럼 간단히 <br>건강하다면 위 장 <br>뭐 쯤 다 채우고 <br>웃자 곧 올게 <br>이따가 보자 행복 <br>King fish <br>fish fish <br>King fish <br>King fish <br>i wish <br>i wish <br>King fish <br>King fish <br>i wish <br>i wish <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>회 뜰 때까지 <br>]]></content><category term="Sikstyn" label="Sikstyn"/><category term="KingFish (Remix Ver.)" label="KingFish (Remix Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sikstyn/KingFish/</id><title>Sikstyn - KingFish - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:53:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:53:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sikstyn/KingFish/" title="Sikstyn - KingFish - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[루비콘 강을 건넜네 <br>젊을 때 엎지른 물 수심 <br>심히 높아져가네 <br>누군 팻말 글자 루비콘 <br>고치래 요단으로 <br>넌 뭐가 그리 걱정돼 <br>챙기기나 해 서핑보드 <br>등 떠밀린 책임도 <br>뜬 햇빛보단 안 따가워 <br>난반사가 된 파도 <br>물결 찰랑이는 머리결 <br>그녀의 한숨도 <br>물방울처럼 터질걸 <br>억 소리 준비해 <br>왜냐면 내 꼬챙이에 Ugh <br>King fish <br>낚싯대 챙겨와 <br>그물도 big size <br>오늘 좀 큰 거 땡기자 <br>조던 신발끈 묶듯 <br>밧줄도 단단히 매듭짓고 <br>놈이 아무리 커도 <br>결국엔 생선 작살 찍어 <br>King fish <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>꼭 잡아내 도마 위 <br>회 뜰 때까지 <br>바람이 세고 <br>파도가 쳐도 날 못 막지 <br>잠수복보다 든든해 <br>내 바람막이 <br>King fish <br>King fish <br>i wish <br>i wish <br>King fish <br>King fish <br>i wish <br>i wish <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>King fish <br>fish fish <br>i wish <br>wish wish <br>King fish <br>fish fish <br>i wish <br>wish wish <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>난 잡어 난 잡어 <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>난 잡어 난 잡어 <br>스피커 베이스처럼 <br>출렁이는 물결 <br>낚시는 쉽지 <br>손가락 질 쯤 Like 키보드 <br>마이크 잡은 어부 <br>예수님 만난 베드로 <br>지국총 어사와 <br>그물을 당겨 힘껏 <br>저 먼 바다 깊이 <br>기포 오르는 잔잔한 곳 <br>배고파 부글부글 대는 <br>놈의 욕망이 발효 <br>난 미끼 하나 던지고 <br>저기 숨다 나와 산호 <br>난 확신해 오늘은 <br>꼭 잡을게 큰 살코기 <br>king fish <br>산 좋고 물 좋아 <br>오늘 밤엔 떴네 <br>탱탱하고 육덕진 보름달 <br>니 굶주린 배를 채워줄게 <br>어서 잔치 벌이자 <br>적신호도 없이 달려 <br>우린 이제 외제차야 <br>king fish <br>살어리 얄라리 <br>인생 뭐 있냐 <br>로또 처럼 간단히 <br>건강하다면 위 장 <br>뭐 쯤 다 채우고 <br>웃자 곧 올게 <br>이따가 보자 행복 <br>King fish <br>King fish <br>i wish <br>i wish <br>King fish <br>King fish <br>i wish <br>i wish <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>King fish <br>fish fish <br>i wish <br>wish wish <br>King fish <br>fish fish <br>i wish <br>wish wish <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>난 잡어 난 잡어 <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>난 잡어 난 잡어 <br>King fish <br>King fish <br>i wish <br>i wish <br>King fish <br>King fish <br>i wish <br>i wish <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>King fish <br>fish fish <br>i wish <br>wish wish <br>King fish <br>fish fish <br>i wish <br>wish wish <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>난 잡어 난 잡어 <br>해 뜰 때까지 <br>난 잡어 난 잡어 <br>]]></content><category term="Sikstyn" label="Sikstyn"/><category term="KingFish" label="KingFish"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/우중/기다리는_중/</id><title>우중 - 기다리는 중 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:56:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:56:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9A%B0%EC%A4%91/%EA%B8%B0%EB%8B%A4%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_%EC%A4%91/" title="우중 - 기다리는 중 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우린 기다리는 중 <br>파도를 <br>지루하기만 한 수평선 너머를 <br>우린 바라보는 중 <br>우린 기다리는 중 <br>파도를 <br>위태로운 판자 위에선 우리를 <br>물속에 처박아 주오 <br>어쩌면 나를 삼켜 <br>어떻게든 나를 육지로 <br>어쩌면 나를 태워 <br>이 바다를 서서 걸을지도 몰라 <br>우린 기다리는 중 <br>바람을 <br>움직이지 않는 원양선 방향키를 <br>그저 돌려보는 중 <br>우린 기다리는 중 <br>태풍을 <br>말라붙은 갑판 위에선 우리를 <br>물속에 처박아 주오 <br>어쩌면 나를 삼켜 <br>어떻게든 나를 육지로 <br>어쩌면 나를 태워 <br>이 바다를 서서 걸을지도 <br>어쩌면 나를 삼켜 <br>어떻게든 나를 육지로 <br>어쩌면 나를 태워 <br>이 바다를 서서 걸을지도 몰라 <br>]]></content><category term="우중" label="우중"/><category term="기다리는 중" label="기다리는 중"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서서서우재/한계_Feat_문두리/</id><title>서서서우재 - 한계 (Feat. 문두리) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T07:56:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T07:56:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EC%84%9C%EC%84%9C%EC%9A%B0%EC%9E%AC/%ED%95%9C%EA%B3%84_Feat_%EB%AC%B8%EB%91%90%EB%A6%AC/" title="서서서우재 - 한계 (Feat. 문두리) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 이제는 정말 <br>더 이상은 안 할래 <br>그 어떤 말로도 <br>난 들리지 않는걸 <br>나 이제는 정말 <br>더 이상은 안 할래 <br>슬픈 노래 들어 봐봐요 <br>위로가 좀 되셨었나요 <br>다들 힘드나요 <br>이젠 기운 내봐요 <br>애인과 헤어졌나 봐요 <br>어깨가 축 처져 있네요 <br>다들 힘드나요 <br>이젠 기운 내봐요 <br>되는 게 하나도 없어도 <br>나의 한계가 온 것 같아도 <br>이젠 끝이라 느껴질 수도 <br>더이상 해낼 수 없어도 <br>이 노래 힘이 좀되나요 <br>위로를 좀 받으셨나요 <br>다들 힘드나요 <br>이젠 기운 내봐요 <br>지금 다들 힘드나요 <br>이젠 기운 내봐요 <br>지금 다들 힘드나요 <br>이젠 기운 내봐요 <br>]]></content><category term="서서서우재" label="서서서우재"/><category term="한계 (Feat. 문두리)" label="한계 (Feat. 문두리)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alex_Angelo/Figured_It_Out/</id><title>Alex Angelo - Figured It Out - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:03:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:03:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alex_Angelo/Figured_It_Out/" title="Alex Angelo - Figured It Out - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So lost, lost in the moment <br>So lost without you <br>You got, you got me broken <br>Not whole without you <br><br>Don't you know that I'll find my way <br>I don't need to be afraid <br>Always gonna be another day <br>So I'll say that I figured it out <br>Even the best of us get broken <br>Don't you worry, baby, I'll be okay <br>Yeah, I figured it out <br>Even the best of us get broken <br>Don't you worry, baby, I'll be okay <br>Yeah, I figured it out <br><br>So lost, lost in the feeling <br>Not sure where I'm going to <br>Just watch, watch me go further <br>On my own without you <br><br>Don't you know that I'll find my way <br>I don't need to be afraid <br>Always gonna be another day <br>So I'll say that I figured it out <br>Even the best of us get broken <br>Don't you worry, baby, I'll be okay <br>Yeah, I figured it out <br>Even the best of us get broken <br>Don't you worry, baby, I'll be okay <br>Yeah, I figured it out <br>Yeah, I figured it out <br>So lost, lost in the moment <br>So lost without you]]></content><category term="Alex Angelo" label="Alex Angelo"/><category term="Figured It Out" label="Figured It Out"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alex_Angelo/Stay_Like_This/</id><title>Alex Angelo - Stay Like This - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:03:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:03:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alex_Angelo/Stay_Like_This/" title="Alex Angelo - Stay Like This - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ooh Ooh <br>Don't let it slip away <br>Ooh Ooh <br>Don't let it get away <br><br>Can you hear me right now <br>I got your number <br>And I'm callin' you out <br>With liquid courage <br>I can beat all my doubt <br>There's not another <br>So I'm chasin' you down <br>Chasin' you down <br><br>Can you see me right now <br>I'm comin' closer <br>Think I figured you out <br>Not like the others <br>You don't blend with the crowd <br>I've blown your cover <br>Now I'm takin' you down <br>Takin' you down <br><br>Can you hear me right now <br>I got your number <br>And I'm callin' you out <br>With liquid courage <br>I can beat all my doubt <br>There's not another <br>So I'm chasin' you down <br>Chasin' you down <br><br>Ooh Ooh <br>Don't let it slip away <br>Ooh Ooh <br>Don't let it get away <br><br>Ooh Ooh <br>Don't let it get away <br>Ooh Ooh <br>Won't let you slip away <br><br>Can you see me right now <br>I'm comin' closer <br>Think I figured you out <br>Not like the others <br>You don't blend with the crowd <br>I've blown your cover <br>Now I'm takin' you down <br>Takin' you down <br><br>Can you hear me right now <br>I got your number <br>And I'm callin' you out <br>With liquid courage <br>I can beat all my doubt <br>There's not another <br>So I'm chasin' you down <br>Chasin' you down <br><br>Can you see me right now <br>I'm comin' closer <br>Think I figured you out <br>Not like the others <br>You don't blend with the crowd <br>I've blown your cover <br>Now I'm takin' you down <br>Takin' you down <br><br>Ooh Ooh <br>Don't let it slip away <br>Ooh Ooh <br>Don't let it get away <br>Ooh Ooh <br>Don't let it get away <br>Ooh Ooh <br>Won't let you slip away <br><br>Can you hear me right now <br>I got your number <br>And I'm callin' you out <br>With liquid courage <br>I can beat all my doubt <br>There's not another <br>So I'm chasin' you down <br>Chasin' you down]]></content><category term="Alex Angelo" label="Alex Angelo"/><category term="Stay Like This" label="Stay Like This"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NCT_127/無限的我_무한적아Limitless/</id><title>NCT 127 - 無限的我 (무한적아;Limitless) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:04:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:04:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NCT_127/%E7%84%A1%E9%99%90%E7%9A%84%E6%88%91_%EB%AC%B4%ED%95%9C%EC%A0%81%EC%95%84Limitless/" title="NCT 127 - 無限的我 (무한적아;Limitless) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어젯밤 내 세계를 뒤 흔들었던 꿈이 <br>악몽인지 혹은 나 아직 꿈 속인지 <br>날 이끈 빛을 따라간 꿈 속 미로 <br>그 곳에서 발견한 또 하나의 통로 <br>공간이 열려 from the bottom up <br>낯선 암흑 속 집요한 call <br>마침내 날 닮은 너를 봐 <br>난 너고 넌 나야 <br>날 두드리고 깨우는 그 빛과 소리를 따라가 <br>전율이 흘러 마침내 알게 돼 <br>Oh baby it’s you <br>이제 시작이야 무한의 나 <br>동의 처음과 서의 끝 쪽부터 <br>빛은 암흑 속 퍼질 수록 강해져 가 <br>눈을 떠 봐 오 <br>점점 커져가 나의 노래가 <br>봤니 뜨겁고 터질듯한 세계 <br>들리니 우리는 하나가 돼 <br>Baby I don’t want nobody but you <br>Ho ho wake me up thirsty thirsty for love <br>Wake me wake me up thirsty thirsty <br>다들 꿈을 쫓았어 다 속은 채 <br>대부분 자기만 진짜 라고 해 <br>혹은 숨어버려 등을 돌린 채 <br>반복되는 매일들은 잔혹해 <br>거짓은 들러붙어 끈적해 <br>회색 빛 도시 It ain’t got a chance <br>언제 오나 싶던 먼 미래 <br>하 지금 눈앞에 <br>짧고 강렬했던 푸른 섬광 섬광 <br>깨어난 일곱 번째 감각 감각 <br>하나는 둘이 되고 때론 100이 돼 <br>굳어버린 세상 유연하게 <br>무거워진 세상을 다 바꿔 바꿔 <br>자유로운 우리를 봐 자유로워 <br>그 안에 오직 너만 허락된 허락된 <br>내 마음을 가져가는 자 그게 너인데 <br>공감이 난 필요해 미치도록 원해 <br>네가 필요해 서로를 온전히 <br>느낄 수 있게 해줄 <br>그게 필요해 네가 필요해 <br>Oh baby it’s you <br>이제 시작이야 무한의 나 <br>동의 처음과 서의 끝 쪽부터 <br>빛은 암흑 속 퍼질 수록 강해져 가 <br>눈을 떠 봐 오 <br>점점 커져가 나의 노래가 <br>봤니 뜨겁고 터질듯한 세계 <br>들리니 우리는 하나가 돼 <br>Baby I don’t want nobody but you <br>나를 도와줘 잘 할 수 있게 <br>가끔 난 길을 잃곤 해 <br>우린 결국 이어져 있단 걸 너도 알잖아 <br>사막을 넘어 찾아낸 큰 바다처럼 <br>무한의 너란 존재 <br>Oh baby it’s you <br>이제 시작이야 무한의 나 <br>동의 처음과 서의 끝 쪽부터 <br>빛은 암흑 속 퍼질 수록 강해져 가 <br>눈을 떠 봐 오 <br>점점 커져가 나의 노래가 <br>봤니 뜨겁고 터질듯한 세계 <br>들리니 우리는 하나가 돼 <br>Baby I don’t want nobody but you <br>Ho ho wake me up thirsty thirsty for love <br>Wake me wake me up thirsty thirsty <br>]]></content><category term="NCT 127" label="NCT 127"/><category term="無限的我 (무한적아;Limitless)" label="無限的我 (무한적아;Limitless)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/미스터_팡/불놀이야/</id><title>미스터 팡 - 불놀이야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:07:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:07:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AF%B8%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B0_%ED%8C%A1/%EB%B6%88%EB%86%80%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC/" title="미스터 팡 - 불놀이야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[저녁노을 지고 달빛 흐를때 <br>작은 불꽃으로 내마음을 날려봐 <br>저들판 사이로 가며 내마음의 <br>창을 열고 <br>두팔을 벌려서 돌면 야 불이 춤춘다 <br>불놀이야 <br>꼬마 불꽃송이 꼬리를 물고 <br>동그라미 그려 너의 꿈을 띄워봐 <br>저들판 사이로 가며 <br>내마음의 창을 열고 <br>두팔을 벌려서 돌면 야 불이 춤춘다 <br>불놀이야 <br>저하늘로 떠난 불꽃을 보며 <br>힘껏 소리치며 우리소원 빌어봐 <br>저들판 사이로 가며 <br>내마음의 창을 열고 <br>두팔을 벌려서 돌면 <br>야 불이 춤추는데 <br>불놀이야 <br>저들판 사이로 가며 내마음의 <br>창을 열고 <br>두팔을 벌려서 돌면 야 불이 춤춘다 <br>불놀이야]]></content><category term="미스터 팡" label="미스터 팡"/><category term="불놀이야" label="불놀이야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Flor/Hold_On/</id><title>Flor - Hold On - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:15:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:15:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Flor/Hold_On/" title="Flor - Hold On - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You come to life <br>When all the people on the streets start to rise <br>And the sun starts to open up our eyes <br>We can make this moment stay with us for a while <br><br>You can count on it, I'm where you left me <br>I can count on you, to show me the way <br>We can keep it light, were going somewhere <br>I won't try to fight it, don't feel like it <br><br>In your skin in your hair I'm tangled up <br>In my head in my mind I can't get out <br>When you twist and you turn teach me to run <br>I'd rather hold on <br>I'd rather hold on tight <br><br>You make it right <br>Every moment that we spend without time <br>Pain is something how we manage on the line <br>It's on us now to keep our route come hell high water <br><br>You can count on it, I'm where you left me <br>I can count on you, to show me the way <br>We can keep it light, were going somewhere <br>I won't try to fight it, don't feel like it <br><br>In your skin in your hair I'm tangled up <br>In my head in my mind I can't get out <br>When you twist and you turn teach me to run <br>I'd rather hold on <br>I'd rather hold on tight <br><br>You know that it's you the reason that I come alive come alive <br>It lives in your eyes <br>You know that it's you the reason that I come alive come alive <br>You know that it's you the reason that I come alive come alive <br>It lives in your eyes <br>You know that it's you the reason that I come alive come alive <br><br>In your skin in your hair I'm tangled up <br>In my head in my mind I can't get out <br>When you twist and you turn teach me to run <br>I'd rather hold on <br>I'd rather hold on <br><br>In your skin in your hair I'm tangled up <br>In my head in my mind I can't get out <br>When you twist and you turn teach me to run <br>I'd rather hold on <br>I'd rather hold on tight]]></content><category term="Flor" label="Flor"/><category term="Hold On" label="Hold On"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sia/Move_Your_Body_Single_Mix/</id><title>Sia - Move Your Body (Single Mix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:17:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:17:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sia/Move_Your_Body_Single_Mix/" title="Sia - Move Your Body (Single Mix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Poetry on your body <br>You got it in every way <br>And can't you see <br>it's you I am watchin' <br>I am hot for you <br>in every way <br>And turn around <br>let me see you <br>Wanna free you <br>with my rhythm <br>I know you can't get enough <br>I'ma turn up <br>with my rhythm <br>Your body's poetry <br>speak to me <br>Won't you let me be <br>the rhythm tonight <br>Move your body <br>move your body <br>I wanna be your muse <br>you refuse <br>Let the movement <br>be the rhythm tonight <br>Move your body <br>move your body <br>Your body's poetry <br>speak to me <br>Won't you let me be <br>the rhythm tonight <br>Move your body <br>move your body <br>I wanna be your muse <br>you refuse <br>Let the movement <br>be the rhythm tonight <br>Move your body <br>move your body <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Poetry on your body <br>Got me started <br>it'll never end <br>Feel my rhythm <br>in your system <br>This is heaven <br>I'm your only friend <br>Feel the beat <br>in your chest <br>Beat your chest <br>like an animal <br>Free the beast <br>from it's cage <br>Free the rage <br>like an animal <br>Your body's poetry <br>speak to me <br>Won't you let me be <br>your rhythm tonight <br>Move your body <br>move your body <br>I wanna be your muse <br>you refuse <br>Let the movement <br>be the rhythm tonight <br>Move your body <br>move your body <br>Your body's poetry <br>speak to me <br>Won't you let me <br>be your rhythm tonight <br>Move your body <br>move your body <br>I wanna be your muse <br>you refuse <br>Let the movement <br>be the rhythm tonight <br>Move your body <br>move your body <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>You body's poetry <br>Move your body for me <br>You're body's poetry <br>Move your body for me <br>Your body's poetry <br>speak to me <br>Won't you let me <br>be your rhythm tonight <br>Move your body <br>move your body <br>I wanna be your muse <br>you refuse <br>Let the movement <br>be the rhythm tonight <br>Move your body <br>move your body <br>Your body's poetry <br>speak to me <br>Won't you let me <br>be your rhythm tonight <br>Move your body <br>move your body <br>I wanna be your muse <br>you refuse <br>Let the movement <br>be the rhythm tonight <br>Move your body <br>move your body <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>]]></content><category term="Sia" label="Sia"/><category term="Move Your Body (Single Mix)" label="Move Your Body (Single Mix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tal/Slow_Down_The_Flow/</id><title>Tal - Slow Down The Flow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:18:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:18:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tal/Slow_Down_The_Flow/" title="Tal - Slow Down The Flow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[World, world, world take time to breathe <br>Everybody is always in a hurry <br>Everybody is always in a hurry <br><br>We all have dreams, hopes and desires <br>The world has changed, what can we do <br>We try to run from the rush hour <br>But nothing goes like it should <br><br>Pass me by like I'm a stranger <br>Don't you see the smile I have to offer <br>Tell me when It is all over <br><br>When it's all moving a lil slower <br>Can we slow down the flow <br>Every second seems a lil longer <br>Can we slow down the flow, heyy heyy <br><br>We don't need to run run run <br>When the problem come, they will come <br>We can over come, come, come, come, heyy heyy <br>We don't need to run run run <br>Life can be so fun, make it fun, make it fun <br>We can over come, come, come, come heyy heyy <br><br>Everybody is always in a hurry <br>Everybody is always in a hurry <br><br>We all have dreams, hopes and desires <br>The wait is long, It's pressuring you <br>Life has a way to turn it all over <br><br>And I believe it is true <br><br>Every day you getting stronger <br>Don't you feel life is a little better <br>Feel so good when It's all over <br>When It's all moving a little slower <br>Can we slow down the flow <br>Every second seems a little longer <br>Can we slow down the flow heyy heyy <br><br>We don't need to run run run <br>When the problem come, they will come <br>We can over come, come, come, come, heyy heyy <br>We don't need to run run run <br>Life can be so fun, make it fun, make it fun <br>We can over come, come, come, come, come heyy heyy <br><br>Can we slow down the flow <br><br>Every second seems a little longer <br>Can we slow down the flow heyy heyy <br>Can we slow down the flow <br>Every second seems a little longer <br>Can we slow down the flow heyy heyy <br><br>We don't need to run run run <br>When the problem come, they will come <br>We can over come, come, come, come, heyy heyy <br>We don't need to run run run <br>Life can be so fun, make it fun, make it fun <br>We can over come, come, come, come, come heyy heyy <br><br>World, world, world take time to breathe <br>Everybody is always in a hurry]]></content><category term="Tal" label="Tal"/><category term="Slow Down The Flow" label="Slow Down The Flow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Fallen_Angel/</id><title>Bee Gees - Fallen Angel - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:20:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:20:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Fallen_Angel/" title="Bee Gees - Fallen Angel - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fool in the night on the stair <br>With the light by the window <br>Out in the jungle of life she was <br>Yearning to go <br>All of the years I've been there for the tears <br>She will sell you <br>Out in the city she search for the face <br>That she knew <br><br>Did you believe that a love so alive <br>Could be over <br><br>Caroline <br>Fallen Angel <br>Caroline <br>Oh oh oh, oh oh oh <br>oh oh oh oh <br>Fallen Angel <br>I'm so lost <br>Tonight, lonely tonight <br>Lonely tonight <br><br>Fool is the father who clings to the <br>Child he is losing <br>Mother too weary to question <br>The wisdom of youth <br>There with your head in your hand <br>As you pray to her picture <br>Out in the rain she would search <br>For somebody to hold <br><br>Did you believe you could find <br>What you need with a stranger <br><br>Caroline <br>Fallen Angel <br>Caroline <br>Oh oh oh, oh oh oh <br>oh oh oh oh <br>Fallen Angel <br>I'm so lost <br>Tonight, lonely tonight <br>Lonely tonight <br><br>Did you believe that a love so alive <br>Could be over <br><br>Caroline <br>Fallen Angel <br>Caroline <br>Oh oh oh, oh oh oh <br>oh oh oh oh <br>Fallen Angel <br>I'm so lost <br>Tonight, lonely tonight <br>Lonely tonight]]></content><category term="Bee Gees" label="Bee Gees"/><category term="Fallen Angel" label="Fallen Angel"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Above_And_Beyond/</id><title>Bee Gees - Above And Beyond - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:20:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:20:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Above_And_Beyond/" title="Bee Gees - Above And Beyond - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I stumble in the night <br>Never really knew what it would've been like <br>You're no longer there to <br>Break my fall <br>The heartache over you <br>I gave it everything but I couldn't get through <br>I never saw the signs <br>You're the last to know when love is blind <br><br>All the tears and the turbulent years <br>When I would not wait for no one <br>I didn't stop, take a look at myself <br>And see me losing you <br><br>When the lonely heart breaks <br>It's the one that forsakes <br>It's the dream that we stole <br>And I'm missing you more <br>And the fire that will roar <br>There's a hole in my soul <br>For you it's goodbye <br>And for me it's to cry <br>For whom the bell tolls <br><br>Seen you in a magazine <br>A picture at a party <br>Where you shouldn't have been <br>Hangin' on the arm of someone else <br>I'm still in love with you <br>Won't you come back to your little boy blue <br>I've come to feel inside <br>This precious love was never mine <br>Now I know but a little too late <br>That I could not live without you <br>In the dark of the broad daylight <br>I promise I'll be there <br><br>When the lonely heart breaks <br>It's the one that forsakes <br>It's the dream that we stole <br>And I'm missing you more <br>And the fire that will roar <br>There's a hole in my soul <br>For you it's goodbye <br>And for me it's to cry <br>For whom the bell tolls <br><br>I never knew there'd be times like this <br>When I couldn't reach out to no one <br>Am I never gonna find someone <br>That knows me like you do <br>Are you leaving me a helpless child <br>When it took so long to save me <br>Fight the devil and the deep blue sea <br>I'll follow you anywhere <br>I promise I'll be there <br><br>When the lonely heart breaks <br>It's the one that forsakes <br>It's the dream that we stole <br>And I'm missing you more <br>And the fire that will roar <br>There's a hole in my soul <br>For you it's goodbye <br>And for me it's to cry <br>For whom the bell tolls]]></content><category term="Bee Gees" label="Bee Gees"/><category term="Above And Beyond" label="Above And Beyond"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Above_And_Beyond/</id><title>Bee Gees - Above And Beyond - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:20:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:20:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Above_And_Beyond/" title="Bee Gees - Above And Beyond - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Woman in a million to me <br>I never loved so much <br>Is it any wonder I'm alive <br>No one ever knows what makes a <br>Virtue or a vice <br>Let it be the spell I'm under <br>These naked eyes <br>Let it be the rain and thunder comes <br><br>I go above and beyond the sun <br>Some love never dies <br>Story of our lives, ohh <br>Swear by the stars above <br>And late at night I pray to myself <br>That you and I got everything we need <br>I'd give it all for you and me <br><br>Love is the earth and the wind <br>And the fire and the soul <br>Love is above and beyond any eye to behold <br>Love is the key and the cause <br>And it's makin' us whole <br><br>Made me a little crazy, but I <br>Soon realize my fate <br>Every little touch I'm paralyzed <br>No one ever know what makes <br>An angel in disguise <br>Let me be the one to taste you <br>Those naked eyes <br>No pity if the city ever crumbles down <br><br>I go above and beyond the sun <br>Some love never dies <br>Story of our lives, ohh <br>Swear by the stars above <br>And late at night I pray to myself <br>That you and I got everything we need <br>I'd give it all for you and me <br><br>Love is the earth and the wind <br>And the fire and we share <br>Love is the force and the edge <br>And it's ready for those who dare <br>Love is above and beyond <br>And I'm taking you there <br>And baby, I'll take you there <br><br>I go above and beyond the sun <br>Some love never dies <br>Story of our lives, ohh <br>Swear by the stars above <br>And late at night I pray to myself <br>That you and I got everything we need <br>I'd give it all for you and me <br><br>Love is the earth and the wind <br>And the fire and the soul <br>Love is the key and the cause <br>And it's makin' us whole <br>Love is the force and the edge <br>And it's yours if you dare <br>Love is above and beyond <br>And I'm taking you there <br>Baby, I'll take you there <br><br>I go above and beyond the sun <br>Some love never dies <br>Story of our lives, ohh <br>Swear by the stars above <br>And late at night I pray to myself <br>That you and I got everything we need <br>I'd give it all for you and me]]></content><category term="Bee Gees" label="Bee Gees"/><category term="Above And Beyond" label="Above And Beyond"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Blue_Island/</id><title>Bee Gees - Blue Island - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:20:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:20:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Blue_Island/" title="Bee Gees - Blue Island - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Living in a world that dies within <br>You are they who try and touch the wind <br>You could be the blessed one that <br>Makes me love you <br>And doing what you've never done before <br>Taking every wave that hits the shore <br>You could be a silver star that shines <br>On my blue island <br>See you on a blue island <br>Take you to a blue island <br><br>You can see the rain <br>You can feel the pain <br>That no part of me is going through <br>Everybody say, we can find a way <br>Do you know the place you're going to <br>You're going to a blue island <br><br>This is what the lonely heart must know <br>This is what it takes to make it grow <br>You could be a child alone <br>But you may save the world <br>Maybe it's the words that mean goodbye <br>There but for the grace of God go I <br>I can see an open door that leads to my blue island <br>Gonna be a blue island <br>See you on a blue island <br>Take you to a blue island <br><br>Blue island <br>Blue island <br>Blue island]]></content><category term="Bee Gees" label="Bee Gees"/><category term="Blue Island" label="Blue Island"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Anything_For_You/</id><title>Bee Gees - Anything For You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:20:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:20:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Anything_For_You/" title="Bee Gees - Anything For You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ooh ooh ooh <br>When you wait and you watch <br>And you're wishing for something wild <br>I figure I can please you someday someway <br>I figure I can put your love on trial <br>I'm taking you back to school <br>Talk about making it something real <br>Nobody could deny you anything <br><br>You know I'd do anything <br>Anything for you <br>You know I'd do anything <br>Anything for you <br>You know I'd do anything <br>Anything for you <br>You know I'd do anything <br>Anything for you <br><br>You you you <br>You can run with the fun <br>You can tickle my nerves inside <br>In the face of heartbreak, heartache <br>It's gonna be a magic carpet ride <br>Better we make it soon <br>Let it be the one that make you <br>Cry for more <br>Anyone else would buy you anything <br>I'd do anything <br><br>You know I'd do anything <br>Anything for you <br>You know I'd do anything <br>Anything for you <br>You know I'd do anything <br>Anything for you <br>You know I'd do anything <br>Anything for you <br><br>I'd do anything <br>I'd do anything <br>I'd do anything <br>I'd do anything <br><br>You know I'd do anything <br>Anything for you <br>You know I'd do anything <br>Anything for you <br>You know I'd do anything <br>Anything for you <br>You know I'd do anything <br>Anything for you <br><br>I'd do anything <br>I'd do anything <br>I'd do anything <br>I'd do anything]]></content><category term="Bee Gees" label="Bee Gees"/><category term="Anything For You" label="Anything For You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Heart_Like_Mine/</id><title>Bee Gees - Heart Like Mine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:20:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:20:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Heart_Like_Mine/" title="Bee Gees - Heart Like Mine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Night grows cold <br>I've been lonely so much <br>Out of reach <br>Save it only for me <br>Nothing in life is the same <br>And the sooner we stop to start <br><br>And there's a heart like mine <br>Somewhere in this world <br>There's a heart like mine <br>Beating but left to burn <br><br>Maybe you can hide your face forever <br>God knows it's true <br>That when you search for someone <br>There's a heart like mine <br>There's a heart like mine <br>To be heard <br><br>Souls on fire <br>Feel her voice in your ear <br>She goes on <br>Living only for me <br>Nothing you say could be wrong <br>'Cause you give me the lovers sign <br><br>And there's a heart like mine <br>Somewhere in this world <br>There's a heart like mine <br>Beating but left to burn <br><br>Maybe we can share it all forever <br>But not 'til we do <br>I'm gonna search for someone <br>There's a heart like mine <br>There's a heart like mine <br>To be heard <br><br>And baby are we waking up together <br>'Cause God knows it's you <br>If there is love for someone <br><br>And there's a heart like mine <br>Somewhere in this world <br>There's a heart like mine <br>Beating but left to burn <br><br>Maybe we can share it all forever <br>But not 'til we do <br>I'm gonna search for someone <br><br>There's a heart like mine <br>There's a heart like mine <br><br>To be heard <br><br>There's a heart like mine <br>There's a heart like mine]]></content><category term="Bee Gees" label="Bee Gees"/><category term="Heart Like Mine" label="Heart Like Mine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Haunted_House/</id><title>Bee Gees - Haunted House - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:20:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:20:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Haunted_House/" title="Bee Gees - Haunted House - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know baby's bad for my self esteem <br>FInd another face for your sympathy <br>Some of us cry, some of them lie <br>But no one sees inside <br><br>The spark of baby's eyes and I turn to stone <br>Maybe I can't survive in the danger zone <br>Sounds of the night <br>Streets without light <br>And baby's not alone <br><br>Try to hold her to myself <br>Someone else is breaking all my dreams, she <br>Needs so many games to play <br>One more time I climb the stairs <br>Open up the door and she was gone <br>And baby here I go <br><br>Like a lamb to slaughter <br>Don't stop haunting me in this old house <br>I still love you when you're not around <br>I'm still waiting for your midnight ride <br>I'll still love you when it's cold outside <br>Me so sorry that I let you down <br>But you keep haunting me in this old town <br><br>SPOKEN <br>And the smile is no longer there <br>The face and the eyes and the hair <br>Nothing stands the test of time <br>You live forever, never mine <br>I cling to dreams that turn to sand <br>Our life is now a distant land <br><br>We commit emotional suicide <br>Every single room is electrified <br>Your memory shadowing me <br>The house where sorrow hides <br><br>Pull it down, blow it up <br>Help me send these walls of love away <br>And baby here I go <br><br>Like a lamb to slaughter <br>Don't stop haunting me in this old house <br>I still love you when you're not around <br>I'm still waiting for your midnight ride <br>I'll still love you when it's cold outside <br>Me so sorry that I let you down <br>But you keep haunting me in this old town]]></content><category term="Bee Gees" label="Bee Gees"/><category term="Haunted House" label="Haunted House"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Omega_Man/</id><title>Bee Gees - Omega Man - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:20:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:20:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Omega_Man/" title="Bee Gees - Omega Man - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We set the same scene <br>Circumstances different than they <br>Might have been <br>People in two places can be <br>Pulled into a scheme <br>Never what you're fighting for <br><br>Life alone <br>Lose a lover's arms <br>Never makes it easy when you try too hard <br>I wish you would define what you feel <br>Hard on or letting go <br><br>I'm the Omega Man <br>Stand tall and understand <br>Everybody needs a plan <br>Mine is a better way <br>There'll be trouble in the world <br>Sex and the single girl <br>I'm an over eager man <br>Find me a better way <br>Find me a better way <br><br>We share the same pain <br>Underneath the covers I will set you free <br>I will prove to you my love is <br>Older than the sky <br>Stronger than the night is long <br><br>Lord of hearts <br>Leader of us all <br>Let it be together if we rise or fall <br>Or is it just my imagination <br>Or the light of a precious stone <br>You'll never be alone <br><br>I'm the Omega Man <br>I travel over land <br>Everybody needs a plan <br>Find me a better way <br>There'll be trouble in the world <br>Sex and the single girl <br>I'm an over eager man <br>Find me a better way <br>Find me a better way <br><br>Here at the scene of the crime <br>Laid in your arms I will die <br>I know it's more than infatuation <br>That's keeping this man alive <br><br>I'm the Omega Man <br>Stand tall and understand <br>Everybody needs a plan <br>Mine is a better way <br>There'll be trouble in the world <br>Sex and the single girl <br>I'm an over eager man <br>Find me a better way <br>Find me a better way <br>I'm the Omega Man <br>I travel over land <br>Everybody needs a plan <br>Find me a better way <br>There'll be trouble in the world <br>Sex and the single girl <br>I'm an over eager man <br>Find me a better way <br>Find me a better way]]></content><category term="Bee Gees" label="Bee Gees"/><category term="Omega Man" label="Omega Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/How_To_Fall_In_Love_Pt1/</id><title>Bee Gees - How To Fall In Love, Pt.1 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:20:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:20:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/How_To_Fall_In_Love_Pt1/" title="Bee Gees - How To Fall In Love, Pt.1 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I got a bad sensation <br>The enemy is all around <br>The traces of my naked heart <br>Are laid upon the ground <br>I suffered side effects <br>That might have been forever <br>Even in my dreams <br>And I was left alone to pray <br>When there was no one in the way <br>And nothin' what it seemed <br><br>And from a hard time, play time <br>Took a trip around the world <br>Made myself invisible <br>The taste was in the wine <br>And just when the thought of someone <br>Needing me forever <br>I don't believe the words are true <br>That only she could be my savior <br><br>Experience is not enough <br>I'll show you how to fall in love <br>She said experience is not enough <br>I'll show you how to fall in love <br><br>And she's all alone with me <br>Every night <br>And lighting all my days of sorrow <br>On my own <br>If there was any more to give <br>You know I'd sacrifice it for her <br><br>And in the prime of my life <br>I was blessed and I was sent <br>Someone sweet and innocent <br>And nervous when she kissed <br>And in the face of my <br>Forbidden fruit forever <br>Miracles are mine <br>And knowing I'm the first <br>In her secret universe <br>There's no sense of space and time <br><br>You take a small town, young girl <br>Someone warm and wonderful <br>That any man would understand <br>That love is like the wind <br>Something deep inside to give you <br>And when the words get in the way <br>The only thing you need is silence <br><br>Experience is not enough <br>I'll show you how to fall in love <br>She said experience is not enough <br>I'll show you how to fall in love]]></content><category term="Bee Gees" label="Bee Gees"/><category term="How To Fall In Love, Pt.1" label="How To Fall In Love, Pt.1"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Kiss_Of_Life/</id><title>Bee Gees - Kiss Of Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:20:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:20:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Kiss_Of_Life/" title="Bee Gees - Kiss Of Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Never more aware of what you do <br>I got you leavin' me and missing you <br>And me believing that you've never done right <br>When you've never done wrong <br><br>You been comin' to me late at night <br>It's not the eye alone that gives you sight <br>I've never given anybody my soul <br>But I'm coming undone <br><br>I'm a survivor but I'm reaching my low <br>But I'm not ready to die <br><br>I'm here for the kiss of life <br>I'm here for the kiss of life <br>Just give me the kiss of life <br><br>Watch them hold you <br>Count their faces <br>A never ending line <br>But they're only imitations <br>Existing out of time <br><br>So now you're telling me it's just a ring <br>You say it's nothing but it's everything <br>I'm under pressure and I'm under <br>Your gun and I'm fingers and thumbs <br><br>You got the questions and the answers <br>I know <br>I'm being buried alive <br><br>I'm here for the kiss of life <br>I'm here for the kiss of life <br>Just give me the kiss of life <br><br>I can't stay here <br>Lost without you <br>Strangers in the dark <br>Holyangel <br>Living for you <br>To love and never cry <br><br>I'm a survivor but I'm reaching my low <br>But I'm not ready to die <br><br>I'm here for the kiss of life <br>I'm here for the kiss of life <br>Just give me the kiss of life]]></content><category term="Bee Gees" label="Bee Gees"/><category term="Kiss Of Life" label="Kiss Of Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Paying_The_Price_Of_Love/</id><title>Bee Gees - Paying The Price Of Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:20:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:20:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bee_Gees/Paying_The_Price_Of_Love/" title="Bee Gees - Paying The Price Of Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How did you find there was somebody <br>More than you want me <br>I never understood <br>Maybe I have never had you <br>I have been lonely for you lately <br>I can't wait another day <br>And when you let me get you close to me <br>You run and leave me <br><br>Paying the price of love <br>The start of my end over you <br>When you're doin' it for someone <br>Who'll never be free <br>Now is all there will ever be <br><br>No more to live without you <br>All the nights I dream about you <br><br>Deep in the dark of the night <br>I'm a man on a mission <br>But safer with you home <br>Never would I make you sorry <br>You are the only drug I crave <br>And I've been saving everyday <br>I held it all inside, I pray <br>You don't forget you got me <br><br>Paying the price of love <br>My heart in my hands over you <br>But the battle is just not fair <br>You'll never be free <br>That emotion is always replaying <br><br>You know the strongest heart <br>Is broken when it falls <br>You turn and walk away <br>And let it die <br>I got this picture in my head <br>Of you in someone else's bed <br>And I am torn apart <br>I'm torn apart inside <br><br>I'll build my world around you <br>I was nothing when I found you <br>Paying the price of love <br><br>Paying the price of love <br>The start of my end over you <br>When you're doing it for someone <br>Who'll never be free <br>Now is all there will ever be <br><br>Paying the price of love <br>My heart in my hands over you <br>But the battle is just not fair <br>You'll never be free <br>That emotion is always replaying]]></content><category term="Bee Gees" label="Bee Gees"/><category term="Paying The Price Of Love" label="Paying The Price Of Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리사/Im_Sorry/</id><title>리사 - I`m Sorry - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:21:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:21:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EC%82%AC/Im_Sorry/" title="리사 - I`m Sorry - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아파도 울지 않겠다 했는데 <br>어느새 눈가가 뜨거워져 <br>눈물이 마르지 못할 것 같아 <br>다 잊고 지워도 눈물이 너만 찾아 <br>목이 메여와도 <br>애써 꾹 참았는데 <br>기억보다 빠른 이 눈물에 <br>끝내는 고갤 떨궈 <br>Baby I'm Sorry <br>이 못난 나의 이 Story <br>너 없이 숨쉬는 난 <br>어떻게 해도 행복할 수 없어 <br>Baby I'm Sorry <br>추억도 못난 이 Story <br>지킬 수 없었기에 <br>붙잡지 못할 이유가 됐나봐 <br>Baby I'm Sorry <br>바보 같지 내가 <br>그땐 잘 몰랐는데 <br>이제와 더 아파하는 내가 <br>끝내는 고갤 떨궈 <br>Baby I'm Sorry <br>이 못난 나의 이 Story <br>너 없이 숨쉬는 난 <br>어떻게 해도 행복할 수 없어 <br>네가 떠난 후로 매일 <br>그 자리에 서 기다려 <br>내 추억엔 너만 살아 <br>네가 너무 보고 싶어 <br>아직도 기다리잖아 <br>사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>Baby I'm Sorry <br>아픔만 남은 이 Story <br>눈물로 널 부르면 <br>내게 다시 돌아올 것 같은데 <br>Baby I'm Sorry <br>이 못난 나의 이 Story <br>너 없이 숨쉬는 난 <br>어떻게 해도 행복할 수 없어 <br>Baby I'm Sorry <br>Baby I'm Sorry <br>Baby I'm Sorry <br>붙잡지 못할 이유가 됐나봐 <br>Baby I'm Sorry <br>Baby I'm Sorry <br>Baby I'm Sorry <br>Baby I'm Sorry <br>]]></content><category term="리사" label="리사"/><category term="I`m Sorry" label="I`m Sorry"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nik/Vi_Vandt_I_Dag_Feat_Landsholdet/</id><title>Nik - Vi Vandt I Dag (Feat. Landsholdet) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:22:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:22:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nik/Vi_Vandt_I_Dag_Feat_Landsholdet/" title="Nik - Vi Vandt I Dag (Feat. Landsholdet) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[La' mig dromme <br>Dromme om mirakler <br>La' mit oje se <br>En skov af haender <br>Hvor vi kom fra <br>Er der ingen der glemmer <br>Nar vi flyver <br>Er det uden vinger <br>Sa hvis de spo'r os hva' vi tror pa <br>Si'r vi 'vi tror pa det her ojeblik' <br> hvor vi star her <br>Skulder mod skulder <br>I rodt and hvidt <br>Ja, vi' dem fra dannevang <br><br>Det stod skrevet i vinden at vi ville gore det <br>Sa vi finder en vej igennem morket <br>De skal vide, at vi er vindere <br>For selv nar vi falder, falder <br>Rejser vi os op igen <br>Med hjaelpen fra en ven <br>and de skal se vores flag <br>For vi vandt idag <br><br>Vi star sammen, sa vi star staerkt <br>Vi fra et lille land men ambitionerne har voksevaerk <br>Du lytter til et dope flow ingen mundkurv <br>Hop fra perronen med pa vognen triumftog <br>Hojt pa stra, vi maler byen rod og himlen bla <br>Vi er foran hele flokken, de far brug for nye kondisko <br>Vi sejler op ad aen, vi sejler ned igen <br>Og nar man siger vores navn, sa ved de hvem]]></content><category term="Nik" label="Nik"/><category term="Vi Vandt I Dag (Feat. Landsholdet)" label="Vi Vandt I Dag (Feat. Landsholdet)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DiBL/What_Cha_Lookin_At__Original_Mix/</id><title>DiBL - What Cha Lookin` At? (Original Mix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:24:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:24:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DiBL/What_Cha_Lookin_At__Original_Mix/" title="DiBL - What Cha Lookin` At? (Original Mix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been thinking <br>about people around me <br>worry about they <br>might say stupid shit <br>about me you know <br>but now I’m kinda tired thinking <br>about you and you and you all <br>I'm just gonna do what I want <br>With that confidency walking <br>and that confidency looking <br>I’m getting all attention <br>with that weird looking eyes <br>from you <br>You might think this is funny <br>or might be hilariously <br>but You donno how I <br>feel how I’ve been waiting <br>for this now <br>you know <br>but You donno how I <br>feel how I’ve been waiting <br>for this now <br>but You donno how I feel <br>Ah a a a a I <br>don’t care what you say <br>I’m just gonna go my way <br>I’m just gonna keep my style <br>You a a a a a <br>are gonna like this feeling <br>but if you don’t <br>like this well then <br>What cha lookin at <br>what cha lookin at <br>sick and <br>tired of you telling me <br>what to do R U done <br>you done <br>now let me give <br>you some wisdom <br>for ppl like you <br>who R U to tell me <br>while you’ doin the same <br>ol things around you <br>huh mind your own business <br>with this confidency boom clap <br>and this confidency feeling <br>I'm solving finencial problem <br>I had all around me <br>you might this is unfair <br>or might be feeling jealousy <br>but you don't know how I've <br>been through to reach now <br>but you don't know how I've <br>been through to reach now <br>but you don't know how I've <br>been <br>Ah a a a a I <br>don’t care what you say <br>I’m just gonna go my way <br>I’m just gonna keep my style <br>You a a a a a <br>are gonna like this feeling <br>but if you don’t <br>like this well then <br>What cha lookin at <br>what cha lookin at <br>I’m just gonna go my way <br>I’m just gonna keep my style <br>I’m just gonna go my way <br>I’m just gonna keep the sound <br>I’m just gonna go my way <br>I’m just gonna keep my style <br>I'm just gonna do this fuckin way <br>I'm just gonna do this fuckin way <br>Ah a a a a I <br>don’t care what you say <br>I’m just gonna go my way <br>I’m just gonna keep my style <br>You a a a a a <br>are gonna like this feeling <br>but if you don’t <br>like this well then <br>What cha lookin at <br>what cha lookin at <br>What cha lookin at <br>what cha lookin at <br>What cha lookin at <br>what cha lookin at <br>What cha lookin at <br>what cha lookin at <br>What cha lookin at <br>what cha lookin at <br>]]></content><category term="DiBL" label="DiBL"/><category term="What Cha Lookin` At? (Original Mix)" label="What Cha Lookin` At? (Original Mix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DiBL/What_Cha_Lookin_At__Radio_Edit/</id><title>DiBL - What Cha Lookin` At? (Radio Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:24:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:24:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DiBL/What_Cha_Lookin_At__Radio_Edit/" title="DiBL - What Cha Lookin` At? (Radio Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been thinking <br>about people around me <br>worry about they <br>might say stupid shit <br>about me you know <br>but now I’m kinda tired thinking <br>about you and you and you all <br>I'm just gonna do what I want <br>With that confidency walking <br>and that confidency looking <br>I’m getting all attention <br>with that weird looking eyes <br>from you <br>You might think this is funny <br>or might be hilariously <br>but You donno how I <br>feel how I’ve been waiting <br>for this now <br>you know <br>but You donno how I <br>feel how I’ve been waiting <br>for this now <br>but You donno how I feel <br>Ah a a a a I <br>don’t care what you say <br>I’m just gonna go my way <br>I’m just gonna keep my style <br>You a a a a a <br>are gonna like this feeling <br>but if you don’t <br>like this well then <br>What cha lookin at <br>what cha lookin at <br>sick and <br>tired of you telling me <br>what to do R U done <br>you done <br>now let me give <br>you some wisdom <br>for ppl like you <br>who R U to tell me <br>while you’ doin the same <br>ol things around you <br>huh mind your own business <br>with this confidency boom clap <br>and this confidency feeling <br>I'm solving finencial problem <br>I had all around me <br>you might this is unfair <br>or might be feeling jealousy <br>but you don't know how I've <br>been through to reach now <br>but you don't know how I've <br>been through to reach now <br>but you don't know how I've <br>been <br>Ah a a a a I <br>don’t care what you say <br>I’m just gonna go my way <br>I’m just gonna keep my style <br>You a a a a a <br>are gonna like this feeling <br>but if you don’t <br>like this well then <br>What cha lookin at <br>what cha lookin at <br>I’m just gonna go my way <br>I’m just gonna keep my style <br>I’m just gonna go my way <br>I’m just gonna keep the sound <br>I’m just gonna go my way <br>I’m just gonna keep my style <br>I'm just gonna do this fuckin way <br>I'm just gonna do this fuckin way <br>Ah a a a a I <br>don’t care what you say <br>I’m just gonna go my way <br>I’m just gonna keep my style <br>You a a a a a <br>are gonna like this feeling <br>but if you don’t <br>like this well then <br>What cha lookin at <br>what cha lookin at <br>What cha lookin at <br>what cha lookin at <br>What cha lookin at <br>what cha lookin at <br>What cha lookin at <br>what cha lookin at <br>What cha lookin at <br>what cha lookin at <br>]]></content><category term="DiBL" label="DiBL"/><category term="What Cha Lookin` At? (Radio Edit)" label="What Cha Lookin` At? (Radio Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Afonso_Cappelo/Love_Of_My_Life_The_Voice_Brasil_2016/</id><title>Afonso Cappelo - Love Of My Life (The Voice Brasil 2016) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:25:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:25:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Afonso_Cappelo/Love_Of_My_Life_The_Voice_Brasil_2016/" title="Afonso Cappelo - Love Of My Life (The Voice Brasil 2016) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love of my life you hurt me <br>You've broken my heart and now you live me <br>Love of my life can't you see <br>Bring it back, bring it back <br>Don't take it away from me <br>Because you don't know <br>What it means to me <br><br>Love of my life don't leave me <br>You've stolen my love <br>And now desert me <br><br>Love of my life, can't you see <br>Bring it back, bring it back <br>Don't take it away from me <br>Because you don't know <br>What it means to me <br><br>You will remember <br>When this is blown over <br>And everything's all by the way <br>When I grow older <br><br>You will remember <br>When this is blown over <br>And everything's all by the way <br>When I grow older <br>I will be there at your side <br>To remind you how, I still love you <br>I still love you <br><br>Back, hurry back <br>Don't take it away from me <br>Because you don't know <br>What it means to me <br>Love of my life <br>Love of my life <br>Oh, yeah]]></content><category term="Afonso Cappelo" label="Afonso Cappelo"/><category term="Love Of My Life (The Voice Brasil 2016)" label="Love Of My Life (The Voice Brasil 2016)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kassia_Marvila/Killing_Me_Softly_The_Voice_Brasil_2016/</id><title>Kassia Marvila - Killing Me Softly (The Voice Brasil 2016) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:25:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:25:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kassia_Marvila/Killing_Me_Softly_The_Voice_Brasil_2016/" title="Kassia Marvila - Killing Me Softly (The Voice Brasil 2016) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Killing me softly with his song <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>I heard he sang a good song <br>I heard he had a style <br>And so I came to see him <br>And listen for a while <br>And there he was this young boy <br>Stranger to my eyes <br>Strumming my pain with his finger <br>Singing my life with his words <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Telling my whole life with his words <br>Killing me softly <br>With his song <br>I felt all flushed with fever <br>Embarrassed by the crowd <br>I felt he found my letters <br>And read each one out loud <br>I prayed that he would finish <br>But he just kept right on <br>Strumming my pain <br>with his fingers one time <br>Singing my life <br>with his words two times <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Telling my whole life with his words <br>Killing me softly <br>With his song <br>]]></content><category term="Kassia Marvila" label="Kassia Marvila"/><category term="Killing Me Softly (The Voice Brasil 2016)" label="Killing Me Softly (The Voice Brasil 2016)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스윗소로우/해피뉴이어/</id><title>스윗소로우 - 해피뉴이어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:25:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:25:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%EC%9C%97%EC%86%8C%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B0/%ED%95%B4%ED%94%BC%EB%89%B4%EC%9D%B4%EC%96%B4/" title="스윗소로우 - 해피뉴이어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어쩜 1년이 다 <br>지나버렸네 <br>뭘 했다고 벌써 <br>새해라는 거냐 하 <br>시간 참 빠르다 <br>한 살 더 먹는구나 <br>다들 참 고생 많았다 <br>올 한 해도 <br>쉽지는 않겠지만 <br>좋은 날들이 많았으면 해 <br>복 많이 많이 받아라 <br>후끈후끈 가열차게 연애하고 <br>다이어트 금연 성공하시고 <br>좋은 데 취직하고 <br>모두 건강하기를 <br>HAPPY <br>해피뉴이어 해피뉴이어 <br>올핸 뭐라도 되겠지 <br>쫄지 말고 살자 즐겁게 <br>해피뉴이어 해피뉴이어 <br>올핸 하는 일마다 <br>술술 잘 풀릴 꺼야 <br>그랬으면 좋겠다 <br>해피뉴이어 행복해 <br>해피뉴이어 <br>스트레스 받지 말고 <br>가내 두루 평안하시고 <br>뜻한 바 이루시고 <br>웃음 가득하시고 <br>회사 안팎으로 <br>경사 차고 넘쳐서 <br>돈 많이 버소서 <br>행복하소서 <br>HAPPY <br>해피뉴이어 해피뉴이어 <br>올핸 뭐라도 되겠지 <br>쫄지 말고 살자 즐겁게 <br>해피뉴이어 해피뉴이어 <br>올핸 꿈꾸는 일마다 <br>확 잘 풀릴 거야 <br>그랬으면 좋겠다 <br>해피뉴이어 <br>해피뉴이어 <br>해피뉴이어 행복해 <br>근하신년 <br>송구영신 <br>해피뉴이어 <br>YEAH <br>]]></content><category term="스윗소로우" label="스윗소로우"/><category term="해피뉴이어" label="해피뉴이어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Professor_Green/Active_feat_Dream_Mclean/</id><title>Professor Green - Active (feat. Dream Mclean) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:28:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:28:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Professor_Green/Active_feat_Dream_Mclean/" title="Professor Green - Active (feat. Dream Mclean) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm active <br>Went out and I came home with an actress <br>I told her I was done with all the madness <br>Then she found a click under my mattress <br>I'm active, I'm active, I'm <br><br>Active, oof <br>That back's got me doing backflips <br>I'm wavey, I'm Swayze, I'm Patrick <br>Tennis, tennis, tennis, tennis racket <br>I'm active, I'm active <br><br>I'm PG, I'm dead cool <br>Vodka and Red Bull <br>Superhero, Deadpool <br>Learn a lesson, boy, get schooled <br>Crush you out, I'll X you <br>Fuck you and my ex too <br>I ain't talking about my ex wife <br>I'm unique, I'm special <br>I'm active <br>Tennis racket, racket, racket, racket, racket <br>Tell me, whose coat is that jacket <br>And then tell me whose coke is that packet <br>Cause I'm active, I'm active <br>I'm active, I'm batshit <br>Crazy, I'm crazy <br>Broke into a flat through a cat flap <br>Then took a shit in the catnip <br>I'm that sick, three birds <br>One rubber, Jimmy hat trick <br>And I'll be this way till I'm a geriatric, I'm active, I'm <br><br>Active, oof <br>That back's got me doing backflips <br>I'm wavey, I'm Swayze, I'm Patrick <br>Tennis, tennis, tennis, tennis racket <br>I'm active, I'm active <br><br>I'm active <br>Went out and I came home with an actress <br>I told her I was done with all the madness <br>Then she found a click under my mattress <br>I'm active, I'm active, I'm <br><br>Savagery <br>Andre Agassi <br>I'm on centre court like racket, please <br>Give me the racket, please <br>Don't make it go John McEnroe <br>Kick down the door to your happy home <br>Back in this, I'm backing Pro <br>Like Dwight Yorke and Andy Cole <br>Played ball, init <br>Yeah, your wifey's a whore, init <br>Relationship goals, I scored in it <br>In the box, I'm onside <br>I'm off nut, I'm online, I'm on stuff <br>And at band camp this one time, I was active <br>Two girls in one night, I smacked it <br>I told her just let me wet the head like a baptist <br>Next thing you know, woosh, Atlantis <br>I'm active, I'm active <br><br>I'm active <br>Went out and I came home with an actress <br>I told her I was done with all the madness <br>Then she found a click under my mattress <br>I'm active, I'm active, I'm <br><br>Active, oof <br>That back squat was doing backflips <br>I'm wavey, I'm Swayze, I'm Patrick <br>Tennis, tennis, tennis, tennis racket <br>I'm active, I'm active, I'm]]></content><category term="Professor Green" label="Professor Green"/><category term="Active (feat. Dream Mclean)" label="Active (feat. Dream Mclean)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rich_Brian/Who_That_Be_Josh_Pan__West1ne_Remix/</id><title>Rich Brian - Who That Be (Josh Pan &amp; West1ne Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:28:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:28:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rich_Brian/Who_That_Be_Josh_Pan__West1ne_Remix/" title="Rich Brian - Who That Be (Josh Pan &amp; West1ne Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yo bitch on me but you can never do nothing <br>Cuz yo momma raised a pussy <br>Everytime I walk to the drop top, can't help but <br>Close my eyes cuz my whip so glossy <br>God damn bitch, I don't smoke no gas <br>I don't pop no Xans hella cake <br>I just need that ass don't worry bout no mans <br>Look at me, look at he, you don't wanna fuck with we <br>Hit the streets roll on me, you gon end up in the sea <br><br>7:30 wake up skrt up in the lobby then proceed to flee <br>All my people riding in the back seat on a killing spree <br>Wait, who that be? ready on the count of 3 <br>Squeeze the G, leave the scene <br>Bouncin like the trampoline <br><br>Getting bread earn income (man) <br>Spend it on this Balmain <br>Working all night I might run into the Bat(man) <br>I don't see no such thing as a motherfucking bro mane <br>You ain't fucking slick if you think you in my team mane <br><br>We gon' pull up on the kids with a flat brim cap and the tats get the brick <br>And I don't give a fuck hit em with the damn dicks <br>Man, hold up, pause, now they red like Santa Claus <br>I'm a G bet there's something wrong with me <br>All these mans on the ground, lookin like the dead ass sea <br>Yeah, pull up on me, sip a high-t, till I OD <br>I don't really give a fuck no more b <br>Skrrt skrrt onamonapee, bitch Grand Prix <br>Pull up on a fuckin enemy, 3rd degree <br>Now imma go right back to the crib (to the crib bitch) <br>And leave the fuckin country with the brick (loudpack) <br><br>I'd call the cops on myself if I can, (if I can) <br>This shit too crazy need the fuckin ambulance (ambulance) <br>Don't wear no jackets, I just wear that metal vest (skrrt skrrt) <br>Got all this money but these bitches unimpressed (yea, yea, yea) <br><br>Getting bread earn income (man) <br>Spend it on this Balmain <br>Working all night I might run into the Bat(man) <br>I don't see no such thing as a motherfucking bro mane <br>You ain't fucking slick if you think you in my team mane <br><br>7:30 wake up skrt up in the lobby then proceed to flee <br>All my people riding in the back seat on a killing spree <br>Wait, who that be? ready on the count of 3 <br>Squeeze the G, leave the scene <br>Bouncin like the trampoline <br>Yeah]]></content><category term="Rich Brian" label="Rich Brian"/><category term="Who That Be (Josh Pan &amp; West1ne Remix)" label="Who That Be (Josh Pan &amp; West1ne Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/The_Night/</id><title>Sundara Karma - The Night - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:29:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:29:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/The_Night/" title="Sundara Karma - The Night - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Promises always leaking through the day <br>Happiness says the daylight sails away <br>But I hear those echoes in myself <br><br>Honey I'm staying in the night <br>I can see your darkness in the light <br>Honey I'm staying in the night, in the night <br>Flesh is flesh, and blood is love <br>A wild desire for the night <br>Honey I'm staying in the night, in the night <br><br>Falling with a heavy heart has marked <br>I will leave for moments in the dark <br>But I hear those echoes in myself <br><br>Honey I'm staying in the night <br>I can see your darkness in the light <br>Honey I'm staying in the night, in the night <br>Flesh is flesh, and blood is love <br>A wild desire for the night <br>Honey I'm staying in the night, in the night <br><br>Honey I'm staying in the night <br>I can see your darkness in the light <br>Honey I'm staying in the night, in the night <br>Flesh is flesh, and blood is love <br>A wild desire for the night <br>Honey I'm staying in the night, in the night <br><br>Honey I'm staying in the night <br>I can see your darkness in the light <br>Honey I'm staying in the night, in the night <br>Flesh is flesh, and blood is love <br>A wild desire for the night <br>Honey I'm staying in the night, in the night]]></content><category term="Sundara Karma" label="Sundara Karma"/><category term="The Night" label="The Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Watching_From_Great_Heights/</id><title>Sundara Karma - Watching From Great Heights - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:29:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:29:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Watching_From_Great_Heights/" title="Sundara Karma - Watching From Great Heights - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sheltered from the rain <br>The weather here has changed <br>But then what's the point of a clear blue sky <br>When there's trouble on your mind <br><br>Won't look back again <br>We've come too far my friend <br>And it's hard to tell when this journey ends <br>But there's one thing you gotta know <br><br>We'll be watching from great heights <br>And we'll observe the things they hide <br>Fight the fear we keep inside <br>The more we seek the higher we'll climb <br><br>Visions of the clear <br>Horizon edges near <br>And I wonder how the high will feel <br>I'm not cool with coming down <br><br>Memories have gone <br>No past to build upon <br>But there's finer things to be rectified <br>So let's live and lose ourselves <br><br>We'll be watching from great heights <br>And we'll observe the things they hide <br>Fight the fear we keep inside <br>The more we seek the higher we'll climb]]></content><category term="Sundara Karma" label="Sundara Karma"/><category term="Watching From Great Heights" label="Watching From Great Heights"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Deep_Relief/</id><title>Sundara Karma - Deep Relief - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:29:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:29:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Deep_Relief/" title="Sundara Karma - Deep Relief - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This demons not for free <br>He's gunna cost you some loving <br>Relinquish deep relief <br>And when we're tired we can <br>Chase our desire hooked in <br><br>When we're alone and there's no time to hesitate <br>Take what you love but try to heal <br>The things you hate <br>We all lust for <br>We all need <br>Another hit from the giving screen <br>Hold on, hold on <br><br>Good things they come and go <br>And if they don't we're wired to forget <br><br>We bare a heavy load <br>'Cause youth is only ever fun in retrospect <br><br>I want it real <br><br>When we're alone and there's no time to hesitate <br>Take what you love but try to heal <br>The things you hate <br>We all lust for <br>We all need <br>Another hit from the giving screen <br>Hold on, hold on <br><br>All my life <br>I heard you suffer <br>Is it wrong <br>I heard you suffer <br>Come online <br>They say it helps the mind <br><br>When we're alone and there's no time to hesitate <br>Take what you love but try to heal <br>The things you hate <br>We all lust for <br>We all need <br>Another hit from the giving screen <br>Hold on, hold on]]></content><category term="Sundara Karma" label="Sundara Karma"/><category term="Deep Relief" label="Deep Relief"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Be_Nobody/</id><title>Sundara Karma - Be Nobody - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:29:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:29:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Be_Nobody/" title="Sundara Karma - Be Nobody - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's hard to think it over when you're trapped <br>Beneath the mud <br>All the kids are ravers 'cause the church <br>Is now the club <br>Lose yourself in something just escape <br>Your body's flaws <br>Baby you don't have to be you anymore <br><br>And there's nothing in the devil <br>Nothing in the sin <br>There's nothing in a hero <br>Nothing from within <br>There's nothing in the devil <br>Nothing in the sin <br>There's nothing in a hero <br>Nothing from within <br><br>But I found you <br>And you found me <br>And we're happy being nobody <br>I found you <br>And you found me <br>And we're happy being nobody <br><br>We'll never see the colour if we live <br>In black and white <br>Guided by the blinkers that <br>We wear instead of pride <br>Guilty of pretending and you know <br>I'm one to blame <br>Would it not be wrong if we were all the same <br><br>And there's nothing in the devil <br>Nothing in the sin <br>There's nothing in a hero <br>Nothing from within <br>There's nothing in the devil <br>Nothing in the sin <br>There's nothing in a hero <br>Nothing from within <br><br>But I found you <br>And you found me <br>And we're happy being nobody <br>I found you <br>And you found me <br>And we're happy being nobody]]></content><category term="Sundara Karma" label="Sundara Karma"/><category term="Be Nobody" label="Be Nobody"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Vivienne/</id><title>Sundara Karma - Vivienne - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:29:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:29:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Vivienne/" title="Sundara Karma - Vivienne - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wild eyes <br>Skinny jeans <br>Disengaged at just nineteen <br>You and I stuck in the in between <br><br>Come on baby lets feel alive <br>We could change the world <br>If we stopped getting high <br>But you know I'd give it all up <br>Just to spend it with you <br><br>If you said I needed <br>To fall in deeper <br>I'd fall <br>Just to stay here with you <br>You know I'd give you <br>It all <br>Vivienne <br><br>I never knew <br>Didn't see <br>That fate could be so tongue in cheek <br>A loving kindness that's both brutal and bleak <br><br>Come on baby let's feel alive <br>We could change the world <br>If we stopped getting high <br>But goddamn I'd give it all up <br>Just to spend it with you <br><br>If you said I needed <br>To fall in deeper <br>I'd fall <br>Just to stay here with you <br>You know I'd give you <br>It all <br>Vivienne <br><br>And I feel that we're close <br>To the fear, heaven knows <br>We pray, we hope, and away we go <br><br>Time after time, as the day turns to night <br>Like a child I cry, kiss it all goodbye <br>Though I've grown I'm a mess, we don't crawl in the west <br>We live and hope for the best, fuck it all and the rest <br><br>If you said I needed <br>To fall in deeper <br>I'd fall <br>Just to stay here with you <br>You know I'd give you <br>It all <br>Vivienne <br><br>Time after time, as the day turns to night Vivienne <br>Like a child I cry kiss it all goodbye Vivienne <br>Though I've grown I'm a mess, we don't crawl in the west Vivienne <br>We live and hope for the best, fuck it all and the rest <br>Vivienne]]></content><category term="Sundara Karma" label="Sundara Karma"/><category term="Vivienne" label="Vivienne"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/She_Said/</id><title>Sundara Karma - She Said - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:29:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:29:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/She_Said/" title="Sundara Karma - She Said - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She said I don't wanna go out chasing <br>I kinda wanna go out dancing <br>Forget about the guys <br>Cause it doesn't feel right <br>So he left <br>Drinking with the boys in convoy <br>Flirting with the girls who play it coy <br>Doubt he even knows that it doesn't feel right <br><br>It started off with her hair <br>Cause every night has gotta start somewhere <br>Another badly combed frown <br>Cause mirrors always seem to bring her down <br>Going through the motions of <br>Strange ways here we come and teenage love <br>Can see there's something inside <br>Her voice is telling her to stay behind <br>So as friends approached her <br>She looked over her shoulder and <br><br>She said I don't wanna go out chasing <br>I kinda wanna go out dancing <br>Forget about the guys <br>Cause it doesn't feel right <br>So he left <br>Drinking with the boys in convoy <br>Flirting with the girls who play it coy <br>Doubt he even knows that it doesn't feel right <br><br>Acting like he doesn't care <br>But he's really the most self aware <br>He taught his heart how to be cool <br>Because everyone loves a criminal <br>Nothing like a drink or two <br>She's on his mind at least he thinks its true <br>But ain't it funny how we're never certain 'bout the way we are <br>Another youth is wasted and eternity tainted <br><br>She said I don't wanna go out chasing <br>I kinda wanna go out dancing <br>Forget about the guys <br>Cause it doesn't feel right <br>So he left <br>Drinking with the boys in convoy <br>Flirting with the girls who play it coy <br>Doubt he even knows that it doesn't feel right]]></content><category term="Sundara Karma" label="Sundara Karma"/><category term="She Said" label="She Said"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Lose_The_Feeling/</id><title>Sundara Karma - Lose The Feeling - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:29:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:29:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Lose_The_Feeling/" title="Sundara Karma - Lose The Feeling - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[As I was roaming through <br>The vast and sacred valley <br>At the heart of the clearing <br>I saw a woman who approached me <br><br>She had old, wise, tired eyes <br>And markings on her cheeks <br>She told me of the meads where enlightenment <br>Could be achieved <br><br>I set off as dawn broke <br>And I walked on down stream <br>Whilst my eyes strained to pierce <br>The haze of my lucid dreams <br><br>I don't want to lose the feeling <br>I've searched so hard to find the meaning <br>I've found the door and I'm kind of hoping <br>To use my head and crack it open <br><br>As I came down from the hills <br>Away from the crying churned up storm <br>I saw a land through the deepening dusk <br>And I knew true, what I had been told <br><br>I want this vibrant grass to cover me <br>If I become too overwrought <br>For the salvation that I seek <br>Is trapped in the silence between my thoughts <br><br>I don't want to lose the feeling <br>I've searched so hard to find the meaning <br>I've found the door and I'm kind of hoping <br>To use my head and crack it open <br><br>I don't want to lose the feeling <br>I don't want the strange to slip away <br>I seek to find true meaning <br>To find a true and better place to stay <br><br>I don't want to lose the feeling <br>I've searched so hard to find the meaning <br>I've found the door and I'm kind of hoping <br>To use my head and crack it open]]></content><category term="Sundara Karma" label="Sundara Karma"/><category term="Lose The Feeling" label="Lose The Feeling"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Flame/</id><title>Sundara Karma - Flame - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:29:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:29:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Flame/" title="Sundara Karma - Flame - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Whoa wow, whoa wow, whoa wow, whoa wow <br><br>Cold fire feeling, is the cold fire feeling in my bones <br>Skylines breathing as the sun lies beating down the door <br><br>I'm tired of watching the shadows on the wall <br>My eyes are foreseeing <br>The shackles open, we're finally free to bolt <br>If you're done with believing <br><br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside <br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside out <br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside <br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside out <br><br>Found true meaning, now my head starts spinning out the cave <br>You won't come with me cause you're just too comfortable in chains <br><br>I'm tired of watching the shadows on the wall <br>My eyes are foreseeing <br>The shackles open, we're finally free to bolt <br>If you're done with believing <br><br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside <br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside out <br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside <br>Hold my flame and set alight <br>Hold my fire screaming inside out <br><br>Oh oh oh, oh oh oh, oh oh oh, oh oh oh, oh oh oh]]></content><category term="Sundara Karma" label="Sundara Karma"/><category term="Flame" label="Flame"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Happy_Family/</id><title>Sundara Karma - Happy Family - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:29:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:29:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Happy_Family/" title="Sundara Karma - Happy Family - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Left and right, they're calling me back home <br>And I've heard their cuts, I've felt it in my bones <br>Left and right, they choke me tight, I over war and outta sight <br>And I've heard their cuts, I've felt it in my bones <br><br>Been searching for a long time in this town <br>But looking for a gold mine so we can get out <br>To finer days, we'll waste away <br>Another day that goes by, another car <br>We know we should be grateful but sometimes it's hard <br>We're so alone, but it's not for long <br><br>Well maybe will be dissolve <br>Careful what you wish for now <br>Nothing lasts forever, time will always take its toll <br>And if a broken home is on the shelf <br>We know what we should ask ourselves <br>Were we ever happy acting in a family role <br><br>Been dreaming of those bright lights in the city <br>Wake up with a cold fright, oh what a pity <br>A bad night's sleep, the force is weak <br>You're longing for a partner to get you through <br>Wishing that in time, you'll find someone <br>To hold onto <br><br>But maybe will be dissolve <br>Careful what you wish for now <br>Nothing lasts forever, time will always take its toll <br>And if a broken home is on the shelf <br>We know what we should ask ourselves <br>Were we ever happy acting in a family role <br><br>Heavens have you seen, the news that's on the screen <br>It's all violence, heart ache and misery <br>Heavens have you seen, what they have done to me <br>I'm a hallow shell from the grim 90's <br><br>Maybe will be dissolve <br>Careful what you wish for now <br>Nothing lasts forever, time will always take its toll <br>And if a broken home is on the shelf <br>We know what we should ask ourselves <br>Were we ever happy acting in a family role]]></content><category term="Sundara Karma" label="Sundara Karma"/><category term="Happy Family" label="Happy Family"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Olympia/</id><title>Sundara Karma - Olympia - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:29:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:29:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Olympia/" title="Sundara Karma - Olympia - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh no <br>Olympia said she loves me <br>Olympia said she needs me <br>But what about all the marquis <br>No not them <br>Because they're all so autocratic <br><br>There's something pale underneath the beat <br>A white innocence marked by lecherous men <br>I thought I'd suffer in the city heat <br>I thought I'd suffer now let's hope to begin again <br><br>If they could see <br>Modern Venus <br>Tender and frail <br>Hell she's nervous <br>But she's the best in all of Paris <br>At aching and breaking hearts <br><br>And oh lord <br>Is heaven such a fine thing <br>We're floating in a dead town <br>Hoping to find someone to be near <br>And we'll fly away <br>Holding onto something <br>We're drifting in a dull sound <br>Hoping to find someone who will hear <br><br>Oh no <br>Olympia said she loves me <br>Olympia said she needs me <br>But what about all the marquis <br>No not them <br>Because they're all so autocratic <br><br>I can't invest with this currency <br>A blind diligence wrapped and bowed with a lie <br>But still we stay for the company <br>But still we stay cause we don't wanna ever die <br><br>If they could see <br>Modern Venus <br>Tender and frail <br>Hell she's nervous <br>But she's the best in all of Paris <br>At aching and breaking hearts <br><br>And oh lord <br>Is heaven such a fine thing <br>We're floating in a dead town <br>Hoping to find someone near <br>And we'll fly away <br>Holding onto something <br>We're drifting in a dull sound <br>Hoping to find someone who will hear]]></content><category term="Sundara Karma" label="Sundara Karma"/><category term="Olympia" label="Olympia"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Loveblood/</id><title>Sundara Karma - Loveblood - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:30:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:30:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/Loveblood/" title="Sundara Karma - Loveblood - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wasted with my arms out, whisper and a loud shout <br>Lost in the way she says my name <br>I'm such a creep <br>Fortune brought me lovers, shadow taro colours <br>Fated to kill the sweetest things <br>One by one <br><br>Hey, what's that from above <br>It's a love for blood <br>Hey, what's that from above <br>It's a love for blood <br><br>Hiding in the silence, one way form of violence <br>Taste of the thunder from her thighs <br>Makes me shake <br>Calmly kicking outwards <br>Since she misunderstood walking the along the razor's edge <br>And she sweetly moans <br><br>Hey, what's there from above <br>It's a love for blood <br><br>Hey, what's that from above <br>It's a love for blood <br>Hey, what's that from above <br>It's a love for blood <br>Hey, what's that from above <br>It's a love for blood <br>Hey, what's that from above <br>It's a love for blood <br><br>One last kiss, away she goes <br>Obsessed with loveblood and yet no one knows]]></content><category term="Sundara Karma" label="Sundara Karma"/><category term="Loveblood" label="Loveblood"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/A_Young_Understanding/</id><title>Sundara Karma - A Young Understanding - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:30:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:30:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sundara_Karma/A_Young_Understanding/" title="Sundara Karma - A Young Understanding - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hold on tight, you've got a way to go <br>You're terrified by the open road <br>In a daze, you've lost control <br>You've found a gang <br>And it makes you feel better than the other girls <br><br>And you pray they're just boys, they're not villains <br>One's got religious tattoos, he'll be forgiven <br><br>Let go, there is nothing more to hide <br>Seeing life through closed eyes <br>It's just a young understanding <br>You know, that time is on your side <br>Seeing life through closed eyes <br>It's just a young understanding <br><br>Cruising round in a friend's new car <br>You've always known that they won't get you far <br>Found yourself on a downward slope <br>It's ok cause it makes you feel better than the other girls <br><br>And you pray they're just boys, they're not villains <br>One's got religious tattoos, he'll be forgiven <br><br>Let go, there is nothing more to hide <br>Seeing life through closed eyes <br>It's just a young understanding <br>You know, that time is on your side <br>Seeing life through closed eyes <br>It's just a young understanding <br><br>Torn apart, can't you see <br>They left their hearts in the 70's <br>Reach for a sign, reach for an understanding <br>Reach for a sign, reach for an understanding <br>Reach for a sign, reach for an understanding <br>Reach for a sign, reach for an understanding <br><br>Let go, there is nothing more to hide <br>Seeing life through closed eyes <br>It's just a young understanding <br>You know, that time is on your side <br>Seeing life through closed eyes <br>It's just a young understanding <br><br>Reach for a sign, reach for an understanding <br>It's just a young understanding <br>Reach for a sign, reach for an understanding <br>It's just a young understanding]]></content><category term="Sundara Karma" label="Sundara Karma"/><category term="A Young Understanding" label="A Young Understanding"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jimilian/Giv_Mig_Noget/</id><title>Jimilian - Giv Mig Noget - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:30:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:30:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jimilian/Giv_Mig_Noget/" title="Jimilian - Giv Mig Noget - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Uh, uh, uh, uh <br>Uh, uh, uh, uh <br><br>Fortæl mig, hva' har du gang i <br>Prøv' at tænd' mig af ligesom ild <br>Lige nu leger du med benzin <br>Du' iskold, la' mig gør' dig varm, pige, ?h <br>Brænder penge, brænder penge <br>Brænder penge til du bli'r helt v?d ja <br>G? lig' hjem, g? lig' hjem <br>G? lig' hjem hvis du ikk' gi'r noget <br>Uh, wow, bitch, f? din røv herhen <br>Uh, wow, vi to, vi har lang vej hjem <br><br>Du siger, at du ved hvad jeg' ude p? <br>Siger' du ikk' en af dem <br>For du' s? uskyldig ?h, ?h <br>Uskyldig ?h, ?h <br>Uskyldig ?h, ?h <br>Gode piger, de ka' bli' slemme <br><br>Du vil bare ha', ha', ha' <br>Uden at gi' <br>Det bruger jeg ikk' tid p? <br>Hvis du vil ha' mig <br>Ha' mig, ha' mig til at bli' <br>S? m? du hellere gi' hoe <br>Gi' noget uh, uh, uh, uh <br>Gi' mig noget uh, uh, uh, uh <br>Gi', gi' mig noget <br><br>Jeg ved, hvad du tænker p?, baby ja <br>Har nok til b?de dig og veninden uh <br>Der' Belvedere p? mit bord <br>Jeg ved godt, at du tror <br>At jeg bar' lader dig sippe hey <br>Jeg ved det, jeg ved det, jeg ved det uh <br>Prøvet det før, jeg kender spillet ?h <br>For bitches de kigger, jeg ved at de knepper <br>Men' vil hellere gør' noget ved dette <br>Uh, wow, bitch, f? din røv herhen <br>Uh, wow, vi to, vi har lang vej hjem <br><br>Du siger, at du ved hvad jeg' ude p? <br>Siger' du ikk' en af dem <br>For du' s? uskyldig ?h, ?h <br>Uskyldig ?h, ?h <br>Uskyldig ?h, ?h <br>Gode piger, de ka' bli' slemme <br><br>Du vil bare ha', ha', ha' <br>Uden at gi' aha <br>Det bruger jeg ikk' tid p? <br>Hvis du vil ha' mig <br>Ha' mig, ha' mig til at bli' aha <br>S? m? du hellere gi' hoe <br>Gi' noget uh, uh, uh, uh <br>Gi' mig noget uh, uh, uh, uh <br>Gi', gi' mig noget <br><br>?h, har ventet p? at lig' her lige nu <br>?h, du started' selv, men pludselig si'r du <br>Nej, nej, er der noget som jeg har misforst?et <br>Ga' den op, og nu gi'r du ikk' noget til mig <br><br>Du vil bare ha', ha', ha' <br>Uden at gi' aha <br>Det bruger jeg ikk' tid p? <br>Hvis du vil ha' mig <br>Ha' mig, ha' mig til at bli' aha <br>S? m? du hellere gi' hoe <br>Gi' noget uh, uh, uh, uh <br>Gi' mig noget uh, uh, uh, uh <br>Gi', gi' mig noget]]></content><category term="Jimilian" label="Jimilian"/><category term="Giv Mig Noget" label="Giv Mig Noget"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kelvin_Jones/Good_Together_Slight_Return/</id><title>Kelvin Jones - Good Together (Slight Return) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T08:33:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T08:33:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kelvin_Jones/Good_Together_Slight_Return/" title="Kelvin Jones - Good Together (Slight Return) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I think I'll always be <br>in love with you <br>I you were honest <br>maybe you would too <br>I'm loosing count <br>of all the fights we had <br>I'm loosing patience trying <br>to make this work <br>I just know what you're gonna say <br>And if you lately made mistakes <br>When we're not good together <br>All we do is hurt each other <br>Did you really think <br>we make it through <br>make it through <br>There's nothing that can save us <br>I just can't find the words <br>to say that <br>All I know is I'm leaving you <br>I'm leaving you <br>All I know is I'm leaving you <br>All I know is I'm leaving you <br>All I know is I'm leaving you <br>ohhh <br>I think I'll always be <br>in love with you <br>I you were honest <br>you knew this from the start <br>Why do I feel alone <br>when I'm with you <br>It's time I said it <br>we're better off apart <br>I just know what you're gonna say <br>And if you lately made mistakes <br>When we're not good together <br>All we do is hurt each other <br>Did you really think <br>we make it through <br>make it through <br>There's nothing that can save us <br>I just can't find the words <br>to say that <br>All I know is I'm leaving you <br>I'm leaving you <br>All I know is I'm leaving you <br>All I know is I'm leaving you <br>All I know is I'm leaving you <br>ohhh <br>Didn't see you falling <br>Didn't see you going <br>Didn't see you falling in love <br>No I didn't see you fall in love <br>No I didn't see you fall in love <br>No I didn't see you fall down <br>No I didn't see you fall down <br>When we're not good together <br>All we do is hurt each other <br>Did you really think <br>we make it through <br>make it through <br>There's nothing that can save us <br>I just can't find the words <br>to say that <br>All I know is I'm leaving you <br>I'm leaving you <br>All I know is I'm leaving you <br>All I know is I'm leaving you <br>All I know is I'm leaving you <br>ohhh <br>]]></content><category term="Kelvin Jones" label="Kelvin Jones"/><category term="Good Together (Slight Return)" label="Good Together (Slight Return)"/></entry></feed>