<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:52:58+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/입질_Bite_me/</id><title>Gimmiky - 입질 (Bite me) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:11:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:11:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/%EC%9E%85%EC%A7%88_Bite_me/" title="Gimmiky - 입질 (Bite me) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Obey Obey 후디 입고 Walkin` <br>내 심길 건들면 Bite me <br>OG OG 라도 된듯 On Fleek Bite me <br>Okay Okay 이방인들 <br>Fuck It 너도 Bite me <br>Oh Man Oh Man 썅년아 Bite me <br>Grrr 물어뜯어죽여 물어뜯어 <br>BITE TIGHT <br>Grrr 물어뜯어죽여 물어뜯어 <br>BITE TIGHT <br>Grrr 물어뜯어죽여 물어뜯어 <br>BITE TIGHT <br>Grrr 물어뜯어죽여 물어뜯어 <br>BITE ya <br>물어뜯어죽여 쟨 냄새가 구려 <br>BITE ME <br>니가 날 알아 다시 말해 <br>U KNOW ABOUT ME <br>난 개새끼 맞아 <br>알아서 자진해 집 나갔네 <br>이곳은 내 영역야 <br>방방곡곡에 오줌 마킹 <br>딴 무리가 구멍을 엿봐 우리 주윌 <br>타협할 생각 좆도 없어 <br>안 낮춰 고유의 가사 수위 <br>안양 to 안산 내 나와바리 <br>광안리 바다까지 <br>주인은 굳이 따로 안두지 <br>외부인들에겐 상당히 살벌하지 <br>날 만지려 들지마 <br>너의 신변에 더 Better <br>중성화는 좆까고 발정이 났어 <br>갓 성기가 선채로 <br>낯선 이들에겐 이를 드러냈지 <br>두렵게 그르렁거려 <br>입질을 준비해 야생 짐승의 <br>본능은 남 못 주네 못 버려 <br>Obey Obey 후디 입고 Walkin` <br>내 심길 건들면 Bite me <br>OG OG 라도 된듯 On Fleek Bite me <br>Okay Okay 이방인들 <br>Fuck It 너도 Bite me <br>Oh Man Oh Man 썅년아 Bite me <br>Grrr 물어뜯어죽여 물어뜯어 <br>BITE TIGHT <br>Grrr 물어뜯어죽여 물어뜯어 <br>BITE TIGHT <br>Grrr 물어뜯어죽여 물어뜯어 <br>BITE TIGHT <br>Grrr 물어뜯어죽여 물어뜯어 <br>BITE ya <br>그래 남 못주네 야생의 본능은 <br>집 나와서 매일밤의 고충을 <br>아무 암컷에게 말한적 없지 <br>홀로 삼키고서 깊은 가사로 적지 <br>동족들이 많더군 밤 <br>공장에는 도무지 미래를 못찾겠는 <br>환경속에 그저 이를 갈고 <br>뇌가 멈춘 기계처럼 일을 하고 <br>아침에 퇴근 일당을 거머쥘때 <br>자연스레 실소가 지어지네 <br>날선 털을 단단한 가죽에 <br>깊숙히 박음질 피어싱해 <br>피부는 썩창인 신세 <br>몰골은 가축과 비슷해 <br>가출이 후회돼 집에 <br>돌아가서 주인의 밑에서 <br>살고싶어 그저 복종하며 <br>생활고는 여전해도 <br>빌어먹을 생존본능은 절대로 <br>굶진 않어 나만 알고 살어 <br>야 박하게 굴게 돼 갈수록 남들에게 <br>경계하고 살아가야 내가 안전하기에 <br>Obey Obey 후디 입고 Walkin` <br>내 심길 건들면 Bite me <br>OG OG 라도 된듯 On Fleek Bite me <br>Okay Okay 이방인들 <br>Fuck It 너도 Bite me <br>Oh Man Oh Man 썅년아 Bite me <br>Grrr 물어뜯어죽여 물어뜯어 <br>BITE TIGHT <br>Grrr 물어뜯어죽여 물어뜯어 <br>BITE TIGHT <br>Grrr 물어뜯어죽여 물어뜯어 <br>BITE TIGHT <br>Grrr 물어뜯어죽여 물어뜯어 <br>BITE ya <br>]]></content><category term="Gimmiky" label="Gimmiky"/><category term="입질 (Bite me)" label="입질 (Bite me)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/잡종_Mix_Feat_Hunger_Noma/</id><title>Gimmiky - 잡종 (Mix) (Feat. Hunger Noma) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:11:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:11:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/%EC%9E%A1%EC%A2%85_Mix_Feat_Hunger_Noma/" title="Gimmiky - 잡종 (Mix) (Feat. Hunger Noma) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이곳의 사람들은 <br>모두 순종을 원해 <br>혈통 따위가 뭔데 <br>그깟 서류를 요구해 <br>출신 지방 따라 <br>고유의 습성을 나누네 <br>경상도는 범죄 또는 <br>전라도는 믿을게 못 돼 <br>댓글에 휩쓸리는 <br>초록색 zombie <br>언론이 노를 저으면 <br>뒤따르는 노비 <br>개돼지들이 모일 때 <br>이제 호랑이는 포식 <br>아니 닭으로 변신 <br>모일 쪼아 먹지 <br>사회를 세뇌한 지역 학벌주의 <br>선후배가 일 순위 친분 없인 이루지 <br>못해 다들 유착하기 바빠 <br>다른 부류는 무시 <br>고집은 곧 신념이 됐고 <br>공존하는 무지 <br>부당한 발언 반박시 <br>빨갱이 취급 받네 <br>힘없이 고개 숙여야지 <br>이름 직급 앞에 <br>세상은 우릴 순종 잡종 <br>둘로 양분하지 <br>그들은 횡포를 일삼아 <br>조선 양반같이 <br>Fuckin` 순혈주의 <br>빌어먹을 순혈주의 <br>다른 종족들은 무시 <br>우린 잡종 그들은 우월한 <br>Fuckin` 순혈주의 <br>빌어먹을 순혈주의 <br>모든 것에 우윌 두지 <br>지역 학벌 부모까지 ya <br>Fuckin` 순혈주의 <br>빌어먹을 순혈주의 <br>다른 종족들은 무시 <br>우린 잡종 그들은 우월한 <br>Fuckin` 순혈주의 <br>빌어먹을 순혈주의 <br>모든 것에 우윌 두지 <br>지역 학벌 부모까지 ya <br>yo fuckin 순혈주의 <br>나의 핏줄이 저주로 느껴질 듯이 <br>난 단 한번도 이 계급의 한계를 <br>넘지 못했지 <br>빈곤계층 저소득층의 자녀란 배지 <br>날 주눅들게 했고 <br>이건 흉터가 됐지 <br>언제나 살피는 눈치 <br>고등학교 때 중단한 급식 <br>그래 사치는 금지 <br>어두운 그림자가 내 둥지 <br>저 경계선을 넘는 짓 <br>그런 것은 꿈도 못 꿨지 <br>애초에 다른 세상 <br>너와 나의 교감은 거짓 <br>날 향한 니 말들은 거짓 <br>진심은 깊이 숨겼지 <br>모두 평등하다는 억지 <br>그 말에 쓴 웃음을 지었지 <br>나 역시 진심은 없지 <br>널 위해 고개를 숙였던 거지 <br>온몸이 간질거려 <br>내 피부 위로 덮인 껍질 <br>정신적 빈곤함 <br>우리가 찬 시계의 가치 <br>그 시계 속 톱니바퀴처럼 <br>움직여 바삐 <br>넌 절대 깨닫지 못하지 <br>여전히 가난한 자신 <br>끝날 때까진 못 멈춰 <br>넌 고통 받지 영원히 <br>Fuckin` 순혈주의 <br>빌어먹을 순혈주의 <br>다른 종족들은 무시 <br>우린 잡종 그들은 우월한 <br>Fuckin` 순혈주의 <br>빌어먹을 순혈주의 <br>모든 것에 우윌 두지 <br>지역 학벌 부모까지 ya <br>Fuckin` 순혈주의 <br>빌어먹을 순혈주의 <br>다른 종족들은 무시 <br>우린 잡종 그들은 우월한 <br>Fuckin` 순혈주의 <br>빌어먹을 순혈주의 <br>모든 것에 우윌 두지 <br>지역 학벌 부모까지 ya <br>서로의 급을 수저로 나누는 <br>몰상식한 개념 <br>강아지들 분양가를 매기듯 <br>서로 가치를 매겨 <br>no money more problem <br>돈이 없는 게 이곳은 죄여 <br>취업보다 꿈을 찾으란 훈수는 <br>사치고 꼰대요 <br>몸이든 나라든 팔아먹은 창놈들은 <br>다 호위호식 <br>가진 거 없는 가축들은 <br>한입거리 몸보신 <br>잡아 먹히기만 <br>기다리는 철창 속에 <br>자유의 문은 좆까 <br>억압만 줄창 맛보네 <br>급여된 사료 외 다른 것은 금지 <br>훈련에 세뇌된 채 <br>그들에게 불리우지 <br>똥개 혹은 잡종 믹스견 <br>아무리 짖고 기어도 <br>우린 순종 밑이여 <br>목줄과 굶주림 앞에 별수 없어 <br>훈육에 굴복해서 <br>꼬리를 쳐들었어 <br>현대판 세습제에 <br>신분 상승은 꿈도 못 꿔 <br>무자비한 도살이 두려워서 YA <br>]]></content><category term="Gimmiky" label="Gimmiky"/><category term="잡종 (Mix) (Feat. Hunger Noma)" label="잡종 (Mix) (Feat. Hunger Noma)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/금수_Beast_Feat_Takeone/</id><title>Gimmiky - 금수 (Beast) (Feat. Takeone) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:11:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:11:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gimmiky/%EA%B8%88%EC%88%98_Beast_Feat_Takeone/" title="Gimmiky - 금수 (Beast) (Feat. Takeone) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 씨발 금수 같은 놈 <br>짐승도 말을 하는 것 <br>처럼 고유의 언어를 뱉지 <br>직언 말곤 못해 반어법 <br>야생성을 갖는 것 <br>요즘 시대에선 죄고 <br>짜여진 판에 체구를 맞추는 게 <br>개인 신변에 better <br>나의 개성 죽이는 게 <br>더 좋을 듯해 <br>싱퍼가 유행이니 유려한 <br>멜로디를 얹는 건 어때 <br>너도 공통된 틀에 속해 <br>비슷한 걸로 <br>승부해 살고 싶음 <br>닥치고 기고 기생해라 <br>숙주에 좆까 <br>내가 복종할 주인은 없어 <br>차라리 버려지고 <br>떠도는 저 유기견처럼 <br>낯선 이들에게는 입질을 <br>걔들 구강에 씹질을 <br>분간을 확실히 행해 <br>각자의 영역 인식을 <br>만일 내가 마킹한 자리에 <br>발을 들였다가는 <br>설령 친목질 또는 <br>교미를 나누었다 한들 <br>것이 동족을 의미함은 아니지 <br>내 노선은 홀로 터있고 <br>자진 안 해 사까시 shit <br>인간들 사이 <br>감히 금수 새낀 주둥이를 벌려 <br>친화력 없지 마치 유기 짐승처럼 <br>LIKE BEAST BEAST <br>CALL ME LIKE BEAST <br>LIKE BEAST BEAST <br>CALL ME LIKE BEAST <br>인간들 사이 <br>감히 금수 새낀 주둥이를 벌려 <br>친화력 없지 마치 유기 짐승처럼 <br>LIKE BEAST BEAST <br>CALL ME LIKE BEAST <br>LIKE BEAST BEAST <br>CALL ME LIKE BEAST <br>ya 어쩌면 집에 <br>갇혀 사는 개보다 <br>내가 더 경계 한 채로 <br>막혀 사는지 몰라 <br>막내로 고이 자라 <br>굳은 일이 힘들던 못난 <br>놈은 죽기보다 싫었어 <br>한때 다녔던 공장 <br>인간이 못할 짓을 몇 번 행했지 <br>개새끼 마냥 난교해 <br>2:1 불순한 관계를 맺지 <br>본능에 앞서 부린 <br>객기가 멋있는 줄 알던 행실 <br>의 망나니 새낀 <br>자퇴한 뒤 무작정 랩질 <br>극악한 죄질 작사할 땐 <br>여과 없이 뱉어 <br>수위 조절 하라는 삼자들 <br>훈수들은 쌩깠 <br>고 내 서사를 <br>미화 시킬려고 애쓸 생각 <br>좆도 없어 우리 영역의 <br>무리들 빼고는 죄다 꺼져 <br>곤두선 털과 갈고 닦은 <br>이빨의 날을 세워 물어 <br>극도의 흥분제 투여된 투견 <br>난 모난 것이 아냐 <br>생존이 목적일 뿐 <br>쌓여온 고충을 토하는 <br>몸부림과 울부짖음 YA <br>짐승 취급 받는 삶 <br>절대 사랑은 못 받지 <br>낮과 밤이 바뀐 날 <br>흡혈귀 마냥 못박지 <br>사랑을 줬던 사람은 <br>변해 늑대인간 <br>달밤에 내 도피처는 <br>오직 무대인가 <br>날 제도화 하려 드는 <br>인간이라는 그는 <br>날 길들여 채우고 <br>싶어하지 그 탐욕을 <br>단지 돈을 얻기 위해서 <br>광대 옷을 입히네 <br>내 모습 비웃으면서 <br>이걸 현실이라 칭해 <br>마귀 손아귀 잡히지 않아 <br>난 똑똑하지 <br>발목에 쇠줄 풀고 날아가 <br>마치 까마귀 <br>ha 이기적인 놈과 달리 <br>탈출한 뒤 <br>난 다시 돌아와 쟁취해 <br>친구들의 자유까지 <br>추악한 본성 인간성 난 결여 <br>난 평범함과는 거리 멀어 <br>저리 꺼져 <br>내 새끼들한테만 먹이 먹여 <br>겁이 없어 난 주인 손 물어 <br>내가 무리 이끌어 <br>인간들 사이 <br>감히 금수 새낀 주둥이를 벌려 <br>친화력 없지 마치 유기 짐승처럼 <br>LIKE BEAST BEAST <br>CALL ME LIKE BEAST <br>LIKE BEAST BEAST <br>CALL ME LIKE BEAST <br>인간들 사이 <br>감히 금수 새낀 주둥이를 벌려 <br>친화력 없지 마치 유기 짐승처럼 <br>LIKE BEAST BEAST <br>CALL ME LIKE BEAST <br>LIKE BEAST BEAST <br>CALL ME LIKE BEAST <br>]]></content><category term="Gimmiky" label="Gimmiky"/><category term="금수 (Beast) (Feat. Takeone)" label="금수 (Beast) (Feat. Takeone)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/허공/따뜻하다/</id><title>허공 - 따뜻하다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:11:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:11:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%88%EA%B3%B5/%EB%94%B0%EB%9C%BB%ED%95%98%EB%8B%A4/" title="허공 - 따뜻하다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[참 따뜻하다 <br>날 보는 너의 눈빛이 <br>참 따뜻하다 <br>내 손을 감싼 두 손이 <br>참 따뜻하다 <br>귓가에 너의 숨결이 <br>고맙다 곁에 있어줘서 <br>사랑한단 한마디로 표현 못해 <br>이렇게라도 내 맘 노래할게 <br>하루 종일 너로 인해 포근해 <br>내겐 사랑이란 게 너의 이름 같아서 <br>눈감으면 느껴지는 너의 온기가 <br>아직도 내겐 꿈만 같은데 <br>깨고 나면 잊혀질까 부르는 이름 <br>널 사랑한 이유 <br>널 바라만 봐도 <br>따뜻하다 <br>사랑한단 한마디론 표현 못해 <br>이렇게라도 내 맘 노래할게 <br>하루 종일 너로 인해 포근해 <br>내겐 사랑이란 게 너의 이름 같아서 <br>눈감으면 느껴지는 너의 온기가 <br>아직도 내겐 꿈만 같은데 <br>깨고 나면 잊혀질까 부르는 이름 <br>널 사랑한 이유 <br>널 바라만 봐도 <br>따뜻하다 <br>설혹 우연뿐인 사랑이라도 <br>널 사랑하니까 믿고 있으니까 <br>눈감으면 느껴지는 너의 온기가 <br>아직도 내겐 꿈만 같은데 <br>깨고 나면 잊혀질까 부르는 이름 <br>널 사랑한 이유 <br>널 바라만 봐도 <br>따뜻하다 <br>]]></content><category term="허공" label="허공"/><category term="따뜻하다" label="따뜻하다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지한수/영원한_미래/</id><title>지한수 - 영원한 미래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:11:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:11:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%ED%95%9C%EC%88%98/%EC%98%81%EC%9B%90%ED%95%9C_%EB%AF%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="지한수 - 영원한 미래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오래된 미래 나에게 <br>주님 나라 임했네 <br>다스리시네 나의 삶 <br>모든 두려움 사라져 <br>영원한 미래 너와 나 <br>구원의 노래 부르자 <br>오 할렐루야 <br>영원히 주를 찬양해 <br>주의 나라 <br>이미 임했네 <br>더 알기원하네 오 <br>주의 영광 <br>온 땅 가득하네 <br>다스리소서 <br>나의 삶 <br>영원한 미래 안에 있네 <br>기쁨의 나라 <br>영원히 주 찬양해 <br>오래된 미래 나에게 <br>주님 나라 임했네 <br>다스리시네 나의 삶 <br>모든 두려움 사라져 <br>영원한 미래 너와 나 <br>구원의 노래 부르자 <br>오 할렐루야 <br>영원히 주를 찬양해 <br>주의 나라 <br>이미 임했네 <br>더 알기원하네 오 <br>주의 영광 <br>온 땅 가득하네 <br>다스리소서 <br>나의 삶 <br>영원한 미래 안에 있네 <br>기쁨의 나라 <br>영원히 주 찬양해 <br>나의 삶 <br>영원한 미래 안에 있네 <br>기쁨의 나라 <br>영원히 주 찬양해 <br>나의 삶 <br>영원한 미래 안에 있네 <br>기쁨의 나라 <br>영원히 주 찬양해 <br>나의 삶 <br>영원한 미래 안에 있네 <br>기쁨의 나라 <br>영원히 주 찬양해 <br>]]></content><category term="지한수" label="지한수"/><category term="영원한 미래" label="영원한 미래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피치트리/풋사랑/</id><title>피치트리 - 풋사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:13:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:13:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EC%B9%98%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AC/%ED%92%8B%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="피치트리 - 풋사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[화창한 햇살 아래 <br>떠나볼까 둘이서 <br>달콤한 바람 속에 떨리는 기분 <br>날아가는 새들도 <br>흩날리는 꽃잎도 <br>세상 모든 게 나를 웃게 만들어 <br>햇살이 밝은 날에 <br>기차 타고 둘이서 <br>어디든 떠나볼까 그대와 함께 <br>창 밖의 풍경들도 <br>살랑대는 바람도 <br>마치 내 기분 같아 설레이는 걸 <br>한 걸음 두 걸음 더 <br>천천히 걸어갈래 <br>그대와 함께 하는 모든 길 <br>수줍게 맘 전할래 <br>설레는 맘 고백할래 <br>사랑해 <br>You're my everything to me <br>함께 길을 걸으며 <br>사랑해 속삭이며 <br>확인 할거야 우리 둘의 사랑을 <br>서롤 바라만 봐도 <br>손만 잡고 있어도 <br>봄 향기 같아 우리 둘의 사랑이 <br>한 걸음 두 걸음 더 <br>천천히 걸어갈래 <br>그대와 함께 하는 모든 길 <br>수줍게 맘 전할래 <br>설레는 맘 고백할래 <br>사랑해 <br>You're my everything to me <br>이런 게 사랑일까 <br>첨 느낀 기분인 걸 <br>궁금해 너와 함께 걷는 길 <br>수줍게 맘 전할래 <br>설레는 맘 고백할래 <br>사랑해 <br>You're my everything to me <br>사랑해 세상 누구 보다 더 <br>]]></content><category term="피치트리" label="피치트리"/><category term="풋사랑" label="풋사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동요마을/호빵/</id><title>동요마을 - 호빵 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:13:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:13:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%84/%ED%98%B8%EB%B9%B5/" title="동요마을 - 호빵 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[호빵은 정말 맛있어 다 함께 먹어요 <br>달콤한 팥 맛이 좋아요 출출할 때는 호빵이 최고 <br><br>호빵을 먹어보세요 따뜻한 호빵 <br>겨울이면 더 생각나는 국민 간식은 호빵이지요 <br><br>호빵이 진짜 맛있어 통통한 호빵 <br>호호호호 바람 불어서 뜨거운 호빵 식혀 드세요]]></content><category term="동요마을" label="동요마을"/><category term="호빵" label="호빵"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엣지스_Edges/Model/</id><title>엣지스 (Edges) - Model - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:13:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:13:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%A3%EC%A7%80%EC%8A%A4_Edges/Model/" title="엣지스 (Edges) - Model - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사뿐사뿐 멋스럽게 걸어 <br>어깨펴고 엣지있게 올라 <br>살아있는 인형같은 표정으로 <br>패션쇼를 시작해 스타일을 완성해 <br>가장 높은 하이힐을 신고서 <br>모두 나를 숭배하는 눈빛으로 <br>독특한 화장과 세련된 옷을 입고 <br>지금부터 걸어가 당당하게 걸어가 <br>춤 추듯 나비처럼 무대 끝까지 <br>날아 노래에 맞춰 상상해봐 <br>꿈 길로 걷게 해 줄 <br>이 멋진 음악에 빠져봐 <br>나풀나풀 우아하게 날아 <br>허리펴고 도도하게 올라 <br>날개짓하는 몸짓으로 걸어봐 <br>스타일을 완성해 패션쇼를 시작해 <br>표정없는 얼굴 높이 들고서 <br>모두 나를 향해 숨을 멈출거야 <br>신비한 색깔과 화려한 무늴입고 <br>지금부터 걸어봐 당당하게 걸어봐 <br>춤 추듯 나비처럼 무대끝까지 <br>날아 노래에 맞춰 상상해봐 <br>꿈 길로 걷게 해 줄 <br>이 멋진음악에 빠져봐 <br>]]></content><category term="엣지스 (Edges)" label="엣지스 (Edges)"/><category term="Model" label="Model"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/링크맨/10년전이었으면/</id><title>링크맨 - 10년전이었으면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:13:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:13:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%81%ED%81%AC%EB%A7%A8/10%EB%85%84%EC%A0%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%97%88%EC%9C%BC%EB%A9%B4/" title="링크맨 - 10년전이었으면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[알람도 없이 그냥 실컷 잠을 잘래 <br>하루종일 PC방에서 <br>게임이나 하고 싶어 <br>저녁이면 친구들과 어김없이 모여 <br>소주나 마시며 떠들며 놀래 <br>오늘도 뭐든지 시간만 <br>되는대로 할 수 있는데 <br>10년전 이었으면 10년전 이었다면 <br>그때로 돌아가면 <br>아무걱정 없던 그때라면 <br>10년전 이었으면 <br>자장면 시켜 먹고 실컷 당구 칠래 <br>하루종일 영화보고 <br>쇼핑이나 하고 싶어 <br>주말이면 깔끔하게 차려입고 모여 <br>맥주나 마시며 떠들며 놀래 <br>오늘도 뭐든지 시간만 <br>되는대로 할 수 있는데 <br>10년전 이었으면 10년전 이었다면 <br>그때로 돌아가면 <br>아무걱정 없던 그때라면 <br>10년전 이었으면 <br>우 우우 우우 우 우우우 우 <br>10년전 이었으면 10년전 이었다면 <br>그때로 돌아가면 <br>아무걱정 없던 그때라면 <br>10년전 이었으면 <br>우우 우우우 우우 우우우우 <br>우우 우우우 우우 우우우우 <br>우우 우우우 우우 우우우우 <br>우우 우우우 <br>]]></content><category term="링크맨" label="링크맨"/><category term="10년전이었으면" label="10년전이었으면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/구본웅_Ku_Bon_Woong/Where_you_go/</id><title>구본웅 (Ku Bon Woong) - Where you go - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:14:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:14:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B5%AC%EB%B3%B8%EC%9B%85_Ku_Bon_Woong/Where_you_go/" title="구본웅 (Ku Bon Woong) - Where you go - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[예전엔 높이 날고 싶었다 <br>지금은 마음만 <br>작년엔 뭐하고 싶었나 <br>올해도 뭘하고 싶은가 <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>연인과 사랑하고 싶었다 <br>지금은 마음만 <br>여름엔 뭐하고 싶었나 <br>겨울엔 뭘하고 싶은가 <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>작년엔 뭐하고 싶었나 <br>올해도 뭘하고 싶은가 <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>Where you go <br>]]></content><category term="구본웅 (Ku Bon Woong)" label="구본웅 (Ku Bon Woong)"/><category term="Where you go" label="Where you go"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안정준/오늘_하루_Feat_최현석/</id><title>안정준 - 오늘 하루 (Feat. 최현석) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:14:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:14:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%A0%95%EC%A4%80/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98_%ED%95%98%EB%A3%A8_Feat_%EC%B5%9C%ED%98%84%EC%84%9D/" title="안정준 - 오늘 하루 (Feat. 최현석) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[또 다른 긴 하루가 지나가고 <br>철없는 아이처럼 <br>헤매이던 내 모습 <br>그래도 내게 의미를 주었던 <br>너를 위해 꿈을 위해 후우 <br>너의 밝은 미소도 <br>아름다운 한마디 나에겐 <br>오늘도 그대가 밝혀주는 내 마음 <br>언제나 내 곁을 지켰던 너와 <br>함께 같은 시간 속에 살다 보면 <br>잊혀지진 않겠죠 <br>다시 일어설 수 있겠죠 <br>반복된 일상 속에 지친 내 모습 <br>어제와 다를 것도 하나 없는데 <br>언젠가 그대 미소 볼 수 있다면 <br>한없이 감싸주고 싶어요 그대를 <br>오늘도 그대가 밝혀주는 내 마음 <br>언제나 내 곁을 지켰던 너와 <br>함께 같은 시간 속에 살다 보면 <br>잊혀지진 않겠죠 <br>다시 일어설 순 있겠죠 <br>오늘 하루는 어땠는지 <br>힘들던 일은 없었는지 <br>걱정만 앞서 마음이 아파 <br>내가 망설이고 있는데 <br>조급한 마음을 숨기지 못한 채 <br>지친 너를 달래보려 고민하다 <br>또 하루가 지나고 <br>그리워하며 잠에 들겠죠 <br>]]></content><category term="안정준" label="안정준"/><category term="오늘 하루 (Feat. 최현석)" label="오늘 하루 (Feat. 최현석)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안정준/후회/</id><title>안정준 - 후회 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:14:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:14:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%A0%95%EC%A4%80/%ED%9B%84%ED%9A%8C/" title="안정준 - 후회 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그때로 다시 돌아갈 수 있다면 <br>나에게도 작은 기회는 있었을까 <br>온통 너의 생각뿐이어서 <br>잠이 오질 않는 <br>내 마음을 넌 알까요 <br>그때로 다시 돌아갈 수 있다면 <br>내 마음을 더 크게 알리고 싶어 <br>하지만 이제는 <br>너의 대답만 남아있어 <br>내가 할 수 있는 건 없어 <br>이제 깨달은 듯 <br>너에게 다시 맘을 주고 <br>너를 바꾸려 해봐도 <br>어차피 안될 사랑인걸 알지만 <br>후회하고 싶지 않았던 나야 <br>다시 돌아갈 수 없는걸 알지만 <br>너를 다시 볼 수 없게 만든 너인걸 <br>내 마음을 누구보다도 <br>잘 알고 있는 넌 <br>마지막에는 내게 <br>상처만 주고 떠나 <br>이제 깨달았어 <br>너에게 다시 맘을 줄 수 없고 <br>바꿀 수 없는걸 <br>어차피 안될 사랑인걸 알지만 <br>후회하고 싶지 않았던 나야 <br>이제 깨달았어 <br>너에게 다시 맘을 줄 수 없고 <br>바꿀 수 없는걸 <br>어차피 안될 사랑인걸 알지만 <br>후회하고 싶지 않았던 <br>보내줄 수 밖에 없었던 <br>잊을 수는 있을까 너를 <br>]]></content><category term="안정준" label="안정준"/><category term="후회" label="후회"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JB_Kim/잃어버린_시절을_찾아서_-_Part1_Feat_김희진/</id><title>JB Kim - 잃어버린 시절을 찾아서 - Part.1 (Feat. 김희진) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:14:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:14:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JB_Kim/%EC%9E%83%EC%96%B4%EB%B2%84%EB%A6%B0_%EC%8B%9C%EC%A0%88%EC%9D%84_%EC%B0%BE%EC%95%84%EC%84%9C_-_Part1_Feat_%EA%B9%80%ED%9D%AC%EC%A7%84/" title="JB Kim - 잃어버린 시절을 찾아서 - Part.1 (Feat. 김희진) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아직은 열한 시 반 <br>자정은 넘지 않아 <br>불타는 금요일 밤 <br>밤샘은 하지 않아 <br>클럽가 잭 콕 한 잔 <br>긴 밤 달래볼까 <br>화려한 낯선 이와 <br>이 밤 달려볼까 <br>어디선가 풍겨오는 치킨 내음 <br>한 마리에 육 천원 uh 옛날 통닭 uh <br>지친 내 마음 달래줄 한 잔의 술 <br>내일의 힘이 되어줄 추억의 술 <br>아빠 월급날 우리 축제의 날 <br>평소와는 다르게 숙제는 완벽하게 <br>기름을 품은 노란 치킨 봉투 <br>가족의 미랠 담은 노란 월급 봉투 <br>통닭을 먹을 때는 날개부터 <br>왼다리는 아빠께 엄마는 또 괜찮대 <br>내가 먹긴 미안해 한 쪽은 동생에게 <br>해서 요즘에도 나는 uh 날개부터 <br>엄마도 아빠도 함께 먹던 얼음과자 <br>네 가족이 먹기에도 크던 얼음과자 <br>아빠는 밥 숟가락 우리는 찻숟가락 <br>들고 머릴 부딪히던 달콤한 밤 <br>엄마 아빤 노란 봉투 들고 안방으로 <br>우리 둘은 문 밖에서 <br>그저 귀만 쫑긋거려 <br>시간 지나 우릴 부르는 아빠의 소리 <br>세종 대왕님 미소 덕에 행복한 밤 <br>자신의 꿈보다는 자식의 꿈이 <br>본인의 삶보다는 아들의 삶이 <br>중요해지는 시기가 올 테지 <br>그럴 때쯤 나도 사랑을 알 테지 <br>처음으로 꼭 잡은 그 손가락 <br>어느새 새어버린 머리카락 <br>나면서부터 받은 절대적 사랑 <br>되갚을 수도 없는 무한한 사랑 <br>나는 부르네 순수했던 그 시절 <br>나는 부르네 돌아가고픈 그날들 <br>나는 그리네 잃어버린 우리 기억을 <br>나는 그리네 돌아가고픈 <br>우리의 추억을 <br>갓 상경한 그는 JYP가 되고팠대 <br>거인 같던 빌딩 앞 포장마차 <br>백열등 아래 <br>지친 청춘의 마음 달래던 닭갈비 <br>이젠 가족에만 허락된 그 레시피 <br>늦게까지 두들기던 신발 가죽 소리 <br>천장에서 뛰어 놀던 생쥐 가족 소리 <br>작은 방 벽에 걸린 별 헤는 밤 <br>서로의 온기 나누던 눈 오던 밤 <br>맨몸으로부터 세운 작은 집 <br>그래 봤자 반은 노란 은행 것이지 <br>대출 통장 바라보며 한숨 쉬다 <br>빚 없는 행복을 그리며 잠이 든다 <br>매일 지친 몸을 달랠 <br>술을 마시셨지 <br>우리 둘을 앞에 <br>앉히고선 말하셨지 <br>다정도 병인양하여 <br>잠 못 이루노라셨지 <br>크면 꼭 오페라 하우스 <br>구경시켜달라 하셨지 <br>자신의 꿈보다는 자식의 꿈이 <br>본인의 삶보다는 아들의 삶이 <br>중요해지는 시기가 올 테지 <br>그럴 때쯤 나도 사랑을 알 테지 <br>처음으로 꼭 잡은 그 손가락 <br>어느새 새어버린 머리카락 <br>나면서부터 받은 절대적 사랑 <br>되갚을 수도 없는 무한한 사랑 <br>나는 부르네 순수했던 그 시절 <br>나는 부르네 돌아가고픈 그날들 <br>나는 그리네 잃어버린 우리 기억을 <br>나는 그리네 돌아가고픈 <br>우리의 추억을 <br>엄마의 두 눈 속에 아빠가 있고 <br>아빠의 두 눈 속에 엄마가 있을 때 <br>영도 다리 넘어 돌아오지 않는 <br>강의 멜로디 <br>그날부터 이어진 러브 스토리 <br>나는 부르네 순수했던 그 시절 <br>나는 부르네 돌아가고픈 그날들 <br>나는 그리네 잃어버린 우리 기억을 <br>나는 그리네 돌아가고픈 <br>우리의 추억을 <br>열두 시 조금 못된 아직은 금요일 밤 <br>반복된 삶에 치여 집으로 오는 길 난 <br>지친 내 마음 달래줄 소주 한 잔 <br>살아갈 힘이 되어줄 추억 한 잔 <br>]]></content><category term="JB Kim" label="JB Kim"/><category term="잃어버린 시절을 찾아서 - Part.1 (Feat. 김희진)" label="잃어버린 시절을 찾아서 - Part.1 (Feat. 김희진)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ovenz/Cemeteries_Feat_Young_Sly/</id><title>O.venz - Cemeteries (Feat. Young Sly) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:14:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:14:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ovenz/Cemeteries_Feat_Young_Sly/" title="O.venz - Cemeteries (Feat. Young Sly) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너의 그림자가 그립네 <br>눈앞에 모든 게 멈추고 허영거리네 <br>마지막 뒷모습이 <br>여전히 또렷하게 보여 <br>더욱더 차가운 어둠으로 향해 숨었네 <br>감정을 전부다 소비해 <br>떠난 너와 다르게 <br>나 홀로 불멸 속에 머물다가 갇혔네 <br>함께한 시간을 <br>퍼즐 조각처럼 맞추다 멈춰 <br>적막 속 행복한 쓴웃음을 지어네 <br>너의 인스타에 또 다른 사람이 <br>그녀의 얼굴을 본다 <br>허무함 비슷한 감정이 머문다 <br>미련인 거 같아 <br>비운한 운명이야 한숨이 깊어져 <br>힘 없이 고개를 떨군다 <br>이별이 찾아왔고 계속 멀어지는 <br>너의 뒷모습만 바라봐 <br>시간이 가도 시간이 가도 <br>모든 게 제자리네 <br>편지를 써도 편지를 써도 <br>갈 곳이 없어 미래가 <br>사라진 파도 사라진 파도 속에 <br>몸을 던질게 <br>여전히 불안한 시선을 감추고 <br>살아난 모든 걸 잃은 후에 <br>너의 그림자가 그립네 <br>눈앞에 모든 게 멈추고 허영거리네 <br>마지막 뒷모습이 <br>여전히 또렷하게 보여 <br>더욱더 차가운 어둠으로 향해 숨었네 <br>감정을 전부다 소비해 <br>떠난 너와 다르게 <br>나 홀로 불멸 속에 머물다가 갇혔네 <br>함께한 시간을 <br>퍼즐 조각처럼 맞추다 멈춰 <br>적막 속 행복한 쓴웃음을 지어네 <br>내 믿음은 더 많은 믿음을 <br>또 요구하지 때론 <br>가끔 동물 같은 분출해도 <br>나는 외로워 <br>I be catch me on the feeling <br>나의 기분 따라 바뀌는 중야 <br>보이는 모든 것들의 위치 <br>I be drop it again but <br>주워 담으려 해 <br>나의 제자리에서 <br>이젠 부담이 됐어 너의 믿음은 <br>얽매이고 뒤집어 내지 되돌아가 <br>난 그 순간으로 매일 <br>네 믿음은 더 많은 <br>믿음을 원하고 있고 <br>그 시간이 가면 갈수록 <br>나를 되돌리고 있어 <br>네 시간은 더 많은 <br>시간을 되돌리고 <br>내 믿음에 더 많은 <br>믿음을 원하고 있어 <br>네 믿음은 더 많은 <br>믿음을 원하고 있고 <br>그 시간이 가면 갈수록 <br>나를 되돌리고 있어 <br>네 시간은 더 많은 시간을 되돌리고 <br>내 믿음에 더 많은 <br>믿음을 원하고 있어 <br>시간이 가도 시간이 가도 <br>모든 게 제자리네 <br>편지를 써도 편지를 써도 <br>갈 곳이 없어 미래가 <br>사라진 파도 사라진 파도 속에 <br>몸을 던질게 <br>여전히 불안한 시선을 감추고 <br>살아난 모든 걸 잃은 후에 <br>]]></content><category term="O.venz" label="O.venz"/><category term="Cemeteries (Feat. Young Sly)" label="Cemeteries (Feat. Young Sly)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/플라스틱/열대야_Feat_다인/</id><title>플라스틱 - 열대야 (Feat. 다인) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:14:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:14:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B1/%EC%97%B4%EB%8C%80%EC%95%BC_Feat_%EB%8B%A4%EC%9D%B8/" title="플라스틱 - 열대야 (Feat. 다인) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뒤척이고 뒤척여도 <br>좀처럼 잠은 오지 않고 <br>귓가에는 시계바늘 <br>돌아가는 소리만 요란한데 <br>창가에 걸려있는 달빛은 <br>눈앞에 아른거리고 <br>고요한 밤하늘의 별빛은 <br>꿈꾸듯 반짝이네 <br>그댄 내게 언제 오려나 <br>오늘 밤도 아니 오려나 <br>애타는 내 마음을 알고 있으려나 <br>기다리고 기다려도 <br>밤새 연락은 오지 않고 <br>혹시 내게 돌아 올까 하는 생각에 <br>잠이 오지 않네 <br>무더운 여름 밤은 어느새 <br>점점 깊어만 가고 <br>한 여름 밤의 열대야속에 <br>그리움도 지쳐가네 <br>그댄 내게 언제 오려나 <br>오늘 밤도 아니 오려나 <br>애타는 내 마음을 알고 있으려나 <br>이 밤이 지나가면 <br>내일은 내게 돌아올까 <br>한 여름 밤을 꼬박 지새며 기다리네 <br>그댄 내게 언제 오려나 <br>오늘 밤도 아니 오려나 <br>애타는 내 마음을 모른 체 하려나 <br>]]></content><category term="플라스틱" label="플라스틱"/><category term="열대야 (Feat. 다인)" label="열대야 (Feat. 다인)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/달콤한_소금/잊을만하면/</id><title>달콤한 소금 - 잊을만하면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:15:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:15:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%AC%EC%BD%A4%ED%95%9C_%EC%86%8C%EA%B8%88/%EC%9E%8A%EC%9D%84%EB%A7%8C%ED%95%98%EB%A9%B4/" title="달콤한 소금 - 잊을만하면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[무표정한 거리를 지나 <br>집으로 가는 길 <br>알 수 없는 허탈한 마음에 <br>무거워지는 내 발걸음 <br>어떤 의미일까 이곳의 난 <br>그 끝의 끝은 어딜까 <br>밀려오는 별의별 생각에 <br>집에 가는 버스를 놓치네 <br>흩날리던 아픈 기억과 <br>깊은 무력감은 <br>잊을만하면 왜 몰려오는지 <br>하루하루 산다는 게 <br>내게만 힘든 일 같아 <br>한없이 슬퍼지는 이 밤 <br>날이 밝아오면 잊혀지겠지 <br>구름 속에 달빛처럼 <br>조금만 더 견디다 보면 <br>조금은 더 단단해지겠지 <br>흩날리던 아픈 기억과 <br>깊은 무력감은 <br>잊을만하면 왜 몰려오는지 <br>하루하루 산다는 게 <br>내게만 힘든 일 같아 <br>한없이 슬퍼지는 이 밤 <br>누군가 나의 손을 잡아 주기를 <br>숨 막히는 이곳에서 날 꺼내주길 <br>누군가 나의 손을 잡아 주기를 <br>숨 막히는 이곳에서 날 꺼내주길 <br>]]></content><category term="달콤한 소금" label="달콤한 소금"/><category term="잊을만하면" label="잊을만하면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리아_Lia/A_Shining_Star/</id><title>리아 (Lia) - A Shining Star - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:18:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:18:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EC%95%84_Lia/A_Shining_Star/" title="리아 (Lia) - A Shining Star - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어둠이 내려올 때면 <br>난 길을 잃어요 <br>무섭고 차가워 <br>두려움만 있죠 <br>한참을 헤매이죠 <br>그저 막막하고 <br>외로움만 내게 <br>남아있죠 <br>어두움이 걷힐 때쯤 <br>따스함이 어두운 날 덮고 <br>알지 못했던 <br>그 손길을 <br>이제야 난 알았죠 <br>A shining star <br>인도해줘요 <br>A shining star <br>날 채워줘요 <br>그 따스함으로 <br>나와 동행해줘요 <br>내가 두렵지 않게 <br>A shining star <br>그대처럼 <br>A shining star <br>빛 비출게요 <br>그 빛을 따라서 <br>어둠을 밝히죠 <br>우리 만나는 그 날까지 <br>어두움이 걷힐 때쯤 <br>따스함이 어두운 날 덮고 <br>알지 못했던 <br>그 손길을 <br>이제야 난 알았죠 <br>A shining star <br>인도해줘요 <br>A shining star <br>날 채워줘요 <br>그 따스함으로 <br>나와 동행해줘요 <br>내가 두렵지 않게 <br>A shining star <br>그대처럼 <br>A shining star <br>빛 비출게요 <br>그 빛을 따라서 <br>어둠을 밝히죠 <br>우리 만나는 그 날까지 <br>]]></content><category term="리아 (Lia)" label="리아 (Lia)"/><category term="A Shining Star" label="A Shining Star"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/심스_IM/전화걸지마/</id><title>심스 ($IM$) - 전화걸지마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:20:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:20:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%AC%EC%8A%A4_IM/%EC%A0%84%ED%99%94%EA%B1%B8%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88/" title="심스 ($IM$) - 전화걸지마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[you never call me no no no more <br>you never call me no no no more <br>너 내게 전화걸지마 <br>우린 여기까지니까 니가 먼저 <br>언제 내게 전화 건 적 있니 <br>다시 내가 하는 일은 없어 <br>don't you believe it <br>니 멋대로만 해 <br>내 의견은 물어보지도 않고 <br>내가 기분 나쁜 장난만 해 <br>다른 커플들과 <br>왜 비교해 우린 우리야 <br>며칠 동안 밤을 새도 넌 <br>일부러 내가 티를 내도 넌 왜 <br>요즘 나한테 무슨 일이 있는 건지 <br>궁금하지도 않아했지 <br>무거워진 마음의 어긋난 대칭 <br>우리라는 그림에 혼자 한 색칠 <br>위로 널 지우려 사랑한 흔적 조차 <br>끝이란 점에는 먼저 도착 <br>이제와 매달린다고 해도 <br>돌아서는 일 따위는 없대도 <br>갑자기 변하지 말고 <br>원래 하던 대로 <br>너란 틀의 밖에 <br>살아볼래 새로이 <br>변명하지마 <br>이제 와서 연연하지마 <br>미안미안 하지만 둘이란 건 없어 <br>없어도 i can do it <br>여기가 우리의 마지막인 거 같애 <br>그리고 친구가 술집에서 본 거 <br>딴 남자랑 너 맞대 <br>내게 전화걸지마 내가 그립대도 <br>i feel there's someone else <br>하필이면 이제야 <br>넌 내게 전화걸지마 넌 내게 devil <br>날 가지고 장난쳐 내 감정도 또 <br>넌 내게 전화걸지마 <br>내게 전화걸지마 <br>내게 전화걸지마 <br>내게 전화걸지마 <br>듣기 싫어 거짓말 <br>나 모르는 번호 안 받는 거 <br>니가 더 잘 알잖아 <br>나 모르는 번호 안 받는 거 <br>니가 더 잘 알잖아 <br>내가 잘 모르는 번호 <br>안받는 건 너도 알잖아 <br>근데 왜 자꾸 번호 바꿔가며 <br>전화 거는 건데 <br>짜증나게 하지 말라고 <br>난 더 이상 할 말이 없다고 <br>ye babe 한 번에 내게 <br>넌 여기까지만이라고 내게 <br>그래 한 대 맞은 기분이야 세게 babe <br>아직도 내가 모르는 거 같다 <br>생각하는 거야 왜 <br>입에 달고 살던 거짓말을 <br>이젠 알겠어 <br>how you feel how you feel ye <br>지금 기분이 어때 <br>한순간에 어이없게 <br>우린 끝났지 <br>how you feel how you feel ye <br>내가 돼보니 어때 <br>잘못한 거야 넌 선택 <br>우린 끝났지 <br>내게 전화걸지마 내가 그립대도 <br>i feel there's someone else <br>하필이면 이제야 <br>넌 내게 전화걸지마 넌 내게 devil <br>날 가지고 장난쳐 내 감정도 또 <br>넌 내게 전화걸지마 <br>내게 전화걸지마 <br>내게 전화걸지마 <br>내게 전화걸지마 <br>듣기 싫어 거짓말 <br>you never call me no no no more <br>you never call me no no no more <br>you never call me no no no more <br>you never call me no no no more <br>내게 전화걸지마 내가 그립대도 <br>i feel there's someone else <br>하필이면 이제야 <br>넌 내게 전화걸지마 넌 내게 devil <br>날 가지고 장난쳐 내 감정도 또 <br>넌 내게 전화걸지마 <br>내게 전화걸지마 <br>내게 전화걸지마 <br>내게 전화걸지마 <br>듣기 싫어 거짓말 <br>서로 정해놓은 건 없지만 <br>넌 나 대신 다른 걸 택했지 <br>한 순간이였대도 그 한 순간으로 <br>이제는 니 옆에는 없지 <br>난 니 옆에 <br>난 니 옆에서 <br>]]></content><category term="심스 ($IM$)" label="심스 ($IM$)"/><category term="전화걸지마" label="전화걸지마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/모노크라운/MONEY_IS/</id><title>모노크라운 - MONEY IS - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:21:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:21:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AA%A8%EB%85%B8%ED%81%AC%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/MONEY_IS/" title="모노크라운 - MONEY IS - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[MONEY IS <br>whose mother <br>whose doctor <br>whose king <br>whose saint <br>생각해봐 우리에겐 누군지 <br>없는 사람에겐 폭력을 휘두르지 <br>누구에겐 삶의 가치 <br>누구에겐 죽음이 <br>저울질하네 가벼운 주머니의 대가 <br>무거운 봉투에 내려가는 죗값 <br>사짜들의 입을 메우기엔 직방 <br>길어지네 구멍 많은 계좌 <br>fuck the money라 외쳐도 <br>지금 나의 입을 먹여주는 건 <br>wherefrom <br>칼이 아닌 날카로운 <br>종이에 목이 베였고 <br>상처가 남은 자리는 <br>매일 아침마다 괴로워해 <br>나를 비롯해 <br>칸 크리트 아래의 삶을 누가 위로해 <br>우린 갇혀있네 자본주의의 미로에 <br>피로 새겨진 지폐들에 기록된 <br>유서 이 무덤들이 우리 돈의 <br>출처 그 지하에는 역사들이 <br>숨 쉬어 누군가는 묘비석을 <br>부셔 지폐들에 기록된 <br>유서 이 무덤들이 우리 돈의 <br>출처 그 지하에는 역사들이 <br>숨 쉬어 누군가는 묘비석을 <br>부셔 지폐들에 기록된 <br>2016 대한민국 중심 서울에선 <br>눈앞에 놓여있는 <br>저기 지폐들은 내 것 <br>갖지 못한 자의 뒷모습을 알기에 <br>목숨 걸지 아니하면 <br>결국 가진 것도 뺏겨 <br>많은 돈일수록 <br>더 많은 문제를 만든대 <br>지금은 없을수록 <br>더 많은 문제를 만드네 <br>수많은 문제들을 해결하는 방법엔 <br>이젠 빠질 수가 없는 <br>종이라고 생각 가지기에 <br>인간이 가져야 할 가치를 상실 <br>인간을 경시하는 풍조라고 다들 알지 <br>그 설명에서 오는 불쾌함 <br>그걸 일반적인 현상이라 보는 부패가 <br>어째서 당연하다 느껴지는지 <br>우리는 만족하는가 당장 지금이 <br>과정이 아닌 결과로 <br>역사에 남아 기록된다면 <br>그것이 자랑스럽다 여길 수 있을지 <br>숨겨 잘난 돈의 추악한 그 <br>출처 지폐들이 머리 위서 <br>춤춰 돈으로 만들어 지 탑을 우린 <br>부셔 여기로부터 <br>숨겨 잘난 돈의 추악한 그 <br>출처 지폐들이 머리 위서 <br>춤춰 돈으로 만들어 지 탑을 우린 <br>부셔 여기로부터 <br>MONEY IS <br>]]></content><category term="모노크라운" label="모노크라운"/><category term="MONEY IS" label="MONEY IS"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/뮤직마루/매일_듣는_노래_MR/</id><title>뮤직마루 - 매일 듣는 노래 (MR) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:23:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:23:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AE%A4%EC%A7%81%EB%A7%88%EB%A3%A8/%EB%A7%A4%EC%9D%BC_%EB%93%A3%EB%8A%94_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98_MR/" title="뮤직마루 - 매일 듣는 노래 (MR) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[힘든 하루 끝에 집 앞에 <br>거리를 서성이다 <br>돋아나는 이 공허함에 그 노래를 um <br>나도 모르게 또 이렇게 <br>흥얼거리고 있어 <br>아마 너를 애타게 너를 부르듯이 <br>세상에서 이 노래가 <br>제일 좋다며 들려주던 <br>함께 듣던 노래 너무 슬픈 이 노래 <br>매일 듣는 이 노래가 또 <br>매일 울려 이 노래가 널 <br>떠올리게 만들어 <br>다 우리 얘기만 같아서 <br>아무리 귀를 막아봐도 <br>자꾸 맴돌아 <br>듣고 싶지 않아 몸부림쳐도 <br>매일 듣는 노래 <br>시간이 지나도 이 노랜 <br>잊혀지질 않았어 <br>가사 하나 멜로디까지 선명해서 <br>네 앞에서 불러주려 <br>매일 매일 혼자 연습했던 <br>함께 듣던 노래 가슴 아픈 이 노래 <br>매일 듣는 이 노래가 또 <br>매일 울려 이 노래가 널 <br>떠올리게 만들어 <br>다 우리 얘기만 같아서 <br>아무리 귀를 막아봐도 <br>자꾸 맴돌아 <br>듣고 싶지 않아 몸부림쳐도 <br>매일 듣는 노래 <br>딴 얘기 같던 노랫말은 <br>곧 우리가 됐고 <br>그렇게 남은 건 망가진 하루들 <br>아주 작은 방 홀로 <br>틀어 놓은 이 노래로 <br>조심스레 다시 널 불러본다 <br>매일 듣는 이 노래가 또 <br>매일 울려 이 노래가 널 <br>떠올리게 만들어 <br>모두 우리 추억들만 같아서 <br>아무리 귀를 막아봐도 <br>자꾸 맴돌아 <br>듣고 싶지 않아 몸부림쳐도 <br>매일 듣는 노래]]></content><category term="뮤직마루" label="뮤직마루"/><category term="매일 듣는 노래 (MR)" label="매일 듣는 노래 (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/가려진_달/이뻐이뻐/</id><title>가려진 달 - 이뻐이뻐 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:23:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:23:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%80%EB%A0%A4%EC%A7%84_%EB%8B%AC/%EC%9D%B4%EB%BB%90%EC%9D%B4%EB%BB%90/" title="가려진 달 - 이뻐이뻐 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[외롭고 차가운 나의 마음에 <br>한줄기 빛처럼 다가온 그대 <br>이뻐이뻐 너무 이뻐 <br>정신을 차릴 수가 없어 <br>비좁고 초라한 나의 마음의 문 <br>두드려준 그대란 사람 <br>놀라 놀라 깜짝 놀라 <br>선뜻 문을 열 수가 없었죠 <br>놓치고 싶지 않아요 <br>행복을 이야기 하고 싶어요 <br>언제까지나 지금처럼 <br>이쁜 그대와 함께 할께요 <br>언제까지나 내 곁에서 <br>그대 곁에서 우리 행복해요 <br>언제까지나 내 곁에서 <br>그대 곁에서 우리 행복해요 <br>놓치고 싶지 않아요 <br>행복을 이야기 하고 싶어요 <br>언제까지나 지금처럼 <br>이쁜 그대와 함께 할께요 <br>언제까지나 내 곁에서 <br>그대 곁에서 우리 행복해요 <br>언제까지나 내 곁에서 <br>그대 곁에서 우리 행복해요 <br>]]></content><category term="가려진 달" label="가려진 달"/><category term="이뻐이뻐" label="이뻐이뻐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/가려진_달/종이비행기/</id><title>가려진 달 - 종이비행기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:23:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:23:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%80%EB%A0%A4%EC%A7%84_%EB%8B%AC/%EC%A2%85%EC%9D%B4%EB%B9%84%ED%96%89%EA%B8%B0/" title="가려진 달 - 종이비행기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비온 뒤 나른한 아침 <br>우울한 비 이제는 없어 <br>모든 것이 바뀌었지 <br>세상은 이렇게 아름다워 <br>더 이상 두려움은 없어 <br>난 그대에게 달려가 <br>거칠 것 없는 시간들 <br>난 그대에게 날아가 <br>하얀 종이 비행기 날렸어 <br>작은 마음도 함께 보냈지 <br>그대가 볼 수 있게 <br>더 이상 두려움은 없어 <br>난 그대에게 달려가 <br>거칠 것 없는 시간들 <br>난 그대에게 날아가 <br>하얀 종이 비행기 날렸어 <br>작은 마음도 함께 보냈지 <br>그대가 볼 수 있게 <br>하얀 종이 비행기 날렸어 <br>작은 마음도 함께 보냈지 <br>그대가 볼 수 있게 <br>]]></content><category term="가려진 달" label="가려진 달"/><category term="종이비행기" label="종이비행기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나태성/더더더/</id><title>나태성 - 더더더 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:25:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:25:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%ED%83%9C%EC%84%B1/%EB%8D%94%EB%8D%94%EB%8D%94/" title="나태성 - 더더더 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[두비두비 두비두비 두비 두비두 <br>두비두비 두비두비 두비 두비두 <br>세상에 지쳐서 힘이 들때면 <br>내곁에 네가 있었지 <br>지친 나의 영혼 토닥이면서 <br>그렇게 너도 울었지 <br>소주 한잔에 슬퍼 질때면 <br>네 이름 나는 불렀어 <br>거친 세상살이 타박하면서 <br>그렇게 둘이 둘이서 <br>보고싶어서 안고싶어서 <br>눈물 나는 사람 <br>그 사람 바로 너잖아 <br>보고있어도 안고있어도 <br>눈물 겨운 사람 <br>그 사람 바로 너잖아 <br>더 더 더 더 더 더 <br>내가 사랑 해줄게 <br>더 더 더 더 더 더 <br>내 사랑 가득 채워 줄게 <br>두비두비 두비두비 두비 두비두 <br>두비두비 두비두비 두비 두비두 <br>사는게 버거워 힘이 들때면 <br>내곁에 네가 있었지 <br>거친 나의 숨결 토닥이면서 <br>그렇게 둘이 둘이서 <br>보고싶어서 안고싶어서 <br>눈물 나는 사람 <br>그 사람 바로 너잖아 <br>보고있어도 안고있어도 <br>눈물 겨운 사람 <br>그 사람 바로 너잖아 <br>더 더 더 더 더 더 <br>내가 사랑 해줄게 <br>더 더 더 더 더 더 <br>내 사랑 가득 채워 줄게 <br>고마워 사랑해 <br>좀 더 내가 잘할게 <br>더 더 더 더 더 더 <br>내 사랑 가득 채워 줄게 <br>내 사랑 가득 채워 줄게 <br>더 더 더 가득 채워 줄게 <br>]]></content><category term="나태성" label="나태성"/><category term="더더더" label="더더더"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안원국/월화수목금토일/</id><title>안원국 - 월화수목금토일 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:25:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:25:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%9B%90%EA%B5%AD/%EC%9B%94%ED%99%94%EC%88%98%EB%AA%A9%EA%B8%88%ED%86%A0%EC%9D%BC/" title="안원국 - 월화수목금토일 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[월화수목금토일 <br>믿음 안에서 살기 <br>난 이렇게 기도를 하는데 <br>교회만 나오면 또 난 넘어지고 <br>또 난 세상에 사네 <br>월화수목금토일 <br>주의 자녀로 살기 <br>난 이렇게 기도를 하는데 <br>예배만 마치면 다른 사람이 되네 <br>또 난 세상에 사네 <br>끝없는 사랑 <br>저 바다보다 더 깊은 그 사랑 <br>날 향해 변치 않을 당신의 마음 <br>놀라운 사랑 <br>거져주신 당신의 그 사랑이 <br>월화수목금토일 <br>모두 주일 되길 <br>월화수목금토일 <br>말씀 안에서 살기 <br>난 이렇게 기도를 하는데 <br>교회만 나오면 또 난 넘어지고 <br>또 난 세상에 사네 <br>끝없는 사랑 <br>저 바다보다 더 깊은 그 사랑 <br>날 향해 변치 않을 당신의 마음 <br>놀라운 사랑 <br>거져주신 당신의 그 사랑이 <br>월화수목금토일 <br>모두 주일 되길 <br>끝없는 사랑 <br>저 바다보다 더 깊은 그 사랑 <br>날 향해 변치 않을 당신의 마음 <br>놀라운 사랑 <br>거져주신 당신의 그 사랑이 <br>월화수목금토일 <br>모두 주일 되길 <br>간절히 바라네 매일 주일이 되길 <br>매일 주와 함께 살아가길 <br>월화수목금토일 <br>모두 주일이 되길 <br>진짜 제자가 되길 <br>]]></content><category term="안원국" label="안원국"/><category term="월화수목금토일" label="월화수목금토일"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/사비나앤드론즈/Glass_Bridge_Inst/</id><title>사비나앤드론즈 - Glass Bridge (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:25:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:25:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%82%AC%EB%B9%84%EB%82%98%EC%95%A4%EB%93%9C%EB%A1%A0%EC%A6%88/Glass_Bridge_Inst/" title="사비나앤드론즈 - Glass Bridge (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Howling moon <br>It has been so while <br>In the silence <br>And if you believe <br>In my little world <br>Tomorrow will <br>Have a wonder <br>Don't know where to go <br>Tell me for sure <br>That you won't leave me here alone <br>I need to know <br>You will I believe <br>When I do need someone to hold <br>You'll be here <br>Little voice I hear <br>Yeah maybe <br>Maybe no <br>Who's to say <br>Slowly drowning in <br>After wave <br>After wave <br>Who to say <br>Then I cross a bridge for <br>Over million reasons to hold on <br>Hide away with me <br>Walk away with me <br>Then we cross a bridge for <br>Over million troubles to meet <br>Nothing is easy <br>Nothing is easy <br>Oh how well you see <br>How will you try How <br>However I mean to you now try <br>Then I cross a bridge for <br>Over million reasons to hold on <br>Hide away with me <br>Walk away with me <br>Then we cross a bridge for <br>Over million troubles to meet <br>Nothing is easy <br>Nothing is easy <br>]]></content><category term="사비나앤드론즈" label="사비나앤드론즈"/><category term="Glass Bridge (Inst.)" label="Glass Bridge (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/사비나앤드론즈/Glass_Bridge/</id><title>사비나앤드론즈 - Glass Bridge - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:25:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:25:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%82%AC%EB%B9%84%EB%82%98%EC%95%A4%EB%93%9C%EB%A1%A0%EC%A6%88/Glass_Bridge/" title="사비나앤드론즈 - Glass Bridge - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Howling moon <br>It has been so while <br>In the silence <br>And if you believe <br>In my little world <br>Tomorrow will <br>Have a wonder <br>Don't know where to go <br>Tell me for sure <br>That you won't leave me here alone <br>I need to know <br>You will I believe <br>When I do need someone to hold <br>You'll be here <br>Little voice I hear <br>Yeah maybe <br>Maybe no <br>Who's to say <br>Slowly drowning in <br>After wave <br>After wave <br>Who to say <br>Then I cross a bridge for <br>Over million reasons to hold on <br>Hide away with me <br>Walk away with me <br>Then we cross a bridge for <br>Over million troubles to meet <br>Nothing is easy <br>Nothing is easy <br>Oh how well you see <br>How will you try How <br>However I mean to you now try <br>Then I cross a bridge for <br>Over million reasons to hold on <br>Hide away with me <br>Walk away with me <br>Then we cross a bridge for <br>Over million troubles to meet <br>Nothing is easy <br>Nothing is easy <br>]]></content><category term="사비나앤드론즈" label="사비나앤드론즈"/><category term="Glass Bridge" label="Glass Bridge"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanotek/Tell_Me_Who_Feat_Eneli/</id><title>Vanotek - Tell Me Who (Feat. Eneli) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:25:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:25:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanotek/Tell_Me_Who_Feat_Eneli/" title="Vanotek - Tell Me Who (Feat. Eneli) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The world gets lonely <br>Find me something to believe in <br>Maybe I’m blind <br>The world’s gone mad now <br>Find me something to believe in <br>Maybe I’m blind <br><br>See I’ve been waiting for so long <br>Waitin’ for so long <br>See I’ve been waiting for so long <br>Why does it always seem so wrong <br>Ooo, it seems so wrong <br>See I’ve been waiting for so long <br><br>Tell me who is gonna be there for you <br>What you do is gonna come back to you <br>Tell me who is gonna be there for you <br>What you do what you do <br><br>This ain’t the truth I wanna find <br>Or am I dreaming <br>Maybe I’m blind <br>This ain’t the place I said <br>I always wanna live in <br>Maybe I’m blind <br><br>See I’ve been waiting for so long <br>Waitin’ for so long <br>See I’ve been waiting for so long <br>Why does it always seem so wrong <br>Ooo, it seems so wrong <br>See I’ve been waiting for so long <br><br>Tell me who is gonna be there for you <br>What you do is gonna come back to you <br>Tell me who is gonna be there for you <br>What you do what you do <br><br>I think I might lose it <br>I’m so tired of usin’ <br>Just different words <br>To say the same story <br>But I guess I’m just lonely <br>What can you do for me <br>Will you just let me be <br>Have I done anything wrong <br><br>Tell me who… <br>Just tell me who… <br>Tell me who… <br>Just tell me who… <br>Just tell me who…]]></content><category term="Vanotek" label="Vanotek"/><category term="Tell Me Who (Feat. Eneli)" label="Tell Me Who (Feat. Eneli)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GooSe_구스/딜레마_Original_Ver/</id><title>GooSe (구스) - 딜레마 (Original Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:26:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:26:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GooSe_%EA%B5%AC%EC%8A%A4/%EB%94%9C%EB%A0%88%EB%A7%88_Original_Ver/" title="GooSe (구스) - 딜레마 (Original Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새벽 다섯 시 멍하니 <br>방안에 갇혀 우두커니 <br>천장을 보고 혼자 속삭여 <br>너 지금 뭐해 <br>미래에 모순되게 또 해가 뜨고 <br>어두웠던 방안이 밝아지고 <br>허무한 하루를 보내고 나서야 <br>정신을 잃어 <br>꿈 안에서 마저 <br>지독한 현실을 만나 <br>숨이 가빠져 <br>제발 이 악몽에서 <br>누가 날 좀 깨워줘 <br>깨 깨 깨긴 아직 일러 <br>실제화로 그려질 것 같은 <br>스포일러에 <br>발버둥치다 눈을 떠보면 <br>등줄기에서 식은땀이 주르르륵 <br>싸구려커피를 마시고 <br>졸음과 맞서 싸우려 <br>두 뺨을 때려가며 <br>시를 쓰던 10년 전 <br>연필이 심어놓은 매일 자라던 <br>중지의 굳은 살은 매끈해지고 <br>배부른 생각에 지배당하며 <br>시대가 바뀜에 따라 <br>사라져버린 나의 기대 <br>빛을 잃어버린 별처럼 <br>날개가 부러진 새처럼 <br>주인을 잃어 <br>어디도 갈 수가 없는 <br>버려진 개처럼 <br>발가벗겨진 임금님처럼 <br>왜 항상 지금 하는 일에 <br>떳떳하지 못할까 <br>아무리 Level을 올려보려고 <br>노력을 해봐도 <br>쌓이지 않는 경험치와 <br>멈춰버린 나의 Stage는 제자리지 <br>넘쳐나는 래퍼 수에 비례하며 <br>좁은 무댄 콜로세움이 되어버렸고 <br>이건 뭐 퍽 하면 넘어질 <br>밀고 당기는 줄다리기 <br>피 튀기는 경쟁 속에 마이크대신 <br>총을 쥐고 친구의 가슴을 겨냥해 <br>이젠 더러운 짓 좀 그만해 <br>차라리 혼자가 낫다며 <br>자신을 토닥거렸고 <br>울리지 않는 휴대폰을 붙들고 <br>액정이 침으로 물들 때까지 <br>뱉고 또 뱉어 <br>주변과 소통이 단절된 채 <br>Logout 된 SNS <br>Send a Message는 Pass <br>결국 내 곁을 떠나가는 사람들 <br>얻지 못한 결과물에 <br>허언증 환자 보듯 <br>가슴에 박힌 과녁을 향해 <br>화살처럼 쏴대는 따가운 시선들 <br>이제서야 하고 싶은 걸 찾았는데 <br>해야 하는 것들에 가려져 사실 잘 <br>보이지가 않아 딜레마 <br>실패가 너무나 두렵다 <br>내일이 오는 게 무섭다 <br>모두에 기억 속에서 <br>잊혀져 가며 죽었다 <br>노트에 눈처럼 하얗던 속살은 <br>개나리처럼 노랗게 물들어 버렸네 <br>추운 겨울이 가고 <br>내게도 봄이 오려나 봐 <br>책상에 앉아서 <br>돌린 적 없었던 한 다스의 <br>연필들은 며칠을 못 버티고 <br>몽땅 몽당연필이 되어 <br>계절 지난 꽃처럼 시들어가 <br>깎아도 나오지 않는 <br>연필심에도 <br>끄적거리는 습관이 <br>모두에 고개를 <br>끄덕거리게 만드는 순간을 <br>나에게 안겨주겠지 <br>날 바라보는 <br>몇몇 동경에 눈빛이 <br>아무도 모르게 <br>군장을 멘 듯이 어깨를 짓누르며 <br>오도가도 못하게 <br>발목에 족쇄를 채워 <br>눈물을 흘려도 옆에서 <br>닦아줄 사람 하나 없고 <br>정신차리게 궁상이라고 <br>욕해줄 사람 하나 없네 <br>가진 거라곤 몇 장의 <br>구겨진 지폐와 <br>슬픔에 젖어 타지 않는 심장 하나 <br>그리고 나의 전부가 된 이 노래 <br>성격은 점점 예민해지고 <br>마음의 문은 이미 닫혀버린 채로 <br>날이 선 자존심에 베일까 <br>이 문 두들겨 줄 사람은 zero <br>나중에 돈 많이 벌면 보자 <br>그 약속을 지키지 못했네 고작 <br>3만원이 없어서 연락할 수 없었고 <br>차가운 작업실 바닥에 앉아 <br>쓴 술을 넘겼네 혼자 쓴 술을 넘겼네 <br>무엇을 위해서 사는가 <br>정말 돈 없이도 행복할 수 있을까 <br>대답해 O 아니면 X <br>or NO 아니면 YES <br>oh 어차피 정답은 뻔해 <br>결국엔 Paradox <br>아무 때나 힘들 때 <br>기댈 수 있게 너에게 <br>어깨를 빌려줄게 <br>어때 라며 물어봐 줄 <br>친구를 한 손으로도 <br>충분히 세 <br>]]></content><category term="GooSe (구스)" label="GooSe (구스)"/><category term="딜레마 (Original Ver.)" label="딜레마 (Original Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GooSe_구스/종이별/</id><title>GooSe (구스) - 종이별 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:26:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:26:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GooSe_%EA%B5%AC%EC%8A%A4/%EC%A2%85%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84/" title="GooSe (구스) - 종이별 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뚝뚝 떨어지던 비가 밤을 적시며 <br>하늘에서 내려와 <br>내 마음을 적시고 창문에 똑똑 <br>노크를 하며 인사 <br>째깍거리던 시곗바늘을 보니 <br>짜증이 밀려와 <br>하루가 시작 되자마자 <br>잔뜩 찌푸린 인상 <br>이런 날에는 온몸이 <br>바늘로 콕콕 찌른 듯 쑤셔 <br>황홀한 새벽공기에 취해 <br>숨을 크게 들이마셔 <br>또 다시 한 주가 시작 됐구나 <br>휴 한숨을 내쉬어 <br>졸린 눈 비비며 냉수 한잔 <br>시원하게 마셔 <br>커튼 틈 사이로 아침햇살이 <br>나를 반겨주네 <br>커피 타고 하늘 위로 <br>쭉 펴보는 기지개 <br>새들이 포롱이는 소리에 <br>창밖을 바라보니 눈앞에 <br>하늘 아래 활짝 펴있는 <br>일곱 빛깔 무지개 <br>매지구름은 새하얀 솜처럼 <br>곱게 물들고 <br>물비늘은 해님 품에서 <br>아스라이 찰랑이네 <br>꽃샘바람에 꽃나무들은 <br>위태롭게 춤을 추고 <br>꽃잎을 벗으며 색을 잃어가는 모습이 <br>꼭 내 자화상 같아라 <br>어릴 적 간절했던 순수한 바람도 <br>내 귀를 스쳐가는 시원한 바람도 <br>저 멀리 그곳에 더 높이 <br>하늘에 <br>자유롭게 날 수 있게끔 <br>해주진 않을거야 <br>아련한 꿈을 꾸며 빌었던 소망으로 <br>막연한 숨을 쉬며 믿었던 로망으로 <br>날개펴고 바다위로 <br>헤엄치고 구름위로 <br>날아올라 은하수에 별을 꽉 안을거야 <br>요즘 재미있다는 영화들 <br>다 챙겨보고 있나요 <br>차 한 잔 하고 바람도 쐬면서 <br>스트레스 좀 푸나요 <br>자기 전 기대를 안고 <br>자신의 미래에 꿈을 꾸나요 <br>각박한 세상 속에서 <br>제대로 숨은 쉬며 사나요 <br>한숨은 뿌연 안개가 되어 <br>회색도시를 그려 <br>내일의 해가 떠도 <br>여긴 앞이 너무나 흐려 <br>선명히 보이는 거라고는 <br>빌딩숲 속 네온사인 <br>눈물이 비가 되어 내릴 때면 <br>빌려 줄게요 내 우산 <br>사는 게 왜 이리도 재미가 없는지 낙 <br>이라곤 맨날 지겹게 듣는 옛날음악 <br>중학생 때나 하던 <br>오락으로 얻는 쾌락 <br>조각 난 꿈은 영락없이 <br>날지 못하는 종이학 <br>매일 아침도 거른 채 <br>빈속에 대고 급히 양치질 <br>내일 아침도 뜀박질 <br>제일 어려운 숨바꼭질 <br>악질의 갑질에 딸꾹질 <br>며칠째 일만하는 현실 <br>이 길이 내 길이 맞는지 <br>적지 못하는 답안지 <br>어릴 적 간절했던 순수한 바람도 <br>내 귀를 스쳐가는 시원한 바람도 <br>저 멀리 그곳에 더 높이 <br>하늘에 <br>자유롭게 날 수 있게끔 <br>해주진 않을거야 <br>아련한 꿈을 꾸며 빌었던 소망으로 <br>막연한 숨을 쉬며 믿었던 로망으로 <br>날개펴고 바다위로 <br>헤엄치고 구름위로 <br>날아올라 은하수에 별을 꽉 안을거야 <br>별찌처럼 쏟아지는 청춘의 범람 <br>마법처럼 들려오는 그대들의 소란 <br>내 마음속 가난은 보물섬에 유랑 <br>몽환의 숲 파랑새는 어른들에 허망 <br>무엇으로 덮어야 <br>춥고 시린 마음이 녹지 <br>무엇으로 적셔야 <br>너에 대한 갈증을 풀지 <br>고비를 넘기면 넘길수록 <br>높아지는 계단 <br>차라리 하늘에 별을 딸래 <br>이게 나의 대답 <br>서른이 코앞인데 <br>어른이 되는 법을 모르니 <br>여전히 앞만 보고 달려서 <br>뒤는 못보고 가버리지 <br>소중한건 모두 잊고 살았었는데 <br>오늘만큼은 이젠 그 랩 쓰면 좋겠네 <br>유리병에 담긴 종이별에게 <br>소원을 빌죠 <br>언젠간 은하수에서 <br>날 비춰 줄 거라 믿죠 <br>아직도 동화 속 주인공처럼 <br>달콤한 꿈을 꾸죠 <br>아무도 당신의 꿈은 <br>절대 비웃을 수 없죠 <br>어릴 적 간절했던 순수한 바람도 <br>내 귀를 스쳐가는 시원한 바람도 <br>저 멀리 그곳에 더 높이 하늘에 <br>자유롭게 날 수 있게끔 <br>해주진 않을거야 <br>아련한 꿈을 꾸며 빌었던 소망으로 <br>막연한 숨을 쉬며 믿었던 로망으로 <br>날개펴고 바다위로 <br>헤엄치고 구름위로 <br>날아올라 은하수에 별을 꽉 안을거야 <br>어릴 적 간절했던 순수한 바람도 <br>내 귀를 스쳐가는 시원한 바람도 <br>저 멀리 그곳에 더 높이 하늘에 <br>자유롭게 날 수 있게끔 <br>해주진 않을거야 <br>아련한 꿈을 꾸며 빌었던 소망으로 <br>막연한 숨을 쉬며 믿었던 로망으로 <br>날개펴고 바다위로 <br>헤엄치고 구름위로 <br>날아올라 은하수에 별을 꽉 안을거야 <br>]]></content><category term="GooSe (구스)" label="GooSe (구스)"/><category term="종이별" label="종이별"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/A7/BEX/</id><title>A7 - BEX - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:34:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:34:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/A7/BEX/" title="A7 - BEX - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>FEEL THE BASS <br>FEEL THE SOUND <br>THAT’S MOVE <br>]]></content><category term="A7" label="A7"/><category term="BEX" label="BEX"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BLVN_BELIEVE_IN/Like_An_Airplane/</id><title>BLVN (BELIEVE IN) - Like An Airplane - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:36:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:36:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BLVN_BELIEVE_IN/Like_An_Airplane/" title="BLVN (BELIEVE IN) - Like An Airplane - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[안개가 하나 둘 사라지고 <br>알람 소린 날 괴롭히며 <br>화려한 도시의 아침을 맞이해 <br>누군가는 한숨을 쉬고 <br>누군가는 밝게 웃으며 <br>서로 다른 기억을 만들어가네 <br>하지만 우리는 다시 걸어가네 <br>대답을 찾기 위해서 떠나가네 <br>Like An Airplane <br>Like An Airplane <br>희미한 구름 속에서 길을 잃네 <br>외로운 별들과 함께 날아가네 <br>Like An Airplane <br>Like An Airplane <br>Like An Airplane <br>해맑게 미소 짓는 아이들 <br>너무 닳아 버린 내 모습 <br>소중한 무언가를 잊고 살아가네 <br>누군가는 포기하라 해 <br>누군가는 힘을 내라 해 <br>이럴 땐 머릿속이 혼란스러워 <br>하지만 우리는 다시 걸어가네 <br>대답을 찾기 위해서 떠나가네 <br>Like An Airplane <br>Like An Airplane <br>희미한 구름 속에서 길을 잃네 <br>외로운 별들과 함께 날아가네 <br>Like An Airplane <br>Like An Airplane <br>Like An Airplane <br>만약에 오늘 밖에 살 수가 없었다면 <br>만약에 내일이 오지 않는다면 <br>희미한 구름 속에서 길을 잃네 <br>외로운 별들과 함께 날아가네 <br>Like An Airplane <br>Like An Airplane <br>Like An Airplane <br>Like An Airplane <br>]]></content><category term="BLVN (BELIEVE IN)" label="BLVN (BELIEVE IN)"/><category term="Like An Airplane" label="Like An Airplane"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BLVN_BELIEVE_IN/Make_A_Memory/</id><title>BLVN (BELIEVE IN) - Make A Memory - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:36:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:36:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BLVN_BELIEVE_IN/Make_A_Memory/" title="BLVN (BELIEVE IN) - Make A Memory - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I saw you talking with your friend <br>you had brown hair <br>small hands <br>When you looked at me suddenly <br>my heart started beating <br>And you are like a rose to me <br>never seen before in my life <br>I don't want to go right now <br>I gotta say one thing <br>Tonight I will never let you go <br>Tonight I wanna make a memory <br>I drank two bottles of Corona <br>‘Cause I felt so nervous <br>Though I'm not a talkative man <br>I have courage <br>I will whisper my sweet love <br>before you leave this bar <br>If I can't talk to you right now <br>maybe I can't sleep <br>Tonight I will never let you go <br>Tonight I wanna make a memory <br>Tonight I will never let you go <br>Tonight I wanna make a memory <br>Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah <br>Never let you go <br>Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah <br>Never let you go <br>Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah <br>Never let you go <br>Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah <br>Never let you go <br>Tonight I will never let you go <br>Tonight I wanna make a memory <br>]]></content><category term="BLVN (BELIEVE IN)" label="BLVN (BELIEVE IN)"/><category term="Make A Memory" label="Make A Memory"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BLVN_BELIEVE_IN/오늘_고민은_내일_하자/</id><title>BLVN (BELIEVE IN) - 오늘 고민은 내일 하자 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:36:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:36:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BLVN_BELIEVE_IN/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98_%EA%B3%A0%EB%AF%BC%EC%9D%80_%EB%82%B4%EC%9D%BC_%ED%95%98%EC%9E%90/" title="BLVN (BELIEVE IN) - 오늘 고민은 내일 하자 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘도 이력서는 거절당해 <br>Why Why Why <br>만약에 회사에 들어가지 못하면 <br>아마 난 Die Die Die <br>실패의 반복들 불안과 두려움 <br>잠시만 Bye Bye Bye <br>머리를 채우는 부정의 대화들 <br>이제는 Bye Bye Bye <br>오늘의 고민들은 모두 털어버리자 <br>내일의 걱정들은 내일 생각해보자 <br>Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo <br>Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo <br>Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo <br>Wait for better days <br>여전히 눈길 한번 주지 않는 <br>Her Her Her <br>너밖에 없는 나 미칠 것 같은 나 <br>잠시만 Bye Bye Bye <br>너에게 속박된 감정의 노예들 <br>이제는 Bye Bye Bye <br>오늘의 고민들은 모두 털어버리자 <br>내일의 걱정들은 내일 생각해보자 <br>Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo <br>Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo <br>Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo <br>Wait for better days <br>오늘의 고민들은 모두 털어버리자 <br>내일의 걱정들은 내일 생각해보자 <br>Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo <br>Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo <br>Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo <br>Wait for better days <br>Don’t worry today <br>Don’t worry today <br>Don’t worry today <br>Find better days <br>Don’t worry today <br>Don’t worry today <br>Don’t worry today <br>Find better days <br>]]></content><category term="BLVN (BELIEVE IN)" label="BLVN (BELIEVE IN)"/><category term="오늘 고민은 내일 하자" label="오늘 고민은 내일 하자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BLVN_BELIEVE_IN/서울하늘/</id><title>BLVN (BELIEVE IN) - 서울하늘 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:36:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:36:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BLVN_BELIEVE_IN/%EC%84%9C%EC%9A%B8%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98/" title="BLVN (BELIEVE IN) - 서울하늘 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[두 볼에 스치는 차가운 새벽 공기 <br>어둠을 푸르게 물들인 아침 하늘 <br>거리를 메우는 자동차와 사람들 <br>무엇에 쫓기듯 서둘러 떠나가네 <br>시간이 지나도 우린 <br>그 자리에 남지만 <br>서울의 하늘은 우릴 외면한 채 <br>너무 빨리 변하네 <br>거리를 비추는 화려한 네온사인 <br>자정이 넘어도 끝나지 않는 도시 <br>내일이 두려워 자신을 재촉해 <br>숨을 고르고 전쟁을 시작하네 <br>시간이 지나도 우린 <br>그 자리에 남지만 <br>서울의 하늘은 우릴 외면한 채 <br>너무 빨리 변하네 <br>성공을 위해서 몸부림 쳐보고 <br>걷고 또 걸어서 <br>답을 찾고 싶은데 오늘도 <br>귓가에 울리는 싸늘한 서울의 메아리 <br>시간이 지나도 우린 <br>그 자리에 남지만 <br>서울의 하늘은 우릴 외면한 채 <br>너무 빨리 변하네 <br>]]></content><category term="BLVN (BELIEVE IN)" label="BLVN (BELIEVE IN)"/><category term="서울하늘" label="서울하늘"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아메바흐/같이_걸어요_Feat_우아한_태영/</id><title>아메바흐 - 같이 걸어요 (Feat. 우아한, 태영) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:38:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:38:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EB%A9%94%EB%B0%94%ED%9D%90/%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B1%B8%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94_Feat_%EC%9A%B0%EC%95%84%ED%95%9C_%ED%83%9C%EC%98%81/" title="아메바흐 - 같이 걸어요 (Feat. 우아한, 태영) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 기다리다 문득 생각났어 <br>난 행복하구나 <br>발 아래로 떨어지는 빗방울도 <br>구슬 같구나 <br>널 바라보다 문득 생각났어 <br>사랑하는구나 <br>속삭이는 바람들이 날 데려가 줬어 <br>네 곁으로 <br>다가올 가을엔 <br>우리 같이 걸어요 <br>아픈 기억 잊고서 <br>따뜻한 겨울을 준비해요 <br>겨울엔 내 손 놓지 말아요 <br>차가운 바람도 그대 함께라면 <br>나 버틸 수 있어요 <br>처음 그 낯선 거리 난 잊을 수 없죠 <br>희망이 없던 곳 그대 없이 어떻게 <br>지냈었는지 몰라 <br>다가올 가을엔 <br>우리 같이 걸어요 <br>아픈 기억 잊고서 <br>따뜻한 겨울을 준비해요 <br>겨울엔 내 손 놓지 말아요 <br>차가운 바람도 그대 함께라면 <br>나 버틸 수 있어요 <br>우 <br>이제는 알겠죠 그대 사랑하는 걸 <br>좋은 추억만 가지고 <br>따스한 햇살과 함께해요 <br>영원히 우리 같이 걸어요 <br>따스한 바람에 그대 함께라면 <br>나 행복할 거예요 <br>우 <br>설레는 마음을 함께해요 <br>]]></content><category term="아메바흐" label="아메바흐"/><category term="같이 걸어요 (Feat. 우아한, 태영)" label="같이 걸어요 (Feat. 우아한, 태영)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tom_Taped/Felice/</id><title>Tom Taped - Felice - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:38:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:38:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tom_Taped/Felice/" title="Tom Taped - Felice - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Heavy heavy breathing <br>Breath into my mind <br>Let me take this further <br>Because further won't let you down <br><br>I will do this better <br>Because better is in your touch <br>While your body's shaking <br>In these trembling lights <br><br>All I want now is forgiveness <br>Washing my sins aside <br>You're the only one show your weakness <br>I really want your taste in my mouth <br><br>I'm down on my knees, for you Felice <br>Because you came and you saw <br>And you conquered it all <br>That's how I feel for you Felice <br><br>I'm down on my knees for you Felice <br>Don't try to be cool, you got nothing to prove <br>Because you came, and you saw <br>And You conquered it all <br>That's how I feel For you Felice <br><br>Please let me come closer <br>Closer to your mind <br>Wrap your thighs around me <br>Scream and let it rise <br>With zero inhibition <br>Give me those yearning eyes <br>Guide my lips, this mission yeah <br>Pleasures all mine tonight <br><br>All want now is forgiveness <br>Washing my sins aside <br>You're the only one show your weakness <br>I really want your taste in my mouth <br><br>And I'll do anything for you <br>And I'll do anything you want me to <br>And I'll do anything for you <br>And I'll do anything you want me to <br><br>Just for you Felice]]></content><category term="Tom Taped" label="Tom Taped"/><category term="Felice" label="Felice"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lounge_Color/Brand_New/</id><title>Lounge Color - Brand New - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:39:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:39:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lounge_Color/Brand_New/" title="Lounge Color - Brand New - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tonight 적막한 도시의 <br>Simply light <br>나 오늘도 잠들 수 없어 <br>깊어진 밤의 도시에 끝에서 <br>우연히 널 만난 거야 <br>차가워진 입술 끝에 <br>닿은 그 한 모금에 잠식된 내 심장 <br>때론 라떼처럼 독한 술처럼 <br>나를 흔들고 있어 <br>Your mind 내 맘과 같은지 <br>Yes right 그래 그대로 됐어 <br>Alright 시크하게 인정 할게 <br>이 게임의 Winner <br>Your mind 한 번만 돌려봐 <br>Yes right 나 진짜 괜찮은 걸 <br>All right 그래 이젠 괜찮아 <br>단지 이 밤만 지난다면 <br>Tight 이 한순간의 열기가 <br>날 다른 시간으로 이끄는 것 같아 <br>설명할 수는 없지만 <br>너의 마음이 원하잖아 <br>지루했던 시선 끝에 <br>닿은 그 한 순간에 잠식된 내 심장 <br>때론 라떼처럼 독한 술처럼 <br>나를 흔들고 있어 <br>Your mind 내 맘과 같은지 <br>Yes right 그래 그대로 됐어 <br>Alright 시크하게 인정 할게 <br>이 게임의 Winner <br>Your mind 한 번만 돌려봐 <br>Yes right 나 진짜 괜찮은 걸 <br>All right 그래 이젠 괜찮아 <br>단지 이 밤만 지난다면 <br>]]></content><category term="Lounge Color" label="Lounge Color"/><category term="Brand New" label="Brand New"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lounge_Color/답장좀주세요/</id><title>Lounge Color - 답장좀주세요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:39:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:39:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lounge_Color/%EB%8B%B5%EC%9E%A5%EC%A2%80%EC%A3%BC%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94/" title="Lounge Color - 답장좀주세요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잠깐이라도 언제까지라도 <br>알고 싶어 그대 안의 마음을 <br>잠깐이라도 언제까지라도 <br>알고 싶어 그대 안의 마음을 <br>어젯밤 내 메일함에 <br>바닷가 모래만큼 쌓인 스팸메일 사이 <br>그대가 뭘 보냈을까 <br>조심히 열어보는 <br>나의 sweet mail box <br>한참을 기다렸지만 <br>아직 아무 소식 없어요 <br>ㅠㅠㅠㅠ <br>혹시 많이 바쁜가요 <br>답장 기다리고 있어요 <br>ㅠㅠㅠㅠ <br>잠깐이라도 나 언제까지라도 <br>말하지 않아도 <br>알고 싶어 나는 그대 안에 있는 <br>마음을 주세요 <br>잠깐이라도 나 언제까지라도 <br>말하지 않아도 <br>알고 싶어 나는 그대 안에 있는 <br>마음을 주세요 <br>I need You u u <br>You need to reply me <br>I need You u u <br>and I'm waiting waiting <br>I need You u u <br>You need to reply me <br>I need You u u <br>and I'm waiting waiting <br>한참을 기다렸지만 <br>아직 아무 소식 없어요 <br>ㅠㅠㅠㅠ <br>혹시 많이 바쁜가요 <br>답장 기다리고 있어요 <br>잠깐이라도 나 언제까지라도 <br>말하지 않아도 <br>알고 싶어 나는 그대 안에 있는 <br>마음을 주세요 <br>잠깐이라도 나 언제까지라도 <br>말하지 않아도 <br>알고 싶어 나는 그대 안에 있는 <br>마음을 주세요 <br>You make me feel so high and low <br>자꾸 더 알고 싶어져 <br>차가운 반응 이래도 <br>마음은 on and on and on <br>You make me feel so high and low <br>자꾸 더 알고 싶어져 <br>차가운 반응 이래도 <br>마음은 on and on <br>잠깐이라도 나 언제까지라도 <br>말하지 않아도 <br>알고 싶어 나는 그대 안에 있는 <br>마음을 주세요 <br>I need You u u <br>You need to reply me <br>I need You u u <br>and I'm waiting waiting <br>I need You u u <br>You need to reply me <br>I need You u u <br>and I'm waiting waiting <br>]]></content><category term="Lounge Color" label="Lounge Color"/><category term="답장좀주세요" label="답장좀주세요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lounge_Color/Wrlking_Notes/</id><title>Lounge Color - W@rlking Notes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:39:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:39:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lounge_Color/Wrlking_Notes/" title="Lounge Color - W@rlking Notes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언제부터인지 노랠 부르지 않아 <br>언제부턴 연봉타령만 하고 있어 <br>나의 회색 재킷 뒤에 <br>아직 미쳐 죽지 못한 파랑이 있을까 <br>오 날지 못한 부르지 못한 노랠 찾아 <br>다시 내게 와줘 <br>다시 날아 봐줘 <br>Oh my friends <br>Makin' makin' real our story <br>다시 내게 와줘 <br>다시 날아 봐줘 <br>Oh my friends <br>Makin' makin' real our band <br>멍하니 지나간 시간 뒷꽁무닐 봐 <br>문득 정신 차려보니 난 제자리에 <br>나의 회색 재킷 뒤에 <br>아직 미쳐 죽지 못한 파랑이 있을까 <br>오 날지 못한 부르지 못한 노랠 찾아 <br>다시 내게 와줘 <br>다시 날아 봐줘 <br>Oh my friends <br>Makin' makin' real our story <br>다시 내게 와줘 <br>다시 날아 봐줘 <br>Oh my friends <br>Makin' makin' real our band <br>다시 날아 봐줘 Oh 내게로 <br>다시 날아 줘 <br>Makin' makin' real our story <br>다시 내게 와줘 <br>다시 날아 봐줘 <br>Oh my friends <br>Makin' makin' real our band <br>다시 내게 와줘 <br>다시 날아 봐줘 <br>Oh my friends <br>Makin' makin' real our story <br>다시 내게 와줘 <br>다시 날아 봐줘 <br>Oh my friends <br>Makin' makin' real our <br>Makin' makin' real our <br>Makin' makin' real our band <br>]]></content><category term="Lounge Color" label="Lounge Color"/><category term="W@rlking Notes" label="W@rlking Notes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Boo_부진철/여름_밤_그대_Feat_낭만유랑악단/</id><title>Boo (부진철) - 여름 밤, 그대 (Feat. 낭만유랑악단) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:39:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:39:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Boo_%EB%B6%80%EC%A7%84%EC%B2%A0/%EC%97%AC%EB%A6%84_%EB%B0%A4_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80_Feat_%EB%82%AD%EB%A7%8C%EC%9C%A0%EB%9E%91%EC%95%85%EB%8B%A8/" title="Boo (부진철) - 여름 밤, 그대 (Feat. 낭만유랑악단) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여름 밤 그대와 <br>함께 바라보던 <br>함께 나누었던 순간 <br>나는 기억해 <br>그때의 우리를 <br>선선한 바람이 불어오고 <br>지친 하루의 끝에 <br>두 눈을 마주하며 <br>두 손을 꼭 잡고서 <br>아무 말 없어도 <br>모든 게 참 소중했던 <br>그 여름 밤의 우리 둘 <br>가만히 누우면 <br>헤아릴 수도 없이 <br>쏟아져 내리는 <br>별빛을 보면서 <br>오늘 어땠었냐고 <br>힘들진 않았냐고 <br>얘기하던 <br>그 밤 <br>그 찬란하고 아름답던 밤 <br>곁에 있어도 네가 보고 싶던 밤 <br>그 모든 게 생각이나 <br>두 눈을 감으면 <br>어느샌가 다가와 <br>귓가에 울리는 <br>파도 소리 들으며 <br>하루가 저문다고 <br>시간이 빠르다며 <br>한숨짓던 <br>그 밤 <br>그 찬란하고 아름답던 밤 <br>그 끝엔 항상 네가 있던 밤 <br>그 모든 게 그리워 <br>나를 바라보던 <br>너의 두 눈빛이 <br>참 그리워 <br>]]></content><category term="Boo (부진철)" label="Boo (부진철)"/><category term="여름 밤, 그대 (Feat. 낭만유랑악단)" label="여름 밤, 그대 (Feat. 낭만유랑악단)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비젤리_Bee_Jelly/Sax_Beach_Feat_Fancy_Jung/</id><title>비젤리 (Bee Jelly) - Sax Beach (Feat. Fancy Jung) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:40:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:40:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%EC%A0%A4%EB%A6%AC_Bee_Jelly/Sax_Beach_Feat_Fancy_Jung/" title="비젤리 (Bee Jelly) - Sax Beach (Feat. Fancy Jung) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밤하늘에 떠 있는 Stars <br>곧 쏟아질 것 같지 않니 <br>달빛에 비춰지는 <br>Small waves Yeah <br>Let me see the smile <br>we're together <br>우릴 비추는 <br>The light of the sun <br>Let me see the love <br>we're in paradise <br>Burnin' up yeah burnin' up <br>릴렉스한 이 기분 All day <br>우리만의 파티를 Anywhere <br>허니문스러운 A fine view <br>Go anywhere <br>Let's go everywhere <br>Make you feel my love <br>Make you feel my love feel my love <br>Make you feel my love baby <br>Share love with you <br>Make you feel my love <br>Make you feel my love feel my love <br>지금 이 순간 <br>Loving you baby <br>Make you feel my love <br>Make you make you <br>feel my love you baby <br>Let me see the smile <br>we're together <br>우릴 비추는 <br>The light of the sun <br>Let me see the love <br>we're in paradise <br>Burnin' up yeah burnin' up <br>릴렉스한 이 기분 All day <br>우리만의 파티를 Anywhere <br>허니문스러운 A fine view <br>Go anywhere <br>Let's go everywhere <br>Make you feel my love <br>Make you feel my love feel my love <br>Make you feel my love baby <br>Share love with you <br>Make you feel my love <br>Make you feel my love feel my love <br>Make you feel my love baby <br>Share love with you <br>Make you feel my love <br>Make you feel my love feel my love <br>Make you feel my love baby <br>Share love with you <br>Make you feel my love <br>Make you feel my love feel my love <br>Make you feel my love <br>Make you make you <br>feel my love you baby <br>Make you feel my love <br>Make you make you <br>feel my love you baby <br>너와 함께 Ocean drive <br>눈이 부신 Shining sky <br>Hold your body close to mine <br>Oh I'm in love with you all day <br>Let's go everywhere <br>Make you feel my love <br>Make you make you <br>feel my love you baby <br>]]></content><category term="비젤리 (Bee Jelly)" label="비젤리 (Bee Jelly)"/><category term="Sax Beach (Feat. Fancy Jung)" label="Sax Beach (Feat. Fancy Jung)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신희영/다시_DASI/</id><title>신희영 - 다시 (DASI) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:41:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:41:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%ED%9D%AC%EC%98%81/%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C_DASI/" title="신희영 - 다시 (DASI) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기나 긴 동안 그댈 향해 <br>기도 드린 수많은 날들은 <br>미련도 없이 가볍게 <br>모든 기억을 지워냈지만 <br>가끔은 예전처럼 <br>나 그때로 되돌아 가고싶어 <br>내 서툰 흔적의 자린 <br>영원히 남겠지만 <br>오 그댄 내게 이대로 <br>영원히 힘든 상처로 <br>지금 그대 여기 없기에 <br>항상 그 자리에 맴돌뿐 <br>내 아픈 꿈에 매일 그댄 <br>내곁에 다가오지만 <br>한참을 서성이며 말 없이 <br>그대는 사라져 버린걸 <br>그대없는 아침 밝아오면 <br>난 잠시 외면하지만 <br>또다시 잊으려 해봐도 <br>그댄 곁에 있는걸 <br>또다시 어제처럼 <br>나 그대의 향기를 느끼지만 <br>언젠가 그대에 모습 <br>희미해 버릴거야 <br>오 그댄 내게 이대로 <br>영원히 힘든 상처로 <br>지금 그대 여기 없기에 <br>항상 그 자리에 맴돌뿐 <br>내 아픈 꿈에 매일 그댄 <br>내곁에 다가오지만 <br>한참을 서성이며 말 없이 <br>그대는 사라져 버린걸 <br>그대없는 아침 밝아오면 <br>난 잠시 외면하지만 <br>또다시 잊으려 해봐도 <br>그댄 곁에 있는걸 <br>아직 고운 그대 숨결만은 <br>내 안에 남아있지만 <br>때로는 이렇게 많은 시간이 <br>가면 잊을까 두려워 <br>그래 지금 그대 세상에서 <br>날 제일 아프게 한게 <br>사실은 그대에 모습이 <br>내겐 변치않는걸 <br>잊으려 해봐도 내곁에 <br>그댄 원치 않나봐 <br>]]></content><category term="신희영" label="신희영"/><category term="다시 (DASI)" label="다시 (DASI)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimeaux/I_Admit_Im_Scared/</id><title>Eskimeaux - I Admit I`m Scared - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:41:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:41:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimeaux/I_Admit_Im_Scared/" title="Eskimeaux - I Admit I`m Scared - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I admit I'm scared <br>Of a warm side of our bed <br>I tremble in the face <br>Of your loneliness <br><br>And everything I think <br>Should be buried in the ground <br>Should be kept inside my head <br>But it's knit into your brow <br><br>I live inside your room <br>And if I reach out with my hand <br>The disturbance sends our things <br>Crashing down upon my head <br><br>And everything I think <br>Should be buried in the ground <br>Should be kept inside my head <br>But it's knit into your brow <br><br>And everything I said <br>Spewed like sparklers from my mouth <br><br>And everything I said <br>Spewed like sparklers from my mouth <br>They looked pretty as they flew <br>But now they're useless and burnt out <br><br>And if I had a dime for <br>Every time I'm freaking out <br>We could fly around the world <br>Or just get out of your parents' house]]></content><category term="Eskimeaux" label="Eskimeaux"/><category term="I Admit I`m Scared" label="I Admit I`m Scared"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimeaux/A_Hug_Too_Long/</id><title>Eskimeaux - A Hug Too Long - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:41:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:41:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimeaux/A_Hug_Too_Long/" title="Eskimeaux - A Hug Too Long - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And if you ever told me <br>That you were scared <br>I'd appear there <br>And if you ever wanted me <br>I'd be scared <br>But I'd appear there <br><br>The light tonight was bluish <br>You didn't see it <br>You went to work <br>I went to New Brunswick <br>And I was feeling foolish <br>Maybe you could see it <br>You went to work <br>I went to New Brunswick <br><br>So maybe I am dead wrong <br>A hug too long <br>A whiff of your hair <br>And if you ever want me <br>You'll hear this song <br>And you will appear there <br>A sway, a bump, a blush <br>The train that carelessly carried us <br><br>You went to work <br>I went to New Brunswick <br>And I can't get enough <br>I'm a thundercloud of love <br>I bloat, I drench, I tear <br>Gabby stop right there]]></content><category term="Eskimeaux" label="Eskimeaux"/><category term="A Hug Too Long" label="A Hug Too Long"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimeaux/Sparrow/</id><title>Eskimeaux - Sparrow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:41:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:41:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimeaux/Sparrow/" title="Eskimeaux - Sparrow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I came back to the east coast <br>Looking out from the beach among the boats <br>From afar I saw two arms <br>Swing together then apart <br><br>You're a shadow from a jaunty kite <br>You're a sparrow with the loudest pipes <br>And I like it <br><br>So I took off my boots <br>And I made my way out to you <br>From afar you are a wrecking ball <br>Swaying dangerous and drunk and high and tired <br><br>But when I got to you, you stood up on the sandbar <br>Spinning circles, laughing, dancing, making waves with your arms <br><br>You're a shadow from a jaunty kite <br>You're a sparrow with the loudest pipes <br>When I think of you it makes me want to cry <br>And I find myself thinking about you all the time <br>And I like it]]></content><category term="Eskimeaux" label="Eskimeaux"/><category term="Sparrow" label="Sparrow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimeaux/Power_/</id><title>Eskimeaux - Power? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:41:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:41:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimeaux/Power_/" title="Eskimeaux - Power? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wish I could love you less like a praying mantis <br>Rip your head off every time this starts to feel right <br>Wish I could love you less <br>Just love, that's it <br><br>Oh how our song's been sung <br>Dropping petals one by one <br>Oh what power can be drawn <br>From just a day of being alone <br><br>Gotta keep in mind it's not always your fault <br>The million tiny ways you make me feel small <br>You can be so anti social <br>And I can just be terrible <br><br>Oh how our song's been sung <br>Dropping petals one by one <br>Oh what power can be drawn <br>From just a day of being alone <br><br>Don't be scared of losing <br>Or something that is ending <br>Love lies in the new things <br>And Every past is worth condemning <br><br>Oh how our song's been sung <br>Dropping petals one by one <br>Oh what power can be drawn <br>From just a day of being alone]]></content><category term="Eskimeaux" label="Eskimeaux"/><category term="Power?" label="Power?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimeaux/The_Thunder_Answered_Back/</id><title>Eskimeaux - The Thunder Answered Back - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:41:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:41:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimeaux/The_Thunder_Answered_Back/" title="Eskimeaux - The Thunder Answered Back - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, how my heart can fly when your smile has good intentions <br>and hi can mean the world to me <br>And I know singing makes you shy when it's in front of me and my friends <br>but your singing means the world to me <br><br>And how I tried to keep my cool when we disappointed you <br>You waxen wing, you foolish thing <br>And oh, how I can still taste your tongue tied stare upon my face <br>You dirty look, you burning bush <br><br>So here I sit, I've come to rest some weight upon your little chest <br>You free for all, you wrecking ball <br>Hovering next to your bed, to lay waste to your healthy head <br>You spider web, you dance of death <br><br>I believe you'd be so cold to leave me hanging all day long <br>You prickly frost, you courage lost <br>But I could never be so mad to shake you by the shoulders screaming <br>You coward <br>You hummingbird <br>You coward <br>You hummingbird <br><br>I screamed out, how'd it get this bad <br>And the thunder answered back <br>If you know not what you lack then you must unturn your back <br><br>Your inside is overcast and you are tethered to your past <br>And it must feel like fucking hell to be a patchwork of yourself <br><br>A bunch of scraps thrown and sewn around your bones <br>And though you're alone it's holding you too tightly <br><br>But who are you <br>From where do you come <br>What do you believe in <br>And whom do you love]]></content><category term="Eskimeaux" label="Eskimeaux"/><category term="The Thunder Answered Back" label="The Thunder Answered Back"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimeaux/Folly/</id><title>Eskimeaux - Folly - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:41:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:41:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimeaux/Folly/" title="Eskimeaux - Folly - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Folly, I was falling <br>I was taller than I wanted to be <br>Hollow, swallowed <br>I was following <br>You were faster than a gelding <br><br>In my mind you're a crow <br>A spirit animal I am won't to know <br>But I don't want to be responsible <br><br>Molding, I was folding <br>Your clothing in some kind of dream <br>Loving, I was hovering <br>I was flipping, fleeting, doving <br><br>In my dreams you're a bathtub running <br>You are warm and tender and bubbling <br>Oh, you are cold and bristling and struggling]]></content><category term="Eskimeaux" label="Eskimeaux"/><category term="Folly" label="Folly"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimeaux/Alone_At_The_Party/</id><title>Eskimeaux - Alone At The Party - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:41:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:41:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eskimeaux/Alone_At_The_Party/" title="Eskimeaux - Alone At The Party - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Are we holding our breath <br>Are you really so depressed <br>Sometimes it's hard to remember you're my friend <br>So I talk to you through my songs instead <br><br>And I know I'm being cold and acting guarded <br>But I can't get stoned so I'm alone at the party <br><br>And how we danced at the show <br>Even with our bags and coats <br>I knocked into your elbow <br>And almost fell onto the floor <br>I was all arms and legs <br>When I looked into your face <br>But now I'm bruised and buckling <br>Did you notice we were touching <br><br>And I know I'm being cold and acting guarded <br>But I can't get stoned so I'm alone at the party <br><br>And I can tell you're afraid <br>And I hate to see you that way <br>But I could be your loner <br>If you would be my stoner <br>And I don't know if it means a thing to you <br>Maybe partly <br>But I'm glad to know you're sad too <br>And feel alone at the party]]></content><category term="Eskimeaux" label="Eskimeaux"/><category term="Alone At The Party" label="Alone At The Party"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임웅균/하늘에_계신_-_주기도문_찬송가_635장/</id><title>임웅균 - 하늘에 계신 - 주기도문 (찬송가 635장) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:41:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:41:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9B%85%EA%B7%A0/%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98%EC%97%90_%EA%B3%84%EC%8B%A0_-_%EC%A3%BC%EA%B8%B0%EB%8F%84%EB%AC%B8_%EC%B0%AC%EC%86%A1%EA%B0%80_635%EC%9E%A5/" title="임웅균 - 하늘에 계신 - 주기도문 (찬송가 635장) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하늘에 계신 아버지 <br>이름 거룩하사 <br>주님 나라 임하시고 뜻이 <br>이루어 지이다 <br>일용할 양식 주시고 <br>우리들의 죄를 다 용서하옵시고 <br>또 시험에 들게 마시고 <br>다만 악에서 구하소서 <br>대게 주의 나라 주의 권세 <br>주의 영광 영원히 <br>아멘 아멘 <br>]]></content><category term="임웅균" label="임웅균"/><category term="하늘에 계신 - 주기도문 (찬송가 635장)" label="하늘에 계신 - 주기도문 (찬송가 635장)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임웅균/참_아름다워라_찬송가_478장/</id><title>임웅균 - 참 아름다워라 (찬송가 478장) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:41:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:41:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9B%85%EA%B7%A0/%EC%B0%B8_%EC%95%84%EB%A6%84%EB%8B%A4%EC%9B%8C%EB%9D%BC_%EC%B0%AC%EC%86%A1%EA%B0%80_478%EC%9E%A5/" title="임웅균 - 참 아름다워라 (찬송가 478장) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[참 아름다워라 주님의 세계는 <br>저 솔로몬의 옷보다 더 고운 백합화 <br>주 찬송하는 듯 저 맑은 새소리 <br>내 아버지의 지으신 그 솜씨 깊도다 <br>참 아름다워라 주님의 세계는 <br>저 아침 해와 저녁놀 밤하늘 빛난 별 <br>망망한 바다와 늘 푸른 봉우리 <br>다 주 하나님 영광을 잘 드러내도다 <br>참 아름다워라 주님의 세계는 <br>저 산에 부는 바람과 잔잔한 시냇물 <br>그 소리 가운데 주 음성 들리니 <br>주 하나님의 큰 뜻을 나 알 듯 하도다 <br>주 찬송하는 듯 저 맑은 새소리 <br>내 아버지의 지으신 그 솜씨 깊도다 <br>그 솜씨 깊도다 <br>아멘 <br>]]></content><category term="임웅균" label="임웅균"/><category term="참 아름다워라 (찬송가 478장)" label="참 아름다워라 (찬송가 478장)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임웅균/성자의_귀한_몸_찬송가_216장/</id><title>임웅균 - 성자의 귀한 몸 (찬송가 216장) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:41:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:41:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9B%85%EA%B7%A0/%EC%84%B1%EC%9E%90%EC%9D%98_%EA%B7%80%ED%95%9C_%EB%AA%B8_%EC%B0%AC%EC%86%A1%EA%B0%80_216%EC%9E%A5/" title="임웅균 - 성자의 귀한 몸 (찬송가 216장) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[성자의 귀한 몸 날 위하여 <br>버리신 그 사랑 고마워라 <br>내 머리 숙여서 주님께 비는 말 <br>나 무엇 주님께 바치리까 <br>지금도 날 위해 간구하심 <br>이 옅은 믿음이 아옵나니 <br>주님의 참 사랑 고맙고 놀라워 <br>찬송과 기도를 쉬지 않네 <br>내 머리 숙여서 주님께 비는 말 <br>나 무엇 주님께 바치리까 <br>]]></content><category term="임웅균" label="임웅균"/><category term="성자의 귀한 몸 (찬송가 216장)" label="성자의 귀한 몸 (찬송가 216장)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임웅균/샤론의_꽃_예수_찬송가_89장/</id><title>임웅균 - 샤론의 꽃 예수 (찬송가 89장) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:42:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:42:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9B%85%EA%B7%A0/%EC%83%A4%EB%A1%A0%EC%9D%98_%EA%BD%83_%EC%98%88%EC%88%98_%EC%B0%AC%EC%86%A1%EA%B0%80_89%EC%9E%A5/" title="임웅균 - 샤론의 꽃 예수 (찬송가 89장) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[샤론의 꽃 예수 나의 마음에 <br>거룩하고 아름답게 피소서 <br>내 생명이 참 사랑의 향기로 <br>간 데마다 풍겨나게 하소서 <br>예수 샤론의 꽃 <br>나의 맘에 사랑으로 피소서 <br>샤론의 꽃 예수 이 세상에서 <br>어느 꽃과 비교할 수 있으랴 <br>나의 삶에 한결같은 은혜와 <br>사랑으로 가득 차게 하소서 <br>예수 샤론의 꽃 <br>나의 맘에 사랑으로 피소서 <br>샤론의 꽃 예수 모든 질병을 <br>한이 없는 능력으로 고치사 <br>고통하며 근심하는 자에게 <br>크신 힘과 소망 내려주소서 <br>예수 샤론의 꽃 <br>나의 맘에 사랑으로 피소서 <br>예수 샤론의 꽃 <br>나의 맘에 사랑으로 피소서 <br>]]></content><category term="임웅균" label="임웅균"/><category term="샤론의 꽃 예수 (찬송가 89장)" label="샤론의 꽃 예수 (찬송가 89장)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임웅균/마귀들과_싸울지라_찬송가_348장/</id><title>임웅균 - 마귀들과 싸울지라 (찬송가 348장) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:42:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:42:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9B%85%EA%B7%A0/%EB%A7%88%EA%B7%80%EB%93%A4%EA%B3%BC_%EC%8B%B8%EC%9A%B8%EC%A7%80%EB%9D%BC_%EC%B0%AC%EC%86%A1%EA%B0%80_348%EC%9E%A5/" title="임웅균 - 마귀들과 싸울지라 (찬송가 348장) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마귀들과 싸울지라 죄악 벗은 형제여 <br>담대하게 싸울지라 저기 악한적병과 <br>심판 날과 멸망의 날 <br>네가 섰는 눈 앞에 <br>곧 다가오리라 <br>영광영광 할렐루야 <br>영광영광 할렐루야 <br>영광영광 할렐루야 곧 승리하리라 <br>마귀들과 싸울지라 죄악 벗은 형제여 <br>고함치는 무리들은 흉한마귀 아닌가 <br>무섭고도 더러운 죄 모두 떨쳐버리고 <br>주 예수 붙들라 <br>영광영광 할렐루야 <br>영광영광 할렐루야 <br>영광영광 할렐루야 곧 승리하리라 <br>영광영광 할렐루야 <br>영광영광 할렐루야 <br>영광영광 할렐루야 곧 승리하리라 <br>곧 승리하리라 <br>]]></content><category term="임웅균" label="임웅균"/><category term="마귀들과 싸울지라 (찬송가 348장)" label="마귀들과 싸울지라 (찬송가 348장)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임웅균/넓은_들에_익은_곡식_찬송가_589장/</id><title>임웅균 - 넓은 들에 익은 곡식 (찬송가 589장) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:42:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:42:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9B%85%EA%B7%A0/%EB%84%93%EC%9D%80_%EB%93%A4%EC%97%90_%EC%9D%B5%EC%9D%80_%EA%B3%A1%EC%8B%9D_%EC%B0%AC%EC%86%A1%EA%B0%80_589%EC%9E%A5/" title="임웅균 - 넓은 들에 익은 곡식 (찬송가 589장) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넓은 들에 익은 곡식 <br>황금물결 뒤치며 <br>어디든지 태양빛에 <br>향기 진동 하도다 <br>무르익은 저 곡식은 <br>낫을 기다리는데 <br>때가 지나가기 전에 <br>어서 추수 합시다 <br>추수할 것 많은 때에 <br>일꾼 매우 적으니 <br>열심 있는 일꾼들을 <br>주여 보내주소서 <br>무르익은 저 곡식은 <br>낫을 기다리는데 <br>때가 지나가기 전에 <br>어서 추수 합시다 <br>먼동 틀 때 일어나서 <br>일찍 들에 나아가 <br>황혼 때가 되기까지 <br>추수하게 하소서 <br>무르익은 저 곡식은 <br>낫을 기다리는데 <br>때가 지나가기 전에 <br>어서 추수 합시다 <br>]]></content><category term="임웅균" label="임웅균"/><category term="넓은 들에 익은 곡식 (찬송가 589장)" label="넓은 들에 익은 곡식 (찬송가 589장)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임웅균/내_주님_입으신_그_옷은_찬송가_87장/</id><title>임웅균 - 내 주님 입으신 그 옷은 (찬송가 87장) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:42:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:42:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9B%85%EA%B7%A0/%EB%82%B4_%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98_%EC%9E%85%EC%9C%BC%EC%8B%A0_%EA%B7%B8_%EC%98%B7%EC%9D%80_%EC%B0%AC%EC%86%A1%EA%B0%80_87%EC%9E%A5/" title="임웅균 - 내 주님 입으신 그 옷은 (찬송가 87장) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 주님 입으신 그 옷은 <br>참 아름다워라 <br>그 향기 내 맘에 사무쳐 <br>내 기쁨 되도다 <br>시온성보다 더 찬란한 <br>저 천성 떠나서 <br>이 세상 오신 예수님 <br>참 내 구세주 <br>내 주는 쓰라린 고통을 <br>다 견디셨도다 <br>주 지신 십자가 대할 때 <br>나 눈물 흘리네 <br>시온성보다 더 찬란한 <br>저 천성 떠나서 <br>이 세상 오신 예수님 <br>참 내 구세주 <br>시온성보다 더 찬란한 <br>저 천성 떠나서 <br>이 세상 오신 예수님 <br>참 내 구세주 <br>참 내 구세주 <br>]]></content><category term="임웅균" label="임웅균"/><category term="내 주님 입으신 그 옷은 (찬송가 87장)" label="내 주님 입으신 그 옷은 (찬송가 87장)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임웅균/날_위하여_십자가의_찬송가_303장/</id><title>임웅균 - 날 위하여 십자가의 (찬송가 303장) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:42:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:42:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9B%85%EA%B7%A0/%EB%82%A0_%EC%9C%84%ED%95%98%EC%97%AC_%EC%8B%AD%EC%9E%90%EA%B0%80%EC%9D%98_%EC%B0%AC%EC%86%A1%EA%B0%80_303%EC%9E%A5/" title="임웅균 - 날 위하여 십자가의 (찬송가 303장) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날 위하여 십자가의 <br>중한고통 받으사 <br>대신 죽은 주 예수의 <br>사랑하신 은혜여 <br>보배로운 피를 흘려 <br>영영 죽을 죄에서 <br>구속함을 받은 우리 <br>어찌 찬양 안 할까 <br>예수 안에 있는 우리 <br>한량없이 즐겁고 <br>주 성령의 위로함이 <br>마음속에 차도다 <br>천국음악 소리 같은 <br>은혜로운 그 말씀 <br>끊임없이 듣는 우리 <br>어찌 찬양 안 할까 <br>이 세상의 모진풍파 <br>쉬지 않고 불어도 <br>주님 안에 보호받는 <br>우리 마음 편하다 <br>늘 깨어서 기도하고 <br>저 천국을 바라며 <br>주님만을 기다리니 <br>어찌 찬양 안 할까 <br>늘 깨어서 기도하고 <br>저 천국을 바라며 <br>주님만을 기다리니 <br>어찌 찬양 안 할까 <br>]]></content><category term="임웅균" label="임웅균"/><category term="날 위하여 십자가의 (찬송가 303장)" label="날 위하여 십자가의 (찬송가 303장)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임웅균/나_어느_곳에_있든지_찬송가_408장/</id><title>임웅균 - 나 어느 곳에 있든지 (찬송가 408장) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:42:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:42:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9B%85%EA%B7%A0/%EB%82%98_%EC%96%B4%EB%8A%90_%EA%B3%B3%EC%97%90_%EC%9E%88%EB%93%A0%EC%A7%80_%EC%B0%AC%EC%86%A1%EA%B0%80_408%EC%9E%A5/" title="임웅균 - 나 어느 곳에 있든지 (찬송가 408장) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 어느 곳에 있든지 <br>늘 맘이 편하다 <br>주 예수 주신 평안함 <br>늘 충만하도다 <br>나의 맘속이 늘 평안해 <br>나의 맘속이 늘 평안해 <br>악한 죄 파도가 많으나 <br>맘이 늘 평안해 <br>내 맘에 솟는 영생수 <br>한없이 흐르니 <br>목마름 다시 없으며 <br>늘 평안하도다 <br>나의 맘속이 늘 평안해 <br>나의 맘속이 늘 평안해 <br>악한 죄 파도가 많으나 <br>맘이 늘 평안해 <br>주 예수 온갖 고난을 <br>왜 몸소 당했나 <br>주 함께 고난 받으면 <br>면류관 얻겠네 <br>나의 맘속이 늘 평안해 <br>나의 맘속이 늘 평안해 <br>악한 죄 파도가 많으나 <br>맘이 늘 평안해 <br>]]></content><category term="임웅균" label="임웅균"/><category term="나 어느 곳에 있든지 (찬송가 408장)" label="나 어느 곳에 있든지 (찬송가 408장)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임웅균/고요한_밤_거룩한_밤_찬송가_109장/</id><title>임웅균 - 고요한 밤 거룩한 밤 (찬송가 109장) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:42:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:42:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%9B%85%EA%B7%A0/%EA%B3%A0%EC%9A%94%ED%95%9C_%EB%B0%A4_%EA%B1%B0%EB%A3%A9%ED%95%9C_%EB%B0%A4_%EC%B0%AC%EC%86%A1%EA%B0%80_109%EC%9E%A5/" title="임웅균 - 고요한 밤 거룩한 밤 (찬송가 109장) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[고요한 밤 거룩한 밤 <br>어둠에 묻힌 밤 <br>주의 부모 앉아서 <br>감사기도 드릴 때 <br>아기 잘도 잔다 <br>아기 잘도 잔다 <br>고요한 밤 거룩한 밤 <br>영광이 둘린 밤 <br>천군천사 나타나 <br>기뻐 노래 불렀네 <br>구주 나셨도다 <br>구주 나셨도다 <br>]]></content><category term="임웅균" label="임웅균"/><category term="고요한 밤 거룩한 밤 (찬송가 109장)" label="고요한 밤 거룩한 밤 (찬송가 109장)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Krayzie_Bone/Those_Kind_Of_Words/</id><title>Krayzie Bone - Those Kind Of Words - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:43:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:43:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Krayzie_Bone/Those_Kind_Of_Words/" title="Krayzie Bone - Those Kind Of Words - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We won't stop hustling until we make it X2 <br>Make it <br><br>Stop trying what never works <br>In my vocabulary <br>You won't find those kind of words <br>Do whatever necessary <br>X2 <br><br>Ever since I was young and my mother told me I can make it <br>Even though daddy told me I'm just wasting my time, the mission was blind <br>The vision is clear, I'm seeing me shine <br>I've been through many dark tunnels, I pummel myself <br>Against the flesh I'm rumbling with myself <br>To reach the top I'm stumbling to prevail <br>But at least I got my feet planted so well <br>I don't really care about the women and the fame <br>All I really care about is money in the bank <br>Hundreds are the same so I hustle everyday <br>Stay strong to the finish <br>Just another day <br>Never say never I know I can do better, you better get on my level <br>Imma stay on my criminals best <br>Never settle for minimum less <br><br>Stop trying what never works <br>In my vocabulary <br>You won't find those kind of words <br>Do whatever necessary <br>X2 <br><br>I'm on my perfect timing shit <br>24 7 the grinder shit <br>Imma survivor let me remind ya that <br>I stay on some grimy shit <br>The thug mentality's is still in me <br>I gotta get up and go get it <br>Imma go get it <br>Imma be ready <br>I'm thinking wicked <br>Cause I'm thinking money mane <br>Strictly money mane <br>It's rough in the hood <br>Keep pushing, it'll never be enough in the hood <br>So we stuck in the hood <br>That's why nobody give a fuck in the hood <br>Always tough luck in the hood <br>So we posted on the block only option hustle your ass off <br>I was dealt a bad hand but I made good with bad cards <br><br>Stop trying what never works <br>In my vocabulary <br>You won't find those kind of words <br>Do whatever necessary <br>X2 <br><br>We hustle hard go hard <br>Go hard all night go hard <br>X4 <br><br>So still I grind everyday <br>Until I rise, I'll be hustling hustling hustling hustling hustling hard <br><br>Stop trying what never works <br>In my vocabulary <br>You won't find those kind of words <br>Do whatever necessary <br>X2 <br><br>We won't stop hustling until we make it X2 <br>Make it <br><br>We won't stop hustling until we make it X2 <br>Make it]]></content><category term="Krayzie Bone" label="Krayzie Bone"/><category term="Those Kind Of Words" label="Those Kind Of Words"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Krayzie_Bone/Let_Me_Learn/</id><title>Krayzie Bone - Let Me Learn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:43:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:43:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Krayzie_Bone/Let_Me_Learn/" title="Krayzie Bone - Let Me Learn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let me learn, let me learn, let me learn <br>Let me learn, let me learn <br>Let me learn, let me learn, let me learn <br>Let me learn, let me learn <br>Just let me live and learn <br>'Cause I like to earn my life <br>Just let me live and learn <br>'Cause I like to earn my life <br><br>Look, I don't know too much <br>A lot of people used to tell me that I hope too much <br>My family they seem to think I drink and smoke too much <br>They know I'm goin' through it tough but I don't show too much <br>I'm livin' life and I'm learnin' from all the experience that has been given to me <br>Now I see how it be really inside of the industry <br>Friends turned to frenemies, then straight up enemies <br>Ain't nobody feelin' me, that's how it really be <br>Lessons I've learned, blessings I've earned, I can clearly see it <br>And I can feel it, it's real and I live it <br>To keep it true its really often times <br>I get confused and kinda lost in the mind <br>Maintain, tryna stay sane <br>It's an exhaustin' grind <br>But I maintain <br><br>Just let me live and learn <br>'Cause I like to earn my life <br>Just let me live and learn <br>'Cause I like to earn my life <br><br>I just wanna make it to the other side <br>And scrape along to the other life <br>Take away the darkness, hardness, feelin' got me nauseous <br>I remember feelin' when my mother died <br>You never know, you could be here one day and then the next day you're gone <br>I gotta get it together, I had to learn <br>Life lessons, I graduated to a much higher class <br>Try myself traveling down a much brighter path <br>Let the sun shine in just a little bit <br>And let us redefine me on some other shit <br>See I was sent here for a purpose, for a reason <br>When God is done with me on Earth, that's when I'm leavin' <br>So I continue learnin', everythin' concern me <br>My family, my future, the movement <br>The tuners, the rulers of it all <br>So every day I'm alive, I celebrate the hella crazy, I defeated my odds <br>Ain't it crazy <br>Jump inside and see my side, it was crazy <br>If you don't focus you'll go crazy <br>Head on your shoulders or you go crazy <br>I've watched them go crazy <br><br>Just let me live and learn <br>'Cause I like to earn my life <br>Just let me live and learn <br>'Cause I like to earn my life]]></content><category term="Krayzie Bone" label="Krayzie Bone"/><category term="Let Me Learn" label="Let Me Learn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Krayzie_Bone/This_Is_Real_Life/</id><title>Krayzie Bone - This Is Real Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:43:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:43:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Krayzie_Bone/This_Is_Real_Life/" title="Krayzie Bone - This Is Real Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hold up, roll that dough <br>Split that swisher, smoke that dro <br>Pour that liquor, watch that hoe <br>Keep my pistol cocked and close <br>What they want I don't know <br>Lots of foes, they plot my dough <br>They plot to slow, I stop, oh no <br>I pop my chrome up on po po <br>Hit the ground, go <br>I'm the chosen one <br>Won't stop, impossible <br>Lots of flow <br>Bring me lot's of dough <br>No more obstacles <br>I suppose <br>Ya'll think I'm supposed to let ya'll stop my show <br>Tryna block my dough <br>You're gonna keep tryin' to cop my soul <br>Let em' know it won't be sold <br><br>Still ain't nothin' changed <br>Bone ain't never changed <br>We do this everyday <br>Not for Fame, not for play <br>This is real life <br>X2 <br><br>A lot niggas hang around but I really don't need em' <br>Don't need security either, that's why I keep a heater <br>Ride up on me if you want to <br>And you gon' see that I'm the wrong dude, fuckin' with the wrong crew <br>Nigga better ask somebody, what happened to the last somebody <br>They thought he was gonna rest somebody <br>Don't make me have to blast somebody <br>Leave you in a body bag, nothin' bout it <br>Shotgun got em', drop em' <br>We ain't worried about it <br>Nigga better lay on off of my shit <br>Bitches better stay on off of my dick, for real <br>Cause Kray ain't soft and I'm lit <br>Everybody say that they the king of the game <br>How many niggas can reign at one time <br>So stay, they frontline <br>You niggas all self proclaimed <br>You suckas so damn lame, don't even get in my lane, lane <br><br>Still ain't nothin' changed <br>Bone ain't never changed <br>We do this everyday <br>Not for Fame, not for play <br>This is real life <br>X2 <br><br>One verse will leave a nigga dead, so a third verse is overkill <br>Nigga I'm so for real, so em' my soldier skills <br>Figured they know the deal <br>Who the fuck over here Still at the top <br>Nigga got older but I only got better <br>I done got so cold I write my rhymes in a sweater <br>You're doin' it for the throne, negative, that's a never <br>We rollin' with Bone, run and tell, that's forever <br>If I gotta hit a nigga, I'ma hit em' cause before I be the victim I'ma make sure they know Krayzie Bone official never artificial any nigga got a issue with it, nigga better split it <br>They can come and get it <br>Don't no body move don't won't nobody get hurt, hurt <br>If you be fuckin' with meeeeee <br>You get murked, murked <br><br>Still ain't nothin' changed <br>Bone ain't never changed <br>We do this everyday <br>Not for Fame, not for play <br>This is real life <br>X2 <br><br>Reeeeeeal what you see <br>It's all reeeeeeal, It's just the thug in me <br>Real <br><br>Still ain't nothin' changed <br>Bone ain't never changed <br>We do this everyday <br>Not for Fame, not for play <br>This is real life <br>X2]]></content><category term="Krayzie Bone" label="Krayzie Bone"/><category term="This Is Real Life" label="This Is Real Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Krayzie_Bone/Make_You_Wanna_Get_High/</id><title>Krayzie Bone - Make You Wanna Get High - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:43:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:43:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Krayzie_Bone/Make_You_Wanna_Get_High/" title="Krayzie Bone - Make You Wanna Get High - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was always told that I had skill <br>And I always known that I had it ill <br>So when I met Bone, the shit got real <br>Now it's been known for 20 somethin years <br>That <br><br>Kray got, the fire that gon' make you wanna smoke and get high <br>Kray got, style that so versatile that make you wanna smoke and get high <br><br>I've been zonin in my time <br>All my lonely in my mind <br>I'm like one of the only ones you'll find <br>That truly really knows how to flip it em' with the rhyme <br>That's cause <br><br>Kray got, the fire that gon' make you wanna smoke and get high <br>Kray got, style that so versatile that make you wanna smoke and get high <br><br>Gotta different kind of sound <br>That's a classic kind of swag <br>No gimmicks, only style <br>Way more massive than the fad <br>No limits can be found in me <br>Ask me course, just ask <br>Just I'm the realist around <br>Not to brag but its just fact <br>That <br><br>Kray got, the fire that gon make you wanna smoke and get high <br>Kray got, style that so versatile that make you wanna smoke and get high <br><br>They say we old timers <br>But the shit seems odd <br>We manage to do the job <br>That's cause this team squad <br>It ain't no competition for me <br>This means all, of y'all <br>I made this with my 16 bars <br>They know <br><br>Kray got, the fire that gon' make you wanna smoke and get high <br>Kray got, style that so versatile that make you wanna smoke and get high <br><br>True artist niggas calling Krayzie Picasso <br>Off the charts with the artistry <br>Sick with the high flow <br>From the start, from the heart <br>So why would I not grow <br>From the dark into a spark <br>These niggas do not know <br><br>Kray got, the fire that gon' make you wanna smoke and get high <br>Kray got, style that so versatile that make you wanna smoke and get high <br><br>We something like implanted in the game <br>And that'll never change <br>Bone tat em' on the brain <br>So we forever remain <br>Of course we on a lane <br>And we can never be tamed <br>We sit back and do our thang <br>While we blaze <br>Flames <br><br>Kray got, the fire that gon' make you wanna smoke and get high <br>Kray got, style that so versatile that make you wanna smoke and get high <br><br>Forever will I reign <br>Forever on the throne <br>Forever I be Kray <br>On the stage, in my zone <br>Cause the stage is my home <br>No place like home <br>You can look but you will never find niggas like Bone, boooone <br><br>Kray got, the fire that gon' make you wanna smoke and get high <br>Kray got, style that so versatile that make you wanna smoke and get high <br><br>It's all original <br>Coming from the Cleveland criminal <br>It's all original <br>Coming from the Cleveland criminal <br><br>Kray got, the fire that gon' make you wanna smoke and get high <br>Kray got, style that so versatile that make you wanna smoke and get high <br><br>Got that fire, fire baby <br>Keep that fire, fire baby <br>Got that fire, fire baby <br>Keep that fire, fire baby <br>They say <br><br>Kray got, the fire that gon' make you wanna smoke and get high <br>Kray got, style that so versatile that make you wanna smoke and get high]]></content><category term="Krayzie Bone" label="Krayzie Bone"/><category term="Make You Wanna Get High" label="Make You Wanna Get High"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리노_쿠_Rino_Ku/먼미래의_나에게_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>리노 쿠 (Rino Ku) - 먼미래의 나에게 (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:43:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:43:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%85%B8_%EC%BF%A0_Rino_Ku/%EB%A8%BC%EB%AF%B8%EB%9E%98%EC%9D%98_%EB%82%98%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_Acoustic_Ver/" title="리노 쿠 (Rino Ku) - 먼미래의 나에게 (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오랫동안 기다려 왔네 <br>이 순간을 기다려 <br>누가 뭐래도 <br>걸어서 왔어 <br>이 길을 이순간 <br>언제나 쉽진 않았지만 <br>그저 내 길을 왔을 뿐 <br>먼 미래의 나에게 <br>부끄럽지 않고 싶어 <br>오랜 후에 너에게 <br>당당하고 싶어 <br>많은 시간 지나서 왔네 <br>이날들을 꿈꾸며 <br>항상 언제나 찾아서 왔네 <br>여기를 오늘에 <br>언제나 쉽진 않았지만 <br>그저 내 길을 왔을 뿐 <br>먼 미래의 나에게 <br>부끄럽지 않고 싶어 <br>오랜 후에 너에게 <br>당당하고 싶어 <br>먼 미래의 나에게 <br>부끄럽지 않고 싶어 <br>오랜 후에 너에게 <br>당당하고 싶어 <br>먼 미래의 나에게 <br>부끄럽지 않고 싶어 <br>오랜 후에 너에게 <br>당당하고 싶어 <br>먼 미래의 나에게 <br>부끄럽지 않고 싶어 <br>부끄럽지 않고 싶어 <br>]]></content><category term="리노 쿠 (Rino Ku)" label="리노 쿠 (Rino Ku)"/><category term="먼미래의 나에게 (Acoustic Ver.)" label="먼미래의 나에게 (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/David_Cook/Gimme_Heartbreak/</id><title>David Cook - Gimme Heartbreak - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:43:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:43:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/David_Cook/Gimme_Heartbreak/" title="David Cook - Gimme Heartbreak - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm high on the neon <br>Chasing the greens, the blues, the reds <br>I keep touching the ceiling <br>But my feelings, they fall for you, instead <br>You're death in a black dress <br>I'm the puppet that's hanging from your thread <br>You're the name of my madness <br>I don't want to get you out of my head <br><br>Gimme the heartbreak <br>Gimme the heartbreak <br>Bring on the hurt, put in the work <br>Baby don't try to fight it <br>Tell me you want me <br>While you push and you shove me <br>You're pulling me close it's getting out of control <br>And you know that I like it <br><br>It's an instant reaction <br>You're like the drug inside my vein <br>Another welcome distraction <br>One more shot of Novocaine <br>You're death in a black dress <br>I'm the puppet that's hanging from your string <br>You're my favorite madness <br>No, I don't want to change a thing <br><br>Gimme the heartbreak <br>Gimme the heartbreak <br>Bring on the hurt, put in the work <br>Baby don't try to fight it <br>Tell me you want me <br>While you push and you shove me <br>You're pulling me close it's getting out of control <br>And you know that I like it <br><br>Gimme the heartbreak <br>Baby, don't try to fight it <br>Gimme the heartbreak <br>Cause you know that I like it <br>Gimme the heartbreak <br>Baby, don't try to fight it <br>Gimme the heartbreak <br>Cause you know that I like it <br><br>Gimme the heartbreak <br>Gimme the heartbreak <br>Bring on the hurt, put in the work <br>Baby don't try to fight it <br>Tell me you want me <br>While you push and you shove me <br>You're pulling me close it's getting out of control <br>And you know that I like it]]></content><category term="David Cook" label="David Cook"/><category term="Gimme Heartbreak" label="Gimme Heartbreak"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/다로_DLOVE/타임머신_Feat_달리_of_마멀레이드_키친/</id><title>다로 (D.LOVE) - 타임머신 (Feat. 달리 of 마멀레이드 키친) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:43:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:43:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EB%A1%9C_DLOVE/%ED%83%80%EC%9E%84%EB%A8%B8%EC%8B%A0_Feat_%EB%8B%AC%EB%A6%AC_of_%EB%A7%88%EB%A9%80%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%93%9C_%ED%82%A4%EC%B9%9C/" title="다로 (D.LOVE) - 타임머신 (Feat. 달리 of 마멀레이드 키친) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리의 연애는 <br>남들이 하는 연애가 아냐 <br>싫어할 수도 좋아할 수도 없는 <br>필름처럼 지나가는 <br>하나의 영화 같은 거지 <br>우리가 원하는 <br>사랑이야기는 말야 <br>남들처럼 좋아만 하고 싶은데 <br>그게 뜻대로 안 돼서 <br>오늘 또 고민할 거야 <br>오늘은 더 일부러 너를 만나서 <br>내일을 위한 노래를 꾸며볼 거야 <br>한때는 달달한 시간이었다고 <br>잠깐 타임머신 타고 <br>돌아가볼 거라고 <br>너와의 사랑은 <br>후회하고 싶지 않아 <br>짜증내고 많이 다퉜더라도 <br>그때 그 시간만큼은 <br>우리의 진심이었으니까 <br>이 다음에 우리가 <br>다시 만날 수 있다면 <br>서로에게 더 좋은 사람이 돼서 <br>그땐 남부럽지 않은 <br>예쁜 사랑을 할 수 있겠지 <br>오늘은 더 일부러 너를 만나서 <br>내일을 위한 노래를 꾸며볼 거야 <br>한때는 달달한 시간이었다고 <br>잠깐 타임머신 타고 <br>돌아가볼 거라고 <br>다시 만나는 그날 <br>너와의 추억을 떠올리겠지 <br>우리가 다시 만난 그날엔 <br>우리 믿음이 통했던 거야 <br>오늘은 더 서로를 사랑해주고 <br>우리를 위한 미래를 그려볼 거야 <br>한때는 아팠던 시간이었지만 <br>그때 너로 인해 <br>우리가 이뤄진 거라고 <br>]]></content><category term="다로 (D.LOVE)" label="다로 (D.LOVE)"/><category term="타임머신 (Feat. 달리 of 마멀레이드 키친)" label="타임머신 (Feat. 달리 of 마멀레이드 키친)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/빌리/한순간이야_Piano_Ver/</id><title>빌리 - 한순간이야 (Piano Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:44:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:44:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%8C%EB%A6%AC/%ED%95%9C%EC%88%9C%EA%B0%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC_Piano_Ver/" title="빌리 - 한순간이야 (Piano Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아침을 깨우는 네 연락이 <br>이젠 부담이 되고 <br>어떻게 이별해야 할지 <br>자주 상상을 해 <br>언제부터 시작된 걸까 <br>그렇게 사랑했는데 <br>나 몰래 찾아온 사랑처럼 <br>이별만 떠오르게 돼 <br>다 한순간이야 <br>그 설레임처럼 <br>이별의 시작도 <br>함께한 시간을 잊은 듯 <br>조용히 다가오는 걸 <br>정말 다 한순간이야 <br>참 사랑했는데 <br>그 모든 흔적들이 <br>조금의 망설임조차 <br>내게 줄 수 없다는 게 슬프다 <br>널 처음 사랑할 때처럼 <br>이별을 향한 마음들이 <br>붙잡을 수도 없을 만큼 <br>자꾸만 커져가는 걸 <br>정말 다 한순간이야 <br>그 설레임처럼 <br>이별의 시작도 <br>함께한 시간을 잊은 듯 <br>조용히 다가오는 걸 <br>정말 다 한순간이야 <br>참 사랑했는데 <br>그 모든 흔적들이 <br>조금의 망설임조차 <br>내게 줄 수 없다는 게 <br>다 한순간이야 <br>누군가 만나고 <br>이별하는 일 너여야만 했었던 <br>나를 더는 찾을 수 없어 <br>너에게 전하려고 해 <br>참 아프겠지만 <br>이제는 이별만이 <br>더 좋은 만남을 위한 <br>우리 서로를 위한 일인걸 <br>]]></content><category term="빌리" label="빌리"/><category term="한순간이야 (Piano Ver.)" label="한순간이야 (Piano Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/빌리/한순간이야/</id><title>빌리 - 한순간이야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:44:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:44:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%8C%EB%A6%AC/%ED%95%9C%EC%88%9C%EA%B0%84%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC/" title="빌리 - 한순간이야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아침을 깨우는 네 연락이 <br>이젠 부담이 되고 <br>어떻게 이별해야 할지 <br>자주 상상을 해 <br>언제부터 시작된 걸까 <br>그렇게 사랑했는데 <br>나 몰래 찾아온 사랑처럼 <br>이별만 떠오르게 돼 <br>정말 다 한 순간이야 <br>그 설레임처럼 <br>이별의 시작도 <br>함께한 시간을 잊은 듯 <br>조용히 다가오는 걸 <br>정말 다 한 순간이야 <br>참 사랑했는데 <br>그 모든 흔적들이 <br>조금의 망설임조차 <br>내게 줄 수 없다는 게 슬프다 <br>널 처음 사랑할 때처럼 <br>이별을 향한 마음들이 <br>붙잡을 수도 없을 만큼 <br>자꾸만 커져가는 걸 <br>정말 다 한 순간이야 <br>그 설레임처럼 <br>이별의 시작도 <br>함께한 시간을 잊은 듯 <br>조용히 다가오는 걸 <br>정말 다 한 순간이야 <br>참 사랑했는데 <br>그 모든 흔적들이 <br>조금의 망설임조차 <br>내게 줄 수 없다는 게 <br>다 한 순간이야 <br>누군가 만나고 이별하는 일 <br>너여야만 했었던 나를 <br>더는 찾을 수 없어 <br>너에게 전하려고 해 <br>참 아프겠지만 <br>이제는 이별만이 <br>더 좋은 만남을 위한 <br>우리 서로를 위한 일인걸 <br>]]></content><category term="빌리" label="빌리"/><category term="한순간이야" label="한순간이야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유자/떠난_당신/</id><title>유자 - 떠난 당신 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:44:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:44:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EC%9E%90/%EB%96%A0%EB%82%9C_%EB%8B%B9%EC%8B%A0/" title="유자 - 떠난 당신 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너만을 사랑했다 <br>진정코 사랑했었다 <br>순정을 다 바쳐서 <br>죽도록 사랑했었다 <br>나에겐 너밖에 <br>너밖에 몰랐다 <br>내 모든걸 다 바쳐서 <br>사랑했었다 <br>영원토록 변치말자 <br>맹세해 놓고 <br>말도 없이 떠난 당신 <br>내 곁을 떠난 당신 <br>내 모든걸 다 바쳐서 <br>너만을 사랑했었다 <br>나에겐 너밖에 <br>너밖에 몰랐다 <br>내 모든걸 다 바쳐서 <br>사랑했었다 <br>영원토록 변치말자 <br>맹세해 놓고 <br>말도 없이 떠난 당신 <br>내 곁을 떠난 당신 <br>내 순정을 다 바쳐서 <br>너만을 사랑했었다 <br>]]></content><category term="유자" label="유자"/><category term="떠난 당신" label="떠난 당신"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리노_쿠_Rino_Ku/남아_있더라/</id><title>리노 쿠 (Rino Ku) - 남아 있더라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:45:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:45:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%85%B8_%EC%BF%A0_Rino_Ku/%EB%82%A8%EC%95%84_%EC%9E%88%EB%8D%94%EB%9D%BC/" title="리노 쿠 (Rino Ku) - 남아 있더라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람이 불어와 <br>내마음 스치고 <br>이언덕 너머엔 <br>너는 날 기다리고 <br>있을까 <br>행복한 표정의 너와 <br>오래된 추억만이 내겐 <br>남아 있더라 <br>사랑이 불어와 <br>내콧등 만지고 <br>이순간 너머엔 <br>나는 널 기억하고 <br>있을까 <br>상쾌한 향기의 너와 <br>변치않은 우리만의 <br>공간이 <br>남아 있더라 <br>이언덕 너머엔 <br>너는 날 기다리고 <br>있을까 <br>행복한 표정의 너와 <br>오래된 추억만이 내겐 <br>상쾌한 향기의 너와 <br>변치않은 우리만의 <br>공간이 <br>남아 있더라 <br>행복한 표정의 너와 <br>오래된 추억만이 내겐 <br>남아 있더라 <br>상쾌한 향기의 너와 <br>변치않은 우리만의 <br>공간이 <br>남아 있더라 <br>]]></content><category term="리노 쿠 (Rino Ku)" label="리노 쿠 (Rino Ku)"/><category term="남아 있더라" label="남아 있더라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Magnettes/So_Bad/</id><title>The Magnettes - So Bad - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:45:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:45:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Magnettes/So_Bad/" title="The Magnettes - So Bad - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We've been having some problems with the girls <br>They're not listening <br>They cuss, they smoke in the restrooms <br>For girls, this is just outrageous <br>Girls are supposed to behave better than this <br>There's no use in starting a riot <br><br>My mama told me not to go <br>But I'm not used to saying no <br>To parties, to your kiss, to any invitation <br>And we get shit faced once again <br>'Cause I'm not used to thinking straight <br>At parties, when we kiss, whenever <br><br>'Cause we're so bad <br>I chew you up, I spit you out, so bad <br>I full you up, I pour you out <br>Like tasty, twisted lullaby <br>Knocks us out every night, so bad <br>And we're so bad <br><br>When they're walking around in short skirts and stockings <br>It's easy to understand that the boys can't handle themselves <br>After all, boys will be boys <br><br>My papa told you not to come <br>He'll be awake when I'll get home <br>Stone faced, in silence <br>Then the investigations <br>I guess they've let me out <br>The twisted sister of the house <br>To parties, to your kiss, whatever <br><br>'Cause we're so bad <br>I chew you up, I spit you out, so bad <br>I full you up, I pour you out <br>Like tasty, twisted lullaby <br>Knocks us out every night, so bad <br>And we're so bad <br><br>So tell me I'm the best you've ever had <br>Had, had, had <br>So tell me I'm the best you've ever had <br>Had, had, had]]></content><category term="The Magnettes" label="The Magnettes"/><category term="So Bad" label="So Bad"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Magnettes/Killers_In_A_Ghost_Town/</id><title>The Magnettes - Killers In A Ghost Town - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:45:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:45:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Magnettes/Killers_In_A_Ghost_Town/" title="The Magnettes - Killers In A Ghost Town - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's a ghost town, always nasty weather <br>Let's be best friends, be alone together <br>And grow up on, Bikini Kill and Back In Black <br><br>You can hold my hand <br>When we walk to school <br>We can let them talk and believe they're cool <br>Spit them in the eye <br>Get high on the fuel <br>Cut right to the bone <br>Leave an open wound <br><br>Sweet little girls, we just wanna fight <br>Make faces, get wasted and fuck around <br>Take on the world for just one night <br>We're killers in a ghost town <br><br>Make 'em thirsty, put something in the water <br>Let's try new clothes, it's a sultry slaughter <br>Let's get drunk to <br>Bikini Kill and Back in Black <br><br>Sweet little girls, we just wanna fight <br>Make faces, get wasted and fuck around <br>Stars in disguise for just one night <br>We're killers in a ghost town <br><br>All I wanna say is <br>All I wanna say is <br>Turpa kiinni minun haters <br><br>Sweet little girls, we just wanna fight <br>Make faces, get wasted and fuck around <br>I'd rather be wrong if they're right <br>We're killers in a ghost town]]></content><category term="The Magnettes" label="The Magnettes"/><category term="Killers In A Ghost Town" label="Killers In A Ghost Town"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DMEANOR_디미너/Dont_Hold_Me_Feat_Swings/</id><title>DMEANOR (디미너) - Don`t Hold Me (Feat. Swings) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:49:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:49:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DMEANOR_%EB%94%94%EB%AF%B8%EB%84%88/Dont_Hold_Me_Feat_Swings/" title="DMEANOR (디미너) - Don`t Hold Me (Feat. Swings) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 따라 바빠진 날이 <br>크게 싫진 않아 싫진 않아 <br>이런저런 생각은 지금 <br>중요하지 않아 중요하지 않아 <br>Let me get that <br>uh yeah yeah yeah <br>uh yeah yeah yeah <br>내게 말해줘 <br>어디로 갈지 어디가 좋은지 <br>Let me get that <br>uh yeah yeah yeah <br>uh yeah yeah yeah <br>나만 느끼는 느낌인 건지 <br>뭘 하고 싶은 건지 나도 몰라 <br>지금 내 맘이 붕 뜬 내 맘이 <br>요즘 나도 내가 왜 이런지 몰라 <br>지금 내 맘이 붕 뜬 내 맘이 <br>Baby don't hold me back <br>bae hold me back <br>기분대로 내버려 둬 <br>Baby don't hold me back <br>bae hold me back <br>기분대로 내버려 둬 <br>The homies back <br>can't hold me back <br>내 길을 가다 보니 <br>조금 lonely 해 <br>바닷물 같은 삶 <br>얼지도 않고 안 멈춰 <br>내가 뭐가 싫은지는 <br>모른 적이 없어 <br>so I just 앞으로만 갈 뿐 <br>누가 무얼 하든 <br>난 그저 내 것만 하고 <br>포기하는 사람만을 <br>loser라고 불러 <br>모난 건 깎고 <br>너도 공처럼 굴러 <br>Let me get that <br>uh yeah yeah yeah <br>uh yeah yeah yeah <br>내게 말해줘 <br>어디로 갈지 어디가 좋은지 <br>Let me get that <br>uh yeah yeah yeah <br>uh yeah yeah yeah <br>나만 느끼는 느낌인 건지 <br>뭘 하고 싶은 건지 나도 몰라 <br>지금 내 맘이 붕 뜬 내 맘이 <br>요즘 나도 내가 왜 이런지 몰라 <br>지금 내 맘이 붕 뜬 내 맘이 <br>Baby don't hold me back <br>bae hold me back <br>기분대로 내버려 둬 <br>Baby don't hold me back <br>bae hold me back <br>기분대로 내버려 둬 <br>내 맘은 내가 어른인 것 같은데 <br>아직까지 나도 어리기만 해 <br>잘 버텨왔지만 <br>뭘 하고 싶은 건지 나도 몰라 <br>지금 내 맘이 붕 뜬 내 맘이 <br>요즘 나도 내가 왜 이런지 몰라 <br>지금 내 맘이 붕 뜬 내 맘이 <br>Baby don't hold me back <br>bae hold me back <br>기분대로 내버려 둬 <br>Baby don't hold me back <br>bae hold me back <br>기분대로 내버려 둬 <br>]]></content><category term="DMEANOR (디미너)" label="DMEANOR (디미너)"/><category term="Don`t Hold Me (Feat. Swings)" label="Don`t Hold Me (Feat. Swings)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김연정/영광이_성부와/</id><title>김연정 - 영광이 성부와 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:49:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:49:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%97%B0%EC%A0%95/%EC%98%81%EA%B4%91%EC%9D%B4_%EC%84%B1%EB%B6%80%EC%99%80/" title="김연정 - 영광이 성부와 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[영광이 성부와 성자와 성령께 <br>처음과 같이 이제와 항상 영원히 아멘 <br><br>영광이 성부와 성자와 성령께 <br>처음과 같이 이제와 항상 영원히 아멘 <br><br>주님께 감사를 주님께 찬양을 <br>주님께 영광을 모두 드리옵니다 <br><br>주님께 감사를 주님께 찬양을 <br>주님께 영광을 모두 드리옵니다 <br><br>주님께 감사를 주님께 찬양을 <br>주님께 영광을 모두 드리옵니다 <br><br>주님께 감사를 주님께 찬양을 <br>주님께 영광을 모두 드리옵니다 <br><br>아멘]]></content><category term="김연정" label="김연정"/><category term="영광이 성부와" label="영광이 성부와"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합/카톨릭성가_메들리/</id><title>한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합 - 카톨릭성가 메들리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:49:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:49:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EA%B5%AD%EA%B0%80%ED%86%A8%EB%A6%AD%EC%A0%8A%EC%9D%80%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9%EC%87%84%EC%8B%A0%EC%97%B0%ED%95%A9/%EC%B9%B4%ED%86%A8%EB%A6%AD%EC%84%B1%EA%B0%80_%EB%A9%94%EB%93%A4%EB%A6%AC/" title="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합 - 카톨릭성가 메들리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[얼마나 위대한 선물인가 우리에게 주신 사랑 <br>마음을 열고서 우리 주님 찬미의 노래하자 <br><br>온 세상이 잠든 밤 고요함이 깔릴 때 주의 말씀이 내리고 <br>주 천사들이 마리아에게 나타나 전하였네 위대한 선물이여 <br><br>오 석양에 방울지던 선혈 선혈 선혈 <br>보았나 메달리신 주님을 <br><br>가난한 이들에게 기쁜 소식 갇힌 이들에게 자유를 <br>장님에게 밝음을 묶인 이를 풀어줄 <br><br>그 일을 맡았네 주님 왕국 왔다고 전하자 <br>모두에게 전하자 주님 왕국 와있도다 <br><br>주님 왕국 와있도다]]></content><category term="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합" label="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합"/><category term="카톨릭성가 메들리" label="카톨릭성가 메들리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합/아도라레_Adorare/</id><title>한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합 - 아도라레 (Adorare) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:49:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:49:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EA%B5%AD%EA%B0%80%ED%86%A8%EB%A6%AD%EC%A0%8A%EC%9D%80%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9%EC%87%84%EC%8B%A0%EC%97%B0%ED%95%A9/%EC%95%84%EB%8F%84%EB%9D%BC%EB%A0%88_Adorare/" title="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합 - 아도라레 (Adorare) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 맘의 사랑이시여 내 생각 만지어 불안한 나의 삶 잠잠히 하소서 <br>하느님 나를 반기어 머물게 하시니 나 주님 안에서 새로워지네 <br><br>아도라레 성령이시여 영원한 사랑의 불꽃 날 쉬게하네 <br>아도라레 성령이시여 영원한 사랑의 불꽃 날 쉬게하네 <br><br>주님을 바라볼 때에 흐르는 눈물 <br>길 잃은 어린양 돌아가길 원해 <br><br>사랑에 목마른 영혼 주 그리워하니 <br>간절한 이 찬양 받아주소서 <br><br>주님을 바라볼 때에 흐르는 눈물 <br>길 잃은 어린양 돌아가길 원해 <br><br>사랑에 목마른 영혼 주 그리워하니 <br>간절한 이 찬양 받아주소서 <br><br>아도라레 성령이시여 영원한 사랑의 불꽃 날 쉬게 하네 <br>아도라레 성령이시여 영원한 사랑의 불꽃 날 쉬게 하네 <br><br>아도라레 성령이시여 영원한 사랑의 불꽃 날 쉬게 하네 <br>아도라레 성령이시여 영원한 사랑의 불꽃 날 쉬게 하네 <br><br>영원한 사랑의 불꽃 날 쉬게 하네]]></content><category term="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합" label="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합"/><category term="아도라레 (Adorare)" label="아도라레 (Adorare)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김도우/주_자비하심/</id><title>김도우 - 주 자비하심 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:49:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:49:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%8F%84%EC%9A%B0/%EC%A3%BC_%EC%9E%90%EB%B9%84%ED%95%98%EC%8B%AC/" title="김도우 - 주 자비하심 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주 자비하심 멈추지 마소서 이 땅위에 늘 임하소서 <br>아파하는 신음하는 영혼들을 위해 일하소서 <br><br>주 자비하심 의탁할 때에 우리 구원이 시작되니 <br>주 창조하신 모든 만물 주 은혜로 이끄소서 <br><br>주의 자비 베푸소서 모든 능력 펼치소서 <br>전능하신 위대하신 주의 영광이 온 세상 가득하도록 <br><br>들어주소서 우리 기도 모든 눈물 드리오니 <br>거룩하신 영원하신 주의 영광을 온 세상 보게 하소서 <br><br>주의 자비 베푸소서 모든 능력 펼치소서 <br>전능하신 위대하신 주의 영광이 온 세상 가득하도록 <br><br>들어주소서 우리 기도 모든 눈물 드리오니 <br>거룩하신 영원하신 주의 영광을 온 세상 보게 하소서 <br><br>들어주소서 우리 기도 모든 눈물 드리오니 <br>거룩하신 영원하신 주의 영광을 온 세상 보게 하소서 <br><br>들어주소서 우리 기도 모든 눈물 드리오니 <br>거룩하신 영원하신 주의 영광을 온 세상 보게 하소서 <br><br>주여]]></content><category term="김도우" label="김도우"/><category term="주 자비하심" label="주 자비하심"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김병곤/평화를_주소서/</id><title>김병곤 - 평화를 주소서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:49:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:49:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%B3%91%EA%B3%A4/%ED%8F%89%ED%99%94%EB%A5%BC_%EC%A3%BC%EC%86%8C%EC%84%9C/" title="김병곤 - 평화를 주소서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아버지 우리에게 평화를 주소서 <br>아버지 우리에게 사랑을 주소서 <br><br>아버지 우리에게 평화를 주소서 <br>아버지 우리에게 사랑을 주소서 <br><br>아버지 우리에게 평화를 주소서 <br>아버지 우리에게 사랑을 주소서 <br><br>아버지 우리에게 평화를 주소서 <br>아버지 우리에게 사랑을 주소서 <br><br>아버지 우리에게 사랑을 주소서 <br>평화를 주소서]]></content><category term="김병곤" label="김병곤"/><category term="평화를 주소서" label="평화를 주소서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박우곤/은총의_단비가_내리네/</id><title>박우곤 - 은총의 단비가 내리네 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:49:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:49:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9A%B0%EA%B3%A4/%EC%9D%80%EC%B4%9D%EC%9D%98_%EB%8B%A8%EB%B9%84%EA%B0%80_%EB%82%B4%EB%A6%AC%EB%84%A4/" title="박우곤 - 은총의 단비가 내리네 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[은총의 단비가 내리네 우리에게 우리에게 <br>은총의 단비가 내리네 우리에게 우리에게 <br><br>메마른 내 마음에 촉촉이 적셔 주시고 <br>목마른 내 영혼에 생명의 물 주시네 <br><br>은총의 단비가 내리네 우리에게 우리에게 <br>은총의 단비가 내리네 우리에게 우리에게 <br><br>은총의 단비가 내리네 우리에게 우리에게 <br>은총의 단비가 내리네 우리에게 우리에게 <br><br>메마른 내 영혼에 촉촉이 적셔 주시고 <br>목마른 내 영혼에 생명의 물 주시네 <br><br>은총의 단비가 내리네 우리에게 우리에게 <br>은총의 단비가 내리네 우리에게 우리에게 <br><br>은총의 단비가 내리네 우리에게 우리에게 <br>은총의 단비가 내리네 우리에게 우리에게 <br><br>은총의 단비가 내리네 우리에게 우리에게 <br>은총의 단비가 내리네 우리에게 우리에게]]></content><category term="박우곤" label="박우곤"/><category term="은총의 단비가 내리네" label="은총의 단비가 내리네"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합/아무것도_걱정마라/</id><title>한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합 - 아무것도 걱정마라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:50:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:50:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EA%B5%AD%EA%B0%80%ED%86%A8%EB%A6%AD%EC%A0%8A%EC%9D%80%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9%EC%87%84%EC%8B%A0%EC%97%B0%ED%95%A9/%EC%95%84%EB%AC%B4%EA%B2%83%EB%8F%84_%EA%B1%B1%EC%A0%95%EB%A7%88%EB%9D%BC/" title="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합 - 아무것도 걱정마라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무것도 걱정마라 내가 너를 지키리라 <br>아무것도 걱정마라 내가 너의 힘 되리라 <br><br>착한 목자 주님 당신의 곁에 언제나 <br>함께하리이다 당신만이 내 주님이시니 <br><br>아무것도 걱정마라 내가 너를 지키리라 <br>아무것도 걱정마라 내가 너의 힘 되리라 <br><br>착한 목자 주님 당신의 곁에 언제나 <br>함께하리이다 당신만이 내 주님이시니 <br><br>아무것도 걱정마라 내가 너를 지키리라 <br>아무것도 걱정마라 내가 너의 힘 되리라 <br><br>내가 너의 힘 되리라]]></content><category term="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합" label="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합"/><category term="아무것도 걱정마라" label="아무것도 걱정마라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조재영/내게_오시네/</id><title>조재영 - 내게 오시네 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:50:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:50:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%9E%AC%EC%98%81/%EB%82%B4%EA%B2%8C_%EC%98%A4%EC%8B%9C%EB%84%A4/" title="조재영 - 내게 오시네 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내게 오시네 깊은 밤 중에 내게 오시네 눈물 흘리며 <br>내게 오시네 따스한 손길 내게 오시네 성령의 꽃으로 <br><br>아파하는 날 위해 십자가 위에서 <br>눈물로 위로하신 주님의 사랑 <br><br>내게 오시네 따스한 손길 <br>내게 오시네 성령의 불로 <br><br>나를 위해 못박힌 주님의 사랑을 <br>그 누가 나를 대신 고백하오리 <br><br>내게 오시네 성령의 불로 내게 오시네 뜨거운 눈물 <br>나를 위해서 십자가 지신 주님의 선물 성령의 꽃으로]]></content><category term="조재영" label="조재영"/><category term="내게 오시네" label="내게 오시네"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합/이보다_더_큰_은혜와/</id><title>한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합 - 이보다 더 큰 은혜와 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:50:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:50:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EA%B5%AD%EA%B0%80%ED%86%A8%EB%A6%AD%EC%A0%8A%EC%9D%80%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9%EC%87%84%EC%8B%A0%EC%97%B0%ED%95%A9/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%B4%EB%8B%A4_%EB%8D%94_%ED%81%B0_%EC%9D%80%ED%98%9C%EC%99%80/" title="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합 - 이보다 더 큰 은혜와 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이보다 더 큰 은혜와 보다 큰 사랑이 있으랴 <br>내 영혼이 침묵 중에 정성된 기도를 드리네 <br><br>수고하는 자의 위로며 굶주린 이들 양식 <br>내 근심을 주께 맡겨 영원히 주 안에 살리라 <br><br>주님은 당신 성혈로 언제나 우리를 씻으사 <br>내 마음을 비추시어 영원한 생명을 주시네 <br><br>거룩한 주님의 부활로 영원한 삶의 길 열리니 <br>내 생명을 주께 맡겨 영원히 주 안에 살리라 <br><br>내 생명을 주께 맡겨 영원히 주 안에 살리라]]></content><category term="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합" label="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합"/><category term="이보다 더 큰 은혜와" label="이보다 더 큰 은혜와"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박헤레나/새로운_성령강림/</id><title>박헤레나 - 새로운 성령강림 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:50:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:50:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%97%A4%EB%A0%88%EB%82%98/%EC%83%88%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B4_%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9%EA%B0%95%EB%A6%BC/" title="박헤레나 - 새로운 성령강림 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오소서 성령이여 이 땅의 젊은이들에게 성령을 <br>오소서 성령이여 세상을 이길 수 있는 힘을 <br><br>우리에게 내려주소서 하늘의 빛 그 빛살을 <br>우리에게 내려주소서 하늘의 문을 열어주소서 <br><br>성령이시여 거룩한 영으로 내 영혼을 채우소서 <br>거룩한 자 되도록 <br><br>성령이시여 깨끗한 영으로 내 영혼을 씻으소서 <br>세상의 빛 되도록 <br><br>오소서 성령이여 이 땅의 젊은이들에게 성령을 <br>오소서 성령이여 세상을 이길 수 있는 힘을 <br><br>우리에게 내려주소서 하늘의 빛 그 빛살을 <br>우리에게 내려주소서 하늘의 문을 열어주소서 <br><br>성령이시여 거룩한 영으로 내 영혼을 채우소서 <br>거룩한 자 되도록 <br><br>성령이시여 깨끗한 영으로 내 영혼을 씻으소서 <br>세상의 빛 되도록 <br><br>세상의 빛 되도록]]></content><category term="박헤레나" label="박헤레나"/><category term="새로운 성령강림" label="새로운 성령강림"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신동헌/주님의_사랑으로만/</id><title>신동헌 - 주님의 사랑으로만 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:50:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:50:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EB%8F%99%ED%97%8C/%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9C%BC%EB%A1%9C%EB%A7%8C/" title="신동헌 - 주님의 사랑으로만 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세상 헛된 것 모두 내려놓게 주님 저를 이끄소서 <br>세상 부귀영화 필요없음을 알게 하여 주소서 <br><br>세상 헛된 것 모두 내려놓게 주님 저를 이끄소서 <br>주님의 말씀에 순종함이 기쁨 되게 하소서 <br><br>가난할 수 있음에 기뻐하게 하소서 진리위해 희생하게 하소서 <br>십자가의 그 은총을 포기하지 않게 하소서 <br><br>저를 거룩한 산 제물로 받아주소서 주님 더욱 사랑하게 이끄소서 <br>주님의 사랑으로만 만족하게 하소서 <br><br>세상 헛된 것 모두 내려놓게 주님 저를 이끄소서 <br>주님의 말씀에 순종함이 기쁨 되게 하소서 <br><br>가난할 수 있음에 기뻐하게 하소서 진리위해 희생하게 하소서 <br>십자가의 그 은총을 포기하지 않게 하소서 <br><br>저를 거룩한 산 제물로 받아주소서 주님 더욱 사랑하게 이끄소서 <br>주님의 사랑으로만 만족하게 하소서 만족하게 하소서 <br><br>만족하게 하소서]]></content><category term="신동헌" label="신동헌"/><category term="주님의 사랑으로만" label="주님의 사랑으로만"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합/하나의_희망/</id><title>한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합 - 하나의 희망 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:50:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:50:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EA%B5%AD%EA%B0%80%ED%86%A8%EB%A6%AD%EC%A0%8A%EC%9D%80%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9%EC%87%84%EC%8B%A0%EC%97%B0%ED%95%A9/%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%ED%9D%AC%EB%A7%9D/" title="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합 - 하나의 희망 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날 사랑하신 예수 그리스도 <br>언제나 내 손을 잡아 주시는 분 <br><br>날 사랑하신 예수 그리스도 <br>언제나 새로운 희망을 채우시는 분 <br><br>희망을 잃고 쓰러진 이에게 <br>내게 주신 사랑을 전해요 <br><br>내 손을 잡고 일으켜주신 사랑으로 <br>이제 내가 손 잡아주어요 <br><br>하느님께서 우리를 부르실 때 하나의 희망을 주셨죠 <br>우리 모두 사랑이 되라고 <br><br>우리의 희망 예수 그리스도의 사랑 <br>가장 큰 사랑으로 우리 함께 희망을 나눠요 예수 그리스도 <br><br>희망을 잃고 쓰러진 이에게 <br>내게 주신 사랑을 전해요 <br><br>내 손을 잡고 일으켜주신 사랑으로 <br>이제 내가 손 잡아주어요 <br><br>하느님께서 우리를 부르실 때 하나의 희망을 주셨죠 <br>우리 모두 사랑이 되라고 <br><br>우리의 희망 예수 그리스도의 사랑 <br>가장 큰 사랑으로 우리 함께 희망을 나눠요 예수 그리스도 <br><br>하느님께서 우리를 부르실 때 하나의 희망을 주셨죠 <br>우리 모두 사랑이 되라고 <br><br>우리의 희망 예수 그리스도의 사랑 <br>가장 큰 사랑으로 우리 함께 희망을 나눠요 예수 그리스도]]></content><category term="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합" label="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합"/><category term="하나의 희망" label="하나의 희망"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합/임하소서_성령이여/</id><title>한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합 - 임하소서 성령이여 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:50:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:50:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EA%B5%AD%EA%B0%80%ED%86%A8%EB%A6%AD%EC%A0%8A%EC%9D%80%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9%EC%87%84%EC%8B%A0%EC%97%B0%ED%95%A9/%EC%9E%84%ED%95%98%EC%86%8C%EC%84%9C_%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9%EC%9D%B4%EC%97%AC/" title="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합 - 임하소서 성령이여 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[임하소서 성령이여 우리에게 임하소서 <br>가장 귀한 분 존귀한 숨결 생명의 주님 오소서 <br><br>임하소서 성령이여 하늘의 빛 비춰주소서 <br>기쁨의 손님 영혼의 위로 구원의 빛을 주소서 <br><br>우리 맘 깊은 곳에 끝없는 사랑으로 <br>채워주소서 창조주시여 임하소서 <br><br>임하소서 성령이여 우리에게 임하소서 <br>가장 귀한 분 존귀한 숨결 생명의 주님 오소서 <br><br>우리 맘 깊은 곳에 끝없는 사랑으로 <br>채워주소서 창조주시여 임하소서 <br><br>채워주소서 창조주시여 임하소서]]></content><category term="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합" label="한국가톨릭젊은이성령쇄신연합"/><category term="임하소서 성령이여" label="임하소서 성령이여"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조영배/너와_같은_하루/</id><title>조영배 - 너와 같은 하루 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:50:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:50:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%98%81%EB%B0%B0/%EB%84%88%EC%99%80_%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%ED%95%98%EB%A3%A8/" title="조영배 - 너와 같은 하루 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 어디쯤 일까 <br>문득 너의 생각에 잠겨봐 <br>잠시 꿈꾸듯 여행하는 기분인 걸 <br>작은 일상 속에 떠나 보는 너란 세상 <br>너무 보고 싶어 <br>아무 이유도 없이 그런 날 있잖아 <br>눈이 닿는 곳마다 <br>누구보다 먼저 그려지는 건 <br>너와 함께한 시간 <br>내 추억에 너의 추억을 이어주면 <br>헤어졌던 우리가 다시 볼 수 있을까 <br>네가 있어야 하는 너와 같은 하루에 <br>모든 순간은 잃어버린 널 찾아 물들어 <br>너와 대화하듯 혼자 <br>뒷이야기를 적어봐 <br>시간은 망설임 없이 나를 데려가 <br>꼭 끝이 찢어진 소설처럼 늘 달라져 <br>혹시 너일까 봐 <br>오는 사람들마다 네 얼굴 떠올려 <br>모두 변한다 해도 <br>언제 어디서도 널 알아볼 거야 <br>어제 만난 것처럼 <br>내 추억에 너의 추억을 이어주면 <br>헤어졌던 우리가 다시 볼 수 있을까 <br>네가 있어야 하는 너와 같은 하루에 <br>모든 순간은 잃어버린 널 찾아 물들어 <br>잿빛 하루의 벽을 넘어 <br>햇살처럼 내 맘을 어루만져 <br>영원한 빛이 된 한 사람 <br>두 눈 감고 너의 이름을 불러보면 <br>따스했던 네 숨결 바람이 돼 불어와 <br>항상 너를 느끼는 너와 같은 하루에 <br>모든 순간은 여전히 너 하나만 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="조영배" label="조영배"/><category term="너와 같은 하루" label="너와 같은 하루"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조영배/우산_쓴_사람/</id><title>조영배 - 우산 쓴 사람 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:50:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:50:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%98%81%EB%B0%B0/%EC%9A%B0%EC%82%B0_%EC%93%B4_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C/" title="조영배 - 우산 쓴 사람 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비가 와 잊혀졌던 꿈처럼 <br>지난 모든 게 그리워 <br>저 분주한 사람들 발길 따라 <br>한 사람 네가 생각나 <br>오랜 추억이 쏟아 지는 <br>세상 어디에도 보여 <br>너란 우산을 들면 <br>작은 수채화로 물든 그 곳엔 <br>기억처럼 네가 와 <br>비 내리는 거리 위로 오는 사람이 <br>너일까 봐 조급해진 순간 <br>그럴 리 없어 <br>뒷모습이 돼 멀어져 간다 <br>넌 늘 우산 쓴 사람 <br>추억은 꼭 빗물처럼 차올라 <br>문득 네 모습을 비춰 <br>홀로 걷는 이 길에 <br>스쳐 지나가듯 흩날린 시간 <br>그때 너의 목소리 <br>비 내리는 거리 위로 오는 사람이 <br>너일까 봐 조급해진 순간 <br>그럴 리 없어 <br>뒷모습이 돼 멀어져 간다 <br>난 널 찾아 헤맨다 <br>네가 없는 이 세상을 채운 이 비가 <br>아름다운 추억으로 내려 <br>비가 갠 뒤에 <br>하얀 햇살에 너를 느껴봐 <br>넌 늘 보고픈 사람 <br>]]></content><category term="조영배" label="조영배"/><category term="우산 쓴 사람" label="우산 쓴 사람"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박용민/사랑하면_할수록_영화_클래식_유영석_작곡/</id><title>박용민 - 사랑하면 할수록 (영화 클래식 유영석 작곡) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:50:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:50:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9A%A9%EB%AF%BC/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%98%EB%A9%B4_%ED%95%A0%EC%88%98%EB%A1%9D_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%ED%81%B4%EB%9E%98%EC%8B%9D_%EC%9C%A0%EC%98%81%EC%84%9D_%EC%9E%91%EA%B3%A1/" title="박용민 - 사랑하면 할수록 (영화 클래식 유영석 작곡) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[노을 지는 언덕너머 <br>그대 날 바라보고있죠 <br>차마 말하지 못한 내 마음을 <br>이미 알고 있었나요 <br>왠지 모르게 우리는 <br>우연처럼 지내왔지만 <br>무지개 문 지나 천국에 가도 <br>나의 마음 변함없죠 <br>사랑하면 할수록 <br>그대 그리워 가슴 아파도 <br>이것만을 믿어요 <br>끝이 아니란 걸 <br>이제야 난 깨달았죠 <br>사랑은 숨길 수 없음을 <br>우연처럼 쉽게 다가온 그대 <br>이젠 운명이 된거죠 <br>사랑하면 할수록 멀어짐이 <br>두렵기만 해도 <br>이것만을 믿어요 <br>끝이 아니란 걸 <br>끝이 아니란 걸 <br>]]></content><category term="박용민" label="박용민"/><category term="사랑하면 할수록 (영화 클래식 유영석 작곡)" label="사랑하면 할수록 (영화 클래식 유영석 작곡)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Utada_Hikaru/大空で抱きしめて___Oozorade_Dakishimete_넓은_하늘로_껴안아_줘/</id><title>Utada Hikaru - 大空で抱きしめて / Oozorade Dakishimete (넓은 하늘로 껴안아 줘) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:50:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:50:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Utada_Hikaru/%E5%A4%A7%E7%A9%BA%E3%81%A7%E6%8A%B1%E3%81%8D%E3%81%97%E3%82%81%E3%81%A6___Oozorade_Dakishimete_%EB%84%93%EC%9D%80_%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98%EB%A1%9C_%EA%BB%B4%EC%95%88%EC%95%84_%EC%A4%98/" title="Utada Hikaru - 大空で抱きしめて / Oozorade Dakishimete (넓은 하늘로 껴안아 줘) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[晴れた日曜日の改札口は <br>하레타 니치요오비노 카이사츠구치와 <br>맑았던 일요일의 개찰구는 <br>誰かを待つ人たちで色づき始め <br>다레카오　마츠 히토타치데 이로즈키하지메 <br>누군가를 기다리는 사람들로 물들기 시작하고 <br><br>今日はどこか遠くへ行きたい？分 <br>오늘은 어딘가 먼 21곳에 가고 싶은 기분 <br>空の見える場所へ <br>소라노 미에루 바쇼에 <br>하늘의 보이는 곳에 <br><br>雲の中飛んでいけたら <br>쿠모노나카 톤데이케타라 <br>구름 속으로 날아갈 수 있다면 <br>大空で抱きしめて <br>오오조라데 다키시메테 <br>넓은 하늘에서 껴안아 줘 <br>君はまだ怒ってるかな <br>키미와 마다 오콧테루카나 <br>너는 아직 화났을까 <br>意地を張らずにいられなくて <br>이지오 하라즈니 이라레나쿠테 <br>고집 부리지 말고 있을 수 없어서 <br><br>いつの日かまた？えたとしたら <br>이츠노히카 마다 아에타토시타라 <br>언젠가 다시 만날 수 있다면 <br>最後と言わずにキスをして <br>사이고토 이와즈니 키스오시테 <br>마지막이라고 하지 말고 키스를 해줘 <br>もし夢の中でしかで？えないから <br>모시 유메노 나카데시카데 아에나이카라 <br>만약 꿈속에서 밖에 만날 수 없다면 <br>朝まで私を抱きしめて <br>아사마데 와타시오 다키시메테 <br>아침까지 나를 껴안아 줘 <br><br>？で目が？めた月曜日の朝 <br>나미다데 메가사메타 게츠요오비노아사 <br>눈물에 잠이 깬 월요일 아침 <br>急いで支度をした <br>이소이데 시타쿠오시타 <br>서둘러 준비를 했어 <br><br>僕はまだあの頃のまま <br>보쿠와 마다 아노 코로노마마 <br>나는 아직 그날 그대로 <br>？空で待ち惚け <br>아오조라데 마치보우케 <br>푸른 하늘에서 멍하니 기다려 <br>夏の花が散る頃には <br>나츠노하나가 치루 코로니와 <br>여름 꽃이 질 즈음에는 <br>笑顔で僕を迎えに？て <br>에가오데 보쿠오 무카이니키테 <br>웃는 얼굴로 나를 데리러 와줘 <br><br>純なあなたが誤解するから <br>쥰나 아나타가 고카이스루카라 <br>순진한 당신이 오해하니까 <br>おしゃべりな私を？らせて <br>오샤베리나 와타시오 다마라세테 <br>말 많은 나를 조용히 시켜 <br>傷ついたのはお互い？だから <br>키즈츠이타노와 오타가이사마다카라 <br>상처받은 것은 서로 마찬가지니까 <br>四の五の言わずに抱き寄せて <br>시노고노 이와즈니 다키요세테 <br>이러쿵저러쿵 하지 말고 껴안아 줘 <br><br>いつの日かまた？えたとしたら <br>언젠가 다시 만날 수 있다면 <br>もう一度私を困らせて <br>한번 더 나를 난처하게 만들어 <br>もし夢の中でしか？えないなら <br>만약 꿈속에서 밖에 만날 수 없다면 <br>朝まで私を抱きしめて <br>아침까지 나를 껴안아 줘 <br><br>わかっているわ、欲張りなのは <br>알고 있어, 많은 욕심이라는 걸 <br>でも最後と言わずにキスをして <br>그래도 마지막이라고 하지말고 키스해 줘 <br>もし夢の中でしか？えないなら <br>모시 유메노 나카데시카 아에나이나라 <br>만약 꿈속에서 밖에 만날 수 없다면 <br>天翔る星よ　消えないで <br>아마카케루 호시요 키에나이데 <br>하늘을 나는 별아 사라지지마]]></content><category term="Utada Hikaru" label="Utada Hikaru"/><category term="大空で抱きしめて / Oozorade Dakishimete (넓은 하늘로 껴안아 줘)" label="大空で抱きしめて / Oozorade Dakishimete (넓은 하늘로 껴안아 줘)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/우연수/은하수/</id><title>우연수 - 은하수 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:50:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:50:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9A%B0%EC%97%B0%EC%88%98/%EC%9D%80%ED%95%98%EC%88%98/" title="우연수 - 은하수 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어쩌면 우리는 별들 사일 헤매나 봐 <br>더 이상 우리는 서로에게 다가설 수 <br>없는지 <br>얼마나 많은 눈물이 흘러야 할까요 <br>얼마나 더 많은 외로운 숨결이 <br>모여야 할지 <br>오늘 밤 나는 보이지 않는 저기 <br>은하수에 별 하나를 그려 놓을게요 <br>그러다 잠시 어둔 밤 하늘에 <br>별빛이 지나면 날 생각해줘요 <br>언제쯤 가려진 진심을 알 수 있을까 <br>닫혀 있던 그 맘 <br>조금만 손을 내밀어 준다면 <br>기나긴 외로움의 끝은 어디인가요 <br>단 한 번이라도 나의 이 숨결이 <br>느껴진다면 <br>오늘 밤 나는 보이지 않는 저기 <br>은하수에 별 하날 그려 놓을게요 <br>그러다 잠시 어둔 밤 하늘에 <br>별빛이 빛나면 날 생각해줘요 <br>지금 우리 둘만의 별을 찾아 <br>떠날 수 있다면 얼마나 좋을지 <br>그곳에서 기다림도 필요 없이 <br>우린 영원히 함께할 텐데 <br>오늘도 난 보이지 않는 멀리 <br>은하수에 별 하날 띄어 놓을 거야 <br>그리고 잠시 어둔 밤 하늘에 <br>빛을 환히 볼 수 있게 <br>]]></content><category term="우연수" label="우연수"/><category term="은하수" label="은하수"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/무딘_Moodin/난_아름답지_않아/</id><title>무딘 (Moodin) - 난 아름답지 않아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:52:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:52:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B4%EB%94%98_Moodin/%EB%82%9C_%EC%95%84%EB%A6%84%EB%8B%B5%EC%A7%80_%EC%95%8A%EC%95%84/" title="무딘 (Moodin) - 난 아름답지 않아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 아름답지 않아 <br>내 모습 너무 <br>나는 오늘도 초라해 <br>난 아름답지 않아 <br>거울 속 나는 <br>매번 그래 <br>오늘 더 초라해 <br>너에게만 기울던 <br>나의 봄이 지나고 <br>너의 계절은 이제 <br>그녀에게만 머물겠지 <br>익숙하기만 했던 <br>우리의 시간들이 <br>이젠 멀어지나 봐 <br>난 아름답지 않아 <br>내 모습 너무 <br>나는 오늘도 초라해 <br>난 아름답지 않아 <br>거울 속 나는 <br>매번 그래 <br>오늘 더 초라해 <br>모두 너여야만 해 <br>난 꼭 그래야만 해 <br>깍지 낀 두 손위엔 <br>작은 점 하나까지 <br>미소 지을 때 입가에 <br>옅은 주름 하나까지 <br>그렇게나 그리고 <br>바래왔던 그대가 <br>이젠 희미해져 <br>난 아름답지 않아 <br>내 모습 너무 <br>나는 오늘도 초라해 <br>난 아름답지 않아 <br>거울 속 나는 <br>매번 그래 <br>오늘 더 초라해 <br>모두 너여야만 해 <br>난 꼭 그래야만 해 <br>난 아무렇지 않아 <br>부서진 맘이 <br>나는 그게 더 익숙해 <br>왜 너완 다른 걸까 <br>되뇌어보지만 <br>소리 내 붙잡아 보지만 <br>난 꼭 너여야 했어 <br>난 늘 너여야 했어 <br>난 아름답지 않아 <br>난 아름답지 않아 <br>모두 너여야만 해 <br>난 꼭 그래야만 해 <br>]]></content><category term="무딘 (Moodin)" label="무딘 (Moodin)"/><category term="난 아름답지 않아" label="난 아름답지 않아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/Legacy/</id><title>JAY-Z - Legacy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:52:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:52:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/Legacy/" title="JAY-Z - Legacy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Daddy, what's a will <br><br>Take those moneys and spread 'cross families <br>My sisters, Hattie and Lou, the nephews, cousins and TT <br>Eric, the rest to B for whatever she wants to do <br>She might start an institute <br>She might put poor kids through school <br>My stake in Roc Nation should go to you <br>Leave a piece for your siblings to give to their children too <br>TIDAL, the champagne, D'USSe, I'd like to see <br>A nice peace fund ideas from people who look like we <br>We gon' start a society within a society <br>That's major, just like the Negro League <br>There was a time America wouldn't let us ball <br>Those times are now back, just now called Afro tech <br>Generational wealth, that's the key <br>My parents ain't have shit, so that shift started with me <br>My mom took her money, she bought me bonds <br>That was the sweetest thing of all time, uh <br><br>Legacy, Legacy, Legacy, Legacy <br>Black excellence baby, you gon' let 'em see <br>Legacy, Legacy, Legacy, Legacy <br>Black excellency, baby, let 'em see <br><br>I remember, like, listenin' to Wu Tang <br>And niggas like, Your seed married his seed, married my seed <br>That's how we keep Carter money all in the family <br><br>You see, my father, son of a preacher man <br>Whose daughter couldn't escape the reach of the preacher's hand <br>That charge of energy set all the Carters back <br>It took all these years to get to zero in fact <br>I hated religion 'cause here was this Christian <br>He was preachin' on Sundays, versus how he was livin' Monday <br>Someday I forgive him <br>'Cause strangely our division led to multiple religions <br>I studied Muslim, Buddhist, and Christians <br>And I was runnin' from him, He was givin' me wisdom <br>See how the universe works <br>It takes my hurt and help me find more of myself <br>It's a gift and a curse <br>That's called the Red Queen's Race <br><br>You run this hard just to stay in place <br>Keep up the pace, baby <br>Keep up the pace <br>You run this hard just to stay in place <br><br>Legacy, Legacy, Legacy, Legacy <br>Black excellence, you gon' let 'em see <br>Legacy, Legacy, Legacy, Legacy <br>Black excellency, baby, let 'em see <br><br>Day, someday, someday we'll all <br>Someday we'll all be free]]></content><category term="JAY-Z" label="JAY-Z"/><category term="Legacy" label="Legacy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/Marcy_Me/</id><title>JAY-Z - Marcy Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:52:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:52:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/Marcy_Me/" title="JAY-Z - Marcy Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Live from Bedford Stuyvesant <br>The livest one representin' BK to the fullest <br>Bastards duckin' when Hov be buckin' <br>Chicken heads be cluckin' <br><br>Back when ratchet was a ratchet and a vixen was a vixen <br>And Jam Master Jay was alive I was mixin' <br>Cookin' coke in the kitchen <br>Back when Rodman was a Piston <br>Mike was losin' to Isiah, but he soon would get his sixth one <br>Gave birth to my verbal imagination <br>Assume a virtue if you have not <br>Or better yet here's a verse from Hamlet <br>Lord, we know who we are <br>Yet we know not what we may be <br>So maybe I'm the one or maybe I'm crazy <br>I'm from Marcy Houses, where the boys die by the thousand <br>Back when Pam was on Martin <br>Yeah, that's where it all started <br>When Denzel was blottin' carpet, I'll pack a nine millimeter <br>When Slick Rick made Mona Lisa <br>When Lisa Bonet was Beyonce of her day, I had divas, y'all <br>Think I just popped up in this bitch like a fetus Nah <br>Pregnant pause, give you some second thoughts <br>There's room on the bandwagon, don't abort <br>Marcy me <br><br>Marcy me <br>Streets is my artery, the vein of my existence <br>I'm the Gotham City heartbeat <br>I started in lobbies, now parley with Saudis <br>I'm a Sufi to goofies, I could prolly speak Farsi <br>That's poetry, reek of coca leaf in my past <br>Came through the bushes smellin' like roses <br>I need a trophy just for that <br>Old Brooklyn, not this new shit, shit feel like a spoof <br>Fat laces in your shoe, I'm talkin' bustin' off the roof <br>Hold a Uzi vertical, let the thing smoke <br>Y'all flirtin' with death, I be winkin' through the scope <br>Shout out to all the murderers turned murals <br>Plural, fuck the Federal Bureau <br>Shout out to Nostrand Ave, Flushing Ave, Myrtle <br>All the County of Kings, may your ground stay fertile <br>Shout out to Big Poppa, Daddy Kane, heroes <br>Thus concludin' my concerto <br>Marcy me <br><br>Must be in the air <br>Oh, can't walk away, I know, I know <br>Just the way I'm raised <br>I know, I know, I know <br>Oh Marcy, Marcy me <br>Just the way I am always gonna be <br>I ain't gonna change, no <br>Marcy, Marcy me, just the way I am <br>I ain't gonna change, no <br>I ain't gonna change, no <br>Couldn't change me if I wanted to <br>You couldn't change me if you wanted to <br>I'ma take this with me to the Moon <br>Como has nome, cavaleiro <br>Eu hei nome Todo o Mundo <br>E meu tempo]]></content><category term="JAY-Z" label="JAY-Z"/><category term="Marcy Me" label="Marcy Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/Moonlight/</id><title>JAY-Z - Moonlight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:52:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:52:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/Moonlight/" title="JAY-Z - Moonlight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, got a lil' cold <br>So bear with me <br>Yeah, yeah <br><br>We stuck in La La Land <br>Even when we win, we gon' lose <br>Y'all got the same fuckin' flows <br>I don't know who is who <br>We got the same fuckin' watch <br>She don't got time to choose <br>We stuck in La La Land <br>We got the same fuckin' moves <br><br>Y'all fuck the same fuckin' chicks <br>I'm in the skrt with ya yeah, right <br>I'm the skrt with ya cool story <br>I'm on the ch 'nough of this <br>Look, I know killers, you no killer, huh <br>Bathing Ape maybe not a gorilla, huh <br>Glorified seat filler, huh <br>Stop walkin' around like y'all made Thriller, huh <br>Fake Dracos all in the videos <br>We sure we shoot 'em in my city though <br>I don't post no threats on the Internet <br>I just pose a threat, blame Lenny S for that <br>I don't be on the 'Gram goin' ham <br>Givin' information to the pork, that's all spam <br>Please don't talk about guns <br>That you ain't never gon' use <br>Y'all always tell on y'all self <br>I'm just so fuckin' confused <br><br>Y'all stuck in La La Land <br>Even when we win, we gon' lose <br>Y'all got the same fuckin' flows <br>I don't know who is who <br>We got the same fuckin' watch <br>She don't got time to choose <br>We stuck in La La Land <br>We got the same fuckin' moves <br><br>Y'all niggas still signin' deals Still <br>After all they done stole, for real <br>After what they done to our Lauryn Hill <br>And y'all niggas is 'posed to be trill <br>That's real talk when you behind on your taxes <br>And you pawned all your chains <br>And they run off with your masters <br>And took it to Beverly Hills <br>While we in Calabasas <br>And my head is scratchin' <br>'Cause that shit is backwards <br>That shit ain't right <br>Lucian is cool but Lucian don't write <br>Doug ain't this tight, so <br>Fuck what we sellin' <br>Fuck is we makin' <br>'Cause their grass is greener <br>'Cause they always rakin' in mo' <br>Nah, nah, nah, nah <br>Nah, nah]]></content><category term="JAY-Z" label="JAY-Z"/><category term="Moonlight" label="Moonlight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/Bam_Feat_Damian_Marley/</id><title>JAY-Z - Bam (Feat. Damian Marley) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:52:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:52:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/Bam_Feat_Damian_Marley/" title="JAY-Z - Bam (Feat. Damian Marley) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Now greetings to the world <br>Gangsta nuh live in a tenement yard <br>Rude boy nuh live in a tenement yard <br>Too much watchy, watchy, watchy <br>Too much su, su, su, su, su <br>Them chatty, chatty, chatty <br>Them su, su, su, su, su <br>Fuck all this pretty Shawn Carter shit nigga, HOV <br><br>Shawn was on that gospel shit <br>I was on the total fuckin' opposite <br>Shit, stuff a million dollars in the sock drawer <br>That's a war chest in case you need your chest knocked off <br>Y'all be talkin' crazy under them IG pictures <br>So when you get to hell you tell 'em Blanco sent ya <br>I can't take no threats, I got a set of twins <br>Those were just the words you'll never hear again <br>For the final time you don't believe these fools <br>I've never seen a worker rock so many jewels <br>I've never seen the runner with so many cars <br>Y'all couldn't stop me, you're not as tough as you say you are <br>My advice is just don't be too nice to niggas <br>Just set the price so niggas'll live your life, my nigga <br>Once upon a time in the projects <br>Shawn was in flight mode, I bought a Pyrex <br>I was in fight mode and now it's fuck me, mijo <br>I was movin' them kilos, help you move your peoples <br>Sometimes you need your ego, gotta remind these fools <br>Who they effin' with, and we got FN's too <br>Before we had AandR's, we had AR's too <br>We the only ones really movin' like y'all say y'all do <br>We still movin' like y'all niggas say y'all did <br>Emory passed you niggas and he did a bid <br>Ty Ty jumped over niggas and he's like 5'6 <br>Got the heart of a giant, don't you ever forget <br>Don't you never forget, Jigga got this shit poppin' <br>I pulled out the pot when we was outta options <br><br>Gangsta nuh live in a tenement yard <br>Rude boy nuh live in a tenement yard <br>Too much watchy, watchy, watchy <br>Them su, su, su, su, su <br>Too much chatty, chatty, chatty <br>And them su, su, su, su, su <br>Fuck all this pretty Shawn Carter shit nigga, HOV <br><br>Put that drum in your ear, don't get Srem'd <br>I'll Bobby Shmurda anybody you heard of <br>Niggas could not be further, I fathered your style <br>Birth of a Nation, Nat Turner style <br>Uh, y'all make me turn up all this talkin' down <br>Uh, niggas is skippin' leg day just to run they mouth <br>I be skippin' leg day, I still run the world <br>I pressed ahead of your team with one finger curled <br>I'll line you all up with one finger wave <br>Make niggas weave, niggas is out here fake <br>Laced front to the back, don't front <br>Y'all gonna make me wig, I'ma give y'all what you want <br><br>Gangsta nuh live in a tenement yard <br>Dreadlocks nuh live in a tenement yard <br>Too much watchy, watchy, watchy <br>And them su, su, su, su, su <br>Too much chatty, chatty, chatty <br>And them su, su, su, su, su <br>Fuck all this pretty Shawn Carter shit nigga, HOV <br><br>Can't you see it's my ambition <br>I come to nice up the whole nation <br>What a bam bam yeah, Lord <br>And mi seh what a bam bam Do it, dread <br>Can't you see it's my ambition <br>I come to nice up the whole nation <br>What a bam bam <br>What a bam bam <br>I don't give a God damn <br>I don't give a God damn <br>When mi come a dance and mi spliff and Guinness <br>Yow, crowd of people go and mind yuh business <br>This a hunting season <br>Mek I tell you hunting season <br>Well, I tell ya something season <br>Yow this a hunting season <br>Cake and dumpling season <br>Spinners and dumpling season <br>Don't play by the king <br>Love is all I and I bring you know <br>Voice of the one pon gully banking <br>Top ranking, keep it skanking <br>Ooh wee, huh <br>Hear me now]]></content><category term="JAY-Z" label="JAY-Z"/><category term="Bam (Feat. Damian Marley)" label="Bam (Feat. Damian Marley)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/Family_Feud_Feat_Beyonce/</id><title>JAY-Z - Family Feud (Feat. Beyonce) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:52:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:52:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/Family_Feud_Feat_Beyonce/" title="JAY-Z - Family Feud (Feat. Beyonce) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My nigga got on <br>My nigga got on all white, no socks <br>My nigga got that cocaina on today <br>That's how he feel <br>Turn my vocal up <br>That's how you feel, Emory <br>Turn my vocal up some more <br>Turn my vocal up, Guru <br>Turn the music up too <br><br>Super Bowl goals <br>My wife in the crib feedin' the kids liquid gold <br>We in a whole different mode <br>Kid that used to pitch bricks can't be pigeonholed <br>I cooked up more chicken when the kitchen closed <br>Oh, we gon' reach a billi' first <br>I told my wife the spiritual shit really work <br>Alhamdulillah, I run through 'em all <br>Hovi's home, all these phonies come to a halt <br>All this old talk left me confused <br>You'd rather be old rich me or new you <br>And old niggas, y'all stop actin' brand new <br>Like 2Pac ain't have a nose ring too, huh <br><br>Nobody wins when the family feuds <br>But my stash can't fit into Steve Harvey's suit <br>I'm clear why I'm here, how about you <br>Ain't no such thing as an ugly billionaire, I'm cute <br>Mmmmm <br>Pretty much <br>If anybody gettin' handsome checks, it should be us <br>Fuck rap, crack cocaine <br>Nah, we did that, Black owned things <br>Hundred percent, Black owned champagne <br>And we merrily merrily eatin' off these streams <br>Y'all still drinkin' Perrier Jouet, huh <br>But we ain't get through to you yet, uh <br>What's better than one billionaire Two two <br>'Specially if they're from the same hue as you <br>Y'all stop me when I stop tellin' the truth <br><br>Hahahaha Ha ya <br>I would say I'm the realest nigga rappin' Ha ya <br>But that ain't even a statement Ha ya <br>That's like sayin' I'm the tallest midget Ha ya <br>Wait, that ain't politically correct Ha ya <br>Forget it Ha ya <br>Can I get Amen from the congregation <br>Amen, amen Ha ya <br>Can I get a Amen from the congregation <br>Amen, amen Ha ya <br>Ha ya ya ya <br><br>Yeah, I'll fuck up a good thing if you let me <br>Let me alone, Becky <br>A man that don't take care his family can't be rich <br>I'll watch Godfather, I miss that whole shit <br>My consciousness was Michael's common sense <br>I missed the karma that came as a consequence <br>Niggas bustin' off through the curtains 'cause she hurtin' <br>Kay losin' the babies 'cause their future's uncertain <br>Nobody wins when the family feuds <br>We all screwed 'cause we never had the tools <br>I'm tryna fix you <br>I'm tryna get these niggas with no stripes to be official <br>Y'all think small, I think Biggie <br>Y'all whole pass is in danger, ten Mississippi <br>Al Sharpton in the mirror takin' selfies <br>How is him or Pill Cosby s'posed to help me <br>Old niggas never accepted me <br>New niggas is the reason I stopped drinkin' Dos Equis <br>We all lose when the family feuds <br>What's better than one billionaire Two <br>I'll be damned if I drink some Belvedere while Puff got CiROC <br>Y'all need to stop <br><br>Ha ya, ha ya, ha ya, ha ya <br>Ha ya, ha ya, ha ya, ha ya <br>Ha ya, ha ya, ha ya, ha ya <br>Ha ya, ha ya, ha ya, ha ya <br>Ha ya, ha ya <br>Love me like, love <br>Ha ya <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Like yeah, yeah, yeah]]></content><category term="JAY-Z" label="JAY-Z"/><category term="Family Feud (Feat. Beyonce)" label="Family Feud (Feat. Beyonce)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/4_44/</id><title>JAY-Z - 4:44 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:52:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:52:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/4_44/" title="JAY-Z - 4:44 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do I find it so hard <br>When I know in my heart <br>I'm letting you down every day <br>Letting you down every day <br>Why do I keep on running away <br>Look I apologize often womanize <br>Took for my child to be born <br>See through a woman's eyes <br>Took for these natural twins <br>to believe in miracles <br>Took me too long for this song <br>I don't deserve you <br>I harass you out in Paris <br>Please come back to Rome <br>you make it home <br>We talked for hours <br>when you were on tour <br>Please pick up the phone <br>pick up the phone <br>I said Don't embarrass me <br>instead of Be mine <br>That was my proposal <br>for us to go steady <br>That was your 21st birthday <br>You mature faster than me <br>I wasn't ready <br>So I apologize <br>I seen the innocence leave your eyes <br>I still mourn this death and <br>I apologize for all the stillborns <br>'Cause I wasn't present <br>your body wouldn't accept it <br>I apologize to all the women whom I <br>Toyed with your emotions <br>because I was emotionless <br>And I apologize 'cause at <br>your best you are love <br>And because I fall short of <br>what I say I'm all about <br>Your eyes leave with the soul <br>that your body once housed <br>And you stare blankly into space <br>Thinkin' of all the time <br>you wasted it on all this basic shit <br>So I apologize <br>I'm never gonna treat you <br>I'm never gonna treat you <br>like I should <br>I apologize <br>Our love was one for the ages <br>and I contained us <br>And all this ratchet shit and <br>we more expansive <br>Not meant to cry and die alone <br>in these mansions <br>Or sleep with our back turned <br>We supposed to vacay <br>'til our backs burn <br>We're supposed to laugh <br>'til our heart stops <br>And then meet in a space <br>where the dark stop <br>And let love light the way <br>Like the men before me <br>I cut off my nose to spite my face <br>I never wanted another <br>woman to know <br>Something about me <br>that you didn't know <br>I promised I cried <br>I couldn't hold <br>I suck at love <br>I think I need a do-over <br>I will be emotionally available <br>if I invited you over <br>I stew over <br>what if you over my shit <br>I'm never gonna treat you <br>I'm never gonna treat you <br>like I should <br>And if my children knew <br>I don't even know what I would do <br>If they ain't look at me the same <br>I would prob'ly die <br>with all the shame <br>You did what with who <br>What good is a menage a trois <br>when you have a soulmate <br>You risked that for Blue <br>If I wasn't a superhero in your face <br>My heart breaks for the day <br>I have to explain my mistakes <br>And the mask goes away <br>and Santa Claus is fake <br>And you go online and see <br>For Blue's tooth <br>the tooth fairy didn't pay <br>I'm never gonna treat you <br>like I should <br>]]></content><category term="JAY-Z" label="JAY-Z"/><category term="4:44" label="4:44"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/Caught_Their_Eyes_Feat_Frank_Ocean/</id><title>JAY-Z - Caught Their Eyes (Feat. Frank Ocean) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:52:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:52:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/Caught_Their_Eyes_Feat_Frank_Ocean/" title="JAY-Z - Caught Their Eyes (Feat. Frank Ocean) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ready for it <br>I'm ready for it <br>Yeah <br>Ah <br><br>East Side nigga <br>With that feets high <br>Nigga with that Lisa <br>Talkin' about that Lisa, nigga <br>With that we sa, nigga <br>With that East Side <br>That dance, uh <br>Your eyes speak the truth when everything else lies <br>May pretend that we kin but the vibes don't fly <br><br>Bruh, I survived readin' guys like you <br>I'm surprised y'all think you can disguise y'all truths <br>I seen eyes wide as they're about to shoot <br>You can be a hairpin off and you can trigger your Roots <br>I wave to these haters, don't give me dap <br>You know the world can see just how phony you act, bruh <br>Y'all body language is all remedial <br>How could you see the difference between you and I <br>My crash course was much tougher <br>'Round friends who kill they friends <br>Then hug their friends' mothers <br>And show up at the funeral, complete with blank stares <br>Invisible ink, I had to read things that wasn't there <br>Memories may sneak down my cheek <br>But I could see a side eye in my sleep <br><br>Ready for it, deep breath, fill up the void <br>Eyes open them up, check off the coins <br>Still stingin' from tears, they try to see you <br>I'm ready for earth, ready for real <br>Solipsistic, admit it, I see you there <br>So it seems, so you seem <br>I can't tell if you're image or are just the flare <br>In my dreams, in my dreams <br><br>I sat down with Prince, eye to eye <br>He told me his wishes before he died <br>Now, Londell McMillan, he must be color blind <br>They only see green from them purple eyes <br>They eyes hide, they eyes high <br>My eyes wide shut to all the lies <br>These industry niggas, they always been fishy <br>But ain't no Biggie, no lazy eye, huh <br>This guy had 'Slave' on his face <br>You think he wanted the masters with his masters <br>You greedy bastards sold tickets to walk through his house <br>I'm surprised you ain't auction off the casket <br>Don't big bro me, don't Big Homie <br>I've seen pure admiration become rivals <br>I've been to Paris at least two times <br>I've seen the Eiffel, I've seen a eyeful <br><br>Ready for it, deep breath, fill up the void <br>Eyes open them up, check off the coins <br>Still stingin' from tears, they try to see you <br>I'm ready for earth, ready for real <br>Solipsistic, admit it, I see you there <br>So it seems, so you seem <br>I can't tell if you're image or are just the flare <br>In my dreams, in my dreams <br><br>I've been out of touch for a couple years <br>I've been ready for this for real <br>Hopin' I can touch what I see <br>'Cause I've been ready for you, for real <br><br>Look, you've done enough Have you no sense of decency, sir <br>At long last, have you left no sense of decency <br><br>East Side nigga <br>With that feets high <br>Nigga with that Li sa <br>Talkin' about that Li sa, nigga <br>With that we sa, nigga <br>With that East Side <br>That dance, uh <br>Your eyes speak the truth with everything else, stars <br>They pretend we can but the vibes don't fly]]></content><category term="JAY-Z" label="JAY-Z"/><category term="Caught Their Eyes (Feat. Frank Ocean)" label="Caught Their Eyes (Feat. Frank Ocean)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/Smile_Feat_Gloria_Carter/</id><title>JAY-Z - Smile (Feat. Gloria Carter) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T20:52:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T20:52:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JAY-Z/Smile_Feat_Gloria_Carter/" title="JAY-Z - Smile (Feat. Gloria Carter) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Good morn' or evening, friends <br>Smile, you recordin' <br><br>Slammin' Bentley doors like we invented doors <br>20 years ago we drove Bentley Azures <br>We drinkin' Cristal and yeah <br>Kept the tray on me like Chris Paul then <br>Drinkin' Ace of Spades like it's codeine now <br>Tryna put a million on the whole team now <br>Push through the pain so we can see new life <br>So all the ladies havin' babies, see a sacrifice <br>Mama had four kids, but she's a lesbian <br>Had to pretend so long that she's a thespian <br>Had to hide in the closet, so she medicate <br>Society shame and the pain was too much to take <br>Cried tears of joy when you fell in love <br>Don't matter to me if it's a him or her <br>I just wanna see you smile through all the hate <br>Marie Antoinette, baby, let 'em eat cake <br><br>Bad times turn to good memories, smile <br>Even when I'm gone and you remember me, smile <br>Good times never fade away, smile <br>Even if I'm not with you here today, smile <br>Good morn' or evening, friends <br>Smile <br>Here's your friendly announcer <br>Smile <br><br>Far as draft picks, my name did not get called <br>Bet before I go I put a billion on the board <br>Hall of Fame Hov, I did it all without a pen <br>Y'all knew that was comin', I had to remind y'all again, huh <br>Flyin' paper planes through the projects <br>Now the whole projects on my jet <br>Now you see the real in the front row <br>In every one of y'all televised shows <br>Super facts <br>Niggas switched sides, traded pride, we don't do all that <br>A loss ain't a loss, it's a lesson <br>Appreciate the pain, it's a blessin' <br><br>Bad times turn to good memories, smile <br>Even when I'm gone and you remember me, smile <br>Good times never fade away, smile <br>Even if I'm not with you here today, smile <br>Good morn' or evening, friends <br><br>I mastered my aesthetics <br>I know you often heard me wax poetic <br>'Bout bein' back in the Lexus <br>But trust me, that was nothin' <br>A nigga up in the hundreds of millions <br>I have no ceilings, ah, this that feelin', I'm that boy <br>Anita Baker's You Bring Me Joy <br>Slappin' out of the toy, the separation is clear <br>In my rear view mirror, objects is further than they appear <br>Oh yeah, I was born with a pair <br>Playin' for high stakes <br>Norman's Cay, he looked up and out of the Lear <br>How niggas can't relate <br>Fuck a slice of the apple pie, want my own cake <br>In charge of my own fate <br>Respect Jimmy Iovine <br>But he gotta respect the Elohim as a whole new regime <br>And niggas playin' for power, huh <br>So our music is ours <br>Niggas only own houses <br>Ours was, Fuck you, pay me <br>Now it's, Fuck payin' me, I pay you <br>Put the rest away for Blue <br>That blood money, I giggle at it <br>Can't even support my miss's habit <br>Jewelry shoppin' in Paris <br>All y'all jewelers should be embarrassed, huh <br>Blood diamonds drippin' with guilt <br>I still ain't trippin', that's life, winners and losers <br>Drug dealers and abusers, America likes me ruthless <br>My therapist said I relapsed <br>I said, Prehaps I Freudian slipped in European whips <br>God sent me to break the chain <br>I'm the true and livin' <br>God in the flesh, the rest of these niggas is vain <br>A stain on the white suit, inferior IQ <br>Niggas'll rip your shit off TIDAL just to spite you <br>Ahhhh, what did I do <br>'Cept try to free you <br>Niggas'll love you but hate you 'cause they can't be you <br>Dump 'em all in the bayou, uh <br>Everybody wave bye to the guy you thought you could lie to <br>This was meant to be a haiku, huh <br>But my story's too wide to fit inside the line or two <br>Oh, these that drugs <br>Heroin flow, I spaz on the stove <br>This is Hov, no flex zone, nigga, who lied to you <br>Look, you a pedestrian <br>Don't ever question the security I provided you <br>Oh y'all thought I was washed <br>I'm at the cleaners <br>Launderin' dirty money like the Teamsters, huh <br>Shout out to Hoffa back home, he in the church <br>When I heard you got booked, that shit hurt <br>Fear for you, bro, we know the system don't work <br>Take a young nigga's freedom over some dirt <br>Yet it's legal in Colorado <br>Yeah, we deny <br>Black entrepreneurs, free enterprise <br>That's why it's a black market, that's why it's called the trap <br>That's why it's called the projects 'cause it's exactly that <br>All these people was gon' kill me, heh <br>'Cause the more I reveal me, the more they 'fraid of the real me <br>Welcome back Carter, smile <br><br>Living in the shadow <br>Can you imagine what kind of life it is to live <br>In the shadows people see you as happy and free <br>Because that's what you want them to see <br>Living two lives, happy, but not free <br>You live in the shadows for fear of someone hurting your family or the person you love <br>The world is changing and they say it's time to be free <br>But you live with the fear of just being me <br>Living in the shadow feels like the safe place to be <br>No harm for them, no harm for me <br>But life is short, and it's time to be free <br>Love who you love, because life isn't guaranteed <br>Smile]]></content><category term="JAY-Z" label="JAY-Z"/><category term="Smile (Feat. Gloria Carter)" label="Smile (Feat. Gloria Carter)"/></entry></feed>