<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:57+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Total_Eclipse_Of_The_Heart_영화_밴디츠___원곡__보니_타일러/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Total Eclipse Of The Heart (영화 `밴디츠` / 원곡: 보니 타일러) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Total_Eclipse_Of_The_Heart_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%B0%B4%EB%94%94%EC%B8%A0___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B3%B4%EB%8B%88_%ED%83%80%EC%9D%BC%EB%9F%AC/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Total Eclipse Of The Heart (영화 `밴디츠` / 원곡: 보니 타일러) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Turn around <br>Every now and then I get a little bit lonely <br>and you're never coming round. <br>Turn around <br>Every now and then I get a little bit tired <br>of listening to the sound of my tears. <br>Turn around <br>Every now and then I get a little bit nervous <br>that the best of all the years have gone by. <br>Turn around <br>Every now and then I get a little bit terrified <br>and then I see the look in your eyes. <br>Turn around, bright eyes <br>Every now and then I fall apart. <br>Turn around, bright eyes <br>Every now and then I fall apart. <br><br>Turn around <br>Every now and then I get a little bit restless <br>and I dream of something wild <br>Turn around <br>Every now and then I get a little bit helpless <br>and I'm lying like a child in your arms <br>Turn around <br>Every now and then I get a little bit angry <br>and I know I've got to get out and cry <br>Turn around <br>Every now and then I get a little bit terrified <br>but then I see the look in your eyes <br>Turn around, bright eyes <br>Every now and then I fall apart. <br>Turn around, bright eyes <br>Every now and then I fall apart. <br><br>And I need you now tonight <br>and I need you more than ever <br>and if you only hold me tight <br>we'll be holding on forever. <br>And we'll only be making it right 'cause we'll never be wrong. <br>Together we can take it to the end of the line. <br>Your love is like a shadow on me all of the time. <br>I don't know what to do and I'm always in the dark. <br>We're living in a powder keg and giving off sparks. <br>I really need you tonight, <br>forever's gonna start tonight, <br>forever's gonna start tonight. <br><br>Once upon a time I was falling in love <br>but now I'm only falling apart. <br>There's nothing I can do, a total eclipse of the heart. <br>Once upon a time there was light in my life <br>but now there's only love in the dark. <br>Nothing I can say, a total eclipse of the heart. <br><br>Turn around, bright eyes <br>Turn around, bright eyes <br><br>Turn around <br>Every now and then I know you'll never be the boy <br>you always wanted to be. <br>Turn around <br>But every now and then I know you'll always be <br>the only boy who wanted me the way that I am. <br>Turn around <br>Every now and then I know there's no one in the universe <br>as magical and wondrous as you. <br>Turn around <br>Every now and then I know there's nothing any better, <br>there's nothing that I just wouldn't do. <br>Turn around, bright eyes <br>Every now and then I fall apart. <br>Turn around, bright eyes <br>Every now and then I fall apart. <br><br>And I need you now tonight <br>and I need you more than ever <br>and if you only hold me tight <br>we'll be holding on forever. <br>And we'll only be making it right 'cause we'll never be wrong. <br>Together we can take it to the end of the line. <br>Your love is like a shadow on me all of the time. <br>I don't know what to do and I'm always in the dark. <br>We're living in a powder keg and giving off sparks. <br>I really need you tonight, forever's gonna start tonight, <br>forever's gonna start tonight. <br><br>Once upon a time I was falling in love <br>but now I'm only falling apart. <br>There's nothing I can do, <br>a total eclipse of the heart. <br>Once upon a time there was light in my life <br>but now there's only love in the dark. <br>Nothing I can say, a total eclipse of the heart. <br>a total eclipse of the heart, <br>a total eclipse of the heart. <br>Turn around bright eyes <br>Turn around bright eyes, turn around... <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Total Eclipse Of The Heart (영화 `밴디츠` / 원곡: 보니 타일러)" label="Total Eclipse Of The Heart (영화 `밴디츠` / 원곡: 보니 타일러)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Na_Na_Hey_Hey_Kiss_Him_Goodbye_원곡__스팀/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Na Na Hey Hey Kiss Him Goodbye (원곡: 스팀) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Na_Na_Hey_Hey_Kiss_Him_Goodbye_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%8A%A4%ED%8C%80/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Na Na Hey Hey Kiss Him Goodbye (원곡: 스팀) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Na na na na, na na na na, hey hey, goodbye <br><br>He'll never love you, the way that I love you <br>'Cause if he did, no no, he wouldn't make you cry <br>He might be thrillin' baby but a-my love <br>(My love, my love) <br><br>So dog-gone willin', so kiss him <br>(I wanna see you kiss him, wanna see you kiss him) <br>Go on and kiss him goodbye, now <br><br>Na na na na, hey hey, goodbye <br>Na na na na, na na na na, hey hey, goodbye <br><br>Listen to me now <br><br>He's never near you to comfort and cheer you <br>When all those sad tears are fallin' baby from your eyes <br>He might be thrillin' baby but a-my love <br>(My love, my love) <br><br>So dog-gone willin', so kiss him <br>(I wanna see you kiss him, I wanna see you kiss him) <br>Go on and kiss him goodbye, na na na na, na na na <br><br>Na na na na, hey hey, goodbye <br><br>Hey hey, goodbye <br>Na na na na, na na na na, hey hey, goodbye <br>Na na na na, na na na na, hey hey, goodbye <br>Na na na na, na na na na, hey hey, goodbye <br><br>Hey hey, goodbye <br>Na na na na, na na na na, hey hey, goodbye <br>Na na na na, na na na na, hey hey, goodbye <br>Na na na na, na na na na, hey hey, goodbye <br><br>Hey hey, goodbye <br>Na na na na, na na na na, hey hey, goodbye <br>Na na na na, na na na na, hey hey, goodbye <br>Na na na na, na na na na, hey hey, goodbye <br><br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Na Na Hey Hey Kiss Him Goodbye (원곡: 스팀)" label="Na Na Hey Hey Kiss Him Goodbye (원곡: 스팀)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Hands_Up_원곡__오타완/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Hands Up (원곡: 오타완) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Hands_Up_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%98%A4%ED%83%80%EC%99%84/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Hands Up (원곡: 오타완) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hands up, baby, hands up, <br>Gimme your heart, gimme, gimme your heart <br>Gimme gimme <br>Hands up, baby, hands up, <br>Gimme your heart, gimme, gimme <br>All your love, <br>All your love. <br><br>Angel face, I love your smile, <br>Love your ways, I like your style. <br>What can I do to get closer to you? <br>Don't think twice or count to ten. <br>Don't take advice, don't ask me when. <br>Just come my way, simply kiss me and say: <br><br>Hands up, baby, hands up, ... <br>With your head up in the sky, <br>Every day you're walkin' by, <br>Why don't you have the stars looking at me? <br><br>Stop that game, don't waste your time, <br>For all your dreams are matchin' mine, <br>No use to play hide n seek for a week. <br><br>Hands up, baby, hands up,... <br>Let me be your Romeo, your wonder boy, <br>And your super champ. <br>Let me take you to the milky way <br>On a holiday, (on a holiday) <br>Follow me (follow me) <br>why don't you follow me (why don&amp;'t you follow me)? <br>Just come my way simply kiss me and say: <br><br>Hands up, baby, hands up, ... <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Hands Up (원곡: 오타완)" label="Hands Up (원곡: 오타완)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Lay_All_Your_Love_On_Me_영화_맘마미아___원곡__아바/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Lay All Your Love On Me (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Lay_All_Your_Love_On_Me_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%A7%98%EB%A7%88%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%84___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%95%84%EB%B0%94/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Lay All Your Love On Me (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wasn't jealous <br>before we met <br>Now every woman I see <br>is a potential threat <br>And I'm possessive it <br>isn't nice <br>You've heard me saying that <br>smoking was my only vice <br>But now it isn't true <br>Now everything is new <br>And all I've learned <br>has overturned <br>I beg of you <br>Don't go wasting <br>your emotion <br>Lay all your love on me <br>It was I shooting <br>a sitting duck <br>A little small talk a smile <br>and baby I was stuck <br>I still don't know <br>what you've done with me <br>A grown up woman should <br>never fall so easily <br>I feel a kind of fear <br>When I don't have you near <br>Unsatisfied I skip my pride <br>I beg you dear <br>Don't go wasting <br>your emotion <br>Lay all your love on me <br>Don't go sharing <br>your devotion <br>Lay all your love on me <br><br>I've had a few little <br>love affairs <br>They didn't last very <br>long and they've been <br>pretty scarce <br>I used to think that <br>was sensible <br>It makes the truth <br>even more incomprehensible <br>Cause everything is new <br>And everything is you <br>And all I've learned <br>has overturned <br>What can I do <br>Don't go wasting <br>your emotion <br>Lay all your love on me <br>Don't go sharing <br>your devotion <br>Lay all your love on me <br>Don't go wasting <br>your emotion <br>Lay all your love on me <br>Don't go sharing <br>your devotion <br>Lay all your love on me <br>Don't go wasting <br>your emotion]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Lay All Your Love On Me (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)" label="Lay All Your Love On Me (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Superstition_원곡__스티비_원더/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Superstition (원곡: 스티비 원더) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Superstition_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B0%EB%B9%84_%EC%9B%90%EB%8D%94/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Superstition (원곡: 스티비 원더) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Very superstitious, writings on the wall, <br>Very superstitious, ladders bout' to fall, <br>Thirteen month old baby, broke the lookin' glass <br>Seven years of bad luck, the good things in your past <br><br>When you believe in things that you don't understand, <br>Then you suffer, <br>Superstition ain't the way <br><br>Very superstitious, wash your face and hands, <br>Rid me of the problem, do all that you can, <br>Keep me in a daydream, keep me goin' strong, <br>You don't wanna save me, sad is my song <br><br>When you believe in things that you don't understand, <br>Then you suffer, <br>Superstition ain't the way, yeh, yeh <br><br>Very superstitious, nothin' more to say, <br>Very superstitious, the devil's on his way, <br>Thirteen month old baby, broke the lookin' glass, <br>Seven years of bad luck, good things in your past <br><br>When you believe in things that you don't understand, <br>Then you suffer, Superstition ain't the way, no, no, no <br><br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Superstition (원곡: 스티비 원더)" label="Superstition (원곡: 스티비 원더)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Jump_원곡__반_헤일런/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Jump (원곡: 반 헤일런) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Jump_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B0%98_%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%BC%EB%9F%B0/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Jump (원곡: 반 헤일런) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I get up, and nothing gets me down. <br>You got it tough. I've seen the toughest all around. <br>And I know, baby, just how you feel. <br>You've got to roll with the punches to get to what's real <br>Oh can't you see me standing here, <br>I've got my back against the record machine <br>I ain't the worst that you've seen. <br>Oh can't you see what I mean? <br>Might as well jump. Jump! <br>Might as well jump. <br>Go ahead, jump. Jump! <br>Go ahead, jump. <br>Aaa-ohh Hey you! Who said that? <br>Baby how you been? <br>You say you don't know, you won't know until you begin. <br>Well can't you see me standing here, <br>I've got my back against the record machine <br>I ain't the worst that you've seen. <br>Oh can't you see what I mean? <br>Might as well jump. Jump! <br>Go ahead, jump. <br>Might as well jump. Jump! <br>Go ahead, jump. <br><br>Might as well jump. Jump! <br>Go ahead, jump. <br>Get it and jump. Jump! <br>Go ahead, jump. <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Jump (원곡: 반 헤일런)" label="Jump (원곡: 반 헤일런)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Everybody_Wants_To_Rule_The_World_영화_스트레이트_아웃_오브_컴턴___원곡__티어스_포_피어스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Everybody Wants To Rule The World (영화 `스트레이트 아웃 오브 컴턴` / 원곡: 티어스 포 피어스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Everybody_Wants_To_Rule_The_World_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%ED%8A%B8_%EC%95%84%EC%9B%83_%EC%98%A4%EB%B8%8C_%EC%BB%B4%ED%84%B4___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%ED%8B%B0%EC%96%B4%EC%8A%A4_%ED%8F%AC_%ED%94%BC%EC%96%B4%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Everybody Wants To Rule The World (영화 `스트레이트 아웃 오브 컴턴` / 원곡: 티어스 포 피어스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to your life <br>There's no turning back <br>Even while we sleep <br>We will find you <br><br>Acting on your best behaviour <br>Turn your back on mother nature <br>Everybody wants to rule the world <br><br>It's my own design <br>It's my own remorse <br>Help me to decide <br>Help me make the most <br><br>Of freedom and of pleasure <br>Nothing ever lasts forever <br>Everybody wants to rule the world <br><br>There's a room where the light won't find you <br>Holding hands while the walls come tumbling down <br>When they do I'll be right behind you <br><br>So glad we've almost made it <br>So sad they had to fade it <br>Everybody wants to rule the world <br><br>I can't stand this indecision <br>Married with a lack of vision <br>Everybody wants to rule the world <br>Say that you'll never never never never need it <br>One headline why believe it ? <br>Everybody wants to rule the world <br><br>All for freedom and for pleasure <br>Nothing ever lasts forever <br>Everybody wants to rule the world]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Everybody Wants To Rule The World (영화 `스트레이트 아웃 오브 컴턴` / 원곡: 티어스 포 피어스)" label="Everybody Wants To Rule The World (영화 `스트레이트 아웃 오브 컴턴` / 원곡: 티어스 포 피어스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/My_Guy__영화_시스터_액트___원곡__메리_웰스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - My Guy (영화 `시스터 액트` / 원곡: 메리 웰스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/My_Guy__%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%8B%9C%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B0_%EC%95%A1%ED%8A%B8___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%A9%94%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9B%B0%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - My Guy (영화 `시스터 액트` / 원곡: 메리 웰스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing you could say <br>Can tear me away from my guy <br>Nothing you could do <br>'Cause I'm stuck like glue to my guy <br><br><br>I'm stickin' to my guy <br>Like a stamp to a letter <br>Like the birds of a feather <br>We stick together <br>I'm tellin' you from the start <br>I can't be torn apart from my guy <br><br><br>Nothing you can do <br>Could make me untrue to my guy <br>Nothing you could buy <br>Could make me tell a lie to my guy <br><br><br>I gave my guy my word of honor <br>To be faithful and I'm gonna <br>You best be believing <br>I won't be deceiving my guy <br><br><br>As a matter of opinion I think he's tops <br>My opinion is he's the cream of the crop <br>As a matter of taste to be exact <br>He's my ideal as a matter of fact <br><br><br>No muscle bound man <br>Could take my hand from my guy <br>No handsome face <br>Could ever take the place of my guy <br>He may not be a movie star <br>But when it comes to being happy we are <br>There's not a man today <br>Who could take me away from my guy <br><br><br>No muscle bound man <br>Could take my hand from my guy <br>No handsome face <br>Could ever take the place of my guy <br>He may not be a movie star <br>But when it comes to being happy we are <br>There's not a man today <br>Who could take me away from my guy <br><br><br>There's not a man today <br>Who could take me away from my guy <br>(Tell me more) <br>There's not a man today <br>Who could take me away from my guy <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="My Guy (영화 `시스터 액트` / 원곡: 메리 웰스)" label="My Guy (영화 `시스터 액트` / 원곡: 메리 웰스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Young_Turks_원곡__로드_스튜어트/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Young Turks (원곡: 로드 스튜어트) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Young_Turks_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%A1%9C%EB%93%9C_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%9C%EC%96%B4%ED%8A%B8/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Young Turks (원곡: 로드 스튜어트) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Billy left his home with a dollar in his pocket and a head full of dreams. <br>He said somehow, some way, it's gotta get better than this. <br>Patti packed her bags, left a note for her momma, she was just seventeen, <br>there were tears in her eyes when she kissed her little sister goodbye. <br><br>They held each other tight as they drove on through the night they were so exited. <br>We got just one shot of life, let's take it while we're still not afraid. <br>Because life is so brief and time is a thief when you're undecided. <br>And like a fistful of sand, it can slip right through your hands. <br><br>Young hearts be free tonight. Time is on your side, <br>Don't let them put you down, don't let 'em push you around, <br>don't let 'em ever change your point of view. <br><br>Paradise was closed so they headed for the coast in a blissful manner. <br>They took a tworoom apartment that was jumping ev'ry night of the week. <br>Happiness was found in each other's arms as expected, yeah <br>Billy pierced his ears, drove a pickup like a lunatic, ooh! <br><br>Young hearts be free tonight.Time is on your side, <br>Don't let them put you down, don't let 'em push you around, <br>don't let 'em ever change your point of view. <br><br>Young hearts be free tonight.Time is on your side. <br><br>Billy wrote a letter back home to Patti's parents tryin' to explain. <br>He said we're both real sorry that it had to turn out this way. <br>But there ain't no point in talking when there's nobody list'ning so we just ran away <br>Patti gave birth to a ten pound baby boy, yeah! <br><br>Young hearts be free tonight, time is on your side. <br>Young hearts be free tonight, time is on your side. <br>Young hearts be free tonight, time in on your side. <br><br>Young hearts gotta run free, be free, live free <br>Time is on, time is on your side <br>Time, time, time, time is on your side <br>is on your side <br>is on your side <br>is on your side <br>Young heart be free tonight <br>tonight, tonight, tonight, tonight, tonight, yeah]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Young Turks (원곡: 로드 스튜어트)" label="Young Turks (원곡: 로드 스튜어트)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Chiquitita_영화_맘마미아___원곡__아바/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Chiquitita (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Chiquitita_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%A7%98%EB%A7%88%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%84___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%95%84%EB%B0%94/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Chiquitita (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Chiquitita, tell me what's wrong <br>You're enchained by your own sorrow <br>In your eyes there is no hope for tomorrow <br>How I hate to see you like this <br>There is no way you can deny it <br>I can see that you're oh so sad, so quiet <br><br>Chiquitita, tell me the truth <br>I'm a shoulder you can cry on <br>Your best friend, I'm the one you must rely on <br>You were always sure of yourself <br>Now I see you've broken a feather <br>I hope we can patch it up together <br><br>Chiquitita, you and I know <br>How the heartaches come and they go and the scars they're leaving <br>You'll be dancing once again and the pain will end <br>You will have no time for grieving <br>Chiquitita, you and I cry <br>But the sun is still in the sky and shining above you <br>Let me hear you sing once more like you did before <br>Sing a new song, Chiquitita <br>Try once more like you did before <br>Sing a new song, Chiquitita <br><br>So the walls came tumbling down <br>And your love's a blown out candle <br>All is gone and it seems too hard to handle <br>Chiquitita, tell me the truth <br>There is no way you can deny it <br>I see that you're oh so sad, so quiet <br><br>Chiquitita, you and I know <br>How the heartaches come and they go and the scars they're leaving <br>You'll be dancing once again and the pain will end <br>You will have no time for grieving <br>Chiquitita, you and I cry <br>But the sun is still in the sky and shining above you <br>Let me hear you sing once more like you did before <br>Sing a new song, Chiquitita <br>Try once more like you did before <br>Sing a new song, Chiquitita <br>Try once more like you did before <br>Sing a new song, Chiquitita]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Chiquitita (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)" label="Chiquitita (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Shes_Like_The_Wind_영화_더티_댄싱___원곡__패트릭_스웨이지/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - She`s Like The Wind (영화 `더티 댄싱` / 원곡: 패트릭 스웨이지) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Shes_Like_The_Wind_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%8D%94%ED%8B%B0_%EB%8C%84%EC%8B%B1___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%ED%8C%A8%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AD_%EC%8A%A4%EC%9B%A8%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80/" title="World Pop Orchestra - She`s Like The Wind (영화 `더티 댄싱` / 원곡: 패트릭 스웨이지) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She's like the wind, <br>Through my tree <br>She rides the night <br>Next to me <br><br>She leads me through moonlight <br>Only to burn me with the sun <br>She's taken my heart <br>But she doesn't know what she's done <br><br>Feel her breath in my face <br>Her body close to me <br>Can't look in her eyes <br>She's out of my league <br><br>Just a fool to believe <br>I have anything she needs <br>She's like the wind <br><br>I look in the mirror <br>And all I see <br>Is a young old man <br>With only a dream <br>Am I just fooling myself <br>That she'll stop the pain? <br>Living without her <br>I'd go insane! <br><br>I feel her breath in my face <br>Her body close to me <br>Can't look in her eyes <br>She's out of my league <br><br>Just a fool to believe <br>I have anything she needs <br>She's like the wind <br><br>I feel your breath in my face <br>Your body close to me <br>Can't look in your eyes <br>You're out of my league <br><br>Just a fool to believe (Just a fool to believe) <br>She's like the wind <br><br>(Just a fool to believe) Just a fool to believe <br>(She's like the wind) <br><br>Just a fool to believe (Just a fool to believe) <br>She's like the wind <br><br>(Just a fool to believe) Just a fool to believe <br>She's like the wind <br><br>(Just a fool...she's like the wind) <br><br>(She's like the wind) <br><br>(Just a fool...she's like the wind) <br>(Just a fool...)]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="She`s Like The Wind (영화 `더티 댄싱` / 원곡: 패트릭 스웨이지)" label="She`s Like The Wind (영화 `더티 댄싱` / 원곡: 패트릭 스웨이지)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Kokomo_영화_칵테일___원곡__비치_보이스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Kokomo (영화 `칵테일` / 원곡: 비치 보이스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Kokomo_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%B9%B5%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%BC___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B9%84%EC%B9%98_%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Kokomo (영화 `칵테일` / 원곡: 비치 보이스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Aruba, Jamaica, oh I want to take ya <br>Bermuda, Bahama, come on pretty mama <br>Key Largo, Montego, baby why don't we go, Jamaica <br><br>Off the Florida Keys, there's a place called Kokomo <br>That's where you want to go to get away from it all <br>Bodies in the sand, tropical drink melting in your hand <br>We'll be falling in love to the rhythm of a steel drum band <br>Down in Kokomo <br><br>Aruba, Jamaica, oh I want to take you to <br>Bermuda, Bahama, come on pretty mama <br>Key Largo, Montego, baby why don't we go <br>oh I want to take you down to <br>Kokomo, we'll get there fast and then we'll take it slow <br>That's where we want to go, way down in Kokomo <br><br>Martinique, that Montserrat mystique <br><br>We'll put out to sea and we'll perfect our chemistry <br>And by and by we'll defy a little bit of gravity <br>Afternoon delight, cocktails and moonlit nights <br>That dreamy look in your eye, give me a tropical contact high <br>Way down in Kokomo <br><br>Aruba, Jamaica, oh I want to take you to <br>Bermuda, Bahama, come on pretty mama <br>Key Largo, Montego, baby why don't we go <br>oh I want to take you down to <br>Kokomo, we'll get there fast and then we'll take it slow <br>That's where we want to go, way down in Kokomo <br><br>Port au Prince, I want to catch a glimpse <br><br>Everybody knows a little place like Kokomo <br>Now if you want to go and get away from it all <br>Go down to Kokomo <br><br>Aruba, Jamaica, oh I want to take you to <br>Bermuda, Bahama, come on pretty mama <br>Key Largo, Montego, baby why don't we go <br>oh I want to take you down to <br>Kokomo, we'll get there fast and then we'll take it slow <br>That's where we want to go, way down in Kokomo <br><br>Aruba, Jamaica, oh I want to take you to <br>Bermuda, Bahama, come on pretty mama <br>Key Largo, Montego, baby why don't we go]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Kokomo (영화 `칵테일` / 원곡: 비치 보이스)" label="Kokomo (영화 `칵테일` / 원곡: 비치 보이스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/I_Just_Died_In_Your_Arms_Tonight_원곡__커팅_크루/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - (I Just) Died In Your Arms Tonight (원곡: 커팅 크루) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/I_Just_Died_In_Your_Arms_Tonight_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%BB%A4%ED%8C%85_%ED%81%AC%EB%A3%A8/" title="World Pop Orchestra - (I Just) Died In Your Arms Tonight (원곡: 커팅 크루) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh I, I just died in your arms tonight <br>It must have been something you said <br>I just died in your arms tonight <br><br>I keep looking for something I can't get <br>Broken hearts lie all around me <br>And I don't see an easy way to get out of this <br><br>Her diary, it sits by the bedside table <br>The curtains are closed, the cat's in the cradle <br>Who would've thought that a boy like me could come to this <br><br>Oh I, I just died in your arms tonight <br>It must've been something you said <br>I just died in your arms tonight <br><br>Oh I, I just died in your arms tonight <br>It must've been some kind of kiss <br>I should've walked away <br><br>Is there any just cause for feeling like this? <br>On the surface I'm a name on a list <br>I try to be discreet, but then blow it again <br><br>I've lost and found, it's my final mistake <br>She's loving by proxy, no give and all take <br>'Cause I've been thrilled to fantasy one too many times <br><br>Oh I, I just died in your arms tonight <br>It must've been something you said <br>I just died in your arms tonight <br><br>Oh I, I just died in your arms tonight <br>It must've been some kind of kiss <br>I should've walked away <br><br>It was a long hot night <br>She made it easy, she made it feel right <br>But now it's over, the moment has gone <br>I followed my hands not my head, I know I was wrong <br><br>Oh I, I just died in your arms tonight <br>It must've been something you said <br>I just died in your arms tonight <br><br>Oh I, I just died in your arms tonight <br>It must've been some kind of kiss <br>I should've walked away <br><br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="(I Just) Died In Your Arms Tonight (원곡: 커팅 크루)" label="(I Just) Died In Your Arms Tonight (원곡: 커팅 크루)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/True_영화_미녀_삼총사___원곡__스팬다우_발레/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - True (영화 `미녀 삼총사` / 원곡: 스팬다우 발레) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/True_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%AF%B8%EB%85%80_%EC%82%BC%EC%B4%9D%EC%82%AC___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%8A%A4%ED%8C%AC%EB%8B%A4%EC%9A%B0_%EB%B0%9C%EB%A0%88/" title="World Pop Orchestra - True (영화 `미녀 삼총사` / 원곡: 스팬다우 발레) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(Ha-ha-ha, ha-ah-hi) <br>(Ha-ha-ha, ha-ah-hi) <br><br>So true <br>Funny how it seems <br>Always in time, but never in line for dreams <br>Head over heels when toe to toe <br>This is the sound of my soul <br>This is the sound <br><br>I bought a ticket to the world <br>But now I've come back again <br>Why do I find it hard to write the next line? <br>Oh, I want the truth to be said <br><br>(Ha-ha-ha, ha-ah-hi) <br>I know this much is true <br>(Ha-ha-ha, ha-ah-hi) <br>I know this much is true <br><br>With a thrill in my head and a pill on my tongue <br>Dissolve the nerves that have just begun <br>Listening to Marvin (All night long) <br>This is the sound of my soul <br>This is the sound <br><br>Always slipping from my hands <br>Sand's a time of its own <br>Take your seaside arms and write the next line <br>Oh, I want the truth to be known <br><br>(Ha-ha-ha, ha-ah-hi) <br>I know this much is true <br>(Ha-ha-ha, ha-ah-hi) <br>I know this much is true <br><br>I bought a ticket to the world <br>But now I've come back again <br>Why do I find it hard to write the next line? <br>Oh, I want the truth to be said <br><br>(Ha-ha-ha, ha-ah-hi) <br>I know this much is true <br>(Ha-ha-ha, ha-ah-hi) <br>I know this much is true <br><br>This much is true <br><br>(This much is a-true-oo) <br>(This much is a-true-oo-oo) <br><br>I know, I know, I know this much is true <br>(This much is a-true-oo) <br>(This much is a-true-oo-oo) <br><br>(This much is a-true-oo) <br>(Ha-ha-ha, ha-ah-hi) <br>(This much is a true-oo-oo) <br>I know this much is true <br>(This much is a-true-oo) <br>(Ha-ha-ha, ha-ah-hi) <br>(This much is a true-oo-oo) <br>Know this much is true <br>(This much is a-true-oo) <br>(Ha-ha-ha, ha-ah-hi) <br>(This much is a-true-oo-oo) <br>(Know this much is true) <br>I know, I know, I know this much is true]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="True (영화 `미녀 삼총사` / 원곡: 스팬다우 발레)" label="True (영화 `미녀 삼총사` / 원곡: 스팬다우 발레)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Nothings_Gonna_Stop_Us_Now_영화_마네킨___원곡__스타쉽/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Nothing`s Gonna Stop Us Now (영화 `마네킨` / 원곡: 스타쉽) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Nothings_Gonna_Stop_Us_Now_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%A7%88%EB%84%A4%ED%82%A8___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80%EC%89%BD/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Nothing`s Gonna Stop Us Now (영화 `마네킨` / 원곡: 스타쉽) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Looking in your eyes I see a paradise <br>This world that I've found <br>Is too good to be true <br>Standing here beside you <br>Want so much to give you <br>This love in my heart that I'm feeling for you <br><br>Let 'em say we're crazy, I don't care about that <br>Put your hand in my hand baby <br>Don't ever look back <br>Let the world around us just fall apart <br>Baby we can make it if we're heart to heart <br><br>And we can build this dream together <br>Standing strong forever <br>Nothing's gonna stop us now <br>And if this world runs out of lovers <br>We'll still have each other <br>Nothing's gonna stop us, nothing's gonna stop us now <br><br>I'm so glad I found you <br>I'm not gonna lose you <br>Whatever it takes I will stay here with you <br>Take it to the good times <br>See it through the bad times <br>Whatever it takes is what I'm gonna do <br><br>Let 'em say we're crazy, what do they know <br>Put your arms around me baby <br>Don't ever let go <br>Let the world around us just fall apart <br>Baby we can make it if we're heart to heart <br><br>And we can build this dream together <br>Standing strong forever <br>Nothing's gonna stop us now <br>And if this world runs out of lovers <br>We'll still have each other <br>Nothing's gonna stop us, nothing's gonna stop us <br><br>Ooh, all that I need is you <br>All that I ever need <br>And all that I want to do <br>Is hold you forever, ever and ever, hey <br><br>And we can build this dream together <br>Standing strong forever <br>Nothing's gonna stop us now <br>And if this world runs out of lovers <br>We'll still have each other <br>Nothing's gonna stop us <br>Nothing's gonna stop us, who <br><br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Nothing`s Gonna Stop Us Now (영화 `마네킨` / 원곡: 스타쉽)" label="Nothing`s Gonna Stop Us Now (영화 `마네킨` / 원곡: 스타쉽)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Hey_원곡__훌리오_이글레시아스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Hey (원곡: 훌리오 이글레시아스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Hey_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%ED%9B%8C%EB%A6%AC%EC%98%A4_%EC%9D%B4%EA%B8%80%EB%A0%88%EC%8B%9C%EC%95%84%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Hey (원곡: 훌리오 이글레시아스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey! no vayas presumiendo por ah <br>diciendo que no puede estar sin tit <br>que sabes de mi. Hey! ya sque a tite <br>gusta presumir decir a los amigos <br>que sin ti ya no puedo vivir. <br><br>Hey! no creas que te haces un favor <br>cuando hablas a la gente de mi amory <br>te burlas de mi. <br><br>Hey! que hay veces que es mejor querer <br>as que ser querido y no poder sentir <br>lo que siento por ti. <br><br>Ya ves tnunca me has querido ya lo ves <br>que nunca he sido tuyo ya lo se fue so <br>por orgullo ese querer <br><br>Ya ves de que te vale ahora presumir <br>ahora que no estoy ya junto a ti <br>que les dir de mi. <br><br>Hey! recuerdo que ganabas siempre tque <br>hacs de ese triunfo una virtud <br>yo era sombra y tluz. <br><br>Hey! no se si ttambi recordar <br>que siempre que intentaba hacer la paz <br>yo era un ren tu mar. <br><br>Ya ves tnunca me has querido ya lo ves <br>que nunca he sido tuyo ya lo se <br>fue so por orgullo ese querer <br><br>Ya ves de que te vale ahora presumir <br>ahora que no estoy ya junto a ti <br>que les dir de mi. <br><br>Hey! ahora que ya todo termin <br>que como siempre soy el perdedor <br>cuando pienses en mi. <br><br>Hey! no creas que te guardo alg rencor <br>es siempre feliz quien am ese siempre fui yo. <br><br>Ya ves de que te vale ahora presumir <br>ahora que no estoy ya junto a ti <br>que les dir de mi <br>Ya ves tnunca me has querido ya lo ves <br>que nunca he sido tuyo ya lo se <br>fue so por orgullo ese querer <br>Ya ves tnunca me has querido ya lo ves <br>que nunca he sido tuyo ya lo se <br>fue so por orgullo ese querer]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Hey (원곡: 훌리오 이글레시아스)" label="Hey (원곡: 훌리오 이글레시아스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Faith_원곡__조지_마이클/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Faith (원곡: 조지 마이클) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Faith_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%A1%B0%EC%A7%80_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B4%ED%81%B4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Faith (원곡: 조지 마이클) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well I guess it would be nice <br>If I could touch your body <br>I know not everybody <br>Has got a body like you <br><br>But I've got to think twice <br>Before I give my heart away <br>And I know all the games you play <br>Because I play them too <br><br>Oh but I <br>Need some time off from that emotion <br>Time to pick my heart up off the floor <br>Oh and when that love comes down <br>Without devotion <br>Well it takes a strong man baby <br>But I'm showing you the door <br><br>'Cause I gotta have faith <br>I gotta have faith <br>'Cause I gotta have faith, faith <br>'Cause I gotta have faith, faith, faith <br><br>Baby, <br>I know you're asking me to stay <br>Say please, please, please don't go away <br>You say I'm giving you the blues Maybe <br>You mean every word you say <br>Can't help but think of yesterday <br>And another who tied me down to loverboy rules <br><br>Before this river <br>Becomes an ocean <br>Before you throw my heart back on the floor <br>Oh oh baby I reconsider <br>My foolish notion <br>Well I need someone to hold me <br>But I'll wait for something more <br><br>Yes I've gotta have faith… <br>Mmm, I gotta have faith <br>'Cause I gotta have faith, faith, faith <br>I gotta have faith-a-faith-a-faith <br><br>Before this river <br>Becomes an ocean <br>Before you throw my heart back on the floor <br>Oh oh baby I reconsider <br>My foolish notion <br>Well I need someone to hold me <br>But I'll wait for something more <br><br>Cause I gotta have faith <br>Mmm I gotta have faith <br>Because I got to have faith-a-faith-a-faith <br>I gotta have faith-a-faith-a-faith]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Faith (원곡: 조지 마이클)" label="Faith (원곡: 조지 마이클)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/SOS_영화_맘마미아___원곡__아바/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - S.O.S (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/SOS_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%A7%98%EB%A7%88%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%84___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%95%84%EB%B0%94/" title="World Pop Orchestra - S.O.S (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Where are those happy days <br>They seem so hard to find <br>I tried to reach for you <br>But you have <br>Closed your mind <br>Whatever happened <br>To our love <br>I wish I understood <br>It used to be so nice <br>It used to be so good <br>So when you're near me <br>Darling can't you hear me <br>S O S <br>The love you gave me <br>Nothing else can save me <br>S O S <br>When you're gone <br>How can I even try to go on <br>When you're gone <br>Though I try how can I <br>Carry on <br>You seem so far away <br>Though you are standing near <br>You made me feel alive <br>But something died I fear <br>I really tried to <br>Make it out <br>I wish I understood <br>What happened to our love <br>It used to be so good <br>So when you're near me <br>Darling can't you hear me <br>S O S <br>The love you gave me <br>Nothing else can save me <br>S O S <br>When you're gone <br>How can I even try to go on <br>When you're gone <br>Though I try how can I <br>Carry on <br><br>So when you're near me <br>Darling can't you hear me <br>S O S <br>And the love you gave me <br>Nothing else can save me <br>S O S <br>When you're gone <br>How can I even try to go on <br>When you're gone <br>Though I try how can I <br>Carry on <br>When you're gone <br>How can I even try to go on <br>When you're gone <br>Though I try how can I <br>Carry on]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="S.O.S (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)" label="S.O.S (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Lady_In_Red_영화_워킹_걸___원곡__크리스_디_버그/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - The Lady In Red (영화 `워킹 걸` / 원곡: 크리스 디 버그) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:21:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:21:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Lady_In_Red_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%9B%8C%ED%82%B9_%EA%B1%B8___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%A4_%EB%94%94_%EB%B2%84%EA%B7%B8/" title="World Pop Orchestra - The Lady In Red (영화 `워킹 걸` / 원곡: 크리스 디 버그) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've never seen you looking so lovely as you did tonight, <br>I've never seen you shine so bright, <br>I've never seen so many men ask you if you wanted to dance, <br>They're looking for a little romance, given half a chance, <br>And I have never seen that dress you're wearing, <br>Or the highlights in your hair that catch your eyes, <br>I have been blind; <br><br>The lady in red is dancing with me, cheek to cheek, <br>There's nobody here, it's just you and me, <br>It's where I want to be, <br>But I hardly know this beauty by my side, <br>I'll never forget the way you look tonight; <br><br>I've never seen you looking so gorgeous as you did tonight, <br>I've never seen you shine so bright, you were amazing, <br>I've never seen so many people want to be there by your side, <br>And when you turned to me and smiled, it took my breath away, <br>And I have never had such a feeling, <br>Such a feeling of complete and utter love, as I do tonight; <br><br>The lady in red is dancing with me, cheek to cheek, <br>There's nobody here, it's just you and me, <br>It's where I want to be, <br>But I hardly know this beauty by my side, <br>I'll never forget the way you look tonight; <br><br>I never will forget the way you look tonight... <br>The lady in red, the lady in red, <br>The lady in red, my lady in red, <br><br>I love you... <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="The Lady In Red (영화 `워킹 걸` / 원곡: 크리스 디 버그)" label="The Lady In Red (영화 `워킹 걸` / 원곡: 크리스 디 버그)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Puff_The_Magic_Dragon_원곡__피터_폴_앤_메리/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Puff The Magic Dragon (원곡: 피터, 폴 앤 메리) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Puff_The_Magic_Dragon_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%ED%94%BC%ED%84%B0_%ED%8F%B4_%EC%95%A4_%EB%A9%94%EB%A6%AC/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Puff The Magic Dragon (원곡: 피터, 폴 앤 메리) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Puff the magic dragon lived by the sea <br>And frolicked in the Autumn mist in a land called Hanalee. <br>Little Jackie Paper loved that rascal Puff and brought <br>him strings and sealing wax and other fancy stuff <br><br>Oh, Puff the magic dragon lived by the sea <br>And frolicked in the Autumn mist in a land called Hanalee. <br>Puff the magic dragon lived by the sea <br>And frolicked in the Autumn mist in a land called Hanalee. <br><br>together they would travel on a boat with billowed sails. <br>Jackie kept a lookout perched on Puff's gigantic tail <br>Noble kings and princess would bow when there they came. <br>Pirate ships would lower their flads when Puff <br>roared out his name. <br><br>Oh, Puff the magic dragon lived by the sea <br>And frolicked in the Autumn mist in a land called Hanalee. <br>Puff the magic dragon lived by the sea <br>And frolicked in the Autumn mist in a land called Hanalee. <br><br>A dragon lives forever but not so little boys <br>Painted wings and giants rings make way for other toys. <br>One gray night it happened <br>Jackie Paper came no more <br>And Puff that mighty dragon, he ceased his fearless roar. <br><br>His head was bent in sorrow. <br>Grief scales fell like rain <br>Puff no longer went to play along the cherry lane. <br>Without his lifelong friend, Puff could not be brave. <br>So Puff that mighty dragon, sadly slipped into his cave. <br><br>Oh, Puff the magic dragon lived by the sea <br>And frolicked in the Autumn mist in a land called Hanalee. <br>Puff the magic dragon lived by the sea <br>And frolicked in the Autumn mist in a land called Hanalee.]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Puff The Magic Dragon (원곡: 피터, 폴 앤 메리)" label="Puff The Magic Dragon (원곡: 피터, 폴 앤 메리)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Macho_Man_원곡__빌리지_피플/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Macho Man (원곡: 빌리지 피플) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Macho_Man_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B9%8C%EB%A6%AC%EC%A7%80_%ED%94%BC%ED%94%8C/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Macho Man (원곡: 빌리지 피플) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Body, wanna feel my body, <br>body, baby, such a thrill, my body <br>Body, wanna touch my body, <br>body, baby, it's too much, my body <br>Body, check it out, my body, body, <br>baby, don't you doubt, my body <br>Body, talking about my body, body, <br>baby, checking out my body <br><br>Listen here <br><br>Every man wants to be a macho man <br>To have the kind of body always in demand <br>Joggin' in the mornings, go man go <br>Workouts in the health spa, muscles grow <br>You can best believe me <br>He's a macho man <br>Glad he took you down with anyone you can <br>Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey <br><br>Macho, macho man <br>I gotta be a macho man <br>Macho macho man <br>I gotta be a macho <br><br>Macho, macho man <br>I gotta be a macho man <br>Macho macho man <br>I gotta be a macho <br><br>Body, its so hot, my body, <br>Body, love to pop my body, <br>Body, love to please my body, <br>Body, don't you tease my body, <br>Body, you'll adore my body, <br>Body, come explore my body, <br>Body, made by God, my body, <br>Body, it's so good, my body <br><br>You can tell a macho, he has a funky walk <br>his western shirts and leather, always look so boss <br>Funky with his body, he's a king <br>call him Mister Ego, dig his chains <br>You can best believe that, he's a macho man <br>likes to be the leader, he never dresses grand <br><br>Hey! Hey! Hey, hey, hey! <br>Macho, macho man <br>I've got to be, a macho man <br>Macho, macho man <br>I've got to be a macho! (all right) <br><br>Macho, macho man (yeah, yeah) <br>I've got to be, a macho man <br>Macho, macho man <br>I've got to be a macho! All Right! <br><br>Body, my body, body, wanna feel my body <br>Body, baby, body, body, come and thrill my body <br>Body, baby, body, body, love to funk, my body <br>Body, baby, body, body, it's so hot, my body <br><br>So hot, yeah my body <br>Allright <br><br>Every man ought to be a macho, macho man <br>To live a life of freedom, machos make a stand <br>Have your own lifestyles and ideals <br>Possess the strength of confidence, that's the skill <br>You can best believe that he's a macho man <br>He's the special god son in anybody's land <br>hey, hey, hey, hey, hey <br><br>Macho, macho man <br>I gotta be a macho man <br>Macho macho man <br>I gotta be a macho <br><br>Macho, macho man <br>I gotta be a macho man <br>Macho macho man <br>I gotta be a macho <br><br>Macho, macho man <br>I gotta be a macho man <br>Macho macho man <br>I gotta be a macho <br><br>I gotta be a macho man <br>I gotta be a mucho mucho, macho macho man <br>I gotta be a macho <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Macho Man (원곡: 빌리지 피플)" label="Macho Man (원곡: 빌리지 피플)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Gloria_원곡__로라_브래니건/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Gloria (원곡: 로라 브래니건) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Gloria_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%A1%9C%EB%9D%BC_%EB%B8%8C%EB%9E%98%EB%8B%88%EA%B1%B4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Gloria (원곡: 로라 브래니건) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Gloria, you're always on the run now. <br>Running after somebody, you gotta get him somehow. <br>I think you've got to slow down, before you start to blow it. <br>I think you're headed for a breakdown, so be careful not to show it <br><br>You really don't remember, was it something that he said? <br>All the voices in your head calling, Gloria? <br>Gloria, don't you think you're fallin'? <br>If everybody wants you, why isn't anybody callin'? <br>You don't have to answer <br>Leave them hangin' on the line, oh-oh-oh, calling Gloria <br>Gloria (Gloria), I think they got your number (Gloria) <br>I think they got the alias (Gloria) that you've been living under (Gloria) <br>But you really don't remember, was it something that they said? <br>All the voices in your head calling, Gloria? <br><br>A-ha-ha, a-ha-ha, Gloria, how's it gonna go down? <br>Will you meet him on the main line, or will you catch him on the rebound? <br>Will you marry for the money, take a lover in the afternoon? <br>Feel your innocence slipping away, don't believe it's comin' back soon <br><br>And you really don't remember, was it something that he said? <br>All the voices in your head calling, Gloria? <br>Gloria, don't you think you're fallin'? <br>If everybody wants you, why isn't anybody callin'? <br>You don't have to answer <br>Leave them hangin' on the line, oh-oh-oh, calling Gloria <br>Gloria (Gloria), I think they got your number (Gloria) <br>I think they got the alias (Gloria) that you've been living under (Gloria) <br>But you really don't remember, was it something that they said? <br>Are the voices in your head calling, Gloria? <br><br>(Gloria, Gloria, Gloria, Gloria, Gloria) <br>(Gloria, Gloria, Gloria, Gloria, Gloria) ... <br><br><br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Gloria (원곡: 로라 브래니건)" label="Gloria (원곡: 로라 브래니건)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Super_Trouper_영화_맘마미아___원곡__아바/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Super Trouper (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Super_Trouper_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%A7%98%EB%A7%88%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%84___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%95%84%EB%B0%94/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Super Trouper (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Super trouper beams are gonna blind me <br>But I won't feel blue <br>Like I always do <br>'Cause somewhere in the crowd there's you <br><br>I was sick and tired of everything <br>When I called you last night from Glasgow <br>All I do is eat and sleep and sing <br>Wishing every show was the last show (wishing every show was the last show) <br>So imagine I was glad to hear you're coming(Glad to hear you're coming) <br>Suddenly I feel all right <br>(And suddenly it's gonna be) <br>And it's gonna be so different <br>When I'm on the stage tonight <br><br>Tonight the super trouper lights are gonna find me <br>Shining like the sun (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>Smiling, having fun (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>Feeling like a number one <br>Tonight the super trouper beams are gonna blind me <br>But I won't feel blue (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>Like I always do (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>'Cause somewhere in the crowd there's you <br><br>Facing twenty thousand of your friends <br>How can anyone be so lonely <br>Part of a success that never ends <br>Still I'm thinking about you only (still I'm thinking about you only) <br>There are moments when I think I'm going crazy (Think I'm going crazy) <br>But it's gonna be alright <br>(You'll soon be changing everything) <br>Everything will be so different <br>When I'm on the stage tonight <br><br>Tonight the super trouper lights are gonna find me <br>Shining like the sun (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>Smiling, having fun (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>Feeling like a number one <br>Tonight the super trouper beams are gonna blind me <br>But I won't feel blue (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>Like I always do (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>'Cause somewhere in the crowd there's you <br><br>So I'll be there when you arrive <br>The sight of you will prove to me I'm still alive <br>And when you take me in your arms <br>And hold me tight <br>I know it's gonna mean so much tonight <br><br>Tonight the super trouper lights are gonna find me <br>Shining like the sun (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>Smiling, having fun (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>Feeling like a number one <br>Tonight the super trouper beams are gonna blind me <br>But I won't feel blue (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>Like I always do (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>'Cause somewhere in the crowd there's you <br><br>(Sup-p-per troup-p-per) lights are gonna find me <br>Shining like the sun (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>Smiling, having fun (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>Feeling like a number one <br><br>(Sup-p-per troup-p-per) beams are gonna blind me <br>But I won't feel blue (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>Like I always do (sup-p-per troup-p-per) <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Super Trouper (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)" label="Super Trouper (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Be-Bop-A-Lula_영화_플레전트빌___원곡__진_빈센트/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Be-Bop-A-Lula (영화 `플레전트빌` / 원곡: 진 빈센트) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Be-Bop-A-Lula_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%ED%94%8C%EB%A0%88%EC%A0%84%ED%8A%B8%EB%B9%8C___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%A7%84_%EB%B9%88%EC%84%BC%ED%8A%B8/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Be-Bop-A-Lula (영화 `플레전트빌` / 원곡: 진 빈센트) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, be-bop-a-lula, she's my baby <br>Be-bop-a-lula, I don't mean maybe <br>Be-bop-a-lula, she's my baby <br>Be-bop-a-lula, I don't mean maybe <br>Be-bop-a-lula, she's my baby love <br>My baby love, my baby love <br><br><br>Well, she's the girl in the red blue jeans <br>She's the queen of all the teens <br>She's the one that I know <br>She's the one that loves me so <br><br><br>Say be-bop-a-lula, she's my baby <br>Be-bop-a-lula, I don't mean maybe <br>Be-bop-a-lula, she's my baby <br>Be-bop-a-lula, I don't mean maybe <br>Be-bop-a-lula, she's my baby love <br>My baby love, my baby love <br><br><br>Well, she's the one that gots that beat <br>She's the one with the flyin' feet <br>She's the one that walks around the store <br>She's the one that gets more more more <br><br><br>Be-bop-a-lula, she's my baby <br>Be-bop-a-lula, I don't mean maybe <br>Be-bop-a-lula, she's my baby <br>Be-bop-a-lula, I don't mean maybe <br>Be-bop-a-lula, she's my baby love <br>My baby love, my baby love <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Be-Bop-A-Lula (영화 `플레전트빌` / 원곡: 진 빈센트)" label="Be-Bop-A-Lula (영화 `플레전트빌` / 원곡: 진 빈센트)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Great_Pretender_원곡__플래터스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - The Great Pretender (원곡: 플래터스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Great_Pretender_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%ED%94%8C%EB%9E%98%ED%84%B0%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - The Great Pretender (원곡: 플래터스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh-oh, yes Im the great pretender <br>Pretending that Im doing well <br>My need is such I pretend too much <br>Im lonely but no one can tell <br><br>Oh-oh, yes Im the great pretender <br>Adrift in a world of my own <br>Ive played the game but to my real shame <br>Youve left me to grieve all alone <br><br>Too real is this feeling of make-believe <br>Too real when I feel what my heart cant conceal <br><br>Yes Im the great pretender <br>Just laughin?and gay like a clown <br>I seem to be what Im not, you see <br>Im wearing my heart like a crown <br>Pretending that youre still around <br><br>Too real is this feeling of make-believe <br>Too real when I feel what my heart cant conceal <br><br>Yes Im the great pretender <br>Just laughin?and gay like a clown <br>I seem to be what Im not, you see <br>Im wearing my heart like a crown <br>Pretending that youre still around]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="The Great Pretender (원곡: 플래터스)" label="The Great Pretender (원곡: 플래터스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Its_Raining_Men_영화_브리짓_존스의_일기___원곡__웨더_걸스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - It`s Raining Men (영화 `브리짓 존스의 일기` / 원곡: 웨더 걸스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Its_Raining_Men_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%AC%EC%A7%93_%EC%A1%B4%EC%8A%A4%EC%9D%98_%EC%9D%BC%EA%B8%B0___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%9B%A8%EB%8D%94_%EA%B1%B8%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - It`s Raining Men (영화 `브리짓 존스의 일기` / 원곡: 웨더 걸스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hi (hi), we're your weather girls (uh-huh) <br>And have we got news for you (you better listen) <br>Get ready all you lonely girls <br>And leave those umbrellas at home (all right) <br><br>Humidity is rising (uh rising) <br>Barometer's getting low (how low girl, uh-oh) <br>According to all sources (what sources now) <br>The street's the place to go (we better hurry up) <br>'Cause tonight for the first time (first time) <br>Just about half past 10 (half past 10) <br>For the first time in history <br>It's gonna start raining men (start raining men) <br><br>It's raining men, Hallelujah <br>It's raining men, Amen <br>I'm gonna go out, I'm gonna let myself get <br>Absolutely soaking wet <br>It's raining men, Hallelujah <br>It's raining men, every specimen <br>Tall, blond, dark and lean <br>Rough and tough and strong and mean <br><br>God bless Mother Nature <br>She's a single woman too <br>She took on the heavens <br>And she did what she had to do <br>She fought every angel <br>She rearranged the sky <br>So that each and every woman <br>Could find the perfect guy <br><br>It's raining men, Hallelujah <br>It's raining men, Amen <br>It's raining men, Hallelujah <br>It's raining men, Amen <br><br>I hear stormy weather movin' in <br>'Bout to break it, about to begin <br>Hear the thunder, don't you lose your head <br>Rip up the roof and stay in bed (rip up the roof and stay in bed) <br><br>God bless Mother Nature <br>She's a single woman too <br>She took on the heavens <br>And she did what she had to do <br>She fought every angel <br>She rearranged the sky <br>So that each and every woman <br>Could find the perfect guy <br>Ooh it's raining men down <br><br>Humidity is rising (humidity is rising, yeah it's rising) <br>Barometer's getting low (it's getting low low low low low low low low low) <br>(Oh it's getting low) <br>According to all sources (according to all sources, oh to all sources) <br>The street's the place to go <br>Because tonight for the first time (first time) <br>Just about half past 10 (half past 10) <br>For the first time in history <br>It's gonna start raining men (start raining men) <br><br>It's raining men (woo), Hallelujah <br>It's raining men, Amen <br>It's raining men, Hallelujah <br>It's raining men, Amen <br>It's raining men, Hallelujah <br>It's raining men, Amen <br>It's raining men, Hallelujah <br>Woah woah woah woah woah woah, Amen <br>It's raining men (tall and blond and dark and lean) <br>It's raining men (and rough and tough and strong and mean) <br>It's raining men (come on), Hallelujah <br>It's raining men, Amen <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="It`s Raining Men (영화 `브리짓 존스의 일기` / 원곡: 웨더 걸스)" label="It`s Raining Men (영화 `브리짓 존스의 일기` / 원곡: 웨더 걸스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Ghostbusters_영화_고스트버스터즈___원곡__레이_파커_주니어/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Ghostbusters (영화 `고스트버스터즈` / 원곡: 레이 파커 주니어) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Ghostbusters_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EA%B3%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%B2%84%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B0%EC%A6%88___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_%ED%8C%8C%EC%BB%A4_%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%88%EC%96%B4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Ghostbusters (영화 `고스트버스터즈` / 원곡: 레이 파커 주니어) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If there's something strange <br>In your neighborhood <br>Who you gonna call? <br>Ghostbusters! <br><br>If there's something weird <br>And it don't look good <br>Who you gonna call? <br>Ghostbusters! <br>I ain't 'fraid of no ghost <br>I ain't 'fraid of no ghost <br><br>If you're seeing things <br>Running through your head <br>Who can you call? <br>Ghostbusters! <br><br>An invisible man <br>Sleepin' in your bed <br>Ow, who you gonna call? <br>Ghostbusters! <br><br>I ain't 'fraid of no ghost <br>I ain't 'fraid of no ghost <br><br>Who you gonna call? <br>Ghostbusters! <br><br>If you're all alone <br>Pick up the phone <br>And call <br>Ghostbusters! <br><br>I ain't 'fraid of no ghost <br>Ooh, I hear it likes the girls <br>Hm, I ain't 'fraid of no ghost <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br><br>Who you gonna call? <br>Ghostbusters! <br><br>Mmm, if you've had a dose of a <br>Freaky ghost, baby <br>You better call <br>Ghostbusters! <br>Ow! <br><br>Lemme tell ya something <br>Bustin' makes me feel good! <br><br>I ain't 'fraid of no ghost <br>I ain't 'fraid of no ghost <br><br>Don't get caught alone oh, no <br>Ghostbusters! <br>When it comes through your door <br>Unless you just a-want some more <br>I think you better call <br>Ghostbusters! <br><br>Ow! Who you gonna call? <br>Ghostbusters! <br>Who you gonna call? <br>Ghostbusters! <br>Uh, think you better call <br>Ghostbusters! <br>Ha ha, who you gonna call? <br>Ghostbusters! <br>I can't hear you <br><br>Who you gonna call? <br>Ghostbusters! <br>Louder <br>Ghostbusters! <br>Who you gonna call? <br>Ghostbusters! <br>Who can you call? <br>Ghostbusters! <br>Who you gonna call? <br>Ghostbusters! <br>Uh, it likes the girls too <br>Ghostbusters!]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Ghostbusters (영화 `고스트버스터즈` / 원곡: 레이 파커 주니어)" label="Ghostbusters (영화 `고스트버스터즈` / 원곡: 레이 파커 주니어)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Brown_Eyed_Girl_영화_7월4일생___원곡__밴_모리슨/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Brown Eyed Girl (영화 `7월4일생` / 원곡: 밴 모리슨) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Brown_Eyed_Girl_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_7%EC%9B%944%EC%9D%BC%EC%83%9D___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B0%B4_%EB%AA%A8%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%A8/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Brown Eyed Girl (영화 `7월4일생` / 원곡: 밴 모리슨) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, where did we go <br>Days when the rains came ? <br>Down in the hollow <br>Playing a new game, <br>Laughing and a-running, hey, hey, <br>Skipping and a-jumping <br>In the misty morning fog with <br>Our, our hearts a-thumping <br>And you, my brown-eyed girl, <br>You, my brown-eyed girl. <br><br>Whatever happened <br>To Tuesday and so slow <br>Going down to the old mine with a <br>Transistor radio. <br>Standing in the sunlight laughing <br>Hide behind a rainbow's wall, <br>Slipping and a-sliding <br>All along the waterfall <br>With you, my brown-eyed girl, <br>You, my brown-eyed girl. <br><br>Do you remember when we used to sing <br>Sha la la la la la la la la la la dee dah <br>Just like that <br>Sha la la la la la la la la la la dee dah <br>La dee dah. <br><br>So hard to find my way <br>Now that I'm all on my own. <br>I saw you just the other day, <br>My, how you have grown! <br>Cast my memory back there, Lord, <br>Sometime I'm overcome thinking about <br>Making love in the green grass <br>Behind the stadium <br>With you, my brown-eyed girl, <br>You, my brown-eyed girl. <br><br>Do you remember when we used to sing <br>Sha la la la la la la la la la la dee dah <br>Laying in the green grass <br>Sha la la la la la la la la la la dee dah <br>Dee dah dee dah dee dah dee dah dee dah dee <br>Sha la la la la la la la la la la la la <br>Dee dah la dee dah la dee dah la <br>D-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d...]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Brown Eyed Girl (영화 `7월4일생` / 원곡: 밴 모리슨)" label="Brown Eyed Girl (영화 `7월4일생` / 원곡: 밴 모리슨)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Money_Money_Money_영화_맘마미아___원곡__아바/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Money, Money, Money (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Money_Money_Money_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%A7%98%EB%A7%88%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%84___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%95%84%EB%B0%94/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Money, Money, Money (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I work all night, I work all day, to pay bills I have to pay-Ain't it sad <br>And still there never seems to be a single penny left for me-That's too bad <br>In my dreams I have a plan <br>If I got me a wealthy man <br>I wouldn't have to work at al, I'd fool around and have a ball... <br><br>Money, money, money <br>Must be funny <br>In the rich man's world <br>Money, money, money <br>Always sunny <br>In the rich man's world <br>Aha-ahaaa <br>All the things I could do <br>If I had a little money <br>It's a rich man's world <br><br>It's a rich man's world <br><br>A man like that is hard to find but I can't get him off my mind-Ain't it sad <br>And if he happens to be free I bet he wouldn't fancy me-That's too bad <br>So I must leave, I'll have to go <br>To Las Vegas or Monaco <br>And win a fortune game, my life will never be the same... <br><br>Money, money, money <br>Must be funny <br>In the rich man's world <br>Money, money, money <br>Always sunny <br>In the rich man's world <br>Aha-ahaaa <br>All the things I could do <br>If I had a little money <br>It's a rich man's world <br><br>Money, money, money <br>Must be funny <br>In the rich man's world <br>Money, money, money <br>Always sunny <br>In the rich man's world <br>Aha-ahaaa <br>All the things I could do <br>If I had a little money <br>It's a rich man's world <br><br>It's a rich man's world <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Money, Money, Money (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)" label="Money, Money, Money (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Ive_Been_Loving_You_Too_Long_To_Stop_Now_원곡__오티스_레딩/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - I`ve Been Loving You Too Long (To Stop Now) (원곡: 오티스 레딩) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Ive_Been_Loving_You_Too_Long_To_Stop_Now_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%98%A4%ED%8B%B0%EC%8A%A4_%EB%A0%88%EB%94%A9/" title="World Pop Orchestra - I`ve Been Loving You Too Long (To Stop Now) (원곡: 오티스 레딩) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been loving you too long to stop now <br><br>You are tired and you want to be free <br>My love is growing stronger, as you become a habit to me <br>Ohh, I've been loving you too long <br>I don't wanna stop now <br><br>With you my life has been so wonderful <br>I can't stop now <br>You are tired and your love is growing cold <br>My love is growing stronger as our affair, affair grows old <br>I've been loving you oh, too long <br>I don't want to stop now, ohh, ohh, ohh <br><br>I've been loving you a little too long <br>I don't wanna stop now, ohh, ohh, ohh <br>And don't make me stop now <br>Oh baby <br>I'm down on my knees <br>Please, don't make me stop now <br><br>I love you, I love you, I love you with all my heart <br>And I can't stop now <br>Please, please, please don't make me stop now <br>Talkin' 'bout heart and soul <br>That I love you <br>I love you <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="I`ve Been Loving You Too Long (To Stop Now) (원곡: 오티스 레딩)" label="I`ve Been Loving You Too Long (To Stop Now) (원곡: 오티스 레딩)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Aint_No_Sunshine_영화_노팅_힐___원곡__빌_위더스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Ain`t No Sunshine (영화 `노팅 힐` / 원곡: 빌 위더스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Aint_No_Sunshine_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%85%B8%ED%8C%85_%ED%9E%90___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B9%8C_%EC%9C%84%EB%8D%94%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Ain`t No Sunshine (영화 `노팅 힐` / 원곡: 빌 위더스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ain't no sunshine when she's gone. <br>It's not warm when she's away. <br>Ain't no sunshine when she's gone <br>and she's always gone too long anytime she goes away. <br>Wonder this time where she's gone, <br>wonder if she's gone to stay <br><br>Ain't no sunshine when she's gone <br>and this house just ain't no home anytime she goes away. <br>And I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, <br>I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, <br>I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, <br>I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know <br><br>Hey, I ought to leave the young thing alone, <br>but ain't no sunshine when she's gone, only darkness everyday. <br>Ain't no sunshine when she's gone, <br>and this house just ain't no home anytime she goes away. <br>Anytime she goes away. <br>Anytime she goes away. <br>Anytime she goes away. <br>Anytime she goes away. <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Ain`t No Sunshine (영화 `노팅 힐` / 원곡: 빌 위더스)" label="Ain`t No Sunshine (영화 `노팅 힐` / 원곡: 빌 위더스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Color_Of_The_Night_영화_컬러_오브_나이트___원곡__로렌_크리시티/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - The Color Of The Night (영화 `컬러 오브 나이트` / 원곡: 로렌 크리시티) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Color_Of_The_Night_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%BB%AC%EB%9F%AC_%EC%98%A4%EB%B8%8C_%EB%82%98%EC%9D%B4%ED%8A%B8___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%A1%9C%EB%A0%8C_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%8B%9C%ED%8B%B0/" title="World Pop Orchestra - The Color Of The Night (영화 `컬러 오브 나이트` / 원곡: 로렌 크리시티) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You and I moving in the dark <br>Bodies close but souls apart <br>Shadowed smiles <br>and secrets unrevealed <br>I need to know the way you feel <br>I'll give you everything I am <br>And everything I want to be <br>I'll put it in your hands <br>If you could open up to me oh <br>Can't we ever <br>get beyond this wall <br>'cause all I want is just once <br>To see you in the light <br>But you hide behind <br>The color of the night <br>I can't go on <br>running from the past <br>Lave has torn away this mask <br>And now like clouds <br>like rain I'm drowning and <br>I blame it all on you <br>I'm lost God save me <br>I'll give you everything I am <br>And everything I want to be <br>I'll put it in your hands <br>If you could open up to me oh <br>Can't we ever <br>get beyond this wall <br>'cause all I want is just once <br>To see you in the light <br>But you hide behind <br>The color of the night <br><br>everything I am <br>And everything I want to be <br>I'll Can't we ever <br>get beyond this wall <br>'cause all I want is just once <br>Forever and again <br>I'm waiting for you <br>I'm standing in the light <br>But you hide behind <br>The color of the night <br><br>Please come out from <br>The color of the night]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="The Color Of The Night (영화 `컬러 오브 나이트` / 원곡: 로렌 크리시티)" label="The Color Of The Night (영화 `컬러 오브 나이트` / 원곡: 로렌 크리시티)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Over_The_Rainbow_영화_오즈의_마법사___원곡__주디_갈랜드/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Over The Rainbow (영화 `오즈의 마법사` / 원곡: 주디 갈랜드) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Over_The_Rainbow_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%98%A4%EC%A6%88%EC%9D%98_%EB%A7%88%EB%B2%95%EC%82%AC___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%A3%BC%EB%94%94_%EA%B0%88%EB%9E%9C%EB%93%9C/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Over The Rainbow (영화 `오즈의 마법사` / 원곡: 주디 갈랜드) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Somewhere over the rainbow way up high <br>There's a land that I heard of once in a lullaby <br>Somewhere over the rainbow skies are blue <br>And the dreams that you dare to dream really do come true <br><br>Someday I'll wish upon a star <br>And wake up where the clouds are far <br>Behind me <br>Where troubles melt like lemon drops <br>Away above the chimney tops <br>That's where you'll find me <br><br>Somewhere over the rainbow bluebirds fly <br>Birds fly over the rainbow. Why then, oh, why can't I? <br><br>If happy little bluebirds fly <br>Beyond the rainbow why, oh, why can't I?]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Over The Rainbow (영화 `오즈의 마법사` / 원곡: 주디 갈랜드)" label="Over The Rainbow (영화 `오즈의 마법사` / 원곡: 주디 갈랜드)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/My_Girl_영화_마이_걸___원곡__템테이션스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - My Girl (영화 `마이 걸` / 원곡: 템테이션스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/My_Girl_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B1%B8___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%ED%85%9C%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4%EC%85%98%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - My Girl (영화 `마이 걸` / 원곡: 템테이션스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've got sunshine on a cloudy day. <br>When it's cold outside I've got the month of May. <br><br>I guess you'd say <br>What can make me feel this way? <br>My girl (my girl, my girl) <br>Talkin' 'bout my girl (my girl). <br><br>I've got so much honey the bees envy me. <br>I've got a sweeter song than the birds in the trees. <br><br>Well, I guess you'd say <br>What can make me feel this way? <br>My girl (my girl, my girl) <br>Talkin' 'bout my girl (my girl). <br><br>Hey hey hey <br>Hey hey hey <br>Ooooh. <br><br>I don't need no money, fortune or fame. <br>I've got all the riches, baby, one man can claim. <br><br>Well, I guess you'd say <br>What can make me feel this way? <br>My girl (my girl, my girl) <br>Talkin' 'bout my girl (my girl). <br><br>I've got sunshine on a cloudy day <br>With my girl. <br>I've even got the month of May <br>With my girl <br>Talkin' 'bout <br>Talkin' 'bout <br>Talkin' 'bout <br>My girl <br>Ooooh <br>My girl <br>As long as I can talk about my girl... <br><br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="My Girl (영화 `마이 걸` / 원곡: 템테이션스)" label="My Girl (영화 `마이 걸` / 원곡: 템테이션스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Have_I_Told_You_Lately_영화_어느_멋진_날___원곡__로드_스튜어트/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Have I Told You Lately (영화 `어느 멋진 날` / 원곡: 로드 스튜어트) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Have_I_Told_You_Lately_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%96%B4%EB%8A%90_%EB%A9%8B%EC%A7%84_%EB%82%A0___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%A1%9C%EB%93%9C_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%9C%EC%96%B4%ED%8A%B8/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Have I Told You Lately (영화 `어느 멋진 날` / 원곡: 로드 스튜어트) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Have I told you lately that I love you <br>Have I told you there's no one else above you <br>Fill my heart with gladness <br>take away all my sadness <br>ease my troubles that's what you do <br><br>For the morning sun in all it's glory <br>greets the day with hope and comfort too <br>You fill my life with laughter <br>and somehow you make it better <br>ease my troubles that's what you do <br>There's a love that's divine <br>and it's yours and it's mine like the sun <br>And at the end of the day <br>we should give thanks and pray <br>to the one, to the one <br><br>Have I told you lately that I love you <br>Have I told you there's no one else above you <br>Fill my heart with gladness <br>take away all my sadness <br>ease my troubles that's what you do <br><br>There's a love that's divine <br>and it's yours and it's mine like the sun <br>And at the end of the day <br>we should give thanks and pray <br>to the one, to the one <br><br>And have I told you lately that I love you <br>Have I told you there's no one else above you <br>You fill my heart with gladness <br>take away my sadness <br>ease my troubles that's what you do <br>Take away all my sadness <br>fill my life with gladness <br>ease my troubles that's what you do <br>Take away all my sadness <br>fill my life with gladness <br>ease my troubles that's what you do <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Have I Told You Lately (영화 `어느 멋진 날` / 원곡: 로드 스튜어트)" label="Have I Told You Lately (영화 `어느 멋진 날` / 원곡: 로드 스튜어트)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Faithfully_원곡__저니/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Faithfully (원곡: 저니) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Faithfully_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%A0%80%EB%8B%88/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Faithfully (원곡: 저니) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Highway run <br>Into the midnight sun <br>Wheels go round and round <br>You're on my mind <br>Restless hearts <br>Sleep alone tonight <br>Sending all my love <br>Along the wire <br><br>They say that the road <br>Ain't no place to start a family <br>Right down the line <br>It's been you and me <br>And lovin' a music man <br>Ain't always what it's supposed to be <br>Oh, girl, you stand by me <br>I'm forever yours <br>Faithfully <br><br>Circus life <br>Under the big top world <br>We all need the clowns <br>To make us smile <br>Through space and time <br>Always another show <br>Wondering where I am <br>Lost without you <br><br>And being apart <br>Ain't easy on this love affair <br>Two strangers learn to fall in love again <br>I get the joy of rediscovering you <br>Oh, girl, you stand by me <br>I'm forever yours <br>Faithfully <br><br>Whooa, oh-oh-ooh <br>Whooa, oh-oh-ooh, oh <br>Whooa, oh-oh-oh, oh-whoooooa-oh <br>Faithfully <br>I'm still yours <br><br>I'm forever yours <br>Ever yours <br>Faithfully]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Faithfully (원곡: 저니)" label="Faithfully (원곡: 저니)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/And_I_Love_You_So_영화_유리의_성_B형_남자친구___원곡__엘비스_프레슬리/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - And I Love You So (영화 `유리의 성`, `B형 남자친구` / 원곡: 엘비스 프레슬리) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/And_I_Love_You_So_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%9C%A0%EB%A6%AC%EC%9D%98_%EC%84%B1_B%ED%98%95_%EB%82%A8%EC%9E%90%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%97%98%EB%B9%84%EC%8A%A4_%ED%94%84%EB%A0%88%EC%8A%AC%EB%A6%AC/" title="World Pop Orchestra - And I Love You So (영화 `유리의 성`, `B형 남자친구` / 원곡: 엘비스 프레슬리) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And I love you so, <br>The people ask me how, <br>How I've lived till now <br>I tell them I don't know <br><br>I guess they understand <br>How lonely life has been <br>But life began again <br>The day you took my hand <br><br>And yes I know how lonely life can be <br>Shadows follow me <br>The night won't set me free <br>But I don't let the evening get me down <br>Now that you're around me <br><br>And you love me too <br>Your thoughts are just for me <br>You set my spirit free <br>I'm happy that you do <br><br>The look at life is brief <br>Once the page is read <br>All but love is dead <br>This is my believe]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="And I Love You So (영화 `유리의 성`, `B형 남자친구` / 원곡: 엘비스 프레슬리)" label="And I Love You So (영화 `유리의 성`, `B형 남자친구` / 원곡: 엘비스 프레슬리)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Everything_I_Do_I_Do_It_For_You_영화_로빈훗___원곡__브라이언_아담스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - (Everything I Do) I Do It For You (영화 `로빈훗` / 원곡: 브라이언 아담스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Everything_I_Do_I_Do_It_For_You_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%A1%9C%EB%B9%88%ED%9B%97___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EC%96%B8_%EC%95%84%EB%8B%B4%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - (Everything I Do) I Do It For You (영화 `로빈훗` / 원곡: 브라이언 아담스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look into my eyes, you will see <br>What you mean to me <br>Search your heart, search your soul <br>And when you find me there <br>You'll search no more <br><br>Don't tell me, it's not worth tryin' for <br>You can't tell me, it's not worth dyin' for <br>You know it's true <br>Everything I do, I do it for you <br><br>Look into your heart, you will find <br>There's nothin' there to hide <br>Take me as I am, take my life <br>I would give it all, I would sacrifice <br><br>Don't tell me it's not worth fightin' for <br>I can't help it, there's nothin' I want more <br>You know it's true <br>Everything I do, I do it for you, oh yeah <br><br>There's no love, like your love <br>And no other could give more love <br>There's nowhere, unless you're there <br>All the time, all the way yeah <br><br>Look into your heart baby <br>Oh yeah <br><br>Oh, you can't tell me it's not worth tryin' for <br>I can't help it, there's nothin' I want more <br><br>Yeah I would fight for you <br>I'd lie for you <br>Walk the wire for you <br>Yeah I'd die for you <br><br>You know it's true <br>Everything I do, ohh, I do it for you <br><br>Everything I do darling <br>We will see it through <br>We will see it through, yeah <br>Yeah, just look into your heart <br>You can't tell me you'll die for love <br>Oh yeah, I'll be there <br>I'm goin' all the way, all the way <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="(Everything I Do) I Do It For You (영화 `로빈훗` / 원곡: 브라이언 아담스)" label="(Everything I Do) I Do It For You (영화 `로빈훗` / 원곡: 브라이언 아담스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Unforgettable_영화_왓치맨___원곡__넷_킹_콜/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Unforgettable (영화 `왓치맨` / 원곡: 넷 킹 콜) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Unforgettable_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%99%93%EC%B9%98%EB%A7%A8___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%84%B7_%ED%82%B9_%EC%BD%9C/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Unforgettable (영화 `왓치맨` / 원곡: 넷 킹 콜) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Unforgettable, that's what you are <br>Unforgettable though near or far <br>Like a song of love that clings to me <br>How the thought of you does things to me <br>Never before has someone been more <br><br>Unforgettable in every way <br>And forever more, that's how you'll stay <br>That's why, darling, it's incredible <br>That someone so unforgettable <br>Thinks that I am unforgettable too <br><br>Unforgettable in every way <br>And forever more, that's how you'll stay <br>That's why, darling, it's incredible <br>That someone so unforgettable <br>Thinks that I am unforgettable too <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Unforgettable (영화 `왓치맨` / 원곡: 넷 킹 콜)" label="Unforgettable (영화 `왓치맨` / 원곡: 넷 킹 콜)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Thank_You_For_The_Music_영화_맘마미아___원곡__아바/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Thank You For The Music (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Thank_You_For_The_Music_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%A7%98%EB%A7%88%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%84___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%95%84%EB%B0%94/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Thank You For The Music (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm nothing special, in fact I'm a bit of a bore <br>If I tell a joke, you've probably heard it before <br>But I have a talent, a wonderful thing <br>'Cause everyone listens when I start to sing <br>I'm so grateful and proud <br>All I want is to sing it out loud <br><br>So I say <br>Thank you for the music, the songs I'm singing <br>Thanks for all the joy they're bringing <br>Who can live without it, I ask in all honesty <br>What would life be? <br>Without a song or a dance what are we? <br>So I say thank you for the music <br>For giving it to me <br><br>Mother says I was a dancer before I could walk <br>She says I began to sing long before I could talk <br>And I've often wondered, how did it all start? <br>Who found out that nothing can capture a heart <br>Like a melody can? <br>Well, whoever it was, I'm a fan <br><br>So I say <br>Thank you for the music, the songs I'm singing <br>Thanks for all the joy they're bringing <br>Who can live without it, I ask in all honesty <br>What would life be? <br>Without a song or a dance what are we? <br>So I say thank you for the music <br>For giving it to me <br><br>I've been so lucky, I am the girl with golden hair <br>I wanna sing it out to everybody <br>What a joy, what a life, what a chance! <br><br>Thank you for the music, the songs I'm singing <br>Thanks for all the joy they're bringing <br>Who can live without it, I ask in all honesty <br>What would life be? <br>Without a song or a dance what are we? <br>So I say thank you for the music <br>For giving it to me <br><br>So I say thank you for the music <br>For giving it to me <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Thank You For The Music (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)" label="Thank You For The Music (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/La_Vie_En_Rose_영화_장밋빛_인생___원곡__에디트_피아프/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - La Vie En Rose (영화 `장밋빛 인생` / 원곡: 에디트 피아프) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/La_Vie_En_Rose_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%9E%A5%EB%B0%8B%EB%B9%9B_%EC%9D%B8%EC%83%9D___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%97%90%EB%94%94%ED%8A%B8_%ED%94%BC%EC%95%84%ED%94%84/" title="World Pop Orchestra - La Vie En Rose (영화 `장밋빛 인생` / 원곡: 에디트 피아프) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Des yeux qui font baisser <br>les miens <br>Un rire qui se perd <br>sur sa bouche <br>Voila le portrait sans retouche <br>De l’homme <br>auquel j’appartiens <br>Quand il me prend <br>dans ses bras <br>Il me parle tout bas <br>Je vois la vie en rose <br>Il me dit des mots d’amour <br>Des mots de tous les jours <br>Et ca me fait quelque chose <br>Il est entre dans mon coeur <br>Une part de bonheur <br>Dont je connais la cause <br>C’est lui pour moi moi <br>pour lui dans la vie <br>Il me l’a dit l’a jure <br>pour la vie <br>Et des que je l’apercois <br>Alors je sens en moi <br>Mon coeur qui bat <br>Des nuits d’amour <br>a plus finir <br>Un grand bonheur <br>qui prend sa place <br>Les ennuis <br>les chagrins s’effacent <br>Heureux heureux a en mourir <br>Quand il me prend dans ses bras <br>Il me parle tout bas <br>Je vois la vie en rose <br>Il me dit des mots d’amour <br>Des mots de tous les jours <br>Et ca me fait quelque chose <br>Il est entre dans mon coeur <br>Une part de bonheur <br>Dont je connais la cause <br>C’est toi pour moi moi <br>pour lui dans la vie <br>Il me l’a dit l’a jure pour la vie <br>Et des que je l’apercois <br>Alors je sens en moi <br>Mon coeur qui bat]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="La Vie En Rose (영화 `장밋빛 인생` / 원곡: 에디트 피아프)" label="La Vie En Rose (영화 `장밋빛 인생` / 원곡: 에디트 피아프)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/I_Do_I_Do_I_Do_I_Do_I_Do_드라마_응답하라_1994___영화_맘마미아___원곡__아바/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - I Do, I Do, I Do, I Do, I Do (드라마 `응답하라 1994` / 영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/I_Do_I_Do_I_Do_I_Do_I_Do_%EB%93%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%A7%88_%EC%9D%91%EB%8B%B5%ED%95%98%EB%9D%BC_1994___%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%A7%98%EB%A7%88%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%84___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%95%84%EB%B0%94/" title="World Pop Orchestra - I Do, I Do, I Do, I Do, I Do (드라마 `응답하라 1994` / 영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love me or leave me <br>make your choice <br>but believe me <br>I love you <br>I do I do I do I do I do <br>I can't conceal it <br>don't you see <br>can't you feel it <br>Don't you too <br>I do I do I do I do I do <br>Oh I've been dreaming <br>through my lonely past <br>Now I just made it <br>I found you at last <br>So come on <br>now let's try it <br>I love you <br>can't deny it <br>'Cos it's true <br>I do I do I do I do I do <br><br>Oh no hard feelings <br>between you and me <br>If we can't make it <br>but just wait and see <br>So come on <br>now let's try it <br>I love you <br>can't deny it <br>'Cos it's true <br>I do I do I do I do I do <br>So love me or leave me <br>make your choice <br>but believe me <br>I love you <br>I do I do I do I do I do <br>I can't conceal it <br>don't you see <br>can't you feel it <br>Don't you too <br>I do I do I do I do I do <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="I Do, I Do, I Do, I Do, I Do (드라마 `응답하라 1994` / 영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)" label="I Do, I Do, I Do, I Do, I Do (드라마 `응답하라 1994` / 영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Funkytown_무한도전_거성체조___원곡__립스_잉크/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Funkytown (무한도전 `거성체조` / 원곡: 립스 잉크) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Funkytown_%EB%AC%B4%ED%95%9C%EB%8F%84%EC%A0%84_%EA%B1%B0%EC%84%B1%EC%B2%B4%EC%A1%B0___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%A6%BD%EC%8A%A4_%EC%9E%89%ED%81%AC/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Funkytown (무한도전 `거성체조` / 원곡: 립스 잉크) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Gotta make a <br>move to a town <br>that's right for me <br>Town to keep me movin' <br>Keep me groovin' <br>with some energy <br>Well I talk about it <br>Talk about it <br>Talk about it <br>Talk about it <br>Talk about Talk about <br>Talk about movin <br>Gotta move on <br>Gotta move on <br>Gotta move on <br><br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br><br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br><br>Gotta make a <br>move to a town <br>that's right for me <br>Town to keep me movin' <br>Keep me groovin' <br>with some energy <br>Well I talk about it <br>Talk about it <br>Talk about it <br>Talk about it <br>Talk about Talk about <br>Talk about movin <br>Gotta move on <br>Gotta move on <br>Gotta move on <br><br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br><br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br><br>Won't you take me town <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me town <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me town <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me town <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br>Won't you take me to <br>Funkytown <br><br>take me Won't you take me <br>take me Won't you take me <br>take me Won't you take me <br>take me Won't you take me <br>I won't a go the funkytown <br>I won't a go the funkytown <br>I won't a go the funkytown <br>I won't a go the funkytown <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Funkytown (무한도전 `거성체조` / 원곡: 립스 잉크)" label="Funkytown (무한도전 `거성체조` / 원곡: 립스 잉크)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Jamaica_Farewell_MBC_세시봉_콘서트_1부___원곡__해리_벨라폰테/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Jamaica Farewell (MBC `세시봉 콘서트` 1부 / 원곡: 해리 벨라폰테) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Jamaica_Farewell_MBC_%EC%84%B8%EC%8B%9C%EB%B4%89_%EC%BD%98%EC%84%9C%ED%8A%B8_1%EB%B6%80___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%ED%95%B4%EB%A6%AC_%EB%B2%A8%EB%9D%BC%ED%8F%B0%ED%85%8C/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Jamaica Farewell (MBC `세시봉 콘서트` 1부 / 원곡: 해리 벨라폰테) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Down the way where the nights are gay <br>and the sun shines daily on the mountain's top <br>I took a trip on a sailing ship <br>and when I reached Jamaica I made a stop <br>But I'm sad to say I'm on my way <br>won't be back for many a day <br>my heart is down my head is turning around <br>I've had to leave a little girl in the Kingston town <br><br>Sounds of laughter every where <br>and the dancing girl swinging two and fro <br>I must declare my head is there <br>though I been from maine to Mexico <br>But I'm sad to say I'm on my way <br>won't be back for many a day <br>my heart is down my head is turning around <br>I've had to leave a little girl in the Kingston town <br><br>Down at the market you can hear <br>ladies cry out while on their heads they bear <br>Akkisai sort fish are nice <br>and the rhum are fine every time a year <br>But I'm sad to say I'm on my way <br>won't be back for many a day <br>my heart is down my head is turning around <br>I've had to leave a little girl in the Kingston town <br><br>Down the way where the nights are gay <br>and the sun shines daily on the mountain's top <br>I took a trip on a sailing ship <br>and when I reached Jamaica I made a stop <br>But I'm sad to say I'm on my way <br>won't be back for many a day <br>my heart is down my head is turning around <br>I've had to leave a little girl in the Kingston town <br>sad to say I'm on my way <br>won't be back for many a day <br>my heart is down my head is turning around <br>I've had to leave a little girl in the Kingston town]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Jamaica Farewell (MBC `세시봉 콘서트` 1부 / 원곡: 해리 벨라폰테)" label="Jamaica Farewell (MBC `세시봉 콘서트` 1부 / 원곡: 해리 벨라폰테)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Hotel_California_원곡__이글스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Hotel California (원곡: 이글스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Hotel_California_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%9D%B4%EA%B8%80%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Hotel California (원곡: 이글스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[On a dark desert highway, <br>Cool wind in my hair <br>Warm smell of *colitas <br>Rising up through the air <br><br>Up ahead in the distance, <br>I saw a shimmering light <br>My head grew heavy, <br>And my sight grew dimmer <br>I had to stop for the night <br><br>There she stood in the doorway; <br>I heard the mission bell <br>And I was thinking to myself, <br>'This could be Heaven or this could be Hell' <br><br>Then she lit up a candle <br>And she showed me the way <br>There were voices <br>Down the corridor, <br>I thought I heard them say... <br><br>Welcome to the Hotel California <br>Such a lovely place <br>(Such a lovely place) <br>Plenty of room at the Hotel California <br>Any time of year, You can find it here <br><br>Her mind is *Tiffany-twisted, <br>She got the *Mercedes bends <br>She's got a lot of pretty, pretty boys, <br>That she calls friends <br>How they dance in the courtyard, <br>Sweet summer sweat. <br><br>Some dance to remember, <br>Some dance to forget <br>So I called up the Captain, <br>'Please bring me my wine' <br>He said, 'We haven't had that spirit here since 1969' <br><br>And still those voices are calling from far away <br>Wake you up in the middle of the night <br>Just to hear them say... <br><br>Welcome to the Hotel California <br>Such a lovely Place <br>(Such a lovely face) <br>They livin' it up at the Hotel California <br>What a nice surprise, <br>Bring your alibis <br><br>Mirrors on the ceiling, <br>The pink champagne on ice <br>And she said 'We are all just <br>Prisoners here, of our own device' <br><br>And in the master's chambers, <br>They gathered for the feast <br>They stab it with their steely knives, <br>But they just can't kill the beast <br><br>Last thing I remember, <br>I was running for the door <br>I had to find the passage back <br>To the place I was before <br><br>'Relax' said the nightman, <br>We are programed to recieve. <br>You can check out any time you like, <br>But you can never leave]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Hotel California (원곡: 이글스)" label="Hotel California (원곡: 이글스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/As_Time_Goes_By_영화_카사블랑카___원곡__토니_베넷/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - As Time Goes By (영화 `카사블랑카` / 원곡: 토니 베넷) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:22:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:22:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/As_Time_Goes_By_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%B9%B4%EC%82%AC%EB%B8%94%EB%9E%91%EC%B9%B4___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%ED%86%A0%EB%8B%88_%EB%B2%A0%EB%84%B7/" title="World Pop Orchestra - As Time Goes By (영화 `카사블랑카` / 원곡: 토니 베넷) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This day and age we're living in <br>Gives cause for apprehension <br>With speed and new invention <br>And things like third dimension <br>Yet we get a trifle weary <br>With Mr Einstein's theory <br>So we must get down to earth <br>At times relax, relieve the tension <br>No matter what the progress <br>Or what may yet be proved <br>The simple facts of life are such <br>They cannot be removed <br><br>You must remember this <br>A kiss is still a kiss <br>A sigh is just a sigh <br>The fundamental things apply as time goes by <br><br>And when two lovers woo <br>They still say I love you <br>On that you can rely <br>No matter what the future brings, as time goes by <br><br>Moonlight and love songs never out of date <br>Hearts full of passion, jealousy, and hate <br>Woman needs man, and man must have his mate <br>That no one can deny <br><br>It's still the same old story <br>A fight for love and glory <br>A case of do or die <br>The world will always welcome lovers as time goes by <br><br>The world will always welcome lovers as time goes by <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="As Time Goes By (영화 `카사블랑카` / 원곡: 토니 베넷)" label="As Time Goes By (영화 `카사블랑카` / 원곡: 토니 베넷)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Phantom_Of_The_Opera_뮤지컬_오페라의_유령/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - The Phantom Of The Opera (뮤지컬 `오페라의 유령`) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Phantom_Of_The_Opera_%EB%AE%A4%EC%A7%80%EC%BB%AC_%EC%98%A4%ED%8E%98%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%98_%EC%9C%A0%EB%A0%B9/" title="World Pop Orchestra - The Phantom Of The Opera (뮤지컬 `오페라의 유령`) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In sleep he sang to me <br>In dreams he came <br>That voice which calls to me <br>And speaks my name <br>And do I dream again <br>For now I find <br>The phantom of the opera is there <br>Inside my mind <br>Sing once again with me <br>Our strange duet <br>My power over you <br>Grows stronger yet <br>And though you turn from me <br>To glance behind <br>The phantom of the opera is there <br>Inside your mind <br>Those who have seen your face <br>Draw back in fear <br>I am the mask you wear <br>It's me they hear <br>My spirit and my voice <br>In one combined <br>The phantom of the opera is there <br>Inside my mind <br>Beware <br>The phantom of the opera <br>He's there <br>The phantom of the opera <br>Sing my angel of music <br>Sing my angel <br>Sing for me <br>Sing my angel <br>Sing for me]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="The Phantom Of The Opera (뮤지컬 `오페라의 유령`)" label="The Phantom Of The Opera (뮤지컬 `오페라의 유령`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Sunshine_On_My_Shoulders_영화_선샤인___원곡__존_덴버/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Sunshine On My Shoulders (영화 `선샤인` / 원곡: 존 덴버) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Sunshine_On_My_Shoulders_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%84%A0%EC%83%A4%EC%9D%B8___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%A1%B4_%EB%8D%B4%EB%B2%84/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Sunshine On My Shoulders (영화 `선샤인` / 원곡: 존 덴버) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sunshine on my shoulders makes me happy, sunshine in my eyes can make me cry. <br>Sunshine on the water looks so lovely, sunshine almost always makes me high. <br>If I had a day that I could give you, I'd give to you the day just like today. <br>If I had a song that I could sing for you, I'd sing a song to make you feel this way. <br><br>Sunshine on my shoulders makes me happy, sunshine in my eyes can make me cry. <br>Sunshine on the water looks so lovely, sunshine almost always makes me high. <br>If I had a tale that I could tell you, I'd tell a tale sure to make you smile. <br>If I had a wish that I could wish for you, I'd make a wish for sunshine for all the while. <br><br>Sunshine on my shoulders makes me happy, sunshine in my eyes can make me cry. <br>Sunshine on the water looks so lovely, sunshine almost always makes me high. <br>Sunshine on my shoulders makes me happy, sunshine in my eyes can make me cry. <br>Sunshine on the water looks so lovely, sunshine almost always makes me high. <br>Sunshine almost all the time makes me high. Sunshine almost always: <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Sunshine On My Shoulders (영화 `선샤인` / 원곡: 존 덴버)" label="Sunshine On My Shoulders (영화 `선샤인` / 원곡: 존 덴버)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Oh_Pretty_Woman_영화_귀여운_여인___원곡__로이_오비슨/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Oh Pretty Woman (영화 `귀여운 여인` / 원곡: 로이 오비슨) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Oh_Pretty_Woman_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EA%B7%80%EC%97%AC%EC%9A%B4_%EC%97%AC%EC%9D%B8___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%A1%9C%EC%9D%B4_%EC%98%A4%EB%B9%84%EC%8A%A8/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Oh Pretty Woman (영화 `귀여운 여인` / 원곡: 로이 오비슨) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty woman, <br>walkin' down the street, pretty woman <br>The kind I like to meet, pretty woman <br>I don't believe you, you're not the truth <br>No one could look as good as you. Mercy! <br><br>Pretty woman, Won't you pardon me? <br>Pretty woman, <br>I couldn't help but see, pretty woman, <br>that you look lovely as can be. <br>Are you lonely just like me? Wow! <br><br>Pretty woman, stop awhile. <br>Pretty woman, talk awhile <br>Pretty woman, give your smile to me. <br>Pretty woman, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Pretty woman, look my way <br>Pretty woman, say you'll stay with me <br>'Cause I need you, I'll treat you right <br>Come with me baby, be mine tonight <br>Pretty woman, don't walk on by <br>Pretty woman, don't make me cry <br>Pretty woman, don't walk away, Hey, O.K. <br>If that's the way it must be, O.K. <br>I guess I'll go on home. It's late. <br>There'll be tomorrow night, but wait! <br>What do I see? Is she walking back to me? <br>Yeah, she's walking back to me, <br>Oh, oh, pretty woman <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Oh Pretty Woman (영화 `귀여운 여인` / 원곡: 로이 오비슨)" label="Oh Pretty Woman (영화 `귀여운 여인` / 원곡: 로이 오비슨)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Winner_Takes_It_All_영화_맘마미아___원곡__아바/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - The Winner Takes It All (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Winner_Takes_It_All_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%A7%98%EB%A7%88%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%84___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%95%84%EB%B0%94/" title="World Pop Orchestra - The Winner Takes It All (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't wanna talk <br>About the things we've gone through <br>Though it's hurting me <br>Now it's history <br>I've played all my cards <br>And that's what you've done too <br>Nothing more to say <br>No more ace to play <br><br>The winner takes it all <br>The loser standing small <br>Beside the victory <br>That's her destiny <br><br>I was in your arms <br>Thinking I belonged there <br>I figured it made sense <br>Building me a fence <br><br>Building me a home <br>Thinking I'd be strong there <br>But I was a fool <br>Playing by the rules <br><br>The gods may throw a dice <br>Their minds as cold as ice <br>And someone way down here <br>Loses someone dear <br><br>The winner takes it all <br>The loser has to fall <br>It's simple and it's plain <br>Why should I complain. <br><br><br><br>But tell me does she kiss <br>Like I used to kiss you? <br>Does it feel the same <br>When she calls your name? <br><br>Somewhere deep inside <br>You must know I miss you <br>But what can I say <br>Rules must be obeyed <br><br>The judges will decide <br>The likes of me abide <br>Spectators of the show <br>Always staying low <br><br>The game is on again <br>A lover or a friend <br>A big thing or a small <br>The winner takes it all <br><br>I don't wanna talk <br>If it makes you feel sad <br>And I understand <br>You've come to shake my hand <br><br>I apologize <br>If it makes you feel bad <br>Seeing me so tense <br>No self-confidence <br><br>But you see <br><br>The winner takes it all <br><br>The winner takes it all]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="The Winner Takes It All (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)" label="The Winner Takes It All (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Memory_뮤지컬_캣츠/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Memory (뮤지컬 `캣츠`) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Memory_%EB%AE%A4%EC%A7%80%EC%BB%AC_%EC%BA%A3%EC%B8%A0/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Memory (뮤지컬 `캣츠`) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight, <br>not a sound from the pavement. <br>Has the moon lost her memory? <br>She is smiling alone. <br>In the lamplight, the withered <br>leaves collect at my feet, <br>and the wind begins to moan. <br><br>Memory, <br>All alone in the moonlight, <br>I can dream of the old days. <br>Life was beautiful then. <br>I remember the time <br>I knew what happiness was. <br>Let the memory live again. <br><br><br>Every steet lamp seems to beat <br>a fatalistic warning. <br>Someone mutters, <br>and the street lamp gutters <br>and soon it will be morning. <br><br>Daylight, <br>I must wait for the sunrise, <br>I must think of a new life <br>and I musn't give in. <br>When the dawn comes, <br>tonight will be a memory too <br>and a new day will begin. <br><br>Burnt out ends of smoky days, <br>the stale cold smell of morning. <br>The street lamp dies, <br>another night is over, <br>another day is dawning. <br><br><br>Touch me, <br>it's so easy to leave me, <br>all alone with the memory <br>of my days in the sun. <br>If you touch me, <br>you'll understand <br>what happiness is. <br>Look, a new day has begun. <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Memory (뮤지컬 `캣츠`)" label="Memory (뮤지컬 `캣츠`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Delilah_영화_세시봉___원곡__톰_존스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Delilah (영화 `세시봉` / 원곡: 톰 존스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Delilah_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%84%B8%EC%8B%9C%EB%B4%89___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%ED%86%B0_%EC%A1%B4%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Delilah (영화 `세시봉` / 원곡: 톰 존스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I saw the light on the night that I passed by her window <br>I saw the flickering shadows of love on her blind <br>She was my woman <br>As she deceived me I watched and went out of my mind <br>My, my, my, Delilah <br>Why, why, why, Delilah <br>I could see that girl was no good for me <br>But I was lost like a slave that no man could free <br>At break of day when that man drove away, I was waiting <br>I cross the street to her house and she opened the door <br>She stood there laughing <br>I felt the knife in my hand and she laughed no more <br>My, my, my Delilah <br>Why, why, why Delilah <br>So before they come to break down the door <br>Forgive me Delilah I just couldn't take any more <br><br>She stood there laughing <br>I felt the knife in my hand and she laughed no more <br>My, my, my, Delilah <br>Why, why, why, Delilah <br>So before they come to break down the door <br>Forgive me Delilah I just couldn't take any more <br>Forgive me Delilah I just couldn't take any more <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Delilah (영화 `세시봉` / 원곡: 톰 존스)" label="Delilah (영화 `세시봉` / 원곡: 톰 존스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Englishman_In_New_York_원곡__스팅/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Englishman In New York (원곡: 스팅) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Englishman_In_New_York_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%8A%A4%ED%8C%85/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Englishman In New York (원곡: 스팅) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't drink coffee I take tea my dear <br>I like my toast done on one side <br>And you can hear it in my accent when I talk <br>I'm an Englishman in New York <br><br>See me walking down Fifth Avenue <br>A walking cane here at my side <br>I take it everywhere I walk <br>I'm an Englishman in New York <br><br>I'm an alien, I'm a legal alien <br>I'm an Englishman in New York <br>I'm an alien, I'm a legal alien <br>I'm an Englishman in New York <br><br>If "Manners maketh man" as someone said <br>Then he's the hero of the day <br>It takes a man to suffer ignorance and smile <br>Be yourself no matter what they say <br><br>I'm an alien, I'm a legal alien <br>I'm an Englishman in New York <br>I'm an alien, I'm a legal alien <br>I'm an Englishman in New York <br><br>Modesty, propriety can lead to notoriety <br>You could end up as the only one <br>Gentleness, sobriety are rare in this society <br>At night a candle's brighter than the sun <br><br>Takes more than combat gear to make a man <br>Takes more than a license for a gun <br>Confront your enemies, avoid them when you can <br>A gentleman will walk but never run <br><br>If "Manners maketh man" as someone said <br>Then he's the hero of the day <br>It takes a man to suffer ignorance and smile <br>Be yourself no matter what they say [3x] <br><br>I'm an alien, I'm a legal alien <br>I'm an Englishman in New York <br>I'm an alien, I'm a legal alien <br>I'm an Englishman in New York <br><br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Englishman In New York (원곡: 스팅)" label="Englishman In New York (원곡: 스팅)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/A_Lovers_Concerto_영화_접속_홀랜드_오퍼스___원곡__더_토이즈/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - A Lover`s Concerto (영화 `접속`, `홀랜드 오퍼스` / 원곡: 더 토이즈) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/A_Lovers_Concerto_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%A0%91%EC%86%8D_%ED%99%80%EB%9E%9C%EB%93%9C_%EC%98%A4%ED%8D%BC%EC%8A%A4___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%8D%94_%ED%86%A0%EC%9D%B4%EC%A6%88/" title="World Pop Orchestra - A Lover`s Concerto (영화 `접속`, `홀랜드 오퍼스` / 원곡: 더 토이즈) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How gentle is the rain <br>That falls softly on the meadow, <br>Birds high up the trees <br>Serenade the clouds with their melodies <br><br><br>Oh, see there beyond the hill, <br>The bright colors of the rainbow. <br>Some magic from above <br>Made this day for us just to fall in love <br><br><br>Now, I belong to you <br>From this day until forever, <br>Just love me tenderly <br>And I'll give to you every part of me. <br><br><br>Oh, don't ever make me cry <br>Through long lonely nights without us. <br>Be always true to me, <br>Keep this day in your heart eternally. <br><br><br>One day we shall return <br>To this place upon the meadow. <br>We'll walk out in the rain, <br>See the birds above singing once again <br><br><br>Oh, you hold me in your arms, <br>And say once again you love me, <br>And if your love is true, <br>Everything will be just as wonderful. <br><br><br>You'll hold me in your arms, <br>And say once again you'll love me, <br>And if your love is true, <br>Everything will be just as wonderful. <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="A Lover`s Concerto (영화 `접속`, `홀랜드 오퍼스` / 원곡: 더 토이즈)" label="A Lover`s Concerto (영화 `접속`, `홀랜드 오퍼스` / 원곡: 더 토이즈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/YMCA_원곡__빌리지_피플/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Y.M.C.A (원곡: 빌리지 피플) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/YMCA_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B9%8C%EB%A6%AC%EC%A7%80_%ED%94%BC%ED%94%8C/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Y.M.C.A (원곡: 빌리지 피플) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Young man, there's no need to feel down <br>I said young man, pick yourself off the ground <br>I said young man, 'cause you're in a new town <br>There's no need to be unhappy <br><br>Young man, there's a place you can go <br>I said young man, when you're short on your dough <br>You can stay there, and I'm sure you will find <br>Many ways to have a good time <br><br>It's fun to stay at the Y.M.C.A. <br>It's fun to stay at the Y.M.C.A. <br>They have everything for young men to enjoy <br>You can hang out with all the boys <br><br>It's fun to stay at the Y.M.C.A. <br>It's fun to stay at the Y.M.C.A. <br>You can get yourself clean, you can have a good meal <br>You can do whatever you feel <br><br>Young man, are you listening to me <br>I said young man, what do you wanna be <br>I said young man, you can make real your dreams <br>But you've got to know this one thing <br><br>No man, does it all by himself <br>I said young man, put your pride on the shelf <br>And just go there, to the Y.M.C.A. <br>I'm sure they can help you today <br><br>It's fun to stay at the Y.M.C.A. <br>It's fun to stay at the Y.M.C.A. <br>They have everything for young men to enjoy <br>You can hang out with all the boys <br><br>It's fun to stay at the Y.M.C.A. <br>It's fun to stay at the Y.M.C.A. <br>You can get yourself clean you can have a good meal <br>You can do whatever you feel <br><br>Young Man, I was once in your shoes <br>I said I was, down and out with the blues <br>I felt no man, cared if I were alive <br>I felt the whole world was so jive <br><br>That's when someone, came up to me <br>And said young man, take a walk up the street <br>There's a place there, called the Y.M.C.A. <br>They can start you back on your way <br><br>It's fun to stay at the Y.M.C.A. <br>It's fun to stay at the Y.M.C.A. <br>Young man, young man there's no need to feel down <br>Young man, young man pick yourself off the ground <br><br>Y.M.C.A. and just go to the Y.M.C.A. <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Y.M.C.A (원곡: 빌리지 피플)" label="Y.M.C.A (원곡: 빌리지 피플)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Take_On_Me_드라마_응답하라_1988___원곡__아하/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Take On Me (드라마 `응답하라 1988` / 원곡: 아하) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Take_On_Me_%EB%93%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%A7%88_%EC%9D%91%EB%8B%B5%ED%95%98%EB%9D%BC_1988___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%95%84%ED%95%98/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Take On Me (드라마 `응답하라 1988` / 원곡: 아하) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We're talking away <br>I don't know what I'm to say <br>I'll say it anyway <br>Today's another day to find you <br>Shying away <br>I'll be coming for your love OK <br>Take on me take on me <br>Take me on take on me <br>I'll be gone <br>In a day or two <br>So needless to say <br>I'm odds and ends <br>But that's me stumbling away <br>Slowly learning that life is OK <br>Say after me <br>It's no better to be safe than sorry <br>Take on me take on me <br>Take me on take on me <br>I'll be gone <br>In a day or two <br>Oh the things that you say <br>Is it live or <br>Just to play my worries away <br>You're all the things <br>I've got to remember <br>You're shying away <br>I'll be coming for you anyway <br>Take me on take on me <br>Take me on take on me <br>I'll be gone <br>In a day <br>Take on me take on me <br>Take me on take on me <br>I'll be gone <br>In a day]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Take On Me (드라마 `응답하라 1988` / 원곡: 아하)" label="Take On Me (드라마 `응답하라 1988` / 원곡: 아하)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Cant_Help_Falling_In_Love_영화_블루_하와이___원곡__엘비스_프레슬리/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Can`t Help Falling In Love (영화 `블루 하와이` / 원곡: 엘비스 프레슬리) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Cant_Help_Falling_In_Love_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8_%ED%95%98%EC%99%80%EC%9D%B4___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%97%98%EB%B9%84%EC%8A%A4_%ED%94%84%EB%A0%88%EC%8A%AC%EB%A6%AC/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Can`t Help Falling In Love (영화 `블루 하와이` / 원곡: 엘비스 프레슬리) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wise men say <br>Only fools rush in <br>But I can't help falling in love with you <br>Shall I stay? <br>Would it be a sin <br>If I can't help falling in love with you? <br><br>Like a river flows <br>Surely to the sea <br>Darling, so it goes <br>Some things are meant to be <br>Take my hand, <br>Take my whole life, too <br>For I can't help falling in love with you <br><br>Like a river flows <br>Surely to the sea <br>Darling, so it goes <br>Some things are meant to be <br>Take my hand, <br>Take my whole life, too <br>For I can't help falling in love with you <br>For I can't help falling in love with you]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Can`t Help Falling In Love (영화 `블루 하와이` / 원곡: 엘비스 프레슬리)" label="Can`t Help Falling In Love (영화 `블루 하와이` / 원곡: 엘비스 프레슬리)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Dont_Worry_Be_Happy_영화_칵테일___원곡__바비_맥퍼린/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Don`t Worry, Be Happy (영화 `칵테일` / 원곡: 바비 맥퍼린) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Dont_Worry_Be_Happy_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%B9%B5%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%BC___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B0%94%EB%B9%84_%EB%A7%A5%ED%8D%BC%EB%A6%B0/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Don`t Worry, Be Happy (영화 `칵테일` / 원곡: 바비 맥퍼린) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a little song I wrote <br>You might want to sing it note for note <br>Don't worry, be happy <br>In every life we have some trouble <br>When you worry you make it double <br>Don't worry, be happy <br><br>Ooh, ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Don't worry) <br>Ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Be happy) <br>Ooh oo-ooh oo-ooh <br>(Don't worry, be happy) <br>Ooh, ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Don't worry) <br>Ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Be happy) <br>Ooh oo-ooh oo-ooh <br>(Don't worry, be happy) <br><br>Ain't got no place to lay your head <br>Somebody came and took your bed <br>Don't worry, be happy <br>The land lord say your rent is late <br>He may have to litigate <br>Don't worry, be happy <br>(Look at me I'm happy) <br><br>Ooh, ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Don't worry) <br>Ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Be Happy) <br>Ooh oo-ooh oo-ooh <br>Here I give you my phone number <br>When you worry call me, I make you happy <br>Ooh, ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Don't worry) <br>Ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Be happy) <br>Ooh oo-ooh oo-ooh <br><br>Ain't got no cash, ain't got no style <br>Ain't got no gal to make you smile <br>But don't worry, be happy <br>'Cause when you worry your face will frown <br>And that will bring everybody down <br>So don't worry, be happy <br>Don't worry, be happy now <br><br>Ooh, ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Don't worry) <br>Ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Be happy) <br>Ooh oo-ooh oo-ooh <br>Don't worry, be happy <br>Ooh, ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Don't worry) <br>Ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Be happy) <br>Ooh oo-ooh oo-ooh <br>Don't worry, be happy <br><br>Now there, is this song I wrote <br>I hope you learned it note for note <br>Like good little children <br>Don't worry, be happy <br>Listen to what I say <br>In your life expect some trouble <br>When you worry you make it double <br>Don't worry, be happy, be happy now <br><br>Ooh, ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Don't worry) <br>Ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Be happy) <br>Ooh oo-ooh oo-ooh <br>Don't worry, be happy <br>Ooh, ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Don't worry) <br>Ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Be happy) <br>Ooh oo-ooh oo-ooh <br>Don't worry, be happy <br><br>Ooh, ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Don't worry) <br>Ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Don't worry, don't worry, don't do it, be happy) <br>Ooh oo-ooh oo-ooh <br>(Put a smile on your face, don't bring everybody down) <br>Ooh, ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(Don't worry) <br>Ooh oo-ooh ooh ooh oo-ooh <br>(It will soon pass, whatever it is) <br>Ooh oo-ooh oo-ooh <br>Don't worry, be happy <br>Ooh oo-ooh oo-ooh <br>I'm not worried, I'm happy]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Don`t Worry, Be Happy (영화 `칵테일` / 원곡: 바비 맥퍼린)" label="Don`t Worry, Be Happy (영화 `칵테일` / 원곡: 바비 맥퍼린)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Killing_Me_Softly_With_His_Song_영화_어바웃_어_보이___K팝스타_이하이_가창곡___원곡__로베타_플랙/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Killing Me Softly With His Song (영화 `어바웃 어 보이` / K팝스타 `이하이` 가창곡 / 원곡: 로베타 플랙) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Killing_Me_Softly_With_His_Song_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%96%B4%EB%B0%94%EC%9B%83_%EC%96%B4_%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4___K%ED%8C%9D%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80_%EC%9D%B4%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B0%80%EC%B0%BD%EA%B3%A1___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%A1%9C%EB%B2%A0%ED%83%80_%ED%94%8C%EB%9E%99/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Killing Me Softly With His Song (영화 `어바웃 어 보이` / K팝스타 `이하이` 가창곡 / 원곡: 로베타 플랙) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Strumming my pain with his fingers <br>Singing my life with his words <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Telling my whole life with his words <br>Killing me softly with his song <br><br>I heard he sang a good song <br>I heard he had a style <br>And so I came to see him <br>To listen for a while <br>And there he was this young boy <br>A stranger to my eyes <br><br>Strumming my pain with his fingers <br>Singing my life with his words <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Telling my whole life with his words <br>Killing me softly with his song <br><br>I felt all flushed with fever <br>Embarassed by the crowd <br>I felt he found my letters <br>And read each one out loud <br>I prayed that he would finish <br>But he just kept right on <br><br>Strumming my pain with his fingers <br>Singing my life with his words <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Telling my whole life with his words <br>Killing me softly with his song <br><br>He sang as if he knew me <br>In all my dark despair <br>And then he looked right through me <br>As if I wasn't there <br>And he just kept on singing <br>Singing clear and strong <br><br>Strumming my pain with his fingers <br>Singing my life with his words <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Telling my whole life with his words <br>Killing me softly with his song <br><br>Strumming my pain with his fingers <br>Singing my life with his words <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Telling my whole life with his words <br>Killing me <br><br>He was strumming my pain <br>Yeah, he was singing my life <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Killing me softly with his song <br>Telling my whole life with his words <br>Killing me softly <br>With his song <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Killing Me Softly With His Song (영화 `어바웃 어 보이` / K팝스타 `이하이` 가창곡 / 원곡: 로베타 플랙)" label="Killing Me Softly With His Song (영화 `어바웃 어 보이` / K팝스타 `이하이` 가창곡 / 원곡: 로베타 플랙)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/When_A_Man_Loves_A_Woman_영화_남자가_여자를_사랑할_때___원곡__퍼시_슬레이지/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - When A Man Loves A Woman (영화 `남자가 여자를 사랑할 때` / 원곡: 퍼시 슬레이지) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/When_A_Man_Loves_A_Woman_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%82%A8%EC%9E%90%EA%B0%80_%EC%97%AC%EC%9E%90%EB%A5%BC_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%A0_%EB%95%8C___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%ED%8D%BC%EC%8B%9C_%EC%8A%AC%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80/" title="World Pop Orchestra - When A Man Loves A Woman (영화 `남자가 여자를 사랑할 때` / 원곡: 퍼시 슬레이지) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When a man loves a woman, <br>Can't keep his mind on nothin' else, <br>He'd change the world for the good thing he's found. <br>If she is bad, he can't see it, <br>She can do no wrong, <br>Turn his back on his best friend if he put her down. <br>When a man loves a woman, <br>He'll spend his very last dime <br>Tryin' to hold on to what he needs. <br>He'd give up all his comforts <br>And sleep out in the rain, <br>If she said that's the way <br>It ought to be. <br>Well, this man loves you, woman. <br>I gave you everything I have, <br>Tryin' to hold on to your heartless love. <br>Baby, please don't treat me bad. <br>When a man loves a woman, <br>Down deep in his soul, <br>She can bring him such misery. <br>If she is playin' him for a fool, <br>He's the last one to know. <br>Lovin' eyes can never see. <br>When a man loves a woman <br>He can do her no wrong, <br>He can never want <br>Some other girl. <br>Yes,When a man loves a woman <br>I know exactly how he feels, <br>'Cause baby, baby, you're my world <br>When a man loves a woman.... <br><br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="When A Man Loves A Woman (영화 `남자가 여자를 사랑할 때` / 원곡: 퍼시 슬레이지)" label="When A Man Loves A Woman (영화 `남자가 여자를 사랑할 때` / 원곡: 퍼시 슬레이지)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/All_I_Ask_Of_You_뮤지컬_오페라의_유령/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - All I Ask Of You (뮤지컬 `오페라의 유령`) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/All_I_Ask_Of_You_%EB%AE%A4%EC%A7%80%EC%BB%AC_%EC%98%A4%ED%8E%98%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%98_%EC%9C%A0%EB%A0%B9/" title="World Pop Orchestra - All I Ask Of You (뮤지컬 `오페라의 유령`) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No more talk of darkness <br>forget these wide-eyed fears <br>I'm here, nothing can harm you <br>my words will warm and calm you <br>Let me be your freedom <br>let daylight dry your tears <br>I'm here, with you, beside you <br>to guard you and to guide you <br>Say you love me <br>every waking moment <br>turn my head with <br>talk of summertime <br>Say you need me <br>with you now and always <br>promise me that <br>all you say is true <br>that's all I ask of you <br>Let me be your shelter <br>let me be your light <br>you're safe, no one will find you <br>your fears are far behind you <br>All I want is freedom <br>a world with no more night <br>and you, always beside me <br>to hold me and to hide me <br>Then say you'll share with me <br>one love, one lifetime <br>let me lead you <br>from your solitude <br>Say you need me with you <br>here beside you <br>anywhere you go, let me go too <br>Christine, that's all I ask of you <br>Say you'll share with me <br>one love, one lifetime <br>say the word and <br>I will follow you <br>Share each day with me <br>each night, each morning <br>Say you love me <br>You know I do <br>Love me that's all I ask of you <br>anywhere you go, let me go too <br>Love me that's all I ask of you]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="All I Ask Of You (뮤지컬 `오페라의 유령`)" label="All I Ask Of You (뮤지컬 `오페라의 유령`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Time_Of_My_Life_영화_더티_댄싱___원곡__빌_메들리__제니퍼_원스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - The Time Of My Life (영화 `더티 댄싱` / 원곡: 빌 메들리 &amp; 제니퍼 원스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Time_Of_My_Life_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%8D%94%ED%8B%B0_%EB%8C%84%EC%8B%B1___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B9%8C_%EB%A9%94%EB%93%A4%EB%A6%AC__%EC%A0%9C%EB%8B%88%ED%8D%BC_%EC%9B%90%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - The Time Of My Life (영화 `더티 댄싱` / 원곡: 빌 메들리 &amp; 제니퍼 원스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Now I've had the time of my life No I never felt like this before <br>Yes I swear it's the truth and I owe it all to you <br>'Cause I've had the time of my life and I owe it all to you <br><br>I've been waiting for so long Now I've finally found someone <br>To stand by me We saw the writing on the wall <br>As we felt this magical Fantasy <br>Now with passion in our eyes <br>There's no way we could disguise it Secretly <br>So we take each other's hand 'Cause we seem to understand <br>The urgency just remember <br><br>You're the one thing I can't get enough of <br>So I'll tell you something This could be love because <br>I've had the time of my life No I never felt this way before <br>Yes I swear it's the truth And I owe it all to you <br><br>With my body and soul I want you more than you'll ever know <br>So we'll just let it go Don't be afraid to loose control <br>Yes I know what's on your mind <br>When you say Stay with me tonight. Just remember <br><br>You're the one thing I can't get enough of <br>So I'll tell you something This could be love because <br>I've had the time of my life No I never felt this way before <br>Yes I swear it's the truth And I owe it all to you <br>'Cause I had the time of my life <br>And I've searched through every open door <br>Till I've found the truth and I owe it all to you <br><br>I've had the time of my life No I never felt this way before <br>Yes I swear it's the truth And I owe it all to you <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="The Time Of My Life (영화 `더티 댄싱` / 원곡: 빌 메들리 &amp; 제니퍼 원스)" label="The Time Of My Life (영화 `더티 댄싱` / 원곡: 빌 메들리 &amp; 제니퍼 원스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/We_Are_The_World_원곡__USA_For_Africa/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - We Are The World (원곡: U.S.A For Africa) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/We_Are_The_World_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__USA_For_Africa/" title="World Pop Orchestra - We Are The World (원곡: U.S.A For Africa) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There comes a time when we hear a certain call <br>When the world must come together as one <br>There are people dying and it's time to lend a hand <br>To life the greatest gift of all. <br><br>We can't go on pretending day by day <br>That someone, somewhere will soon make a change <br>We are all part of God's great big family <br>And the truth, you know, love is all we need <br><br>We are the world, we are the children <br>We are the ones who make a brighter day so let's start giving <br>There's a choice we're making, we're saving our own lives <br>It's true we'll make a better day just you and me <br><br>Well, send them your heart so they'll know that someone cares <br>And their lives will be stronger and free <br>As God has shown us by turning stones to bread <br>And so we all must lend a helping hand <br><br>We are the world, we are the children <br>We are the ones who make a brighter day so let's start giving <br>There's a choice we're making, we're saving our own lives <br>It's true we'll make a better day just you and me <br><br>When you're down and out, there seems no hope at all <br>But if you just believe, there's no way we can fall <br>Well, well, well, well let us realize that a change can only come <br>When we stand together as one <br><br>We are the world, we are the children <br>We are the ones who make a brighter day so let's start giving <br>There's a choice we're making, we're saving our own lives <br>It's true we'll make a better day just you and me <br><br>We are the world, we are the children <br>We are the ones who make a brighter day so let's start giving <br>There's a choice we're making, we're saving our own lives <br>It's true we'll make a better day just you and me <br><br>We are the world, we are the children <br>We are the ones who make a brighter day so let's start giving <br>There's a choice we're making, we're saving our own lives <br>It's true we'll make a better day just you and me <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="We Are The World (원곡: U.S.A For Africa)" label="We Are The World (원곡: U.S.A For Africa)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Way_We_Were_영화_추억___원곡__바브라_스트라이샌드/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - The Way We Were (영화 `추억` / 원곡: 바브라 스트라이샌드) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Way_We_Were_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%B6%94%EC%96%B5___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B0%94%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%8C%EB%93%9C/" title="World Pop Orchestra - The Way We Were (영화 `추억` / 원곡: 바브라 스트라이샌드) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Mem'ries, <br>Light the corners of my mind <br>Misty water-colored memories <br>Of the way we were <br>Scattered pictures, <br>Of the smiles we left behind <br>Smiles we gave to one another <br>For the way we were <br>Can it be that it was all so simple then? <br>Or has time re-written every line? <br>If we had the chance to do it all again <br>Tell me, would we? Could we? <br>Mem'ries, may be beautiful and yet <br>What's too painful to remember <br>We simply choose to forget <br>So it's the laughter <br>We will remember <br>Whenever we remember... <br>The way we were... <br>The way we were... <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="The Way We Were (영화 `추억` / 원곡: 바브라 스트라이샌드)" label="The Way We Were (영화 `추억` / 원곡: 바브라 스트라이샌드)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/FlashdanceWhat_A_Feeling_영화_플래쉬댄스___원곡__아이린_카라/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Flashdance...What A Feeling (영화 `플래쉬댄스` / 원곡: 아이린 카라) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/FlashdanceWhat_A_Feeling_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%ED%94%8C%EB%9E%98%EC%89%AC%EB%8C%84%EC%8A%A4___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EB%A6%B0_%EC%B9%B4%EB%9D%BC/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Flashdance...What A Feeling (영화 `플래쉬댄스` / 원곡: 아이린 카라) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[First when there's nothing <br>But a slow glowing dream <br>That your fear seems to hide <br>Deep inside your mind <br><br>All alone, I have cried <br>Silent tears full of pride <br>In a world made of steel <br>Made of stone <br><br>Well, I hear the music <br>Close my eyes, feel the rhythm <br>Wrap around, take a hold of my heart <br><br>What a feeling <br>Being's believing <br>I can have it all <br>Now I'm dancing for my life <br><br>Take your passion <br>And make it happen <br>Pictures come alive <br>You can dance right through your life <br><br>Now I hear the music <br>Close my eyes, I am rhythm <br>In a flash, it takes hold of my heart <br><br>What a feeling, being's believing <br>I can have it all <br>Now I'm dancing for my life <br><br>Take your passion <br>And make it happen <br>Pictures come alive <br>Now I'm dancing through my life <br><br>What a feeling <br><br>What a feeling (I am music now) <br>Being's believing (I am rhythm now) <br>Pictures come alive <br>You can dance right through your life <br><br>What a feeling (I can really have it all) <br>What a feeling <br>(Pictures come alive when I call) <br>I can have it all (I can really have it all) <br><br>Have it all (pictures come alive when I call) <br>(Call, call ,call, call, what a feeling) <br>I can have it all (being's believing) <br>Being's believing (take your passion) <br>(Make it happen) Make it happen <br>(What a feeling) What a feeling]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Flashdance...What A Feeling (영화 `플래쉬댄스` / 원곡: 아이린 카라)" label="Flashdance...What A Feeling (영화 `플래쉬댄스` / 원곡: 아이린 카라)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Stayin_Alive_영화_토요일_밤의_열기___원곡__비지스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Stayin` Alive (영화 `토요일 밤의 열기` / 원곡: 비지스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Stayin_Alive_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%ED%86%A0%EC%9A%94%EC%9D%BC_%EB%B0%A4%EC%9D%98_%EC%97%B4%EA%B8%B0___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B9%84%EC%A7%80%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Stayin` Alive (영화 `토요일 밤의 열기` / 원곡: 비지스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, you can tell by the way I use my walk, <br>I'm a woman's man: no time to talk. <br>Music loud and women warm, I've been kicked around <br>since I was born. <br>And now it's all right. It's OK. <br>And you may look the other way. <br>We can try to understand <br>the New York Times' effect on man. <br><br>Whether you're a brother or whether you're a mother, <br>you're stayin' alive, stayin' alive. <br>Feel the city breakin' and everybody shakin', <br>and we're stayin' alive, stayin' alive. <br>Ah, ha, ha, ha, stayin' alive, stayin' alive. <br>Ah, ha, ha, ha, stayin' alive. <br><br>Well now, I get low and I get high, <br>and if I can't get either, I really try. <br>Got the wings of heaven on my shoes. <br>I'm a dancin' man and I just can't lose. <br>You know it's all right. It's OK. <br>I'll live to see another day. <br>We can try to understand <br>the New York Times' effect on man. <br><br>Whether you're a brother or whether you're a mother, <br>you're stayin' alive, stayin' alive. <br>Feel the city breakin' and everybody shakin', <br>and we're stayin' alive, stayin' alive. <br>Ah, ha, ha, ha, stayin' alive, stayin' alive. <br>Ah, ha, ha, ha, stayin' alive. <br><br>Life goin' nowhere. Somebody help me. <br>Somebody help me, yeah. <br>Life goin' nowhere. Somebody help me. <br>Somebody help me, yeah. Stayin' alive. <br><br>Well, you can tell by the way I use my walk, <br>I'm a woman's man: no time to talk. <br>Music loud and women warm, <br>I've been kicked around since I was born. <br>And now it's all right. It's OK. <br>And you may look the other way. <br>We can try to understand <br>the New York Times' effect on man. <br><br>Whether you're a brother or whether you're a mother, <br>you're stayin' alive, stayin' alive. <br>Feel the city breakin' and everybody shakin', <br>and we're stayin' alive, stayin' alive. <br>Ah, ha, ha, ha, stayin' alive, stayin' alive. <br>Ah, ha, ha, ha, stayin' alive. <br><br>Life goin' nowhere. Somebody help me. <br>Somebody help me, yeah. <br>Life goin' nowhere. Somebody help me, yeah. <br>I'm stayin' alive]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Stayin` Alive (영화 `토요일 밤의 열기` / 원곡: 비지스)" label="Stayin` Alive (영화 `토요일 밤의 열기` / 원곡: 비지스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_End_Of_The_World_영화_아메리칸_어페어___원곡__스키터_데이비스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - The End Of The World (영화 `아메리칸 어페어` / 원곡: 스키터 데이비스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_End_Of_The_World_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%95%84%EB%A9%94%EB%A6%AC%EC%B9%B8_%EC%96%B4%ED%8E%98%EC%96%B4___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%8A%A4%ED%82%A4%ED%84%B0_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%B9%84%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - The End Of The World (영화 `아메리칸 어페어` / 원곡: 스키터 데이비스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Why does the sun go on shining <br>Why does the sea rush to shore <br>Don't they know it's the end of the world <br>'Cause you don't love me any more <br><br><br>Why do the birds go on singing <br>Why do the stars glow above <br>Don't they know it's the end of the world <br>It ended when I lost your love <br><br><br>I wake up in the morning and I wonder <br>Why everything's the same as it was <br>I can't understand, no, I can't understand <br>How life goes on the way it does <br><br><br>Why does my heart go on beating <br>Why do these eyes of mine cry <br>Don't they know it's the end of the world <br>It ended when you said goodbye <br><br><br>Why does my heart go on beating <br>Why do these eyes of mine cry <br>Don't they know it's the end of the world <br>It ended when you said goodbye <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="The End Of The World (영화 `아메리칸 어페어` / 원곡: 스키터 데이비스)" label="The End Of The World (영화 `아메리칸 어페어` / 원곡: 스키터 데이비스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/What_A_Wonderful_World_영화_굿모닝_베트남___원곡__루이_암스트롱/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - What A Wonderful World (영화 `굿모닝 베트남` / 원곡: 루이 암스트롱) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/What_A_Wonderful_World_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EA%B5%BF%EB%AA%A8%EB%8B%9D_%EB%B2%A0%ED%8A%B8%EB%82%A8___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%A3%A8%EC%9D%B4_%EC%95%94%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A1%B1/" title="World Pop Orchestra - What A Wonderful World (영화 `굿모닝 베트남` / 원곡: 루이 암스트롱) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I see trees of green, <br>red roses too. <br>I see them bloom, <br>for me and you. <br>And I think to myself, <br>what a wonderful world. <br><br>I see skies of blue, <br>And clouds of white. <br>The bright blessed day, <br>The dark sacred night. <br>And I think to myself, <br>What a wonderful world. <br><br>The colors of the rainbow, <br>So pretty in the sky. <br>Are also on the faces, <br>Of people going by, <br>I see friends shaking hands. <br>Saying, "How do you do?" <br>They're really saying, <br>"I love you". <br><br>I hear babies cry, <br>I watch them grow, <br>They'll learn much more, <br>Than I'll ever know. <br>And I think to myself, <br>What a wonderful world. <br><br>Yes, I think to myself, <br>What a wonderful world. <br><br>Oh yeah. <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="What A Wonderful World (영화 `굿모닝 베트남` / 원곡: 루이 암스트롱)" label="What A Wonderful World (영화 `굿모닝 베트남` / 원곡: 루이 암스트롱)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Singin_In_The_Rain_영화_사랑은_비를_타고___원곡__진_켈리/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Singin` In The Rain (영화 `사랑은 비를 타고` / 원곡: 진 켈리) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Singin_In_The_Rain_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%80_%EB%B9%84%EB%A5%BC_%ED%83%80%EA%B3%A0___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%A7%84_%EC%BC%88%EB%A6%AC/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Singin` In The Rain (영화 `사랑은 비를 타고` / 원곡: 진 켈리) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm singin' in the rain <br>Just singin' in the rain, <br>What a glorious feeling, <br>And I'm happy again. <br>I'm laughing at clouds <br>So dark, up above, <br>The sun's in my heart <br>And I'm ready for love. <br><br>Let the stormy clouds chase. <br>Everyone from the place, <br>Come on with the rain <br>I have a smile on my face. <br>I'll walk down the lane <br>With a happy refrain <br>Just singin', singin' in the rain. <br><br>Dancing in the rain. <br><br>I'm happy again. <br><br>I'm singin' and dancin' in the rain. <br><br>Dancin' and singin' in the rain.]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Singin` In The Rain (영화 `사랑은 비를 타고` / 원곡: 진 켈리)" label="Singin` In The Rain (영화 `사랑은 비를 타고` / 원곡: 진 켈리)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/I_Just_Called_To_Say_I_Love_You_드라마_응답하라_1988___영화_우먼_인_레드___원곡__스티비_원더/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - I Just Called To Say I Love You (드라마 `응답하라 1988` / 영화 `우먼 인 레드` / 원곡: 스티비 원더) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/I_Just_Called_To_Say_I_Love_You_%EB%93%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%A7%88_%EC%9D%91%EB%8B%B5%ED%95%98%EB%9D%BC_1988___%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%9A%B0%EB%A8%BC_%EC%9D%B8_%EB%A0%88%EB%93%9C___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B0%EB%B9%84_%EC%9B%90%EB%8D%94/" title="World Pop Orchestra - I Just Called To Say I Love You (드라마 `응답하라 1988` / 영화 `우먼 인 레드` / 원곡: 스티비 원더) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No New Year's Day to celebrate <br>No chocolate covered candy hearts to give away <br>No first of spring <br>No song to sing <br>In fact here's just another ordinary day <br><br>No April rain <br>No flowers bloom <br>No wedding Saturday within the month of June <br>But what it is, is something true <br>Made up of these three words that I must say to you <br><br>I just called to say I love you <br>I just called to say how much I care <br>I just called to say I love you <br>And I mean it from the bottom of my heart <br><br>No summer's high <br>No warm July <br>No harvest moon to light one tender August night <br>No autumn breeze <br>No falling leaves <br>Not even time for birds to fly to southern skies <br><br>No Libra sun <br>No Halloween <br>No giving thanks to all the Christmas joy you bring <br>But what it is, though old so new <br>To fill your heart like no three words could ever do <br><br>I just called to say I love you <br>I just called to say how much I care, I do <br>I just called to say I love you <br>And I mean it from the bottom of my heart <br><br>I just called to say I love you <br>I just called to say how much I care, I do <br>I just called to say I love you <br>And I mean it from the bottom of my heart, of my heart, <br>of my heart <br><br>I just called to say I love you <br>I just called to say how much I care, I do <br>I just called to say I love you <br>And I mean it from the bottom of my heart, of my heart, <br>baby of my heart]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="I Just Called To Say I Love You (드라마 `응답하라 1988` / 영화 `우먼 인 레드` / 원곡: 스티비 원더)" label="I Just Called To Say I Love You (드라마 `응답하라 1988` / 영화 `우먼 인 레드` / 원곡: 스티비 원더)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Hard_To_Say_Im_Sorry__드라마_응답하라_1994___영화_썸머_러버스___원곡__시카고/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Hard To Say I`m Sorry (드라마 `응답하라 1994` / 영화 `썸머 러버스` / 원곡: 시카고) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Hard_To_Say_Im_Sorry__%EB%93%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%A7%88_%EC%9D%91%EB%8B%B5%ED%95%98%EB%9D%BC_1994___%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%8D%B8%EB%A8%B8_%EB%9F%AC%EB%B2%84%EC%8A%A4___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%8B%9C%EC%B9%B4%EA%B3%A0/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Hard To Say I`m Sorry (드라마 `응답하라 1994` / 영화 `썸머 러버스` / 원곡: 시카고) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Everybody needs a little time away," <br>I heard her say, <br>"from each other." <br>"Even lover's need a holiday far away from each other." <br>Hold me now. <br>It's hard for me to say I'm sorry. <br>I just want you to stay. <br><br>After all that we've been through, <br>I will make it up to you. <br>I promise to. <br>And after all that's been said and done, <br>You're just the part of me I can't let go. <br><br>Couldn't stand to be kept away just for the day from your body. <br>Wouldn't wanna be swept away, far away from the one that I love. <br>Hold me now. <br>It's hard for me to say I'm sorry. <br>I just want you to know. <br>Hold me now. <br>I really want to tell you I'm sorry. <br>I could never let you go. <br><br>After all that we've been through, <br>I will make it up to you. <br>I promise to. <br>And after all that's been said and done, <br>You're just the part of me I can't let go. <br><br>After all that we've been through, <br>I will make it up to you. <br>I promise to. <br><br>You're gonna be the lucky one.]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Hard To Say I`m Sorry (드라마 `응답하라 1994` / 영화 `썸머 러버스` / 원곡: 시카고)" label="Hard To Say I`m Sorry (드라마 `응답하라 1994` / 영화 `썸머 러버스` / 원곡: 시카고)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Imagine_영화_킬링필드___원곡__존_레논/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Imagine (영화 `킬링필드` / 원곡: 존 레논) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Imagine_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%ED%82%AC%EB%A7%81%ED%95%84%EB%93%9C___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%A1%B4_%EB%A0%88%EB%85%BC/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Imagine (영화 `킬링필드` / 원곡: 존 레논) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine there's no heaven <br>It's easy if you try <br>No hell below us <br>Above us only sky <br>Imagine all the people <br>Living for today... Aha-ah... <br><br>Imagine there's no countries <br>It isn't hard to do <br>Nothing to kill or die for <br>And no religion, too <br>Imagine all the people <br>Living life in peace... You... <br><br>You may say I'm a dreamer <br>But I'm not the only one <br>I hope someday you'll join us <br>And the world will be as one <br><br>Imagine no possessions <br>I wonder if you can <br>No need for greed or hunger <br>A brotherhood of man <br>Imagine all the people <br>Sharing all the world... You... <br><br>You may say I'm a dreamer <br>But I'm not the only one <br>I hope someday you'll join us <br>And the world will live as one]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Imagine (영화 `킬링필드` / 원곡: 존 레논)" label="Imagine (영화 `킬링필드` / 원곡: 존 레논)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Unchained_Melody_영화_사랑과_영혼___원곡__라이처스_브라더스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Unchained Melody (영화 `사랑과 영혼` / 원곡: 라이처스 브라더스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Unchained_Melody_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EA%B3%BC_%EC%98%81%ED%98%BC___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EC%B2%98%EC%8A%A4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EB%8D%94%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Unchained Melody (영화 `사랑과 영혼` / 원곡: 라이처스 브라더스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Whoa, my love <br>My darling <br>I've hungered for your touch <br>A long, lonely time <br><br>And time goes by so slowly <br>And time can do so much <br>Are you still mine? <br><br>I need your love <br>I need your love <br>God speed your love to me <br><br>Lonely rivers flow to the sea, to the sea <br>To the open arms of the sea <br>Lonely rivers sigh, "Wait for me, wait for me <br>I'll be coming home, wait for me" <br><br>Whoa, my love <br>My darling <br>I've hungered, hungered for your touch <br>A long, lonely time <br><br>And time goes by so slowly <br>And time can do so much <br>Are you still mine? <br><br>I need your love <br>I need your love <br>God speed your love to me]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Unchained Melody (영화 `사랑과 영혼` / 원곡: 라이처스 브라더스)" label="Unchained Melody (영화 `사랑과 영혼` / 원곡: 라이처스 브라더스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Time_After_Time_영화_써니___원곡__신디_로퍼/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Time After Time (영화 `써니` / 원곡: 신디 로퍼) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:23:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:23:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Time_After_Time_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%8D%A8%EB%8B%88___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%8B%A0%EB%94%94_%EB%A1%9C%ED%8D%BC/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Time After Time (영화 `써니` / 원곡: 신디 로퍼) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lying in my bed I hear <br>the clock tick <br>and think of you <br>caught up in circles confusion <br>is nothing new <br>Flashback warm nights <br>almost left behind <br>suitcases of memories <br>time after <br>sometimes you picture me <br>I'm walking too far ahead <br>you're calling to me <br>I can't hear <br>what you've said <br>Then you say go slow <br>I fall behind <br>the second hand unwinds <br>if you're lost you can look <br>and you will find me <br>time after time <br>if you fall I will catch you <br>I'll be waiting <br>time after time <br>if you're lost you can look <br>and you will find me <br>time after time <br>if you fall I will catch you <br>I'll be waiting <br>time after time <br><br>after my picture fades <br>and darkness has turned to gray <br>watching through windows <br>you're wondering if I'm okay <br>secrets stolen from deep inside <br>the drum beats out of time <br>if you're lost <br>you can look and you will find me <br>time after time <br>if you fall I will catch you <br>I'll be waiting <br>time after time <br><br>you said go slow <br>I fall behind <br>the second hand unwinds <br>if you're lost you can look <br>and you will find me <br>time after time <br>if you fall I will catch you <br>I'll be waiting <br>time after time <br>if you're lost you can look <br>and you will find me <br>time after time <br>if you fall I will catch you <br>I'll be waiting <br>time after time <br>time after time <br>time after time <br>time after time <br>time after time <br>time after time <br>time after time <br>time after time <br>time after time]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Time After Time (영화 `써니` / 원곡: 신디 로퍼)" label="Time After Time (영화 `써니` / 원곡: 신디 로퍼)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Happy_Together_영화_해피투게더___원곡__더_터틀즈/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Happy Together (영화 `해피투게더` / 원곡: 더 터틀즈) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Happy_Together_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%ED%95%B4%ED%94%BC%ED%88%AC%EA%B2%8C%EB%8D%94___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%8D%94_%ED%84%B0%ED%8B%80%EC%A6%88/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Happy Together (영화 `해피투게더` / 원곡: 더 터틀즈) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine me and you, I do <br>I think about you day and night, it's only right <br>To think about the girl you love and hold her tight <br>So happy together <br><br>If I should call you up, invest a dime <br>And you say you belong to me and ease my mind <br>Imagine how the world could be, so very fine <br>So happy together <br><br>I can't see me lovin' nobody but you <br>For all my life <br>When you're with me, baby the skies'll be blue <br>For all my life <br><br>Me and you and you and me <br>No matter how they toss the dice, it had to be <br>The only one for me is you, and you for me <br>So happy together <br><br>I can't see me lovin' nobody but you <br>For all my life <br>When you're with me, baby the skies'll be blue <br>For all my life <br><br>Me and you and you and me <br>No matter how they toss the dice, it had to be <br>The only one for me is you, and you for me <br>So happy together <br><br>Ba-ba-ba-ba ba-ba-ba-ba ba-ba-ba ba-ba-ba-ba <br>Ba-ba-ba-ba ba-ba-ba-ba ba-ba-ba ba-ba-ba-ba <br><br>Me and you and you and me <br>No matter how they toss the dice, it had to be <br>The only one for me is you, and you for me <br>So happy together <br><br>So happy together <br>And how is the weather <br>So happy together <br>We're happy together <br>So happy together <br>Happy together <br>So happy together <br>So happy together (ba-ba-ba-ba ba-ba-ba-ba) <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Happy Together (영화 `해피투게더` / 원곡: 더 터틀즈)" label="Happy Together (영화 `해피투게더` / 원곡: 더 터틀즈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Billie_Jean_영화_미녀_삼총사___원곡__마이클_잭슨/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Billie Jean (영화 `미녀 삼총사` / 원곡: 마이클 잭슨) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Billie_Jean_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%AF%B8%EB%85%80_%EC%82%BC%EC%B4%9D%EC%82%AC___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B4%ED%81%B4_%EC%9E%AD%EC%8A%A8/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Billie Jean (영화 `미녀 삼총사` / 원곡: 마이클 잭슨) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She was more like a beauty queen from a movie scene <br>I said don't mind, but what do you mean I am the one <br>Who will dance on the floor in the round <br>She said I am the one who will dance on the floor in the round <br><br>She told me her name was Billie Jean, as she caused a scene <br>Then every head turned with eyes that dreamed of being the one <br>Who will dance on the floor in the round <br><br>People always told me be careful of what you do <br>And don't go around breaking young girls' hearts <br>And mother always told me be careful of who you love <br>And be careful of what you do 'cause the lie becomes the truth <br><br>Billie Jean is not my lover <br>She's just a girl who claims that I am the one <br>But the kid is not my son <br>She says I am the one, but the kid is not my son <br><br>For forty days and forty nights <br>The law was on her side <br>But who can stand when she's in demand <br>Her schemes and plans <br>'cause we danced on the floor in the round <br>So take my strong advice, just remember to always think twice <br>(do think twice.) <br><br>She told my baby we'd danced 'til three <br>Then she looked at me <br>She showed a photo of a baby crying <br>His eyes looked like mine <br>Go on dance on the floor in the round, baby <br><br>People always told me be careful of what you do <br>And don't go around breaking young girls' hearts <br>She came and stood right by me <br>Then the smell of sweet perfume <br>This happened much too soon <br>She called me to her room <br><br>Billie Jean is not my lover <br>She's just a girl who claims that I am the one <br>But the kid is not my son <br>Billie Jean is not my lover <br>She's just a girl who claims that I am the one <br>But the kid is not my son <br>She says I am the one, but the kid is not my son <br><br>She says I am the one, but the kid is not my son <br><br>Billie Jean is not my lover <br>She's just a girl who claims that I am the one <br>But the kid is not my son <br>She says I am the one, but the kid is not my son <br>She says I am the one, she says he is my son <br>She says I am the one <br>Billie Jean is not my lover <br>Billie Jean is not my lover <br>Billie Jean is not my lover <br>Billie Jean is not my lover <br>Billie Jean is not my lover <br>Billie Jean is not my lover]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Billie Jean (영화 `미녀 삼총사` / 원곡: 마이클 잭슨)" label="Billie Jean (영화 `미녀 삼총사` / 원곡: 마이클 잭슨)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Stand_By_Me_영화_편지___원곡__벤_이_킹/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Stand By Me (영화 `편지` / 원곡: 벤 이 킹) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Stand_By_Me_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%ED%8E%B8%EC%A7%80___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B2%A4_%EC%9D%B4_%ED%82%B9/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Stand By Me (영화 `편지` / 원곡: 벤 이 킹) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When the night has come <br>And the land is dark <br>And the moon is the only light we'll see <br>No I won't be afraid <br>Oh, I won't be afraid <br>Just as long as you stand, stand by me <br><br>So darling, darling <br>Stand by me, oh stand by me <br>Oh stand, stand by me <br>Stand by me <br><br>If the sky that we look upon <br>Should tumble and fall <br>Or the mountain should crumble to the sea <br>I won't cry, I won't cry <br>No, I won't shed a tear <br>Just as long as you stand, stand by me <br><br>And darling, darling <br>Stand by me, oh stand by me <br>Oh stand now, stand by me <br>Stand by me <br><br>So darling, darling <br>Stand by me, oh stand by me <br>Oh stand now, stand by me, stand by me <br>Whenever you're in trouble won't you stand by me <br>Oh stand by me, won't you stand now, oh, stand <br>Stand by me]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Stand By Me (영화 `편지` / 원곡: 벤 이 킹)" label="Stand By Me (영화 `편지` / 원곡: 벤 이 킹)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Evergreen_드라마_응답하라_1988___영화_스타_탄생___원곡__바브라_스트라이샌드/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Evergreen (드라마 `응답하라 1988` / 영화 `스타 탄생` / 원곡: 바브라 스트라이샌드) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Evergreen_%EB%93%9C%EB%9D%BC%EB%A7%88_%EC%9D%91%EB%8B%B5%ED%95%98%EB%9D%BC_1988___%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80_%ED%83%84%EC%83%9D___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B0%94%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%8C%EB%93%9C/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Evergreen (드라마 `응답하라 1988` / 영화 `스타 탄생` / 원곡: 바브라 스트라이샌드) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love soft as an easy chair <br>Love fresh as the morning air <br>One love that is shared by two <br>I have found with you <br><br>Like a rose under the April snow <br>I was always certain love would grow <br>Love ageless and evergreen <br>Seldom seen by two <br><br>You and I will make each night the first <br>Everyday a beginning <br>Spirits rise and their dance is unrehearsed <br>They warm and excite us, Cause we have the brightest love <br><br>Two lights that shine as one Morning glory and midnight sun <br>Time... we've learned to sail above <br>Time... won't change the meaning of one love <br>Ageless and ever evergreen... <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Evergreen (드라마 `응답하라 1988` / 영화 `스타 탄생` / 원곡: 바브라 스트라이샌드)" label="Evergreen (드라마 `응답하라 1988` / 영화 `스타 탄생` / 원곡: 바브라 스트라이샌드)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/My_Way_영화_친구___원곡__프랭크_시나트라/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - My Way (영화 `친구` / 원곡: 프랭크 시나트라) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/My_Way_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%ED%94%84%EB%9E%AD%ED%81%AC_%EC%8B%9C%EB%82%98%ED%8A%B8%EB%9D%BC/" title="World Pop Orchestra - My Way (영화 `친구` / 원곡: 프랭크 시나트라) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And now, the end is near <br>And so I face the final curtain <br>My friend, I'll say it clear <br>I'll state my case, of which I'm certain <br>I've lived a life that's full <br>I traveled each and every highway <br>And more, much more than this, I did it my way <br><br>Regrets, I've had a few <br>But then again, too few to mention <br>I did what I had to do and saw it through without exemption <br>I planned each charted course, each careful step along the byway <br>And more, much more than this, I did it my way <br><br>Yes, there were times, I'm sure you knew <br>When I bit off more than I could chew <br>But through it all, when there was doubt <br>I ate it up and spit it out <br>I faced it all and I stood tall and did it my way <br><br>I've loved, I've laughed and cried <br>I've had my fill, my share of losing <br>And now, as tears subside, I find it all so amusing <br>To think I did all that <br>And may I say, not in a shy way <br>Oh, no, oh, no, not me, I did it my way <br><br>For what is a man, what has he got? <br>If not himself, then he has naught <br>To say the things he truly feels and not the words of one who kneels <br>The record shows I took the blows and did it my way <br><br>Yes, it was my way <br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="My Way (영화 `친구` / 원곡: 프랭크 시나트라)" label="My Way (영화 `친구` / 원곡: 프랭크 시나트라)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Let_It_Be_영화_어크로스_더_유니버스___원곡__비틀즈/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Let It Be (영화 `어크로스 더 유니버스` / 원곡: 비틀즈) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Let_It_Be_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%96%B4%ED%81%AC%EB%A1%9C%EC%8A%A4_%EB%8D%94_%EC%9C%A0%EB%8B%88%EB%B2%84%EC%8A%A4___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B9%84%ED%8B%80%EC%A6%88/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Let It Be (영화 `어크로스 더 유니버스` / 원곡: 비틀즈) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I find myself in times of trouble <br>Mother Mary comes to me <br>Speaking words of wisdom, let it be <br>And in my hour of darkness <br>She is standing right in front of me <br>Speaking words of wisdom, let it be <br><br>Let it be, let it be <br>Let it be, let it be <br>Whisper words of wisdom, let it be <br><br>And when the broken-hearted people <br>Living in the world agree <br>There will be an answer, let it be <br>For though they may be parted <br>There is still a chance that they will see <br>There will be an answer, let it be <br><br>Let it be, let it be <br>Let it be, let it be <br>Yeah, there will be an answer, let it be <br>Let it be, let it be <br>Let it be, let it be <br>Whisper words of wisdom, let it be <br><br>Let it be, let it be <br>Ah, let it be, yeah, let it be <br>Whisper words of wisdom, let it be <br><br>And when the night is cloudy <br>There is still a light that shines on me <br>Shine on until tomorrow, let it be <br>I wake up to the sound of music, <br>Mother Mary comes to me <br>Speaking words of wisdom, let it be <br><br>Let it be, let it be <br>Let it be, yeah, let it be <br>Oh, there will be an answer, let it be <br>Let it be, let it be <br>Let it be, yeah, let it be <br>Whisper words of wisdom, let it be]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Let It Be (영화 `어크로스 더 유니버스` / 원곡: 비틀즈)" label="Let It Be (영화 `어크로스 더 유니버스` / 원곡: 비틀즈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Music_Of_The_Night_뮤지컬_오페라의_유령/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - The Music Of The Night (뮤지컬 `오페라의 유령`) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_Music_Of_The_Night_%EB%AE%A4%EC%A7%80%EC%BB%AC_%EC%98%A4%ED%8E%98%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%98_%EC%9C%A0%EB%A0%B9/" title="World Pop Orchestra - The Music Of The Night (뮤지컬 `오페라의 유령`) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Night time sharpens <br>heightens each sensation... <br>Darkness wakes <br>and stirs imagination <br>Silently the senses <br>abandon their defences <br>Helpless to resist <br>the notes I write <br>For I compose <br>the music of the night... <br><br>Slowly, gently <br>night unfurls its splendour. <br>Grasp it, sense it - <br>tremulous and tender <br>Hearing is believing <br>music is deceiving <br>Hard as lightning <br>soft as candlelight <br>dare you trust <br>the music of the night... <br><br>Close your eyes <br>for your eyes will only tell the truth <br>And the truth <br>isn't what you want to see. <br>In the dark <br>it is easy to pretend <br>that the truth <br>is what it ought to be. <br><br>Softly, deftly <br>music shall caress you... <br>Hear it, feel it <br>secretly possess you... <br><br>Open up your mind <br>let your fantasies unwind <br>in this darkness which <br>you know you cannot fight - <br>the darkness of <br>the music of the night... <br><br>Close your eyes <br>start a journey through a <br>strange new world! <br>Leave all thoughts <br>of the world <br>you knew before! <br><br>Close your eyes <br>and let music set you free... <br>Only then <br>can you belong to me... <br><br>Floating, falling <br>sweet intoxication! <br>Touch me, trust me <br>savour each sensation... <br><br>Let the dream <br>begin <br>let your darker side <br>give in <br>to the power of <br>the music that I write - <br>the power of <br>the music of the night... <br><br>You alone <br>can make my song take flight - <br>help me make <br>the music of the night... <br><br>Come we must return - <br>those two fools <br>who run my theatre <br>will be missing you...]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="The Music Of The Night (뮤지컬 `오페라의 유령`)" label="The Music Of The Night (뮤지컬 `오페라의 유령`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/I_Left_My_Heart_In_San_Francisco_원곡__토니_베넷/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - I Left My Heart In San Francisco (원곡: 토니 베넷) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/I_Left_My_Heart_In_San_Francisco_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%ED%86%A0%EB%8B%88_%EB%B2%A0%EB%84%B7/" title="World Pop Orchestra - I Left My Heart In San Francisco (원곡: 토니 베넷) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The loveliness of Paris seems somehow sadly gay <br>The glory that was Rome is of another day <br>I've been terribly alone and forgotten in Manhattan <br>I'm going home to my city by the Bay <br><br>I left my heart in San Francisco <br>High on a hill, it calls to me <br>To be where little cable cars climb halfway to the stars <br>The morning fog may chill the air, I don't care <br><br>My love waits there in San Francisco <br>Above the blue and windy sea <br>When I come home to you, San Francisco <br>Your golden sun will shine for me]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="I Left My Heart In San Francisco (원곡: 토니 베넷)" label="I Left My Heart In San Francisco (원곡: 토니 베넷)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Waterloo_영화_마션_맘마미아___원곡__아바/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Waterloo (영화 `마션`, `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Waterloo_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%A7%88%EC%85%98_%EB%A7%98%EB%A7%88%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%84___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%95%84%EB%B0%94/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Waterloo (영화 `마션`, `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My, my, at Waterloo Napoleon did surrender <br>Oh yeah, and I have met my destiny in quite a similar way <br>The history book on the shelf <br>Is always repeating itself <br><br>Waterloo - I was defeated, you won the war <br>Waterloo - Promise to love you for ever more <br>Waterloo - Couldn't escape if I wanted to <br>Waterloo - Knowing my fate is to be with you <br>Waterloo - Finally facing my Waterloo <br><br>My, my, I tried to hold you back but you were stronger <br>Oh yeah, and now it seems my only chance is giving up the fight <br>And how could I ever refuse <br>I feel like I win when I lose <br><br>Waterloo - I was defeated, you won the war <br>Waterloo - Promise to love you for ever more <br>Waterloo - Couldn't escape if I wanted to <br>Waterloo - Knowing my fate is to be with you <br>Waterloo - Finally facing my Waterloo <br><br>So how could I ever refuse <br>I feel like I win when I lose - <br><br>Waterloo - Couldn't escape if I wanted to <br>Waterloo - Knowing my fate is to be with you <br>Waterloo - Finally facing my Waterloo]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Waterloo (영화 `마션`, `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)" label="Waterloo (영화 `마션`, `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Blowin_In_The_Wind_영화_포레스트_검프___원곡__피터_폴_앤_메리/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Blowin` In The Wind (영화 `포레스트 검프` / 원곡: 피터, 폴 앤 메리) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Blowin_In_The_Wind_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%ED%8F%AC%EB%A0%88%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8_%EA%B2%80%ED%94%84___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%ED%94%BC%ED%84%B0_%ED%8F%B4_%EC%95%A4_%EB%A9%94%EB%A6%AC/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Blowin` In The Wind (영화 `포레스트 검프` / 원곡: 피터, 폴 앤 메리) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How many roads must a man walk down <br>Before they call him a man? <br>How many seas must a white dove sail <br>Before she sleeps in the sand? <br>How many times must the cannon balls fly <br>Before they're forever banned? <br><br>The answer, my friend, is blowin' in the wind <br>The answer is blowin' in the wind. <br><br>How many years must a mountain exist <br>Before it is washed to the sea? <br>How many years can some people exist <br>Before they're allowed to be free? <br>How many times can a man turn his head <br>And pretend that he just doesn't see? <br><br>The answer, my friend, is blowin' in the wind <br>The answer is blowin' in the wind. <br><br>How many times must a man look up <br>Before he can see the sky? <br>How many ears must one man have <br>Before he can hear people cry? <br>How many deaths will it take 'til he knows <br>That too many people have died? <br><br>The answer, my friend, is blowin' in the wind <br>The answer is blowin' in the wind. <br>The answer is blowin' in the wind.]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Blowin` In The Wind (영화 `포레스트 검프` / 원곡: 피터, 폴 앤 메리)" label="Blowin` In The Wind (영화 `포레스트 검프` / 원곡: 피터, 폴 앤 메리)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Save_The_Last_Dance_For_Me_MBC_세시봉_콘서트___영화_쉘_위_댄스___원곡__드리프터즈/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Save The Last Dance For Me (MBC `세시봉 콘서트` / 영화 `쉘 위 댄스` / 원곡: 드리프터즈) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Save_The_Last_Dance_For_Me_MBC_%EC%84%B8%EC%8B%9C%EB%B4%89_%EC%BD%98%EC%84%9C%ED%8A%B8___%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%89%98_%EC%9C%84_%EB%8C%84%EC%8A%A4___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%93%9C%EB%A6%AC%ED%94%84%ED%84%B0%EC%A6%88/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Save The Last Dance For Me (MBC `세시봉 콘서트` / 영화 `쉘 위 댄스` / 원곡: 드리프터즈) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You can dance <br>Every dance with the guy <br>Who gave you the eye <br>Let him hold you tight <br><br>You can smile <br>Every smile for the man <br>Who held your hand <br>'Neath the pale moonlight <br><br>But don't forget who's taking you home <br>And in whose arms you're gonna be <br>So darlin' <br>Save the last dance for me, mmm <br><br>Oh I know <br>That the music is fine <br>Like sparkling wine <br>Go and have your fun <br><br>Laugh and sing <br>But while we're apart <br>Don't give your heart <br>To anyone <br><br>But don't forget who's taking you home <br>And in whose arms you're gonna be <br>So darlin' <br>Save the last dance for me, mmm <br><br>Baby don't you know I love you so <br>Can't you feel it when we touch <br>I will never, never let you go <br>I love you oh so much <br><br>You can dance <br>Go and carry on <br>Till the night is gone <br>And it's time to go <br><br>If he asks <br>If you're all alone <br>Can he take you home <br>You must tell him no <br><br>'Cause don't forget who's taking you home <br>And in whose arms you're gonna be <br>So darlin' <br>Save the last dance for me <br><br>'Cause don't forget who's taking you home <br>And in whose arms you're gonna be <br>So darlin' <br>Save the last dance for me, mmm <br><br>Save the last dance for me, mmm <br>Save the last dance for me]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Save The Last Dance For Me (MBC `세시봉 콘서트` / 영화 `쉘 위 댄스` / 원곡: 드리프터즈)" label="Save The Last Dance For Me (MBC `세시봉 콘서트` / 영화 `쉘 위 댄스` / 원곡: 드리프터즈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/LOVE_원곡__넷_킹_콜/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - L.O.V.E. (원곡: 넷 킹 콜) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/LOVE_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%84%B7_%ED%82%B9_%EC%BD%9C/" title="World Pop Orchestra - L.O.V.E. (원곡: 넷 킹 콜) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[L is for the way you look at me <br>O is for the only one I see <br>V is very, very extraordinary <br>E is even more than anyone that you adore can <br><br>Love is all that I can give to you <br>Love is more than just a game for two <br>Two in love can make it <br>Take my heart and please don't break it <br>Love was made for me and you <br><br>L is for the way you look at me <br>O is for the only one I see <br>V is very, very extraordinary <br>E is even more than anyone that you adore can <br><br>Love is all that I can give to you <br>Love is more than just a game for two <br>Two in love can make it <br>Take my heart and please don't break it <br>Love was made for me and you <br>Love was made for me and you <br>Love was made for me and you <br><br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="L.O.V.E. (원곡: 넷 킹 콜)" label="L.O.V.E. (원곡: 넷 킹 콜)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/If_You_Dont_Know_Me_By_Now_영화_마이걸___원곡__심플리_레드/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - If You Don`t Know Me By Now (영화 `마이걸` / 원곡: 심플리 레드) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/If_You_Dont_Know_Me_By_Now_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B4%EA%B1%B8___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%8B%AC%ED%94%8C%EB%A6%AC_%EB%A0%88%EB%93%9C/" title="World Pop Orchestra - If You Don`t Know Me By Now (영화 `마이걸` / 원곡: 심플리 레드) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If you don't know me by now <br>You will never never never know me <br><br>All the things <br>That we've been through <br>You should understand me <br>Like I understand you <br>Now girl I know the difference <br>Between right and wrong <br>I ain't gonna do nothing <br>To break up our happy home <br>Don't get so excited <br>When I come home <br>A little late at night <br>Cos we only act like children <br>When we argue fuss and fight <br><br>If you don't know me by now <br>You will never never never know me <br><br>We've all got our <br>Own funny moods <br>I've got mine, <br>Woman you've got yours too <br>Just trust in me like I trust in you <br>As long as we've been together <br>It should be so easy to do <br>Just get yourself together <br>Or we might as well say goodbye <br>What good is a love affair <br>When you can't see eye to eye <br><br>If you don't know me by now <br>You will never <br>Never never know me]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="If You Don`t Know Me By Now (영화 `마이걸` / 원곡: 심플리 레드)" label="If You Don`t Know Me By Now (영화 `마이걸` / 원곡: 심플리 레드)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Eye_Of_The_Tiger_영화_록키_3___원곡__서바이버/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Eye Of The Tiger (영화 `록키 3` / 원곡: 서바이버) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Eye_Of_The_Tiger_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%A1%9D%ED%82%A4_3___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%84%9C%EB%B0%94%EC%9D%B4%EB%B2%84/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Eye Of The Tiger (영화 `록키 3` / 원곡: 서바이버) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Risin' up, back on the street <br>Took my time, <br>Took my chances <br>Went the distance <br>Now I'm back on my feet <br>Just a man and his will to survive <br><br>So many times, <br>it happened too fast <br>You trade your passion for glory <br>Don't lose your grip <br>on the dreams of the past <br>You must fight just to keep them alive <br><br>It's the eye of the tiger <br>It's the thrill of the fight <br>Risin' up to the challenge of our rival <br>And the last known survivor <br>Stalks his prey in the night <br>And he's watching us all with <br>The eye of the tiger <br><br>Face to face, out in the heat <br>Hangin' tough, stayin' hungry <br>They stack the odds <br>Still we take to the street <br>For the kill with the skill to survive <br><br>It's the eye of the tiger <br>It's the thrill of the fight <br>Risin' up to the challenge of our rival <br>And the last known survivor <br>Stalks his prey in the night <br>And his fortune must always be <br>Eye of the tiger <br><br>Risin' up straight to the top <br>Having guts, got the glory <br>Went the distance <br>Now I'm not gonna stop <br>Just a man and his will to survive <br><br>It's the eye of the tiger <br>It's the thrill of the fight <br>Risin' up to the challenge of our rival <br>And the last known survivor <br>Stalks his prey in the night <br>And he's watching us all with <br>The eye of the tiger]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Eye Of The Tiger (영화 `록키 3` / 원곡: 서바이버)" label="Eye Of The Tiger (영화 `록키 3` / 원곡: 서바이버)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Besame_Mucho_영화_위대한_유산/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Besame Mucho (영화 `위대한 유산`) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Besame_Mucho_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%9C%84%EB%8C%80%ED%95%9C_%EC%9C%A0%EC%82%B0/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Besame Mucho (영화 `위대한 유산`) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Besame, Besame mucho <br>Como si fuera esta noche <br>La ultima vez. <br><br>Besame, besame mucho <br>Que tengo miedo a perderte <br>Perderte despues. <br><br>Besame, Besame mucho <br>Como si fuera esta noche <br> a ultima vez <br><br>Besame, besame mucho <br>Que tengo miedo a perderte <br>Perderte despues <br><br>Quiero tenerte muy cerca <br>Mirarme en tus ojos <br>Verte junto a mi <br>Piensa que tal vez manana <br>Yo ya estare Lejos, <br>Muy lejos de ti. <br><br>Besame, Besame mucho <br>Como si fuera esta noche <br>La ultima vez. <br><br>Besame, besame mucho <br>Que tengo miedo a perderte <br>Perderte despues. <br><br>Besame, Besame mucho <br>Que tengo miedo a perderte <br>Perderte despues. <br><br>Que tengo miedo a perderte <br>Perderte despues.]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Besame Mucho (영화 `위대한 유산`)" label="Besame Mucho (영화 `위대한 유산`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Woman_In_Love_원곡__바브라_스트라이샌드/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Woman In Love (원곡: 바브라 스트라이샌드) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Woman_In_Love_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%B0%94%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%8C%EB%93%9C/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Woman In Love (원곡: 바브라 스트라이샌드) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Life is a moment in space <br>When the dream is gone it's a lonelier place <br>I kiss the morning goodbye <br>But down inside you know we never know why <br><br>The road is narrow and long <br>When eyes meet eyes and the feeling is strong <br>I turn away from the wall <br>I stumble and fall but i give you it all <br><br>I am a woman in love <br>And i'd do anything to get you into my world and hold you within <br>It's a right i defend over and over again <br>What do i do? <br><br>With you eternally mine <br>In love there is no measure of time <br>We planned it all at the start <br>That you and i live in each other's heart <br><br>We may be oceans away <br>You feel my love i hear what you say <br>No truth is ever a lie <br>I stumble and fall but i give you it all <br><br>I am a woman in love <br>And i'd do anything to get you into my world and hold you within <br>It's a right i defend over and over again <br>What do i do? <br><br>Ohh i am a woman in love and i'm talking to you <br>I know how you feel what a woman can do <br>It's a right i defend over and over again <br><br>I am a woman in love <br>And i'd do anything to get you into my world and hold you within <br>It's a right i defend over and over again]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Woman In Love (원곡: 바브라 스트라이샌드)" label="Woman In Love (원곡: 바브라 스트라이샌드)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Lovin_You_영화_브리짓_존스의_일기___원곡__미니_리퍼튼/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Lovin` You (영화 `브리짓 존스의 일기` / 원곡: 미니 리퍼튼) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Lovin_You_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%AC%EC%A7%93_%EC%A1%B4%EC%8A%A4%EC%9D%98_%EC%9D%BC%EA%B8%B0___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%AF%B8%EB%8B%88_%EB%A6%AC%ED%8D%BC%ED%8A%BC/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Lovin` You (영화 `브리짓 존스의 일기` / 원곡: 미니 리퍼튼) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Loving you it's easy <br>Cause you're beautiful <br>Making love with you is all I want to do <br><br>Loving you is more than <br>just a dream come true <br>And everything that I do <br>is out of loving you <br><br>La la la la la, do do do do do do <br><br>No one else can make me feel <br>the colours that you bring <br>Stay with me while we grow old <br>And we will live each day in springtime <br><br>Cause loving you has made <br>my life so beautiful <br>And everyday of my life <br>is filled with loving you <br><br>Loving you I see your soul <br>come shining through <br>And every time that we ooh <br>I'm more in love with you <br><br>La la la la la, do do do do do do <br><br>No one else can make me feel <br>the colours that you bring <br>Stay with me while we grow old <br>And we will live each day in springtime <br><br>Cause loving you it's easy <br>Cause you're beautiful <br>And everyday of my life <br>is filled with loving you <br><br>Loving you I see your soul <br>come shining through <br>And every time that we ooh <br>I'm more in love with you <br><br>La la la la la, do do do do do do <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Lovin` You (영화 `브리짓 존스의 일기` / 원곡: 미니 리퍼튼)" label="Lovin` You (영화 `브리짓 존스의 일기` / 원곡: 미니 리퍼튼)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Knowing_Me_Knowing_You_영화_맘마미아___원곡__아바/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Knowing Me Knowing You (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Knowing_Me_Knowing_You_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%A7%98%EB%A7%88%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%84___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%95%84%EB%B0%94/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Knowing Me Knowing You (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No more carefree laughter <br>Silence ever after <br>Walking through an empty house, tears in my eyes <br>Here is where the story ends, this is goodbye <br><br>Knowing me, knowing you (ah-haa) <br>There is nothing we can do <br>Knowing me, knowing you (ah-haa) <br>We just have to face it, this time we're through <br>(This time we're through, this time we're through <br>This time we're through, we're really through) <br>Breaking up is never easy, I know but I have to go <br>(I have to go this time <br>I have to go, this time I know) <br>Knowing me, knowing you <br>It's the best I can do <br><br>Mem'ries (mem'ries), good days (good days), bad days (bad days) <br>They'll be (they'll be), with me (with me) always (always) <br>In these old familiar rooms children would play <br>Now there's only emptiness, nothing to say <br><br>Knowing me, knowing you (ah-haa) <br>There is nothing we can do <br>Knowing me, knowing you (ah-haa) <br>We just have to face it, this time we're through <br>(This time we're through, this time we're through <br>This time we're through, we′re really through) <br>Breaking up is never easy, I know but I have to go <br>(I have to go this time <br>I have to go, this time I know) <br>Knowing me, knowing you <br>It's the best I can do <br><br>(Repeat)]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Knowing Me Knowing You (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)" label="Knowing Me Knowing You (영화 `맘마미아` / 원곡: 아바)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Fragile_원곡__스팅/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Fragile (원곡: 스팅) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Fragile_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%8A%A4%ED%8C%85/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Fragile (원곡: 스팅) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If blood will flow when flesh and steel are one <br>Drying in the color of the evening sun <br>Tomorrow's rain will wash the stains away <br>But something in our minds will always stay <br><br>Perhaps this final act was meant <br>To clinch a lifetime's argument <br>That nothing comes from violence <br>and nothing ever could <br>For all those born beneath an angry star <br>Lest we forget how fragile we are <br><br>On and on the rain will fall <br>Like tears from a star like tears from a star <br>On and on the rain will say <br>How fragile we are <br>How fragile we are <br><br>On and on the rain will fall <br>Like tears from a star like tears from a star <br>On and on the rain will say <br>How fragile we are <br>How fragile we are]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Fragile (원곡: 스팅)" label="Fragile (원곡: 스팅)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Careless_Whisper_영화_데드풀___원곡__왬/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Careless Whisper (영화 `데드풀` / 원곡: 왬) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Careless_Whisper_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EB%8D%B0%EB%93%9C%ED%92%80___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%99%AC/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Careless Whisper (영화 `데드풀` / 원곡: 왬) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I feel so unsure <br>As I take your hand and lead you to the dance floor <br>As the music dies, something in your eyes <br>Calls to mind a silver screen <br>And all it's sad goodbyes <br><br>I'm never gonna dance again <br>Guilty feet have gotten no rhythm <br>Though it's easy to pretend <br>I know you're not a fool <br><br>I should have known better than to cheat a friend <br>And waste the chance that I've been given <br>So I'm never gonna dance again <br>The way I danced with you <br><br>Time can never mend <br>The careless whispers of a good friend <br>To the heart and mind <br>Ignorance is kind <br>There's no comfort in the truth <br>Pain is all you'll find <br><br>I'm never gonna dance again <br>Guilty feet have got no rhythm <br>Though it's easy to pretend <br>I know you're not a fool <br><br>I should have known better than to cheat a friend <br>And waste the chance that I've been given <br>So I'm never gonna dance again <br>The way I danced with you <br><br>Tonight the music seems so loud <br>I wish that we could lose this crowd <br>Maybe it's better this way <br>We''d hurt each other with the things we'd wanna say <br><br>We could have been so good together <br>We could have lived this dance forever <br>But now who's gonna dance with me? <br>Please stay <br><br>And I'm never gonna dance again <br>Guilty feet have got no rhythm <br>Though it's easy to pretend <br>I know you're not a fool <br><br>I should have known better than to cheat a friend <br>And waste the chance that I've been given <br>So I'm never gonna dance again <br>The way I danced with you <br><br>(Now that you're gone) Now that you're gone <br>(Now that you're gone) Was what I did so wrong, so wrong <br>That you had to leave me alone]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Careless Whisper (영화 `데드풀` / 원곡: 왬)" label="Careless Whisper (영화 `데드풀` / 원곡: 왬)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Against_All_Odds_영화_어케인스트_올_오즈___원곡__필_콜린스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Against All Odds (영화 `어케인스트 올 오즈` / 원곡: 필 콜린스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Against_All_Odds_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%96%B4%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B8%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8_%EC%98%AC_%EC%98%A4%EC%A6%88___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%ED%95%84_%EC%BD%9C%EB%A6%B0%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Against All Odds (영화 `어케인스트 올 오즈` / 원곡: 필 콜린스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How can I just let you walk away, just let you leave without a trace <br>When I stand here taking every breath with you, ooh <br>You're the only one who really knew me at all <br><br>How can you just walk away from me, <br>When all I can do is watch you leave <br>Cause we've shared the laughter and the pain and even shared the tears <br>You're the only one who really knew me at all <br><br>So take a look at me now, oh there's just an empty space <br>And there's nothing left here to remind me, <br>Just the memory of your face <br>Ooh take a look at me now, well there's just an empty space <br>And you coming back to me is against the odds and that's what I've got to face <br><br>I wish I could just make you turn around, <br>Turn around and see me cry <br>There's so much I need to say to you, <br>So many reasons why <br>You're the only one who really knew me at all <br><br>So take a look at me now, well there's just an empty space <br>And there's nothing left here to remind me, just the memory of your face <br>Now take a look at me now, cause there's just an empty space <br><br>But to wait for you, is all I can do and that's what I've got to face <br>Take a good look at me now, cause I'll still be standing here <br>And you coming back to me is against all odds <br>It's the chance I've gotta take <br><br>Take a look at me now <br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Against All Odds (영화 `어케인스트 올 오즈` / 원곡: 필 콜린스)" label="Against All Odds (영화 `어케인스트 올 오즈` / 원곡: 필 콜린스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_First_Time_Ever_I_Saw_Your_Face_영화_어둠_속에_벨이_울릴_때___원곡__로베타_플랙/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - The First Time Ever I Saw Your Face (영화 `어둠 속에 벨이 울릴 때` / 원곡: 로베타 플랙) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/The_First_Time_Ever_I_Saw_Your_Face_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%96%B4%EB%91%A0_%EC%86%8D%EC%97%90_%EB%B2%A8%EC%9D%B4_%EC%9A%B8%EB%A6%B4_%EB%95%8C___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%A1%9C%EB%B2%A0%ED%83%80_%ED%94%8C%EB%9E%99/" title="World Pop Orchestra - The First Time Ever I Saw Your Face (영화 `어둠 속에 벨이 울릴 때` / 원곡: 로베타 플랙) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The first time ever I saw your face <br>I thought the sun rose in your eyes <br>And the moon and the stars were the gifts you gave <br>To the dark and the endless skies, my love <br>To the dark and the endless skies <br><br>And the first time ever I kissed your mouth <br>I felt the earth move in my hand <br>Like the trembling heart of a captive bird <br>That was there at my command, my love <br>That was there at my command, my love <br><br>And the first time ever I lay with you <br>I felt your heart so close to mine <br>And I knew our joy would fill the earth <br>And last 'til the end of time, my love <br>And it would last 'til the end of time, my love <br><br>The first time ever I saw your face <br>Your face <br>Your face <br>Your face <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="The First Time Ever I Saw Your Face (영화 `어둠 속에 벨이 울릴 때` / 원곡: 로베타 플랙)" label="The First Time Ever I Saw Your Face (영화 `어둠 속에 벨이 울릴 때` / 원곡: 로베타 플랙)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/When_I_Need_You_원곡__리오_세이어/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - When I Need You (원곡: 리오 세이어) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/When_I_Need_You_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%A6%AC%EC%98%A4_%EC%84%B8%EC%9D%B4%EC%96%B4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - When I Need You (원곡: 리오 세이어) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I need you <br>I just close my eyes and I'm with you <br>And all that I so want to give you <br>It's only a heartbeat away <br><br>When I need love <br>I hold out my hands and I touch love <br>I never knew there was so much love <br>Keeping me warm night and day <br><br>Miles and miles of empty space in between us <br>The telephone can't take the place of your smile <br>But you know I won't be traveling forever <br>It's cold out, but hold out, and do I like I do <br><br>When I need you <br>I just close my eyes and I'm with you <br>And all that I so wanna give you babe <br>It's only a heartbeat away <br><br>It's not easy when the road is your driver <br>Honey that's a heavy load that we bear <br>But you know I won't be traveling a lifetime <br>It's cold out, but hold out, and do like I do <br>Oh, I need you <br><br>When I need love <br>I hold out my hands and I touch love <br>I never knew there was so much love <br>Keeping me warm night and day <br><br>When I need you <br>I just close my eyes <br>and you're right here by my side <br>keeping me warm night and day <br><br>I just hold out my hands <br>I just hold out my hands <br>And I'm with you darling <br>Yes, I'm with you darling <br>All I wanna give you <br>It's only a heartbeat away <br>Oh I need you darling]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="When I Need You (원곡: 리오 세이어)" label="When I Need You (원곡: 리오 세이어)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Lady_원곡__케니_로저스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Lady (원곡: 케니 로저스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Lady_%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%BC%80%EB%8B%88_%EB%A1%9C%EC%A0%80%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Lady (원곡: 케니 로저스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lady, I'm your knight in shining armor and I love you <br>You have made me what I am and I am yours <br>My love, there's so many ways I want to say I love you <br>Let me hold you in my arms forever more <br><br>You have gone and made me such a fool <br>I'm so lost in your love <br>And oh, we belong together <br>Won't you believe in my song? <br><br>Lady, for so many years I thought I'd never find you <br>You have come into my life and made me whole <br>Forever let me wake to see you each and every morning <br>Let me hear you whisper softly in my ear <br><br>In my eyes I see no one else but you <br>There's no other love like our love <br>And yes, oh yes, I'll always want you near me <br>I've waited for you for so long <br><br>Lady, your love's the only love I need <br>And beside me is where I want you to be <br>'Cause, my love, there's somethin' I want you to know <br>You're the love of my life, you're my lady!]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Lady (원곡: 케니 로저스)" label="Lady (원곡: 케니 로저스)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Hello_영화_슈렉_포에버_패팅턴___원곡__라이오넬_리치/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Hello (영화 `슈렉 포에버`, `패팅턴` / 원곡: 라이오넬 리치) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Hello_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%8A%88%EB%A0%89_%ED%8F%AC%EC%97%90%EB%B2%84_%ED%8C%A8%ED%8C%85%ED%84%B4___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EC%98%A4%EB%84%AC_%EB%A6%AC%EC%B9%98/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Hello (영화 `슈렉 포에버`, `패팅턴` / 원곡: 라이오넬 리치) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ive been alone with you inside my mind <br>And in my dreams Ive kissed your lips a thousand times <br>I sometimes see you pass outside my door <br>Hello, is it me youre looking for? <br><br>I can see it in your eyes <br>I can see it in your smile <br>Youre all Ive ever wanted, and my arms are open wide <br>Cause you know just what to say <br>And you know just what to do <br>And I want to tell you so much, I love you <br><br>I long to see the sunlight in your hair <br>And tell you time and time again how much I care <br>Sometimes I feel my heart will overflow <br>Hello, Ive just got to let you know <br><br>Cause I wonder where you are <br>And I wonder what you do <br>Are you somewhere feeling lonely, or is someone loving you? <br>Tell me how to win your heart <br>For I havent got a clue <br>But let me start by saying, I love you <br><br>Hello, is it me youre looking for? <br>Cause I wonder where you are <br>And I wonder what you do <br>Are you somewhere feeling lonely, or is someone loving you? <br>Tell me how to win your heart <br>For I havent got a clue <br>But let me start by saying I love you]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Hello (영화 `슈렉 포에버`, `패팅턴` / 원곡: 라이오넬 리치)" label="Hello (영화 `슈렉 포에버`, `패팅턴` / 원곡: 라이오넬 리치)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Up_Where_We_Belong_영화_사관과_신사___원곡__조_카커_제니퍼_원스/</id><title>World Pop Orchestra - Up Where We Belong (영화 `사관과 신사` / 원곡: 조 카커, 제니퍼 원스) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T21:24:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T21:24:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/World_Pop_Orchestra/Up_Where_We_Belong_%EC%98%81%ED%99%94_%EC%82%AC%EA%B4%80%EA%B3%BC_%EC%8B%A0%EC%82%AC___%EC%9B%90%EA%B3%A1__%EC%A1%B0_%EC%B9%B4%EC%BB%A4_%EC%A0%9C%EB%8B%88%ED%8D%BC_%EC%9B%90%EC%8A%A4/" title="World Pop Orchestra - Up Where We Belong (영화 `사관과 신사` / 원곡: 조 카커, 제니퍼 원스) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Who knows what tomorrow brings <br>in a world few hearts survive <br>All I know is the way I feel <br>And if it's real <br>I'm keep it alive <br>the road is long <br>There are mountains in our way <br>But we climb still higher everyday <br>Love lift us up where we belong <br>Where the eagles fly <br>on a mountain high <br>Love lift us up where we belong <br>Up from the worlds we know <br>Where the clear winds blow <br><br>Som hang on what used to be <br>living your life looking behind <br>all we have is you right now <br>All our lives are in you tonight <br>the road is long <br>There are mountains in our way <br>But we climb still higher everyday <br>Love lift us up where we belong <br>Where the eagles fly <br>on a mountain high <br>Love lift us up where we belong <br>Up from the worlds we know <br>Where the clear winds blow <br>Times go by <br>No time to cry <br>Life's you and I alive today <br>Love lift us up where we belong <br>Where the eagles cry <br>on a mountain high <br>Love lift us up where we belong <br>Far from the world we know <br>up where clear winds blow <br>Love lift us up where we belong <br>Where the eagles cry <br>on a mountain high]]></content><category term="World Pop Orchestra" label="World Pop Orchestra"/><category term="Up Where We Belong (영화 `사관과 신사` / 원곡: 조 카커, 제니퍼 원스)" label="Up Where We Belong (영화 `사관과 신사` / 원곡: 조 카커, 제니퍼 원스)"/></entry></feed>