<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:31:16+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김호용/어느_날_만난_내_마음/</id><title>김호용 - 어느 날 만난 내 마음 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:31:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:31:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%98%B8%EC%9A%A9/%EC%96%B4%EB%8A%90_%EB%82%A0_%EB%A7%8C%EB%82%9C_%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C/" title="김호용 - 어느 날 만난 내 마음 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보고 싶다 <br>보고 싶다 <br>난 아직 그대를 사랑하는데 <br>그대는 그렇지 않아요 <br>그대 있다 <br>그대 있다 <br>모든 곳엔 그대의 흔적 있는데 <br>그대는 보이지 않아요 <br>그대 다시는 볼 수 없나요 <br>그대 눈빛 속에 나 <br>그대 행복했었던 시간들 <br>다시 돌아가 <br>그대 다시는 볼 수 없나요 <br>그대 눈빛 속에 나 <br>그대 행복했었던 시간들 <br>다시 돌아가 <br>그대 사랑은 진심이었죠 <br>영원히 기억해요 <br>언제나 따뜻했던 그 미소 <br>잃지 말아요 <br>]]></content><category term="김호용" label="김호용"/><category term="어느 날 만난 내 마음" label="어느 날 만난 내 마음"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정경순/Listen_To_This_Story/</id><title>정경순 - Listen To This Story - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:31:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:31:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B2%BD%EC%88%9C/Listen_To_This_Story/" title="정경순 - Listen To This Story - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Listen to this story <br>It is now common <br>Birds are singing and <br>the wind whispering <br>Listen to this story <br>It is now common <br>Birds are singing and <br>the wind whispering <br>Listen to me It is like a dream <br>I think the magic I think dreaming <br>Maybe you would not know my feeling <br>Maybe you'll never really imagine <br>Just two of us <br>It is beautiful world <br>Don't worry about anything <br>Maybe you would not know my feeling <br>Maybe you'll never really imagine <br>Just two of us <br>It is beautiful world <br>Don't worry about anything <br>Maybe you would not know my feeling <br>Maybe you'll never really imagine <br>Just two of us <br>It is beautiful world <br>Don't worry about anything <br>Maybe you would not know my feeling <br>Maybe you'll never really imagine <br>Just two of us <br>It is beautiful world <br>Don't worry about anything <br>Don't worry about anything <br>Don't worry about anything <br>Listen to this story <br>It is like a dream <br>]]></content><category term="정경순" label="정경순"/><category term="Listen To This Story" label="Listen To This Story"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김찬오/Bye_All_Let/</id><title>김찬오 - Bye All Let - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:31:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:31:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%B0%AC%EC%98%A4/Bye_All_Let/" title="김찬오 - Bye All Let - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't forget me <br>지워지는 그림자 속에 <br>Don't forget me <br>젖어가는 어둠 안에서 <br>Don't forget me <br>피어나는 빗소리처럼 <br>Don't forget me <br>오지 않을 바람 곁에서 <br>so thank you told me <br>so thanks to say me <br>and don't forget me <br>you don't be sad bye all let <br>너 떠난 뒤에 <br>너 떠난 자리에 <br>피어나는 그 향기는 <br>bye all let <br>Don't forget me <br>가둘 수 없는 아픔 안에 <br>Don't forget me <br>잡을 수 없는 하늘 아래 <br>Don't forget me <br>멀어지는 시간 안에서 <br>Don't forget me <br>다가오는 너의 눈빛에 <br>so thank you told me <br>so thanks to say me <br>and don't forget me <br>you don't be sad bye all let <br>너 떠난 뒤에 <br>너 떠난 자리에 <br>피어나는 그 향기는 <br>bye all let <br>]]></content><category term="김찬오" label="김찬오"/><category term="Bye All Let" label="Bye All Let"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이봄/위로/</id><title>이봄 - 위로 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:31:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:31:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B4%84/%EC%9C%84%EB%A1%9C/" title="이봄 - 위로 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘은 정말 내겐 <br>너무 벅찬 하루였어요 <br>남들에겐 아무렇지 <br>않았겠지만 <br>견디다 보면 이 아픔도 <br>몰래 숨어 흘린 눈물도 <br>모두 지나가겠지만 <br>쉽진 않네요 <br>내가 사랑하는 사람들마저 <br>나를 외면하는 것만 같아 <br>슬퍼지면 <br>나는 어떡해야 하나요 <br>지쳐 힘들어 모든 걸 다 <br>포기하고 싶어서 <br>울어 봐도 소리 쳐봐도 <br>기댈 곳 하나 없어 <br>누구라도 내게 <br>다가와 아픈 눈물 닦아주면 <br>괜찮을 텐데 정말 괜찮을 텐데 <br>나를 바라보던 <br>사람들마저 <br>뒤돌아서 떠나갈 것 같아 <br>두려워지면 <br>나는 어떡해야 할까요 <br>지쳐 힘들어 모든 걸 다 <br>포기하고 싶어서 <br>울어 봐도 소리 쳐봐도 <br>기댈 곳 하나 없어 <br>누구라도 내게 <br>다가와 아픈 눈물 닦아주면 <br>괜찮을 텐데 정말 괜찮을 텐데 <br>정말 괜찮을 텐데 <br>지쳐 힘들어 모든 걸 다 <br>포기하고 싶어서 <br>울어 봐도 소리 쳐봐도 <br>닿을 곳 하나 없어 <br>누구라도 내게 <br>다가와 지친 마음 안아주면 <br>괜찮을 텐데 정말 괜찮을 텐데 <br>]]></content><category term="이봄" label="이봄"/><category term="위로" label="위로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAHANDSOME_나핸썸/니_주말은_언제나_내꺼_Wit_Me/</id><title>NAHANDSOME (나핸썸) - 니 주말은 언제나 내꺼 (Wit Me) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:33:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:33:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAHANDSOME_%EB%82%98%ED%95%B8%EC%8D%B8/%EB%8B%88_%EC%A3%BC%EB%A7%90%EC%9D%80_%EC%96%B8%EC%A0%9C%EB%82%98_%EB%82%B4%EA%BA%BC_Wit_Me/" title="NAHANDSOME (나핸썸) - 니 주말은 언제나 내꺼 (Wit Me) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hold up she called me <br>한국 흑인 like that <br>날아다녀 Like <br>I'm Desiigner's dab <br>밤마다 너를 <br>마시지 Champagne <br>나는 먹고 싶은 건 <br>결국 먹지 baby <br>I got you shawty <br>Swallow my D <br>그녀는 너무 화끈해서 <br>Like WASABI <br>날아서 난 그녀에게 <br>벌처럼 쏘지 <br>운동하는 여자 엉덩인 <br>너무 좋아 Hold up <br>평범한 여자도 <br>나랑 있으면 예뻐 <br>넌 예뻐 니 주말은 <br>언제나 내꺼 <br>니 뒷모습이 말하지 <br>She wanna <br>나처럼 튀는 남잘 <br>해본 게 니 첫경험 <br>Baby 난 잘생긴 얼굴 <br>자신감까지 원빈 <br>SWAG은 하늘 끝까지 <br>NAHANDSOME They Call Me <br>SWAG KING <br>니 여친이 좋아하는 <br>내 옷차림 <br>너같은 여자가 <br>날 채워줘 내 빈자릴 <br>난 Da Vinci 넌 그림이고 <br>다른 여잔 다 Bih <br>She just wanna be <br>my Gangsta Bih <br>나 거짓말 못하게 하는 <br>니 다리 날 겸손하게 <br>만들어 니 허리 <br>Shawty 난 너의 <br>새벽 두시 2am <br>Yes I am she call me Rollie <br>넌 Lolly Stephen Curry ballin' <br>She fallin' me <br>너한테 난 <br>Love and HipHop only <br>Got it on me <br>다 좋아하지 <br>everybody love me <br>Hold up she called me <br>한국 흑인 like that <br>날아다녀 Like <br>I'm Desiigner's dab <br>밤마다 너를 <br>마시지 Champagne <br>나는 먹고 싶은 건 <br>결국 먹지 baby <br>I got you shawty <br>Swallow my D <br>그녀는 너무 화끈해서 <br>Like WASABI <br>날아서 난 그녀에게 <br>벌처럼 쏘지 <br>운동하는 여자 엉덩인 <br>너무 좋아 hold up <br>니 엉덩인 My heart <br>바퀴처럼 skrr now I'm run <br>Baby we in the club <br>마지막처럼 오늘도 <br>맨날 그냥 돈 버는 거 <br>I know you love <br>Puss money love <br>I know It's love <br>너를 볼 때마다 <br>자꾸 하는 말 <br>OH MA OH GOD <br>THANK GOD OH 난 <br>I'm hustle mania <br>GYM하지 MuscleMania <br>You know me hustle <br>never stop <br>What you think VIKISI <br>입은 넌 마네킹 <br>아래 위 넌 답이지 <br>갑이지 Freakin' hip <br>말 안해도 알잖아 <br>다 되지 넌 여전히 <br>Baby calm down calm down <br>calm down you gotta trust me <br>주말마다 니안에 들어가지 <br>난 <br>여자들만 아는 척 하지 <br>Right Now <br>그녀는 힙합 노래만 <br>들으면 내 생각 <br>뮤비처럼 살지 A-Town <br>Hold up she called me <br>한국 흑인 like that <br>날아다녀 Like <br>I'm Desiigner's dab <br>밤마다 너를 <br>마시지 Champagne <br>나는 먹고 싶은 건 <br>결국 먹지 baby <br>I got you shawty <br>Swallow my D <br>그녀는 너무 화끈해서 <br>Like WASABI <br>날아서 난 그녀에게 <br>벌처럼 쏘지 <br>운동하는 여자 엉덩인 <br>너무 좋아 Hold up <br>Baby shawty show me <br>what you got I creat <br>I'm a new wave <br>그녀는 지금 내 파도만 타지 <br>I know my lady <br>Baby shawty show me <br>what you got I creat <br>I'm a new wave <br>그녀는 지금 내 파도만 타지 <br>I know my lady <br>Hold up she called me <br>한국 흑인 like that <br>날아다녀 Like <br>I'm Desiigner's dab <br>밤마다 너를 <br>마시지 Champagne <br>나는 먹고 싶은 건 <br>결국 먹지 baby <br>I got you shawty <br>Swallow my D <br>그녀는 너무 화끈해서 <br>Like WASABI <br>날아서 난 그녀에게 <br>벌처럼 쏘지 <br>운동하는 여자 엉덩인 <br>너무 좋아 Hold up <br>]]></content><category term="NAHANDSOME (나핸썸)" label="NAHANDSOME (나핸썸)"/><category term="니 주말은 언제나 내꺼 (Wit Me)" label="니 주말은 언제나 내꺼 (Wit Me)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ROO_루/연애의_하수/</id><title>ROO (루) - 연애의 하수 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:34:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:34:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ROO_%EB%A3%A8/%EC%97%B0%EC%95%A0%EC%9D%98_%ED%95%98%EC%88%98/" title="ROO (루) - 연애의 하수 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[워어 <br>You've got to me <br>그 사람은 대체 왜 그렇게 <br>애매한 거니 <br>남자가 진심이면 <br>널 헷갈리게 <br>만들지는 않을 거야 <br>쉼 없이 흘리는 눈웃음 <br>딱 봐도 끼쟁이잖아 <br>정신 좀 차려 얘 <br>괜찮은 남잔 세상에 많은데 <br>아 됐다고 안다고 <br>이만함 됐다고 <br>누가 그걸 몰라 <br>나도 뻔히 알아 <br>충분해 그런 말 <br>그 누가 뭐래도 <br>내 마음을 따를래 <br>다 소용없어 그런 잔소리들 <br>그러니까 그만 좀 해줘 <br>나도 알아 애매한 그 녀석 <br>못 놓는 내가 <br>가끔은 초라해서 <br>완전 구겨져 <br>얇아진 내 자존심들 <br>쉼 없이 쏟아지는 질문 <br>언제쯤 결혼할 거니 <br>뭐가 그리 급해 <br>너처럼 속도위반이라도 해 <br>아 됐다고 안다고 <br>이만함 됐다고 <br>누가 그걸 몰라 <br>나도 뻔히 알아 <br>충분해 그런 말 <br>그 누가 뭐래도 <br>내 마음을 따를래 <br>다 소용없어 그런 잔소리들 <br>그러니까 그만 좀 해줘 <br>다들 남의 일에 <br>참 오지랖이 넓으셔서 <br>웃는 것도 한계가 있어 <br>또 참아야지 하면서도 난 <br>아 예민해 지루해 <br>짜증나 그런 말 <br>누가 그걸 몰라 <br>나도 뻔히 알아 <br>충분해 충분해 <br>그 누가 뭐래도 <br>이건 내 인생이야 <br>난 사랑할래 못난 내 모습도 <br>그러니깐 그만 좀 해줘 <br>워어 <br>You've got to me <br>]]></content><category term="ROO (루)" label="ROO (루)"/><category term="연애의 하수" label="연애의 하수"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전지애/You_Told_Me/</id><title>전지애 - You Told Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:34:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:34:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%A7%80%EC%95%A0/You_Told_Me/" title="전지애 - You Told Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 소리 없이 보는 두 눈이 <br>뭔가 슬픈 말을 하는 것 같아 <br>나지막하던 너의 그 음성이 <br>오늘따라 조금 먹먹해 <br>You 걱정되게 왜 그래 <br>벌써 울컥하는 나의 맘이 <br>그날을 예감하듯이 <br>You 숨죽여 말하는 목소리 <br>그 소리에 예민해져 <br>너 왜 그래 나 불안하게 <br>You told me <br>not to cry no more <br>내 눈을 바라보던 눈동자 <br>Please hold me <br>not to lose no more <br>그 안에 비친 <br>내 모습 초라해 <br>밝은 하늘 정말 <br>무심한 듯해 <br>비라도 내리면 울 텐데 <br>위로하는 건지 <br>날 비웃는 건지 <br>대체 하늘은 <br>왜 내 편이 아닌지 <br>You 걷는 것도 힘들어 <br>너무 높은 나의 구두도 <br>덜컹거리는 버스도 <br>You 새로 입은 옷들도 <br>거울에 비친 내 모습 <br>초라해 너무 예쁜데 <br>You told me <br>not to cry no more <br>내 눈을 바라보던 눈동자 <br>Please hold me <br>not to lose no more <br>그 안에 비친 <br>내 모습 초라해 <br>You was my love <br>You was my heaven <br>전부였던 네가 과거로 <br>You was my love <br>You was my dream <br>돌아와 줘 내 옆으로 <br>널 꿈꾸던 내 안으로 <br>You told me <br>not to cry no more <br>내 눈을 바라보던 눈동자 <br>Please hold me <br>not to lose no more <br>그 안에 비친 <br>내 모습 초라해 <br>You told me <br>not to cry no more <br>내 눈을 바라보던 눈동자 <br>Please hold me <br>not to lose no more <br>그 안에 비친 <br>내 모습 초라해 <br>You told me not to cry no more <br>not to cry no more <br>]]></content><category term="전지애" label="전지애"/><category term="You Told Me" label="You Told Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전지애/시간아_날/</id><title>전지애 - 시간아 날 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:34:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:34:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%A7%80%EC%95%A0/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B0%84%EC%95%84_%EB%82%A0/" title="전지애 - 시간아 날 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[네가 없는 하루 이틀 <br>구름 낀 하늘처럼 <br>답답한 기분에 <br>새벽길을 걸어 <br>터벅터벅이 <br>나지막한 네 목소리 <br>바람이 준 메아리 <br>상상만으로도 <br>눈앞에 보이는 <br>다정한 우리 <br>시간아 날 그대로 날 <br>따뜻한 바람 안에 <br>내가 자연스레 스며들게 <br>바람아 날 이대로 <br>날 보내줄래 <br>우리 그 때로 <br>다투던 그 날의 너 <br>낯설은 그 얼굴로 <br>그만하자 말하던 <br>네 표정에 많은걸 느껴 <br>뭐 때문인 건지 <br>어떤 이유인지 <br>차가운 눈 <br>또 굳은 표정 <br>손 내밀 수 없던 말투도 <br>용기 내지 못한 날로 <br>그때의 그 날로 <br>따뜻한 바람 안에 <br>내가 자연스레 스며들게 <br>바람아 날 이대로 <br>날 보내줄래 <br>우리 그 때로 <br>눈물 그보다 먼저 <br>떠오르는 너를 누르며 <br>같이 마시던 커피 <br>그 흔한 것들이 <br>나를 울려 생각나게 해 <br>시간아 날 그대로 날 <br>웃으며 너를 볼 수 있던 <br>시간으로 우리 함께 갈래 <br>바람아 날 이대로 <br>날 보내줄래 보내줄래 <br>]]></content><category term="전지애" label="전지애"/><category term="시간아 날" label="시간아 날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전지애/뭐하니_Vocal_Ver/</id><title>전지애 - 뭐하니 (Vocal Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:34:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:34:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%A7%80%EC%95%A0/%EB%AD%90%ED%95%98%EB%8B%88_Vocal_Ver/" title="전지애 - 뭐하니 (Vocal Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뭐하니 새벽만 되면 <br>울리는 벨 소리 <br>나를 흔드는 멘트가 <br>Oh 예술이야 보통 아니야 <br>뻔한 여자라면 <br>딱 넘어갈 네 말들 <br>자니 새벽 네 시에 <br>그럼 넌 왜 안자니 <br>조금 어설픈 멘트가 <br>oh 뻔하지만 지겹지만 <br>안 오면 또 괜히 서운한 거 <br>나도 참 이상해 <br>자꾸 생각나 <br>니가 니가 니가 니가 <br>우린 너무 다른데 <br>맘이 안 떠나 <br>하나 하나 하나 하나 <br>다 기억나는데 <br>괜히 찝찝한 마음만 <br>갖고 있다가 <br>너를 보면 자연스런 <br>미소만 지어 왜 <br>왜 왜 왜 자꾸 왜 왜 왜 <br>너를 보면 자꾸 <br>왜 왜 왜 왜 왜 왜 <br>나 웃음이 <br>왜 왜 왜 자꾸 왜 왜 왜 <br>너를 보면 자꾸 <br>왜 왜 왜 왜 왜 왜 <br>아침에 일어나 <br>자연스레 핸드폰을 보니 <br>우리가 연락 안 한지 <br>벌써 24시간 째 <br>무슨 일 바쁜 일 <br>어쩜 내가 싫어진 걸까 <br>이른 걱정을 해 <br>자꾸 생각나 <br>니가 니가 니가 니가 <br>우린 너무 다른데 <br>맘이 안 떠나 <br>하나 하나 하나 하나 <br>다 기억나는데 <br>괜히 찝찝한 마음만 <br>갖고 있다가 <br>너를 보면 자연스런 <br>미소만 지어 왜 <br>왜 왜 왜 자꾸 왜 왜 왜 <br>너를 보면 자꾸 <br>왜 왜 왜 왜 왜 왜 <br>나 웃음이 <br>왜 왜 왜 자꾸 왜 왜 왜 <br>너를 보면 자꾸 <br>왜 왜 왜 왜 왜 왜 <br>말이 없는 통화연결음 <br>오늘은 내가 용기를 냈는데 <br>항상 전활 받던 <br>내 모습이 초라해져 <br>뭐하니 새벽만 되면 <br>울리던 벨소리 <br>떨리지만 두렵지만 <br>너라면 받아줄 거라 믿어 <br>자꾸 생각나 <br>니가 니가 니가 니가 <br>우린 너무 다른데 <br>맘이 안 떠나 <br>하나 하나 하나 하나 <br>다 기억나는데 <br>괜히 찝찝한 마음만 <br>갖고 있다가 <br>너를 보면 자연스런 <br>미소만 지어 왜 <br>왜 왜 왜 자꾸 왜 왜 왜 <br>너를 보면 자꾸 <br>왜 왜 왜 왜 왜 왜 <br>나 웃음이 <br>왜 왜 왜 자꾸 왜 왜 왜 <br>너를 보면 자꾸 <br>왜 왜 왜 왜 왜 왜 <br>]]></content><category term="전지애" label="전지애"/><category term="뭐하니 (Vocal Ver.)" label="뭐하니 (Vocal Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전지애/이_멜로디의_시작은/</id><title>전지애 - 이 멜로디의 시작은 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:34:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:34:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%A7%80%EC%95%A0/%EC%9D%B4_%EB%A9%9C%EB%A1%9C%EB%94%94%EC%9D%98_%EC%8B%9C%EC%9E%91%EC%9D%80/" title="전지애 - 이 멜로디의 시작은 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 래퍼는 아니지만 <br>할 말은 참 많아 <br>예쁜 언니들 춤추는데 <br>누가 날 알아 <br>내 목소리 찾아 듣고 <br>익히는 사람 하나 <br>그 하나 열이 되고 <br>수백이 되는 그날 <br>이 멜로디의 시작은 <br>내가 걸을 때부터 <br>step 도 레 미 파 솔 도 <br>이 노래의 시작은 <br>새벽 한시 비가 오는 <br>이층 침대 위에서 <br>이 멜로디의 시작은 <br>내가 걸을 때부터 <br>step 도 레 미 파 솔 도 <br>이 노래의 시작은 <br>새벽 두시 가사를 쓰는 <br>미치광이 이야기 <br>내가 노래하는 이유는 <br>셀 수도 없이 많아 <br>우리 엄마 그리고 아빠 <br>언젠가 웃으리라 <br>채우지 못한 잘남 <br>행복 그리고 희망 <br>다 부어주리라 <br>넘치게 쏟아주리라 <br>이 멜로디의 시작은 <br>내가 걸을 때부터 <br>step 도 레 미 파 솔 도 <br>이 노래의 시작은 <br>새벽 한시 비가 오는 <br>이층 침대 위에서 <br>이 멜로디의 시작은 <br>내가 걸을 때부터 <br>step 도 레 미 파 솔 도 <br>이 노래의 시작은 <br>새벽 두시 가사를 쓰는 <br>미치광이 이야기 <br>미안해 다 관두려 했었어 <br>미래에 두려움 너무 컸었어 <br>사랑해 놓아주진 못 하겠어 <br>사랑해 노래하는 날 사랑해 <br>이 멜로디의 시작은 <br>처음으로 사랑을 느낀 <br>딴따라의 이야기 <br>이 노래의 시작은 <br>새벽 두시 가사를 쓰는 <br>미치광이 이야기 <br>이 멜로디의 시작은 <br>내가 걸을 때부터 <br>step 도 레 미 파 솔 도 <br>이 노래의 시작은 <br>새벽 두시 가사를 쓰는 <br>미치광이 이야기 <br>불안한 마음에 <br>딴 길로 새 버리고 말아 <br>너와의 이별을 <br>몰래 준비하고 말이야 <br>내가 준 사랑 시간 <br>딱 그만큼 들려줄래 <br>네가 얼마나 멋진 놈인지 <br>]]></content><category term="전지애" label="전지애"/><category term="이 멜로디의 시작은" label="이 멜로디의 시작은"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전지애/첫사랑이_되어주세요/</id><title>전지애 - 첫사랑이 되어주세요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:34:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:34:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%A7%80%EC%95%A0/%EC%B2%AB%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4_%EB%90%98%EC%96%B4%EC%A3%BC%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94/" title="전지애 - 첫사랑이 되어주세요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보통의 첫사랑은 <br>이뤄질 수 없다는 <br>속설을 갖고 있죠 잘 알아요 <br>나의 첫사랑을 <br>아직 내 처음 사랑을 <br>말한 적 없어 <br>잘 모르겠지만 앞으로 <br>FIRST LOVE LOVE <br>나의 첫사랑이 되어주세요 <br>FIRST LOVE LOVE <br>우리 영원할 걸 잘 알아요 <br>멀리에 있어도 <br>숨소리가 들리는 <br>그런 사랑을 하고 있어요 <br>말이 없어도 <br>늘 즐거울 수 있는 <br>그런 당신이 <br>난 너무 좋아요 항상 <br>FIRST LOVE LOVE <br>나의 첫사랑이 되어주세요 <br>FIRST LOVE LOVE <br>우리 영원할 걸 잘 알아요 <br>이해만 하다 끝난 사랑은 <br>박하사탕처럼 청량하지만 <br>당신과의 사랑을 끝낸다면 <br>내 맘 벌써부터 먹먹하네요 항상 <br>LAST LOVE LOVE <br>나의 마지막이 되어주세요 <br>FIRST LOVE LOVE <br>나의 처음 사랑이 되어주세요 <br>나의 첫사랑이 되어주세요 <br>]]></content><category term="전지애" label="전지애"/><category term="첫사랑이 되어주세요" label="첫사랑이 되어주세요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전지애/카멜레온/</id><title>전지애 - 카멜레온 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:34:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:34:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%A7%80%EC%95%A0/%EC%B9%B4%EB%A9%9C%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A8/" title="전지애 - 카멜레온 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 노랜 와인과 같이 <br>빨간색이 잘 어울려 <br>슬쩍 웃어주면은 노란 빛깔이 <br>화사하게 날 둘러 <br>좀 웃어달라고 그게 너답다고 <br>이런 비트 위에는 밝게 <br>때론 Girlish <br>때론 Cynical <br>What I wish <br>가끔 내 맘 깊숙이 <br>어둠이 찾아들 때 <br>이런 목소리로 날 달래 <br>Cause wish <br>어딜 가도 당당하게 <br>mic 위에서 춤을 추네 <br>목소린 Welcome <br>미소는 Thank god <br>Would you be my muse <br>자 자꾸만 생각나게 <br>맴맴 돌아 널 방해할래 <br>내 목소린 널 꼬셔 꼬셔 <br>매일 아침 젖은 머리를 <br>대충 틀어 올려 <br>바쁜 스케줄 지나면 <br>항상 새벽 늘 지금처럼 <br>Woo Sentimental mood <br>Sentimental mood <br>이런 비트 위에는 밝게 <br>때론 Girlish <br>때론 Cynical <br>What I wish <br>가끔 내 맘 깊숙이 <br>어둠이 찾아들 때 <br>이런 목소리로 날 달래 <br>Cause wish <br>어딜 가도 당당하게 <br>mic 위에서 춤을 추네 <br>목소린 Welcome <br>미소는 Thank god <br>Would you be my muse <br>자 자꾸만 생각나게 <br>맴맴 돌아 널 방해할래 <br>내 목소린 널 꼬셔 꼬셔 <br>네가 어디에 있던 <br>어느 곳에서나 <br>밝게 빛나는 별이 될 테니 <br>그곳에서 날 지켜봐 줘 <br>날 안아줘 날 감싸줘 <br>어딜 가도 당당하게 <br>mic 위에서 춤을 추네 <br>목소린 Welcome <br>미소는 Thank god <br>Would you be my muse <br>자 자꾸만 생각나게 <br>맴맴 돌아 널 방해할래 <br>내 목소린 널 꼬셔 꼬셔 <br>]]></content><category term="전지애" label="전지애"/><category term="카멜레온" label="카멜레온"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전지애/듣는_마법/</id><title>전지애 - 듣는 마법 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:34:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:34:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%A7%80%EC%95%A0/%EB%93%A3%EB%8A%94_%EB%A7%88%EB%B2%95/" title="전지애 - 듣는 마법 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[울컥하지 마 <br>조금만 참아봐 <br>늘 그랬듯 지나갈 거야 <br>고개를 들어봐 <br>곧 말라 사라질 거야 <br>네 눈물은 <br>아무도 못 볼 거야 <br>오늘은 또 무슨 일 있었니 <br>또 누가 널 아프게 했니 <br>오늘도 또 혼자인 거니 <br>오늘도 또 숨겨버렸니 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 <br>마법을 걸어줄게 <br>이 노래를 들으면 <br>웃을 수 있게 나 너 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 <br>마법을 걸어줄게 <br>따라 부르며 <br>웃을 수 있게 나 너 <br>오늘은 또 무슨 일 있었니 <br>어떤 일이 <br>널 또 힘들게 했니 <br>뭔지는 몰라도 <br>널 위로해줄게 <br>내 목소리로 촉촉한 <br>비를 내려줄게 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 <br>마법을 걸어줄게 <br>이 노래를 들으면 <br>웃을 수 있게 나 너 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 <br>마법을 걸어줄게 <br>따라 부르며 <br>웃을 수 있게 나 너 <br>뾰족한 화살이 <br>스쳐가 남긴 상처는 <br>지울 수 있는 게 아닌 걸 <br>걱정 마 넌 의미 있는 걸 <br>언제든 웃어버릴 <br>커다란 용기를 넌 가진 걸 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 <br>마법을 걸어줄게 <br>이 노래를 들으면 <br>웃을 수 있게 나 너 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 <br>마법을 걸어줄게 <br>따라 부르며 <br>웃을 수 있게 나 너 <br>]]></content><category term="전지애" label="전지애"/><category term="듣는 마법" label="듣는 마법"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전지애/Why_Why/</id><title>전지애 - Why Why - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:34:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:34:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%A7%80%EC%95%A0/Why_Why/" title="전지애 - Why Why - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[촉촉한 그 말투로 <br>날 깨워주세요 <br>물 안개 핀 아침에 <br>석양이 지는 곳에도 <br>가고 싶구요 <br>손잡고 걷고 싶다요 <br>맨 얼굴 보이기가 <br>왜 이렇게 신경 쓰이는지 <br>눈 뜨면 내 얼굴이 <br>제일 예쁘길 바라요 <br>Why Why <br>그대는 날 보고 웃나요 <br>이런 내가 웃긴가요 <br>Why Why <br>그대는 달콤한 건 가요 <br>입 맞춰줄래요 <br>다라라라 따 예 <br>외롭게 설레이는 <br>사랑이 아니어서 <br>참 다행이에요 <br>맨 얼굴 예쁘다며 <br>볼 꼬집는 그대 <br>Why Why <br>그대는 날 보고 웃나요 <br>이런 내가 웃긴가요 <br>Why Why <br>그대는 달콤한 건 가요 <br>입 맞춰줄래요 <br>가끔 그대도 기대어 <br>울고픈 날이 있을 텐데 <br>모든 걸 다 알 수는 없지만 <br>기꺼이 안아줄게요 <br>Why Why <br>그대는 날 보고 웃나요 <br>이런 내가 웃긴가요 <br>Why Why <br>그대를 꼭 안아줄래요 <br>입 맞춰줄래요 <br>사랑해 줄래요 <br>Why Why <br>그대는 <br>Why Why <br>어쩌면 <br>Why Why <br>그대는 날 위한 건가요 <br>입 맞춰줄래요 <br>사랑해 줄래요 <br>]]></content><category term="전지애" label="전지애"/><category term="Why Why" label="Why Why"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전지애/밤/</id><title>전지애 - 밤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:34:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:34:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%A7%80%EC%95%A0/%EB%B0%A4/" title="전지애 - 밤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이런 밤이 올 때면 <br>익숙하다는 듯 <br>TV를 켜고 소파에 누워 <br>무슨 말을 하는지도 모르는 <br>코미디를 틀어둔 채 <br>같이 웃어 하하 <br>내가 슬프다는 게 슬퍼 <br>내가 우울하다는 게 우울해 <br>이런 나를 보고도 <br>조용한 핸드폰이 싫어 <br>밤 너를 목 놓아 부르던 밤 <br>이런 날 두고 떠나간 날 <br>상처 가득한 날 홀로 감싸주던 <br>오늘 밤 오늘 밤 <br>찬물을 끼얹어봐 <br>좀 나아질까 <br>대체 어디에 묶여 <br>헤매이는 거야 <br>눈에 보이지 않는 <br>덫에 걸리고 걸려 <br>상처만 자꾸 덧이 나 <br>아파 보이는 게 싫어 <br>누구보다 웃고 싶어 <br>그래 너보다 웃고 싶어 <br>네 행복보다 더 괜찮고 싶어 <br>밤 너를 목 놓아 부르던 밤 <br>이런 날 두고 떠나간 날 <br>상처 가득한 날 홀로 감싸주던 <br>오늘 밤 오늘 밤 <br>시간은 지나 내일이 오고 <br>또 가고 자꾸 흐르고 <br>시간이 네 발자국이라면 <br>멀어지는 걸까 너도 내게서 <br>바로 오늘 밤 <br>너를 목 놓아 부르던 밤 <br>이런 날 두고 떠나간 날 <br>상처 가득한 날 홀로 지켜주던 <br>오늘 밤 <br>그 어느 밤 내 눈물이 전부인 밤 <br>다른 표정은 다른 얼굴은 없는 밤 <br>]]></content><category term="전지애" label="전지애"/><category term="밤" label="밤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코다_브릿지/Go_Own_Way/</id><title>코다 브릿지 - Go Own Way - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:34:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:34:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%8B%A4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80/Go_Own_Way/" title="코다 브릿지 - Go Own Way - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[where I can go someday <br>ain't no other way <br>so listen to my day <br>ain't no other way <br>over again <br>눈이 떠지질 않아 <br>출근길 버스 안에서 <br>또 하룰 그려 <br>이건 내 잘못이 아닌데 <br>다 내가 했대 <br>내가 제일 만만해 <br>앞에선 한마디도 못해 <br>억지로 웃어야 해 <br>오늘 꾹 참고 어떻게든 견디면 <br>더 좋은 날이 오겠지 <br>내가 하고 싶은 것과 <br>해야 하는 건 너무 많이 달라 <br>내가 할 수 있는 건 <br>이겨내라 하는데 <br>왜이리 쉽지 않아 <br>where I can go someday <br>there ain't no other way <br>난 할 수 있는데 이 길 끝에 <br>so listen to my day <br>the reason to go own way <br>웃으며 서있는 그날 <br>go own way <br>하루의 반은 회사 안에서 <br>살은 빼야 해 <br>점심엔 고픈 배를 참어 <br>종일 일에 시달리다가도 <br>저녁엔 나만의 <br>작업실에서 노래하며 <br>다시 행복할 텐데 나만의 시간에 <br>새벽3시반 늦은 잠을 청할 때면 <br>나은 내일이 오겠지 <br>내가 하고 싶은 것과 <br>해야 하는 건 너무 많이 달라 <br>내가 할 수 있는 건 <br>이겨내라 하는데 <br>왜이리 쉽지 않아 <br>where I can go someday <br>there ain't no other way <br>난 할 수 있는데 이 길 끝에 <br>so listen to my day <br>the reason to go own way <br>웃으며 서있는 그날 <br>go own way <br>니가 뭘 한다고 <br>나를 조금 안다고 <br>그렇게 해서 되겠냐고 <br>말은 쉽게 잘하고 <br>바로 어제도 <br>내가 뭘 했었는지 <br>모르게 흘러가는 <br>하루들 안에서 <br>go own way <br>]]></content><category term="코다 브릿지" label="코다 브릿지"/><category term="Go Own Way" label="Go Own Way"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/추가열/상사몽_MR/</id><title>추가열 - 상사몽 (MR) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:36:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:36:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%94%EA%B0%80%EC%97%B4/%EC%83%81%EC%82%AC%EB%AA%BD_MR/" title="추가열 - 상사몽 (MR) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 품 안에 있는 세상은 <br>다른 세상이요 <br>꽃비가 내리고 <br>단비가 흐르는 <br>그런 세상이요 <br>힘이 들 때면 내게 오오 <br>사각거리는 저고리 <br>품 안에 안겨 <br>꿈을 꾸어요 <br>별 나비 춤을 추고 <br>오색이 아름다운 <br>노래로 수를 놓은 <br>아름다운 꿈나라 <br>비단도포 휘날리듯 <br>산바람 들바람 부여안고 <br>사랑할 테요 <br>별 나비 춤을 추고 <br>오색이 아름다운 <br>노래로 수를 놓은 <br>아름다운 꿈나라 <br>비단도포 휘날리듯 <br>산바람 들바람 부여안고 <br>사랑할 테요 <br>비단도포 휘날리듯 <br>산바람 들바람 부여안고 <br>사랑할 테요]]></content><category term="추가열" label="추가열"/><category term="상사몽 (MR)" label="상사몽 (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/추가열/사랑꽃/</id><title>추가열 - 사랑꽃 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:36:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:36:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%94%EA%B0%80%EC%97%B4/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EA%BD%83/" title="추가열 - 사랑꽃 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아픔속에 피는 꽃이 <br>사랑이구나 <br>사랑 사랑이구나 <br>내가 아파도 행복한 게 <br>사랑이구나 <br>사랑 사랑이구나 <br>구구절절 인생을 다 써도 <br>한가지만 남아 있구나 <br>내 인생 걸러 남는 것도 <br>오로지 사랑이구나 <br>피다가 피다가 진다 해도 <br>내가 꼭 붙잡고 싶은 사랑 <br>죽어도 죽어도 못 잊을 <br>내 사랑 당신이니까 <br>아픔속에 피는 꽃이 <br>사랑이구나 <br>사랑 사랑이구나 <br>내가 아파도 행복한 게 <br>사랑이구나 <br>사랑 사랑이구나 <br>구구절절 인생을 다 써도 <br>한가지만 남아 있구나 <br>내 인생 걸러 남는 것도 <br>오로지 사랑이구나 <br>피다가 피다가 진다 해도 <br>내가 꼭 붙잡고 싶은 사랑 <br>죽어도 죽어도 못 잊을 <br>내 사랑 당신이니까 <br>죽어도 죽어도 못 잊을 <br>내 사랑 당신이니까 <br>]]></content><category term="추가열" label="추가열"/><category term="사랑꽃" label="사랑꽃"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/추가열/잠깐만요/</id><title>추가열 - 잠깐만요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:36:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:36:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%94%EA%B0%80%EC%97%B4/%EC%9E%A0%EA%B9%90%EB%A7%8C%EC%9A%94/" title="추가열 - 잠깐만요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잠깐만요 실례할게요 <br>내가 길을 잃어서 그러는데요 <br>내 사랑에게 갈 수 있는 길 <br>아시면 가르쳐 주세요 <br>내 옆에 있던 사람 나만을 <br>사랑해주던 <br>내 옆에 있던 사람 <br>어느 쪽으로 갔나요 <br>내 사랑 나를 데리고 가는 걸 <br>잊으셨나봐요 <br>난 어떡하라고 <br>당신없이 못 사는 <br>나를 잘 알면서 <br>어디로 떠나셨나요 <br>잠깐만요 실례할게요 <br>내가 길을 잃어서 그러는데요 <br>내 사랑에게 갈 수 있는 길 <br>아시면 가르쳐 주세요 <br>내 옆에 있던 사람 나만을 <br>사랑해주던 <br>내 옆에 있던 사람 <br>어느 쪽으로 갔나요 <br>내 사랑 나를 데리고 가는 걸 <br>잊으셨나봐요 <br>난 어떡하라고 <br>당신없이 못 사는 <br>나를 잘 알면서 <br>어디로 떠나셨나요 <br>내 사랑 나를 데리고 가는 걸 <br>잊으셨나봐요 <br>난 어떡하라고 <br>당신없이 못 사는 <br>나를 잘 알면서 <br>어디로 떠나셨나요 <br>당신없이 못 사는 <br>나를 잘 알면서 <br>어디로 떠나셨나요 <br>어디로 떠나셨나요 <br>]]></content><category term="추가열" label="추가열"/><category term="잠깐만요" label="잠깐만요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/추가열/그리운_얼굴/</id><title>추가열 - 그리운 얼굴 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:36:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:36:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%94%EA%B0%80%EC%97%B4/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9A%B4_%EC%96%BC%EA%B5%B4/" title="추가열 - 그리운 얼굴 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너를 사랑한다고 <br>그땐 왜 말 못했나 <br>밀려가고 밀려오는 파도처럼 <br>그리움이 가슴을 적시는데 <br>어느새 계절은 가고 <br>또 다시 단풍이 물들었네 <br>그러나 세월 가면 <br>잊혀진다는 그 말이 <br>오히려 나를 울리네 <br>너를 사랑한다고 <br>그땐 왜 말을 못했나 <br>잊을 수 없는 그대 <br>볼 수 없는 그대 <br>진한 커피 한 잔에 <br>지울 수 있을까 <br>사랑이라는 그리운 얼굴 <br>아직도 나에게는 <br>찾아올 줄을 모르고 <br>이제는 잊어야 할 <br>그리운 그대 모습 <br>어이해 내 곁을 떠나지 않나 <br>어느새 계절은 가고 <br>또 다시 단풍이 물들었네 <br>그러나 세월 가면 <br>잊혀진다는 그 말이 <br>오히려 나를 울리네 <br>너를 사랑한다고 <br>그땐 왜 말을 못했나 <br>잊을 수 없는 그대 <br>볼 수 없는 그대 <br>진한 커피 한 잔에 <br>지울 수 있을까 <br>사랑이라는 그리운 얼굴 <br>아직도 나에게는 <br>찾아올 줄을 모르고 <br>이제는 잊어야 할 <br>그리운 그대 모습 <br>어이해 내 곁을 떠나지 않나 <br>어이해 내 곁을 떠나지 않나 <br>어이해 <br>]]></content><category term="추가열" label="추가열"/><category term="그리운 얼굴" label="그리운 얼굴"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/추가열/고목/</id><title>추가열 - 고목 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:36:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:36:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%94%EA%B0%80%EC%97%B4/%EA%B3%A0%EB%AA%A9/" title="추가열 - 고목 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[낙엽 떨어지던 날에 <br>그대와 함께 걸었던 <br>그 길을 따라 걸으며 <br>한잔의 술에 젖네 <br>바람 불어오는 날에 <br>그대의 향기 느끼며 <br>소리 없이 흐느끼던 <br>내 눈물에 젖어보네 <br>그리워라 그대 얼굴 <br>다시 볼 수 없는 사람 <br>사랑한다는 그 말 한마디 못한 <br>그 시절이 미워라 <br>그리워라 그대 얼굴 <br>다시 볼 수 없는 사람 <br>사랑한다는 그 말 한마디 못한 <br>그 시절이 미워라 <br>나무 세월은 흘러서 <br>그 푸르름 사라지고 <br>지금은 베어진 그곳에 <br>이렇게 나 혼자 서있네 <br>지금은 베어진 그곳에 <br>이렇게 나 혼자 서있네 <br>]]></content><category term="추가열" label="추가열"/><category term="고목" label="고목"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/추가열/상사몽/</id><title>추가열 - 상사몽 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:36:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:36:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%94%EA%B0%80%EC%97%B4/%EC%83%81%EC%82%AC%EB%AA%BD/" title="추가열 - 상사몽 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 품 안에 있는 세상은 <br>다른 세상이요 <br>꽃비가 내리고 <br>단비가 흐르는 <br>그런 세상이요 <br>힘이 들 때면 내게 오오 <br>사각거리는 저고리 <br>품 안에 안겨 <br>꿈을 꾸어요 <br>별 나비 춤을 추고 <br>오색이 아름다운 <br>노래로 수를 놓은 <br>아름다운 꿈나라 <br>비단도포 휘날리듯 <br>산바람 들바람 부여안고 <br>사랑할 테요 <br>별 나비 춤을 추고 <br>오색이 아름다운 <br>노래로 수를 놓은 <br>아름다운 꿈나라 <br>비단도포 휘날리듯 <br>산바람 들바람 부여안고 <br>사랑할 테요 <br>비단도포 휘날리듯 <br>산바람 들바람 부여안고 <br>사랑할 테요 <br>]]></content><category term="추가열" label="추가열"/><category term="상사몽" label="상사몽"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/추가열/소풍같은_인생/</id><title>추가열 - 소풍같은 인생 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:36:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:36:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%94%EA%B0%80%EC%97%B4/%EC%86%8C%ED%92%8D%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EC%9D%B8%EC%83%9D/" title="추가열 - 소풍같은 인생 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너도 한번 나도 한번 <br>누구나 한번 왔다 가는 인생 <br>바람 같은 시간이야 <br>멈추지 않는 세월 <br>하루하루 소중하지 <br>미련이야 많겠지만 <br>후회도 많겠지만 <br>어차피 한번 왔다 가는 걸 <br>붙잡을 수 없다면 <br>소풍 가듯 소풍 가듯 <br>웃으며 행복하게 살아야지 <br>너도 한번 나도 한번 <br>누구나 한번 왔다 가는 인생 <br>바람 같은 시간이야 <br>멈추지 않는 세월 <br>하루하루 소중하지 <br>미련이야 많겠지만 <br>후회도 많겠지만 <br>어차피 한번 왔다 가는 걸 <br>붙잡을 수 없다면 <br>소풍 가듯 소풍 가듯 <br>웃으며 행복하게 살아야지 <br>미련이야 많겠지만 <br>후회도 많겠지만 <br>어차피 한번 왔다 가는 걸 <br>붙잡을 수 없다면 <br>소풍 가듯 소풍 가듯 <br>웃으며 행복하게 살아야지 <br>웃으며 행복하게 살아야지 <br>]]></content><category term="추가열" label="추가열"/><category term="소풍같은 인생" label="소풍같은 인생"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/추가열/호강/</id><title>추가열 - 호강 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:36:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:36:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B6%94%EA%B0%80%EC%97%B4/%ED%98%B8%EA%B0%95/" title="추가열 - 호강 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[당신만 사랑한다 <br>말 한마디 해놓고 <br>그 약속 지키지 못하고 <br>세월 지나 뒤돌아보니 <br>정신 없이 걸어 온 날들 <br>지난 날 미안해요 고마워요 <br>남은 인생 행복 합시다 <br>몇 년이라도 <br>돌아갈 수 있다면 <br>돌아갈 수 있다면 <br>그대 아픔 대신 질 텐데 <br>호강이란 거 <br>못 시켜줘 미안해 <br>세월이 원망이구나 <br>당신만 사랑한다 <br>말 한마디 해놓고 <br>그 약속 지키지 못하고 <br>세월 지나 뒤돌아보니 <br>정신 없이 살아 온 날들 <br>지난 날 미안해요 고마워요 <br>남은 인생 행복 합시다 <br>몇 년이라도 <br>돌아갈 수 있다면 <br>돌아갈 수 있다면 <br>그대 아픔 대신 질 텐데 <br>호강이란 거 <br>못 시켜줘 미안해 <br>세월이 원망이구나 <br>세월이 원망이구나 <br>]]></content><category term="추가열" label="추가열"/><category term="호강" label="호강"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bonobo/Figures/</id><title>Bonobo - Figures - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:37:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:37:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bonobo/Figures/" title="Bonobo - Figures - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, if it hadn't been for, don't need me no more <br>Oh, if it hadn't been for, don't need me no more <br>Oh, if it hadn't been for, don't need me no more <br>Oh, if it hadn't been for, don't need me no more <br>You'd be happy some, why do you feel Don't need me no more <br>Oh, if it hadn't been for, don't need me no more <br>You'd be happy some, off <br>Believe it, be off, don't need me no more, why do you feel <br>Don't need me no more <br>Oh, if it hadn't been for, don't need me no more <br>You'd be happy some, off <br>You'd be happy some, off, don't need me no more, believe it <br>Why do you feel you'd be happy some <br>Why do you feel <br>Believe it <br>Believe it <br>Believe it, off <br>Don't need me no, believe it <br>Oh, if it hadn't been for, don't need me no, you'd be happy some <br>Why do you feel Don't need me no, you'd be happy some <br>Why do you feel You say I tie, don't need me no <br>Oh, if it hadn't been for, don't need me no, had enough <br>Oh, if it hadn't been for, you say, don't need me no <br>Believe it, off, believe it, off <br>You say I tie, believe it, off, believe it, off <br>You say I tie, believe it, off <br>Don't need me no, believe it, off <br>You say I tie, believe it, off <br>Don't need me no, believe it, off <br>You say I tie, believe it, off <br>Don't need me no, believe it, off <br>You say I tie, believe it, off <br>Don't need me no, believe it, off <br>You say I tie, believe it, off <br>You say, don't, believe it, off, believe it, off <br>You say, don't need me no]]></content><category term="Bonobo" label="Bonobo"/><category term="Figures" label="Figures"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bonobo/No_Reason_Feat_Nick_Murphy/</id><title>Bonobo - No Reason (Feat. Nick Murphy) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:37:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:37:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bonobo/No_Reason_Feat_Nick_Murphy/" title="Bonobo - No Reason (Feat. Nick Murphy) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's beautiful, and even though <br>I told you so, you know <br>We'd face survival, we're leaving lights on <br>We'll move or go on somehow <br><br>Looking like soldiers waiting to drown <br>And I'm not around no more <br>And looking at people that don't make a sound <br>When music's around, stay warm <br><br>And we've got no rhyme or no reason now <br>We've got the time of our lives now <br><br>It's seasonal, nobody knows <br>We'll make it known somehow <br>Just you and me, and we can see <br>Small machines and sunrise <br><br>Looking like soldiers waiting to drown <br>And I'm not around no more <br>Pictures of people that don't make a sound <br>When music's around, stay warm <br><br>And we've got no rhyme and no reason now <br>We've got the time of our lives now <br><br>Pictures of people that don't make a sound <br>When music's around, stay warm <br>And we've got no rhyme and no reason now <br><br>Looking like soldiers waiting to drown <br>And I'm not around no more <br>Lookin at people that don't make a sound <br>When music's around, stay warm <br><br>And we've got no rhyme and no reason now <br>We've got the time of our lives now]]></content><category term="Bonobo" label="Bonobo"/><category term="No Reason (Feat. Nick Murphy)" label="No Reason (Feat. Nick Murphy)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bonobo/Surface_Feat_Nicole_Miglis/</id><title>Bonobo - Surface (Feat. Nicole Miglis) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:37:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:37:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bonobo/Surface_Feat_Nicole_Miglis/" title="Bonobo - Surface (Feat. Nicole Miglis) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Make me <br>I've been paper thin so I cannot fly <br>I cannot move without wind, without wind <br><br>Saw the side of you I never knew <br>But were we ever good enough <br>And all we have to do is talk it through <br>But words are never good enough <br><br>Can we get anywhere <br>Paper thin paperweight <br>Are we close enough <br>Close enough <br><br>Seek the surface <br>I can make it up <br>By not being perfect <br>I can make it up, I can make it up <br>I can make it up, I can make it up <br>I can make it up, I can make it up <br>I can make it up, can I make it up <br><br>But what you wonder, if I'm crystal blue <br>But you were never clear enough <br>And every word to you is hard to say <br>'Cause words are never good enough <br><br>Can we get anywhere <br>Paper thin paperweight <br>Are we close enough <br>Close enough <br><br>Seek the surface <br>I can make it up <br>By not being perfect <br>I can make it up, I can make it up Seek the surface <br>I can make it up, I can make it up <br>I can make it up, I can make it up By not being perfect <br>I can make it up, can I make it up <br>I can make it up <br><br>I can make it up, I can make it up <br>I can make it up, I can make it up <br>I can make it up, I can make it up <br>I can make it up, I can make it up <br><br>Can we get anywhere <br>Paper thin paperweight <br>Are we close enough <br><br>I can make it up, I can make it up <br>I can make it up, I can make it up <br>I can make it up, I can make it up <br>Can I make it up I can make it up <br><br>Can we get anywhere <br>Paper thin paperweight <br>Are we close enough <br><br>Seek the surface <br>Seek the surface <br>Seek the surface]]></content><category term="Bonobo" label="Bonobo"/><category term="Surface (Feat. Nicole Miglis)" label="Surface (Feat. Nicole Miglis)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bonobo/Grains/</id><title>Bonobo - Grains - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:37:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:37:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bonobo/Grains/" title="Bonobo - Grains - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One, sand <br>One drop of water, water, sand <br>One, sand <br>One drop of water, water, sand <br>One, sand, one, sand <br>One, sand, one, sand <br>One grain of sand <br>One drop of water, water, sand <br>One, sand, one, sand <br>One, sand, one, sand <br>One grain of sand, one, sand <br>One grain of sand <br>Water in the sea <br>One grain of sand <br>One grain of sand <br>Water in the sea <br>One grain of sand <br>One grain of sand <br>Water in the sea <br>One grain of sand <br>One grain of sand <br>One grain of sand]]></content><category term="Bonobo" label="Bonobo"/><category term="Grains" label="Grains"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bonobo/Break_Apart_Feat_Rhye/</id><title>Bonobo - Break Apart (Feat. Rhye) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:37:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:37:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bonobo/Break_Apart_Feat_Rhye/" title="Bonobo - Break Apart (Feat. Rhye) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's hard to take all of this hate <br>It's hard to take all of this hate, this hate <br><br>First move they think they never saw <br>Be careful with me, be careful with <br>Join with me <br><br>I should've heard your fear <br>So, it's on me, so, it's on <br>I should've heard your needs <br>So, it's on, so, it's on, so, it's on <br><br>We've thrown apart these pieces <br>We've thrown apart these pieces <br>So, I don't go home <br>Tell me love, tell me love <br><br>You're my favourite, you're my favourite <br>But we're phasing, but we're phasing <br>You're my favourite, you're my favourite <br>But we're phasing, but we're phasing <br>You're my favourite, you're my favourite <br>But we're phasing, but we're phasing <br>You're my favourite, you're my favourite <br>You're my <br><br>Instead of something to break apart <br>Instead, it's just broke apart <br>Stand up and shake this heart <br>Instead, it's just a break apart from us <br><br>I should've heard your fear <br>Shame on me <br>I should've heard your needs <br>Shame on me <br><br>Help me out, on me, help me out, on me <br>Help me out, on me, help me out, on me <br>Help me out, on me, help me out, on me <br>Help me out]]></content><category term="Bonobo" label="Bonobo"/><category term="Break Apart (Feat. Rhye)" label="Break Apart (Feat. Rhye)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태리_Terry/그냥_지내_Feat_라경원_Of_지어반/</id><title>태리 (Terry) - 그냥 지내 (Feat. 라경원 Of 지어반) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:38:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:38:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EB%A6%AC_Terry/%EA%B7%B8%EB%83%A5_%EC%A7%80%EB%82%B4_Feat_%EB%9D%BC%EA%B2%BD%EC%9B%90_Of_%EC%A7%80%EC%96%B4%EB%B0%98/" title="태리 (Terry) - 그냥 지내 (Feat. 라경원 Of 지어반) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 뭐 그럭저럭 지내 <br>밥 잘 챙겨 먹고 다니긴 해 <br>나름 바빠 일이 잘 풀려서 <br>거지 같았던 그때에 비해서 <br>덩달아 생활도 조금 나아졌어 <br>물론 아직 부족한 게 많아 <br>어쩌면 하나도 <br>안 바뀌었나 봐 여전히 <br>그때 너와의 추억 속을 헤매 <br>어제 같았던 기억 아팠던 이별 <br>상처는 아물지 않아 <br>품에 남은 미련 <br>안았던 감촉이 너무 생생한데 <br>너 떠날 때 잡았다면 <br>이러지 않을 텐데 <br>아무것도 바라지 않아 단지 <br>서로 안부라도 <br>가끔은 주고받았으면 해 <br>라고 마무리한 톡 <br>전송 누르지 못하고 뒤집는 폰 <br>똑같은 매일과 똑같을 내일 <br>별다른 의미 없이 그냥 지내 <br>넌 어떻게 지내는지 묻고 싶지만 <br>내가 부끄러워서 <br>그냥 좀 미안해서 그래 <br>그래 미안해서 <br>그래 나아진 게 뭣도 없네 <br>나는 제일 서툰 게 <br>너라 아직까지도 이래 <br>어쩜 이리 <br>너에게만 찌질 해지는지 <br>하루 왠 종일 니 프로필 <br>사진만 들여다보네 <br>넌 내가 뭐하고 지내는지 <br>궁금하지도 않겠지 <br>너에게 다른 사람이 <br>생겼으니까 말이지 <br>I don't care about it <br>당연하지 <br>주변의 남자 놈들이 <br>널 가만히 둘 리 없지 <br>어쩌면 혹시라도 니가 <br>나처럼 아프진 않을까 <br>걱정이 돼서 아니 일부러 애써 <br>상탯말을 너로 암시해 그리워라 <br>적어 봤지만 <br>헛수고야 나도 알아 <br>나 따위한테 <br>관심 없는 거 나도 알아 <br>그래도 아름다웠던 <br>그림 하나를 남겨줘서 <br>그것만으로도 난 고마워 <br>똑같은 매일과 똑같을 내일 <br>별다른 의미 없이 그냥 지내 <br>넌 어떻게 지내는지 묻고 싶지만 <br>내가 부끄러워서 <br>그냥 좀 미안해서 그래 <br>Sorry but I can't leave you <br>Sorry but I can't remove <br>너와 나 사이의 기억만 가질게 <br>Sorry but I can't leave you <br>Sorry but I can't remove <br>너와 나 사이의 추억만 남길게 <br>똑같은 매일과 똑같을 내일 <br>별다른 의미 없이 그냥 지내 <br>넌 어떻게 지내는지 묻고 싶지만 <br>내가 부끄러워서 <br>그냥 좀 미안해서 그래 <br>똑같은 매일 하루의 반복 <br>나 혼자는 더 못 참을 것 같아 <br>너가 아닌 다른 <br>누구든 절대 <br>난 못 만날 것 같아 <br>지울 수 없나 봐 <br>]]></content><category term="태리 (Terry)" label="태리 (Terry)"/><category term="그냥 지내 (Feat. 라경원 Of 지어반)" label="그냥 지내 (Feat. 라경원 Of 지어반)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정영화/나는_믿네/</id><title>정영화 - 나는 믿네 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:38:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:38:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%98%81%ED%99%94/%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%AF%BF%EB%84%A4/" title="정영화 - 나는 믿네 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내게 허락하신 <br>시련을 통해 <br>나의 믿음 <br>더욱 강하게 <br>자라나고 <br>험한 산과 골짜기 <br>지나는 동안 <br>주께 더 가까이 <br>나를 이끄시네 <br>내가 겪는 시험이 <br>어렵고 힘겨워도 <br>내 주님 보다 <br>크지 않네 <br>내 앞에 바다가 <br>갈라지지 않으면 <br>주가 나로 <br>바다 위에 <br>걷게 하리라 <br>나는 믿네 <br>주의 능력으로 <br>내 삶 새롭게 되리 <br>나는 믿네 <br>주의 능력으로 <br>담대히 나가리라 <br>주와 함께 싸워 <br>승리하리라 <br>날마다 믿음으로 <br>나 살아가리 <br>내게 허락하신 <br>시련을 통해 <br>나의 믿음 <br>더욱 강하게 <br>자라나고 <br>험한 산과 골짜기 <br>지나는 동안 <br>주께 더 가까이 <br>나를 이끄시네 <br>내가 겪는 시험이 <br>어렵고 힘겨워도 <br>내 주님 보다 <br>크지 않네 <br>내 앞에 바다가 <br>갈라지지 않으면 <br>주가 나로 <br>바다 위에 <br>걷게 하리라 <br>나는 믿네 <br>주의 능력으로 <br>내 삶 새롭게 되리 <br>나는 믿네 <br>주의 능력으로 <br>담대히 나가리라 <br>주와 함께 싸워 <br>승리하리라 <br>날마다 믿음으로 <br>나 살아가리 <br>나는 믿네 <br>주의 능력으로 <br>내 삶 새롭게 되리 <br>나는 믿네 <br>주의 능력으로 <br>담대히 나가리라 <br>주와 함께 싸워 <br>승리하리라 <br>날마다 믿음으로 <br>나 살아가리 <br>날마다 믿음으로 <br>나 살아가리 <br>]]></content><category term="정영화" label="정영화"/><category term="나는 믿네" label="나는 믿네"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/배승연/모진/</id><title>배승연 - 모진 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:39:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:39:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B0%EC%8A%B9%EC%97%B0/%EB%AA%A8%EC%A7%84/" title="배승연 - 모진 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루를 견디고 <br>이틀을 울었던 <br>그런 날이 있었어 <br>이틀을 울다가 <br>나흘이 아팠던 <br>그런 날이 있었어 <br>그런 내게 문득 다가와 <br>수줍게 웃어주던 <br>어여쁜 한 사람이 있었어 <br>니가 있어서 참 다행이야 <br>내게 와줘서 참 다행이야 <br>복잡한 맘 떨쳐버리고 <br>나를 선택해줘서 <br>모진 날 믿고 사랑해줘서 <br>니가 없으면 안 된다는 말 <br>내게 와줘서 고맙다는 말 <br>한번도 말한 적 없네요 <br>이제야 말할게요 <br>내 곁에 평생 함께 해줘요 <br>사랑해요 <br>오랜만이었어 그때 난 <br>설레었던 것 같아 <br>한참 몰래 널 훔쳐보다 <br>들키기도 했었지 <br>그런 내게 문득 다가와 <br>말없이 웃어줘서 <br>날 믿고 내 손 꼭 잡아줘서 <br>니가 있어서 참 다행이야 <br>내게 와줘서 참 다행이야 <br>복잡한 맘 떨쳐버리고 <br>나를 선택해줘서 <br>모진 날 믿고 사랑해줘서 <br>니가 없으면 안 된다는 말 <br>내게 와줘서 고맙다는 말 <br>한번도 말한 적 없네요 <br>이제야 말할게요 <br>내 곁에 평생 함께 해줘요 <br>사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="배승연" label="배승연"/><category term="모진" label="모진"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PaaS_파스/이렇게_바쁠줄은_몰랐어_Feat_수진/</id><title>PaaS (파스) - 이렇게 바쁠줄은 몰랐어 (Feat. 수진) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:40:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:40:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PaaS_%ED%8C%8C%EC%8A%A4/%EC%9D%B4%EB%A0%87%EA%B2%8C_%EB%B0%94%EC%81%A0%EC%A4%84%EC%9D%80_%EB%AA%B0%EB%9E%90%EC%96%B4_Feat_%EC%88%98%EC%A7%84/" title="PaaS (파스) - 이렇게 바쁠줄은 몰랐어 (Feat. 수진) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그 5분이란 시간에 <br>난 핸드폰만 수백 번 <br>넌 연락 한 통 없었고 <br>난 하루 종일 기다려 <br>이렇게 <br>바쁠 줄은 <br>몰랐어 <br>1분이면 되는데 <br>이렇게 바쁠 줄은 <br>몰랐어 <br>너와 있는 시간이 <br>너무 좋아서 <br>매일을 안절부절 못하는 난데 <br>그런 식으로 따지면 나도 곤란해 <br>난 항상 내 맘에 너를 담고 <br>있는데 간단해 보이는 일도 <br>손에 잡히지 않을 때가 많아 <br>너의 시무룩한 <br>답장을 받아보고는 <br>답을 하고 싶어도 못할 때가 많아 <br>내가 참 미안하지만 너무나 바빠 <br>몇 시간만 있다가 답장 할게 <br>이 말마저도 쓸 시간이 없어 <br>너와 나의 입장을 <br>바꿀 수가 없어서 <br>잘 모르겠지만 <br>진짜로 바쁜걸 어떡해 <br>그 5분이란 시간에 <br>난 핸드폰만 수백 번 <br>넌 연락 한 통 없었고 <br>난 하루 종일 기다려 <br>이렇게 <br>바쁠 줄은 <br>몰랐어 <br>1분이면 되는데 <br>그렇게 시간이 지나고 <br>너도 내게 조금씩 지쳐가고 <br>헌데 내가 왜 미쳤다고 <br>답장을 일부러 안 하겠냐고 <br>항상 너가 많이 보고 싶다고 <br>매일 사랑한다 말하고 <br>별것 없는 나란 놈 <br>만나주는 너에 대한 <br>내 마음 이게 아닌데 <br>너에겐 변명 같겠지만 <br>그런 게 아닌데 <br>정말로 너무 바빠서 그래 <br>정말로 너를 사랑하는데 <br>정말로 항상 보고 싶은데 <br>정말로 늘 껴안고 싶은데 <br>날씨 탓일까 왜인지 <br>서늘한 기운이 <br>너의 차가워진 <br>맘에서 불어온 건지 <br>일보다 너가 <br>더 중요하고 소중해 <br>근데 널 챙겨주려면 <br>별수없이 일을 해 <br>그 5분이란 시간에 <br>난 핸드폰만 수백 번 <br>넌 연락 한 통 없었고 <br>난 하루 종일 기다려 <br>이렇게 <br>바쁠 줄은 <br>몰랐어 <br>1분이면 되는데 <br>나도 너의 전화 <br>받고 싶고 <br>나도 매일 전화 <br>하고 싶어 <br>사랑한다고 말 <br>하고 싶고 <br>나도 그 말이 참 <br>듣고 싶어 <br>그 5분이란 시간에 <br>난 핸드폰만 수백 번 <br>넌 연락 한 통 없었고 <br>난 하루 종일 기다려 <br>이렇게 <br>바쁠 줄은 <br>몰랐어 <br>1분이면 되는데 <br>]]></content><category term="PaaS (파스)" label="PaaS (파스)"/><category term="이렇게 바쁠줄은 몰랐어 (Feat. 수진)" label="이렇게 바쁠줄은 몰랐어 (Feat. 수진)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rvao/Phantom_Feat_딜러_Of_Buyers/</id><title>R.vao - Phantom (Feat. 딜러 Of Buyers) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:40:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:40:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rvao/Phantom_Feat_%EB%94%9C%EB%9F%AC_Of_Buyers/" title="R.vao - Phantom (Feat. 딜러 Of Buyers) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[제물을 올려 <br>의심은 멈춰 <br>종을 울려 <br>할렐루야 <br>이젠 문이 열려 <br>펼쳐져 another world <br>전부 손 모으고 묵념 <br>길로틴 길로틴 <br>포도 알처럼 똑 하고 <br>떨어진 윗대가리 <br>실없이 웃는 면상이 <br>난 열 받아 눈에 꽂은 가위 <br>니들이 좋아할 <br>포도쥬스 blood 1 hunnid <br>재료가 너무 많지 <br>상하기 전에 얼른 짜야지 <br>Yeah I'm a phantom <br>나는 실체가 아닌 듯이 <br>Cuban cigar <br>연기처럼 덮지 너희 머리 <br>Codeine party <br>안되 난 한국인 <br>개되지 걔네집 하얀벽엔 <br>Cocaine 으로 덧칠 덧칠 <br>되 있어도 그건 <br>예술작품 이래 damm <br>포도 송이들 전부 <br>걔네 집에 모여 <br>이 나라의 내일 <br>본토느낌 으로 <br>혀가 꼬여 토론해 <br>미래는 damm <br>개돼지 개 되지 다 <br>dirty smell <br>what you want it <br>for the fame <br>for the money <br>I agree man <br>I'm phantom for the judge <br>Why your eyes is wet <br>So dirty your tears smell <br>Yeah I'm a phantom <br>Yeah I'm a phantom <br>Yeah I'm a phantom <br>Yeah I'm a phantom <br>Yeah I'm a phantom <br>Yeah I'm a phantom <br>Yeah I'm a phantom <br>Yeah <br>Cuz I'm a phantom <br>나도 변할지도 몰라 <br>니네 처럼 right <br>내가 흰색을 골랐던 게 <br>잘못 이야 <br>원래 때는 더 깨끗한 쪽이 <br>티가 많이 나지 바로 나 <br>내가 니네처럼 <br>물든 다면 그건 악몽각 <br>근데 난 phantom <br>하찮은 것들과는 딴 level <br>난 날개도 없이 <br>날지 또 가능하지 <br>빙 의 까지 what ever <br>날 보면 모두 지리면서 <br>난리 부루스 <br>강제로 선한 세상을 만들어 <br>가 보자 역시 성악설 <br>what the F glory <br>말로 해선 못 알아 들어 <br>손에 들어 흉기 <br>이긴 쪽의 말을 들어 <br>갖다 버려 정의 <br>걍 쓰레기들을 정리 <br>간편하고 없지 고민 bro <br>내가 악역인 가봐 <br>그래 난 phantom <br>같잖은 평화 주의자들 <br>믹서에 갈아 버려 완자로 <br>꼭 피를 봐야 바꿀라 해 <br>니넨 한자론 폐기처리 <br>정도가 딱 맞어 <br>what you want it <br>for the fame <br>for the money <br>I agree man <br>I'm phantom for the judge <br>Why your eyes is wet <br>So dirty your tears smell <br>Yeah I'm a phantom <br>Yeah I'm a phantom <br>Yeah I'm a phantom <br>Yeah I'm a phantom <br>Yeah I'm a phantom <br>Yeah I'm a phantom <br>Yeah I'm a phantom <br>Yeah <br>Cuz I'm a phantom <br>]]></content><category term="R.vao" label="R.vao"/><category term="Phantom (Feat. 딜러 Of Buyers)" label="Phantom (Feat. 딜러 Of Buyers)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주나/신의_한_수_Acoustic_Ver_Inst/</id><title>김주나 - 신의 한 수 (Acoustic Ver.) (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:41:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:41:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%EB%82%98/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9D%98_%ED%95%9C_%EC%88%98_Acoustic_Ver_Inst/" title="김주나 - 신의 한 수 (Acoustic Ver.) (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흔들리는 별빛 속 <br>품었던 작은 꿈들 <br>겁이 없이 찾아 나섰던 <br>그 길이 버거울 때 <br>네가 있었어 마치 꿈처럼 <br>그때 알게 된 또 다른 세상 <br>깨져버렸던 맘의 조각도 <br>너의 숨결에 빛이 되었던 <br>난 너 하나만 있으면 돼 <br>저 별을 쫓아 <br>하늘 위 걸어둔 <br>꿈 닿을 때까지 <br>어둠이 날 감싸도 <br>너만은 절대로 <br>놓치지 않을 거야 <br>You’re my everything <br>거친 운명이 <br>나의 정해진 길이라면 <br>답은 하나 나를 비추는 <br>너라는 신의 한 수 <br>자꾸만 내 맘 되물어 봐도 <br>누가 뭐래도 결국 난 너야 <br>멈출 수 없는 모래시계 속 <br>남은 내 삶에 그 시간 끝에 <br>난 너 하나만 있으면 돼 <br>저 별을 쫓아 <br>하늘 위 걸어둔 <br>꿈 닿을 때까지 <br>어둠이 날 감싸도 <br>너만은 절대로 <br>놓치지 않을 거야 <br>You’re my everything <br>작은 바람 되어 <br>네게 갈 테니 <br>넌 꽃이 돼줘 <br>난 너 하나만 있으면 돼 <br>저 별을 쫓아 <br>하늘 위 걸어둔 <br>꿈 닿을 때까지 <br>어둠이 날 감싸도 <br>너만은 절대로 <br>놓치지 않을 거야 <br>You’re my everything <br>]]></content><category term="김주나" label="김주나"/><category term="신의 한 수 (Acoustic Ver.) (Inst.)" label="신의 한 수 (Acoustic Ver.) (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양요섭/신의_한_수_Inst/</id><title>양요섭 - 신의 한 수 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:41:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:41:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EC%9A%94%EC%84%AD/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9D%98_%ED%95%9C_%EC%88%98_Inst/" title="양요섭 - 신의 한 수 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흔들리는 별빛 속 <br>품었던 작은 꿈들 <br>겁이 없이 찾아 나섰던 <br>그 길이 버거울 때 <br>네가 있었어 마치 꿈처럼 <br>그때 알게 된 또 다른 세상 <br>깨져버렸던 맘의 조각도 <br>너의 숨결에 빛이 되었던 <br>난 너 하나만 있으면 돼 <br>저 별을 쫓아 <br>하늘 위 걸어둔 <br>꿈 닿을 때까지 <br>어둠이 날 감싸도 <br>너만은 절대로 <br>놓치지 않을 거야 <br>You’ll always be mine <br>워 에 오 오에오 <br>워어어어 워어어어 <br>더 가까이 와줘 <br>거친 운명이 <br>나의 정해진 길이라면 <br>답은 하나 나를 비추는 <br>너라는 신의 한 수 <br>자꾸만 내 맘 되물어 봐도 <br>누가 뭐래도 결국 난 너야 <br>멈출 수 없는 모래시계 속 <br>남은 내 삶에 그 시간 끝에 <br>난 너 하나만 있으면 돼 <br>저 별을 쫓아 <br>하늘 위 걸어둔 <br>꿈 닿을 때까지 <br>어둠이 날 감싸도 <br>너만은 절대로 <br>놓치지 않을 거야 <br>You’ll always be mine <br>워 에 오 오에오 <br>워어어어 워어어어 <br>더 가까이 와줘 <br>작은 바람 되어 <br>네게 갈 테니 <br>넌 꽃이 돼줘 <br>난 너 하나만 있으면 돼 <br>저 별을 쫓아 <br>하늘 위 걸어둔 <br>꿈 닿을 때까지 <br>어둠이 날 감싸도 <br>너만은 절대로 <br>놓치지 않을 거야 <br>You’ll always be mine <br>워 에 오 오에오 <br>워어어어 워어어어 <br>더 가까이 와줘 <br>워 에 오 오에오 <br>워어어어 워어어어 <br>You’re everything to me <br>]]></content><category term="양요섭" label="양요섭"/><category term="신의 한 수 (Inst.)" label="신의 한 수 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김주나/신의_한_수_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>김주나 - 신의 한 수 (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:41:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:41:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A3%BC%EB%82%98/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9D%98_%ED%95%9C_%EC%88%98_Acoustic_Ver/" title="김주나 - 신의 한 수 (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흔들리는 별빛 속 <br>품었던 작은 꿈들 <br>겁이 없이 찾아 나섰던 <br>그 길이 버거울 때 <br>네가 있었어 마치 꿈처럼 <br>그때 알게 된 또 다른 세상 <br>깨져버렸던 맘의 조각도 <br>너의 숨결에 빛이 되었던 <br>난 너 하나만 있으면 돼 <br>저 별을 쫓아 <br>하늘 위 걸어둔 <br>꿈 닿을 때까지 <br>어둠이 날 감싸도 <br>너만은 절대로 <br>놓치지 않을 거야 <br>You’re my everything <br>거친 운명이 <br>나의 정해진 길이라면 <br>답은 하나 나를 비추는 <br>너라는 신의 한 수 <br>자꾸만 내 맘 되물어 봐도 <br>누가 뭐래도 결국 난 너야 <br>멈출 수 없는 모래시계 속 <br>남은 내 삶에 그 시간 끝에 <br>난 너 하나만 있으면 돼 <br>저 별을 쫓아 <br>하늘 위 걸어둔 <br>꿈 닿을 때까지 <br>어둠이 날 감싸도 <br>너만은 절대로 <br>놓치지 않을 거야 <br>You’re my everything <br>작은 바람 되어 <br>네게 갈 테니 <br>넌 꽃이 돼줘 <br>난 너 하나만 있으면 돼 <br>저 별을 쫓아 <br>하늘 위 걸어둔 <br>꿈 닿을 때까지 <br>어둠이 날 감싸도 <br>너만은 절대로 <br>놓치지 않을 거야 <br>You’re my everything <br>]]></content><category term="김주나" label="김주나"/><category term="신의 한 수 (Acoustic Ver.)" label="신의 한 수 (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양요섭/신의_한_수/</id><title>양요섭 - 신의 한 수 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:41:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:41:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EC%9A%94%EC%84%AD/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9D%98_%ED%95%9C_%EC%88%98/" title="양요섭 - 신의 한 수 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흔들리는 별빛 속 <br>품었던 작은 꿈들 <br>겁이 없이 찾아 나섰던 <br>그 길이 버거울 때 <br>네가 있었어 마치 꿈처럼 <br>그때 알게 된 또 다른 세상 <br>깨져버렸던 맘의 조각도 <br>너의 숨결에 빛이 되었던 <br>난 너 하나만 있으면 돼 <br>저 별을 쫓아 <br>하늘 위 걸어둔 <br>꿈 닿을 때까지 <br>어둠이 날 감싸도 <br>너만은 절대로 <br>놓치지 않을 거야 <br>You’ll always be mine <br>워 에 오 오에오 <br>워어어어 워어어어 <br>더 가까이 와줘 <br>거친 운명이 <br>나의 정해진 길이라면 <br>답은 하나 나를 비추는 <br>너라는 신의 한 수 <br>자꾸만 내 맘 되물어 봐도 <br>누가 뭐래도 결국 난 너야 <br>멈출 수 없는 모래시계 속 <br>남은 내 삶에 그 시간 끝에 <br>난 너 하나만 있으면 돼 <br>저 별을 쫓아 <br>하늘 위 걸어둔 <br>꿈 닿을 때까지 <br>어둠이 날 감싸도 <br>너만은 절대로 <br>놓치지 않을 거야 <br>You’ll always be mine <br>워 에 오 오에오 <br>워어어어 워어어어 <br>더 가까이 와줘 <br>작은 바람 되어 <br>네게 갈 테니 <br>넌 꽃이 돼줘 <br>난 너 하나만 있으면 돼 <br>저 별을 쫓아 <br>하늘 위 걸어둔 <br>꿈 닿을 때까지 <br>어둠이 날 감싸도 <br>너만은 절대로 <br>놓치지 않을 거야 <br>You’ll always be mine <br>워 에 오 오에오 <br>워어어어 워어어어 <br>더 가까이 와줘 <br>워 에 오 오에오 <br>워어어어 워어어어 <br>You’re everything to me <br>]]></content><category term="양요섭" label="양요섭"/><category term="신의 한 수" label="신의 한 수"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/반/12월의_퀄리아/</id><title>반 - 12월의 퀄리아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:41:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:41:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%98/12%EC%9B%94%EC%9D%98_%ED%80%84%EB%A6%AC%EC%95%84/" title="반 - 12월의 퀄리아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왠지 누구에게도 <br>다정하지 않은 날씨 <br>게을러진 따뜻함에 <br>비라도 내렸으면 <br>한쪽 눈을 감으면 <br>다른 세상이 보일까 <br>반쯤 어두워진 하늘은 <br>밝아지지 않네 <br>어젯밤 꿈과 오늘밤 꿈은 <br>제목이 다른 영화 같은 걸 <br>하지만 눈을 뜨면 이상하게 <br>어제와 똑같은 냄새의 세계 <br>두근거림이 <br>멈추지 않았던 나날들도 <br>더는 좋아할 수 없게 된 <br>계절을 만나고 <br>눈물의 의미마저 <br>잊을 정도로 울었던 <br>파아란 새벽만이 <br>계속 되는 십이월에 <br>어젯밤 꿈과 오늘밤 꿈은 <br>제목이 다른 영화 같은 걸 <br>하지만 눈을 뜨면 이상하게 <br>언제나 똑같은 <br>지금 잠들어버리면 <br>영영 깨지 못할 것만 <br>같은 기분의 세계 <br>]]></content><category term="반" label="반"/><category term="12월의 퀄리아" label="12월의 퀄리아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/P_Money_Remix_Feat_P_Money_Bonus/</id><title>Wiley - P Money Remix (Feat. P Money) (Bonus) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:42:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:42:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/P_Money_Remix_Feat_P_Money_Bonus/" title="Wiley - P Money Remix (Feat. P Money) (Bonus) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I tell a don it ain't funny <br>That's why I practice, so I stay on point like <br>P Money <br>I tell a don it ain't funny <br>That's why I practice, so I stay on point like P Money <br>I tell a don it ain't funny <br>That's why I practice, so I stay on point like P Money, P Money <br>I tell a don it ain't funny <br>That's why I practice, so I stay on point like P Money, P Money <br><br>I ain't never been the type of spitter on a track <br>To have a donny murk me and never murk back <br>Cause all I wanna do is see my name at the top <br>That's why I can't act like I never heard <br>I've got ears, am I hearing, any pussy test, I will spear him <br>Them man have got one bag of chat <br>They've got one bag of Ps, what you bringing round here <br>Ask them what they're doing round here <br>Cuh if they want a bit of mine, tell a man I want to get rid of guys <br>I'm known for rolling with man that's clearly uncivilised <br>Man will fill in these pitta guys <br>About they wanna take man for a mouse <br>Till I press a button and get your fanpage minimised <br>Every single one of their flows are opitimised <br>Everyone's sick till I realised <br>Nobody's sicker than the sickest MC <br>When you realise nobody's slewing 'em again <br>I ain't Skepta, but man's been there, done that <br>And now man is on doing it again <br>Don't touch my set, you'll ruin it again <br>There he goes offbeat, you're doing it again <br>Mad, man can't diss my mum <br>Every clash I've had, I'm on bringing in a skeng <br>Oi, Wiley, tell them again <br><br>I tell a don it ain't funny <br>That's why I practice, so I stay on point like <br>P Money <br>I tell a don it ain't funny <br>That's why I practice, so I stay on point like P Money <br>I tell a don it ain't funny <br>That's why I practice, so I stay on point like P Money, P Money <br>I tell a don it ain't funny <br>That's why I practice, so I stay on point like P Money, P Money <br><br>When I was broke, I was better at this <br>My money got me couple iceberg sweaters and this <br>When I started, I didn't know I'd get on the list <br>Of MCs who were top flight, spraying on the top mic <br>Ain't done the work but you boast that it's not right <br>Used to waste grands on garms but now I shop right <br>First ten years, G, I was on a block hype <br>Some MCs are alike but I'm not like <br>None of them, and I've had wars with a ton of 'em <br>Nobody's ever gonna do what we done again <br>Put me in any scene, I end up running it <br>My crew are winners, we end up sonning them <br>Cuh my dons stand on the frontline <br>Ready for the war in the cold or the sunshine <br>You wanna flop in your game but I run mine <br>I be in the skillzone, bullseye, one time <br><br>That's why I practice, so I stay on point like <br>P Money I'm telling you <br>I tell a don it ain't funny <br>That's why I practice, so I stay on point like P Money brap, brap <br>I tell a don it ain't funny <br>That's why I practice, so I stay on point like P Money, P Money <br>I tell a don it ain't funny hey <br>That's why I practice, so I stay on point like P Money, P Money <br><br>Yo, a lot of these MCs think they're bad <br>I held the MAC and the MAC went mad <br>This something screaming ratatat <br>And now you're a myth nobody know, blam <br>Everybody scatters, nobody look back <br>Don't drink loads and think that you're rough, blud <br>I will show you Jack and Daniels gassed]]></content><category term="Wiley" label="Wiley"/><category term="P Money Remix (Feat. P Money) (Bonus)" label="P Money Remix (Feat. P Money) (Bonus)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Laptop_Feat_Manga/</id><title>Wiley - Laptop (Feat. Manga) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:42:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:42:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Laptop_Feat_Manga/" title="Wiley - Laptop (Feat. Manga) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's my life, that machine <br>All of my thoughts inside that machine <br>I've got my youts laptops young <br>So when they get older, money ah go run <br>Get your IT skills up, and watch how your bank fills up <br>You want thousands Then you get your mills up <br>This lappy can buy you houses <br>Me and mine go together like real love <br>I've been a MacBook pro for a while <br>And you ain't seen me at a show for a while <br>But I'm back with a couple of bangers for my culture <br>Couldn't stop me even if you was a vulture <br>Right now, I've gotta charge up <br>When I see eight green dots, then I'm charged up <br>Bigging up Danny, Target, large up <br>From Roman disc days to start up <br><br>I take pride in what I do, it's why I've got a laptop <br>I do it every day, I've gotta hit the jackpot <br>I hit the jackpot when they say the track's hot <br>Had bare records on the wall, it was looking like <br>A New Era hat shop, no backdrop <br>Pray this beat is like a goalie here <br>Dem man saved couple shots but they couldn't stop that shot <br>I've got one main tool my laptop <br><br>Let me tell you how man got here <br>Started off with the cracked software <br>All them plugins made man <br>So much money and it didn't stop there <br>Went on for years of my life <br>I was in the kitchen making riddims all night <br>Sound card, mic and a keyboard <br>And I wasn't looking for a reward <br>I was doing it, passion the leader <br>Since and the fever <br>Any vision that I had was a real one <br>I'm a Logic user a real one <br>Reach for a draw of the peng and then I build one <br>Wanted a scene and I built one <br>My laptop's part of my brain <br>Since I've had one, I ain't ever been the same <br><br>I take pride in what I do, it's why I've got a laptop <br>I do it every day, I've gotta hit the jackpot <br>I hit the jackpot when they say the track's hot <br>Had bare records on the wall, it was looking like <br>A New Era hat shop, no backdrop <br>Pray this beat is like a goalie here <br>Dem man saved couple shots but they couldn't stop that shot <br>I've got one main tool my laptop <br><br>Oi, it's my tool, that machine <br>That MacBook Pro <br>MacBook Pro forever, trust me <br><br>Use that, get back, draw for the Mac <br>Ayy, yo, record, biggerman <br>Do the video and the artwork too <br>Yeah, man, all of that jazz <br>No, I never backtrack, black jeans, black hat <br>Mac in my backpack like I'm tryna war with a man <br>Quad core does more <br> for what, rudeboy on a man <br>Ready fi get bill up, hard drive fill up <br>Gotta do works if you wanna be a winner <br>Anything I gotta do, I'm gonna do it quicker <br>Only relying on the brudda in the mirror <br>A me that, life, you can't CMD+Z that <br>Me done preed that, mad if you can't see that <br>Send out, I bring up the riddims <br>No, I can't ever relax <br><br>I take pride in what I do, it's why I've got a laptop <br>I do it every day, I've gotta hit the jackpot <br>I hit the jackpot when they say the track's hot <br>Had bare records on the wall, it was looking like <br>A New Era hat shop, no backdrop <br>Pray this beat is like a goalie here <br>Dem man saved couple shots but they couldn't stop that shot <br>I've got one main tool my laptop]]></content><category term="Wiley" label="Wiley"/><category term="Laptop (Feat. Manga)" label="Laptop (Feat. Manga)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Lucid/</id><title>Wiley - Lucid - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:43:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:43:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Lucid/" title="Wiley - Lucid - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was on point when I made The Elusive <br>Mum told me, Stop makin' excuses <br>I'ma drop my album on fans exclusive <br>Do it for my people, they say I'm lucid <br>People tell me they only want true shit no lie <br>Tell a man don't take the food if you know you can't move it leave that there <br>I'ma drop my album on fans exclusive that's right <br>I do it for my people, they say I'm lucid <br><br>All these days in a month <br>Tryna get everything done <br>When I try do too much <br>I don't get anything done <br>Rollin' through like a bulldozer <br>I go hard, here I go, here I come <br>Now when I think about what I wanna do <br>I wanna do what's never been done <br>I wanna see my genre where it belongs <br>It's gettin' bigger, are you hearin' the songs <br>I wanna hail up Meridian Dan <br>And the rest of the Meridian Gang <br>Big up the youngers who were comin' up in the game <br>Yes, you can make a million pound <br>I was with Geeneus, we made the wickedest ting <br>From day, we've been living this sound <br><br>I was on point when I made The Elusive <br>Mum told me, Stop makin' excuses <br>I'ma drop my album on fans exclusive <br>Do it for my people, they say I'm lucid <br>People tell me they only want true shit no lie <br>Tell a man don't take the food if you know you can't move it leave that there <br>I'ma drop my album on fans exclusive that's right <br>I do it for my people, they say I'm lucid <br><br>All these months in a year <br>Sippin' on wine and beer <br>So much gyal over here <br>Must be love in the air <br>All I wanna do is party all night <br>So let me just make that clear <br>I can see bottles of the Grey Goose <br>I can see bottles of Belvedere <br>Rise in the mornin', I put the work in <br>Flow's wavy like a duck surfin' <br>You can stand still but the clock's turnin' <br>If you don't work then you're not earnin' <br>For the right reason, I know about cash <br>I should have a birthday bash <br>Then I can draw for my <br>25 MCs chilling out back <br><br>I was on point when I made The Elusive <br>Mum told me, Stop makin' excuses <br>I'ma drop my album on fans exclusive <br>Do it for my people, they say I'm lucid <br>People tell me they only want true shit no lie <br>Tell a man don't take the food if you know you can't move it leave that there <br>I'ma drop my album on fans exclusive that's right <br>I do it for my people, they say I'm lucid <br><br>All these dons in the crew <br>Bare shows, always on the move <br>Murk it where we go to <br>Man skank out, I should do a bogul <br>If the show's live then I'll do a stage dive <br>You got your phone out, you're on FaceTime <br>Fist pumpin' like before race time <br>Heart beatin' like it's police chase time <br>I've been given new time <br>I've learned loads and loads through time <br>Let me give a shout to my scene one time <br>Let me give a shout to my scene two time <br>Now I get clocked like a sport shoe sign <br>Man jump ahead like more food time <br>I can still spray up the riddims <br>Of the oldest or the new grime <br><br>I was on point when I made The Elusive <br>Mum told me, Stop makin' excuses <br>I'ma drop my album on fans exclusive <br>Do it for my people, they say I'm lucid <br>People tell me they only want true shit no lie <br>Tell a man don't take the food if you know you can't move it leave that there <br>I'ma drop my album on fans exclusive that's right <br>I do it for my people, they say I'm lucid]]></content><category term="Wiley" label="Wiley"/><category term="Lucid" label="Lucid"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Like_It_Or_Not_Feat_Breeze/</id><title>Wiley - Like It Or Not (Feat. Breeze) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:43:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:43:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Like_It_Or_Not_Feat_Breeze/" title="Wiley - Like It Or Not (Feat. Breeze) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Swifta production <br><br>Ride for the side, die for the team <br>First in the scene, like it or not <br>Ride for the side, die for the team <br>First in the scene, like it or not <br>Been around the block, spin around the block <br>Been around the top, my streets hot <br>Been around the block, spin around the block <br>Been around the top, like it or not <br><br>Like it or not, I was at the start <br>You was saying stop dat, we was in the dance <br>We were getting reloads inside clubs <br>We were getting reloads out in the parks <br>Flew past everyone who had a head start <br>Time flew quick, then I had to get smart <br>Now it's a new day, everybody's got new ways <br>That's why I'm not living in the past <br>I perceived the whole game on the whole same as a ref <br>Started on the right but I came from the left <br>Born in the east but stayed in the west <br>Put my money down, I ain't changing my bet <br>Never been a goal hanger cause I can dribble <br>I was in jungle spraying bars with Riddles <br>Used to blaze weed, eat food, get the giggles <br>See me in a sweet shop looking for the Skittles <br><br>Ride for the side, die for the team <br>First in the scene, like it or not <br>Ride for the side, die for the team <br>First in the scene, like it or not <br>Been around the block, spin around the block <br>Been around the top, my streets hot <br>Been around the block, spin around the block <br>Been around the top, like it or not <br><br>Like it or not, I came from the block <br>What I've seen might just leave you in shock <br>Man are in the station, prison or dock <br>Man are on the street with MACs, knives and Glocks <br>And dons getting ran down, chased round blocks <br>Dons getting skied by multiple shots <br>Dons getting kidnapped, dons getting robbed <br>That's why I tell a don just go get a job <br>Blud, I was on the roof, I was in the trenches <br>I was on the mic chatting 'bout sixth senses <br>I was on the radio, legal and pirate <br>I was in the hood when they first called Trident <br>Doors getting kicked off, guns getting found <br>How'd you think I produced the coldest sound <br>I was in the zone, anywhere you go <br>You can tell a man this ain't a bogus sound <br><br>Ride for the side, die for the team <br>First in the scene, like it or not <br>Ride for the side, die for the team <br>First in the scene, like it or not <br>Been around the block, spin around the block <br>Been around the top, my streets hot <br>Been around the block, spin around the block <br>Been around the top, like it or not <br><br>Yo, do it every year, fam, I never stop <br>The level of my lyrics will never drop <br>You've been watching us years now <br>I've already written gold bars I could never top <br>Made sick beats I could never top <br>Couple ideas that will never drop <br>Started together in the game <br>Some man are so sick with it <br>But they will never pop <br>Me and my team will forever pop <br>I ain't gotta go and get a better job <br>This one's cool, we all get along <br>Man want a tea Put the kettle on <br>Clear my brain and I'm better off <br>If you know she's mad, then don't set her off <br>Told you before <br>I do my show, then I'm jetting off <br><br>Ride for the side, die for the team <br>First in the scene, like it or not <br>Ride for the side, die for the team <br>First in the scene, like it or not <br>Been around the block, spin around the block <br>Been around the top, my streets hot <br>Been around the block, spin around the block <br>Been around the top, like it or not]]></content><category term="Wiley" label="Wiley"/><category term="Like It Or Not (Feat. Breeze)" label="Like It Or Not (Feat. Breeze)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/My_Direction/</id><title>Wiley - My Direction - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:43:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:43:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/My_Direction/" title="Wiley - My Direction - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I go to war, I dun them <br>Could be this crew or that crew, I dun them <br>Could've joined that friend up, I will dun them <br>Out of town, that's where I run them <br>When I go to war, I dun them <br>Could be this crew or that crew, I dun them <br>Could've joined that friend up, I will dun them <br>Out of town, that's where I run them <br><br>Out of town, that's where I run you <br>I'll run up on the stage right now and I will dun you <br>I did it on my own in my city like a one yout <br>Ain't a battle but I'm spitting like a one two <br>Cyan't find me cause I'm lost like a <br>Door's open, everybody wanna run through <br>I run through crew, I've got the pass for the run through <br>See a buff gyal, then I'm like come through <br>Always see me killing it, killing it like a madman <br>Everybody's into man or tryna be a badman <br> man snaked man and grabbed man <br>Fling you in the boot, uppercut, then jab man <br>Flow's so wavy, fitting like a snapback <br>Grew up on The Prodigy, grew up on the rap act <br>My flow's ebola, my flow's anthrax <br>Yo, I've got a new vibe, everybody's on that <br><br>When I go to war, I dun them <br>Could be this crew or that crew, I dun them <br>Could've joined that friend up, I will dun them <br>Out of town, that's where I run them <br>When I go to war, I dun them <br>Could be this crew or that crew, I dun them <br>Could've joined that friend up, I will dun them <br>Out of town, that's where I run them <br><br>In '04, said I wanna be the best MC <br>I don't care about being on TV <br>I make couple mil, couple gyal, that's me <br>Have couple yards, couple cars, that's me <br>Two sixteen out here, murking shows <br>No Akademics now, I wear Dench clothes <br>Had a Punto, now I cop Lambos <br>Hard work pays off, yeah, don, I know <br>Sold out tours, yeah, come to a show <br>If you ain't got the right P, the answer's no <br>Didn't see you on Rinse, didn't see you on Deja <br>Now you wanna call me family, bro Leave it <br>Looking for a bringing You won't receive it <br>To get this far, you won't believe it <br>I'm not from Newham, I'm a general <br>Put some respeck on my name when you speak it <br><br>When I go to war, I dun them <br>Could be this crew or that crew, I dun them <br>Could've joined that friend up, I will dun them <br>Out of town, that's where I run them <br>When I go to war, I dun them <br>Could be this crew or that crew, I dun them <br>Could've joined that friend up, I will dun them <br>Out of town, that's where I run them <br><br>Yo, my name's Wiley, I'm grimy <br>I'm too shiesty, you won't get beside me <br>You won't get by or past me, don't put it past me <br>Blud, you will never outlast me <br>Yo, my name's Wiley, I'm grimy <br>I'm too shiesty, you won't get beside me <br>You won't get by or past me, don't put it past me <br>Blud, you will never <br>I've got stripes on my shoulders, scars of all the wars I've been in <br>Blud, I've never been a fortunate king <br>But if a man can live through the worse, avoiding the curse <br>Don't matter 'bout the wars I've been in <br>I've been getting run down and running man down too <br>If man are grass then I can't be around you <br>I'm in the trenches, man might surround you <br>Man get rushed, can't swing Then you better learn how to <br><br>Dun them <br>Could be this crew or that crew, I dun them <br>Could've joined that friend up, I will dun them <br>Out of town, that's where I run them <br>When I go to war, I dun them <br>Could be this crew or that crew, I dun them <br>Could've joined that friend up, I will dun them <br>Out of town, that's where I run them]]></content><category term="Wiley" label="Wiley"/><category term="My Direction" label="My Direction"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Bait_Face_Feat_Scratchy/</id><title>Wiley - Bait Face (Feat. Scratchy) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:43:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:43:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Bait_Face_Feat_Scratchy/" title="Wiley - Bait Face (Feat. Scratchy) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My face is bait, I can't hide it <br>I make the beat sound better when I ride it <br>We're top of the game, they don't like it <br>I hit the road everyday like a cyclist <br>They can't battle with us, we're like vikings <br>Freestyle straight off the brain with no writing <br>When I get off the plane, I'm still flying <br>Dem man are at the bottom of the food chain, crying <br><br>Jump onstage looking for a reload with your best bar <br>And don't get one, that's hype <br>That means the crowd don't wanna hear you on the mic <br>For some reason, they're thinking that's hype <br>All they wanna do is sit and hear who they like <br>I've been killing sets in the middle of the night <br>My lyrical flow is flying high up like a kite <br>That's why you can't touch it cause we are not alike <br>I walk in the place like everybody's better than me <br>Hmm, sike, yeah, that's hype <br>I can ride riddim as good as I ride bikes <br>Small bikes, mountain bikes and power bikes <br>But if I add flash for the wheelie <br>And drop down, bro, that's hype <br>Even though I'm used to doing what I like <br>Some of what I do is right or it's hype <br><br>My face is bait, I can't hide it <br>I make the beat sound better when I ride it <br>We're top of the game, they don't like it <br>I hit the road everyday like a cyclist <br>They can't battle with us, we're like vikings <br>Freestyle straight off the brain with no writing <br>When I get off the plane, I'm still flying <br>Dem man are at the bottom of the food chain, crying <br><br>There's only one of me, there ain't two <br>There's a donny round here and it ain't you <br>I ain't rich but I make do <br>Get the job done in one, fuck take two <br>You don't like me but your mates do <br>Scratchy's about, stay tuned <br>Yiyiyiyi, take that <br>Sharpest knife in the drawer, cutting straight through <br>If you go looking for war, you're gonna find it <br>But I ain't scared of war, I don't mind it <br>Don't try read my mind, you're not psychic <br>Next time, think before you start typing <br>Next time, think before you start hyping <br>I make the car look better when I drive it <br>I make the bike look better when I ride it <br>Bass, followed by strings and violins <br><br>My face is bait, I can't hide it <br>I make the beat sound better when I ride it <br>We're top of the game, they don't like it <br>I hit the road everyday like a cyclist <br>They can't battle with us, we're like vikings <br>Freestyle straight off the brain with no writing <br>When I get off the plane, I'm still flying <br>Dem man are at the bottom of the food chain, crying <br><br>Live life on water, live life on dry land <br>I've got the words flowing from my right hand <br>Man are generous, never been a tight man <br>If you've got a problem, step on the grass and fight, fam <br>Sprite got me off 7Up <br>Then I drink so much, I am a Sprite man <br>Do it solo, I don't wanna hype man <br>I can make a song off top, I rock and write, fam <br>Anytime I speak, that's bars for the fans <br>I've been on a high note from I started my plans <br>Got a face for music, hail up Chams <br>Wasting any time ain't part of the plan <br>It's about man grabbing yellow dots like it's Pac Man <br>Be your own boss so a man can't sack man <br>Drop the first one, drop the sequel <br>You might last long in the game just like Lethal <br><br>My face is bait, I can't hide it <br>I make the beat sound better when I ride it <br>We're top of the game, they don't like it <br>I hit the road everyday like a cyclist <br>They can't battle with us, we're like vikings <br>Freestyle straight off the brain with no writing <br>When I get off the plane, I'm still flying <br>Dem man are at the bottom of the food chain, crying]]></content><category term="Wiley" label="Wiley"/><category term="Bait Face (Feat. Scratchy)" label="Bait Face (Feat. Scratchy)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/On_This_Feat_Chip_Ice_Kid__Little_D/</id><title>Wiley - On This (Feat. Chip, Ice Kid &amp; Little D) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:43:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:43:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/On_This_Feat_Chip_Ice_Kid__Little_D/" title="Wiley - On This (Feat. Chip, Ice Kid &amp; Little D) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Name won't die out <br>I proved my point at the try outs <br>Can't sell things for the wrong price <br>Wanna own stuff, no buy outs <br>Had a flow for the longest <br>Had bars for the longest <br>Other dons wonder why they won't last so long <br>It's cause they ain't on this <br><br>I'm on tings, ring my phone, no long ting <br>Could've been the right or the wrong ting <br>Make a big song ting <br>Everybody sing along ting <br>Hold tight my gang, though, sing along kings <br>I bring along kings <br>They bring along other sing along kings <br>I've shown you already what a string of luck brings <br>Don't matter about your upbringing <br>Man are still winning, on this ting every day though <br>Songs don't drop everyday, they're getting made though <br>Ain't on the radio much, I'm getting played though <br>No, I ain't new in the game, I'm getting paid dough <br>Top grime dons are the livest <br>All the fans come through and decide this <br>History's written, I ain't gotta rewrite it <br>Man are the elite, bro, we ain't gotta hide it <br><br>Name won't die out <br>I proved my point at the try outs <br>Can't sell things for the wrong price <br>Wanna own stuff, no buy outs <br>Had a flow for the longest <br>Had bars for the longest <br>Other dons wonder why they won't last so long <br>It's cause they ain't on this <br><br>RIP jokes 'llow that, 'llow that <br>Man can't die out never <br>I book that and fly out somewhere hot <br>I let it boom bye bye out <br>Tek man for chocolate chip <br>You can't melt me or deep fry me 'llow that, 'llow that <br>I beg a man don't doubt me <br>Put lion bars on a bounty <br>Can't let nuttin' slide, come on guys come on <br>Tell a boy fuck your watch, take your time come on <br>You man forced the wheel, on your bike come on <br>You're bad in your ends, not in mine 'llow it <br>You're nice over there, not on grime come on <br>Don't come over here, stay aside yeah <br>Mad ting, over here <br>Lyrics fly like birds in the sky <br><br>Name won't die out <br>I proved my point at the try outs <br>Can't sell things for the wrong price <br>Wanna own stuff, no buy outs <br>Had a flow for the longest <br>Had bars for the longest <br>Other dons wonder why they won't last so long <br>It's cause they ain't on this <br>Name won't die out <br>I proved my point at the try outs <br>Can't sell things for the wrong price <br>Wanna own stuff, no buy outs <br>Had a flow for the longest <br>Had bars for the longest <br>Other dons wonder why they won't last so long <br>It's cause they ain't on this <br><br>Anybody fronting <br>Like you're on top, I'ma dun your hype <br>Cold like a chunk of ice, undefined <br>Best stick to your humble pie <br>You know me, man, I flow deep like when I <br>Anybody coming here better come precise <br>Quit talking a bunch of shite, you're not hard <br>Man have got bars something like RondoNumbaNine <br>Feel like I be the greatest to ever <br>Step foot on the face of the earth <br>Got a way with the words, haters wanna rain on my turf <br>Till I take 'em away in a hearse <br>Vacate cause you ain't got the nerve or the <br>So many things I can state in a verse <br>Spray words for the cake in your purse <br>But you man are all broke, it's like you ain't able to work <br><br>Name won't die out <br>I proved my point at the try outs <br>Can't sell things for the wrong price <br>Wanna own stuff, no buy outs <br>Had a flow for the longest <br>Had bars for the longest <br>Other dons wonder why they won't last so long <br>It's cause they ain't on this <br><br>Look, our line of work was lining work <br>Now I'm in the game doing grime with nerds <br>Said that I'm a diamond in the dirt <br>But I don't know what a diamond's worth <br>I was in the big house riding bird <br>Sitting with Skrigz, Hattie and Church <br>Real life link up behind the bars <br>Now I'm back in the lab like Heisenberg <br>Still spitting that meth, turn up to a man's set <br>Giving it as good as he gets <br>Wasn't impressed, labels show interest <br>Still don't wanna invest <br>Anyone's guess, man said he wanted me dead <br>I put the piece to a man's chest, then I put him in check <br>No, I don't indirect <br>Something that I need to address I'll be at your address <br><br>Name won't die out <br>I proved my point at the try outs <br>Can't sell things for the wrong price <br>Wanna own stuff, no buy outs <br>Had a flow for the longest <br>Had bars for the longest <br>Other dons wonder why they won't last so long <br>It's cause they ain't on this]]></content><category term="Wiley" label="Wiley"/><category term="On This (Feat. Chip, Ice Kid &amp; Little D)" label="On This (Feat. Chip, Ice Kid &amp; Little D)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Bang_Feat_Ghetts/</id><title>Wiley - Bang (Feat. Ghetts) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:43:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:43:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Bang_Feat_Ghetts/" title="Wiley - Bang (Feat. Ghetts) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bang, same city, new blocks <br>Bang, boombox on the rooftop <br>Bang, who's hot Who's not <br>Bang, new job, who's boss <br><br>Self employed wealthy boy <br>Dealt with pain, dealt with joy <br>Me and Wiley are cool now <br>But I'm the same nigga who tried help destroy him <br>Tell Lorraine, tell McCoy <br>I failed again, felt annoyed <br>Now I've got paper round <br>Me, Daily Star cause I sell the voice <br>Oi, it's the paper boy, I'm in effect <br>Don't like me I've always been a threat <br>My only competition is the man in the mirror <br>My niggas or my silhouette <br>They know I'm a flamethrower <br>Make man lay low and lay lower <br>Anybody says that they can't get hold of me <br>Tell them niggas I'll be on the same blower <br>Who am I The baddest MC that grime ever produced <br>The resident Eskimo goer <br>Culture vultures, they owe us <br>Oh, now they know us <br><br>Bang, same city, new blocks <br>Bang, boombox on the rooftop <br>Bang, who's hot Who's not <br>Bang, new job, who's boss <br>Bang, same city, new blocks <br>Bang, boombox on the rooftop <br>Bang, who's hot Who's not <br>Bang, new job, who's boss <br><br>Bang I'm hot, so what <br>Bang I'm out spitting for free, no gwop <br>Bang And my path is clear, no stops <br>Got yards in the sticks, no shops, no cops <br>Bang Keep my mind on the cash <br>I see if I can turn a stack <br>I know you love practicing but <br>Me and my niggas were born burning tracks <br>Like yo, they know I'm that post quitter <br>Mind that gyal dere, she's a gold digger <br>Chatting 'bout with her <br>Push me far, turn me to a cold figure <br>Respect, you do it, but man have done it <br>Anybody from the elite, you know we run it <br>Here's what it feels like to win <br>Get rewarded, I'll do a hundred miles and running <br><br>Bang, same city, new blocks <br>Bang, boombox on the rooftop <br>Bang, who's hot Who's not <br>Bang, new job, who's boss <br>Bang, same city, new blocks <br>Bang, boombox on the rooftop <br>Bang, who's hot Who's not <br>Bang, new job, who's boss <br><br>Bang, same city, new blocks <br>Bang, boombox on the rooftop <br>Bang, who's hot Who's not <br>Bang, new job, who's boss <br>Bang, same city, new blocks <br>Bang, boombox on the rooftop <br>Bang, who's hot Who's not <br>Bang, new job, who's boss <br><br>GH, and I've been doing this <br>Since I had an Ericsson 338 <br>And I have pushed more wigs back <br>Than a label has done to an album release date <br>If I send for an MC <br>Then man better reply tonight, not a week late <br>If a man can't move on from the war <br>Right after it, bro, that's a weak trait <br>I'm not a lager lout <br>But I'm still throwing bars about <br>Midday, looking for a haircut <br>Shop's packed, gotta go to the barber's house <br>I'm doing business everyday here <br>That's why I can't mess or laugh about <br>When it comes to the grime in 2016, rudeboy <br>I'm the hardest out <br><br>Bang, same city, new blocks <br>Bang, boombox on the rooftop <br>Bang, who's hot Who's not <br>Bang, new job, who's boss <br>Bang, same city, new blocks <br>Bang, boombox on the rooftop <br>Bang, who's hot Who's not <br>Bang, new job, who's boss]]></content><category term="Wiley" label="Wiley"/><category term="Bang (Feat. Ghetts)" label="Bang (Feat. Ghetts)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Cant_Go_Wrong/</id><title>Wiley - Can`t Go Wrong - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:43:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:43:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Cant_Go_Wrong/" title="Wiley - Can`t Go Wrong - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My team's got a lot of dons <br>And we're doing this ting, go check out the songs <br>Man Don't Care, we shut down the park <br>You can see us onstage like what's going on <br>BBK got a lot going on <br>Skepta, that's my brudda, that's my don <br>They could never control how man are doing it <br>It's authentic, can't go wrong <br><br>Can't go wrong <br>Can't go wrong <br>When it's straight from the heart, you can't go wrong <br>If it's a real vibe then you can't go wrong <br>Can't go wrong <br>Can't go wrong <br>When it's straight from the heart, you can't go wrong <br>If it's a real vibe then you can't go wrong <br><br>When it's straight from the heart, the music gets heard <br>Could've been a roadman, could've been a nerd <br>Dad told me don't follow the herd <br>Instinct, yes, I follow the word <br>I used to go and get what I'm given <br>Now I go and get what I'm worth <br>Still going strong cause I gotta believe <br>That I'm the wickedest grime MC on this earth <br><br>My team's got a lot of dons <br>And we're doing this ting, go check out the songs <br>Man Don't Care, we shut down the park <br>You can see us onstage like what's going on <br>BBK got a lot going on <br>Skepta, that's my brudda, that's my don <br>They could never control how man are doing it <br>It's authentic, can't go wrong <br><br>Can't go wrong <br>Can't go wrong <br>When it's straight from the heart, you can't go wrong <br>If it's a real vibe then you can't go wrong <br>Can't go wrong <br>Can't go wrong <br>When it's straight from the heart, you can't go wrong <br>If it's a real vibe then you can't go wrong <br><br>Yo, I wanna MC, bruv <br>Step in the place and I MC, bruv <br>Jump on the stage and I MC, bruv <br>Mash up the place when I MC, bruv <br>Bruv, I wanna MC, bruv <br>Pass me the mic, I'mma MC, bruv <br>No question, top flight MC, bruv <br>Full clip, never on empty, bruv <br><br>My team's got a lot of dons <br>And we're doing this ting, go check out the songs <br>Man Don't Care, we shut down the park <br>You can see us onstage like what's going on <br>BBK got a lot going on <br>Skepta, that's my brudda, that's my don <br>They could never control how man are doing it <br>It's authentic, can't go wrong <br><br>Can't go wrong <br>Can't go wrong <br>When it's straight from the heart, you can't go wrong <br>If it's a real vibe then you can't go wrong <br>Can't go wrong <br>Can't go wrong <br>When it's straight from the heart, you can't go wrong <br>If it's a real vibe then you can't go wrong <br><br>What's gwaning What's the motion <br>Fresh out the oven like a Sunday roast <br>You can find me swimming in the ocean <br>Sunset, I might drive round the coast <br>When it's showtime, jump on a plane and take flight <br>I stand out like one brake light <br>Everybody wants their crew to be sick <br>But you and your crew are just one great hype <br><br>My team's got a lot of dons <br>And we're doing this ting, go check out the songs <br>Man Don't Care, we shut down the park <br>You can see us onstage like what's going on <br>BBK got a lot going on <br>Skepta, that's my brudda, that's my don <br>They could never control how man are doing it <br>It's authentic, can't go wrong <br><br>Can't go wrong <br>Can't go wrong <br>When it's straight from the heart, you can't go wrong <br>If it's a real vibe then you can't go wrong <br>Can't go wrong <br>Can't go wrong <br>When it's straight from the heart, you can't go wrong <br>If it's a real vibe then you can't go wrong]]></content><category term="Wiley" label="Wiley"/><category term="Can`t Go Wrong" label="Can`t Go Wrong"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Pattern_Up_Properly_Feat_Flowdan__Jamakabi/</id><title>Wiley - Pattern Up Properly (Feat. Flowdan &amp; Jamakabi) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:43:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:43:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Pattern_Up_Properly_Feat_Flowdan__Jamakabi/" title="Wiley - Pattern Up Properly (Feat. Flowdan &amp; Jamakabi) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I'm on a mission <br>I can't let anything stop me <br>When I'm on a mission <br>I can't let anyone knock me <br>That's why when I go out <br>Gotta make sure my ting pattern up properly <br>That's why when I go out <br>Gotta make sure my ting pattern up properly, listen <br><br>My ting pattern up like mosh <br>Trouser, blazer, waistcoat and shirt <br>In my life, now man are big brand like Bosch <br>I won't forget I came from the dirt <br>If I go to a dance to rave, I think smart <br>Keep humble, I play my part <br>I've had a sick flow from the start <br>And I walked in the shubs with Jermaine and Marc <br>I've got bars for the shubs <br>Bars for the gyal dem, bars for the crooks <br>Anyone tryna set pace <br>Gonna get a nah look straight in the face <br>Anyone tryna get lairy <br>Better be careful, don't come near me <br>My dons are in here <br>I'm right but a couple of wrongs are in here <br><br>When I'm on a mission <br>I can't let anything stop me <br>When I'm on a mission <br>I can't let anyone knock me <br>That's why when I go out <br>Gotta make sure my ting pattern up properly <br>That's why when I go out <br>Gotta make sure my ting pattern up properly, listen <br><br>Yo, so everyting pattern <br>When the big dog's on campus <br>OGs, killers and champions <br>My darg, remember your manners <br>Cuh mi nuh tek tough talk, rise every cannon <br>Slap one out of the rooftop <br>We mek dem scatter when they say they wanna group up <br>Bumbahole dead, tell a man move up <br>Alright then, shut down shop and then roll out <br>Global, we nuh lock one town <br>Gun bag, 'nuff of dem are gun clown <br>None of them are ready for us to start dumping <br>Man ah move scary like Halloween pumpkin <br>Clart one, mek them stop fronting <br>Some likkle man need to remember <br>That the farrda always been a don king <br><br>When I'm on a mission <br>I can't let anything stop me <br>When I'm on a mission <br>I can't let anyone knock me <br>That's why when I go out <br>Gotta make sure my ting pattern up properly <br>That's why when I go out <br>Gotta make sure my ting pattern up properly, listen <br><br>When I'm on a mission <br>I can't let anything stop me <br>When I'm on a mission <br>I can't let anyone knock me <br>That's why when I go out <br>Gotta make sure my ting pattern up properly <br>That's why when I go out <br>Gotta make sure my ting pattern up properly, listen <br><br>I'm a lyrical phenomenon <br>When I'm on the riddim, ain't nobody badder than this <br>I'm honey, lemon and overproof rum <br>You're just a likkle Lemsip <br>I'm an old school vet, you're a bandwagonist <br>Ayy bwoy, tek time inna dis <br>I'm an HGV, you're a full licence <br>Don't carry no weight like this <br>I'm a known heavyweight inna dis <br>You're known as a bantamweight inna dis <br>If your girl ever saw me in the dance <br>You would ah get left looking ever so pissed <br>Your girl told me when it comes to the beating <br>I am the pro on and you're on a mist <br>But let me tell you straight, when it comes to the eating <br>You are the pro cuh <br><br>When I'm on a mission <br>I can't let anything stop me <br>When I'm on a mission <br>I can't let anyone knock me <br>That's why when I go out <br>Gotta make sure my ting pattern up properly <br>That's why when I go out <br>Gotta make sure my ting pattern up properly, listen <br><br>When I'm on a mission <br>I can't let anything stop me <br>When I'm on a mission <br>I can't let anyone knock me <br>That's why when I go out <br>Gotta make sure my ting pattern up properly <br>That's why when I go out <br>Gotta make sure my ting pattern up properly, listen]]></content><category term="Wiley" label="Wiley"/><category term="Pattern Up Properly (Feat. Flowdan &amp; Jamakabi)" label="Pattern Up Properly (Feat. Flowdan &amp; Jamakabi)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Joe_Bloggs_Feat_Newham_Generals__President_T /</id><title>Wiley - Joe Bloggs (Feat. Newham Generals &amp; President T) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:43:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:43:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Joe_Bloggs_Feat_Newham_Generals__President_T%09/" title="Wiley - Joe Bloggs (Feat. Newham Generals &amp; President T) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Call shots, go against odds <br>Can't go fishing if you ain't got rods <br>'Nuff of dem are spring leg just like frogs <br>But man ah man are old school like Joe Bloggs <br>Gotta bill a pension now so when I'm older <br>I can live when I can't get jobs <br>When I make a song, I ain't looking for a nod <br>Cause man ah man are old school like Joe Bloggs <br><br>Man can't say how war wicked I was <br>Man are old school like the Wizard of Oz <br>Man are old school like Bucky O'Hare <br>Man'll pull out the ting and Bucky O'Hare <br>Man are old school, 2Pac had hair <br>Man are old school, 2Pac was here <br>Man are old school just like Ghostbusters <br>And the smoke with them old school rusters <br>Oi, remember when Sharon Stone opened a leg <br>Man are old school like Bill and Ted <br>Now, you wouldn't know that cuh you was in bed <br>Cuddling up with SuperTed <br>That's never been a super bread <br>Budubupbup <br>Follow the leader, leader, leader <br>Follow the leader, budubup, we <br><br>Call shots, go against odds <br>Can't go fishing if you ain't got rods <br>'Nuff of dem are spring leg just like frogs <br>But man ah man are old school like Joe Bloggs <br>Gotta bill a pension now so when I'm older <br>I can live when I can't get jobs <br>When I make a song, I ain't looking for a nod <br>Cause man ah man are old school like Joe Bloggs <br><br>Man ah man are old school, two strap FILA <br>Look, I can show you the odds <br>'Nuff man ah talk 'bout putting in work <br>None of these breddas ain't got no jobs <br>Man ah man ah talk 'bout how they hook gyal like fish <br>But man ah man ain't got rods <br>Don't talk 'bout wait on the re up <br>You get a benners, I get a ki up <br>Just link one two gyal <br>Dun know, they're both gonna free up <br>I made four five moves at six <br>I've gotta big my P up <br>I keep it N to the G up <br>I stay away from knobs <br>If there's a known probability <br>Then I'm gonna tell man probs <br><br>Call shots, go against odds <br>Can't go fishing if you ain't got rods <br>'Nuff of dem are spring leg just like frogs <br>But man ah man are old school like Joe Bloggs <br>Gotta bill a pension now so when I'm older <br>I can live when I can't get jobs <br>When I make a song, I ain't looking for a nod <br>Cause man ah man are old school like Joe Bloggs <br><br>Man ah man are old school like Joe Bloggs <br>Blazing, blazing, but I ain't calling squads <br>Key to the block but I ain't holding fobs <br>Took advice from my uncle but it ain't Bob's <br>Started the shop in the town <br>Back to the city of gods, wow <br>Never been after a head shake <br>Gave him a chance, call it a dead take <br>'Nuff of dem are spring feet, thousand missions <br>Not one of 'em complete <br>I was the whole grain without the wheat <br>So old school, I still purchase without receipt <br>Call me a president without the suite <br>Old school, old school, I don't give a monkey's <br>If I'm off beat <br><br>Call shots, go against odds <br>Can't go fishing if you ain't got rods <br>'Nuff of dem are spring leg just like frogs <br>But man ah man are old school like Joe Bloggs <br>Gotta bill a pension now so when I'm older <br>I can live when I can't get jobs <br>When I make a song, I ain't looking for a nod <br>Cause man ah man are old school like Joe Bloggs <br><br>Yo, I come through with the peng <br>Cuh man are shit, draw only the peng <br>When I was a kid, I went so many house raves <br>Somebody always came through with the leng <br>Could've been a rebore that fired couple duds <br>Still, everybody in the place gonna run <br>Still, everybody in the place gonna dust <br>They don't wanna fight, no, they don't wanna fuss <br>I had a wild upbringing, I was never stable <br>But I had manners at the dinner table <br>Stand out when I've gotta stand up tall <br>I've got a chair at the winners' table, like <br>Say my name when giving out awards <br>My life's crazy, I never get bored <br>Can't lie, blud, man ah man's toured <br>On top of that, yeah, man ah man's warred <br><br>Call shots, go against odds <br>Can't go fishing if you ain't got rods <br>'Nuff of dem are spring leg just like frogs <br>But man ah man are old school like Joe Bloggs <br>Gotta bill a pension now so when I'm older <br>I can live when I can't get jobs <br>When I make a song, I ain't looking for a nod <br>Cause man ah man are old school like Joe Bloggs <br><br>Call shots, go against odds <br>Can't go fishing if you ain't got rods <br>'Nuff of dem are spring leg just like frogs <br>But man ah man are old school like Joe Bloggs <br>Gotta bill a pension now so when I'm older <br>I can live when I can't get jobs <br>When I make a song, I ain't looking for a nod <br>Cause man ah man are old school like Joe Bloggs]]></content><category term="Wiley" label="Wiley"/><category term="Joe Bloggs (Feat. Newham Generals &amp; President T) " label="Joe Bloggs (Feat. Newham Generals &amp; President T) "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slaughter_Beach/Glaze/</id><title>Slaughter Beach - Glaze - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:43:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:43:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slaughter_Beach/Glaze/" title="Slaughter Beach - Glaze - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm so sorry that I let you down <br>Made it crumble overnight <br>So I try to keep <br>Out of your way now <br>And out of the sun <br>So get on your way now <br>This is the longest run <br>This is the longest run <br><br>Out of your way now <br>And out of the sun <br>So get on your way now <br>This is the longest run <br>This is the longest run]]></content><category term="Slaughter Beach" label="Slaughter Beach"/><category term="Glaze" label="Glaze"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Back_With_A_Banger/</id><title>Wiley - Back With A Banger - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:43:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:43:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Back_With_A_Banger/" title="Wiley - Back With A Banger - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fire in my belly cause I'm back in the manor <br>I've spent my whole life there stacked in the manor <br>Yo, I've done a lot of tracks in the manor <br>E3, you can get the loud pack in the manor <br>I know gyal who are good and live normal <br>But I know gyal who are bad like Rihanna <br>Anybody wanna know what I'm doing right now <br>Go tell 'em that I'm back with a banger Preditah <br><br>Yo, yo, liquid flow <br>I fire like a MAC, it's not a biscuit flow <br>E3 but I kill 'em with the Chrisp Street flow <br>DJs, spin the riddim better mix me, though <br>Too clued up, how you gonna trick me, bro <br>Buy a lump, I don't wanna tick three Os <br>Got the KFC, man have got the Dixy flow <br>They never break, you've never gotta fix these flows <br>I'm a K I N G, the liquid flows <br>With the cracks in the concrete, I'm in them, bro <br>Yellow like a Simpson though, Bart Simpson flow <br>You know I've got that instant flow <br>Hello, hello, hi, liquid pro <br>See me in the club, killing off a liquid show <br>First measure, I tell my don pick these shows <br>Cause I wanna be in the club drinking, bro <br><br>Fire in my belly cause I'm back in the manor <br>I've spent my whole life there stacked in the manor <br>Yo, I've done a lot of tracks in the manor <br>E3, you can get the loud pack in the manor <br>I know gyal who are good and live normal <br>But I know gyal who are bad like Rihanna <br>Anybody wanna know what I'm doing right now <br>Go tell 'em that I'm back with a banger <br><br>Thinking cap on <br>My flow's what it's like when you turn the tap on <br>You ever see me often you're gonna see me back on <br>See me with white, might see me with black on <br>Ayy, man got the army Nike track on <br>I ain't gonna bother nobody, I just crack on <br>Stack up, stack up, stack up, stack on <br>It's my riddim the DJ wanna slap on <br>Step up, step in, watch everybody step out <br>I'm back on the Dizzee like when a man first set out <br>If you ain't going for the jugular then brudda, get out <br>Land and I do what I gotta do, then I jet out <br>Jet out, man get out, the jets ain't private <br>I'll be in the aisle seats sitting in silence <br>Spit bars and the crowd go wild <br>When I look into the dance where it looks like violence <br><br>Fire in my belly cause I'm back in the manor <br>I've spent my whole life there stacked in the manor <br>Yo, I've done a lot of tracks in the manor <br>E3, you can get the loud pack in the manor <br>I know gyal who are good and live normal <br>But I know gyal who are bad like Rihanna <br>Anybody wanna know what I'm doing right now <br>Go tell 'em that I'm back with a banger <br><br>Backstage chilling in the dance with my dargs dem <br>None of them are fake, you can ask them <br>People who are looking a hype, I walk past them <br>Dons could be richer or poor, I won't class them <br>Dons could be ready for war, my bars spark them <br>My sound travels the seas, that's why I part them <br>I can be foul, poisonous dart them <br>But the gyal dem wanna hype if I uh <br>It's been a good year, couple wars, couple sick tunes <br>But now I've got a deal with a couple quick few <br>I will clash MCs, I will clash crews <br>You will know if you wanna try the choice you choose <br>I will roll up on my ones and bring twos <br>In the war, I don't get confused <br>You just get defused, nobody can't snooze <br>I ain't really got any points I wanna prove <br>But I gotta make a move <br><br>Fire in my belly cause I'm back in the manor <br>I've spent my whole life there stacked in the manor <br>Yo, I've done a lot of tracks in the manor <br>E3, you can get the loud pack in the manor <br>I know gyal who are good and live normal <br>But I know gyal who are bad like Rihanna <br>Anybody wanna know what I'm doing right now <br>Go tell 'em that I'm back with a banger <br><br>Fire in my belly cause I'm back in the manor <br>I've spent my whole life there stacked in the manor <br>Yo, I've done a lot of tracks in the manor <br>E3, you can get the loud pack in the manor <br>I know gyal who are good and live normal <br>But I know gyal who are bad like Rihanna <br>Anybody wanna know what I'm doing right now <br>Go tell 'em that I'm back with a banger <br><br>Boy Better Know <br>I've got the badboy flow <br>Yo <br>Preditah]]></content><category term="Wiley" label="Wiley"/><category term="Back With A Banger" label="Back With A Banger"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Name_Brand_Feat_JME_Frisco__J2K/</id><title>Wiley - Name Brand (Feat. JME, Frisco &amp; J2K) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:43:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:43:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Name_Brand_Feat_JME_Frisco__J2K/" title="Wiley - Name Brand (Feat. JME, Frisco &amp; J2K) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I came to jam and hold a vibes <br>Hold a vibes <br>You know I go to the studio all the time <br>All the time <br>Sounding ever so grimy, they're causing fights <br>Causing fights <br>Dance dun, now they're switching on all the lights <br>I'm a name brand, I can't afford to hype <br><br>I'm a name brand, yeah that's right, G <br>I'm a name brand, just like Nike <br>I'm a name brand, man wanna fight me <br>Cause I'm a name brand, but you can't take man <br>I'm a name brand, yeah that's right, G <br>I'm a name brand, just like Nike <br>I'm a name brand, man wanna fight me <br>Cause I'm a name brand, but you can't take man <br><br>Wiley, where are you going <br>I'm going to keep an old brand going <br>Back then, everyting was steady <br>Lately, it's getting a bit edgy <br>Got a couple tings that I wanna try <br>Wanna expand so I gotta try <br>Have to make sure that my vibes hold sick <br>When I sell a ticket, it's what they're gonna buy <br>Branching out, new business <br>Cop the Landlord album, Giggs' <br>Fire, all round fire <br>Hold tight Giggs, the real vibe supplier <br>London's changed a bit, but I can still hit the booth <br>Start spraying and give the crowd fire <br>We don't deflate, we stay pumped up <br>And dem man are flat tyre <br><br>I came to jam and hold a vibes <br>Hold a vibes <br>You know I go to the studio all the time <br>All the time <br>Sounding ever so grimy, they're causing fights <br>Causing fights <br>Dance dun, now they're switching on all the lights <br>I'm a name brand, I can't afford to hype <br><br>I'm a name brand, yeah that's right, G <br>I'm a name brand, just like Nike <br>I'm a name brand, man wanna fight me <br>Cause I'm a name brand, but you can't take man <br>I'm a name brand, yeah that's right, G <br>I'm a name brand, just like Nike <br>I'm a name brand, man wanna fight me <br>Cause I'm a name brand, but you can't take man <br><br>Next to my name, there's no losses <br>X 'em out with all crosses <br>That girl couldn't get used to me <br>Because she ain't used to no bosses <br>Ahah, all I got now is sausage <br>I do not count the losses <br>I just grab on the big back ting <br>And turn onto new topics, new ting <br>Come and ring ring the bell, lights on <br>Curtains open as well, enter <br>Don't get gassed off no rich sex <br>We're just gonna do this calmly as hell <br>Is that cool Well, that's swell <br>Do you feel me Well, that's braille <br>I'm like a high street store to the gyal dem <br>Who can't keep their hands off the name brand sales <br>Oh well, well, well <br><br>I came to jam and hold a vibes <br>Hold a vibes <br>You know I go to the studio all the time <br>All the time <br>Sounding ever so grimy, they're causing fights <br>Causing fights <br>Dance dun, now they're switching on all the lights <br>I'm a name brand, I can't afford to hype <br><br>I'm a name brand, yeah that's right, G <br>I'm a name brand, just like Nike <br>I'm a name brand, man wanna fight me <br>Cause I'm a name brand, but you can't take man <br>I'm a name brand, yeah that's right, G <br>I'm a name brand, just like Nike <br>I'm a name brand, man wanna fight me <br>Cause I'm a name brand, but you can't take man <br><br>That's the gameplan <br>The thug dem rate man <br>The gyal dem rate man <br>Frisco's a name brand <br>And where I come from, the police all hate man <br>Haters hate cuh they ain't man <br>Think you can call me out cause I'm a name brand <br>Man wanna draw me out, what a shame, man <br>Man claim that they're out here but I can't see 'em <br>Anyhow, I think the piss has been taken <br>I'mma start moving like Liam, it's mad <br>Spin an MC round like a kebab <br>New bars in my notepad, nigga, hold that <br>I'm a G by myself, you've gotta hold hands <br>I've never been disloyal <br>Like to buss joke, but I've never been a joke man <br><br>I came to jam and hold a vibes <br>Hold a vibes <br>You know I go to the studio all the time <br>All the time <br>Sounding ever so grimy, they're causing fights <br>Causing fights <br>Dance dun, now they're switching on all the lights <br>I'm a name brand, I can't afford to hype <br><br>I'm a name brand, yeah that's right, G <br>I'm a name brand, just like Nike <br>I'm a name brand, man wanna fight me <br>Cause I'm a name brand, but you can't take man <br>I'm a name brand, yeah that's right, G <br>I'm a name brand, just like Nike <br>I'm a name brand, man wanna fight me <br>Cause I'm a name brand, but you can't take man]]></content><category term="Wiley" label="Wiley"/><category term="Name Brand (Feat. JME, Frisco &amp; J2K)" label="Name Brand (Feat. JME, Frisco &amp; J2K)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Bring_Them_All___Holy_Grime_Feat_Devlin/</id><title>Wiley - Bring Them All / Holy Grime (Feat. Devlin) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:43:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:43:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wiley/Bring_Them_All___Holy_Grime_Feat_Devlin/" title="Wiley - Bring Them All / Holy Grime (Feat. Devlin) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ayy, listen <br><br>Drink 'nough beers before the game, what d'ya call that Georgie Best MC <br>Listen, I don't rest MC <br>You man sleep, that's why you're not the best MC <br>You man are part time, never had beef <br>Now you're on the mic like a bulletproof vest MC <br>I'm a double, precious Tek MC <br>Separate heads from necks <br>I was in the shadows, I came to the light with a path <br>Us spitters who wanna be first and never be last <br>I've been ahead of the game, I've been ahead of the craft <br>I wanna laugh <br>Come sailing along like a boss <br>With the flow I'm like rah, what the ras <br>I'm a striker, yo where the pass Get my triple A passes <br>I'm sitting with the stars <br>Listen up, I ain't normal, I'm sicker than my bars <br>Driven myself crazy, I've been in every condo <br>I like to fly by on my black Yamaha, that's winging <br>Some man do the crime and talk but that's singing <br>Not many man have been in the wars that I've been in <br>I can work here but it's not a place that I could live in <br>Getting new money though but I've already made a killing <br>I've already made a scene, I already live a dream <br>And the king's road's lonely, you can't go with him <br>When it's time for a test <br>Man ah man have gotta move swiftly 'cause you don't want a knife in your chest <br>In the hood every day, it's heroin, living like they're dead <br>Made it, now you're lying in your bed <br>It's like yo, has anybody seen my flow right here, cuz <br>Live in your ears like earplugs <br>Keep myself away like rare dubs <br>What makes you so scared I'm sure fear does <br>On the real though, I stand up and face it <br>The levels high in my scene, that's why I embrace it <br>Let me go on and enjoy what I created <br>Man will jump on the stage and go ape shit <br>For years I've been killing it, trust me <br>Swear down, I will never get rusty <br>My lyrics dem will rough up your lyrics like rugby <br>For the work I put in, the fans love me <br><br>This one ain't free but it's the liberty <br>Street divinity <br>Me and Will's tyranny <br>And this one's willing me to rise like Pyrenees peaks and I'm lyrically <br>In the sky and then I'm right through infinity <br>Forever after, Devs be the master <br>Hit 'em with the Carleone ting, Godfather of grime <br>Don't charter to ride through parts of <br>This precinct when it gets darker <br>Don't think you can stand the heat <br>You can't stand this peak <br>I'm like a million and one lightyears way past of an artist's reach <br>Mary, I'm hard to beat <br>Now think deep <br>About this collabo <br>Historical events unravel <br>Like I went Middlesex, I came to Harrow <br>My man said he feel paro <br>Bloody cuffs, heart on my sleeve <br>This shit feels like beef to me <br>When I spit and my arms start swiniging, I'm bringing <br>More raw shit than a Beckton works <br>Smell it and know why Kano writ it <br>Wrote it, fuck me, alright, don't quote it <br>Focus, look, now I'm back and it's hopeless <br>Comparing me with these seeds <br>Too rare a breed of MC and the flow shifts <br>More than once a minute <br>Getting off like Dahmer, I come and I kill it <br>A Dagenham'er strapped with a bunch of lyrics <br>That bang harder, where the fuck's the gimmicks <br>There ain't nada <br>I've got the heart and spirit they can't harbor <br>Silly men pass the limit and then scarper <br>When it comes on top with the urban legend, I get 'em like Carter <br><br>Spitters can't better these levels of terror <br>I leave my brain in my car but my head is together <br>I make a team of dons quit when I'm put under pressure <br>Rate Devlin, why He's a grime treasure <br>In grime, I've lined my catalogue up, prime seller <br>I'm never too far from the hype that I set up <br>I step up like a bredda who's livin' in nice weather <br>At work, puttin' words together with ice letters <br>I spray, make a big tree lean in the road <br>Trees drop on your house to leave them a cold <br>Trees drop on your car, the windows smash <br>Eski brought O2 Indigo back <br>But this whole time, fam, I've been holy in grime <br>Even a first time who don't know me in grime <br>But you love my stage vibe when I'm holding a mic <br>I'm a pro now, bro, I jump over the spike <br><br>Any hardcore fan of grime <br>Go mad when you hear this bang inside <br>I got the keys like pianists, black and white <br>I've been a beast in the scene all my adult life <br>Ever since Will said Hello, hi <br>I was sat in the shadows, high <br>Concocting the maddest vibe <br>With a way less narrow sight <br>Than a Homosapien eye <br>X Ray, make way for my death ray <br>Nikola Tesla reborn to a next stage <br>Technology stole our children <br>The world's in debt and our men are all templates <br>I'll bring ten crates of my best mates <br>Puttin' up my worst and best traits <br>Converse in a verse with dead saints <br>Holy grime, it's a blessed day]]></content><category term="Wiley" label="Wiley"/><category term="Bring Them All / Holy Grime (Feat. Devlin)" label="Bring Them All / Holy Grime (Feat. Devlin)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/라지스몰/Envy/</id><title>라지스몰 - Envy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:44:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:44:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9D%BC%EC%A7%80%EC%8A%A4%EB%AA%B0/Envy/" title="라지스몰 - Envy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내년 이맘때 즘에 <br>내 왼쪽 손목엔 Rollies <br>그냥 몇 개를 <br>찰지부터가 고민이 <br>되길 바래 내 지갑 <br>안에는 패기밖에 <br>없으니까 일시불로 uh <br>내 미래는 <br>지하 작업실로부터 <br>숨 쉬어 왔고 <br>새로운 새싹이 텄어 <br>습관처럼 말했던 <br>랩 머니는 벌써 <br>내 지갑을 향해서 <br>조금씩 다 기어들고 있어 <br>늘 새로운 걸 <br>추구하는 나의 입 <br>절대 쉴 수 없지 <br>just do it NIKE <br>Sippin my lyric <br>likes a codeine <br>모두 다 두 다 call me <br>재미가 우선시 <br>되는 나의 초침 <br>1분 1초가 아깝지 <br>고민 없는 <br>내 상태는 몰입 <br>믿고 있었지 늘 <br>내가 걸어온 터널 <br>아직은 보이지 않아도 <br>큰 어둠을 삼켜 <br>담대해진 것 <br>같이 뛰어 심장이 <br>점쳐도 될 거 같은 <br>내 성공은 지푸라기 <br>잡기보다 쉬울 거야 <br>Don’t pull out me <br>난 걸어 내길 <br>넌 내게 걸어 <br>Way back 계속 <br>늘 바래 왔지 여기에 <br>Somebody call me <br>back envy me <br>Don’t care <br>Way back 계속 <br>늘 바래 왔지 여기에 <br>Somebody call me <br>back envy me <br>Don’t care <br>다시 studio 목말라 <br>내가 장전하는 무기고 <br>상상력은 마르지 않지 <br>pour liquor <br>더 독하게 팬을 쥐어 <br>쥐어 짜내 타는 상상하며 <br>Range Rover <br>절대 game over라는 <br>단어는 생각조차 없지 <br>늘 내 앞으로만 노를 저어 <br>Do you wanna anything <br>아니 난 정확해 <br>Deja vu 매번 <br>내 가사장에 서서 <br>매일 제자리걸음을 해 <br>더 좋은 가사를 알아 <br>고민의 흔적 끝에 <br>절대 쉬지 않네 <br>I am rockin all day <br>ah 너 잘 봐봐 <br>ah 다짐을 해 <br>ah 밤하늘 아래다 <br>모두 이뤄지도록 <br>ah 네 카메라 <br>ah 찍고 다시 마이크에다 <br>16마디 한 번에 shot <br>Cot damn <br>Way back 계속 <br>늘 바래 왔지 여기에 <br>Somebody call me <br>back envy me <br>Don’t care <br>Way back 계속 <br>늘 바래 왔지 여기에 <br>Somebody call me <br>back envy me <br>Don’t care <br>Like this ah ha ah ha <br>Like that ah ha ah ha <br>Like this ah ha ah ha <br>Like that ah ha ah ha <br>하나씩 이뤄가고 있지 <br>몸 풀고 또 가볍게 chillin <br>작은 것들을 천천히 이룰 때 <br>내가 가진 것들을 믿을래 <br>너무 무거워 안 해도 돼 <br>자유로운 나의 머릿속에 <br>담겨있는 것을 계속 꺼내 <br>그대로 움직여 매일 baby <br>Like this ah ha ah ha <br>Like that ah ha ah ha <br>Like this ah ha ah ha <br>Like that ah ha ah ha <br>]]></content><category term="라지스몰" label="라지스몰"/><category term="Envy" label="Envy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김희석/그의_두손_합창_아이노스_합창단/</id><title>김희석 - 그의 두손 합창 (아이노스 합창단) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:45:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:45:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%9D%AC%EC%84%9D/%EA%B7%B8%EC%9D%98_%EB%91%90%EC%86%90_%ED%95%A9%EC%B0%BD_%EC%95%84%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8%EC%8A%A4_%ED%95%A9%EC%B0%BD%EB%8B%A8/" title="김희석 - 그의 두손 합창 (아이노스 합창단) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 영 갈 곳을 잃어 <br>깊은 어둠 헤매일 때에 <br>절망 끝에 저 멀리 보이는 빛 <br>나의 영혼을 감싸 안으며 <br>내 쳐진 어깨 위에 <br>두 손 얹고 내 눈물 보신 주 <br>너의 고통 나 잠잠케 하러 왔도다 <br>거친 환란파도 물리치리라 <br>너는 나의 귀한 종이라 <br>내가 널 택하고 버리지 않으니 <br>두려 말라 너의 하나님이라 <br>내가 너와 함께 하리라 <br>내 쳐진 어깨 위에 <br>두 손 얹고 내 눈물 보신 주 <br>너의 고통 나 잠잠케 하러 왔도다 <br>거친 환란파도 물리치리라 <br>내가 널 굳세게 하리라 <br>나의 두 손으로 너를 붙들리라 <br>두려 말라 너의 하나님이라 <br>내가 너와 함께 하리라 <br>두려 말라 너의 하나님이라 <br>내가 너와 함께 하리라 <br>]]></content><category term="김희석" label="김희석"/><category term="그의 두손 합창 (아이노스 합창단)" label="그의 두손 합창 (아이노스 합창단)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김희석/그의_두손_3중창_Sasso_Bianco/</id><title>김희석 - 그의 두손 (3중창) (Sasso Bianco) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:45:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:45:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%9D%AC%EC%84%9D/%EA%B7%B8%EC%9D%98_%EB%91%90%EC%86%90_3%EC%A4%91%EC%B0%BD_Sasso_Bianco/" title="김희석 - 그의 두손 (3중창) (Sasso Bianco) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 영 갈 곳을 잃어 <br>깊은 어둠 헤매일 때에 <br>절망 끝에 저 멀리 보이는 빛 <br>나의 영혼을 감싸 안으며 <br>내 쳐진 어깨 위에 <br>두 손 얹고 내 눈물 보신 주 <br>너의 고통 나 잠잠케 하러 왔도다 <br>거친 환란파도 물리치리라 <br>너는 나의 귀한 종이라 <br>내가 널 택하고 버리지 않으니 <br>두려 말라 너의 하나님이라 <br>내가 너와 함께 하리라 <br>내 영 갈 곳을 잃어 <br>깊은 어둠 헤매일 때에 <br>절망 끝에 저 멀리 보이는 빛 <br>나의 영혼을 감싸 안으며 <br>내 쳐진 어깨 위에 <br>두 손 얹고 내 눈물 보신 주 <br>너의 고통 나 잠잠케 하러 왔도다 <br>거친 환란파도 물리치리라 <br>내가 널 굳세게 하리라 <br>나의 두 손으로 너를 붙들리라 <br>두려 말라 너의 하나님이라 <br>내가 너와 함께 하리라 <br>내가 널 굳세게 하리라 <br>나의 두 손으로 너를 붙들리라 <br>두려 말라 너의 하나님이라 <br>내가 너와 함께 하리라 <br>내가 너와 함께 하리라 <br>]]></content><category term="김희석" label="김희석"/><category term="그의 두손 (3중창) (Sasso Bianco)" label="그의 두손 (3중창) (Sasso Bianco)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김희석/그의_두손_Classic_Ver/</id><title>김희석 - 그의 두손 (Classic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:45:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:45:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%9D%AC%EC%84%9D/%EA%B7%B8%EC%9D%98_%EB%91%90%EC%86%90_Classic_Ver/" title="김희석 - 그의 두손 (Classic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 영 갈 곳을 잃어 <br>깊은 어둠 헤매일 때에 <br>절망 끝에 저 멀리 보이는 빛 <br>나의 영혼을 감싸 안으며 <br>내 쳐진 어깨 위에 <br>두 손 얹고 내 눈물 보신 주 <br>너의 고통 <br>나 잠잠케 하러 왔도다 <br>거친 환란파도 물리치리라 <br>너는 나의 귀한 종이라 <br>내가 널 택하고 버리지 않으니 <br>두려 말라 너의 하나님이라 <br>내가 너와 함께 하리라 <br>내가 널 굳세게 하리라 <br>나의 두 손으로 너를 붙들리라 <br>두려 말라 너의 하나님이라 <br>내가 너와 함께 하리라 <br>오 두려 말라 너의 하나님이라 <br>내가 너와 함께 하리라 <br>내가 너와 함께 하리라 <br>]]></content><category term="김희석" label="김희석"/><category term="그의 두손 (Classic Ver.)" label="그의 두손 (Classic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김희석/그의_두손/</id><title>김희석 - 그의 두손 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:45:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:45:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%9D%AC%EC%84%9D/%EA%B7%B8%EC%9D%98_%EB%91%90%EC%86%90/" title="김희석 - 그의 두손 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 영 갈 곳을 잃어 <br>깊은 어둠 헤매일 때에 <br>절망 끝에 저 멀리 보이는 빛 <br>나의 영혼을 감싸 안으며 <br>내 쳐진 어깨 위에 <br>두 손 얹고 내 눈물 보신 주 <br>너의 고통 <br>나 잠잠케 하러 왔도다 <br>거친 환란파도 물리치리라 <br>너는 나의 귀한 종이라 <br>내가 널 택하고 버리지 않으니 <br>두려 말라 너의 하나님이라 <br>내가 너와 함께 하리라 <br>내 영 갈 곳을 잃어 <br>깊은 어둠 헤매일 때에 <br>절망 끝에 저 멀리 보이는 빛 <br>나의 영혼을 감싸 안으며 <br>내 쳐진 어깨 위에 <br>두 손 얹고 내 눈물 보신 주 <br>너의 고통 <br>나 잠잠케 하러 왔도다 <br>거친 환란파도 물리치리라 <br>내가 널 굳세게 하리라 <br>나의 두 손으로 너를 붙들리라 <br>두려 말라 너의 하나님이라 <br>내가 너와 함께 하리라 <br>내가 널 굳세게 하리라 <br>나의 두 손으로 너를 붙들리라 <br>두려 말라 너의 하나님이라 <br>내가 너와 함께 하리라 <br>내가 너와 함께 하리라 <br>]]></content><category term="김희석" label="김희석"/><category term="그의 두손" label="그의 두손"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오레오스틱_Oreostic/Next_Lifetime/</id><title>오레오스틱 (Oreostic) - Next Lifetime - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:46:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:46:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A4%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B1_Oreostic/Next_Lifetime/" title="오레오스틱 (Oreostic) - Next Lifetime - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No hesitation <br>No limitation <br>In the same situation <br>No more agitation <br>Ride on the wave <br>dont behave like a slave of <br>no money tree <br>to feel the real free now <br>No hesitation <br>No limitation <br>In the same situation <br>No more agitation <br>Ride on the wave <br>dont behave like a slave of <br>no money tree <br>to feel the real free now <br>no money tree <br>to feel the real free now <br>no money tree <br>to feel the real free now <br>no money tree <br>to feel the real free <br>if there's Next lifetime <br>I'm gonna meet you again <br>in the same place <br>in the same time <br>with the same aims <br>share our thoughts <br>share our dream <br>if there's next lifetime <br>I'm wanna meet you again <br>in the same place <br>in the same time <br>with the same aims <br>share our thoughts <br>share our dream <br>No hesitation <br>No limitation <br>In the same situation <br>No more agitation <br>Ride on the wave <br>dont behave like a slave of <br>no money tree <br>to feel the real free now <br>No hesitation <br>No limitation <br>In the same situation <br>No more agitation <br>Ride on the wave <br>dont behave like a slave of <br>no money tree <br>to feel the real free now <br>No hesitation <br>No limitation <br>In the same situation <br>No more agitation <br>Ride on the wave <br>dont behave like a slave of <br>no money tree <br>to feel the real free now <br>No hesitation <br>No limitation <br>In the same situation <br>No more agitation <br>Ride on the wave <br>dont behave like a slave of <br>no money tree <br>to feel the real free now <br>No hesitation <br>No limitation <br>In the same situation <br>No more agitation <br>Ride on the wave <br>dont behave like a slave of <br>no money tree <br>to feel the real free now <br>No hesitation <br>No limitation <br>In the same situation <br>No more agitation <br>Ride on the wave <br>dont behave like a slave of <br>no money tree <br>to feel the real free now <br>no money tree <br>to feel the real free now <br>no money tree <br>to feel the real free <br>no money tree <br>to feel the real free now <br>no money tree <br>to feel the real free <br>]]></content><category term="오레오스틱 (Oreostic)" label="오레오스틱 (Oreostic)"/><category term="Next Lifetime" label="Next Lifetime"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오레오스틱_Oreostic/Say_You_Love_Me/</id><title>오레오스틱 (Oreostic) - Say You Love Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:46:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:46:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A4%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B1_Oreostic/Say_You_Love_Me/" title="오레오스틱 (Oreostic) - Say You Love Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[don’t you know <br>that something’s changed <br>it feels kinda strange <br>we’re not like us used to be <br>I just wanna make it right <br>but things are getting worse <br>it would be ain’t our way <br>i just thought it was <br>All of a sudden thing <br>As anyone does <br>But I doubt about <br>it could be any better <br>there is no exit <br>ah <br>say you love me <br>ah <br>if you believe it could be nice <br>ah <br>say you love me <br>Please just love me <br>Im just trying to figure out <br>The reason why we are through <br>please just say you love me <br>i just thought it was <br>All of a sudden thing <br>As anyone does <br>But I doubt about <br>it could be any better <br>there is no exit <br>ah <br>say you love me <br>ah <br>if you believe it could be nice <br>ah <br>say you love me <br>Please just love me <br>Please love me <br>if you believe it could be nice <br>Just say you love me <br>Please just love me <br>Please just love me <br>]]></content><category term="오레오스틱 (Oreostic)" label="오레오스틱 (Oreostic)"/><category term="Say You Love Me" label="Say You Love Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오레오스틱_Oreostic/Harbour_City/</id><title>오레오스틱 (Oreostic) - Harbour City - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:46:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:46:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A4%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B1_Oreostic/Harbour_City/" title="오레오스틱 (Oreostic) - Harbour City - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We walked under the bridge <br>On a long summer day <br>Bewitching starlit night <br>The beautiful city lights <br>Beyond the sea <br>The night in harbor city <br>Oh oh <br>It’s so beautiful beautiful night <br>I’m in love I’m in love <br>I’m in love with you <br>It’s so beautiful beautiful night <br>I’m in love I’m in love <br>I’m in love with you <br>Oh Oh Oh <br>I love you oh baby sweet pea <br>I need you honey sugar <br>I love you oh baby sweet pea <br>I need you honey sugar <br>The view of the city <br>From the mountain peak <br>It was a beginning of love <br>The memories of harbour city <br>You and me and the night <br>The sweetest dream <br>Oh oh <br>It’s so beautiful beautiful night <br>I’m in love I’m in love <br>I’m in love with you <br>It’s so beautiful beautiful night <br>I’m in love I’m in love <br>I’m in love with you <br>Oh Oh Oh <br>I love you oh baby sweet pea <br>I need you honey sugar <br>I love you oh baby sweet pea <br>I need you honey sugar <br>I love you oh baby sweet pea <br>I need you honey sugar <br>I love you oh baby sweet pea <br>I need you honey sugar <br>]]></content><category term="오레오스틱 (Oreostic)" label="오레오스틱 (Oreostic)"/><category term="Harbour City" label="Harbour City"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더_스페이드/Here_We_Stand/</id><title>더 스페이드 - Here We Stand! - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:46:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:46:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8E%98%EC%9D%B4%EB%93%9C/Here_We_Stand/" title="더 스페이드 - Here We Stand! - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모든게 끝나버렸고 <br>여긴 적막 뿐이야 <br>사라진 이들은 남긴 것 <br>하나 없이 떠나갔지 <br>되돌릴 수 없다는 건 <br>우리 모두 잘 알아 <br>무엇을 해야할지 <br>모르겠는 것도 <br>다 이해해 <br>Listen to my words <br>지금껏 있던 일들은 <br>전부 잊어 <br>Listen to my heart <br>만약 괴로울 지라도 <br>버텨야해 <br>지나가 버린 시간 속을 <br>헤매는 것도 <br>이 정도면 충분해 <br>무의미한 자책은 <br>그만 두어도 괜찮아 <br>이제 앞으로 나아가야 해 <br>더 이상 웅크려 있지도 마 <br>네가 다시 일어설 때 까지 <br>Here We Stand <br>단지 한 순간 빛나고 나서 <br>허무히 불타 버릴거란 말 <br>정말 질리도록 <br>많이 들었는걸 <br>지쳐 쓰러져 버릴지라도 <br>또다시 멈춰 있을 수 없어 <br>미래를 위한 길을 <br>걷는 것뿐이야 <br>지나가 버린 시간 속을 <br>헤매는 것도 <br>이 정도면 충분해 <br>무의미한 자책은 <br>그만 두어도 괜찮아 <br>이제 앞으로 나아가야 해 <br>더 이상 웅크려 있지도 마 <br>네가 다시 일어설 때 까지 <br>Here We Stand <br>]]></content><category term="더 스페이드" label="더 스페이드"/><category term="Here We Stand!" label="Here We Stand!"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제이세라/10분마다/</id><title>제이세라 - 10분마다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:48:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:48:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B8%EB%9D%BC/10%EB%B6%84%EB%A7%88%EB%8B%A4/" title="제이세라 - 10분마다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 만나기 전 어젯밤 <br>어린 아이가 된 것 같아 <br>잠을 못자 밤새 뒤척거려 <br>소풍가기 전날처럼 <br>널 만나기 전 어젯밤 <br>마치 공주가 된 것같아 <br>하루종일 거울앞에 서성거려 <br>한숨을 못자 <br>언제나 항상 그대를 그댈 <br>사랑하고 있죠 <br>10분마다 옷깃을 몇번 여미고 <br>10분마다 떨리는 가슴 붙잡아 <br>설레는 걸음 한걸음 마다 <br>네 모습을 떠올려 <br>10분마다 화장을 몇번 고치고 <br>10분마다 떨리는 가슴 어떡해 <br>그댈 만나러가는 한걸음 마다 <br>설레는 내 맘 아나요 <br>널 만난 후 내 모습이 <br>좋아졌다고 말들을 해 <br>나는 그저 너를 사랑하고 <br>있는 것 뿐인데 말야 <br>널 만난 후 내 모습이 <br>예뻐졌다고 말들을 해 <br>나는 그저 나 하나만 바라보는 <br>널 가진건데 <br>언제나 항상 그대를 그댈 <br>사랑하고 있죠 <br>10분마다 옷깃을 몇번 여미고 <br>10분마다 떨리는 가슴 붙잡아 <br>설레는 걸음 한걸음 마다 <br>네 모습을 떠올려 <br>10분마다 화장을 몇번 고치고 <br>10분마다 떨리는 가슴 어떡해 <br>그댈 만나러가는 한걸음 마다 <br>설레는 <br>그대를 만나 <br>그대를 만나 <br>웃으며 하루를 시작해 <br>우리 언제나 변치않기를 <br>처음처럼 사랑해요 <br>봄이오면 손잡고 같이 걸어요 <br>여름에는 시원한 바다도 가요 <br>설레는 걸음 한걸음 마다 <br>추억을 만들어요 <br>가을에는 가끔씩 여행도가요 <br>겨울에는 가끔씩 술한잔해요 <br>서로 마주보면서 얘기 나누며 <br>말해요 사랑한다고 <br>]]></content><category term="제이세라" label="제이세라"/><category term="10분마다" label="10분마다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동요사랑/순대국송/</id><title>동요사랑 - 순대국송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:49:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:49:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/%EC%88%9C%EB%8C%80%EA%B5%AD%EC%86%A1/" title="동요사랑 - 순대국송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[순대국 정말로 맛있어 <br>얼큰한 맛이 최고야 <br><br>고소한 순대를 꺼내서 <br>소금에 찍어 먹어요 <br><br>양념장 국물에 풀어서 <br>땀 한 번 흘리며 먹어요 <br><br>순대국 정말로 맛있어 <br>얼큰한 맛이 최고야 <br><br>고소한 순대를 꺼내서 <br>소금에 찍어 먹어요 <br><br>양념장 국물에 풀어서 <br>땀 한 번 흘리며 먹어요순대국 정말로 맛있어 <br>얼큰한 맛이 최고야 <br><br>고소한 순대를 꺼내서 <br>소금에 찍어 먹어요 <br><br>양념장 국물에 풀어서 <br>땀 한 번 흘리며 먹어요 <br><br>순대국 정말로 맛있어 <br>얼큰한 맛이 최고야 <br><br>고소한 순대를 꺼내서 <br>소금에 찍어 먹어요 <br><br>양념장 국물에 풀어서 <br>땀 한 번 흘리며 먹어요]]></content><category term="동요사랑" label="동요사랑"/><category term="순대국송" label="순대국송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Migos/Call_Casting/</id><title>Migos - Call Casting - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:50:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:50:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Migos/Call_Casting/" title="Migos - Call Casting - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Buddah blessed this beat <br>Yeah trap shit <br>No no no no no no <br>Up early in the morning <br>trapping trap trap <br>You can get 'em <br>how you asking ask <br>How many chickens you can <br>get 'em whichever way <br>Nigga trap turned Zaxby's Zax <br>I beat the pot with a passion <br>beat it up <br>A hundred acres <br>on the mansion <br>mansion <br>I dab in the latest fashion <br>eat it up <br>Bitches need to <br>call casting yeah <br>Ack Ack <br>Put the backends in the back <br>back <br>Draco on me <br>it's attached 'ttached <br>Name a nigga with the pack <br>pack <br>Name a nigga with the sack <br>sack <br>I love my Glock <br>I got the MAC MAC <br>She eat the molly <br>like a snack eat it up <br>This gold on my neck <br>a plaque plaque <br>Bando Shane's Rib <br>Shack eat it up <br>Rob the plug if you tax tax <br>Sip the lean and <br>relax drink it up <br>Park the Lamb <br>in the back skrt skrt <br>Big dog you a cat cat <br>Rich in the matte <br>black skrt skrt <br>Twenty hoes to be <br>exact yeah <br>I need ten that's a dime <br>Want a nickel that's a five <br>One to fly one to slide <br>One to glide ain't got time <br>Put a thirty on my nine <br>For a nigga out of line <br>Mama cryin' niggas dyin' <br>Wonder why I done <br>grip the fire yeah <br>Up early in the morning <br>trapping trap trap <br>You can get 'em <br>how you asking ask <br>How many chickens you can <br>get 'em whichever way <br>Nigga trap turned Zaxby's Zax <br>I beat the pot with a passion <br>beat it up <br>A hundred acres <br>on the mansion <br>mansion <br>I dab in the latest fashion <br>eat it up <br>Bitches need to <br>call casting yeah <br>Brrrt skrt skrt skrt <br>skrt burrr pot <br>Niggas tried to send a thot <br>That's the only way to plot <br>Klay Thomp corner shot brrr <br>Eight ball corner pocket ay <br>White boys in the gang white <br>Call 'em Andy Milonakis yeah <br>He won't hesitate to <br>shoot 'em shoot <br>Private jet to Bermuda woo <br>I knew I been had sauce who <br>Cause I was fuckin' <br>on my tutor who <br>Truck backin' up the dooley <br>A hundred pounds <br>out the cooler <br>Came from a Cup O' Noodles <br>I fucked the game <br>karma sutra <br>I got M's on my mind <br>I got boulders in my time <br>Put a model bitch on coca <br>Told her read between <br>the lines coco <br>J's out there snitchin' yeah <br>Heard it through the vine J's <br>Packin' up the kitchen <br>Think I ran out of time yeah <br>Up early in the morning <br>trapping trap trap <br>You can get 'em <br>how you asking ask <br>How many chickens you can <br>get 'em whichever way <br>Nigga trap turned Zaxby's Zax <br>I beat the pot with a passion <br>beat it up <br>A hundred acres <br>on the mansion <br>mansion <br>I dab in the latest fashion <br>eat it up <br>Bitches need to <br>call casting yeah <br>Woo woo woo <br>woo woo packs <br>I paid the ticket <br>get you whacked brrr <br>I chop the brick <br>with the axe hey <br>The cookie smellin' <br>like a casket cookie <br>I'm sellin' crack <br>in my Raf's crack <br>Put the addy <br>in the nav addy <br>He steady poppin' <br>know it's cap cap <br>I hit the jungle <br>then adapt rarr <br>30 thousand <br>on the couch 30 bars <br>All my bitches from <br>an app app <br>Instagram and the Snap <br>Snap <br>I bet a hundred <br>on the craps crap <br>I'm good on shawty <br>do without ooh <br>She fucking niggas <br>for the check check <br>I'ma only get the mouth <br>Hop out a Lambo <br>crossover on a bitch skrt <br>I poured a four Actavis Act <br>Walk in Goyard <br>got a bag for my bitch bag <br>Won't give a kiss 'cause I know <br>you suck dick mwah <br>Spent you hundred <br>Philippe on your wrist Patek <br>Twenty five pointers <br>one fist points <br>Twenty five bitches <br>on list twenty five <br>Kill ten rubber band grip brrr <br>Up early in the morning <br>trapping trap trap <br>You can get 'em <br>how you asking ask <br>How many chickens you can <br>get 'em whichever way <br>Nigga trap turned Zaxby's Zax <br>I beat the pot with a passion <br>beat it up <br>A hundred acres <br>on the mansion <br>mansion <br>I dab in the latest fashion <br>eat it up <br>Bitches need to <br>call casting <br>yeah yeah yeah <br>]]></content><category term="Migos" label="Migos"/><category term="Call Casting" label="Call Casting"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ONDO_온도/29/</id><title>ONDO (온도) - 29 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:50:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:50:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ONDO_%EC%98%A8%EB%8F%84/29/" title="ONDO (온도) - 29 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그렇게 지나간 하루 <br>차가운 새벽 공기에 <br>나의 한 숨을 담아 <br>친구들의 소식을 <br>하나 둘씩 보다가 <br>순간 초라해진 내가 보여 <br>세상에서 내게 바라는 <br>시선이 곱진 않아 <br>돈 명예 인기 결혼까지 <br>성공의 기준이 <br>잡혀버린 세상에서 <br>발버둥치네 <br>20대의 끝자락에서 <br>내가 가는 이 길이 <br>맞는지도 모른 채로 <br>그렇게 노래를 하면서 <br>울다 웃으며 하룰 보내 <br>친구들의 부러움도 사고 <br>꿈을 가진 게 <br>넌 멋있다고 하지만 <br>꿈 가진 것 하나에 <br>내 모든 걸 거는 게 <br>스물아홉에 <br>느낀 현실 앞에서 <br>잘 하고 있는 걸까 <br>이 길이 맞는 걸까 <br>너무 늦진 않았을까 <br>그렇게 <br>다시 생각해봐도 <br>또 생각해봐도 <br>]]></content><category term="ONDO (온도)" label="ONDO (온도)"/><category term="29" label="29"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김문선/파트너는_누굴까/</id><title>김문선 - 파트너는 누굴까 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:50:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:50:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%AC%B8%EC%84%A0/%ED%8C%8C%ED%8A%B8%EB%84%88%EB%8A%94_%EB%88%84%EA%B5%B4%EA%B9%8C/" title="김문선 - 파트너는 누굴까 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하모니카 잘 불어서 정말 멋있어 <br>머리에 뿔이 달린 모티스 디지몬 <br>우리 둘이 누굴까 환상의 파트너 <br>매튜랑 파피몬 Hey <br>수수께끼 좋아하는 컴퓨터소년 <br>번쩍번쩍 꼬마번개 <br>곤충형 디지몬 우리 둘이 누굴까 환상파트너 <br>한솔이랑 텐타몬 Hey <br>공부는 서툴러도 운동은 <br>내가 최고 나는 나는 누굴까 <br>일이 일이 신태일 <br>꼬마불꽃 뿜어대는 <br>무슨무슨 디지몬 아구아구디지몬 <br>순진하고 착하지만 못말리는 공주병 <br>머리에 꽃이있어 <br>더 귀여운 디지몬 우리 둘이 누굴까 환상의 파트너 <br>미나랑 팔몬 Hay <br>누가봐도 엘리트 고지식한 우등생 <br>바다에서 내가 일등 헤엄치는 디지몬 <br>우리 둘이 누굴까 환상의 파트너 <br>정석이랑 쉬라몬 Hey <br>축구도 아주 잘해 발레라고 깜찍해 나는 나는 누굴까 <br>소라 소라 한소라 빙빙 돌아 회오리 <br>날개달린 디지몬 <br>나는 나는 누굴까 피요 피요 피요몬 <br>그리고 또 누가 있나 리키랑 파닥몬 <br>파닥 파닥 날고싶어 <br>특기는 공기팡 여덟번째 선택됐다 <br>신나리라고해 <br>니 파트너 가트몬 Hey Hey]]></content><category term="김문선" label="김문선"/><category term="파트너는 누굴까" label="파트너는 누굴까"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정재윤_Tula/파워_업/</id><title>정재윤 (Tula) - 파워 업 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:50:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:50:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%9E%AC%EC%9C%A4_Tula/%ED%8C%8C%EC%9B%8C_%EC%97%85/" title="정재윤 (Tula) - 파워 업 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[무엇인가 나를 향해 달려오고있어~ <br>약해지지마~ 우린 해낼수 있어 <br>어디선가 누구인가 나를 부르고 있어 <br>걱정하지마 이젠 괜찮아 <br>어제에 내 모습 모두 잊어줘 <br>오늘은 새롭게 다시 태어나 <br>나도 모르는 놀라운 힘들이 <br>또 다른 나를 지금 깨우고 있어 <br>power up 조금만 더 힘을 내야해]]></content><category term="정재윤 (Tula)" label="정재윤 (Tula)"/><category term="파워 업" label="파워 업"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/방대식/날_지켜줘/</id><title>방대식 - 날 지켜줘 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:50:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:50:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%A9%EB%8C%80%EC%8B%9D/%EB%82%A0_%EC%A7%80%EC%BC%9C%EC%A4%98/" title="방대식 - 날 지켜줘 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나나나 나나나 나나나나나나나 <br><br>아무것도 모르고 깊이 잠들어 있는 <br>날 깨우는 너의 목소리 <br>짙은 어둠을 밝혀줄 한줄기 빛 날 비쳐줘 <br><br>내 맘속에 자라는 꿈이라는 이름의 알 수 없는 나의 미래를 <br>이젠 깨워줘 어른이 되가는 날 지켜봐줘 <br><br>내게 더 용기를 준다면 다시 시작할 수가 있어 <br>당당하게 새로 태어날 내가 있어 <br><br>잊지마 너와 나 이젠 할 수 있어 기회는 지금 뿐이야 <br>언제나 기억해 기다리고 있어 끝까지 날 지켜봐줘 <br>give me a way <br><br>잊지마 너와 나 이젠 할 수 있어 기회는 지금 뿐이야 <br>언제나 기억해 기다리고 있어 끝까지 날 지켜봐줘 <br>give me a way]]></content><category term="방대식" label="방대식"/><category term="날 지켜줘" label="날 지켜줘"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정미영/미라클_Miracle_프론티어_엔딩/</id><title>정미영 - 미라클 (Miracle) (프론티어 엔딩) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:50:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:50:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EB%AF%B8%EC%98%81/%EB%AF%B8%EB%9D%BC%ED%81%B4_Miracle_%ED%94%84%EB%A1%A0%ED%8B%B0%EC%96%B4_%EC%97%94%EB%94%A9/" title="정미영 - 미라클 (Miracle) (프론티어 엔딩) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[풀리지 않는 그 수수께끼 해답을 찾고 있어 <br>나도 모르는 그 얘기들 그 끝을 알고 싶어 <br>거짓처럼 되어 가는 진실 비밀을 찾고 있어 <br>혼자서도 할 수 있을까 조금 외로운 마음 <br>하지만 더 이상 난 혼자가 아닌 걸 <br>같은 길 위에서 같은 꿈을 꾸는 <br>널 만난 거야 <br><br>다가갈수록 멀어지던 꿈들이 <br>바로 눈앞에 펼쳐지고 있어 <br>너와 함께 난 뭐든 할 수 있어 <br><br>파란 하늘에 그려보던 세상이 <br>너와 내가 꿈꾸던 Miracle <br>너와 함께 난 뭐든 이룰 거야 <br><br>하지만 이제 더 이상 난 혼자가 아닌 걸 <br>같은 길 위에서 같은 꿈을 꾸는 널 만난 거야 <br><br>다가갈수록 멀어지던 꿈들이 <br>바로 눈앞에 펼쳐지고 있어 <br>너와 함께 난 뭐든 할 수 있어 <br><br>파란 하늘에 그려보던 세상이 <br>너와 내가 꿈꾸던 Miracle <br>너와 함께 난 뭐든 이룰 거야 <br>너와 함께 난 뭐든 이룰 거야]]></content><category term="정미영" label="정미영"/><category term="미라클 (Miracle) (프론티어 엔딩)" label="미라클 (Miracle) (프론티어 엔딩)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박응식/더_프론티어_프론티어_오프닝/</id><title>박응식 - 더 프론티어 (프론티어 오프닝) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:50:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:50:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9D%91%EC%8B%9D/%EB%8D%94_%ED%94%84%EB%A1%A0%ED%8B%B0%EC%96%B4_%ED%94%84%EB%A1%A0%ED%8B%B0%EC%96%B4_%EC%98%A4%ED%94%84%EB%8B%9D/" title="박응식 - 더 프론티어 (프론티어 오프닝) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지금 내 맘속엔 커다란 날개가 숨어있어 <br>저높은 곳으로 언제라도 날수 있어 <br>지나버린 시간들은 모두 다 잊어버려 <br>누구보다 멋지게 날아오를 그날 위해 <br><br>더앞으로 힘차게 벅찬 내일을 향해서 <br>반드시 해낼꺼야 미래를 부르는 그 이름 <br>프론티어 <br><br>나를이끄는 미지의 세계 아무도 대신할수는없어 <br>자랑스러운 그 이름 We are the frontier <br>휘몰아치는 운명의 바다 거치른 파도를 넘어서 <br>영원히 빛날 그 이름 We are the frontier <br><br>멈추지 않을꺼야 멋지게 해낼꺼야! <br>Frontier <br>]]></content><category term="박응식" label="박응식"/><category term="더 프론티어 (프론티어 오프닝)" label="더 프론티어 (프론티어 오프닝)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김문선/외롭지_않아_디지몬_테이머즈_엔딩/</id><title>김문선 - 외롭지 않아 (디지몬 테이머즈 엔딩) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:50:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:50:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%AC%B8%EC%84%A0/%EC%99%B8%EB%A1%AD%EC%A7%80_%EC%95%8A%EC%95%84_%EB%94%94%EC%A7%80%EB%AA%AC_%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4%EB%A8%B8%EC%A6%88_%EC%97%94%EB%94%A9/" title="김문선 - 외롭지 않아 (디지몬 테이머즈 엔딩) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이제 더 이상 외롭지 않아 <br>너만 내 곁에 있어주면 <br>지금의 마음 잊지 않게 <br>약속해줘 <br><br>혼자라고 생각했었어 <br>내 곁에 아무도 없다고 <br>알 수 없는 미래가 두려워 <br>까만 눈동자 속에 간절히 바라고 있었지 <br>언제나 함께 해 줄 누군가를 <br><br>기적처럼 나에게 다가와 준 너 <br>젖은 어깨 감싸 안아주네 <br>조금만 더 힘을 내 혼자가 아냐 <br>나의 손을 꼭 잡아 <br><br>이제 더 이상 외롭지 않아 <br>너만 내 곁에 있어주면 <br>지금의 마음 잊지 않게 <br>약속해 줘 <br><br>저기 늘 파란 하늘이 보여 <br>나의 마음 알아줄까 <br>언제까지나 우리 함께 <br>언제까지나 우리 함께]]></content><category term="김문선" label="김문선"/><category term="외롭지 않아 (디지몬 테이머즈 엔딩)" label="외롭지 않아 (디지몬 테이머즈 엔딩)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박응식/질주_디지몬_테이머즈_오프닝/</id><title>박응식 - 질주 (디지몬 테이머즈 오프닝) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:50:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:50:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9D%91%EC%8B%9D/%EC%A7%88%EC%A3%BC_%EB%94%94%EC%A7%80%EB%AA%AC_%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4%EB%A8%B8%EC%A6%88_%EC%98%A4%ED%94%84%EB%8B%9D/" title="박응식 - 질주 (디지몬 테이머즈 오프닝) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언제까지 달려나가 꿈을 이룰 때 까지 <br>용기를 줘 내게 힘을 줘 <br><br>내가 누군지 잊어버렸어 <br>여기가 어딘지 기억나지 않아 <br>단 하나 분명히 떠오르는 건 <br>날 지키는 건 오직 나일 뿐이야 <br>기회는 항상 오지 않아 <br>언제나 준비하고 있어 <br>지금 이 순간 최선을 다해 힘껏 뛰어올라 <br><br>언제까지 달려나가 꿈을 이룰 때까지 <br>용기를 줘 내게 힘을 줘 일어설 수 있도록 (디지몬) <br>마지막에 남는 것이 상처뿐일지라도 <br>내 전부를 걸거라고 후회하지 않을거야 (디지몬) <br><br>언제까지 달려나가 꿈을 이룰 때까지 <br>용기를 줘 내게 힘을줘 꿈을 이룰때까지 <br><br>기회는 항상 오지 않아 <br>언제나 준비하고 있어 <br>지금 이순간 최선을 다해 힘껏 뛰어올라 <br><br>언제까지 달려나가 꿈을 이룰 때까지 <br>용기를 줘 내게 힘을 줘 일어설 수 있도록(디지몬) <br>마지막에 남는 것이 상처뿐일지라도 <br>내 전부를 걸거라고 후회하지 않을거야(디지몬) <br><br>언제까지 달려나가 꿈을 이룰 때까지 <br>용기를 줘 내게 힘을 줘 꿈을 이룰 때까지]]></content><category term="박응식" label="박응식"/><category term="질주 (디지몬 테이머즈 오프닝)" label="질주 (디지몬 테이머즈 오프닝)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정여진/투_마이_위시_To_My_Wish_파워디지몬_엔딩/</id><title>정여진 - 투 마이 위시 (To My Wish) (파워디지몬 엔딩) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:50:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:50:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%97%AC%EC%A7%84/%ED%88%AC_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B4_%EC%9C%84%EC%8B%9C_To_My_Wish_%ED%8C%8C%EC%9B%8C%EB%94%94%EC%A7%80%EB%AA%AC_%EC%97%94%EB%94%A9/" title="정여진 - 투 마이 위시 (To My Wish) (파워디지몬 엔딩) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잠깐만 하고 말하는 사이 사라져 버리는 너 <br>마치 아무 일도 없던 것처럼 어느새 웃고 있는 너 <br>어떻게 말 할 수가 있을까 두근거리는 이 맘 <br>마치 아무 것도 모르는 것처럼 말어이 바라보는 너 <br><br>네가 바람이라도 오늘은 꼭 만나고 싶어 <br>이루어지길 바래 To My Wish <br><br>기다려줘 조금만 더 시간이 얼마 남지 않았어 <br>마지막 소원을 이루는 날 까지 <br>보고 싶어 보고 싶어 맑은 너의 눈동자 <br>너와 함께 하고 싶어 이 세상 끝까지 <br>너와 함께 하고 싶어 <br>My Wish To My Wish <br><br>아직도 아련한 내 그리움 깊은 꿈속의 너 <br>마치 나의 손을 잡아 줄 것처럼 조용히 미소 짓는 너 <br>기억 속의 널 조금씩 새기고 싶어 <br>꿈처럼 다가 와줘 To My Wish <br><br>기다려줘 조금만 더 시간이 얼마 남지 않았어 <br>마지막 소원을 이루는 날 까지 <br>보고 싶어 보고 싶어 맑은 너의 눈동자 <br>너와 함께 하고 싶어 이 세상 끝까지 <br>너와 함게 하고 싶어 <br>My Whish To My Wish]]></content><category term="정여진" label="정여진"/><category term="투 마이 위시 (To My Wish) (파워디지몬 엔딩)" label="투 마이 위시 (To My Wish) (파워디지몬 엔딩)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/방대식/내일을_찾아_파워디지몬_오프닝/</id><title>방대식 - 내일을 찾아 (파워디지몬 오프닝) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:51:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:51:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%A9%EB%8C%80%EC%8B%9D/%EB%82%B4%EC%9D%BC%EC%9D%84_%EC%B0%BE%EC%95%84_%ED%8C%8C%EC%9B%8C%EB%94%94%EC%A7%80%EB%AA%AC_%EC%98%A4%ED%94%84%EB%8B%9D/" title="방대식 - 내일을 찾아 (파워디지몬 오프닝) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 숨쉬는 이곳 여기 <br>현실이 아니더라도 <br>세상 모든일엔 무엇이든 의미가있어 <br>지금 내 곁에 있는 모두가 <br>진실이 아니더라도 <br>네가 있는것만으로도 의미가 있어 <br>언제까지나 빛을 잃지않도록 <br>내 곁에서 영원히 날 지켜줘 <br>(날 지켜줘) <br>지치지 않도록 <br>눈을 떠라 눈을 떠라 <br>내 안에 잠든 미래 <br>잠시라도 쉬어갈 시간이 없어 <br>할 수 있어 할 수 있어 <br>진실을 가져봐 <br>잃어버린 내일찾아 내일을 찾아 <br>자 떠라떠라 눈을 떠라 <br>그래 있어있어 할 수 있어 <br>좀 더 힘을 내 조금만 더 달려가 <br>내가 찾던 그 길이 여기 있어 <br>(여기 있어) <br>그 길을 밝혀줘 <br>눈을 떠라 눈을 떠라 <br>내 안에 잠든 미래 <br>잠시라도 쉬어갈 시간이 없어 <br>할 수 있어 할 수 있어 <br>진실을 가져봐 <br>잃어버린 내일찾아 내일을 찾아 <br>(내일을 찾아 찾!아!)]]></content><category term="방대식" label="방대식"/><category term="내일을 찾아 (파워디지몬 오프닝)" label="내일을 찾아 (파워디지몬 오프닝)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/장숙희/안녕_디지몬_엔딩/</id><title>장숙희 - 안녕 디지몬 (엔딩) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:51:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:51:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%EC%88%99%ED%9D%AC/%EC%95%88%EB%85%95_%EB%94%94%EC%A7%80%EB%AA%AC_%EC%97%94%EB%94%A9/" title="장숙희 - 안녕 디지몬 (엔딩) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[설레이는 이 마음은 뭘까 <br>왠지 잠을 이룰 수가 없어 <br>혹시 꿈을 꾸고 있는지 <br>나는 몰라 <br>내가 있는 곳 여기가 어딘지 <br>언제부터 시작되어 온 건지 <br>아무도 내게 말 안해 <br>가르쳐 주지 않아 <br>눈으로 볼 수 있는 세상이 <br>너무나 작다는 걸 알았어 <br>바람에 실려 온 <br>세상 저 편에 <br>소식들 궁금해 <br>안녕 디지몬 <br>네 꿈을 꾸면서 잠이 들래 <br>안녕 디지몬 <br>친구들 모두 안녕 <br>안녕 디지몬 <br>너와 함께하고 싶어 <br>안녕 디지몬 <br>난 너를 찾아갈래 <br><br>어디선가 넌 가만히 다가와 <br>나의 손을 잡아 줄 것 같아 <br>미지의 세상 그 곳에 <br>나를 데려가줘 <br>조용히 눈을 감고 있으면 <br>저 파란하늘 높이 날아가 <br>모두가 꿈꾸던 <br>환한 세상이 보이는 것 같아 <br>안녕 디지몬 <br>네 꿈을 꾸면서 잠이 들래 <br>안녕 디지몬 <br>친구들 모두 안녕 <br>안녕 디지몬 <br>너와 함께 하고 싶어 <br>안녕 디지몬 <br>난 너를 찾아 갈래]]></content><category term="장숙희" label="장숙희"/><category term="안녕 디지몬 (엔딩)" label="안녕 디지몬 (엔딩)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍종명/디지몬_어드벤처_오프닝/</id><title>홍종명 - 디지몬 어드벤처 (오프닝) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:51:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:51:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%A2%85%EB%AA%85/%EB%94%94%EC%A7%80%EB%AA%AC_%EC%96%B4%EB%93%9C%EB%B2%A4%EC%B2%98_%EC%98%A4%ED%94%84%EB%8B%9D/" title="홍종명 - 디지몬 어드벤처 (오프닝) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[찾아라 비밀의 열쇠 미로같이 얽힌 모험들 <br>현실과 또 다른 세상 환상의 디지털 세상 <br>펼쳐라 마음 속 날개 이대로 멈출 순 없어 <br>빛나는 희망을 싣고 어둠 뚫고 나가자 <br>어쩌다 함정속에 빠질지라도 위기의 파도속에 갇힐지라도 <br>생각한대로 이루고 싶어 우리가 가는 그 곳 어디든 <br>디지몬 친구들 Let's go, Let's go <br>세상을 구하자 Let's go, Let's go <br>승리는 언제나 우리의 것 Let's go, go, go <br>디지몬 친구들 Let's go, Let's go <br>세상을 구하자 Let's go, Let's go <br>승리는 언제나 우리의 것 Let's go, go, go, Let's go, go, go <br><br>떠나자 모험을 찾아 선택받은 일곱 친구들 <br>눈앞에 펼쳐진 세상 신기한 디지털 세상 <br>외치자 세상을 향해 구하자 디지털 세상 <br>우리들 지혜를 모아 빛을 찾아 나가자 <br>아직은 힘이 벅차 보일지라도 힘들고 어려운 일 생길지라도 <br>진화를 위한 힘찬 발걸음 수없이 많은 모험 헤친다 <br>디지몬 친구들 Let's go, Let's go <br>세상을 구하자 Let's go, Let's go <br>승리는 언제나 우리의 것 Let's go, go, go <br>디지몬 친구들 Let's go, Let's go <br>세상을 구하자 Let's go, Let's go <br>승리는 언제나 우리의 것 Let's go, go, go, Let's go, go, go]]></content><category term="홍종명" label="홍종명"/><category term="디지몬 어드벤처 (오프닝)" label="디지몬 어드벤처 (오프닝)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Funeral_Advantage/CEOT7K/</id><title>Funeral Advantage - C.E.O.T.7.K. - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:51:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:51:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Funeral_Advantage/CEOT7K/" title="Funeral Advantage - C.E.O.T.7.K. - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Is it impossible to pretend you're not alone <br>Or is it harder because I don't try <br>Beside you, I've reduced to <br>An amputee, dead, always here but never again <br>I am at rest now trying desperately and still hoping to fit in <br><br>Bury me in earth's hands <br>The birds told me something that I don't understand <br>Nothing has changed, we're still on track <br>This world gave me nothing, so I'll give nothing back <br><br>Is it a problem to abstain from relief for so long <br>You said I made you feel sick so I swallowed <br>Inside you, I felt used too <br>And if you see Dan tell him that I'm looking for him <br>He is a ghost now trying desperately and is longing to fit in <br><br>Bury me in earth's hands <br>The birds told me something that I don't understand <br>God please show me anything, 'cause I'm your punching bag <br>This world gave me nothing, so I'll give nothing back]]></content><category term="Funeral Advantage" label="Funeral Advantage"/><category term="C.E.O.T.7.K." label="C.E.O.T.7.K."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정다운/Aroma_Vocal_안준혁/</id><title>정다운 - Aroma (Vocal 안준혁) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:52:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:52:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EB%8B%A4%EC%9A%B4/Aroma_Vocal_%EC%95%88%EC%A4%80%ED%98%81/" title="정다운 - Aroma (Vocal 안준혁) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람 그 목소리 <br>수놓은 저 별 위로 <br>우리의 밤은 <br>조금씩 저물고 <br>춤을 추던 우리 <br>서로를 감싸고 <br>언제나 내게 아름다웠던 <br>꿈이었네요 <br>그 고마운 마음 전해주려고 <br>작은 종잇장에 편지를 적는 <br>그리움에 쌓여가는 시간들 <br>긴 밤 그대 안에 있어 <br>더 아픈 그 밤 <br>작은 마음 하나 <br>못 줍던 그 밤 <br>아무것도 모른 채 <br>다 사라졌네요 <br>그 밤 무너질 거 같아서 <br>참아왔던 긴 시간을 <br>눈물로 보내네요 <br>우연을 바라고 <br>기적을 바랐던 <br>그 쓸모 없는 <br>진심에 밤들은 <br>사라져가네요 <br>그 미소만은 간직하려고 <br>넓지 못한 맘에 그대를 적는 <br>그리움에 쌓여가는 시간들 <br>긴 밤 그대 안에 있어 <br>더 아픈 그 밤 <br>작은 마음 하나 <br>못 줍던 그 밤 <br>아무것도 모른 채 <br>다 사라졌네요 <br>그 밤 무너질 거 같아서 <br>참아 왔던 긴 시간을 <br>눈물로 보내네요 <br>그리운 밤에 <br>그대를 그려 보아요 <br>]]></content><category term="정다운" label="정다운"/><category term="Aroma (Vocal 안준혁)" label="Aroma (Vocal 안준혁)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/케이트_윤_Kate_Yoon/Just_Like_This_Time_SBS_몬스터팜_주제가/</id><title>케이트 윤 (Kate Yoon) - Just Like This Time (SBS `몬스터팜` 주제가) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:52:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:52:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4%ED%8A%B8_%EC%9C%A4_Kate_Yoon/Just_Like_This_Time_SBS_%EB%AA%AC%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B0%ED%8C%9C_%EC%A3%BC%EC%A0%9C%EA%B0%80/" title="케이트 윤 (Kate Yoon) - Just Like This Time (SBS `몬스터팜` 주제가) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can't believe it <br>Do you think <br>I am only dreaming <br>Woo Woo Woo Woo <br>Just like the morning <br>sunlight shining brightly <br>in my eyes <br>Woo Woo Woo Woo Woo <br>Believe the wonder <br>Memories lingering <br>in my mind <br>yeah yeah <br>Without me knowing <br>puts a smile on me <br>like a glowing child <br>yeah eh yeah eh <br>yeah eh eh eh eh <br>The times I spent for me <br>making me so lonely <br>The times I had so hard <br>raising fear inside me <br>Saying goodbye <br>to those yesterdays <br>Now I only hope <br>to see you again <br>It's the first time <br>feeling this way <br>Wanting to know <br>all I can of you <br>Wanting you near <br>always keeping close to you <br>Forever this time <br>I want this feeling <br>Wanting to keep <br>the memory of you <br>Just like this time <br>always keeping close to you <br>]]></content><category term="케이트 윤 (Kate Yoon)" label="케이트 윤 (Kate Yoon)"/><category term="Just Like This Time (SBS `몬스터팜` 주제가)" label="Just Like This Time (SBS `몬스터팜` 주제가)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/케이트_윤_Kate_Yoon/Card_Capter_Cherry_SBS_카드캡터_체리_주제가/</id><title>케이트 윤 (Kate Yoon) - Card Capter Cherry (SBS `카드캡터 체리` 주제가) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:52:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:52:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4%ED%8A%B8_%EC%9C%A4_Kate_Yoon/Card_Capter_Cherry_SBS_%EC%B9%B4%EB%93%9C%EC%BA%A1%ED%84%B0_%EC%B2%B4%EB%A6%AC_%EC%A3%BC%EC%A0%9C%EA%B0%80/" title="케이트 윤 (Kate Yoon) - Card Capter Cherry (SBS `카드캡터 체리` 주제가) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want to see you <br>but I cannot see you here <br>It's a kind of sadness I fear <br>I want to tell you <br>but I cannot tell you now <br>I would show you <br>too much of me <br>If I just knew <br>love had a magic key <br>made for me <br>That'd be the reason <br>the world was made of <br>violets and roses <br>Catch you catch you <br>catch me catch me <br>playing hide and seek with you <br>no more <br>Anything blue <br>can be buried in t he sky <br>no more sorrow <br>It's today I can see <br>I am running straight to you <br>I really truly dearly like you so <br>]]></content><category term="케이트 윤 (Kate Yoon)" label="케이트 윤 (Kate Yoon)"/><category term="Card Capter Cherry (SBS `카드캡터 체리` 주제가)" label="Card Capter Cherry (SBS `카드캡터 체리` 주제가)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Yantzi/Digiman_Advanture__KBS_디지몬_어드벤처_주제가/</id><title>Michael Yantzi - Digiman Advanture (KBS `디지몬 어드벤처` 주제가) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:52:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:52:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Yantzi/Digiman_Advanture__KBS_%EB%94%94%EC%A7%80%EB%AA%AC_%EC%96%B4%EB%93%9C%EB%B2%A4%EC%B2%98_%EC%A3%BC%EC%A0%9C%EA%B0%80/" title="Michael Yantzi - Digiman Advanture (KBS `디지몬 어드벤처` 주제가) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Secret key we all hope to gaze <br>advantures winding <br>like a twisted maze <br>here is a world that's so different <br>it is a digital fantasy <br>open up come and let it out <br>we all know we can't make it stop <br>pray that our hopes <br>will shine bright <br>break the dark let in the light <br>sometimes you might have seen us <br>caught up in a trap <br>sometimes you see that <br>we are slipping down and far <br>well always do the things <br>the way we want <br>wherever it may be that we may go <br>digimon friends are we <br>let's go let's go <br>saving the world today <br>let's go let's go <br>we know forever <br>the victory is ours <br>digimon friends are we <br>let's go let's go <br>saving the world today <br>let's go let's go <br>we know forever <br>the victory is ours <br>Journey starts we will conquer all <br>seven friends are chosen we are told <br>here we are making it happen <br>it is a digital fantasy <br>shout it out so that all can hear <br>save it now digital is here <br>bringing our powers together <br>we will find the light today <br>sometimes you might have seen us <br>tired out and cold <br>soemtimes you see that <br>we are weak and not so bold <br>future is always just a step away <br>never to back away from challenges <br>digimon friends are we <br>let's go let's go <br>saving the world today <br>let's go let's go <br>we know forever <br>the victory is ours <br>digimon friends are we <br>let's go let's go <br>saving the world today <br>let's go let's go <br>we know forever <br>the victory is ours <br>]]></content><category term="Michael Yantzi" label="Michael Yantzi"/><category term="Digiman Advanture (KBS `디지몬 어드벤처` 주제가)" label="Digiman Advanture (KBS `디지몬 어드벤처` 주제가)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/케이트_윤_Kate_Yoon/Hello_Digimon_KBS_디지몬_어드벤처_주제가/</id><title>케이트 윤 (Kate Yoon) - Hello Digimon (KBS `디지몬 어드벤처` 주제가) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:53:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:53:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4%ED%8A%B8_%EC%9C%A4_Kate_Yoon/Hello_Digimon_KBS_%EB%94%94%EC%A7%80%EB%AA%AC_%EC%96%B4%EB%93%9C%EB%B2%A4%EC%B2%98_%EC%A3%BC%EC%A0%9C%EA%B0%80/" title="케이트 윤 (Kate Yoon) - Hello Digimon (KBS `디지몬 어드벤처` 주제가) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can't find the reason <br>for my heart flit <br>I just stay awake <br>and keep the night lit <br>maybe I'm just dreaming <br>I don't know <br>tell me it's true <br>can you tell me <br>where I am who I am <br>when is it that <br>what you see all started <br>no one can tell me anything <br>no one can show me the way <br>all that your eyes see <br>today you know <br>can't see the world <br>because it's just too big <br>I'm always wondering <br>bout the blowing wind <br>it wants to tell me so <br>hello digimon <br>I want to dream of you every night <br>hello digimon <br>everyone saying hello <br>hello digimon <br>tell me that together well be <br>hello digimon <br>I'm going to find you today <br>I know you will come to me <br>your own way <br>and you'll take my hand <br>into your own hand <br>taking me far away today <br>fantasy it will be <br>sliently close my eyes <br>and wait for it <br>then I think I can fly up to the sky <br>I'm going to the place <br>where it will amaze <br>it will take me so <br>hello digimon <br>I want to dream of you every night <br>hello digimon <br>everyone saying hello <br>hello digimon <br>tell me that together well be <br>hello digimon <br>I'm going to find you today <br>hello digimon <br>I want to dream of you every night <br>hello digimon <br>everyone saying hello <br>hello digimon <br>tell me that together well be <br>hello digimon <br>I'm going to find you today <br>]]></content><category term="케이트 윤 (Kate Yoon)" label="케이트 윤 (Kate Yoon)"/><category term="Hello Digimon (KBS `디지몬 어드벤처` 주제가)" label="Hello Digimon (KBS `디지몬 어드벤처` 주제가)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Yantzi/Dragon_Ball_SBS_드래곤볼_주제가/</id><title>Michael Yantzi - Dragon Ball (SBS `드래곤볼` 주제가) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:53:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:53:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Yantzi/Dragon_Ball_SBS_%EB%93%9C%EB%9E%98%EA%B3%A4%EB%B3%BC_%EC%A3%BC%EC%A0%9C%EA%B0%80/" title="Michael Yantzi - Dragon Ball (SBS `드래곤볼` 주제가) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I will run to the ends <br>of the earth yeah <br>I can find wherever you are <br>I will fly to the ends <br>of the space yeah <br>looking for you <br>I will find <br>no one can stop <br>never can stop <br>never stop me no way <br>never oeasing to grow <br>ever rising in me spirit <br>and the strength <br>can you feel it <br>somewhere here now <br>waiting sliently for me <br>there are seven dragon balls <br>into my hands <br>they'll surely fall <br>wish come alive make it so <br>dragon ball <br>making dreams come <br>alive make it so <br>dragon ball <br>give it light making <br>a brand new world <br>It’s the beginning start <br>of a journey <br>Fighting for the honor and truth <br>It will be me there <br>in the end you’ll see <br>Give me power <br>that I may last <br>Just like a beast <br>caged in a world <br>no one can lock me inside <br>just like towering waves <br>that are crashing to me <br>it's the hour of truth <br>can you feel it <br>somewhere here now <br>waiting sliently for me <br>there are seven dragon balls <br>into my hands <br>they'll surely fall <br>wish come alive make it so <br>dragon ball <br>making dreams come <br>alive make it so <br>dragon ball <br>give it light making <br>a brand new world <br>]]></content><category term="Michael Yantzi" label="Michael Yantzi"/><category term="Dragon Ball (SBS `드래곤볼` 주제가)" label="Dragon Ball (SBS `드래곤볼` 주제가)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Yantzi/Power_Up_KBS_디지몬어드벤처_주제가/</id><title>Michael Yantzi - Power Up (KBS `디지몬어드벤처` 주제가) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:53:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:53:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Yantzi/Power_Up_KBS_%EB%94%94%EC%A7%80%EB%AA%AC%EC%96%B4%EB%93%9C%EB%B2%A4%EC%B2%98_%EC%A3%BC%EC%A0%9C%EA%B0%80/" title="Michael Yantzi - Power Up (KBS `디지몬어드벤처` 주제가) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There is something coming to me <br>something running to me <br>don't be weak of frail <br>think of only the victory <br>from a distance somebody calls <br>someone calling me somewhere <br>don't be worried now <br>everythings all right <br>what you were yesterday <br>is the past no more <br>you will be born again <br>todays a brand new day <br>I don't know where I <br>get the strength flying high <br>waking me once more <br>it's a surge I can't refuse <br>power up <br>all we need is just a little more <br>never losing anymore <br>change up <br>give me just a little more <br>wait for me <br>just until I can serve and protect <br>power up change up <br>power up change up <br>what you were yesterday <br>is the past no more <br>you will be born again <br>todays a brand new day <br>I don't know where I <br>get the strength flying high <br>waking me once more <br>it's a surge I can't refuse <br>power up <br>all we need is just a little more <br>never losing anymore <br>change up <br>give me just a little more <br>wait for me <br>just until I can serve and protect <br>power up change up <br>power up change up <br>power up <br>]]></content><category term="Michael Yantzi" label="Michael Yantzi"/><category term="Power Up (KBS `디지몬어드벤처` 주제가)" label="Power Up (KBS `디지몬어드벤처` 주제가)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Draper/Jealous_Feat_Bb_Diamond/</id><title>Draper - Jealous (Feat. Bb Diamond) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:55:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:55:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Draper/Jealous_Feat_Bb_Diamond/" title="Draper - Jealous (Feat. Bb Diamond) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You treated me so unkind, my love for you was blind <br>I should've know, I should've know, I should've know better, baby <br>All the signs were there to see, out chasing girls when you're here with me <br>What am I supposed to do You treat me like a fool <br><br>And you took my heart, left a scar <br>Don't pretend she's just a friend <br>Why are you so cruel <br>Acting like you do to make me <br><br>Jealous, jealous, jealous <br>Jealous, jealous, jealous <br><br>Tell me lies to humour me, playing on insecurities <br>I should've know, I should've know, oh I should've know better, baby <br>First time that I met you, I told my doubts I was lost for you <br>What am I supposed to do You treat me like a fool <br><br>And you took my heart, left a scar <br>Don't pretend she's just a friend <br>Why are you so cruel <br>Acting like you do to make me <br><br>Jealous, jealous, jealous <br>Jealous, jealous, jealous <br><br>I don't wanna question where you are or who you're with <br>But you're testing my patience, playing games and running tricks <br>Is it too much to ask you just to be love <br>Why are you so cruel acting like you do to make me <br><br>Jealous, jealous, jealous <br>Jealous, jealous, jealous <br>Oh no, jealous <br>Oh no, I'm jealous <br>Oh no, jealous <br>Oh no, oh, I'm jealous]]></content><category term="Draper" label="Draper"/><category term="Jealous (Feat. Bb Diamond)" label="Jealous (Feat. Bb Diamond)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Draper/Want_You_More_Feat_Sam_Sure/</id><title>Draper - Want You More (Feat. Sam Sure) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:55:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:55:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Draper/Want_You_More_Feat_Sam_Sure/" title="Draper - Want You More (Feat. Sam Sure) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Walk around <br>So I don't sleep <br>Running red <br>Trying to act casually <br>You'll test <br>She'll leave alone <br>Little hearts <br>that you want <br>Let me be the one to set the tone <br>And now I want you <br>Said where are you to hear the tone <br>and now I want you more]]></content><category term="Draper" label="Draper"/><category term="Want You More (Feat. Sam Sure)" label="Want You More (Feat. Sam Sure)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Powers/Dance/</id><title>Powers - Dance - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:56:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:56:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Powers/Dance/" title="Powers - Dance - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Body snatchers and karma catchers <br>They pitter patter through the night <br>Money loving, a dime a dozen <br>But hey now, all we want to do is dance <br><br>Payphone preachers and twisted creatures <br>On TV clawing out your eyes <br>Candy stealing, vampire dealing <br>But hey now, all we want to do is dance <br><br>Yeah, there's a riot in the ball pit <br>The president is on a spaceship <br>Cause Mother Nature got a facelift <br>And all we want to do is dance <br>All we want to do is dance <br>All we want to do is dance <br><br>Dodging bullets, God fearing mullets <br>Afraid of changing in the tide <br>Singing choir we're too close to the fire <br>But hey now, all we want to do is dance <br><br>Yeah, there's a riot in the ball pit <br>The president is on a spaceship <br>Cause Mother Nature got a facelift <br>And all we want to do is dance <br>All we want to do is dance <br>All we want to do is dance <br>All we want to do is dance <br><br>Hurry, baby <br>Through the fire <br>While it's burning <br>Higher, higher <br><br>Hurry, baby Yeah, there's a riot in the ball pit <br>Through the fire The president is on a spaceship <br>While it's burning Cause Mother Nature got a facelift <br>Yeah And all we want to do is dance <br><br>All we want to do is dance <br>All we want to do is dance <br>All we want to do is dance <br>And all we want to do is dance]]></content><category term="Powers" label="Powers"/><category term="Dance" label="Dance"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/해아래/부르심따라/</id><title>해아래 - 부르심따라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:59:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:59:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%B4%EC%95%84%EB%9E%98/%EB%B6%80%EB%A5%B4%EC%8B%AC%EB%94%B0%EB%9D%BC/" title="해아래 - 부르심따라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오직 주님만 예배하며 살리라 <br>오직 주님만 찬양하며 살리라 <br>나의 가는 길 오직 그가 아시나니 <br>그가 나를 단련하신 후에 <br>내가 정금 같이 나아 가리라 <br>내가 정금 같이 나아 가리라 <br>나의 나 됨은 오직 <br>오직 주의 은혜니 <br>그 부르심 따라 나아가리 <br>그 부르심 따라 나 달려 가리라 <br>그 부르심 따라 가리라 <br>오직 주의 나라 위해 <br>오직 주의 의를 위해 <br>이 길 나 달려 가리라 <br>나 두려움 없이 <br>나 망설임 없이 <br>그 소망을 따라 가리라 <br>오직 주의 나라 위해 <br>오직 주의 영광 위해 <br>이 길 나 달려 가리라 <br>내가 정금 같이 나아 가리라 <br>내가 정금 같이 나아 가리라 <br>나의 나 됨은 오직 <br>오직 주의 은혜니 <br>그 부르심 따라 나아가리 <br>그 부르심 따라 나 달려 가리라 <br>그 부르심 따라 가리라 <br>오직 주의 나라 위해 <br>오직 주의 의를 위해 <br>이 길 나 달려 가리라 <br>나 두려움 없이 <br>나 망설임 없이 <br>그 소망을 따라 가리라 <br>오직 주의 나라 위해 <br>오직 주의 영광 위해 <br>이 길 나 달려 가리라 <br>이 길의 끝에서 주의 얼굴 뵈올 때 <br>주님께 듣고 싶은 말 <br>착하고 충성된 종이라 <br>칭찬 들을 수 있게 <br>부르심 따라 오늘도 나아가리라 <br>내게 주어진 길을 가리라 <br>오직 주의 나라 위해 <br>오직 주의 영광 위해 <br>이 길 나 달려 가리라 <br>이 길 나 달려 가리라 <br>]]></content><category term="해아래" label="해아래"/><category term="부르심따라" label="부르심따라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/The_Apostle_In_Triumph/</id><title>Opeth - The Apostle In Triumph - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:59:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:59:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/The_Apostle_In_Triumph/" title="Opeth - The Apostle In Triumph - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In solitude I wander <br>Through the vast enchanted forest <br>The surrounding skies are one <br>Torn apart by the phenomenon of lightning <br>Rain is pouring down my now shivering shoulders <br>In the rain my tears are forever lost <br><br>The darkened oaks are my only shelter <br>Red leaves are blown by the wind <br>An ebony raven now catches my eye <br>Sitting in calmness <br>Before spreading his black wings <br>Reaching for the skies <br><br>In this forest <br>Where wolves cry their agony unto the moon <br>My spirit is hidden <br>In the form of wisdom <br>carved on a black stone <br>The only way to follow <br><br>Open your soul <br>Redeem, I am immortal <br><br>Blinded by a light <br>My soul is held up in glory <br>I engulf the skies <br>The apostle in triumph <br><br>Through the eternal flame I travel <br>As the rain keeps falling]]></content><category term="Opeth" label="Opeth"/><category term="The Apostle In Triumph" label="The Apostle In Triumph"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/The_Twilight_Is_My_Robe/</id><title>Opeth - The Twilight Is My Robe - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:59:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:59:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/The_Twilight_Is_My_Robe/" title="Opeth - The Twilight Is My Robe - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Unto you I whisper <br>The wildest dreams <br><br>In the coldness of night <br><br>Shrouded in crystals <br>Through a frosty dusk <br>Souls of the fullmoon awaits <br>Their shadows ablaze <br><br>We are all bending <br>Our tired leaves over your empty shell <br>In the sign of true esteem <br>Are you beloved lord <br>Sighing deep under these waterfalls <br><br>The birds of the sun <br>Seperates these dark clouds <br>While the winds of winter sleeps gently around <br>I am sworn to the oath <br>To breathe <br><br>At the waters I dwell <br>The waves are still whispering <br>Ancient lullabies <br>I die <br>While our mystic brothers still seek <br><br>Under your command I will obey <br>In my vision <br>You are the embodiment of pure freedom <br>But through my eyes you are made of stone]]></content><category term="Opeth" label="Opeth"/><category term="The Twilight Is My Robe" label="The Twilight Is My Robe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/Forest_Of_October/</id><title>Opeth - Forest Of October - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:59:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:59:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/Forest_Of_October/" title="Opeth - Forest Of October - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The memories that now rests in this forest <br>Forever shadowing the sunrise of my heart <br>Wings leave their nest at my coming <br>Swaying away unto the cold glowing sky <br>Dreaming away for a while <br>My spirit sighs in peace <br>Gazing unto the stars <br>Please, take me there <br><br>I am so alone, so cold <br>My heart is to scarred to glow <br>I wish the sunrise to come <br>Take my soul away <br>From this cold, lonely shell <br>I am free <br><br>From the eternal sea I rose <br>Veiled in darkness on either shore <br>Lost my pride, lost its glow <br>For me the sun rose no more <br><br>The forest of October <br>Sleeps silent when I depart <br>The web of time <br>Hides my last trace <br><br>My blaze travel the last universe <br>Like the sights of magic <br>Wrapped in aeons <br>My mind is one with my soul <br>I fall alone <br>While leaves fall from the weeping trees]]></content><category term="Opeth" label="Opeth"/><category term="Forest Of October" label="Forest Of October"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/Under_The_Weeping_Moon/</id><title>Opeth - Under The Weeping Moon - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:59:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:59:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/Under_The_Weeping_Moon/" title="Opeth - Under The Weeping Moon - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Once again I've cried <br>Unto the moon <br>That burning flame <br>That has guided me <br>Through all these years <br>The lake from which you flow <br><br>With eyes of fire <br>Once unlit but now alive <br>This energy, sparkling <br>Like a morning star <br><br>The morning star <br><br>Riding the fires of <br>The northern gold <br>I've searched the eye <br>I laugh under the weeping moon <br><br>I am the watcher in the skies <br>Nor the emeralds know my mark <br>Glisten to mark their presence <br>Set the enigma ablaze <br>Searching <br>Finding <br><br>Burn the winter landmarks <br>That said I was there <br>Burn the spirit of cold <br>That travel through my soul]]></content><category term="Opeth" label="Opeth"/><category term="Under The Weeping Moon" label="Under The Weeping Moon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/In_The_Mist_She_Was_Standing/</id><title>Opeth - In The Mist She Was Standing - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:59:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:59:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/In_The_Mist_She_Was_Standing/" title="Opeth - In The Mist She Was Standing - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Seven milestones <br>Under a watching autumn eye <br>Contorted trees are spreading forth <br>The message of the wind <br><br>With frozen hands I rode with the stars <br><br>With anger the wind blew <br>Giving wings to my stallion <br>Clouds gathered across the moon <br>Blazing the white light <br><br>Passing the lake I know so well <br>I am near, yet so far away <br><br>Arrival <br>I saw her shadow standing in the darkness <br>Awaiting me like the night <br>Awaits the day <br>Standing silent smiling at my presence <br>A black candle holds the only light <br><br>Darkness encloses <br>And the candle seem to expire <br>In her cold, cold hand <br>And as a forlorn soul <br>It will fade away <br><br>Touching her flesh in this night <br>My blood froze forever <br>Embraced before the dawn <br>A kiss brought total eclipse <br><br>And she spoke <br>Once and forever <br>I am so cold <br>In mist enrobed the twilight <br>She was standing]]></content><category term="Opeth" label="Opeth"/><category term="In The Mist She Was Standing" label="In The Mist She Was Standing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/Eternal_Soul_Torture/</id><title>Opeth - Eternal Soul Torture - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:59:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:59:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/Eternal_Soul_Torture/" title="Opeth - Eternal Soul Torture - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The deceased awake from beyond their sleep <br>Search for blood and mortal meat <br>Maggots crawl out from their eyes <br>Feel their pain, it's mournful cries <br>Pull your veins, tear out your heart <br>Consume the blood, feast on flesh <br>Torn apart, intestines scattered <br>Alimentary canal ripped and shattered <br>Pieces of your body eaten <br>Painful death as time stands still <br>Where your mind bursts in torture <br>Feel your soul be torn apart <br>Demons crawling through your system <br>Hell has risen, the gods of pain <br>Rip your skin, burn your bones <br>Internal organs torn and drained <br>Smell of flesh burnt to ashes <br>Cries of death from hell <br>Pain is all you revolve around <br>Where the souls of Satan's grounds <br>Rooms of eternal torture, reveal endurance of endless pain <br>Disintegrating mortals, bodies burn <br>There you feel the hellish torture <br>Hellish torment, brutal butchering <br>Demonic creatures revolve in torment]]></content><category term="Opeth" label="Opeth"/><category term="Eternal Soul Torture" label="Eternal Soul Torture"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/To_Bid_You_Farewell/</id><title>Opeth - To Bid You Farewell - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:59:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:59:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/To_Bid_You_Farewell/" title="Opeth - To Bid You Farewell - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I am awaiting the sunrise <br>Gazing modestly through the coldest morning <br>Once it came you lied <br>Embracing us over autumn's proud treetops <br><br>I stand motionless <br>In a parade of falling rain <br>Your voice I cannot hear <br>As I am falling again <br><br>Devotion eludes <br>And in sadness I lumber <br>In my own ashes I am standing without a soul <br>She wept and whispered I know <br><br>We walked into the night <br>Am I to bid you farewell <br><br>Why can't you see that I try <br>When every tear I shed <br>Is for you]]></content><category term="Opeth" label="Opeth"/><category term="To Bid You Farewell" label="To Bid You Farewell"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/Black_Rose_Immortal/</id><title>Opeth - Black Rose Immortal - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:59:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:59:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/Black_Rose_Immortal/" title="Opeth - Black Rose Immortal - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In the name of desperation <br>I call your name <br>A lamentation I sigh <br>Again and again <br><br>Spiritual eclipse <br>The gateways are closed for me to seek <br><br>The night <br>A veil of stars, watching <br>My shadow is born from light <br>The light of the eye, in darkness <br><br>Over troubled waters memories soar <br>Endlessly, searching night and day <br>The moonlight caresses a lonely hill <br>With the calmness of a whisper <br><br>I wear a naked soul <br>A blank face in the streaming water <br>It is cold in here <br>Frost scar my coat with dust <br><br>Eyes attach to your mute portrait <br>We spoke only through thoughts <br>Together we gazed, awaited <br>Hours brought thirst and the rising sun <br><br>Sunbirds leave their dark recesses <br>Shadows glide the archways <br><br>Do not turn your face towards me <br>Confronting me with my loneliness <br>You are in a forest unknown <br>The secret orchard <br>And your voice is vast and achromatic <br>But still so precious <br><br>Lullaby of the crescent moon took you <br>Mesmerized, its kaleidoscopic face <br>Granted you a hollow stare <br>Another soul within the divine herd <br><br>I have kept it <br>The Amaranth symbol <br>Hiddin inside the golden shrine <br>Until we rejoice in the meadow <br>Of the end <br>When we both walk the shadows <br>It will set ablaze and vanish <br>Black rose immortal <br><br>It is getting dark again <br>Dusk shuffle across the fields <br>The evening trees moan as if they knew <br>At night I always dream of you]]></content><category term="Opeth" label="Opeth"/><category term="Black Rose Immortal" label="Black Rose Immortal"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/Nectar/</id><title>Opeth - Nectar - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:59:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:59:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/Nectar/" title="Opeth - Nectar - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I arose from the lullaby <br>Enduring yet another tale <br>You tempt me again <br>With your embrace, so tainted <br>Within the night you beckon <br>Cursing me with every glance <br><br>Bring me through <br>Carry my empty shadow <br>And guide me inside your warped labyrinth <br>To the well of sin <br>I swear I will always love you <br><br>Leave me speechless <br>Release my yearning <br>The soil I walk is clad with light <br>Drifting moons thrust me with their rays <br>And I fall inside <br><br>I lament this heritage <br>Cannot bid farewell <br>The pale faceyou went as far as you could <br>And from that moment <br>I witnessed your beauty, felt your death <br><br>Mine is yours, mine is yours <br><br>In the wake of dawn <br>The mist of morning linger before it leaves <br>Invisible eyes, red reflection <br>It is you <br>Smiling in the midst of the moor]]></content><category term="Opeth" label="Opeth"/><category term="Nectar" label="Nectar"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/The_Night_And_The_Silent_Water/</id><title>Opeth - The Night And The Silent Water - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T14:59:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T14:59:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Opeth/The_Night_And_The_Silent_Water/" title="Opeth - The Night And The Silent Water - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And so you left us <br>Jaded and gaunt, some September <br>Wilted with the seasons <br>But hidden inside the delusion <br>I saw you eyes, somewhere <br><br>Devoid of death <br>The aura poises amidst the storm <br>In solid tears I linger <br>A parlour glade, moonlit sorrow <br><br>Lonely resting pools <br>Relics of the moon dogged lake <br>Whisper All your words are missgiven <br><br>Am I like them <br>Those who mourn and turn away <br>Those who would give anything <br>To see you again <br>If only for another second <br><br>Your face was, like the photograph <br>Painted white <br>We did not speak very often about it <br>What does it matter now <br><br>Cloak of autumn shroud <br>I gaze, dim ricochet of stars <br>I reckon it is time for me to leave <br><br>You sleep in the light <br>Yet the night and the silent water <br>Still so dark]]></content><category term="Opeth" label="Opeth"/><category term="The Night And The Silent Water" label="The Night And The Silent Water"/></entry></feed>