<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:37+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이동우_LEE_DONG_WOO/Smiling_Face/</id><title>이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - Smiling Face - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%B0_LEE_DONG_WOO/Smiling_Face/" title="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - Smiling Face - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[인형 같은 너의 발등에 입 맞추면 <br>꽃잎 같은 손 그 위에 앉은 평화 <br>반짝이는 눈엔 하늘이 새들이 <br>온 세상이 보였고 정말 신기했어 <br>네가 태어난 거야 <br>까만 밤에 피는 하얀 꽃잎처럼 <br>그 위에 별처럼 <br>다가서면 사라질까 <br>손 내밀면 달아날까 봐 <br>까만 밤에 더 빛나는 촛불처럼 <br>그 위에 기도처럼 <br>나를 착하게 만드는 숨결 <br>꿈결같이 달콤한 Smiling face <br>잠옷 바람에 쓴 털모자 <br>화이트 크리스마스 <br>이른 아침부터 기다렸던 산타클로스 <br>반짝이는 눈엔 크리스마스트리 실버벨 <br>온 하늘을 뒤덮은 썰매 끄는 루돌프 <br>다시 태어난 거야 <br>까만 밤에 내려오는 흰 눈처럼 <br>그 위에 별처럼 <br>다가서면 사라질까 <br>손 내밀면 달아날까 봐 <br>까만 밤에 찾아와준 선물처럼 <br>그 위에 축복처럼 <br>나를 착하게 만드는 숨결 <br>꿈결같이 달콤한 Smiling face <br>꽁꽁 얼어버린 두 볼과 손 <br>눈사람과 친구가 된 요정 <br>언젠간 이사진을 보겠지 <br>까만 밤에 날아와 준 천사처럼 <br>난 너를 사랑해 <br>다가서면 사라질까 <br>손 내밀면 달아날까 봐 <br>까만 밤에 찾아와준 산타처럼 <br>그 위에 별들처럼 <br>나를 착하게 만드는 숨결 <br>꿈결같이 달콤한 Smiling face <br>You are my angel <br>You make me smile <br>I love you girl <br>I always will <br>]]></content><category term="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)" label="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)"/><category term="Smiling Face" label="Smiling Face"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이동우_LEE_DONG_WOO/차가운_밤_Lonely_Night/</id><title>이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - 차가운 밤 (Lonely Night) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%B0_LEE_DONG_WOO/%EC%B0%A8%EA%B0%80%EC%9A%B4_%EB%B0%A4_Lonely_Night/" title="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - 차가운 밤 (Lonely Night) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흰 눈 소복한 밤 <br>와인 잔 놓인 밤 <br>음악이 꺼진 뒤에도 널 기다려 <br>꿈을 꾸는 건지 <br>시간이 멈춘 것인지 <br>그리움 소복한 밤 <br>고요만 소란스러운 밤 <br>달빛이 꺼진 뒤에도 <br>나는 너를 기다려 <br>꿈이 깨진 건지 <br>내가 멈춘 건지 <br>차가운 밤 차가운 밤 차가운 밤 <br>흰 눈이 쌓이고 <br>그리움으로 소복한 <br>온 세상이 단 하나도 <br>아름답지가 않아 <br>꿈을 좇는 건지 <br>심장이 멈춘 건지 <br>차가운 밤 차가운 밤 차가운 밤 <br>]]></content><category term="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)" label="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)"/><category term="차가운 밤 (Lonely Night)" label="차가운 밤 (Lonely Night)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이동우_LEE_DONG_WOO/Sweet_Island_Feat_신연아/</id><title>이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - Sweet Island (Feat. 신연아) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%B0_LEE_DONG_WOO/Sweet_Island_Feat_%EC%8B%A0%EC%97%B0%EC%95%84/" title="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - Sweet Island (Feat. 신연아) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[별빛 가득한 밤하늘 건너 <br>시간을 건너 그대와 같이 <br>손 내밀면 닿는 그대 가슴 <br>그대는 바다 그댄 내 모두 <br>둘만 바라볼 수 있는 곳 <br>둘만 잠들 수 있는 Now you are mine <br>한 여름밤 Sweet honeymoon <br>오늘 밤 제일 빛나는 <br>이건 꿈 설마 꿈 아닐까 <br>별이 내리는 Valley 그대 입술은 젤리 <br>풀벌레들과 반딧불이 신나고 <br>달빛 아래 비친 그대 <br>고운 어깨 하얀 드레스 My baby <br>별 비속에 젖은 그대 <br>촉촉하고 맑은 Lips My baby <br>Please come and hold me <br>터질 듯 다시 미칠 듯 <br>꿈속에서 본 듯 내 앞에 수줍은 듯 <br>내 사랑 우리 둘만의 Sweet island <br>All through the night <br>I love you love you love again <br>달빛 아래 비친 그대 <br>고운 어깨 하얀 드레스 My baby <br>별 비속에 젖은 그대 <br>촉촉하고 맑은 Lips My baby <br>Please come and hold me <br>터질 듯 다시 미칠 듯 <br>꿈속에서 본 듯 내 앞에 수줍은 듯 <br>내 사랑 우리 둘만의 Sweet island <br>All through the night <br>I love you love you love again <br>그대 두 눈 속에 가득 피어나는 향기 <br>Rose My baby <br>별 비처럼 내려오신 그대 <br>신비로운 Muse My baby <br>Please come and hold me <br>터질 듯 다시 미칠 듯 <br>꿈속에서 본 듯 <br>내 앞에 수줍은 듯 내 사랑 <br>우리 둘만 <br>여긴 아무도 없는 <br>우리 둘만의 Sweet island Yeah <br>]]></content><category term="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)" label="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)"/><category term="Sweet Island (Feat. 신연아)" label="Sweet Island (Feat. 신연아)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이동우_LEE_DONG_WOO/커피나무_Marry_Me/</id><title>이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - 커피나무 (Marry Me) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%B0_LEE_DONG_WOO/%EC%BB%A4%ED%94%BC%EB%82%98%EB%AC%B4_Marry_Me/" title="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - 커피나무 (Marry Me) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈 뜨면 부드러운 바람 <br>널 닮은 귀여운 화분 <br>향기로운 널 바라볼 수 있는 <br>이 순간이 마냥 행복해 <br>그댄 내 아침을 알고 있을까 <br>키 작은 커피나무엔 <br>반지를 걸어 둘 거야 <br>초라해 보이진 않을까 <br>떨리는 마음 밤바다 같았던 <br>내 인생에 별이 되어준 <br>You’re the Stella of my eyes <br>Will you marry me <br>내 마음 너에게 줄 거야 <br>내 품에 안긴 이 향기를 <br>커피나무를 <br>Will you marry me <br>놓지 않을 거야 <br>꼭 잡은 두 손 위에 노래할 거야 <br>I do I will do <br>너를 사랑해 눈부신 아침 사라진대도 <br>사랑해 사랑해 너만을 사랑해 <br>비가 와도 좋겠어 <br>커피나무 자라난 모습 <br>바라보는 그대의 맑은 두 눈 <br>달처럼 고운 Smile <br>상상만으로도 행복해 <br>You’re the moonlight of my eyes <br>Will you marry me <br>내 마음 너에게 줄 거야 <br>내 품에 안긴 이 향기를 <br>커피나무를 <br>Will you marry me <br>놓지 않을 거야 <br>꼭 잡은 두 손 위에 노래할 거야 <br>I do I will do <br>너를 사랑해 <br>눈부신 아침 사라진대도 <br>사랑해 사랑해 너만을 사랑해 <br>너를 사랑해 <br>저 나무 아래 묻힐 때까지 <br>사랑해 사랑해 너만을 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)" label="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)"/><category term="커피나무 (Marry Me)" label="커피나무 (Marry Me)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이동우_LEE_DONG_WOO/톡탁_What_A_Wonderful_Cane/</id><title>이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - 톡탁 (What A Wonderful Cane) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%B0_LEE_DONG_WOO/%ED%86%A1%ED%83%81_What_A_Wonderful_Cane/" title="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - 톡탁 (What A Wonderful Cane) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새까만 선글라스 새하얀 지팡이 <br>톡탁톡탁 길을 걸으면 <br>바람을 타고 온 고단한 다람쥐 <br>내 머리 위에 누워 잠을 자고 <br>하늘엔 돌고래들 <br>짝을 지어서 지지베베 지지베베 <br>난 흰 지팡이 지휘자 <br>출근하는 악어들 <br>모두 춤을 추며 노래하네 <br>It’s a wonderful day <br>what a wonderful cane <br>씩씩하게 톡탁 톡탁 걷다가 <br>내가 바라본 <br>오늘 이 하루가 나는 좋아 <br>휘파람 신나게 불어봐 <br>달아나는 기린 쫓아가는 펭귄 <br>누굴 응원 해야 할까 <br>아 몰라 내가 바라본 <br>이 하루가 나는 좋아 <br>And I think to myself <br>what a wonderful world <br>루이 암스트롱 노래 들으면 <br>빵 가게 아저씨 코끝에 밀가루 <br>오늘도 나비 되어 춤을 추네 Oh yeah <br>학교 가는 고릴라 짝을 지어서 <br>헐레벌떡 허둥지둥 <br>난 흰 지팡이 지휘자 <br>놀이터에 오리들 <br>모두 춤을 추며 노래하네 <br>It’s a wonderful day <br>what a wonderful cane <br>씩씩하게 톡탁 톡탁 걷다가 <br>내가 바라본 <br>오늘 이 하루가 나는 좋아 <br>휘파람 신나게 불어봐 <br>달아나는 기린 쫓아가는 펭귄 <br>누굴 응원해야 할까 <br>아 몰라 내가 바라본 <br>이 하루가 나는 좋아 <br>눈 감고 상상하면 맘대로 그려지는 세상 <br>보고 싶은 대로 듣고 싶은 대로 <br>이대로도 좋아 Yeah <br>It’s a wonderful day <br>what a wonderful cane <br>씩씩하게 톡탁톡탁 걷다가 <br>내가 바라본 <br>오늘 이 하루가 나는 좋아 <br>휘파람을 불어봐 Yeah <br>사과하는 기린 용서하는 펭귄 <br>모두 기뻐 환호하고 <br>오늘도 내가 바라본 Oh so Beautiful <br>우리 함께 바라본 <br>눈 감고 한번 그려본 <br>It’s another wonderful day <br>]]></content><category term="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)" label="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)"/><category term="톡탁 (What A Wonderful Cane)" label="톡탁 (What A Wonderful Cane)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이동우_LEE_DONG_WOO/사랑이_있었다_Once_There_Was_A_Love/</id><title>이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - 사랑이 있었다 (Once There Was A Love) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%B0_LEE_DONG_WOO/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4_%EC%9E%88%EC%97%88%EB%8B%A4_Once_There_Was_A_Love/" title="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - 사랑이 있었다 (Once There Was A Love) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어디서 걸어오는 걸까 <br>메마른 이 바람은 <br>다가온 계절 쓸쓸한 놀이터 <br>혼자 그네를 타는 아이 <br>조용한 나뭇가지마다 <br>널 찾는 내 기억은 <br>미련도 없이 욕심 하나 없이 <br>낙엽처럼 떨어지네 <br>후 한숨에도 세월은 돌아오지 않아 <br>낯선 곳으로만 가고 싶어 지금은 <br>이대로 서성이고 싶어 지금은 <br>아무도 몰래 울고 싶어 오늘은 <br>내 눈에 내 두 손에 <br>가슴에 사랑이 있었다 <br>후 한숨에도 세월은 돌아오지 않아 <br>낯선 곳으로만 가고 싶어 <br>지금은 이대로 서성이고 싶어 <br>지금은 아무도 몰래 울고 싶어 오늘은 <br>내 눈에 내 두 손에 가슴에 <br>메마른 이 바람 속에도 <br>사랑이 있었다 그땐 <br>]]></content><category term="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)" label="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)"/><category term="사랑이 있었다 (Once There Was A Love)" label="사랑이 있었다 (Once There Was A Love)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/케이플라워_K_Flower/하늘에_떠있는_별처럼_Feat_더데이지/</id><title>케이플라워 (K. Flower) - 하늘에 떠있는 별처럼 (Feat. 더데이지) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4%ED%94%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9B%8C_K_Flower/%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98%EC%97%90_%EB%96%A0%EC%9E%88%EB%8A%94_%EB%B3%84%EC%B2%98%EB%9F%BC_Feat_%EB%8D%94%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80/" title="케이플라워 (K. Flower) - 하늘에 떠있는 별처럼 (Feat. 더데이지) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하늘에 떠있는 별처럼 <br>내게만 빛을 보이는거같아 <br>난 알 수가 있어 <br>그대의 그 마음 <br>빛나는 사랑 좋아 <br>밤이 되는 소리에 <br>내 마음이 깨어나 <br>널 볼 수 있단 생각에 <br>벌써부터 들뜨는 나야 <br>하늘에 떠있는 별처럼 <br>내게만 빛을 보이는거같아 <br>난 알 수가 있어 <br>그대의 그 마음 <br>빛나는 사랑 좋아 <br>밤이 되는 소리에 <br>내 마음이 깨어나 <br>널 볼 수 있단 생각에 <br>벌써부터 들뜨는 나야 <br>하늘에 떠있는 별처럼 <br>내게만 빛을 보이는거같아 <br>난 알 수가 있어 <br>그대의 그 마음 <br>빛나는 사랑 좋아 <br>손 내 밀어 그대 느끼고 있어 <br>다 느껴지는걸 그 사랑이 <br>행복하게만 다가와줘 <br>그대와 나 <br>아침이 오지 않았으면해 <br>또 다시 기다려야만 하잖아 <br>곁에 있고싶어 <br>잠시도 난 싫어 <br>날 꼭 안아줘 <br>하늘에 떠있는 별처럼 <br>내게만 빛을 보이는거같아 <br>난 알 수가 있어 <br>그대의 그 마음 <br>빛나는 사랑 좋아 <br>]]></content><category term="케이플라워 (K. Flower)" label="케이플라워 (K. Flower)"/><category term="하늘에 떠있는 별처럼 (Feat. 더데이지)" label="하늘에 떠있는 별처럼 (Feat. 더데이지)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/에스나_eSNa/Attention_Inst/</id><title>에스나 (eSNa) - Attention (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%90%EC%8A%A4%EB%82%98_eSNa/Attention_Inst/" title="에스나 (eSNa) - Attention (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Listen <br>넌 참 이기적인 사람이야 <br>뭐 하니 <br>외로움도 많이 타는 사람이 <br>정신 못 차리고 있네 <br>이러면 오래 못 갈 텐데 <br>생각을 좀 해봐 내가 떠나면 어쩔래 <br>혼자서 잘 살아봐 이젠 나도 못 참겠어 <br>Ooh Look at me <br>Do I have your attention <br>너처럼 게으른 남자는 아닌 것 같아 <br>참아줄 만큼 참았어 더 이상은 안돼 <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won't you please be a man <br>네 엄마가 아니야 네 아빠도 아냐 <br>널 사랑하니까 이만큼 참아 준거야 <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won't you please be a man <br>Watch out mister <br>그 대가리 속에 무슨 생각 하고 있는지 <br>난 모르겠지만 <br>You're playin with fire <br>And I ain't burnin out <br>Do I have your attention <br>미안 하지만 미안 하지 않아 <br>사랑하지만 너무 힘들잖아 <br>잡고 싶다면 get your shit together <br>Do I have your attention <br>너처럼 게으른 남자는 아닌 것 같아 <br>참아줄 만큼 참았어 더 이상은 안돼 <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won't you please be a man <br>네 엄마가 아니야 네 아빠도 아냐 <br>널 사랑하니까 이만큼 참아 준거야 <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won't you please be a man <br>무심한 action 거칠은 말투 <br>막 대하는 널 보면 빡쳐서 미치겠어 <br>그래도 난 기회를 줬어 <br>계속 실망할 뿐야 <br>너처럼 게으른 남자는 아닌 것 같아 <br>참아줄 만큼 참았어 더 이상은 안돼 <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won't you please be a man <br>네 엄마가 아니야 네 아빠도 아냐 <br>널 사랑하니까 이만큼 참아준 거야 <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won't you please be a man <br>Hey won't you be a man <br>Cuz I can't take it anymore no <br>Be a man won't you please be a man <br>]]></content><category term="에스나 (eSNa)" label="에스나 (eSNa)"/><category term="Attention (Inst.)" label="Attention (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/에스나_eSNa/Attention_English_Ver/</id><title>에스나 (eSNa) - Attention (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%90%EC%8A%A4%EB%82%98_eSNa/Attention_English_Ver/" title="에스나 (eSNa) - Attention (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Listen <br>You treat me like I’ll always be here <br>But honey lonely is how you might end up <br>If you don’t pull yourself together <br>Wake up I’m already miles up ahead <br>Think about it carefully <br>you don’t have many options <br>You lie around thinking <br>that everything is done with magic <br>Ooh look at me <br>Do I have your attention <br>I’ve had it with your lazy ass <br>I’m halfway out the door <br>I’m warning you I'm watching you <br>No I ain’t playin around <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won’t you please be a man <br>Don’t you whine I ain’t your mama <br>ain’t your papa too <br>I love you that’s the only reason <br>why I’ve stuck around <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won’t you please be a man <br>Watch out mister <br>I don’t know what is going on <br>in that little head of yours <br>But let me tell you this <br>You’re playing with fire <br>And I ain’t burning out <br>Do I have your attention <br>I am sorry boy but I'm not sorry <br>Yes I love you but I've just had enough <br>Want me to stay <br>Then get your shit together <br>Do I have your attention <br>I’ve had it with your lazy ass <br>I’m halfway out the door <br>I’m warning you I'm watching you <br>No I ain’t playin around <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won’t you please be a man <br>Don’t you whine I ain’t your mama <br>ain’t your papa too <br>I love you that’s the only reason <br>why I’ve stuck around <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won’t you please be a man <br>You let yourself get too comfortable now <br>I'm still a woman baby <br>start treating me better baby <br>I'm trying to be reasonable <br>But you keep letting me down <br>I’ve had it with your lazy ass <br>I’m halfway out the door <br>I’m warning you I'm watching you <br>No I ain’t playin around <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won’t you please be a man <br>Don’t you whine I ain’t your mama <br>ain’t your papa too <br>I love you that’s the only reason <br>why I’ve stuck around <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won’t you please be a man <br>Hey won't you be a man <br>Cuz I can't take it anymore no <br>Be a man won't you please be a man <br>]]></content><category term="에스나 (eSNa)" label="에스나 (eSNa)"/><category term="Attention (English Ver.)" label="Attention (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/에스나_eSNa/Attention/</id><title>에스나 (eSNa) - Attention - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%90%EC%8A%A4%EB%82%98_eSNa/Attention/" title="에스나 (eSNa) - Attention - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Listen <br>넌 참 이기적인 사람이야 <br>뭐 하니 <br>외로움도 많이 타는 사람이 <br>정신 못 차리고 있네 <br>이러면 오래 못 갈 텐데 <br>생각을 좀 해봐 내가 떠나면 어쩔래 <br>혼자서 잘 살아봐 이젠 나도 못 참겠어 <br>Ooh Look at me <br>Do I have your attention <br>너처럼 게으른 남자는 아닌 것 같아 <br>참아줄 만큼 참았어 더 이상은 안돼 <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won't you please be a man <br>네 엄마가 아니야 네 아빠도 아냐 <br>널 사랑하니까 이만큼 참아 준거야 <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won't you please be a man <br>Watch out mister <br>그 대가리 속에 무슨 생각 하고 있는지 <br>난 모르겠지만 <br>You're playin with fire <br>And I ain't burnin out <br>Do I have your attention <br>미안 하지만 미안 하지 않아 <br>사랑하지만 너무 힘들잖아 <br>잡고 싶다면 get your shit together <br>Do I have your attention <br>너처럼 게으른 남자는 아닌 것 같아 <br>참아줄 만큼 참았어 더 이상은 안돼 <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won't you please be a man <br>네 엄마가 아니야 네 아빠도 아냐 <br>널 사랑하니까 이만큼 참아 준거야 <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won't you please be a man <br>무심한 action 거칠은 말투 <br>막 대하는 널 보면 빡쳐서 미치겠어 <br>그래도 난 기회를 줬어 <br>계속 실망할 뿐야 <br>너처럼 게으른 남자는 아닌 것 같아 <br>참아줄 만큼 참았어 더 이상은 안돼 <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won't you please be a man <br>네 엄마가 아니야 네 아빠도 아냐 <br>널 사랑하니까 이만큼 참아준 거야 <br>All my patience is running out boy <br>Be a man won't you please be a man <br>Hey won't you be a man <br>Cuz I can't take it anymore no <br>Be a man won't you please be a man <br>]]></content><category term="에스나 (eSNa)" label="에스나 (eSNa)"/><category term="Attention" label="Attention"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김우주/이별_5분/</id><title>김우주 - 이별, 5분 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9A%B0%EC%A3%BC/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84_5%EB%B6%84/" title="김우주 - 이별, 5분 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[물끄러미 보고 있어 <br>네 입술이 내뱉는 말 <br>멍하게 널 보고 있어 <br>말도 없이 표정 없이 <br>너 지금 정말 다른 사람 같아 <br>내가 사랑 했었던 그 사람 말고 <br>우리 이렇게 끝내고 말거니 <br>미안해 지금은 <br>아무 생각 못하겠어 <br>덩그러니 놓여있어 <br>우리 했던 약속들만 <br>아무렇지 않은 거니 <br>그런 말을 쉽게 해도 <br>너 지금 정말 다른 사람 같아 <br>내가 사랑 했었던 그 사람 말고 <br>내가 그렇게 잘못했던 거니 <br>미안해 지금은 <br>아무 말도 못하겠어 <br>너 지금 대체 무슨 말을 한 거니 <br>우리 어디서부터 잘못 된 거니 <br>헤어질 수 있다는 걸 <br>한 번도 생각해 본 적 없는데 <br>이제 혼자라는 걸 느껴 <br>허무해 너무해 <br>하고 싶던 얘기 <br>너무 너무 많았는데 <br>너 지금 정말 다른 사람 같아 <br>내가 사랑 했었던 그 사람 말고 <br>우리 이렇게 끝내고 말거니 <br>미안해 지금은 <br>아무 생각 못하겠어 <br>]]></content><category term="김우주" label="김우주"/><category term="이별, 5분" label="이별, 5분"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/철규/Rainy_you/</id><title>철규 - Rainy you - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%A0%EA%B7%9C/Rainy_you/" title="철규 - Rainy you - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니가 내리던 <br>니가 내리던 날에 <br>달이 내리던 <br>녹아 내리던 날에 <br>내가 흐르던 <br>내가 흐르던 날에 <br>별이 흐르던 <br>내가 흐르던 날에 <br>평범한 나의 일상속에 <br>거짓말처럼 어울리지 않는 <br>환한 색으로 가만히 내게 <br>내려앉은 그대 <br>세상에 없던 너의 향기 <br>니가 내리던 <br>니가 내리던 날에 <br>달이 내리던 <br>녹아 내리던 날에 <br>내가 흐르던 <br>내가 흐르던 날에 <br>별이 흐르던 <br>내가 흐르던 날에 <br>달콤한 너의 웃음소리 <br>몰랐어 정말 <br>내 전부가 될줄 <br>내 말 웃으며 듣다가 멈짓 <br>바라본 눈빛에 <br>내 모든 걸 오직 너에게 <br>니가 내리던 <br>니가 내리던 날에 <br>달이 내리던 <br>녹아 내리던 날에 <br>내가 흐르던 <br>내가 흐르던 날에 <br>별이 흐르던 <br>내가 흐르던 날에 <br>떨리는 손끝 <br>너의 체온 <br>또 하나 써지는 <br>둘만의 비밀 <br>너만의 가사로 <br>가득채울 나의 노래 <br>You're first and last of my life <br>니가 내리던 <br>니가 내리던 날에 <br>달이 내리던 <br>녹아 내리던 날에 <br>내가 흐르던 <br>내가 흐르던 날에 <br>별이 흐르던 <br>내가 흐르던 날에 <br>니가 내리던 <br>니가 내리던 날에 <br>달이 내리던 <br>녹아 내리던 날에 <br>내가 흐르던 <br>내가 흐르던 날에 <br>별이 흐르던 <br>]]></content><category term="철규" label="철규"/><category term="Rainy you" label="Rainy you"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/거인/Dead_Dream_Prod_By_일랑/</id><title>거인 - Dead Dream (Prod. By 일랑) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B1%B0%EC%9D%B8/Dead_Dream_Prod_By_%EC%9D%BC%EB%9E%91/" title="거인 - Dead Dream (Prod. By 일랑) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사람은 누구나 죽어 <br>아마도 나의 꿈도 <br>나의 육신과 함께 <br>불씨도 없이 <br>날아가겠지 이건 <br>내 운명 <br>다들 욕망 아래 <br>기름을 부어 <br>그리고는 말하네 <br>이게 날 구원 <br>할 거라고 닿을 거라고 <br>하느님이 보이고 <br>그는 나라고 <br>이 모든 게 헛되고 <br>헛되서 버리고 <br>진실로 가려해 <br>내가 욕망한 것들은 <br>멋지게 포장돼 <br>꿈이라 불렸네 <br>음란하게 뒤엉킨 <br>거울 뒤의 <br>자기혐오와 나르시시즘 <br>그만 할래 비현실적인 비행 <br>날리 없지 난 <br>날 안 믿거든 <br>난 장님이야 미래 <br>보이지 않아 <br>사람이니까 당연히 <br>결점이 많아 <br>솔직히 말할거야 <br>그걸 위해 고민해 <br>창작의 밤하늘에 <br>별빛이 고이네 <br>듣고있네 누군가는 나를 <br>명작이 되려고 <br>노력했지 나름 <br>근데 세상은 <br>내 가지를 자르고 <br>나한테 왜 이렇게 <br>남들과 다르냐고 <br>말도 안 되는 걸 묻지 <br>나도 몰라 내가 누군지 <br>시험 많은 삶 <br>채점은 죽은 뒤 <br>하여튼 당장은 <br>랩퍼를 꿈꾸지 <br>결국엔 답을 몰라 아직도 <br>하고싶은대로 하지 또 <br>어두운 인생 믿음의 달이 떠 <br>근데 욕망이란 <br>가로등이 밝지 더 <br>거기 멀뚱히 서있지 말고 <br>나를 위해 춤춰줄래 <br>거기 가만히 서있지 말고 <br>나를 위해 손 들어줄래 <br>내가 얼마나 원하는지 <br>몰라도 욕망이 내 주인 <br>거기 멀찍이 서있지 말고 <br>나를 위해 기도해줄래 <br>나의 머릿속의 나와 <br>남이 보는 나는 달라 <br>인정 받아야만 <br>밤에 잠이 잘 와 <br>다들 보고 싶은대로 봐 <br>그래서 나는 외로워 <br>그저 우스운 존재로만 <br>비춰질까 괴로워 <br>맘 속에 열등감이 넘칠 때 <br>난 그걸 창작욕에 먹이네 <br>이 자식이 살이 찌고 <br>커질 때를 <br>지켜보는 것이 <br>내겐 즐거움이네 <br>코흘리개 때부터 <br>시를 썼던 <br>애가 바로 나야 <br>다른 길은 없어 <br>그러니까 이건 <br>아마 저주야 <br>이 십자가를 대체 <br>누가 져줄까 <br>타고나진 못했지 <br>근데 끊임 없는 고갯짓 <br>깨 가식의 껍데기 <br>민달팽이처럼 <br>속살을 꺼냈지 <br>이 창조의 <br>욕망은 불가항력 <br>맘 속의 평화를 <br>꿈과 바꿨더니 <br>가끔 랩이 고문과 같어 <br>허나 멈추지 않아 <br>게으름과 맞서 <br>가살 매일 쓰곤 해 <br>사서하는 수고네 <br>대뇌가 용광로라 뜨겁네 <br>철근 같이 단어들은 굳건해 <br>매일 밤 작업을 해 홀로 <br>난 거꾸로 오르니 연어 <br>이제 죽어도 여한이 없어 <br>거짓말이었고 또 시를 적어 <br>거기 멀뚱히 서있지 말고 <br>나를 위해 춤춰줄래 <br>거기 가만히 서있지 말고 <br>나를 위해 손 들어줄래 <br>내가 얼마나 원하는지 <br>몰라도 욕망이 내 주인 <br>거기 멀찍이 서있지 말고 <br>나를 위해 기도해줄래 <br>이건 그냥 내 고집 <br>성공의 보장 없지 <br>신은 절대 내게 랩하라고 <br>명령한 적이 없지 <br>가사장이 태양이었지 <br>눈이 멀어 안 보이게 된 현실 <br>욕망은 항상 기댈 배반하고 <br>고통들만 늘었지 <br>이건 그냥 내 고집 <br>성공의 보장 없지 <br>신은 절대 내게 랩하라고 <br>명령한 적이 없지 <br>가사장이 태양이었지 <br>눈이 멀어 안 보이게 된 현실 <br>욕망은 항상 기댈 배반하고 <br>고통들만 늘었지 <br>늘었지 <br>]]></content><category term="거인" label="거인"/><category term="Dead Dream (Prod. By 일랑)" label="Dead Dream (Prod. By 일랑)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/찬_ChAN/사랑해/</id><title>찬 (ChAN) - 사랑해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B0%AC_ChAN/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4/" title="찬 (ChAN) - 사랑해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지금 나와 <br>마주 앉은 사람이 <br>당신이 정말 맞는지 <br>아직 꿈을 <br>깨지 못한 것 같아 <br>조금만 더 가까이 <br>올 수 있겠니 <br>조심스럽게 <br>그대 손을 잡아볼거야 <br>떨리는 이 마음 알겠니 <br>사랑해 <br>내게 와준 당신에게 <br>하고픈 말 <br>지금처럼 영원히 <br>너를 사랑해 <br>지금 나를 <br>바라보는 사람이 <br>당신이 정말 맞는지 <br>아직 꿈을 <br>깨지 못한 것 같아 <br>조금만 더 가까이 <br>가도 되겠니 <br>조심스럽게 <br>그댈 힘껏 안아볼거야 <br>떨리는 내 마음 알겠니 <br>사랑해 내게 와준 당신에게 <br>하고픈 말 <br>지금처럼 영원히 <br>너를 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="찬 (ChAN)" label="찬 (ChAN)"/><category term="사랑해" label="사랑해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제이세라/사랑도_단순하게_Inst/</id><title>제이세라 - 사랑도 단순하게 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B8%EB%9D%BC/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EB%8F%84_%EB%8B%A8%EC%88%9C%ED%95%98%EA%B2%8C_Inst/" title="제이세라 - 사랑도 단순하게 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대를 보면 <br>가슴이 떨리는데 <br>다가가지 못하는 이유 <br>난 겁이 많아서 <br>그대가 내 옆을 스쳐도 <br>난 그저 바라만 <br>바라만 보네요 <br>그랬었죠 나란 사람은 <br>사랑도 하기 전에 <br>이별부터 겁을 냈던 <br>나였지만 <br>사랑도 단순하게 <br>생각할래요 <br>사랑이 그래요 <br>생각할수록 <br>눈물만 흘리죠 <br>더 이상 속으로만 <br>널 바라보며 <br>후회하며 살지 않을래 <br>그렇게 살래 <br>사랑도 단순하게 <br>그대가 보이는데 <br>난 그저 웃음만 <br>웃음만 짓네요 <br>마음 주면 떠날거라고 <br>마음을 닫은 채로 <br>너를 항상 <br>밀어내던 나였지만 <br>사랑도 단순하게 <br>생각할래요 <br>사랑이 그래요 <br>생각할수록 <br>눈물만 흘리죠 <br>더 이상 속으로만 <br>널 바라보며 <br>후회하며 살지 않을래 <br>그렇게 살래 <br>사랑도 단순하게 <br>이렇게 우리 멀어져도 <br>나는 항상 그대뿐이에요 <br>세상이 다 변해도 <br>사랑할게요 <br>내 맘이 그래요 <br>24시간 그대만 원하죠 <br>더 이상 멀리서만 <br>바라보면서 <br>열 번이고 수백 번은 <br>더 매일 하던 말 <br>이제야 말하네요 <br>]]></content><category term="제이세라" label="제이세라"/><category term="사랑도 단순하게 (Inst.)" label="사랑도 단순하게 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제이세라/사랑도_단순하게/</id><title>제이세라 - 사랑도 단순하게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B8%EB%9D%BC/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EB%8F%84_%EB%8B%A8%EC%88%9C%ED%95%98%EA%B2%8C/" title="제이세라 - 사랑도 단순하게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대를 보면 <br>가슴이 떨리는데 <br>다가가지 못하는 이유 <br>난 겁이 많아서 <br>그대가 내 옆을 스쳐도 <br>난 그저 바라만 <br>바라만 보네요 <br>그랬었죠 나란 사람은 <br>사랑도 하기 전에 <br>이별부터 겁을 냈던 <br>나였지만 <br>사랑도 단순하게 <br>생각할래요 <br>사랑이 그래요 <br>생각할수록 <br>눈물만 흘리죠 <br>더 이상 속으로만 <br>널 바라보며 <br>후회하며 살지 않을래 <br>그렇게 살래 <br>사랑도 단순하게 <br>그대가 보이는데 <br>난 그저 웃음만 <br>웃음만 짓네요 <br>마음 주면 떠날거라고 <br>마음을 닫은 채로 <br>너를 항상 <br>밀어내던 나였지만 <br>사랑도 단순하게 <br>생각할래요 <br>사랑이 그래요 <br>생각할수록 <br>눈물만 흘리죠 <br>더 이상 속으로만 <br>널 바라보며 <br>후회하며 살지 않을래 <br>그렇게 살래 <br>사랑도 단순하게 <br>이렇게 우리 멀어져도 <br>나는 항상 그대뿐이에요 <br>세상이 다 변해도 <br>사랑할게요 <br>내 맘이 그래요 <br>24시간 그대만 원하죠 <br>더 이상 멀리서만 <br>바라보면서 <br>열 번이고 수백 번은 <br>더 매일 하던 말 <br>이제야 말하네요 <br>]]></content><category term="제이세라" label="제이세라"/><category term="사랑도 단순하게" label="사랑도 단순하게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/쟈코비플래닛_Jacoby_Planet/동창회/</id><title>쟈코비플래닛 (Jacoby Planet) - 동창회 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9F%88%EC%BD%94%EB%B9%84%ED%94%8C%EB%9E%98%EB%8B%9B_Jacoby_Planet/%EB%8F%99%EC%B0%BD%ED%9A%8C/" title="쟈코비플래닛 (Jacoby Planet) - 동창회 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[와 몇 년 만이야 <br>이렇게 다 모이기 <br>정말이지 쉽지 않아 <br>누군 많이 변했고 <br>누군 여전해 <br>늦는 애들 전화 왔으니까 <br>먼저 한잔해 <br>보고 싶었어 이 망할 놈들 <br>가끔 주변 통해 들었어 <br>니들 사는 얘기는 <br>나 아직 음악 하냐고 <br>그래 걱정 마 나 <br>나름 잘사니까 <br>오늘은 좀 묻지 말아줄래 <br>나 오늘 니들 얘기 <br>듣고 싶었어 <br>왜 맨날 나만 <br>위로 받나 싶었어 <br>그래 일단 속 얘긴 <br>좀 마신 담에 하자고 <br>지난 추억 팔이 하며 <br>일단 살짝 시동 걸자고 <br>오 애들 더 왔다 일루와 <br>어서 좁혀 앉아 <br>오늘 분위기가 좋다야 <br>자 우리 사진 한 장 찍자 <br>언제 이렇게 또 보겠냐 <br>다 어서 붙어 <br>좀 잘 나가는 놈 <br>좀 못 나가는 놈 <br>그 속에 나는 그저 <br>항상 꿈만 꾸는 놈 <br>맘 편히 잘 노는 놈 <br>불편해 눈치 보는 놈 <br>난 뭣도 없이 <br>여기저기 잘 끼는 놈 <br>술 좀 들어가니까 <br>누군 울고 누군 웃네 <br>창열인 대체 뭘 해야 <br>잘 살 수 있냐 묻네 <br>나도 알아 <br>이 나라 살기 힘든 거 <br>학자금 빚더미 앉은 거 <br>엄마 늙어 가는 거 <br>안정적인 것과 거리가 <br>먼 삶은 괴롭단 거 <br>내가 왜 모르겠냐 <br>나도 안다고 <br>근데 정작 해줄 말은 없단 게 <br>니 쳐진 어깰 보니 <br>그간 몰라줘서 너무 미안해 <br>야 쟤들 여자 얘기 시작했다 <br>너 불편하면 자리 딴대로 옮기자 <br>2차는 내가 살 테니까 <br>지금 나가는 게 어때 <br>사진으로 남은 우리의 동창회 <br>사진으로 남은 우리의 동창회 <br>사진으로 남은 우리의 동창회 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라 라라 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라 라라 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라 라라 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라 라라 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라 라라 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라 라라 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라 라라 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라 라라 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라 라라 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라 라라 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라 라라 <br>라라라 라라라 라라라 라라 <br>]]></content><category term="쟈코비플래닛 (Jacoby Planet)" label="쟈코비플래닛 (Jacoby Planet)"/><category term="동창회" label="동창회"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/쟈코비플래닛_Jacoby_Planet/POWDER_Love__Peace/</id><title>쟈코비플래닛 (Jacoby Planet) - POWDER (Love &amp; Peace) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9F%88%EC%BD%94%EB%B9%84%ED%94%8C%EB%9E%98%EB%8B%9B_Jacoby_Planet/POWDER_Love__Peace/" title="쟈코비플래닛 (Jacoby Planet) - POWDER (Love &amp; Peace) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[무슨 일 있냔 물음에 <br>대답하기 힘들 땐 <br>아무 말 않고 널 기다릴게 <br>원한다면 나 언제나 <br>소파에 몸을 기댄 채 <br>너의 얘길 밤새 들어줄게 <br>세상이 가끔 미워질 때 <br>따스한 노래로 <br>너의 맘 다 녹일 거야 <br>사랑이 널 아프게 할 때 <br>아무 말 못 했던 <br>널 감싸 안아 줄 거야 <br>Powder <br>너의 안식처가 될 테니 <br>넌 그저 내 어깨 위에 <br>기대면 돼 <br>Be the shoulder <br>순간보단 영원을 밝히는 <br>굵은 심지로 <br>너의 옆에 설게 <br>Powder <br>너란 밤바다를 밝혀줄 <br>단 하나의 등대로 <br>너를 비춰줄게 <br>Sing it louder <br>오늘 밤 걱정 대신 <br>이불을 꼭 덮은 채 <br>깊은 잠이 드는 거야 <br>우린 잠시 멈춰서 <br>어떤 말도 잊은 채 <br>저 하늘을 바라보고 있어 <br>인생은 케익 같아서 <br>기쁨을 나눠 줄 <br>누군가가 필요할지 몰라 <br>세상이 가끔 미워질 때 <br>따스한 노래로 <br>너의 맘 다 녹일 거야 <br>사랑이 널 아프게 할 때 <br>아무 말 못 했던 <br>널 감싸 안아 줄 거야 <br>Powder <br>너의 안식처가 될 테니 <br>넌 그저 내 어깨 위에 <br>기대면 돼 <br>Be the shoulder <br>순간보단 영원을 <br>밝히는 굵은 심지로 <br>너의 옆에 설게 <br>Powder <br>너란 밤바다를 밝혀줄 <br>단 하나의 등대로 <br>너를 비춰줄게 <br>Sing it louder <br>오늘 밤 걱정 대신 <br>이불을 꼭 덮은 채 <br>깊은 잠이 드는 거야 <br>Powder <br>너의 안식처가 될 테니 <br>넌 그저 내 어깨 위에 <br>기대면 돼 <br>Be the shoulder <br>순간보단 영원을 <br>밝히는 굵은 심지로 <br>너의 옆에 설게 <br>Powder <br>너란 밤바다를 밝혀줄 <br>단 하나의 등대로 <br>너를 비춰줄게 <br>Sing it louder <br>오늘 밤 걱정 대신 <br>이불을 꼭 덮은 채 <br>깊은 잠이 드는 거야 <br>Powder <br>너의 안식처가 될 테니 <br>넌 그저 내 어깨 위에 <br>기대면 돼 <br>Be the shoulder <br>순간보단 영원을 <br>밝히는 굵은 심지로 <br>너의 옆에 설게 <br>Powder <br>너란 밤바다를 밝혀줄 <br>단 하나의 등대로 <br>너를 비춰줄게 <br>Sing it louder <br>오늘 밤 걱정 대신 <br>이불을 꼭 덮은 채 <br>깊은 잠이 드는 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="쟈코비플래닛 (Jacoby Planet)" label="쟈코비플래닛 (Jacoby Planet)"/><category term="POWDER (Love &amp; Peace)" label="POWDER (Love &amp; Peace)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/앤씨아/봄에_오면_괴롭힐_거예요_Inst/</id><title>앤씨아 - 봄에 오면 괴롭힐 거예요 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%A4%EC%94%A8%EC%95%84/%EB%B4%84%EC%97%90_%EC%98%A4%EB%A9%B4_%EA%B4%B4%EB%A1%AD%ED%9E%90_%EA%B1%B0%EC%98%88%EC%9A%94_Inst/" title="앤씨아 - 봄에 오면 괴롭힐 거예요 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[올해는 더 춥구나 <br>겨울 네가 온 게 반갑진 않아 <br>내 연애세포들은 다 얼어 죽었나 <br>통 움직이질 않네 <br>너무 무료해 나 혼자 뭐해 <br>요즘 내 애인은 저 네모난 TV <br>해보고 싶다 뜨거운 연애 <br>누구 나랑 연애 안 해볼래요 <br>내게 불장난 좀 쳐 줄래 <br>또 활활 타게 만들어줄래 <br>oh baby <br>방구석 겨울 이불 속 겨울 <br>이젠 탈출하고 싶은데 <br>내 짝 대체 어디 있나요 <br>내게 미치게 만들어줄게 <br>혹시나 봄에 온다면 <br>그땐 괴롭힐 거예요 <br>올해는 더 춥구나 <br>겨울 네가 온 게 반갑진 않아 <br>내 연애세포들은 다 얼어 죽었나 <br>통 움직이질 않네 <br>살이나 뺄까 모델들처럼 <br>아냐 이 살들마저 없음 더 춥다 <br>가장 좋은 건 뜨거운 연애 <br>누구 나랑 연애 안 해볼래요 <br>내게 불장난 좀 쳐 줄래 <br>또 활활 타게 만들어 줄래 <br>oh baby <br>방구석 겨울 이불 속 겨울 <br>no no <br>탈출하고 싶은데 <br>내 님 대체 어디 있나요 <br>내게 오다 넘어 졌나요 <br>혹시나 봄에 온다면 <br>그땐 괴롭힐 거예요 <br>내 님 대체 어디 있나요 <br>내게 오다 넘어 졌나요 <br>혹시나 봄에 온다면 <br>그땐 괴롭힐 거예요 <br>지금 와요 <br>네 손 꼭 잡고 <br>겨울바다 보고 싶다 <br>]]></content><category term="앤씨아" label="앤씨아"/><category term="봄에 오면 괴롭힐 거예요 (Inst.)" label="봄에 오면 괴롭힐 거예요 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/앤씨아/봄에_오면_괴롭힐_거예요/</id><title>앤씨아 - 봄에 오면 괴롭힐 거예요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%A4%EC%94%A8%EC%95%84/%EB%B4%84%EC%97%90_%EC%98%A4%EB%A9%B4_%EA%B4%B4%EB%A1%AD%ED%9E%90_%EA%B1%B0%EC%98%88%EC%9A%94/" title="앤씨아 - 봄에 오면 괴롭힐 거예요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[올해는 더 춥구나 <br>겨울 네가 온 게 반갑진 않아 <br>내 연애세포들은 다 얼어 죽었나 <br>통 움직이질 않네 <br>너무 무료해 나 혼자 뭐해 <br>요즘 내 애인은 저 네모난 TV <br>해보고 싶다 뜨거운 연애 <br>누구 나랑 연애 안 해볼래요 <br>내게 불장난 좀 쳐 줄래 <br>또 활활 타게 만들어줄래 <br>oh baby <br>방구석 겨울 이불 속 겨울 <br>이젠 탈출하고 싶은데 <br>내 짝 대체 어디 있나요 <br>내게 미치게 만들어줄게 <br>혹시나 봄에 온다면 <br>그땐 괴롭힐 거예요 <br>올해는 더 춥구나 <br>겨울 네가 온 게 반갑진 않아 <br>내 연애세포들은 다 얼어 죽었나 <br>통 움직이질 않네 <br>살이나 뺄까 모델들처럼 <br>아냐 이 살들마저 없음 더 춥다 <br>가장 좋은 건 뜨거운 연애 <br>누구 나랑 연애 안 해볼래요 <br>내게 불장난 좀 쳐 줄래 <br>또 활활 타게 만들어 줄래 <br>oh baby <br>방구석 겨울 이불 속 겨울 <br>no no <br>탈출하고 싶은데 <br>내 님 대체 어디 있나요 <br>내게 오다 넘어 졌나요 <br>혹시나 봄에 온다면 <br>그땐 괴롭힐 거예요 <br>내 님 대체 어디 있나요 <br>내게 오다 넘어 졌나요 <br>혹시나 봄에 온다면 <br>그땐 괴롭힐 거예요 <br>지금 와요 <br>네 손 꼭 잡고 <br>겨울바다 보고 싶다 <br>]]></content><category term="앤씨아" label="앤씨아"/><category term="봄에 오면 괴롭힐 거예요" label="봄에 오면 괴롭힐 거예요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이브/멜로디_Feat_김희철/</id><title>이브 - 멜로디 (Feat. 김희철) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B8%8C/%EB%A9%9C%EB%A1%9C%EB%94%94_Feat_%EA%B9%80%ED%9D%AC%EC%B2%A0/" title="이브 - 멜로디 (Feat. 김희철) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다 거짓말 <br>어느 바보가 만든 멜로디 <br>버림받고 술에 취해 만든 멜로디 <br>내 헤어짐에 <br>그 상처가 아물 즈음에 <br>또 내 귓가에 파고들어 <br>눈물 짜내는 멜로디 <br>한 남자가 사랑해 <br>그 한 여자도 그를 사랑해 <br>모두 헛소리 뻔한 그 스토리 <br>이젠 사랑을 끊는다 <br>다 지켜내지도 못할 약속 <br>모두 헛소리 개울음소리 <br>네가 내 곁을 떠나간 뒤에 <br>텅 빈 이 내 마음속에 <br>괴물이 자라나 미움만 가득해 <br>지독한 내 버러지 같은 마음 <br>다 거짓말 <br>어느 바보가 만든 멜로디 <br>버림받고 술에 취해 만든 멜로디 <br>내 헤어짐에 <br>그 상처가 아물 즈음에 <br>또 내 귓가에 파고들어 <br>눈물 짜내는 멜로디 <br>한 여자가 떠나면 <br>그 한 남자는 그리워하는 <br>지겨운 스토리 뻔한 멜로디 <br>네가 내 곁을 떠나간 뒤에 <br>텅 빈 이 내 마음속에 <br>괴물이 자라나 미움만 가득해 <br>지독한 내 버러지 같은 마음 <br>다 거짓말 <br>어느 바보가 만든 멜로디 <br>버림받고 술에 취해 만든 멜로디 <br>내 헤어짐에 <br>그 상처가 아물 즈음에 <br>또 내 귓가에 파고들어 <br>자꾸 맴도는 멜로디 <br>애써 뿌리쳐내지만 <br>머저리 같은 내 맘 그 한구석에서 <br>그 괴물이 또다시 자라나 <br>난 주저앉아 소리 질러 <br>가라 가라고 <br>다 거짓말 <br>나 혼자서 미친 듯 소리쳐봐도 <br>난 안 되는가 봐 <br>제발 그만 그만해줘 <br>눈물 나게 죽도록 쓰라린 멜로디 <br>귓가에 맴도는 멜로디 <br>]]></content><category term="이브" label="이브"/><category term="멜로디 (Feat. 김희철)" label="멜로디 (Feat. 김희철)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Olly_Murs/Flaws_Acoustic/</id><title>Olly Murs - Flaws (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Olly_Murs/Flaws_Acoustic/" title="Olly Murs - Flaws (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I got flaws I can't disguise <br>I've been running <br>from them all my life <br>On the surface I'm all smiles <br>But I'm only living half a lie <br>Stuck behind the glass <br>and the walls are closing in <br>Stuck inside a past <br>that won't let me leave <br>But I'm in chains <br>while you're breaking free <br>Stuck behind the glass <br>and im waiting for your call <br>Nothing ever lasts for a prisoner <br>I'm in chains <br>while you're breaking free <br>And it's killing me <br>I got flaws I can't disguise <br>And you tried to pull me <br>to the light <br>I can't go back and make it right <br>And I wonder <br>where you sleep tonight <br>Stuck behind the glass <br>and the walls are closing in <br>Stuck inside a past <br>that won't let me leave <br>But I'm in chains <br>while you're breaking free <br>Stuck behind the glass <br>and I'm waiting for your call <br>Nothing ever lasts for a prisoner <br>And I'm in chains <br>while you're breaking free <br>And it's killing me <br>We were never born to make it <br>out of this alive <br>When were never born to make it <br>how could we to survive <br>Stuck behind the glass <br>and the walls are closing in <br>Stuck inside a past <br>that won't let me leave <br>And I'm in chains <br>while you're breaking free <br>Stuck behind the glass <br>and I'm waiting for your call <br>Nothing ever lasts for a prisoner <br>I'm in chains <br>while you're breaking free <br>And it's killing me <br>]]></content><category term="Olly Murs" label="Olly Murs"/><category term="Flaws (Acoustic)" label="Flaws (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Olly_Murs/Love_You_More_Acoustic/</id><title>Olly Murs - Love You More (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Olly_Murs/Love_You_More_Acoustic/" title="Olly Murs - Love You More (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cold hearted in an empty bed <br>Broken pieces <br>And i know I lost my head <br>But I lied when I said <br>that I could have lived <br>without you <br>Cause I can't live without you <br>If you could see me now <br>from the inside out <br>You'd see the wreckage <br>of a man trying to find a way out <br>I couldn't love you more <br>Love you more <br>Love you more <br>Cause I made my mistakes <br>And you can walk away <br>You know that ain't nobody <br>gonna love you more <br>Ain't nobody gonna love you more <br>Heartbreak and the time it takes <br>From true love to too late <br>Oh man what a mess I've made <br>Well I dug my own grave <br>But I won't live without you <br>No I won't live without you <br>If you could see me now <br>from the inside out <br>You'd see the wreckage <br>of a man trying to find a way out <br>I couldn't love you more <br>Love you more <br>Love you more <br>Cause I made my mistakes <br>And you can walk away <br>You know that ain't nobody <br>gonna love you more <br>Ain't nobody gonna love you more <br>So put your keys away <br>Cause you're not thinking straight <br>You know that ain't nobody <br>gonna love you more <br>Ain't nobody gonna love you more <br>Oh yeah <br>You know that ain't nobody <br>gonna love you more <br>Ain't nobody gonna love you more <br>Cause I made my mistakes <br>And you can walk away <br>You know that <br>ain't nobody <br>gonna love you more <br>Ain't nobody gonna love you more <br>]]></content><category term="Olly Murs" label="Olly Murs"/><category term="Love You More (Acoustic)" label="Love You More (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Olly_Murs/Years__Years_Acoustic/</id><title>Olly Murs - Years &amp; Years (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Olly_Murs/Years__Years_Acoustic/" title="Olly Murs - Years &amp; Years (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I'm alone in the dark <br>And paint a picture inside my mind <br>Of all the things that I want <br>But I never thought I would find <br>And it blows my mind <br>Because there you are by my side <br>Maybe you know maybe you don't <br>But it's a question I have to ask <br>I know we're young <br>and we've got life <br>But life always goes so fast <br>But while you're mine <br>Yeah it feels <br>like time's on our side <br>Years and years forever young <br>Years and years yet to come <br>I take every second <br>of every minute <br>Long as you're in it <br>you know I'm winning <br>Years and years we won't forget <br>The time and place that we met <br>And now I remember <br>we're all so clear <br>You signed your name on my heart <br>Saying you were here <br>No we're not at the end <br>But we're close <br>maybe once or twice <br>We got burned but we learned not <br>to listen to bad advice <br>Now I know you're mine <br>Cause it feels <br>like time's on our side <br>This feeling will never get old <br>or will never be over <br>While you're still mine <br>Years and years forever young <br>Years and years yet to come <br>I take every second <br>of every minute <br>Long as you're in it <br>you know I'm winning <br>Years and years we won't forget <br>The time and place that we met <br>And now remember <br>we're all so clear <br>You signed your name on my heart <br>Saying you were here <br>It doesn't matter where we go <br>It's all I want it's all I know <br>This feeling's never ever <br>getting old <br>Cause all I know <br>Know oh oh <br>Know oh ooh <br>Years and years forever young <br>Years and years yet to come <br>I take every second <br>of every minute <br>Long as you're in it <br>I know I'm winning <br>Years and years we won't forget <br>The time and place that we met <br>And now remember <br>we're all so clear <br>You signed your name on my heart <br>Saying you were here <br>Years and years <br>Years and years <br>Years and years <br>You signed your name on my heart <br>Saying you were here <br>Years and years <br>Years and years <br>Years and years <br>You signed your name on my heart <br>Saying you were here <br>]]></content><category term="Olly Murs" label="Olly Murs"/><category term="Years &amp; Years (Acoustic)" label="Years &amp; Years (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Olly_Murs/Grow_Up_Acoustic/</id><title>Olly Murs - Grow Up (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Olly_Murs/Grow_Up_Acoustic/" title="Olly Murs - Grow Up (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I thought about you the other day <br>What the hell happened with you and me <br>Cause, oh, ain't no lovin' no more <br>You ain't as cool as you used to be <br>Closer to the mirror than you are to me <br>I said, oh, had to show you that door <br><br>Someday I hope we can fix it, 'cause I ain't too proud to try <br>Say hi to your friends, and if they ever ask you why <br>We don't talk <br><br>Know you gotta grow up <br>Ain't you sick of being immature <br>Talkin' loud 'cause you're insecure <br>You always turn it up, turn it up, turn it up, c'mon <br>Why you always gotta show off <br>You're so vain that I already know <br>That when you hear this on the radio <br>You're gonna turn it up, turn it up, turn it up <br><br>'Cause it's all about you oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo <br>It's all about you oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo <br><br>Now you said some stuff that you can't take back <br>How did you think that I would react <br>Cause oh, you must be out of your mind <br>How did we go straight from love to hate <br>Now it's so deep that we can't be mates <br>I said, oh, we should give it some time <br><br>Someday I hope we can fix it, 'cause I ain't too proud to try <br>Say hi to your friends, and if they ever ask you why <br>We don't talk <br><br>Know you gotta grow up <br>Ain't you sick of being immature <br>Talkin' loud 'cause you're insecure <br>You always turn it up, turn it up, turn it up, c'mon <br>Why you always gotta show off <br>You're so vain that I already know <br>That when you hear this on the radio <br>You're gonna turn it up, turn it up, turn it up <br><br>'Cause it's all about you oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo <br>It's all about you oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo <br><br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>Anytime you start it <br>You're growing up a little darlin' <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>Anytime you start it <br>You're growing up a little darlin' <br><br>Know you gotta grow up Know you gotta grow up <br>Ain't you sick of being immature Ain't you sick of being immature <br>Talkin' loud 'cause you insecure <br>You always turn it up, turn it up, turn it up, c'mon <br>Why you always gotta show off Why you always gotta show off <br>You're so vain that I already know You're so vain that I already know <br>That when you hear this on the radio <br>You're gonna turn it up, turn it up, turn it up <br><br>'Cause it's all about you oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>It's all about you oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Anytime you start it <br>You're growing up a little darlin' <br>'Cause it's all about you oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>It's all about you oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br>Anytime you start it <br>You're growing up a little darlin']]></content><category term="Olly Murs" label="Olly Murs"/><category term="Grow Up (Acoustic)" label="Grow Up (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Olly_Murs/You_Dont_Know_Love_Acoustic/</id><title>Olly Murs - You Don`t Know Love (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:54:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:54:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Olly_Murs/You_Dont_Know_Love_Acoustic/" title="Olly Murs - You Don`t Know Love (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't wanna be your lover <br>I don't wanna be your fool <br>Pick me up whenever you want it <br>Throw me down when you're through <br>'Cause I've learned more <br>from what's missing <br>It's about me and not about you <br>I know I made some bad decisions <br>But my last one was you <br>Thanks to you I know lies <br>lies lies <br>How it feels when love dies <br>dies dies <br>And you told me goodbye bye bye <br>I don't know when it's over <br>when it's over <br>You don't know love <br>'til it tears up your heart <br>And cuts and it leaves you <br>with scars <br>You're still feeling <br>You don't know love <br>You don't know love <br>You say I can't do better <br>Better than someone like you <br>What I feel <br>can't write in a letter <br>So I wrote this for you <br>Thanks to you I know lies <br>lies lies <br>How it feels when love dies <br>dies dies <br>And you told me goodbye bye bye <br>I don't know when it's over <br>when it's over <br>You don't know love <br>'til it tears up your heart <br>And cuts and it leaves you <br>with scars <br>You're still feeling <br>You don't know love <br>You don't know love <br>You don't know love <br>'til it feels like you died <br>when it's missing <br>It leaves you blind with no vision <br>You don't know love <br>You don't know love <br>you you you you <br>You won't ever get no better <br>you you you you <br>Got a lot more to lose <br>you you you you <br>You won't ever ever get it <br>You don't know love <br>You don't know love <br>You don't know love <br>You don't know love <br>'til it tears up your heart <br>And cuts and it leaves you <br>with scars <br>You're still feeling <br>You don't know love <br>You don't know love <br>You don't know love <br>'til it feels like you died <br>when it's missing <br>It leaves you blind with no vision <br>You don't know love <br>You don't know love <br>You don't know love <br>]]></content><category term="Olly Murs" label="Olly Murs"/><category term="You Don`t Know Love (Acoustic)" label="You Don`t Know Love (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ycplayer/그러려니_Feat_홍가/</id><title>Ycplayer - 그러려니 (Feat. 홍가) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:55:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:55:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ycplayer/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%AC%EB%A0%A4%EB%8B%88_Feat_%ED%99%8D%EA%B0%80/" title="Ycplayer - 그러려니 (Feat. 홍가) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[헤어질 때 넌 말하지 <br>매번 BYE BYE <br>싸우고 난 뒤에 오는 <br>문자 잘살아 <br>남이 라는 듯이 뒤돌아 <br>서서 잘 가 <br>딴사람 만나 <br>행복하게 잘살아 <br>마음에도 없는 소리 <br>나는 간섭하지 않아 굳이 <br>철부지 도 아니고 이게 뭔지 <br>삶과 같애 사랑도 <br>사람과 사람이 벌리지 <br>때론 지루하다가 달콤해 <br>잘 지내다가 또다시 <br>또 다투네 <br>비지니스 갑과 을 <br>다를 바 없네 <br>행복과 불행은 <br>늘 공존해 삶에 <br>가네 가네 또 떠나 가네 <br>다시 오네 오네 <br>또 다시 오네 <br>봄 여름 가을 겨울 <br>순환 되듯이 <br>마음도 돌고 돌아 <br>다시 제자리 오지 <br>그러려니 해 <br>너는 떠나고 <br>난 그러려니 해 <br>아쉬울 때 또 찾고 <br>난 그러려니 해 <br>날 사랑한다고 <br>난 그러려니 해 <br>레파토리는 반복 된다고 <br>자기 입장에서 만 <br>말하지 사랑 <br>전부 다 이기적인 거야 <br>그게 사람 <br>모두 머릿속 계산기 <br>두드려 살아 <br>부인하지 마라 지내다 <br>보면 알아 <br>그래서 거짓말을 해 <br>그리고 떠보기도 해 <br>마음을 확 열지 못해 <br>그러면서 상대에게 <br>일관성을 요구해 어이없게 <br>항상 부족함을 드러내지 <br>말로는 자신감 가지라 하지 <br>주도권 쥐고 싶어해 <br>사랑의 사장 <br>자기 뜻대로 만들려고 <br>하지 마라 <br>우린 모두 부족한 인간 <br>사랑도 마찬가지야 <br>우리는 불완전 하니까 <br>같이 함께 하려는 거야 <br>그러려니 해 <br>너는 떠나고 <br>난 그러려니 해 <br>아쉬울 때 또 찾고 <br>난 그러려니 해 <br>날 사랑한다고 <br>난 그러려니 해 <br>레파토리는 반복 된다고 <br>그러려니 해 <br>너는 떠나고 <br>난 그러려니 해 <br>아쉬울 때 또 찾고 <br>난 그러려니 해 <br>날 사랑한다고 <br>난 그러려니 해 <br>레파토리는 반복 된다고 <br>]]></content><category term="Ycplayer" label="Ycplayer"/><category term="그러려니 (Feat. 홍가)" label="그러려니 (Feat. 홍가)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한그루/한숨아/</id><title>한그루 - 한숨아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:55:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:55:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EA%B7%B8%EB%A3%A8/%ED%95%9C%EC%88%A8%EC%95%84/" title="한그루 - 한숨아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세상은 그랬어 <br>언제나 나에게 <br>모든 것들을 <br>뺏어갔지 희망조차 <br>한숨아 한숨아 <br>제발 멈춰 <br>더 이상 <br>울고 싶지 않아 <br>희미해 눈앞이 희미해 <br>눈물이 앞을 가려 <br>무엇도 보이지가 않아 <br>빛바랜 사진 속 <br>시간은 멈춰있어 <br>내일은 없다고 <br>이대로 가슴을 <br>찢으며 있어 <br>세상은 그랬어 <br>언제나 나에게 <br>모든 것들을 <br>뺏어갔지 희망조차 <br>한숨아 한숨아 <br>제발 멈춰 <br>더 이상 <br>울고 싶지 않아 <br>심장이 터질 듯 아파도 <br>내 가슴속 <br>뜨거운 사랑은 <br>영원할 테니까 <br>시간이 흐르면 <br>모두 잊혀지겠지 <br>나 혼자 쓸쓸히 <br>기억하겠지 <br>걱정 말고 떠나 <br>세상은 그랬어 <br>언제나 나에게 <br>모든 것들을 <br>뺏어갔지 희망조차 <br>한숨아 한숨아 <br>제발 멈춰 <br>더 이상 <br>울고 싶지 않아 <br>다시 되돌아가고 싶어 <br>예전의 나로 돌아갈래 <br>미치도록 사랑받으며 <br>살아갈래 <br>세상은 그랬어 <br>언제나 나에게 <br>모든 것들을 <br>뺏어갔지 희망조차 <br>한숨아 한숨아 <br>제발 멈춰 <br>더 이상 <br>울고 싶지 않아 <br>]]></content><category term="한그루" label="한그루"/><category term="한숨아" label="한숨아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/티어라이너/Red_Forest_Feat_정은수/</id><title>티어라이너 - Red Forest (Feat. 정은수) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:55:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:55:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8B%B0%EC%96%B4%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EB%84%88/Red_Forest_Feat_%EC%A0%95%EC%9D%80%EC%88%98/" title="티어라이너 - Red Forest (Feat. 정은수) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Why can't you see <br>You don't know anything <br>You came at the night <br>You don't know anything <br>Covered your eyes <br>You never see me <br>What did you see at that night <br>Why do you want to leave me now <br>I want you to stay with me <br>Anyone can let you down <br>Why can't you see <br>You covered your mouth <br>You never answer me <br>Waves keep making <br>on music rhythmically <br>What would you say if I told you so <br>Didn't see it before <br>Now I see <br>Why do you want to leave me now <br>Yes we need more air my love <br>Hours turn into days soon <br>Nothing's left <br>]]></content><category term="티어라이너" label="티어라이너"/><category term="Red Forest (Feat. 정은수)" label="Red Forest (Feat. 정은수)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임주은/선물/</id><title>임주은 - 선물 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:55:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:55:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%A3%BC%EC%9D%80/%EC%84%A0%EB%AC%BC/" title="임주은 - 선물 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈을 감고 두 손 모아 <br>주님께 기도해 <br>나만을 위한 주님의 계획 <br>이제 세상에 전할래 <br>눈이 와 세상에 <br>내려진 하나님 사랑 <br>우리 마음속에 가득 찬 사랑 <br>잊고 있던 우리 맘 속에 <br>내려주신 이 선물 <br>보내주신 그 사랑 <br>한 번 더 일어서라고 내게 <br>손을 내밀어 주는 분 예수 <br>나를 둘러싼 세상의 노래 <br>내 맘을 무너뜨린 노래 <br>하지만 우리들 마음속에 <br>내려주시는 그 사랑 <br>눈이 와 세상에 <br>내려진 하나님 사랑 <br>우리 마음속에 가득 찬 사랑 <br>잊고 있던 우리 맘 속에 <br>내려주신 이 선물 <br>보내주신 그 사랑 <br>나나나 나나나나나나 나나 <br>나나나 나나나나나나 나나 <br>나나나 나나나나나나 나나 <br>조금씩 멀어진다고 이젠 <br>버틸 수 없을 거라고 <br>나를 둘러싼 세상의 노래 <br>내 맘을 무너뜨린 노래 <br>하지만 우리들 마음속에 <br>내려주시는 그 사랑 <br>눈이 와 세상에 <br>내려진 하나님 사랑 <br>우리 마음속에 가득 찬 사랑 <br>잊고 있던 우리 맘 속에 <br>내려주신 이 선물 <br>보내주신 그 사랑 <br>창밖에 하얗게 내리는 <br>저 눈을 좀 봐 <br>주님 내게 주신 한 없는 사랑 <br>감사해 사랑해 날 위한 선물 <br>오직 나에게 주신 선물 <br>예수님 그분 <br>나나나나 나 나나 <br>Merry Christmas <br>]]></content><category term="임주은" label="임주은"/><category term="선물" label="선물"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이안_Ean/또_그때처럼/</id><title>이안 (E.an) - 또 그때처럼 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:55:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:55:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%88_Ean/%EB%98%90_%EA%B7%B8%EB%95%8C%EC%B2%98%EB%9F%BC/" title="이안 (E.an) - 또 그때처럼 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이젠 그만했으면 해 <br>우린 아니라고 해 <br>억지로 끌고 가는 건 너도 <br>나도 너무 힘만 드니까 <br>잠깐 뜸 들이다 말했지 난 <br>우리 이런 거 처음도 아닌데 <br> 왜 또 반복하는데 <br>사실은 너무 힘들었다고 <br>간신히 날 참아왔었다고 <br>더 이상은 우리 안될 것 같아 <br>여기까지가 <br>우리의 마지막이라고 <br>또 그때처럼 네 손 꼭 붙잡고 <br>따뜻하게 안고 싶어도 <br>또 그때처럼 홀로 남겨진 <br>날 보는 게 두려워 <br>또 그때처럼 널 또 그때처럼 널 <br>또 그때처럼 널 난 못해 못해 <br>눈치를 못 챘었지 <br>아니 모른척했었지 <br>다신 날 떠나지 않을 거라고 <br>안심했었지 <br>같은 곳만 바라보자 <br>늘 얘기하면서 <br>내 뒤로 멀어져 가는 <br>널 보지 못했어 <br>더 이상은 우리 안될 것 같아 <br>여기까지가 <br>우리의 마지막이라고 <br>또 그때처럼 네 손 꼭 붙잡고 <br>따뜻하게 안고 싶어도 <br>또 그때처럼 홀로 남겨진 <br>날 보는 게 두려워 <br>다시 또 한번 나를 <br>안아줄 순 없니 <br>멀어져 가는 <br>내 손잡아 줄 수 없니 <br>나를 바라보던 예전 눈빛으로 <br>다시 돌아와 줘 <br>또 그때처럼 네 손 꼭 붙잡고 <br>따뜻하게 안고 <br>또 그때처럼 홀로 남겨진 날 <br>보는 게 두려워 <br>또 그때처럼 널 또 그때처럼 널 <br>또 그때처럼 너 없이는 안되 <br>]]></content><category term="이안 (E.an)" label="이안 (E.an)"/><category term="또 그때처럼" label="또 그때처럼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/형지/그대로/</id><title>형지 - 그대로 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:55:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:55:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%98%95%EC%A7%80/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%A1%9C/" title="형지 - 그대로 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[엄마 그 때 기억해요 <br>작기만 하던 어린 내가 <br>온 몸이 다 부서지게 <br>버텼던 그 때 기억해요 <br>난 괜찮아요 <br>너무 걱정하지 마세요 <br>웃으며 말해도 내 걱정뿐이던 <br>언제 울릴지 모를 전활 붙잡고 <br>기도할 엄마 손 <br>잡아주고 싶었어요 <br>엄마 참 아름다운 우리 엄마 <br>그저 젊음으로 빛나던 시간들을 <br>깊어진 눈으로 쓸어 내리죠 <br>엄마 참 아름다운 우리 엄마 <br>오랫동안 그대를 안아줄게요 <br>아빠 그 때 기억해요 <br>어렸던 내가 걱정 되도 <br>따뜻하게 안아주며 <br>믿어준 그 때 기억해요 <br>예쁜 우리 딸 <br>잘 해낼 거라 말했던 <br>보고픈 아빠 손 <br>잡아주고 싶었어요 <br>아빠 나의 영웅 우리 아빠 <br>그저 젊음으로 빛나던 시간들을 <br>깊어진 눈으로 쓸어 내리죠 <br>아빠 나의 영웅 우리 아빠 <br>오랫동안 그대로 <br>곁에 있어주세요 <br>그대 참 아름다운 <br>세월 지났어도 <br>엄마 참 아름다운 우리 엄마 <br>찬란하고 꿈 많던 그대 이름들을 <br>그댈 닮은 내게 안겨줬나요 <br>아빠 나의 영웅 우리 아빠 <br>그댈 그대로 오래 사랑할게요 <br>]]></content><category term="형지" label="형지"/><category term="그대로" label="그대로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오태석/날_부르는_너/</id><title>오태석 - 날 부르는 너 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:55:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:55:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%ED%83%9C%EC%84%9D/%EB%82%A0_%EB%B6%80%EB%A5%B4%EB%8A%94_%EB%84%88/" title="오태석 - 날 부르는 너 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[줄곧 난 너만을 그리며 <br>다 견뎌냈어 오늘도 <br>집으로 돌아가는 길 <br>내 주변의 온 빛들이 <br>길을 비추고 <br>조였던 마음이 풀어져 <br>미소 가득한 내 얼굴 <br>너를 볼 수 있음에 <br>나 벅차 오르는 가슴 도저히 <br>주체를 못하네 <br>타오르는 저 노을 너머로 <br>날 기다리는 너 <br>그리고 우리만의 <br>비밀 정원에 다다른다 <br>나 어느새 저기 네가 보여 <br>날 부르는 너를 <br>이 멀리서 바라보기만 해도 <br>정말 아름다워 나 당장에 달려가 <br>꼭 끌어안겠어 너를 <br>이 차가웠던 도시의 밤을 <br>따듯하게 녹여주네 <br>네 생각에 모든 걸 <br>해낼 수 있었다는 걸 <br>너에게 돌아가던 길 <br>얼른 말해주고 싶은 <br>맘이었다고 <br>네 앞에 서있는 난 말야 <br>너와 함께 있을 때야 <br>가장 나다워지네 <br>나 온전히 진심으로 <br>너만을 사랑할 수 있어 <br>피어 오르는 주방의 연기와 <br>맛있는 냄새가 풍겨와 <br>포근한 온기에 감싸여 너를 본다 <br>나 눈물 나게 너를 사랑한다 <br>날 부르는 너를 이 앞에서 <br>바라보기만 해도 <br>정말 아름다워 너의 손을 잡고서 <br>꼭 놓지 않겠어 너를 <br>넌 차가웠던 내 손을 잡고 <br>따듯하게 녹여주네 <br>온 세상이 <br>온통 너로 가득 찬 이 밤 <br>나 노래하네 너를 위해 <br>줄곧 난 너만을 그리며 <br>견뎌냈어 오늘도 <br>날 부르는 너와 <br>너에게로 달려가고 있는 나 <br>너를 사랑하는 내가 여기 서있어 <br>꼭 끌어안아줘 나를 <br>언제까지나 우리의 하늘 <br>아름답게 물들이네 <br>]]></content><category term="오태석" label="오태석"/><category term="날 부르는 너" label="날 부르는 너"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Culture_Code/Make_Me_Move_Feat_Karra/</id><title>Culture Code - Make Me Move (Feat. Karra) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:55:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:55:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Culture_Code/Make_Me_Move_Feat_Karra/" title="Culture Code - Make Me Move (Feat. Karra) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Open eyes <br>Through the waves cut through me <br>Hypnotised <br>By the sounds I'm breatthing in <br>Hold tight, hold tight <br>Can't make calls collide <br>Hold tight, hold tight, hold tight <br><br>Tripping lights <br>Paint the skies <br>All because of you <br><br>Tripping lights <br>Paint the skies <br>Only you can make me move <br>You, you can make me moveee <br>Can make me moveee <br>You you can make me moveee <br>Can make me <br><br>Move <br>You, you can make me moveee <br>Can make me <br>So alive <br>Make it last forever <br>Stopping tight <br>Your arms surrendering <br><br>Hold tight, hold tight <br>Can't make calls collide <br>Hold tight, hold tight, hold tight <br><br>Tripping lights <br>Paint the skies <br>All because of you <br><br>Tripping lights <br>Paint the skies <br>Only you can make me moveee <br>You, you can make me moveee <br>Can make me moveee <br>You you can make me moveee <br>Can make me <br><br>Move <br>Can make me moveee <br>You, you can make me moveee <br>Can make meee]]></content><category term="Culture Code" label="Culture Code"/><category term="Make Me Move (Feat. Karra)" label="Make Me Move (Feat. Karra)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Unknown_Brain/Superhero_Feat_Chris_Linton/</id><title>Unknown Brain - Superhero (Feat. Chris Linton) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:56:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:56:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Unknown_Brain/Superhero_Feat_Chris_Linton/" title="Unknown Brain - Superhero (Feat. Chris Linton) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Like you, be strong, to hold the powers of the sun <br>To dream, believe, in strength now I'm the only one, only one <br>I was an ordinary boy <br>Until I broke the rules, my life destroyed, my life destroyed <br>Until I woke awake, scream my mind I shout the ground shakes <br>How much can I take My mind will break <br>Will it break <br>What can I take <br>Can I be your superhero <br>Superhero <br><br>Can I be your superhero <br>Superhero, superhero, superhero <br><br>Fly up, away, it's the first time of today, today <br>To dream, believe, you are the strength, you're all i need, need, need <br>Oh, gonna give it a shot, only one of me, to shoot you off from the enemy <br>Your superhero <br>Your superhero <br><br>Can I be your superhero <br>Superhero, superhero, superhero <br>Can I be your superhero]]></content><category term="Unknown Brain" label="Unknown Brain"/><category term="Superhero (Feat. Chris Linton)" label="Superhero (Feat. Chris Linton)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cartoon/I_Remember_U_Feat_Juri_Pootsmann/</id><title>Cartoon - I Remember U (Feat. Juri Pootsmann) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:56:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:56:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cartoon/I_Remember_U_Feat_Juri_Pootsmann/" title="Cartoon - I Remember U (Feat. Juri Pootsmann) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I close my eyes, I can almost see it <br>When I take a breath you fill up my lungs <br>And if my mind works backwards just for a minute <br>I hold on to you, before the memory's gone <br><br>I remember u <br>You lift my spirit <br>With you, high is all I'm feeling <br>Remember how we felt alive <br><br>I remember u <br>You make me stronger <br>Can't go without it much longer <br>Remember, remember <br><br>I remember u <br>You lift my spirit <br>With you, high is all I'm feeling <br>Remember how we felt alive <br><br>I remember u <br>You make me stronger <br>Can't go without it much longer <br>Remember, remember <br><br>O o o o oh, o o o oh 4x <br><br>When I close my eyes I can almost see it <br>When I take a breath you fill up my lungs <br>And if my mind works backwards for just a minute <br>I'm all over you, before the memory's gone <br><br>I remember u <br>You lift my spirit <br>With you, high is all I'm feeling <br>Remember how we felt alive <br><br>I remember u <br>You make me stronger <br>Can't go without end much longer <br>Remember, remember <br><br>I remember u <br>You lift my spirit <br>With you, high is all I'm feeling <br>Remember how we felt alive <br><br>I remember u <br>You make me stronger <br>Can't go without it much longer <br>Remember, remember <br><br>O o o o oh, o o o oh 4x <br><br>I remember u]]></content><category term="Cartoon" label="Cartoon"/><category term="I Remember U (Feat. Juri Pootsmann)" label="I Remember U (Feat. Juri Pootsmann)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jo_Cohen/We_Are/</id><title>Jo Cohen - We Are - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:56:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:56:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jo_Cohen/We_Are/" title="Jo Cohen - We Are - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh oh oh <br>Reaching for the stars <br>I wonder where You are <br>Oh oh oh <br>We are <br>We are dreaming in the dark <br>We are nothing more than dust <br>I search but You stay lost <br>We are <br>We are reaching for the stars <br>But We're making this too hard <br>And I wonder where You are <br>Mysterious <br>That's the part You always show <br>You're soncurious <br>Baby, You should take it slow <br>Mysterious <br>That's the part you always show <br>You're so curious <br>Baby, You shold take it slow <br>We're dreaming in the dark <br>We are nothing more than dust <br>I search but you stay lost <br>I search but you stay lost <br>We're reaching for the stars <br>But We're making this too hard <br>And I wonder where You are <br>And I wonder where You are <br>Mysterious <br>That's the part you always show <br>You're so curious <br>Baby, You should take it slow <br>Mysterious <br>That's the part You always show <br>You're so curious <br>Baby, You should take it slow <br>Oh oh oh <br>Reaching for the stars <br>I wonder where You are <br>Oh oh oh]]></content><category term="Jo Cohen" label="Jo Cohen"/><category term="We Are" label="We Are"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/K-391/Earth/</id><title>K-391 - Earth - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:56:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:56:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/K-391/Earth/" title="K-391 - Earth - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you want to get off the darkest ground <br>But gravity pulls you straight down <br>Earth from a birdseye view <br>You should go feathers and see this too <br>When you want to get off the darkest ground <br>But gravity pulls you straight down <br>When you want to get off the darkest ground <br>But gravity pulls you straight down <br>Clear skies <br>When you want to get off the darkest ground <br>But gravity pulls you straight down <br>Earth from a birdseye view <br>You should go feathers and see this too <br>When you want to get off the darkest ground <br>But gravity pulls you straight down <br>When you want to get off the darkest ground <br>But gravity pulls you straight down <br>Clear skies]]></content><category term="K-391" label="K-391"/><category term="Earth" label="Earth"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ship_Wrek/Pain_Feat_Mia_Vaile/</id><title>Ship Wrek - Pain (Feat. Mia Vaile) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:56:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:56:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ship_Wrek/Pain_Feat_Mia_Vaile/" title="Ship Wrek - Pain (Feat. Mia Vaile) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wherever love goes there is also misery <br>It's no mystery <br>And you and i, we got history, yeah <br>Wherever love flows there is also tragedy <br>When we're in too deep <br>And you and i, we got history, yeah <br>Go look in the mirror <br>Say Hey, I'm sorry for all the pain <br>I'm sorry for all the pain <br>Go look in the mirror <br>Say Hey, I'm sorry for all the pain <br>I'm sorry for all the pain <br>Go look in the mirror <br>Say Hey, I'm sorry for all the pain <br>I'm sorry for all the pain <br>My love it grows with the memories <br>Like a symphony <br>And you and i, we got history, yeah <br>And when you're alone <br>Do you say my name <br>Or you say her name Yeah <br>My love it grows with the memories <br>Like a symphony <br>And you and i, we got history, yeah <br>And when you're alone <br>Wherever love flows there is also tragedy <br>When we're in too deep <br>And you and i, we got history, yeah]]></content><category term="Ship Wrek" label="Ship Wrek"/><category term="Pain (Feat. Mia Vaile)" label="Pain (Feat. Mia Vaile)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JPB/Feels_Right_Feat_Yung_Fusion/</id><title>JPB - Feels Right (Feat. Yung Fusion) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:56:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:56:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/JPB/Feels_Right_Feat_Yung_Fusion/" title="JPB - Feels Right (Feat. Yung Fusion) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Whatcha gonna do <br>This is just for us now <br><br>Yeah <br>I can never ever find the right words <br>And there's no way this is real life <br>There's no telling you're the right girl <br>So I can only say that it feels right <br><br>It feels right <br>It feels right <br>It feels right <br>Yeah <br>I can only say that it feels right <br>It feels right <br>It feels right <br>It feels right <br>Yeah <br>I can only say that it feels right <br><br>That it feels right <br><br>It feels right <br>So right <br>So right <br>So right <br><br>I'm just going with the gut <br>Never had a doubt, felt like this is just a must <br>Put me in perspective, I'm the deepest in the cut <br>Everybody tuning in, but this is just for us now <br>We know I ain't balling yet <br>Hoes wanna holla, oh no I don't call them back <br>Girl let me see your, hold it down, we gonna have a blast <br>Because, I just wanna know what you are going to do with all of that <br>Ain't gotta say a word <br>I know what's up <br>You can have it all <br>Watch me whip it all <br>I'll admit it <br>You got me feeling hella love <br>Even when it's going down, know that we gonna live it up <br>Young shot caller, always been a baller <br>Know that you are the one, I can feel it in my heart <br>Yeah <br>Won't stop charging <br>Only come harder <br>I can see you and I, way beyond the stars girl <br><br>I can never ever find the right words <br>And there's no way this is real life <br>There's no telling you're the right girl <br>So I can only say that it feels right <br><br>It feels right <br>It feels right <br>It feels right <br><br>It feels right <br><br>It feels right <br><br>So right <br>So right <br>So right <br><br>I'm just going with the gut <br>Never had a doubt, felt like this is just a must <br>Put me in perspective, I'm the deepest in the cut <br>Everybody tuning in, but this is just for us now]]></content><category term="JPB" label="JPB"/><category term="Feels Right (Feat. Yung Fusion)" label="Feels Right (Feat. Yung Fusion)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Glude/Identity/</id><title>Glude - Identity - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:56:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:56:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Glude/Identity/" title="Glude - Identity - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We wanna be, wanna be all saints <br>Trying hard to be someone else <br>All we want, all we want is please <br>Giving us, giving no time to breathe <br><br>This is our identity <br>This is our identity <br>This is our identity <br><br>When we're under summer sky <br>We can't help it, we're by your side <br>In the end when the winter comes <br>We turn our backs, we can't help, we're gone <br><br>This is our identity <br>This is our identity]]></content><category term="Glude" label="Glude"/><category term="Identity" label="Identity"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Razihel/Love_U/</id><title>Razihel - Love U - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:56:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:56:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Razihel/Love_U/" title="Razihel - Love U - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oooh, oh, oh, oh, oh <br>Baby <br>Oooh, oh, oh, oh, oh <br>Baby, baby <br>Oooh, oh, oh, oh, oh <br>Baby <br>Oooh, oh, oh, oh, oh <br>Baby, my babe, bye, bye <br>Oooh, oh, oh, oh, oh <br>Baby <br>Oooh, oh, oh, oh, oh <br>Baby, baby, my babe <br>Oooh, oh, oh, oh, oh <br>Baby <br>Oooh, oh, oh, oh, oh <br>Baby, my babe <br><br>We don't need this <br>But we don't need this <br>'Cause we don't need this <br>Oh, baby, get it on <br>Oh, I feel, feel, feel, my life <br>We don't need this <br>But we don't need this <br>'Cause we don't need this <br>Oh, baby, get it on <br>Oh, I feel, feel, feel, my life <br>Get it on <br>We don't need this <br>But we don't need this <br>'Cause we don't need this <br>Oh, baby, get it on <br>Oh, I feel, feel, feel, my life <br><br>I, I, I, I, I <br>I, I, I, I love you <br>I, I, I, miss you <br>I, I, I love you <br>I, I, I, I <br>I, I, I, I love you <br>I, I, I, miss you <br>I, I, I love you <br>We don't need this <br>I, I, I, I love you <br>I, I, I, miss you <br>I, I, I love you <br>I, I, I, I <br>I, I, I, I love you <br>I, I, I, miss you <br>I, I, I love you <br>I, I, I, I <br><br> Didn't understand this part at all <br><br>We don't need this <br>But we don't need this <br>'Cause we don't need this <br>Oh, baby, get it on <br>Oh, I feel, feel, feel, my life <br>Get it on <br>We don't need this <br>But we don't need this <br>'Cause we don't need this <br>Oh, baby, get it on <br>Oh, I feel, feel, feel, my life <br>You're my babe <br><br>I, I, I, I, I <br>I, I, I, I love you <br>I, I, I, miss you <br>I, I, I love you <br>I, I, I, I <br>I, I, I, I love you <br>I, I, I, miss you <br>I, I, I love you <br>We don't need this <br>I, I, I, I love you <br>I, I, I, miss you <br>I, I, I love you <br>I, I, I, I <br>I, I, I, I love you <br>I, I, I, miss you <br>I, I, I love you <br>I, I, I, I]]></content><category term="Razihel" label="Razihel"/><category term="Love U" label="Love U"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Retrovision/Puzzle/</id><title>Retrovision - Puzzle - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:56:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:56:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Retrovision/Puzzle/" title="Retrovision - Puzzle - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If I Got To You <br>Ain't got to you <br>If I Got To You <br>Ain't got to you <br>If I Got To You <br>Ain't got to you <br>If I Got To You <br>Ain't got to you <br>Crack it <br><br>If I Got To You <br>Ain't got to you <br>If I Got To You <br>Ain't got to you <br>If I Got To You <br>Ain't got to you <br>If I Got To You <br>Ain't got to you <br>Crack it]]></content><category term="Retrovision" label="Retrovision"/><category term="Puzzle" label="Puzzle"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Big_Cream/Gamechanger/</id><title>Big Cream - Gamechanger - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:56:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:56:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Big_Cream/Gamechanger/" title="Big Cream - Gamechanger - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I would like to bring the sun on your face <br>I just wanna light the fire in your eyes <br>Friendly giants pick their side on your sorrow]]></content><category term="Big Cream" label="Big Cream"/><category term="Gamechanger" label="Gamechanger"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Big_Cream/Gatlin/</id><title>Big Cream - Gatlin - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:56:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:56:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Big_Cream/Gatlin/" title="Big Cream - Gatlin - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let me spit into mire and let me see <br>blood signs of the sacrifice <br>of your tragic life <br>so I can pray my evil god <br>In this day with a rusted sun, a rusted sun <br>Buried by the children of the corn <br>Leave me here in the fire and let me see <br>the holy wheat under the sky <br>of this sultry night <br>Now I can pray my evil lord <br>In this may with a rusted sun, a rusted sun <br>Buried by the children of the corn <br><br>He walks behind the rows]]></content><category term="Big Cream" label="Big Cream"/><category term="Gatlin" label="Gatlin"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Max_Him/No_Escape/</id><title>Max Him - No Escape - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:57:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:57:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Max_Him/No_Escape/" title="Max Him - No Escape - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Through the twilight I can see <br>Faces staring back at me <br>I can tell what's on their minds <br>And the reason isn't hard to find <br><br>Never it was <br>If I thought twice <br>Now I've got to pay the price <br>Pay the price for all your sins <br>This is where they're reckoning again <br><br>Hey, hey, hey <br>Hey, hey, hey <br>No escape for me <br><br>Hey, hey, hey <br>Hey, hey, hey <br>No escape for me <br><br>Turn my back from crying eyes <br>No escape I realized <br>They can see what's on my mind <br>And the reason isn't hard to find <br><br>Hey, hey, hey <br>Hey, hey, hey <br>No escape for me <br><br>Hey, hey, hey <br>Hey, hey, hey <br>No escape for me]]></content><category term="Max Him" label="Max Him"/><category term="No Escape" label="No Escape"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Savage/Only_You/</id><title>Savage - Only You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:57:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:57:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Savage/Only_You/" title="Savage - Only You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Only you <br>When I really get nothing to do <br>Can't be true <br>Only you <br>When I'm looking for somebody new <br>You're the clue <br>Only change my mind <br>When I feel so blind <br>Then you make me see <br>Love is free <br>Only you <br>When I look at your eyes in the blue <br>Love me too <br>Only you <br>When your teardrops are lit by the moon <br>Laugh too soon <br>Only change my mind <br>When I feel so blind <br>Then you make me see <br>Love is free <br><br>Don't push me aside my love's alive <br>Don't leave me to die you will survive <br>You hold me so tight turn off the light <br>It all seems so right <br>Only you <br>When I really got nothing to do <br>Can't be true <br>Only you <br>When I look at your eyes in the blue <br>Love me too <br>Only change my mind <br>When I feel so blind <br>Then you make me see <br>Love is free <br><br>Don't push me aside my love's alive <br>Don't leave me to die you will survive <br>You hold me so tight turn off the light <br>It all seems so right <br><br>Don't push me aside my love's alive <br>Don't leave me to die you will survive <br>You hold me so tight turn off the light <br>It all seems so right <br><br>Don't push me aside my love's alive <br>Don't leave me to die you will survive <br>You hold me so tight turn off the light <br>It all seems so right <br><br>Don't push me aside my love's alive <br>Don't leave me to die you will survive <br>You hold me so tight turn off the light <br>It all seems so right]]></content><category term="Savage" label="Savage"/><category term="Only You" label="Only You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lian_Ross/Say_U_Will_Never/</id><title>Lian Ross - Say U Will Never - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:57:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:57:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lian_Ross/Say_U_Will_Never/" title="Lian Ross - Say U Will Never - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look into my eyes and tell me what you see <br>If this meant to show one say it's mystery <br>Since the day I met you baby I can feel <br>Deep inside my heart I know it's real <br>You have turned my dreams into reality <br>Baby not my hunter, you're sweet melody <br>It's the same old feeling baby, it's so real <br>Deep inside my heart I know it's real <br><br>Say you'll never, never, never go away <br>Say you'll never, never, never never go away <br><br>Yesterday my life was just a history <br>Now I feel like mastering my destiny <br>It's the same old feeling baby, it's so real <br>Deep inside my heart I know it's real <br><br>Say you'll never, never, never go away <br>Say you'll never, never, never never go away]]></content><category term="Lian Ross" label="Lian Ross"/><category term="Say U Will Never" label="Say U Will Never"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Linda_Jo_Rizzo/Heartflash/</id><title>Linda Jo Rizzo - Heartflash - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:57:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:57:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Linda_Jo_Rizzo/Heartflash/" title="Linda Jo Rizzo - Heartflash - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You can travel around the world <br>You can have all kinds of girls <br>But you never gonna find a one <br>To love you like I do <br>You can try to walk away <br>And your heart can go astray <br>But you'll come back to me <br>You knew it at the stars <br><br>Flash baby, flash maybe <br><br>Flash in the night <br>Let me feel your body melt in mine <br>Heartflash tonight <br>Whisper Ti amo all through the night <br><br>Flash in the night <br>Never knew your touch can be so nice <br>Wanna heartflash tonight <br>I can't resist your charm <br>Turn me on <br>Now I'll understand <br>That you're not a one lady man <br>My friends said Beware <br>But you know I don't care <br><br>Flash, flash <br><br>In the edge we always knew <br>It's gonna be me and you <br>Don't turn away <br>Baby hear what I say <br><br>Flash baby, Flash maybe <br><br>Flash in the night <br>Let me feel your body melt in mine <br>Heartflash tonight <br>Whisper Ti amo all through the night <br>Flash in the night <br>Never knew your touch can be so nice <br>Wanna heartflash tonight <br>I can't resist your charm <br>Turn me on <br><br>Flash in the night <br>Let me feel your body melt in mine <br>Heartflash tonight <br>Whisper Ti amo all through the night <br><br>Flash in the night <br>Never knew your touch can be so nice <br>Wanna heartflash tonight <br>I can't resist your charm, flash]]></content><category term="Linda Jo Rizzo" label="Linda Jo Rizzo"/><category term="Heartflash" label="Heartflash"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/P_Lion/Dreams/</id><title>P. Lion - Dreams - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:57:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:57:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/P_Lion/Dreams/" title="P. Lion - Dreams - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm singing there on the moon <br>We cannot see the sunshine <br>The city is too great for us <br>I hope to see the moon tonight again <br>I like to think when you're with me <br>And stay in only my mind <br>I dream to go so far with you <br>But now we have to wait tonight again <br><br>Dream in the moon <br>I'm singing in the night <br>Light up your eyes <br>Dream in the night <br>I'm singing on the moon <br>Light up your eyes <br><br>I'm singing there on the moon <br>Now I can see the sunshine <br>This space is beautiful for me <br>I want to stay alone tonight again <br>Then music goes to my heart <br>I feel the peace in my mind <br>So in the morning I come back <br>But now want to see tonight again <br><br>Dream in the moon <br>I'm singing in the night <br>Light up your eyes <br>Dream in the night <br>I'm singing on the moon <br>Light up your eyes <br><br>Dream in the night <br>Dream in the night <br>Dream in the night, oh]]></content><category term="P. Lion" label="P. Lion"/><category term="Dreams" label="Dreams"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mozzart/Jasmine_China_Girl/</id><title>Mozzart - Jasmine China Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:57:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:57:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mozzart/Jasmine_China_Girl/" title="Mozzart - Jasmine China Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My Jasmin China Girl <br><br>My jasmin girl find out city lights <br>Touch my cheek in China <br>All the dragons cry in China <br>I'm livin' in a dream with you on my mind <br>Oh Oh Oh Ouah <br>Foggy roads of love left me far behind <br>Oh Oh Oh Ouah <br>In China <br><br>I'm livin' in a dream with you on my mind <br>Oh Oh Oh Ouah <br>Foggy roads of love left me far behind <br>Oh Oh Oh Ouah <br>In China <br><br>In China <br><br>My jasmin China girl you're my way <br>My jasmin China girl you must stay <br><br>Bakin' moon's palin' far away <br>Wait for long in China <br>Circles haven't hearts in China <br>I'm livin' in a dream with you on my mind <br>Oh Oh Oh Ouah <br>Foggy roads of love left me far behind <br>Oh Oh Oh Ouah <br>In China <br><br>I'm livin' in a dream with you on my mind <br>Oh Oh Oh Ouah <br>Foggy roads of love left me far behind <br>Oh Oh Oh Ouah <br>In China <br>In China <br>In China <br>In China <br><br>My jasmin China girl you're my way <br>My jasmin China girl you must stay <br><br>My jasmin, jasmin <br><br>Whispers fly sheltered in the sky <br>My time is out in China <br><br>My jasmin China girl you're my way <br>My jasmin China girl you must stay <br><br>My jasmin China girl you're my way <br>My jasmin China girl you must stay <br><br>Whispers fly sheltered in the sky <br>My time is out in China <br><br>My jasmin China girl you're my way <br>My jasmin China girl you must stay]]></content><category term="Mozzart" label="Mozzart"/><category term="Jasmine China Girl" label="Jasmine China Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Robert_Camaro/Love_Games/</id><title>Robert Camaro - Love Games - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:57:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:57:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Robert_Camaro/Love_Games/" title="Robert Camaro - Love Games - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Everyday you live inside of me <br>Waiting for my desire <br>There's no way to make you feel like me <br>Now it's <br>Should you walk away <br>I could say that it must be a sign <br><br>I don't want to be mysterious <br>But you got to realize <br><br>Everything has got too serious <br>I know feeelings don't lie <br><br>Let me hear you say <br>You don't want now to play no games <br><br>I just want to hold you in my arms <br>There is nothing I could ask for more <br>But I know I will never play this game <br><br>I just want to whisper that you know <br>Tell you that I'll always love you so <br>Can't you know that it's time to go away <br><br>I don't want to be mysterious <br>But remember my pride <br><br>Something near is so serious <br>I know cause I can't hide <br><br>Let me hear you say <br>If you want now to play no games <br><br>Everytime you look within my eyes <br>There is nothing I can really hide <br>Cause I know that it's always just the same <br><br>I just want to hold you in my arms <br>There is nothing I could ask for more <br>But I know I will never play this game <br><br>Everytime you look within my eyes <br>There is nothing I can really hide <br>Cause I know that it's always just the same <br><br>I just want to whisper that you know <br>Tell you that I'll always love you so <br>Can't you know that it's time to go away x2]]></content><category term="Robert Camaro" label="Robert Camaro"/><category term="Love Games" label="Love Games"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan_Paris/Fall_In_Love/</id><title>Ryan Paris - Fall In Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:57:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:57:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan_Paris/Fall_In_Love/" title="Ryan Paris - Fall In Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fall in love, I will fall in love, but I know that someday I' ll regret it <br>When you talk you sing, when you dance you swing <br>And your eyes are more than heaven, fall in love <br>Caroline don' t waste your time, come, won't you kiss me once again <br>Caroline, for sure it' s no, no crime, come, won't you drive me more insane <br>Cause I feel I will fall in love <br>Fall in love you will fall in love, let your passion grow on, love me stronger <br>Yes I know, you know, what we want for sure And I love you more than ever, fall in love <br><br>Caroline don' t waste your time, turn on the city lights with me <br>Caroline, for sure it' s no, no crime, come, you are so beautiful to me <br>And I feel you will fall in love <br>Fall in love, I will fall in love, but I know that someday I' ll regret it <br>When you talk you sing, when you dance you swing And your eyes are more than heaven, fall in love]]></content><category term="Ryan Paris" label="Ryan Paris"/><category term="Fall In Love" label="Fall In Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Duke_Lake/Dance_Tonight/</id><title>Duke Lake - Dance Tonight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:57:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:57:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Duke_Lake/Dance_Tonight/" title="Duke Lake - Dance Tonight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dance tonight <br>Love is right <br>Dance tonight <br>Love, Oo Oo Oo <br><br>Anytime I think about my life <br>I can't find the key <br>Of what I wanna be <br><br>Anytime I wake up in the night <br>The thing was not forever <br>There to be together <br><br>There's no way to say goodbye I can't say goodbye <br>Love me, stay until you die <br><br>So dance, tonight will be alright to fly <br>Love, tonight will be so fine so right <br>So dance, tonight will be alright to fly, Oo oo oo <br><br>Love o love the music in my life <br>It's the real care of what I wanna do <br>No more wake up in the night <br>Maybe it's not forever <br>But to be together <br><br>There's no way to say goodbye I can't say goodbye <br>Love me, stay until you die <br><br>So dance, tonight will be alright to fly <br>Love, tonight will be so fine Oo oo oo <br>So dance, tonight will be alright to fly <br>Love, tonight will be so fine to fly, Oo oo oo]]></content><category term="Duke Lake" label="Duke Lake"/><category term="Dance Tonight" label="Dance Tonight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Den_Harrow/To_Meet_Me/</id><title>Den Harrow - To Meet Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:57:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:57:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Den_Harrow/To_Meet_Me/" title="Den Harrow - To Meet Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The girl is dressed up for the coronation <br>I want to come out of a situation <br>It's not the cowl that makes the monk you say <br>But if don't look good I'm not OK <br><br>And anywhere I go I'm not the one <br>And anything I do the pain's not gone <br>I have a tweedy suit and pointy shoes <br>My hat is not on straight <br>Oh baby nothing to do <br><br>I spread my wings now and I wanna fly <br>My jacket clings now bye bye bye <br>I'm just becoming what I wanna be <br>You will be running to meet me <br><br>The boys are running for the stimulation <br>Hypocrisy's a big contamination <br>Inside my pants today there beats a heart <br>But now I never know the way to start <br><br>And anywhere I go I'm not the one <br>And anything I do the pain's not gone <br>I have a tweedy suit and pointy shoes <br>My hat is not on straight <br>Oh baby nothing to do <br><br>I spread my wings now and I wanna fly <br>My jacket clings now bye bye bye <br>I'm just becoming what I wanna be <br>You will be running to meet me]]></content><category term="Den Harrow" label="Den Harrow"/><category term="To Meet Me" label="To Meet Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Valerie_Dore/Its_So_Easy/</id><title>Valerie Dore - It`s So Easy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:57:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:57:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Valerie_Dore/Its_So_Easy/" title="Valerie Dore - It`s So Easy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How can it be so easy <br>No one can take you from me <br>You will be forever <br>Mine <br><br>There's no reason why <br>Feelings can come and go so easy <br>And as time goes by <br>You live for love <br>For love <br><br>There's no reason why <br>We should be living in the past time <br>Every day you stay <br>In my heart <br><br>Sweet pretender <br>I've got the key to find <br>True surrender <br>I'm gonna make you're mine <br><br>It's so easy now <br>How can it be so easy <br>And tonight <br>I realize how lucky <br>Love can be with you <br><br>It's so easy now <br>How can it be so easy <br>And tonight <br>No one can take you from me <br>You're forever mine <br><br>There's no reason why <br>We two were made for one another <br>When you're near I try <br>To be for love <br>For love <br><br>Please don't pass me by <br>Make up your mind <br>And I won't let you go <br>Don't waste precious time <br>Here and now <br><br>Sweet pretender <br>I've got the key to find <br>True surrender <br>I'm gonna make you're mine <br><br>It's so easy now <br>How can it be so easy <br>And tonight <br>I realize how lucky <br>Love can be with you <br><br>It's so easy now <br>How can it be so easy <br>And tonight <br>No one can take you from me <br>You're forever mine]]></content><category term="Valerie Dore" label="Valerie Dore"/><category term="It`s So Easy" label="It`s So Easy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Styloo/Pretty_Face/</id><title>Styloo - Pretty Face - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:57:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:57:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Styloo/Pretty_Face/" title="Styloo - Pretty Face - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Awwright Woooohhhh <br>A pretty face and a dirty look <br>Knew right away that i'd have to get my hooks in you <br>Yeah yeah yeah <br>I'm running low on my memories <br>If you wanna make a fuss, boy, you gotta be a disease, uhuh <br>I say yeah yeah <br>I need it all, baby, that's no lie <br>I need a lover with an alibi <br>I wanna fall into a love so sweet <br>Honey baby baby I'm hard to beat <br>Hot flesh and I touch alone <br>Smells in the air and I'm feeling so alone, uhuh <br>I say yeah yeah <br>Hallucination true romance <br>I need a love but I only got a face, uhuh <br>That ain't all <br>I'll tell ya honey it's a crying shame <br>All the pretty women look the same <br>I wanna fall into a love so sweet <br>Honey baby baby I'm hard to beat <br>Wooooh hey hey <br>Your pretty face is going to hell <br>Your pretty face is going to hell <br>Honey honey I can tell <br>Your pretty face is going to HELL <br>HELL <br>A pretty face and a dirty look <br>Knew right away that i'd have to get my hooks in you <br>I say yeah yeah <br>I'm running low on my memories <br>If you wanna make a fuss, boy, you gotta be a tease <br>Uhuh and that ain't all <br>I say yeah yeah <br>I need it all, baby, that's no lie <br>I need a lover with an alibi <br>I wanna fall into a love so sweet <br>Honey baby baby I'm hard to beat <br>Woooh yeah hey <br>Your pretty face is going to hell]]></content><category term="Styloo" label="Styloo"/><category term="Pretty Face" label="Pretty Face"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fake/Donna_Rouge/</id><title>Fake - Donna Rouge - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:57:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:57:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fake/Donna_Rouge/" title="Fake - Donna Rouge - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wanna see you dance in the night <br>I wanna see you move <br>And on the floor the queen in the light <br>Let all your feeling groove <br><br>Since sunday night I've been dreaming 'bout you my love <br>Then stayed around my head <br>Tonight, tonight and I'm ready for you <br>I see you, you see me <br><br>Ho tanta voglia di fare l'amore con te <br>Ti voglio <br>I don't understand but <br><br>I can feel it, too <br>I can feel it <br>Feel the heat of your eyes <br><br>I can feel it, too <br>I can feel it <br>Feel the heat of your eyes <br><br>Don't know the words girl I sure understand <br>Tonight, tonight <br>And you're around you melt with our faces <br>Hanging their eyes up for you <br><br>I wanna see you dance in the night again <br>I wanna see you move <br>And on the floor the queen in the light <br>Let all your feeling groove for me <br><br>Voglio fare l'amore tutto il giorno <br>Tutta la notte, sempre <br>I don't understand but <br><br>I can feel it, too <br>I can feel it <br>Feel the heat of your eyes <br><br>I can feel it, too <br>I can feel it <br>Feel the heat of your eyes <br><br>I don't understand but <br><br>Ho tanta voglia di fare l'amore con te <br>Andiamo a letto <br>I don't understand but <br><br>I can feel it, too <br>I can feel it <br>Feel the heat of your eyes <br><br>I can feel it, too <br>I can feel it <br>Feel the heat of your eyes]]></content><category term="Fake" label="Fake"/><category term="Donna Rouge" label="Donna Rouge"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alan_Ross/Valentino_Mon_Amour/</id><title>Alan Ross - Valentino Mon Amour - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:57:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:57:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alan_Ross/Valentino_Mon_Amour/" title="Alan Ross - Valentino Mon Amour - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Valentino mon amour hey hey <br>Everybody wants to say hey hey <br>Valentino mon amour hey hey <br>Everybody wants to say valentino hey hey <br>Not many reasons <br>to be movin' tonight <br>Not many chances <br>to have it together <br><br>You never give me <br>any beautiful night's <br>And now I'm feeling <br>we're dancing together <br>Because the light of your eyes <br>looks like a milion little stars <br>when you're talking about <br>you got to feel you full of <br>full of emotions <br>full of romantic dreams <br>who leave together <br>like many of yours <br>like many of yours freinds <br>who leaves forever <br>Valentino mon amour <br>everybody dream somebody <br>everybody want to say <br>Valentino, Hey Hey]]></content><category term="Alan Ross" label="Alan Ross"/><category term="Valentino Mon Amour" label="Valentino Mon Amour"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mozzart/Money/</id><title>Mozzart - Money - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:58:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:58:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mozzart/Money/" title="Mozzart - Money - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Money <br>It was the things <br>That makes a world go round <br>You're hardest do them do them <br>Damn on this ground <br>Money <br>He cased the rock <br>That is a girl's best friend <br>What makes you land off <br>Take me in this surrend <br>Money <br>You know the stuff that <br>Everyone love to spell <br>Should we do a money <br>The stuff that <br>Nobody is willing to left <br>should we do a money <br>We come closer <br>Give me the tone <br>Dollar Ien Deutchemark <br>Should we do a money <br>Should we do a money <br>How we can trick the police <br>Who's gonna pay <br>I wear the suit <br>That shoot for ruling LA <br>Money <br>Heavenly whistling <br>Baby in pink shampagne <br>We need the new time <br>That doesn't drive you insane <br>Money]]></content><category term="Mozzart" label="Mozzart"/><category term="Money" label="Money"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magazine_60/Pancho_Villa/</id><title>Magazine 60 - Pancho Villa - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:58:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:58:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Magazine_60/Pancho_Villa/" title="Magazine 60 - Pancho Villa - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Y tu, y tu <br>Dime lo que bailas <br>Y tu, y tu <br>Dime lo que bailas <br>Y tu, y tu <br>Dime lo que bailas <br>Dime lo que bailas <br>Dime lo que bailas <br>Y tu, y tu <br>Dime lo que bailas <br>Y tu, y tu <br>Dime lo que bailas <br>Y tu, y tu <br>Dime lo que bailas <br>Y tu, y tu <br>Dime lo que bailas <br>Arriba, arriba <br>Baila el baile de Pancho Villa <br>Cual la triste historia, de macho enamorado <br>Qu cantaba en un bar, un langido cha cha <br>Canta jiripollas, canta <br>Bandolero, amigo, viene a los sombreros <br>Comme un caballero qui prepare sa revolution <br>Ces baisers <br>Aquellos besos <br>Baila chico, baila <br>Tu emballes les senoritas comme un hidalgo <br>Un accord de guitare, un verre du tequila, la fiesta <br>Arriba Villa arriba Pancho Villa, uo ooh <br>Arriba Villa arriba Pancho Villa, uo ooh <br>Arriba Villa ahh, uhh, ahh, uhh <br><br>Ay gringo por que te mueves asi <br>Este es el nuevo baile <br>El baile de Pacho Villa Cha Cha <br>Ay, Ay Pacho pero no me digas <br>Es una acta de cantida <br><br>Metete en la cabeza <br>Para hacer el solo <br>en la palza mayor ay senorita <br>No estas en Mexico <br>Baila chico baila <br>Tu emballes les senoritas comme un hidalgo <br>Arriba Villa arriba Pancho Villa, uo ooh <br>Arriba Villa arriba Pancho Villa, uo ooh <br>Arriba Villa ahh, uhh, ahh, uhh]]></content><category term="Magazine 60" label="Magazine 60"/><category term="Pancho Villa" label="Pancho Villa"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Linda_Jo_Rizzo/Youre_My_First__Last/</id><title>Linda Jo Rizzo - You`re My First &amp; Last - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:58:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:58:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Linda_Jo_Rizzo/Youre_My_First__Last/" title="Linda Jo Rizzo - You`re My First &amp; Last - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There was a time that love for me <br>Was like a cand of stone <br>It tempted me and look so nice I wanted more <br>And when you came into my life, it was a dream come true <br>I was little girl again, you felt it too <br><br>But then you only took my life for a ride <br>Can't you see I'm breaking up inside <br><br>You're my first <br>I give you all of my love <br>You're my last <br>Cause I can't take any more of thou love again <br>It's only breaks my heart in the end, my heart <br><br>You're my first <br>I give you all of my love <br>You're my last <br>Cause I can't take any more of thou love again <br>It's only breaks my heart in the end, ooh heart <br><br>There was a time when I was strong <br>And try to walk away <br>But when you ask me back again, I have to stay <br>I can't belive in all your lies, You're are still the same <br>But do we have to keep on play silly games <br><br>Cause I know you used to take my life for a ride <br>Now can't you see I'm breaking up inside <br><br>You're my first <br>I give you all of my love <br>You're my last <br>Cause I can't take any more of thou love again <br>It's only breaks my heart in the end, my heart <br><br>You're my first <br>I give you all of my love <br>You're my last <br>Cause I can't take any more of thou love again <br>It only breaks my heart in the end, ooh heart]]></content><category term="Linda Jo Rizzo" label="Linda Jo Rizzo"/><category term="You`re My First &amp; Last" label="You`re My First &amp; Last"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Babys_Gang/Happy_Song/</id><title>Baby`s Gang - Happy Song - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:58:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:58:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Babys_Gang/Happy_Song/" title="Baby`s Gang - Happy Song - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We are down, we are crazy fools everyday at school <br>Teachers here, teachers there <br>Books and books, they are everywhere <br>Come on boys, we need to dance <br>We have got a good chance <br>Lay your problems on the floor <br>Clap your hands and sing to me once more <br><br>Everybody, let's go to the King <br>We can dance there, dance and eat an ice cream <br>Everybody dancing all night long <br>Try to do it, sing a happy song <br><br>Music, dancing in the night <br>We can get so high <br>For no reason no long stop <br>Now's the time to go to the top <br><br>It's a sweeter happy song <br>We'll sing all night long <br>Lay your problems on the floor <br>Clap your hands and sing once more <br><br>It's time to dance, it's time to sing, sing a happy song <br>Sing a happy song <br>Let's go, let's go boys, come with me and sing <br>Sing a happy song, our song <br><br>Let's go, let's go boys, come with me and sing <br><br>We are down, we are crazy fools everyday at school <br>Teachers here, teachers there <br>Books and books, they are everywhere <br>Come on boys, we need to dance <br>We have got a good chance <br>Lay your problems on the floor <br>Clap your hands and sing to me once more <br><br>Everybody, let's go to the King <br>We can dance there, dance and eat an ice cream <br>Everybody dancing all night long <br>Try to do it, sing a happy song <br><br>Sing a happy song <br>Sing a happy song, our song]]></content><category term="Baby`s Gang" label="Baby`s Gang"/><category term="Happy Song" label="Happy Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brando/Rainy_Day/</id><title>Brando - Rainy Day - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:58:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:58:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brando/Rainy_Day/" title="Brando - Rainy Day - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What time is it <br>Now I'm walking alone in this street <br>Oh, what a night <br><br>I can't sleep tonight <br>Now I'm searching for someone a friend <br>To pass the time <br><br>Oh, something in the air <br>Makes me feel so strange <br>Now I'm wasting my time <br>So it's time to change <br><br>Rainy day <br>My girl has gone away <br>It's time to change my life <br>Something will happen tomorrow <br><br>Rainy day <br>I can't forget this name <br>Oh, no regrets you can find <br>A new love, a new life <br><br>Sorry to say <br>But I'm down on my knees <br>Yes, I think I lost my way <br><br>But while there is life <br>There is hope <br>And I hope that I'll find a friend tonight <br><br>I'm walking in the rain <br>But the sun will rise <br>There's no reason to cry <br>For a name, for a smile <br><br>Rainy day <br>My girl has gone away <br>It's time to change my life <br>Something will happen tomorrow <br><br>Rainy day <br>I can't forget this name <br>Oh, no regrets you can find <br>A new love, a new life <br><br>Rainy day <br>The clouds will go away <br>Oh, no regrets you can find <br>A new love, a new life]]></content><category term="Brando" label="Brando"/><category term="Rainy Day" label="Rainy Day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GJ_Lunghi/Acapulco_Nights/</id><title>G.J. Lunghi - Acapulco Nights - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:58:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:58:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GJ_Lunghi/Acapulco_Nights/" title="G.J. Lunghi - Acapulco Nights - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Every night in my room <br>I'm wandering <br>Always thinking of you <br><br>And every step that I take <br>Reminds me <br>Of your wonderful face <br><br>Acapulco nights <br>I hear the voices in the dark tonight you know <br>Acapulco nights <br>I hear them calling that's where I wanna go <br><br>It's a rainy day <br>And this town <br>Is so wetty and cold <br><br>Maybe I'm wasting my time <br>I'm always <br>Always looking for you <br><br>Acapulco nights <br>I hear the voices in the dark tonight you know <br>Acapulco nights <br>I hear them calling that's where I wanna go <br><br>I never can say goodbye <br>Cause you, you are my music <br>Oh I never can say goodbye <br>Cause you, you are my feelings <br>I really can't forget those Acapulco nights <br><br>Every night in my room <br>I'm wandering <br>Always thinking of you <br><br>And every move that I make <br>Reminds me <br>Of your wonderful face <br><br>Acapulco nights <br>I hear the voices in the dark tonight you know <br>Acapulco nights <br>I hear them calling that's where I wanna go <br><br>I never can say goodbye <br>Cause you, you are my music <br>Oh I never can say goodbye <br>Cause you, you are my feelings <br>I really can't forget those Acapulco nights <br><br>I never can say goodbye <br>Cause you, you are my music <br>Oh I never can say goodbye <br>Cause you, you are my feelings <br>I really can't forget those Acapulco nights <br><br>Every night in my room <br>I'm wandering <br>Always thinking of you <br><br>And every step that I take <br>Reminds me <br>Of your wonderful face <br><br>Acapulco nights <br>I hear the voices in the dark tonight you know <br>Acapulco nights <br>I hear them calling that's where I wanna go <br><br>I never can say goodbye <br>Cause you, you are my music <br>Oh I never can say goodbye <br>Cause you, you are my feelings <br>I really can't forget those Acapulco nights <br><br>I never can say goodbye <br>Cause you, you are my music]]></content><category term="G.J. Lunghi" label="G.J. Lunghi"/><category term="Acapulco Nights" label="Acapulco Nights"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Warriyo/Mortals_Feat_Laura_Brehm/</id><title>Warriyo - Mortals (Feat. Laura Brehm) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:58:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:58:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Warriyo/Mortals_Feat_Laura_Brehm/" title="Warriyo - Mortals (Feat. Laura Brehm) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stranded in the open <br>Dried out tears of sorrow <br>Lacking all emotion <br>Staring down the barrel waiting for the <br>Final gates to open <br>To a new tomorrow <br>Moving with the motion <br>Following the light that sets me free]]></content><category term="Warriyo" label="Warriyo"/><category term="Mortals (Feat. Laura Brehm)" label="Mortals (Feat. Laura Brehm)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/종근이형/Day_Dream_Feat_캡틴시하/</id><title>종근이형 - Day Dream (Feat. 캡틴시하) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:59:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:59:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A2%85%EA%B7%BC%EC%9D%B4%ED%98%95/Day_Dream_Feat_%EC%BA%A1%ED%8B%B4%EC%8B%9C%ED%95%98/" title="종근이형 - Day Dream (Feat. 캡틴시하) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어쩌다 한번은 <br>드물게 하루쯤 <br>힘들어 줄래요 <br>내 생각 나게요 그대 <br>멀리서 보여도 <br>반기며 달려 오던 소녀 <br>사소한 얘기도 <br>귀 기울여 들어준 소녀 <br>내 속에 곱게 핀 <br>속에 곱게 핀 <br>rosy baby <br>속에 곱게 핀 <br>발걸음이 나눠졌던 <br>비 내리던 한강공원 <br>떠오를 때면 내 눈에는 <br>온 종일을 보아도 <br>내 얼굴만 찾았던 소녀 <br>내 얼굴 보면은 <br>아이처럼 웃었던 소녀 <br>내 속에 곱게 핀 <br>속에 곱게 핀 <br>rosy baby <br>속에 <br>lily lady <br>곱게 핀 <br>발걸음이 나눠졌던 <br>비 내리던 한강공원 <br>떠오를 때면 내 눈에는 <br>oh 내 속에 곱게 핀 <br>rosy baby <br>So Disgusting cliche <br>freakin' cheesy <br>like a silly love song <br>속에 곱게 핀 <br>cloudy daydream <br>]]></content><category term="종근이형" label="종근이형"/><category term="Day Dream (Feat. 캡틴시하)" label="Day Dream (Feat. 캡틴시하)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/종근이형/Bye_My_Feat_캡틴시하/</id><title>종근이형 - Bye My (Feat. 캡틴시하) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:59:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:59:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A2%85%EA%B7%BC%EC%9D%B4%ED%98%95/Bye_My_Feat_%EC%BA%A1%ED%8B%B4%EC%8B%9C%ED%95%98/" title="종근이형 - Bye My (Feat. 캡틴시하) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 자주 갔던 <br>Starbucks 2층 그 자리 <br>내가 선물 했던 <br>Swarovski 목걸이 <br>너를 붙잡고 싶었지만 <br>그랬지만 난 <br>곁에 있던 멋진 분 <br>놀라실 까봐 난 <br>못 본 척 할 수 밖에 없었어 <br>편해 보이더라 <br>꺼져있던 전화기 속에 <br>멘트가 마치 melody <br>되돌릴 수 없어져 버린 <br>우리들만의 memory <br>이 곳에 혼자 남은 <br>나만의 지친 rhapsody <br>kind of lunartic philosophy <br>bye my bye my <br>bye my girl yeah <br>bye my bye my <br>bye my girl yeah <br>제자리를 찾기를 바랬던 <br>나의 마음은 널 외면했고 <br>안될 것을 알던 내 가슴은 <br>보내줬지 woo wah <br>내게 화내고 싶었지만 <br>그랬지만 난 <br>곁에 있던 멋진 분 <br>그보다 못한 난 <br>널 보내 줄 수 밖에 없었어 <br>좋아 보이더라 <br>다가올 일을 알려주던 <br>차오르는 심장소리 <br>이지러진 문을 열려던 <br>엉켜버린 내 의지 <br>무기력할 수 밖에 없던 <br>바닥 같은 내 위치 <br>everything's mystic bleak <br>bye my bye my <br>bye my girl yeah <br>bye my bye my <br>bye my girl yeah <br>bye my bye my <br>bye my girl yeah <br>bye my bye my <br>bye my girl yeah <br>우리 자주 갔던 <br>Starbucks 2층 <br>그 자리에 앉아서 <br>내가 선물 했던 <br>Swarovski 목걸이 한 <br>너의 곁에 이젠 <br>]]></content><category term="종근이형" label="종근이형"/><category term="Bye My (Feat. 캡틴시하)" label="Bye My (Feat. 캡틴시하)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CBAND/If_I/</id><title>CBAND - If I... - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:59:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:59:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/CBAND/If_I/" title="CBAND - If I... - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나에게 꿈이라는 건 <br>끝없이 펼쳐진 바다야 <br>지금 나의 쉴 곳을 찾아 <br>계속 노래해 찢겨진 마음 <br>닦아줘 <br>say something <br>i'm giving up on you <br>i'm giving up on you <br>shelter 를 찾아서 <br>say something <br>if you want me to <br>if you want me to <br>If I were you <br>I wouldn't do that <br>내 안의 꿈 영원히 지킬게 <br>If you stay with me <br>I'll be happy <br>Ekey Hubae Hangui <br>KimD Junky Bullgo yo <br>돈의 노예야 저리 비켜라 <br>거짓 웃음이 마치 가치인가 <br>배부른 돼지야 기름진 뱃살아 <br>신나게 마신 맥주 거품처럼 <br>say something <br>i'm giving up on you <br>i'm giving up on you <br>shelter 를 찾아서 <br>say something <br>if you want me to <br>if you want me to <br>If I were you <br>I wouldn't do that <br>내 안의 꿈 영원히 지킬게 <br>If you stay with me <br>I'll be happy <br>Ekey Hubae Hangui <br>KimD Junky Bullgo yo <br>my love my Dream my soul <br>this is my story <br>my love my Music my soul <br>this is my story <br>my love my Dream my soul <br>this is my story <br>my love my Music my soul <br>this is my story story <br>If I were you <br>I wouldn't do that <br>내 안의 꿈 영원히 지킬게 <br>If you stay with me <br>I'll be happy <br>Ekey Hubae Hangui <br>KimD Junky Bullgo yo <br>]]></content><category term="CBAND" label="CBAND"/><category term="If I..." label="If I..."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/채민/그밤/</id><title>채민 - 그밤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:59:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:59:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B1%84%EB%AF%BC/%EA%B7%B8%EB%B0%A4/" title="채민 - 그밤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[조용한 밤에 보이는 빛나는 별 <br>한눈에 담을 수 없던 그밤에 너 <br>아쉬운 마음들 그리운 마음들 <br>내 맘에 담아 보낸다 <br>너의 눈에도 <br>별이 많이 보이길 바라 <br>너의 마음속도 <br>이렇게 환하길 바라 <br>어두운 밤 되면 <br>고개를 들어 천천히 <br>따뜻한 너의 품 속으로 들어가 <br>네 맘을 녹일 거야 <br>외로워 하지마 <br>이 밤을 선물할게 woo ah <br>I wanna give everlasting love <br>wuh woo wuh woo yeah <br>wuh woo wuh woo yeah <br>Um 그렇게 널 <br>wuh woo wuh woo yeah <br>wuh woo wuh woo yeah <br>한걸음 더 다가가 <br>창가에 걸터앉아 날 바라보던 <br>달빛을 끼고 환하게 웃음 짓던 <br>아름다웠지 눈이 부셨지 <br>더 바라게 해줘 너의 그 모든걸 <br>Um I wanna give everlasting love <br>조용한 밤에 보이는 빛나는 별 <br>한눈에 담을 수 없던 그 밤에 너 <br>아쉬운 마음들 그리운 마음들 <br>내 마음에 담아 보낸다 <br>너의 눈에도 <br>별이 많이 보이길 바라 <br>너의 마음속도 <br>이렇게 환하길 바라 <br>어두운 밤 되면 <br>고개를 들어 천천히 <br>wuh woo wuh woo yeah <br>wuh woo wuh woo yeah <br>Um 그렇게 널 <br>wuh woo wuh woo yeah <br>wuh woo wuh woo yeah <br>한걸음 더 다가가 <br>]]></content><category term="채민" label="채민"/><category term="그밤" label="그밤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/WallT_태현수/왔다갔다_Arr_by_hyungho_Bae/</id><title>Wall.T (태현수) - 왔다갔다 (Arr. by hyungho Bae) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:59:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:59:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/WallT_%ED%83%9C%ED%98%84%EC%88%98/%EC%99%94%EB%8B%A4%EA%B0%94%EB%8B%A4_Arr_by_hyungho_Bae/" title="Wall.T (태현수) - 왔다갔다 (Arr. by hyungho Bae) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[무슨말로 얘기를 할지 <br>고민하다가 <br>하루가 지나가면 <br>혼자 또 거울을 바라보며 <br>오글거리는 말들을 <br>난 또 해보고 <br>3시간정도 고민을 하고서 <br>문자를 보냈지 <br>잠깐 나올 수 있어 <br>집앞에 나온 <br>니 얼굴을 보면서 <br>용기내 한다는 말은 <br>밥 밥먹었어 <br>니앞에 서면 난 왔다갔다 <br>심장이 콩닥콩닥 <br>아무것도 할 수가 없어 <br>니 얼굴 보면 난 갈팡질팡 <br>마음이 조마조마 <br>아무말도 할 수가 없어 <br>엊그젠 니 선물을 사서 <br>손에 잔뜩 들고서 <br>너를 또 불러냈어 <br>오다가 주웠단 <br>말을하며 주고싶었지만 <br>한다는말은 <br>그 그게 <br>니앞에 서면 난 왔다갔다 <br>심장이 콩닥콩닥 <br>아무것도 할 수가 없어 <br>니 얼굴 보면 난 갈팡질팡 <br>마음이 조마조마 <br>아무말도 할 수가 없어 <br>몇번이고 다시 <br>생각해봐도 <br>이건 아닌것만 <br>같다고 얘길해봐도 <br>언제쯤 나는 <br>말을 할 수 있을까 <br>다시 생각해봐도 <br>결국 또 제자리로와 <br>여보세요 <br>어 저기 그게 <br>이따 시간 괜찮아 <br>니앞에 서면 난 왔다갔다 <br>심장이 콩닥콩닥 <br>아무것도 할 수가 없어 <br>니 얼굴 보면 난 갈팡질팡 <br>마음이 조마조마 <br>아무말도 할 수가 없어 <br>니앞에 서면 난 왔다갔다 <br>심장이 콩닥콩닥 <br>아무것도 할 수가 없어 <br>니 얼굴 보면 난 갈팡질팡 <br>마음이 조마조마 <br>아무말도 할 수가 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="Wall.T (태현수)" label="Wall.T (태현수)"/><category term="왔다갔다 (Arr. by hyungho Bae)" label="왔다갔다 (Arr. by hyungho Bae)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HER/Pigment/</id><title>H.E.R. - Pigment - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:59:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:59:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HER/Pigment/" title="H.E.R. - Pigment - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The things that I would do to you with just a couple seconds <br>I would color every moment, make you feel like it's forever <br>I'm comin' over, so you can start undressin' <br>I'm givin' you a chance to finally make a good impression <br>On me, yeah <br>On me, I'll make you feel like it's forever <br><br>Because it's clear I'm getting bigger <br>I know you visualize my figure <br>I was the one that made you look <br>At your old girl and reconsider <br>You see me in that black dress <br>On the first date <br>And I'm causin' frustration on your mind <br>Only in the best ways <br><br>Secretly I'm anxious, 'cause the thirst has never been mutual <br>It's unusual <br>That someone like you thinks I'm beautiful <br>It's beautiful, yeah <br>What we have is beautiful <br>Remember when you said <br><br>The things that I would do to you with just a couple seconds <br>I would color every moment, make you feel like it's forever baby <br>I'm coming over so you can start undressing <br>I hope this is my chance to finally make a good impression on you, on you <br><br>But just when you think you have forever he has you lost in your emotions <br>And you hate feeling so alone and you're because you know <br>You shouldn't have stayed until the morning <br>It wasn't worth all of the heartache <br>It wasn't worth all of the pleasure <br>Because you once were a diamond, he made you feel like buried treasure I guess <br><br>Nothing lasts forever <br>Nothing lasts forever baby <br>Nothing lasts forever <br><br>The things that I would do to you with just a couple seconds <br>You colored every moment, make it feel like it's forever <br>And after a while we lost a real connection <br>And I realized there's others using the time we've been spending no more <br>I'm still lost, holding in all of the anger at the bottom of the ocean <br>And I thought you'd be my savior <br>I was distracted, unaware of his behavior <br>But when I started drowning I didn't know he was the anchor]]></content><category term="H.E.R." label="H.E.R."/><category term="Pigment" label="Pigment"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Still_PM/Tanie_Feat_호재/</id><title>Still PM - Tanie (Feat. 호재) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:00:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:00:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Still_PM/Tanie_Feat_%ED%98%B8%EC%9E%AC/" title="Still PM - Tanie (Feat. 호재) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니가 내 삶에 <br>들어온 뒤로 <br>모든게 바뀌어버렸지 <br>상처들에겐 위로 <br>니가 아프지 않기를 <br>난 매일 밤 기도해 <br>정말 한시도 니 <br>생각없이 보내지 못하는 <br>내가 신기하기도 해 <br>아무리 보고 또 봐도 <br>진지하게 이쁘기만한 네 <br>작은 얼굴 손 발이 <br>자꾸 미소 짓게 하네 yeah <br>지구 상에서 가장 <br>사랑스런 생물체 <br>찡찡거리는 것 쯤은 <br>평생도 해도 돼 <br>화가 날 일이 없어 <br>그 눈빛 앞에선 <br>음식 앞에서만 <br>내게 내미는 니 손 <br>평생 놓지 않을게 <br>이건 감히 장담해 <br>지친 하루였어도 <br>너가 쳐주는 장난에 <br>내 맘은 녹아내리지 <br>니가 있어서 다행이야 <br>너 없는 우리 집은 <br>이제 상상도 안해 난 <br>Beautiful you're beautiful to me <br>내 눈엔 you're too beautiful <br>you're beautiful to me <br>너 없이 난 안돼 <br>아프면 안돼 <br>내가 잘할게 <br>넌 그냥 최선을 다 해 <br>행복하면 돼 <br>난 그거면 돼 <br>이쁜이 넌 그 <br>이상의 존재 <br>가끔씩은 널 위해 <br>억지로도 혼내 <br>내 맘은 찢어지는데 <br>어쩔 수 없을 때도 <br>금방 웃음이 터지네 <br>너의 필살 애교 <br>아가 아가 내가 <br>부를 때면 갸우뚱 <br>거리는 니 표정은 <br>내 말을 알듯 말듯 <br>못 알아들어도 괜찮아 <br>내 맘은 알고 있잖아 <br>너랑 하루종일 놀아도 <br>하나도 안 귀찮아 <br>Beautiful you're beautiful to me <br>내 눈엔 you're too beautiful <br>you're beautiful to me <br>너 땜에 내가 <br>바뀐거 그 첫번째 <br>일을 마치면 술자리 <br>대신 니 옆에 <br>억지로 하는게 아냐 <br>내게 안정감을 준 너 <br>나 역시 보답할게 <br>평생 너를 지켜줄거야 <br>유난이라 말하지 <br>궁금해 나도 왠지 <br>이쁜걸 어떡해 <br>니가 한번 봐봐 왠지 <br>그 단어가 들어가는 <br>욕은 이젠 하지 않네 <br>우리 항상 행복하자 <br>공주님 나의 타니 <br>Beautiful beautiful to me <br>내 눈엔 you're too beautiful <br>beautiful to me <br>]]></content><category term="Still PM" label="Still PM"/><category term="Tanie (Feat. 호재)" label="Tanie (Feat. 호재)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/봉구/봄날은_간다/</id><title>봉구 - 봄날은 간다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:00:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:00:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B4%89%EA%B5%AC/%EB%B4%84%EB%82%A0%EC%9D%80_%EA%B0%84%EB%8B%A4/" title="봉구 - 봄날은 간다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈을 감으면 문득 <br>그리운 날의 기억 <br>아직까지도 마음이 <br>저려 오는 건 <br>그건 아마 사람도 <br>피고 지는 꽃처럼 <br>아름다워서 슬프기 때문일 거야 <br>아마도 <br>봄날은 가네 무심히도 <br>꽃잎은 지네 바람에 <br>머물 수 없던 아름다운 사람들 <br>가만히 눈 감으면 잡힐 것 같은 <br>아련히 마음 아픈 추억 같은 것들 <br>봄은 또 오고 <br>꽃은 피고 또 지고 피고 <br>아름다워서 너무나 슬픈 이야기 <br>봄날은 가네 무심히도 <br>꽃잎은 지네 바람에 <br>머물 수 없던 아름다운 사람들 <br>가만히 눈 감으면 잡힐 것 같은 <br>아련히 마음 아픈 추억 같은 것들 <br>눈을 감으면 문득 <br>그리운 날의 기억 <br>아직까지도 마음이 <br>저려 오는 건 <br>오 랄랄랄라 <br>꽃이 피고 지고 <br>다시 피고 지고 <br>아름다운 슬픈 이야기 <br>]]></content><category term="봉구" label="봉구"/><category term="봄날은 간다" label="봄날은 간다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/세비야/착시/</id><title>세비야 - 착시 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:00:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:00:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%B8%EB%B9%84%EC%95%BC/%EC%B0%A9%EC%8B%9C/" title="세비야 - 착시 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[거리 어디에나 네가 있어서 <br>지나가는 그 아무라도 <br>너로 보여서 <br>난 힘들어서 just stay <br>한 걸음도 난 뗄 수 없어서 <br>내 방 어디에나 네가 있어서 <br>집에 혼자 있는 것도 난 <br>너무 힘이 들어 어떻게 할지 몰라 <br>또 난 어쩔 수 없이 난 눈을 감아 <br>널 어떻게 보내줘야 잘하는 걸까 <br>네가 떠나간 후로 난 <br>여전히 너와 살고 있어 <br>차라리 난 이대로 널 <br>담아두고 살아가는 게 <br>널 잊고 사는 것보단 나을 것 같아 <br>곁에 있는 것만 같은 착각에 <br>네가 쓰던 향수 잠옷도 <br>챙겨 놓곤 해 <br>내 맘은 둘 곳 없이 <br>덩그러니 하나만 남았네 <br>또 미련만 남아 <br>더 잘해주지 못했던 <br>날 원망하다가 <br>아직도 버리지 못했던 <br>네 사진을 보고 난 혼잣말 <br>여전히 너만을 생각해 <br>널 어떻게 보내줘야 잘하는 걸까 <br>네가 떠나간 후로 난 <br>여전히 너와 살고 있어 <br>차라리 난 이대로 널 <br>담아두고 살아가는 게 <br>널 잊고 사는 것보단 나을 것 같아 <br>]]></content><category term="세비야" label="세비야"/><category term="착시" label="착시"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Christopher/Lot_To_Learn_Garage_Sessions/</id><title>Luke Christopher - Lot To Learn (Garage Sessions) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:00:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:00:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Luke_Christopher/Lot_To_Learn_Garage_Sessions/" title="Luke Christopher - Lot To Learn (Garage Sessions) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Feeling like a digit in a system <br>just another stupid number <br>I don't know know know <br>Everything is twisted <br>I can feel it <br>It's another stupid summer <br>where it's cold cold cold <br>And we can do this <br>on our own <br>Head up to a place <br>where baby no one goes <br>In a rocket full of liquor <br>bring a Polaroid for pictures <br>Baby you should stop me <br>'fore I lose control <br>How imperfect a person am I <br>Go through your purse <br>and put on your disguise <br>You see the stars <br>but they just see the skies <br>And you see my scars <br>what do they see <br>If I was a question <br>would you be my answer <br>If I was a music <br>would you be the dancer <br>If I was a student <br>would you be the teacher <br>If I was a sinner <br>would you be the preacher <br>Would you be my <br>N' dun d dun dun <br>I still got a lot of shit to learn <br>I'll admit it <br>N' dun d dun dun <br>I still got a lot of shit to learn <br>I'll admit it <br>Got your finger on the trigger <br>and you aimin' at the mirror <br>Don't you shoot <br>that ain't you love <br>Cause on the outside you <br>pretending <br>But you hurtin' in the inner <br>what's the truth <br>what's the truth now <br>How imperfect a person am I <br>Go through your purse <br>and put on your disguise <br>You see the stars <br>but they just see the skies <br>And you see my scars <br>what do they see <br>If I was a question <br>would you be my answer <br>If I was a music <br>would you be the dancer <br>If I was a student <br>would you be the teacher <br>If I was a sinner <br>would you be the preacher <br>Would you be my <br>Cause it dun d dun dun <br>I still got a lot of shit to learn <br>I'll admit it <br>Cause it dun d dun dun <br>I still got a lot of shit to learn <br>I'll admit it <br>]]></content><category term="Luke Christopher" label="Luke Christopher"/><category term="Lot To Learn (Garage Sessions)" label="Lot To Learn (Garage Sessions)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동화/Bonus_Track_구름이_무심탄_말이/</id><title>동화 - (Bonus Track) 구름이 무심탄 말이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:00:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:00:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%ED%99%94/Bonus_Track_%EA%B5%AC%EB%A6%84%EC%9D%B4_%EB%AC%B4%EC%8B%AC%ED%83%84_%EB%A7%90%EC%9D%B4/" title="동화 - (Bonus Track) 구름이 무심탄 말이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[구름이 무심탄 말이 <br>아마도 허량하다 <br>열구름 몽니한 이 말은 <br>버덩한 심정이라 <br>중천에 떠이셔 임에 단니며셔 <br>높이 뜬 구름은 잡히지 않을 것을 <br>구태야 광명한 날빗츨 <br>따라가며 덮나니 <br>내 얘기를 들어줘요 <br>아무도 관심 없나요 <br>나도 저 밝은 빛을 보고 <br>꿈을 꿀 수 있을까요 <br>아 까만 공기 속에 <br>아 새까만 구름 타고 <br>저 어디론가 떠나면 <br>그때는 알아 줄 수 있나요 <br>노여운 네 마음을 <br>온종일 헤윰하노니 <br>허량한 그 구름은 <br>날빗츨 가리지 못할 것을 <br>아 아 아 아아 아 아 아 <br>구름이 무심탄 말이 <br>아마도 허량하다 <br>열구름 몽니한 이 말은 <br>버덩한 심정이라 <br>]]></content><category term="동화" label="동화"/><category term="(Bonus Track) 구름이 무심탄 말이" label="(Bonus Track) 구름이 무심탄 말이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동화/시인에게_보내는_편지/</id><title>동화 - 시인에게 보내는 편지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:00:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:00:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%ED%99%94/%EC%8B%9C%EC%9D%B8%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_%EB%B3%B4%EB%82%B4%EB%8A%94_%ED%8E%B8%EC%A7%80/" title="동화 - 시인에게 보내는 편지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[봄이 오는 소리에 <br>당신은 어떤 생각을 하고 있나요 <br>당신의 마음 <br>내가 조금만 헤아려볼게요 <br>초록 색으로 물들은 <br>그때의 여름은 어떤 일 있었나요 <br>가을비 먹은 낙엽도 <br>흰 눈 덮고 잠 들었어요 <br>내 손가락 만해진 <br>몽땅 연필 손에 쥐고 <br>색 바랜 종이 한 장 뜯어 <br>써 내려간 그 글자들을 <br>내가 노래해요 <br>온 맘 다해 노래해요 <br>이세상에 그 마음이 <br>울려 퍼질 수 있도록 <br>라 라라라라 라 라라라라 <br>라 라라 라 <br>라 라라라라 라 라라라라 <br>라 라라 라 <br>비가 내리던 날엔 <br>코끝 에서 맴도는 <br>꿈에 본 자취 따라 <br>내가 따라 걷고 있을게요 <br>내가 노래해요 <br>온 맘 다해 노래해요 <br>이세상에 그 마음이 <br>울려 퍼질 수 있도록 <br>내가 노래해요 <br>온 맘 다해 노래해요 <br>이세상에 그 마음이 <br>울려 퍼질 수 있도록 <br>그 나뭇잎 배는 <br>별들 춥다 안아주던 소년은 <br>볼 순 없지만 어둔 길에도 <br>우두커니 서 있는 <br>저 해바라기처럼 약속할게요 <br>라 라라라라 라 라라라라 <br>라 라라 라 <br>라 라라라라 라 라라라라 <br>라 라라 라 라라라 라 <br>라 라 라라라 라 <br>라 라라라라 라 라라라라 <br>라 라라 라 <br>봄이 오는 소리에 <br>깨어난 들판 위에 작은 풀잎들도 <br>당신의 마음 <br>깊숙이 새겨진 꽃이 될 거예요 <br>]]></content><category term="동화" label="동화"/><category term="시인에게 보내는 편지" label="시인에게 보내는 편지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동화/해바라기의_비명/</id><title>동화 - 해바라기의 비명 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:00:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:00:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%ED%99%94/%ED%95%B4%EB%B0%94%EB%9D%BC%EA%B8%B0%EC%9D%98_%EB%B9%84%EB%AA%85/" title="동화 - 해바라기의 비명 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나의 무덤앞에는 <br>차가운 빗돌을 <br>세우지 말라 <br>나의 무덤 주위에는 <br>노란 해바라기를 <br>심어달라 <br>그리고 해바라기의 <br>긴 줄기 사이로 <br>끝 없는 보리밭을 <br>보여달라 <br>노오란 해바라기는 <br>늘 태양같이 태양같이 <br>화려한 나의 사랑 <br>푸른 보리밭 사이로 <br>하늘을 쏘는 <br>노고지리가 있거든 <br>아직도 날아오르는 <br>나의 꿈이라 <br>나의 무덤앞에는 <br>차가운 빗돌을 <br>세우지 말라 <br>나의 무덤 주위에는 <br>노란 해바라기를 <br>심어달라 <br>그리고 해바라기의 <br>긴 줄기 사이로 <br>끝 없는 보리밭을 <br>보여달라 <br>노오란 해바라기는 <br>늘 태양같이 태양같이 <br>화려한 나의 사랑이라고 <br>생각 하라 <br>푸른 보리밭 사이로 <br>하늘을 쏘는 <br>노고지리가 있거든 <br>아직도 날아오르는 <br>나의 꿈이라 <br>노오란 해바라기는 <br>늘 태양같이 <br>화려한 나의 사랑 <br>푸른 보리밭 사이로 <br>하늘을 쏘는 <br>노고지리가 있거든 <br>아직도 날아오르는 <br>나의 꿈이라 <br>생각 하라 <br>]]></content><category term="동화" label="동화"/><category term="해바라기의 비명" label="해바라기의 비명"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동화/나뭇잎배/</id><title>동화 - 나뭇잎배 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:00:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:00:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%ED%99%94/%EB%82%98%EB%AD%87%EC%9E%8E%EB%B0%B0/" title="동화 - 나뭇잎배 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어저께 띄워논 나뭇잎배는 <br>궂은비가 오는데 어디로 갔나 <br>물가의 비젖은 풀숲새에는 <br>종이쪽 흰돛이 있을 뿐 일세 <br>어저께 벌레손님 태워 건네던 <br>새파란 나뭇잎 작은 나룻배 <br>돛대와 뱃몸은 어디로 가고 <br>연못에는 빗방울 소리 뿐 일세 <br>어저께 띄워논 나뭇잎배는 <br>궂은비가 오는데 어디로 갔나 <br>언니와 만들던 나뭇잎배는 <br>궂은비가 오는데 어디로 갔나 <br>창가에 찾아온 귀뚜라미는 <br>귀뚤 귀뚤 울기만하네 <br>어저께 벌레손님 태워 건네던 <br>새파란 나뭇잎 작은 나룻배 <br>돛대와 뱃몸은 어디로 가고 <br>연못에는 빗방울 소리 뿐 일세 <br>어저께 벌레손님 태워 건네던 <br>새파란 나뭇잎 작은 나룻배 <br>돛대와 뱃몸은 어디로 가고 <br>돛대와 뱃몸은 어디로 가고 <br>돛대와 뱃몸은 어디로 가고 <br>]]></content><category term="동화" label="동화"/><category term="나뭇잎배" label="나뭇잎배"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동화/소년에게/</id><title>동화 - 소년에게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:00:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:00:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%ED%99%94/%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C/" title="동화 - 소년에게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[차디찬 아침이슬 <br>진주가 빛나는 못가 <br>연꽃 하나 다복이 피고 <br>음 음 음 음 음 <br>음 음 음 음 음 음 <br>으음 으음 으으으 으으음 <br>소년아 네가 낳다니 <br>맑은 넋에 깃 드려 <br>박꽃처럼 자랐세라 <br>큰 강 목놓아 흘러 <br>여울은 흰 돌 쪽 마다 소리 <br>석양을 새기고 <br>너는 준마 달리며 <br>죽도 져 곧은 기운을 <br>목숨같이 사랑 했거늘 <br>거리를 쫓아 단여도 <br>볼 수 있는 풍경 속에 <br>동상답게 <br>동상답게 서봐도 좋다 <br>아 <br>음 음 음 음 음 <br>음 음 음 음 음 음 <br>서풍 뺨을 스치고 <br>하늘 한가 구름 뜨는 곳 <br>희고 푸른 지음을 노래하며 <br>노래 가락은 흔들리고 <br>별들 춥다 얼어 붙고 <br>너 조차 미친들 어떠랴 <br>음 음 음 음 음 <br>음 음 음 음 음 음 <br>으음 으음 으으으 으으음 <br>]]></content><category term="동화" label="동화"/><category term="소년에게" label="소년에게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동화/예전엔_미처_몰랐어요/</id><title>동화 - 예전엔 미처 몰랐어요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:00:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:00:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%ED%99%94/%EC%98%88%EC%A0%84%EC%97%94_%EB%AF%B8%EC%B2%98_%EB%AA%B0%EB%9E%90%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="동화 - 예전엔 미처 몰랐어요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[봄 가을 없이 밤마다 돋는 달도 <br>예전엔 미처 몰랐어요 <br>봄 가을 없이 밤마다 돋는 달도 <br>예전엔 미처 몰랐어요 <br>이렇게 사무치게 그리울 줄도 <br>이렇게 사무치게 그리울 줄도 <br>예전엔 미처 몰랐어요 <br>음 음 음 <br>예전엔 미처 몰랐어요 <br>예전엔 미처 몰랐어요 <br>달이 암만 아 밝아도 <br>쳐다 볼 줄도 몰랐어요 <br>저 달이 날 아 불러도 <br>대답 할 줄도 몰랐어요 <br>예전엔 미처 몰랐어요 <br>이제 금 저 달이 설움인 줄은 <br>예전엔 미처 몰랐어요 <br>이제 금 저 달이 설움인 줄은 <br>예전엔 미처 몰랐어요 <br>]]></content><category term="동화" label="동화"/><category term="예전엔 미처 몰랐어요" label="예전엔 미처 몰랐어요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanze/Survive_Feat_Neon_Dreams/</id><title>Vanze - Survive (Feat. Neon Dreams) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:00:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:00:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanze/Survive_Feat_Neon_Dreams/" title="Vanze - Survive (Feat. Neon Dreams) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Told you to walk away <br>That was my first and last mistake <br>I blew without your faith <br>Oh what can I do <br>Cause I'm just a sinking ship <br>And you're just a pair of lips <br>That I've lost in the moment <br>All I want is for you to come back <br><br>Now I'm caught <br>In the middle of life <br>And I need <br>I need you to survive <br>Survive, survive <br>I need you to survive <br>Cause without you by my side <br>I can't survive <br>Survive <br>I need you to survive <br>Cause without you by my side <br>I can't survive <br><br>And this can be the end <br>I want to settle for being your friend <br>Our broken bond is not too late to mend <br>But what can I do <br>Cause I'm just a sinking ship <br>And you're just a pair of lips <br>That I've lost in the moment <br>All I want is for you to come back <br><br>Now I'm caught <br>In the middle of life <br>And I need <br>I need you to survive <br><br>She said won't you walk right <br>So I can give you one more chance <br>You're only living in your damn head <br>Yeah, cause without you by my side <br>I can't survive <br>I need you to survive yeah <br>Cause without you by my side <br>I can't survive <br>Yeah, cause without you by my side <br>I can't survive]]></content><category term="Vanze" label="Vanze"/><category term="Survive (Feat. Neon Dreams)" label="Survive (Feat. Neon Dreams)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/기현_Kihyun/그런건_슬픈게_아니야_Inst/</id><title>기현 (Kihyun) - 그런건 슬픈게 아니야 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:00:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:00:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%B0%ED%98%84_Kihyun/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%B0%EA%B1%B4_%EC%8A%AC%ED%94%88%EA%B2%8C_%EC%95%84%EB%8B%88%EC%95%BC_Inst/" title="기현 (Kihyun) - 그런건 슬픈게 아니야 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그런건 슬픈게 아니야 <br>니 앞에서 돌아서는 일 <br>그런건 슬픈게 아니야 <br>기억 속에 잊혀지는 일 <br>도대체 얼만큼이나 <br>니 앞에서 무너질런지 <br>입술이 혼자 말해 <br>지쳐도 미치도록 <br>그리워도 기다려 <br>사랑은 끝이 없는 걸 <br>타오르다 사라지는 걸 <br>아파도 아픈줄도 모르고 <br>너만 생각하게 되는 걸 <br>그런건 쉬운게 아니야 <br>세상앞에 날 버리는 일 <br>그런건 쉬운게 아니야 <br>니 옆에서 멀어지는 일 <br>도대체 얼만큼이나 <br>울고불고 매달릴런지 <br>내 눈물이 널 데려와 <br>달래도 조각이난 <br>그리움만 흩어져 <br>사랑은 끝이 없는 걸 <br>타오르다 사라지는 걸 <br>아파도 아픈줄도 모르고 <br>너만 생각하게 되는 걸 <br>가슴속에 맴도는 <br>너란 한사람 <br>말라버린 니 <br>이름만 바라봐 <br>사랑은 끝이 없는 걸 <br>타오르다 사라지는 걸 <br>다쳐도 다친 줄도 모르고 <br>너만 생각하게 되는 걸 <br>너만 생각나 <br>]]></content><category term="기현 (Kihyun)" label="기현 (Kihyun)"/><category term="그런건 슬픈게 아니야 (Inst.)" label="그런건 슬픈게 아니야 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/기현_Kihyun/그런건_슬픈게_아니야/</id><title>기현 (Kihyun) - 그런건 슬픈게 아니야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:00:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:00:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%B0%ED%98%84_Kihyun/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%B0%EA%B1%B4_%EC%8A%AC%ED%94%88%EA%B2%8C_%EC%95%84%EB%8B%88%EC%95%BC/" title="기현 (Kihyun) - 그런건 슬픈게 아니야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그런건 슬픈게 아니야 <br>니 앞에서 돌아서는 일 <br>그런건 슬픈게 아니야 <br>기억 속에 잊혀지는 일 <br>도대체 얼만큼이나 <br>니 앞에서 무너질런지 <br>입술이 혼자 말해 <br>지쳐도 미치도록 <br>그리워도 기다려 <br>사랑은 끝이 없는 걸 <br>타오르다 사라지는 걸 <br>아파도 아픈줄도 모르고 <br>너만 생각하게 되는 걸 <br>그런건 쉬운게 아니야 <br>세상앞에 날 버리는 일 <br>그런건 쉬운게 아니야 <br>니 옆에서 멀어지는 일 <br>도대체 얼만큼이나 <br>울고불고 매달릴런지 <br>내 눈물이 널 데려와 <br>달래도 조각이난 <br>그리움만 흩어져 <br>사랑은 끝이 없는 걸 <br>타오르다 사라지는 걸 <br>아파도 아픈줄도 모르고 <br>너만 생각하게 되는 걸 <br>가슴속에 맴도는 <br>너란 한사람 <br>말라버린 니 <br>이름만 바라봐 <br>사랑은 끝이 없는 걸 <br>타오르다 사라지는 걸 <br>다쳐도 다친 줄도 모르고 <br>너만 생각하게 되는 걸 <br>너만 생각나 <br>]]></content><category term="기현 (Kihyun)" label="기현 (Kihyun)"/><category term="그런건 슬픈게 아니야" label="그런건 슬픈게 아니야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/에디킴/이쁘다니까_Inst/</id><title>에디킴 - 이쁘다니까 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:00:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:00:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%90%EB%94%94%ED%82%B4/%EC%9D%B4%EC%81%98%EB%8B%A4%EB%8B%88%EA%B9%8C_Inst/" title="에디킴 - 이쁘다니까 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자꾸 물어보는 너 <br>늘 확인하고픈 너 <br>같은 말해줘도 <br>매일 말해줘도 <br>왜 계속 물어 <br>입술이 말라오네 <br>또 식은땀이 흐르네 <br>또 정답은 알지만 <br>니가 듣고 싶은 말 <br>그 듣고 싶은 말 <br>나를 시험하는 말 <br>너 정말 이쁘다 <br>이쁘다 이쁘다니까 <br>왜 내 말 <br>믿지 않는 건데 왜 <br>말하고 말하고 <br>아무리 말해도 <br>화난 듯한 <br>너의 그 표정 <br>말 수가 없어진 너 <br>더 불안해지는 나 <br>매일 같은 퀴즈 <br>반복되는 게임 <br>난 항상 술래 <br>머리를 새로 했나 <br>오 손톱이 바뀌었을까 <br>오 감이 오질 않아 <br>니가 듣고 싶은 말 <br>그 듣고 싶은 말 <br>정말 힌트도 없는지 <br>너 정말 이쁘다 <br>이쁘다 이쁘다니까 <br>왜 내 말 <br>믿지 않는 건데 왜 <br>말하고 말하고 <br>아무리 말해도 <br>화난 듯한 <br>너의 그 표정 <br>이쁘단 말 하나론 <br>널 표현 하긴 부족하잖아 <br>baby 내 맘이라도 <br>꺼내줘야 넌 믿겠니 <br>널 정말 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑하는데 <br>왜 변했다고 하는건데 왜 <br>화내고 삐지고 <br>매일 토라져도 <br>그것마저 사랑스러워 <br>니가 백번 아니 <br>천번 내게 물어도 <br>정답은 늘 하난데 <br>어제도 오늘도 <br>내일 또 물어도 <br>세상에서 니가 <br>제일 이뻐 <br>]]></content><category term="에디킴" label="에디킴"/><category term="이쁘다니까 (Inst.)" label="이쁘다니까 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/에디킴/이쁘다니까/</id><title>에디킴 - 이쁘다니까 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:00:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:00:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%90%EB%94%94%ED%82%B4/%EC%9D%B4%EC%81%98%EB%8B%A4%EB%8B%88%EA%B9%8C/" title="에디킴 - 이쁘다니까 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자꾸 물어보는 너 <br>늘 확인하고픈 너 <br>같은 말해줘도 <br>매일 말해줘도 <br>왜 계속 물어 <br>입술이 말라오네 <br>또 식은땀이 흐르네 <br>또 정답은 알지만 <br>니가 듣고 싶은 말 <br>그 듣고 싶은 말 <br>나를 시험하는 말 <br>너 정말 이쁘다 <br>이쁘다 이쁘다니까 <br>왜 내 말 <br>믿지 않는 건데 왜 <br>말하고 말하고 <br>아무리 말해도 <br>화난 듯한 <br>너의 그 표정 <br>말 수가 없어진 너 <br>더 불안해지는 나 <br>매일 같은 퀴즈 <br>반복되는 게임 <br>난 항상 술래 <br>머리를 새로 했나 <br>오 손톱이 바뀌었을까 <br>오 감이 오질 않아 <br>니가 듣고 싶은 말 <br>그 듣고 싶은 말 <br>정말 힌트도 없는지 <br>너 정말 이쁘다 <br>이쁘다 이쁘다니까 <br>왜 내 말 <br>믿지 않는 건데 왜 <br>말하고 말하고 <br>아무리 말해도 <br>화난 듯한 <br>너의 그 표정 <br>이쁘단 말 하나론 <br>널 표현 하긴 부족하잖아 <br>baby 내 맘이라도 <br>꺼내줘야 넌 믿겠니 <br>널 정말 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑하는데 <br>왜 변했다고 하는건데 왜 <br>화내고 삐지고 <br>매일 토라져도 <br>그것마저 사랑스러워 <br>니가 백번 아니 <br>천번 내게 물어도 <br>정답은 늘 하난데 <br>어제도 오늘도 <br>내일 또 물어도 <br>세상에서 니가 <br>제일 이뻐 <br>]]></content><category term="에디킴" label="에디킴"/><category term="이쁘다니까" label="이쁘다니까"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/꽃가람/여운/</id><title>꽃가람 - 여운 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:01:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:01:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%BD%83%EA%B0%80%EB%9E%8C/%EC%97%AC%EC%9A%B4/" title="꽃가람 - 여운 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[떨어지는 태양 노을 앞에서 <br>나는 바라본다 너의 모습을 <br>붉게 물든 얼굴 흐릿한 시선 <br>멀어지는 노을 잊혀져 가네 <br>내 기억 저편에 넌 <br>한걸음 한걸음 <br>그때를 기억하니 잔잔해 <br>흐릿한 모습들과 너와의 흔적은 <br>비가 온다 잔잔해 진다 <br>뭘 하고 있는지 알고 싶지 않아 <br>이렇게 외면을 한다 <br>보고 싶지 않아 널 버린다 <br>천천히 날 떠나 <br>하지만 <br>잊으려고 애를 쓰면 희미해지는 <br>눈망울에 흐르는 눈물은 <br>내리는 비 밤처럼 널 보내려 한다 <br>비가 오는 밤에 너 보낸다 <br>그 순간을 기억해 <br>내 기억 속 저편 <br>평생토록 살아서 숨쉰다 <br>천천히 내 맘속 깊이 보내려 한다 <br>우린 서로 잔잔해진다 <br>노을이 지고 밤이 왔어도 <br>나는 외롭지가 않아 <br>숨어 지내는 너와 추억들은 <br>내 맘속에 왔어 <br>이렇게 <br>항상 생각하며 살아가볼게 <br>기억 들이 점점 잊혀져 가도 <br>비가 오는 새벽 지나만 간다 <br>시원 해질 거야 아침이 오면 <br>떨어 지는 태양 노을 앞에서 <br>나는 바라본다 너의 모습을 <br>붉게 물든 얼굴 흐릿한 시선 <br>멀어지는 노을 잊혀져 가네 <br>]]></content><category term="꽃가람" label="꽃가람"/><category term="여운" label="여운"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동요_천사/응원가/</id><title>동요 천사 - 응원가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:01:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:01:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EC%B2%9C%EC%82%AC/%EC%9D%91%EC%9B%90%EA%B0%80/" title="동요 천사 - 응원가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 팀이 이겨라 우리 팀이 이긴다 <br>힘을 모아서 승리하자 이번 승리는 우리꺼 <br><br>너무 잘한다 잘한다 신이 나게 잘한다 <br>화이팅하고 힘을 내자 결국 1등은 우리꺼 <br><br>잘해보자 이기자 좀 더 힘을 내보자 <br>좀 더 힘차게 소리 질러 힘을 모아서 이기자 <br><br>우리 팀이 이겨라 우리 팀이 이긴다 <br>힘을 모아서 승리하자 이번 승리는 우리꺼 <br><br>너무 잘한다 잘한다 신이 나게 잘한다 <br>화이팅하고 힘을 내자 결국 1등은 우리꺼 <br><br>잘해보자 이기자 좀 더 힘을 내보자 <br>좀 더 힘차게 소리 질러 힘을 모아서 이기자]]></content><category term="동요 천사" label="동요 천사"/><category term="응원가" label="응원가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/Ebony_Sky/</id><title>Young Fathers - Ebony Sky - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:01:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:01:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/Ebony_Sky/" title="Young Fathers - Ebony Sky - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bird in the hand, two in the bush <br>Define your intentions in truth <br>Abandon abandon <br>But never ever say what you ran from <br>Staring at the fragments <br>In your sleep laughing <br>Thought crime champion <br>Take another Ambien <br>Back to the wall but the ceiling's still cracking <br><br>Young, unassuming <br>Eucalyptus blooming <br>Masquerade of masochists <br>Said I'm only human <br>Five past eleven, ten past dead <br>Twenty to the hour til the hour spells dread <br>Fortunes to the killer who's convinced he's a healer <br>Give a smile to the patient <br>You know the connotation <br>Maggot in the mallet <br>Feel the force of the malice <br>Killer cannae cut it cos he couldnae get the credit <br><br>I spy <br>Ebony sky <br>She's looking for love <br>She's looking for love <br><br>I am the lion, the lamb <br>Turn on the faucet <br>Let the gas blast <br>Counterfeit emotion <br>From a womanizer <br>Booze on her body <br>A one two timer <br>Hand prints left on a contender <br>Signs of a winner <br>You'll always remember <br>Homegrown, living on the throne <br>Let it be known, beholder unknown <br><br>I spy <br>Ebony sky <br>She's looking for love <br>She's looking for trouble <br>In the wrong places <br>In the wrong places]]></content><category term="Young Fathers" label="Young Fathers"/><category term="Ebony Sky" label="Ebony Sky"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/Way_Down_In_The_Hole/</id><title>Young Fathers - Way Down In The Hole - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:01:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:01:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/Way_Down_In_The_Hole/" title="Young Fathers - Way Down In The Hole - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How many colors does she need to know <br>When you're way way way down in the hole <br>When the night time comes round <br>When the night time comes around <br>When the night time comes round <br>In the night <br><br>If fortune sides with him who dares <br>A life in bliss in the Garden of Eden <br>One bad kiss from Casanova, prestige over, keep the claws <br>He may be old but his mind's like a razor <br>Dissipate, disappear like vapour <br>Cufflinks on a chartered curator <br>Haven the wager <br><br>Work your life, don't ask why <br>Give your mother good goodbye <br>Show me where you run and hide <br>Drop your gun, fix your tie <br>Don't you know the price is low <br>Fire in the hole <br>Way down in the hole <br>Told you once, told you twice <br>La de da, roll the dice <br>I'm gunna tell you twice <br><br>Out of sight, replaced by a young man in a suit <br>Silhouettes and recruits <br>Snakes in the bushes were none the wiser <br>Lost direction I'll come to Dada <br>Call on the doctor, bring on the healing <br>Insert the brother, hit the kill switch <br>View my crime but nothing published <br>Choir boys singing, my demise it's hunting season <br>It's hunting season <br>It's hunting season <br>It's hunting season <br>It's hunting season <br><br>How many colors does she need to know <br>When you're way way way down in the hole <br>When the night time comes round <br>When the night time comes around <br>When the night time comes round <br>In the night]]></content><category term="Young Fathers" label="Young Fathers"/><category term="Way Down In The Hole" label="Way Down In The Hole"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/Mr_Martyr/</id><title>Young Fathers - Mr. Martyr - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:01:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:01:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/Mr_Martyr/" title="Young Fathers - Mr. Martyr - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Watch em laugh laugh laugh laugh laugh like a hyena <br>Taking a chance wouldn't last if you ask Mr Martyr <br>Watch em laugh laugh laugh laugh laugh like a hyena <br>Taking a chance wouldn't last if you ask Mr Martyr <br><br>If you're sicker than sickle cells then follow me in hell I'm possessed by the devil <br>Brand new heart for a heartless bastard <br>When evil spills it all but dissolves <br>Spreads in a cluster <br>Mic check checky checky wish I could go back to the beginning give it meaning <br>But I definitely can't <br>Instead of walking away shoulda definitely ran <br>Shoulda woulda coulda but I definitely can't <br>Could be my daughter first old words have no recovery <br>Tryna muscle her way through the back door <br>Caught at the end still tryna dig deep <br>Forever at drift key hole vision <br>Painting all over the walls cause I don't have a canvas <br>I know it won't last still taking my chances <br>Playground games double dutch with a pro <br>She's an artist <br>Most likely to be crucified straight talkin' head honcho <br>Most likely to be crucified straight talkin' head honcho <br><br>I shoulda waited for the rescue <br>No connection to the legend that was untrue <br><br>I shoulda waited for the rescue <br><br>I shoulda waited for the rescue <br>No connection to the legend that was untrue <br>I shoulda waited for the rescue <br>No connection to the legend that was untrue]]></content><category term="Young Fathers" label="Young Fathers"/><category term="Mr. Martyr" label="Mr. Martyr"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/Freefalling/</id><title>Young Fathers - Freefalling - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:01:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:01:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/Freefalling/" title="Young Fathers - Freefalling - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stay a little longer <br>We can't deny ourselves <br>Search a little harder <br>Deeper inside the well <br>Search is getting strong <br>Reeks of the Witch's Brew <br>Pushing you, stop resisting <br>Pushing you, where I can't follow <br><br>I see you now <br>Freefalling, freefalling <br>I see you now <br>Befallen, befallen <br>I see you now <br>Freefalling, freefalling <br>I see you now <br>Befallen, befallen <br><br>Stay a little longer <br>We can't deny ourselves <br>Search a little harder <br>Deeper inside the well <br>Search is getting strong <br>Reeks of the Witch's Brew <br>Pushing you, stop resisting <br>Pushing you, where I can't follow]]></content><category term="Young Fathers" label="Young Fathers"/><category term="Freefalling" label="Freefalling"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/Queen_Is_Dead/</id><title>Young Fathers - Queen Is Dead - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:01:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:01:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/Queen_Is_Dead/" title="Young Fathers - Queen Is Dead - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sent to death in a filthy Colosseum <br>By an ugly secretary who goes by the name of Mary <br>Living the life less ordinary, London Beriberi <br>Shoot to maim even though she wanna kill <br>Indiscretions tell the tales <br>So forget about the children <br>All this and that and <br>Always attacking him <br>A nibble on the crack and <br>Go tell 'em, I only write my felon <br>Poke the needle in the eye <br>Burning bridges, breaking ties <br>Spark a new born, blue blood, royal baby cry <br>Til her face turns red <br>Til the brain has bled <br>Last rites are said <br>Worms are fed <br>And the headline said <br><br>The Queen is dead The Queen is dead <br>The Queen is dead The Queen is dead <br>The Queen is d d d d dead <br>She's Dead <br>The Queen is dead The Queen is dead <br>The Queen is dead The Queen is dead <br>The Queen is dead <br><br>Money money cash for gold money money cash for gold <br>Money money cash for gold money money cash for gold <br>Money money cash for gold money money cash for gold <br>Money money cash for gold money money cash for gold <br>Money money cash for gold money money cash for gold <br>Money money cash for gold money money cash for gold <br>Money money cash for gold money money cash for gold <br>Money money cash for gold money money cash for gold <br><br>Met an America <br>Vomit on the carper <br>Joined in the fellowship <br>Ready for a road trip <br>Settled in a settlement <br>A calm man's habitat <br>Interesting development <br>Her body for a handbag <br>Mouth like a pelican <br>Draft up the relevance <br>Habitat from the cold <br>Money money money money money money <br>Cash for gold]]></content><category term="Young Fathers" label="Young Fathers"/><category term="Queen Is Dead" label="Queen Is Dead"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/Only_Child/</id><title>Young Fathers - Only Child - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:01:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:01:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/Only_Child/" title="Young Fathers - Only Child - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I find it hard to be an honest man <br>I guess I'll go and find God again <br>I can hear lonely, lonely sounds <br>Living like an only child <br>I can hear lonely, lonely sounds <br>Living like an only child <br><br>Hallelujah it's a boy <br>Celebrations gems and toys <br>So blatant to the cause <br>Blame the clients on the job <br>Calm, cold, in control <br>Young, bold, viscious <br>This manufactured chemistry <br>Weaving in and out the tapestry <br><br>Breastfeed the baby that wasn't raised in the nanny state <br>Or hidden from the belly, closer, closer to ascertain <br>Body like a statue, grace of an antelope <br>Displayed on the market, dispensing assets <br><br>All that, gimme that, gimme that, all that <br>All that, all that, gimme that, gimme that <br>All that, gimme that, gimme that, all that <br>All that, all that, gimme that, gimme that <br>All that, gimme that, gimme that, all that <br>All that, all that, gimme that, gimme that <br>All that, gimme that, gimme that, all that <br>All that, all that, gimme that, gimme that <br>All that, gimme that, gimme that, all that <br>All that, all that, gimme that, gimme that <br>All that, gimme that, gimme that, all that <br>All that, all that, gimme that, gimme that <br><br>I find it hard to be an honest man <br>I guess I'll go and find God again <br>I can hear lonely, lonely sounds <br>Living like an only child <br>I can hear lonely, lonely sounds <br>Living like an only child]]></content><category term="Young Fathers" label="Young Fathers"/><category term="Only Child" label="Only Child"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/Come_To_Life/</id><title>Young Fathers - Come To Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:01:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:01:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/Come_To_Life/" title="Young Fathers - Come To Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The nature is nurture <br>In response to this amicable lecture <br>Could it be written underneath the deckchair <br>Play fair <br>False pretences <br>Underhanded tactics <br>Undermine your mind <br>Add the balance to the debt <br>When you hear the bells chime <br>Suck up noses <br>Retract slowly <br>Detatch the slack slogan <br>Pick up only <br><br>I heard it in a monologue <br>Reconsideration in a motorway Travelodge <br>Stand up, rip your honours off <br>History, survivor of the cannon balls <br>Mother doesn't sleep well if I'm not in town <br>She couldn't give a fuck if the exchange rate is down <br>So come to the rope in the service of hope <br>Gather all the children and head for the coast <br><br>Come to life, you're dead <br>Don't you go in there <br>Come to life, you're dead <br>Don't you go in there <br><br>Just before the fuck it up <br>Ch ch ch ch chop it up and put it your pot <br><br>Tell him 'bout the visions and your feelings and the guns <br>If you come to a decision <br>You can come to a decision <br><br>Daily necessities, tangled by a safety net <br>Fixed term penalties, stocks on the internet <br>Paying for a green card, starting off at Bucharest <br>Talking to my mother <br>Send another cheque <br>Philosophical bullshit is the shit I resurrect <br>Smoke a weaker substance <br>And I suck a Nicorette <br>And mixing, almost there <br>Answer, before you say yes <br>Honestly <br><br>Come to life, you're dead <br>Don't you go in there <br>Come to life, you're dead <br>Don't you go in there <br><br>Just before fuck it up Just before fuck it up <br>Just before fuck it up Just before fuck it up <br>Just before fuck it up Just before fuck it up <br>Just before fuck it up Just before fuck it up]]></content><category term="Young Fathers" label="Young Fathers"/><category term="Come To Life" label="Come To Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/I_Heard/</id><title>Young Fathers - I Heard - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:01:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:01:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Young_Fathers/I_Heard/" title="Young Fathers - I Heard - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Science is eerie when you're still around <br>Killing your body cos they found you out <br>Calling the shots and I'm falling down <br>Look at the dust explode on the ground <br><br>I'm there, I'm there, I'm there, I'm there, I'm there, I'm there, under, I'm THERE <br>I'm there, I'm there, under, I've heard <br>I've heard, I've head <br>I've heard, I've head <br><br>Inside I'm feeling dirty <br>Inside I'm feeling dirty <br>Inside I'm feeling dirty <br>It's only cos I'm hurting <br><br>Telephone the father sat on the armchair with a pint and a smoke <br>Sure, no more back handed compliments but the dishes are still in the sink <br>Walk towards the door and there's an empty dresser, time to bring out the duster <br>Left with a bone and a smile to last you a while <br>Rest a shore captain from your sea of travails <br><br>Inside I'm feeling dirty <br>Inside I'm feeling dirty <br>Inside I'm feeling dirty <br>It's only cos I'm hurting <br><br>Science is eerie when you're still around <br>Killing your body cos they found you out <br>Calling the shots and I'm falling down <br>Look at the dust explode on the ground <br><br>I'm there, I'm there, I'm there, I'm there, I'm there, I'm there <br>Under, I'm THEREInside I'm feeling dirty <br>I'm there, I'm there, under, I've heardInside I'm feeling dirty <br>I've heard, I've headInside I'm feeling dirty <br>I've heard, I've headIt's only cos I'm hurting <br><br>I'm there, I'm there, I'm there, I'm there, I'm there, I'm there <br>Under, I'm THEREInside I'm feeling dirty <br>I'm there, I'm there, under, I've heardInside I'm feeling dirty <br>I've heard, I've headInside I'm feeling dirty <br>I've heard, I've headIt's only cos I'm hurting <br><br>Inside I'm feeling dirty <br>Inside I'm feeling dirty <br>Inside I'm feeling dirty <br>It's only cos I'm hurting]]></content><category term="Young Fathers" label="Young Fathers"/><category term="I Heard" label="I Heard"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김감미_T-Shine/슬플_비/</id><title>김감미 (T-Shine) - 슬플 비 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:01:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:01:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EA%B0%90%EB%AF%B8_T-Shine/%EC%8A%AC%ED%94%8C_%EB%B9%84/" title="김감미 (T-Shine) - 슬플 비 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비가 내리네 <br>니가 좋아하던 <br>비가 내리네 <br>많이도 오네 <br>니가 또 머리 <br>속에 맴도네 <br>내가 못나서 <br>끝내 너에게 <br>상처준게 나라서 <br>자꾸 생각나나봐 <br>니가 <br>오늘도 어김 없이 <br>내리는 비 <br>별안간 맑다가도 <br>매몰차게 흐르는 이 <br>비를 보면 또 <br>너와의 기억이 떠올라 <br>보고싶단 말이 <br>다시 내 목을 졸라와 <br>지금 널 봐도 <br>난 당당하지 못할 걸 <br>쥐 죽은 듯이 살아보려 <br>난 애 쓰고 있어 <br>근데 이 비가 <br>나를 안도와주네 <br>또 널 그리네 <br>비가 내리는 날이면 <br>이 분위기가 좋다며 <br>웃던 니가 또 생각나 <br>행복했던 추억에 잠겨 <br>비가 싫던 나마저도 <br>니가 있기에 좋았지 <br>하지만 이젠 니 생각만 <br>나게 되는 그저 슬플 비 <br>너와 헤어지던 <br>날 조차 비가 <br>내렸었던 기억 <br>운명의 장난이네 <br>니가 좋아했던 비였고 <br>그런 널 볼 때 <br>난 늘 웃고 있었던 <br>기억뿐인데 <br>이젠 슬픔 속에 <br>사무쳐있네 <br>매일이 맑을 수는 <br>없는 것 같아 <br>아무렇지 않게 살다가도 <br>니가 생각나 <br>지금 다시 생각해보면 <br>무슨 말부터 꺼내야할지 <br>panic에 빠져 <br>멍때렸던 나와는 달리 <br>넌 다 알고 있다는 듯이 <br>너무 차분해 <br>그에 반해 내 정신은 <br>이미 분해 된지 오래 <br>아직도 니가 내 곁에서 <br>살아 숨쉬는 것만 같아 <br>이 비가 내릴 때마다 <br>너를 또 생각하며 <br>널 그리겠지 <br>아직 못 지운 니 번호를 <br>누르려하겠지 <br>비가 내리는 날이면 <br>이 분위기가 좋다며 <br>웃던 니가 또 생각나 <br>행복했던 추억에 잠겨 <br>비가 싫던 나마저도 <br>니가 있기에 좋았지 <br>하지만 이젠 니 생각만 <br>나게 되는 그저 슬플 비 <br>넌 비가 내려도 <br>나를 생각하진 않겠지 <br>내가 비를 좋아한 건 <br>아니었으니 <br>비가 내려도 <br>내가 생각날리는 없겠지 <br>넌 비가 내려도 <br>내가 생각 날린 없겠지 <br>내가 비를 좋아한 건 <br>아니었으니 <br>비가 내려도 <br>생각날리는 없겠지 <br>내가 <br>이 비가 지나가도 <br>언젠간 다시 <br>비가 내리겠지 <br>Oh 넌 또 <br>생각나겠지 yeah <br>또 <br>비가 내리는 날이면 <br>이 분위기가 좋다며 <br>웃던 니가 또 생각나 <br>행복했던 추억에 잠겨 <br>비가 싫던 나마저도 <br>니가 있기에 좋았지 <br>하지만 이젠 니 생각만 <br>나게 되는 그저 슬플 비 <br>비가 내리는 날이면 <br>이 분위기가 좋다며 <br>웃던 니가 또 생각나 <br>행복했던 추억에 잠겨 <br>난 니생각에 또 잠겨 <br>널 그리겠지 난 또 <br>어쩔 수 없이 널 <br>또 생각하겠지 <br>]]></content><category term="김감미 (T-Shine)" label="김감미 (T-Shine)"/><category term="슬플 비" label="슬플 비"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Omar_Varela/Stronger_Feat_Miss_Lina/</id><title>Omar Varela - Stronger (Feat. Miss Lina) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:01:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:01:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Omar_Varela/Stronger_Feat_Miss_Lina/" title="Omar Varela - Stronger (Feat. Miss Lina) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What if I grow stronger <br>What if I get higher <br>What if I start doing things I know I will regret <br>I will make my own way <br>I will not surrender <br>I will do my best <br>Until I get put Under <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>W nohat I get higher <br>What if I start doing things I know I will regret <br>I will make my own way <br>I will not surrender <br>I will do my best <br>Until I get put Under <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger <br>What if I grow stronger]]></content><category term="Omar Varela" label="Omar Varela"/><category term="Stronger (Feat. Miss Lina)" label="Stronger (Feat. Miss Lina)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/2winsome_투윈썸/The_Eyes/</id><title>2winsome (투윈썸) - The Eyes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T19:01:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T19:01:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/2winsome_%ED%88%AC%EC%9C%88%EC%8D%B8/The_Eyes/" title="2winsome (투윈썸) - The Eyes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[네 눈을 좋아해 <br>깊은 눈을 가진 널 좋아해 <br>슬픈 너의 눈을 좋아해 <br>슬픈 너의 눈을 좋아해 <br>남들과는 좋아함의 <br>기준이 다른 너 <br>언제나 내게 말했어 <br>마음을 보는 눈이 있다면 <br>무슨 말이 필요할까 <br>and then you said <br>네 눈을 좋아해 <br>깊은 눈을 가진 널 좋아해 <br>슬픈 너의 눈을 좋아해 <br>슬픈 너의 눈을 좋아해 <br>상처 입은 마음에 <br>속상해 하던 너 <br>지금도 넌 내게 말해 <br>난 슬프고 우울해 보인대 <br>그래서 싫대 <br>너에게 마음으로 말해 <br>네 눈을 좋아해 <br>깊은 눈을 가진 널 좋아해 <br>슬픈 너의 눈을 좋아해 <br>슬픈 너의 눈을 좋아해 <br>네 눈을 좋아해 <br>깊은 눈을 가진 널 좋아해 <br>슬픈 너의 눈을 좋아해 <br>슬픈 너의 눈을 좋아해 <br>]]></content><category term="2winsome (투윈썸)" label="2winsome (투윈썸)"/><category term="The Eyes" label="The Eyes"/></entry></feed>