<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:30:25+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/어린이_경배와_찬양팀/바이블_어드벤처/</id><title>어린이 경배와 찬양팀 - 바이블 어드벤처 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:30:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:30:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%B4%EB%A6%B0%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B2%BD%EB%B0%B0%EC%99%80_%EC%B0%AC%EC%96%91%ED%8C%80/%EB%B0%94%EC%9D%B4%EB%B8%94_%EC%96%B4%EB%93%9C%EB%B2%A4%EC%B2%98/" title="어린이 경배와 찬양팀 - 바이블 어드벤처 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[믿음의 여행을 떠나요 <br>말씀의 여행을 떠나요 <br>신비롭고 놀라운 이야기가 <br>가득 가득해 <br>믿음의 여행을 떠나요 <br>말씀의 여행을 떠나요 <br>말씀이 생명 되어 <br>우리의 삶에 역사 하시네 <br>바이블 어드벤처 <br>성경 속으로 <br>바이블 어드벤처 <br>함께 떠나요 <br>바이블 어드벤처 <br>성경 속으로 <br>신나는 성경여행 떠나요 <br>우리 함께 <br>기적 속으로 <br>믿음의 여행을 떠나요 <br>말씀의 여행을 떠나요 <br>말씀이 생명 되어 <br>우리의 삶에 역사 하시네 <br>바이블 어드벤처 <br>성경 속으로 <br>바이블 어드벤처 <br>함께 떠나요 <br>바이블 어드벤처 <br>성경 속으로 <br>신나는 성경여행 떠나요 <br>우리 함께 <br>기적 속으로 <br>바이블 어드벤처 <br>성경 속으로 <br>신나는 성경여행 떠나요 <br>우리 함께 <br>기적 속으로 <br>]]></content><category term="어린이 경배와 찬양팀" label="어린이 경배와 찬양팀"/><category term="바이블 어드벤처" label="바이블 어드벤처"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/What_Shouldnt_I_Be_/</id><title>Sampha - What Shouldn`t I Be? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:30:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:30:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/What_Shouldnt_I_Be_/" title="Sampha - What Shouldn`t I Be? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You can always, you can always come home <br>I know you've been out there, out there on your own <br>Out there on your own <br>I wake up in my own skin again <br>Thinking all about me <br>What shouldn't I be? <br>What shouldn't I be? <br>What shouldn't I be? <br>What shouldn't I be today? <br>Family ties <br>Put them 'round my neck <br>I'm walkin' 'round high <br>A ghost by my side <br>Challenges come <br>Challenges come and they go <br>I need someone to help me down <br>You can always come home <br>You can always come home <br>A mother always knows <br>I needed to grow <br>Just, it's all about you now <br>And what shouldn't you be? <br>What shouldn't you be? <br>What shouldn't you be? <br>I should visit my brother <br>But I haven't been there in months <br>I've lost connection, signal <br>To how we were <br>What shouldn't I be? <br>(What shouldn't I be?) <br>It's not all about me <br>(What shouldn't I be?)]]></content><category term="Sampha" label="Sampha"/><category term="What Shouldn`t I Be?" label="What Shouldn`t I Be?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Incomplete_Kisses/</id><title>Sampha - Incomplete Kisses - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:30:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:30:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Incomplete_Kisses/" title="Sampha - Incomplete Kisses - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Those incomplete kisses <br>Were weighing you down with every step <br>In this house we're sinking <br>But we're too far numb to really care <br>The TV keeps glitching <br>The lights dim down and portals appear <br>And somehow you step out <br>To say you're not by yourself now <br>Those incomplete kisses <br>Those incomplete kisses <br>Wait too long, you'll miss it <br>Before long you're missing <br>Don't let your heart hide your story <br>Don't let your mind hide your story <br>'Cause if you deny others inside <br>It gets harder to move along <br>Moving on <br>Flying high above all your memories <br>I have a birds-eye view <br>A child stood at the cemetery <br>He looks just like you <br>Orange, yellow, purple, blue skies <br>A painting so true <br>And I hear those cries <br>Don't you leave me here <br>Don't you leave me here <br>Those incomplete kisses <br>Those incomplete <br>Wait too long, you'll miss it <br>Wait too long <br>Those incomplete kisses <br>Those incomplete <br>Those incomplete kisses <br>Those incomplete kisses <br>Wait too long, you'll miss it <br>Before long, you're missing <br>Don't let your heart hide your story <br>Don't let your heart hide your story <br>'Cause if you deny others inside <br>It gets harder to move along <br>Moving on <br>Those incomplete kisses <br>Were weighing you down with every step <br>In this house we're sinking <br>But we're too far numb to really care <br>The TV keeps glitching <br>The lights dim down and portals appear]]></content><category term="Sampha" label="Sampha"/><category term="Incomplete Kisses" label="Incomplete Kisses"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Timmys_Prayer/</id><title>Sampha - Timmy`s Prayer - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:30:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:30:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Timmys_Prayer/" title="Sampha - Timmy`s Prayer - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If ever you're listening <br>If ever you're listening <br>If ever you're listening <br>If ever you're listening <br>If heaven's a prison <br>Then I am your prisoner <br>Yes, I am your prisoner <br>I messed up, ooh <br>I know now <br>There's no room for me to play now <br>Nowhere to dig my way out <br>My vital organs are beating through <br>My ribcage opened, my heart ballooned <br>I... I've lost another one <br>I'm on the floor trying to dress my wounds <br>Address the fact it was mine to lose <br>I... I didn't try enough <br>And when I'm left without your love <br>It could feel like a lifetime baby <br>And somewhere in the start we had it alright <br>Sunshine and blue skies, yes I call <br>But now there's a darker blue <br>I'm bleeding and you don't care <br>The sun sinks and you're not there <br>If ever you're listening <br>If heaven's a prison <br>Then I am your prisoner <br>Yes, I am your prisoner <br>I messed up, ooh <br>I know now <br>There's no room for me to play now <br>Nowhere to dig my way out <br>My brother always said I'm a dreamer, dreamer <br>You better watch out where this life will lead ya <br>And he always said she's a keeper keeper <br>She'll stay by your side when the rest will leave ya <br>Well I'm looking on my left side, I'm looking on my right <br>She's nowhere to be seen now when I close my eyes at night <br>Dreaming, surely you can find me by the shore <br>I'm singing so blindly, can you hear me? <br>Can you find me? <br>If you find me, wanna tell you I love you so <br>I wanna tell you that love comes and goes <br>That it comes and goes <br>I hear the footsteps in the water and I feel the breeze <br>I open my eyes and no words, no words <br>I wish that I listened when I was in prison <br>Now I'm just a visitor <br>I came to the gates but you turned me away <br>You asked me what am I waiting for <br>I'm waiting cause I fucked up, ooh <br>I got thrown out <br>I don't know which way to go now <br>Don't know which way is home now <br>If ever you're listening <br>If heaven's a prison <br>Then I am your prisoner <br>Yes, I am your prisoner <br>I messed up, oh <br>I know now <br>There's no room for me to play now <br>Nowhere to dig my way out]]></content><category term="Sampha" label="Sampha"/><category term="Timmy`s Prayer" label="Timmy`s Prayer"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Under/</id><title>Sampha - Under - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:30:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:30:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Under/" title="Sampha - Under - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Under, under, under, under, under, under, under, under, under <br>You, you, you, you, you, ooh <br>Thunder, thunder, thunder, thunder, thunder <br>under, under, under, under, under, under <br>You, you, you, you, you, ooh-ooh-ooh <br>Sophisticated bitter queen <br>You're the ghost in my machine <br>As I sit at my piano <br>And flick through every channel <br>Channeling those memories <br>Trying to put and end to these <br>I don't need you now <br>I don't need you now <br>I don't need you now <br>I don't, I don't <br>I wonder, sit and watch you wonder <br>I see you manipulate your lover <br>Take cover, waves come crashing over us <br>And I go under <br>Under, under, under, under <br>And yes, I'm under your spell <br>Thunder, thunder, thunder, thunder <br>Under <br>You, you, you, you, you <br>Waves come crashing over me <br>I'm somewhere in open sea <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>I'm gasping for air <br>A nemesis, an enemy <br>You're the crack inside the screen <br>As I'm singing my soprano <br>Still flicking through the channels <br>Signal lost and out of reach <br>You're eyes become the TV screens <br>As I sit I watch you walk my way <br>Static, the static on those screens now <br>We're together, on this balcony yeah <br>I'm still swimming in those eyes <br>You made it rain like you own the sky, oh <br>You made it rain like you own the sky <br>I wonder, sit and watch you wonder <br>I see you manipulate your lover <br>Take cover, waves come crashing over us <br>And I go under <br>Under, under, under, under <br>And yes, I'm under your spell <br>Thunder, thunder, thunder, thunder <br>Under <br>You, you, you, you, you <br>Waves come crashing over me <br>I'm somewhere in open sea <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeahh <br>I'm gasping for air <br>I can feel it <br>Slipping away <br>Slipping away <br>Under, under, under, under <br>You, you, you, you, you, ooh <br>Thunder, thunder, thunder <br>You, you, you, you, you, you]]></content><category term="Sampha" label="Sampha"/><category term="Under" label="Under"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Reverse_Faults/</id><title>Sampha - Reverse Faults - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:30:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:30:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Reverse_Faults/" title="Sampha - Reverse Faults - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a fault in my structure <br>It's always you and never me <br>I threw the blame and it shattered <br>And now there's broken glass praying to be healed <br>You struck a chord and I listened <br>You damn near broke all the strings <br>When you get close, I get distant <br>Instead I'll drive away to a place surreal <br>And tell me how that feels <br>Took the brake pads out the car <br>And I flew <br>Smashed this window in my heart <br>And I blamed you <br>This anger's taking me apart <br>Explosive truths <br>Except this time I went too far <br>And I hurt you <br>I wish I could take it back right now <br>Where's that smile when it matters? <br>Where was I when you called? <br>I shot the blame and it scattered <br>Now there's bullet holes spread across the walls <br>I took the shape of a letter <br>Slipped myself underneath your door <br>In this red room we develop <br>An understanding of all our wrongs <br>Now we can move along <br>Took the brake pads out the car <br>And I flew <br>Smashed this window in my heart <br>And I blamed you <br>This anger's taking me apart <br>Explosive truths <br>Except this time I went too far <br>And I hurt you <br>I wish I could take it back right]]></content><category term="Sampha" label="Sampha"/><category term="Reverse Faults" label="Reverse Faults"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Take_Me_Inside/</id><title>Sampha - Take Me Inside - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:30:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:30:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Take_Me_Inside/" title="Sampha - Take Me Inside - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Does he still make your blood rush? <br>These days I'm just not sure how to feel <br>Does he still make you run wild? <br>Silence, and your lips were sealed <br>As if you didn't care <br>And your love was gone <br>Her love was lost <br>Calm before the storm <br>I don't care if you take me inside <br>You can be what you want every time <br>And I know it's hard to find the mind to say you do <br>You're free <br>You're free <br>You're free <br>You're free <br>You're free enough to find your feet <br>You're also free enough to hide from me <br>And I seek <br>I seek <br>I seek <br>I seek <br>I'm seeking something I can't see <br>I may be reading in too deep <br>And maybe this is all a dream]]></content><category term="Sampha" label="Sampha"/><category term="Take Me Inside" label="Take Me Inside"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/No_One_Knows_Me_Like_The_Piano/</id><title>Sampha - (No One Knows Me) Like The Piano - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:30:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:30:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/No_One_Knows_Me_Like_The_Piano/" title="Sampha - (No One Knows Me) Like The Piano - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[no one knows me like the piano <br>in my mother's home <br>you would show me <br>i had something <br>some people call a soul <br>you dropped out the sky <br>oh you arrived <br>when i was 3 years old <br>no one knows me like the piano <br>in my mother's home <br><br>you know i left, i flew the nest <br>and you know i won’t be long <br>and in my chest you know me best <br>and you know i’ll be back home <br><br>an angel by her side <br>oh all the times, <br>i knew we couldn't cope <br>they said that it's her time, <br>no tears in sight <br>i kept the feelings close <br>and you took hold of me <br>and never never, never <br>let me go <br><br>cos no one knows me like the piano <br>in my mother's home]]></content><category term="Sampha" label="Sampha"/><category term="(No One Knows Me) Like The Piano" label="(No One Knows Me) Like The Piano"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Kora_Sings/</id><title>Sampha - Kora Sings - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:30:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:30:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Kora_Sings/" title="Sampha - Kora Sings - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's no one here for miles <br>It's just me in the burning sun <br>It's just me, myself and my gun <br>Remembering the times <br>Oh grapes on the vines <br>But with family, I <br>I don't have the time <br>The time to be questioning life <br>You just gotta be there <br>A mother needs her sons <br>Oh she needs them near <br>We don't have to talk <br>I just need you here <br>But if you go away <br>Please don't disappear <br>The heat is making light <br>Of a heavy year <br>I really hope there's rainfall <br>My hands together looking at the stars <br>I really hope there's angels <br>Because the world is turning, turning way too fast <br>She says she can't turn tables <br>Well I say you don't know how wrong you are <br>Or just how strong you are <br>You don't know how strong you are <br>A pillow on your face soaking up those tears <br>Who's anyone to say you should have no fear? <br>A mouth full of smoke really made things clear <br>You've been with me since the cradle <br>You've been with me, you're my angel <br>Please don't you disappear <br>It's just me in the burning sun <br>It's just me, myself and my gun <br>Remembering the times]]></content><category term="Sampha" label="Sampha"/><category term="Kora Sings" label="Kora Sings"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Blood_On_Me/</id><title>Sampha - Blood On Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:30:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:30:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Blood_On_Me/" title="Sampha - Blood On Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[grey hoodies, they cover their heads <br>i can’t see their faces, can’t see see see <br>they knew me, look sweat on my head <br>my heart was thumping, drumming <br><br>no need, no need to take from me <br>don’t throw the paint on me <br>i see this lake forming <br>i got lost astray, <br>in this forest running away <br><br>i slip up, i’m on the edge now, <br>they see me and i nearly, <br>i nearly lose my grip <br>but you held on to me, <br>and you shake and tell me that i'm ok but <br><br>i swear they smell the blood on me <br>i hear them coming for me <br><br>i wake up, and the sky's blood red <br>still heavy breathing <br>felt so much more than dreaming <br>i get up, they’re at the edge of my bed <br>how did they finally find me. <br>they said, there’s something bleeding in me <br>something screaming in me <br>something buried deep beneath <br><br>well i need to, need to get away <br>so get in, steal this get away <br>and i accelerate and i accelerate <br>but my gears got stuck <br>i’m on this road now <br>i’m so alone now, <br>swerving out of control now. <br>and i crash the whip, <br>and this tree flew through me <br>arms out you pull me <br>and wipe my wounds clean but <br><br>i swear they smell the blood on me <br>i hear them coming for me]]></content><category term="Sampha" label="Sampha"/><category term="Blood On Me" label="Blood On Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Plastic_100C/</id><title>Sampha - Plastic 100`C - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:30:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:30:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sampha/Plastic_100C/" title="Sampha - Plastic 100`C - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[magnetic light in the blue high haze <br>magnifying glass upon my face <br>it's so hot I've been melting out here <br>I'm made out of plastic out here <br>you touched down in the base of my fears <br>Houston... can you hear? <br><br>and we both had to harness our pain <br>close it and hope it decays <br>oh inhale and I'm up and away <br>up and away <br><br>I love those mornings <br>when the sun's up <br>smoking in the lobby <br>waiting for my name to pop up <br>yeah pop up <br><br>usually I'd run home <br>and tuck the issue under <br>oh <br>sleeping with my worries yeah <br>I didn't really know what that lump was <br>my luck <br><br>it's so hot I've been melting out here <br>I'm made out of plastic out here <br>you touched down in the base of my fears <br>and that's when your beauty appears <br>Houston can you hear me now? <br> You dare know what the scarecrow hears <br>it's like outer space in his inner ears <br>like a blossom you opened up <br>and understood why you could not love <br><br>it's so hot I've been melting out here <br>I'm made out of plastic out here <br><br>you touched down in the base of my fears <br>Houston... can you hear? <br><br>Sky high deflating ideas <br>thriving off your lessons <br>and yes you are my lantern <br>shy light curves around my ears <br>the more you speak the more I see <br>the more your light grows upon me <br>and the more it grows the closer <br>I think you are the closer I think you are <br>to seeing me whole <br>what if you don't like what you see, <br>silhouettes inside a dream <br><br>and I'm melting from the light <br>one drip at a time <br>I'm melting from the light <br>one drip, one drip at a time]]></content><category term="Sampha" label="Sampha"/><category term="Plastic 100`C" label="Plastic 100`C"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/청혜/사는_동안에/</id><title>청혜 - 사는 동안에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:31:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:31:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%AD%ED%98%9C/%EC%82%AC%EB%8A%94_%EB%8F%99%EC%95%88%EC%97%90/" title="청혜 - 사는 동안에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세상이 힘들어도 <br>웃으며 살자고 <br>누가 그런 말을 모르나 <br>나도 웃고싶다 <br>사랑하는 그대와 <br>친구도 있었지 <br>지금은 모두 떠나가고 <br>아무도 없지만 <br>사는 동안에 나에게도 <br>꿈이 있었지 <br>사는 동안에 나에게도 <br>가슴벅찬 날들 <br>세상이 속일지라도 <br>행복했던 날들 하하 <br>한번쯤 울어 볼 수 있어 <br>사는 동안에 <br>사랑하는 그대와 <br>친구도 있었지 <br>지금은 모두 떠나가고 <br>아무도 없지만 <br>사는 동안에 나에게도 <br>꿈이 있었지 <br>사는 동안에 나에게도 <br>가슴벅찬 날들 <br>세상이 속일지라도 <br>행복했던 날들 하하 <br>한번쯤 울어 볼 수 있어 <br>사는 동안에 <br>한번쯤 울어 볼 수 있어 <br>사는 동안에 <br>]]></content><category term="청혜" label="청혜"/><category term="사는 동안에" label="사는 동안에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/청혜/남자는_울지_않는다/</id><title>청혜 - 남자는 울지 않는다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:31:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:31:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%AD%ED%98%9C/%EB%82%A8%EC%9E%90%EB%8A%94_%EC%9A%B8%EC%A7%80_%EC%95%8A%EB%8A%94%EB%8B%A4/" title="청혜 - 남자는 울지 않는다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑 때문에 울지않으리 <br>사랑 때문에 울긴 왜 울어 <br>어차피 떠나갈 사람인 것을 <br>남자가 울긴 왜 울어 <br>그대가 떠나가면 <br>사랑도 가고 <br>남겨진 추억뿐인데 <br>사랑이 떠나가는 <br>길목에 서서 <br>그대 행복 빌어주면서 <br>돌아서는 가슴이 아파도 <br>남자는 울지않는다 <br>사랑 때문에 울지않으리 <br>사랑 때문에 울긴 왜 울어 <br>어차피 떠나갈 사람인 것을 <br>남자가 울긴 왜 울어 <br>그대가 떠나가면 <br>사랑도 가고 <br>남겨진 추억뿐인데 <br>사랑이 떠나가는 <br>길목에 서서 <br>그대 행복 빌어주면서 <br>돌아서는 가슴이 아파도 <br>남자는 울지않는다 <br>돌아서는 가슴이 아파도 <br>남자는 울지않는다 <br>]]></content><category term="청혜" label="청혜"/><category term="남자는 울지 않는다" label="남자는 울지 않는다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/청혜/그리움/</id><title>청혜 - 그리움 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:31:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:31:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%AD%ED%98%9C/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9B%80/" title="청혜 - 그리움 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세월은 소리 없이 흘러가고 <br>사랑도 그렇게 떠나가고 <br>흘러간 그 세월은 소리 없이 <br>그리움이 되어 다가오네 <br>떠나간 그 사람은 어디에서 <br>한번쯤 내 모습 생각할까 <br>그리워 눈감으면 그대 모습 <br>언제나 내 곁에 있었네 <br>단 한번만이라도 <br>돌아올 수 없을까 <br>가슴 속에 머물러 <br>떠나지 않는 그 모습 <br>단 한번만이라도 <br>만날 수는 없을까 <br>내 모든걸 다 바쳐 <br>사랑했던 그 사람 <br>세월은 소리 없이 흘러가고 <br>사랑도 그렇게 떠나가고 <br>흘러간 그 세월은 소리 없이 <br>그리움이 되어 다가오네 <br>떠나간 그 사람은 어디에서 <br>한번쯤 내 모습 생각할까 <br>그리워 눈감으면 그대 모습 <br>언제나 내 곁에 있었네 <br>단 한번만이라도 <br>돌아올 수 없을까 <br>가슴 속에 머물러 <br>떠나지 않는 그 모습 <br>단 한번만이라도 <br>만날 수는 없을까 <br>내 모든걸 다 바쳐 <br>사랑했던 그 사람 <br>사랑했던 그 사람 <br>]]></content><category term="청혜" label="청혜"/><category term="그리움" label="그리움"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/청혜/떠나가시면/</id><title>청혜 - 떠나가시면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:31:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:31:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%AD%ED%98%9C/%EB%96%A0%EB%82%98%EA%B0%80%EC%8B%9C%EB%A9%B4/" title="청혜 - 떠나가시면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대 떠나가시면 <br>잊을 수 있을까요 <br>그토록 사랑한 날들 <br>잊을 수 있을까요 <br>내사랑 모두 거두어 <br>함께 갈 수 없나요 <br>당신의 사랑으로 <br>함께했던 날들 <br>그대 없는 하늘은 <br>눈물이 되겠지 <br>그대 없는 세상도 <br>눈물 속에 잠기고 <br>메마른 내사랑 <br>헤매어 울 텐데 <br>떠나가시면 그대 <br>잊을 수 있을까요 <br>내사랑 모두 거두어 <br>함께 갈 수 없나요 <br>당신의 사랑으로 <br>함께했던 날들 <br>그대 없는 하늘은 <br>눈물이 되겠지 <br>그대 없는 세상도 <br>눈물 속에 잠기고 <br>메마른 내사랑 <br>헤매어 울 텐데 <br>떠나가시면 그대 <br>잊을 수 있을까요 <br>]]></content><category term="청혜" label="청혜"/><category term="떠나가시면" label="떠나가시면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/청혜/서울역/</id><title>청혜 - 서울역 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:31:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:31:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%AD%ED%98%9C/%EC%84%9C%EC%9A%B8%EC%97%AD/" title="청혜 - 서울역 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[서울역에 밤비가 <br>비가 내린다 <br>하염없이 나를 울리네 <br>한번 준 이 마음 잊을 수가 없어 <br>나 여기 다시 찾아왔네 <br>어디로 갔는지 <br>그 누굴 사랑하는지 <br>나에게 남은 사랑 <br>당신뿐이라는데 <br>서울역의 밤이여 <br>그 사람은 어디에 <br>마지막 열차는 떠나가는데 <br>서울역에 밤비가 <br>비가 내린다 <br>하염없이 나를 울리네 <br>한번 준 이 마음 잊을 수가 없어 <br>나 여기 다시 찾아왔네 <br>어디로 갔는지 <br>그 누굴 사랑하는지 <br>나에게 남은 사랑 <br>당신뿐이라는데 <br>서울역의 밤이여 <br>그 사람은 어디에 <br>마지막 열차는 떠나가는데 <br>서울역의 밤이여 <br>그 사람은 어디에 <br>마지막 열차는 떠나가는데 <br>]]></content><category term="청혜" label="청혜"/><category term="서울역" label="서울역"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김태훈/영원한_사랑이여/</id><title>김태훈 - 영원한 사랑이여 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:31:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:31:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%83%9C%ED%9B%88/%EC%98%81%EC%9B%90%ED%95%9C_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4%EC%97%AC/" title="김태훈 - 영원한 사랑이여 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 너를 처음 보았을 때 <br>내 가슴은 뛰었죠 <br>하늘은 맑고 푸르러 <br>나는 하늘을 날으고 있죠 <br>너의 시선 내 눈 속에 있을 때 <br>나는 느끼고 있죠 <br>가슴 뭉클한 사랑을 <br>영원토록 간직하리 <br>사랑하는 그대와 함께 <br>기쁨을 주고 받을 때 <br>세상 값진 그 무엇보다 <br>정말로 소중하리 <br>사랑하는 그대와 함께 <br>슬픔을 나누어도 <br>그 슬픔은 우리의 진정 <br>사랑의 결실이리 <br>이 땅에 그 무엇보다 <br>우리는 아름다워 <br>모두가 우리를 축복해요 <br>영원한 사랑이여 <br>사랑하는 그대와 함께 <br>기쁨을 주고 받을 때 <br>세상 값진 그 무엇보다 <br>정말로 소중하리 <br>사랑하는 그대와 함께 <br>슬픔을 나누어도 <br>그 슬픔은 우리의 진정 <br>사랑의 결실이리 <br>이 땅에 그 무엇보다 <br>우리는 아름다워 <br>모두가 우리를 축복해요 <br>영원한 사랑이여 <br>이 땅에 그 무엇보다 <br>우리는 아름다워 <br>모두가 우리를 축복해요 <br>영원한 사랑이여 <br>모두가 우리를 축복해요 <br>영원한 사랑이여 <br>]]></content><category term="김태훈" label="김태훈"/><category term="영원한 사랑이여" label="영원한 사랑이여"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김태훈/할아버지와_담배연기/</id><title>김태훈 - 할아버지와 담배연기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:31:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:31:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%83%9C%ED%9B%88/%ED%95%A0%EC%95%84%EB%B2%84%EC%A7%80%EC%99%80_%EB%8B%B4%EB%B0%B0%EC%97%B0%EA%B8%B0/" title="김태훈 - 할아버지와 담배연기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 어렸을 적에 <br>할아버지 담배연기 <br>정말로 싫어서 <br>할아버질 피해 다녔죠 <br>그러나 할아버지는 <br>항상 나를 찾았죠 <br>나는 정말 철부지 같았죠 <br>할아버진 지금 <br>계시지는 않지만 <br>나는 할아버질 사랑해요 <br>할아버지가 뿜어내는 <br>담배연긴 싫지만 <br>나는 지금 할아버지가 <br>그리워요 <br>나는 지금 뒷동산에서 <br>할아버지와 뛰놀던 <br>그때를 생각 하면서 <br>할아버질 그리죠 <br>할아버지는 <br>나를 이 세상에서 <br>언제나 제일 <br>사랑한다 하셨죠 <br>할아버진 지금 <br>계시지는 않지만 <br>나는 할아버질 사랑해요 <br>할아버지가 뿜어내는 <br>담배연긴 싫지만 <br>나는 지금 할아버지가 <br>그리워요 <br>나는 지금 뒷동산에서 <br>할아버지와 뛰놀던 <br>그때를 생각 하면서 <br>할아버질 그리죠 <br>할아버지는 <br>나를 이 세상에서 <br>언제나 제일 <br>사랑한다 하셨죠 <br>나도 할아버지를 <br>이 세상에서 <br>언제나 제일 사랑해요 <br>사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="김태훈" label="김태훈"/><category term="할아버지와 담배연기" label="할아버지와 담배연기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김태훈/소리쳐봐/</id><title>김태훈 - 소리쳐봐 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:31:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:31:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%83%9C%ED%9B%88/%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC%EC%B3%90%EB%B4%90/" title="김태훈 - 소리쳐봐 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[소리쳐봐 소리쳐봐 <br>세상 속에 나의 꿈을 펼쳐봐 <br>아름다운 꿈을 그려 내봐 <br>소리쳐봐 소리쳐봐 <br>세상 속에 나의 꿈을 펼쳐봐 <br>아름다운 꿈을 그려봐 <br>힘들었었던 나의 과거를 잊었니 <br>고통스러운 지난 시절을 기억해 <br>세상이 나를 모두가 <br>외면해도 두렵지 않아 <br>나에게는 커다란 꿈이 있잖아 <br>자 쉬지 말고 달리는 거야 <br>가슴속에 아픔을 삼켜둔 채 <br>소리쳐봐 소리쳐봐 <br>세상 속에 나의 꿈을 펼쳐봐 <br>아름다운 꿈을 그려 내봐 <br>소리쳐봐 소리쳐봐 <br>세상 속에 나의 꿈을 펼쳐봐 <br>아름다운 꿈을 그려봐 <br>세상은 넓고 할 일은 너무 많은데 <br>어두움만이 무겁게 나를 누르네 <br>새벽이 오는 광활한 <br>대지 위를 힘껏 뛰어봐 <br>나에게는 커다란 꿈이 있잖아 <br>자 두 팔 벌려 하늘을 보라 <br>저 태양을 내 안에 삼켜버려 <br>소리쳐봐 소리쳐봐 <br>세상 속에 나의 꿈을 펼쳐봐 <br>아름다운 꿈을 그려 내봐 <br>소리쳐봐 소리쳐봐 <br>세상 속에 나의 꿈을 펼쳐봐 <br>아름다운 꿈을 그려봐 <br>소리쳐봐 소리쳐봐 <br>세상 속에 나의 꿈을 펼쳐봐 <br>아름다운 꿈을 그려 내봐 <br>소리쳐봐 소리쳐봐 <br>세상 속에 나의 꿈을 펼쳐봐 <br>아름다운 꿈을 그려봐 <br>아름다운 꿈을 그려봐 <br>아름다운 꿈을 그려봐 <br>소리쳐봐 <br>]]></content><category term="김태훈" label="김태훈"/><category term="소리쳐봐" label="소리쳐봐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김태훈/동창회/</id><title>김태훈 - 동창회 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:31:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:31:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%83%9C%ED%9B%88/%EB%8F%99%EC%B0%BD%ED%9A%8C/" title="김태훈 - 동창회 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[몰랐었다 예전에 <br>내가 누군지 <br>잊었었다 나의 기억들 <br>지나버린 세월만큼 <br>아련한 추억 <br>바로 어제만 같은데 <br>흘러가는 세월 속에서 <br>멈춰버린 시간 속에서 <br>예전처럼 울고 웃고 <br>마음껏 마셔봐 <br>아 대차게 한번 사는 거야 <br>어차피 인생 한번이야 <br>어느 누가 감히 <br>나를 비웃을 소냐 <br>그래 우리 모두 <br>예전에 꿈들 <br>한잔 술에 담아 마셔봐 <br>몰랐었다 내 청춘 <br>그리 짧은지 <br>잊었었다 나의 꿈들을 <br>이젠 모두 누군가의 <br>사람이 되어 <br>내 꿈을 잊고 사누나 <br>흘러가는 세월 속에서 <br>멈춰버린 시간 속에서 <br>예전처럼 울고 웃고 <br>마음껏 마셔봐 <br>아 대차게 한번 사는 거야 <br>어차피 인생 한번이야 <br>어느 누가 감히 <br>나를 비웃을 소냐 <br>그래 우리 모두 <br>예전에 꿈들 <br>한잔 술에 담아 마셔봐 <br>대차게 한번 사는 거야 <br>어차피 인생 한번이야 <br>어느 누가 감히 <br>나를 비웃을 소냐 <br>그래 우리 모두 <br>예전에 꿈들 <br>한잔 술에 담아 마셔봐 <br>한잔 술에 담아 마셔봐 <br>]]></content><category term="김태훈" label="김태훈"/><category term="동창회" label="동창회"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/찬_ChAN/Im_In_Love/</id><title>찬 (ChAN) - I`m In Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:32:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:32:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B0%AC_ChAN/Im_In_Love/" title="찬 (ChAN) - I`m In Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[고작 하루 새 <br>달라진 아침이 <br>너무 반가워 <br>오늘이 온 거야 <br>좋은 꿈도 꾼 게 아닌데 <br>난 웃음이 나 <br>I’m in Love 난 그대와 <br>사랑스런 그대와 <br>정말 오랫동안 <br>너에게 주고 싶던 맘 <br>사랑스런 그대와 I’m in Love <br>고작 하루 새 <br>하루가 달콤해 <br>너무 행복해 <br>너를 안을 거야 <br>좋은 꿈도 꾼 게 아닌데 <br>난 웃음이 나 <br>I’m in Love 난 그대와 <br>사랑스런 그대와 <br>정말 오랫동안 <br>너에게 주고 싶던 맘 <br>사랑스런 그대와 I’m in Love <br>언제나 말하고 싶던 말 <br>너에게 나 간다고 <br>정말 오랫동안 <br>너에게 주고 싶던 맘 <br>이제는 보이니 I’m in Love <br>]]></content><category term="찬 (ChAN)" label="찬 (ChAN)"/><category term="I`m In Love" label="I`m In Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/크로스진_CROSS_GENE/Black_mind/</id><title>크로스진 (CROSS GENE) - Black mind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:32:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:32:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%81%AC%EB%A1%9C%EC%8A%A4%EC%A7%84_CROSS_GENE/Black_mind/" title="크로스진 (CROSS GENE) - Black mind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Black or White <br>Black or White <br>자극하지마 나를 <br>꿈꾸게 좀 하지마 <br>달콤한 유혹 <br>눈을 가리려고 하지마 <br>자꾸 겁이나 겁이 나 <br>겁이 나 네가 참 <br>퍽이나 퍽이나 <br>퍽이나 내게 <br>그딴 거짓말 <br>나를 속일 수는 없잖아 <br>take your mind take your mind <br>너의 맘을 갖겠어 <br>두 귀를 닫아도 막지 못해 <br>there is no way <br>벗어날 수 없어 넌 <br>take your time take your time <br>시간을 내게 맡겨 <br>못 믿겠지만 지켜 봐왔어 <br>all day <br>드디어 막이 오르네 <br>진실을 막을 수 없네 <br>타락한 나를 구원해 <br>회색빛으로 물든 날 <br>어디로 갈지 몰라 <br>Black or White <br>기대하지마 미래 따윈 <br>내겐 없잖아 <br>마지막 기회 눈앞에서 <br>놓쳐 봤잖아 <br>네가 감히 날 감히 <br>날 감히 날 판단해 <br>깊숙이 감춰진 <br>진실의 가면 <br>새빨간 사과 독이 <br>들어있을게 뻔해 <br>take your mind take your mind <br>너의 맘을 갖겠어 <br>어느 누구도 <br>널 가지지 못해 <br>정해진 레이스 <br>내가 선두를 달려 <br>take your time take your time <br>시간을 내게 맡겨 <br>의심하지마 무조건 <br>이기는 game <br>드디어 막이 오르네 <br>진실을 막을 수 없네 <br>타락한 나를 구원해 <br>회색빛으로 물든 날 <br>어디로 갈지 몰라 <br>어둠이 지나가고 <br>빛이 쏟아지는 시공간에 <br>발길을 멈추게 하는 <br>타락하지 않은 유일한 너 <br>드디어 막이 오르네 <br>진실을 막을 수 없네 <br>타락한 나를 구원해 <br>회색빛으로 물든 날 <br>어디로 갈지 몰라 <br>절대 굴하지 않아 <br>I’ll never give up <br>]]></content><category term="크로스진 (CROSS GENE)" label="크로스진 (CROSS GENE)"/><category term="Black mind" label="Black mind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christina_Aguilera/Fighter/</id><title>Christina Aguilera - Fighter - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:32:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:32:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christina_Aguilera/Fighter/" title="Christina Aguilera - Fighter - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hm, after all you put me through <br>You think I despise you. <br>But in the end, I wanna thank you <br>Cuz you made me that much stronger <br><br>When I thought I knew you <br>Thinkin’ that you were true Guess I, I couldn’t trust <br>Caught your bluff <br>Time is up cuz I’ve had enough <br>You were there by my side <br>Always down for the ride...but your <br>Joyride just came down in flames <br>Cuz you greed sold me out to shame <br>After all of the stealing and cheating <br>You probably think that I hold resentment for you <br>But uh uh <br>No no..you’re wrong <br>See if it wasn’t for all that you tried to do <br>I wouldn’t know just how capable <br>I am to pull through so I wanna say thank you <br>Cuz it makes me that much stronger <br>Makes me work a little bit harder <br>Makes me that much wiser <br>So thanks for making me a fighter <br>Made me learn a little bit faster <br>Made my skin a little bit thicker <br>Made me that much smarter <br>Thanks for making me a fighter <br>Ohh Ohh Ohhh Ohhh <br>Yeah Yeah Yeah <br>Never saw it coming <br>All of your backstabbing <br>I guess so you could cash in on a good thing before I realized your game <br>I heard you’re going around playing <br>The victim now, but don’t <br>Even begin feelin I’m the one to blame <br>Cuz you dug your own grave, uh huh <br>After all of the fights and the lies yes you wanted to harm me <br>But that won’t work anymore <br>No more... no no... it’s over <br>See if it wasn’t for all of your torture <br>I wouldn’t know how to be this way now and never back down <br>So I wanna say thank you <br>Cuz it makes me that much stronger <br>Makes me work a little bit harder <br>Makes me that much wiser <br>So thanks for making me a fighter <br>Made me learn a little bit faster <br>Made my skin a little bit thicker <br>Made me that much smarter <br>Thanks for making me a fighter <br>How could this man I thought I knew <br>Turn out to be unjust, so cruel <br>Could only see the good in you <br>Pretended not to say the truth <br>You tried to hide your lies <br>Disguise yourself, you’re living in denial <br>But in the end you see, you won't stop me <br>I am a fighter and I <br>(I'm a fighter) <br>I ain’t gon' stop <br>(I ain't gon' stop) <br>There is no turning back <br>I’ve had enough, yeah... <br>Makes me that much stronger <br>Makes me work a little bit harder <br>(Oh, ooh yeah, ooh yeah) <br>It makes me that much wiser <br>So thanks for making me a fighter <br>Made me learn a little bit faster <br>Made my skin a little bit thicker <br>Makes me that much smarter <br>So thanks for making me a fighter <br>Thought I would forget (thought I) <br>I remember (ohh) <br>'Cause I remember (ohh) <br>I remember <br>Thought I would forget (ooh) <br>I remember (ohh) <br>'Cause I remember (ohh) <br>I remember <br>Makes me that much stronger <br>Makes me work a little bit harder <br>Makes me that much wiser <br>So thanks for making me a fighter <br>Made me learn a little bit faster <br>Made my skin a little bit thicker <br>Made me that much smarter <br>Thanks for making me a fighter]]></content><category term="Christina Aguilera" label="Christina Aguilera"/><category term="Fighter" label="Fighter"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kelly_Rowland/Work_Freemasons_Radio_Edit/</id><title>Kelly Rowland - Work (Freemasons Radio Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:32:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:32:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kelly_Rowland/Work_Freemasons_Radio_Edit/" title="Kelly Rowland - Work (Freemasons Radio Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This aint gon’ be easy <br>Uh! <br>You got it <br>You got it <br>Put it in <br><br>Tables turnin’ to a situation <br>Now you standin’ in my face like <br>you’ve been patiently waitin <br>I’m rollin over words forget the conversation <br>Thinkin’ maybe we can make a combination <br><br>Wanna see me lose my breath <br>and wanna hear me moan <br>BETTER BE READY, WILLING, ABLE <br>when we get alone <br>You was talkin’ confident upon the telephone <br>So you gotta put it in when we get it on <br><br>No turning back from this party <br>put you through enough to complain <br>Aint no comin down from this side <br>my love don’t go nowhere 'LESS I SAY <br>Look at what you got yourself into <br>Best take advantage be all that you can be <br>Best take advantage see all that you can see <br>Cause this could be your last opportunity <br>WITH ME (PUT IT IN) <br><br>Check it baby, get it baby, check it baby get it <br>Do it baby d-do it, d-do it baby get it (put it in) <br>Check it baby, get it baby, check it baby get it (work) <br>Do it baby d-do it, d-do it baby get it (GO HARD) <br>Check it baby, get it baby, check it baby get it <br>Do it baby d-do it, d-do it baby get it <br>Don’t come around if you gone let me down <br>You gotta get it all the way in <br>I wanna see you work <br><br>You lookin like you’re lookin for an explaination <br>Use the curves in my body for your motivation <br>Skip the petty games no need for complication <br>Use those things for sure I’ll reach my destination <br><br>Better leave a good impression <br>before you hit the door <br>Cause you don’t want me talkin <br>bout ya busniess on the low <br>You show it off I had to fit you in my schedule <br>So you better put it on when its time to go <br><br>No turning back from this party put <br>you through enough to complain <br><br>Aint no comin down from this side <br>my love don’t nowhere 'LESS I SAY <br>Look at what you got yourself into <br>Best take advantage be all that you can be <br>Best take advantage see all that you can see <br>cause this could be your last opportunity to <br>WITH ME (PUT IT IN) <br><br>Check it baby, get it baby, check it baby get it <br>Do it baby d-do it, d-do it do it (put it in) <br>Check it baby, get it baby, check it baby get it (work) <br>Do it baby d-do it, d-do it baby get it (GO HARD) <br>Check it baby, get it baby, check it baby get it (work) <br>Do it baby d-do it, d-do it baby get it <br>Don’t come around if you gone let me down <br>You gotta get it all the way in <br>I wanna see you work <br><br>I aint acceptin no exuses baby <br>To brag about it would be useless baby <br>You better blow me away <br>Make a girl wanna stay <br>At your spot goin all around <br>It’s your chance to prove <br>Don’t forget your move <br>There’s nothing to lose <br>BUT ME (PUT IT IN) <br><br>Check it baby, get it baby, check it baby get it <br>Do it baby d-do it, d-do it baby get it babe (put it in) <br>Check it baby, get it baby, <br>check it baby get it babe(work) <br>Do it baby d-do it, d-do it baby get it <br>Check it baby, get it baby, check it baby get it <br>Do it baby d-do it, d-do it baby get it <br>Don’t come around if you gone let me down <br>You gotta get it all the way in <br>I wanna see you work <br><br>Check it baby, get it baby, check it baby get it <br>Do it baby d-do it, d-do it baby get it <br>Check it baby, get it baby, check it baby get it <br>Do it baby d-do it, d-do it baby get it <br>Check it baby, get it baby, check it baby get it <br>Do it baby d-do it, d-do it baby get it]]></content><category term="Kelly Rowland" label="Kelly Rowland"/><category term="Work (Freemasons Radio Edit)" label="Work (Freemasons Radio Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Little_Mix/Power/</id><title>Little Mix - Power - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:33:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:33:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Little_Mix/Power/" title="Little Mix - Power - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hold up no you didn't bow bow <br>I ain't the chick to walk behind you around town <br>Just cos you're packin' packin' whoop down south <br>That don't mean <br>I'm ever gonna take it laying down baby <br>Oh I'm a machine when I do it <br>I'll be catching fire gasoline when I do it <br>Just cos you're packin' packin' whoop down south <br>That don't mean I'm ever gonna take it laying down <br><br>Baby you're the man <br>But I got I got I got the power <br>You make rain <br>But I'll make it I'll make it I'll make it shower <br>You should know I'm the one who's in control <br>I'll let you come take the wheel <br>as long as you don't forget <br><br>Who got the power? <br>I got the I got the power <br>I got the I got the power <br>I got the I got the power <br>Hold up! <br><br>My turn <br>I make this look easy <br>Tick Tick boom like gasoline-y <br>Yeah they call me Lamborghini <br>Cos I know just what I'm worth <br>Zero to hundred <br>B-b-body make' em stutter <br>Start my engine push the button <br>Cos I'm gon' be coming first <br>Yeah I'm a machine when I do it <br>I'll be catching fire gasoline when I do it <br>Just cos you're packin' packin' whoop down south <br>That don't mean I'm ever gonna take it laying down <br><br>Baby you're the man <br>But I got I got I got the power <br>You make rain <br>But I'll make it I'll make it I'll make it shower <br>You should know I'm the one who's in control <br>I'll let you come take the wheel <br>as long as you don't forget <br><br>Who got the power <br>I got the I got the power <br>I got the I got the power <br>I got the I got the power <br>I got the <br>Who got the power <br>I got the I got the power <br>I got the I got the power <br>I got the I got the power <br>Who got the power <br><br>Don't be fooled I got you wrapped up <br>In the arms of an animal <br>Got you thinking that I'm all innocent <br>But wait 'till I get you home <br>If you don't baby you should know <br>I'm the one who's in control <br>Motorbike motorbike motorbike motorbike <br>Bike bike bike bike <br>Bike bike bike bike bike bike whoop <br><br>You're the man <br>But I got I got I got the power <br>You make rain <br>But I'll make it I'll make it I'll make it shower <br>You should know I'm the one who's in control <br>I'll let you come take the wheel <br>as long as you don't forget <br>You're the man <br>But I got I got I got the power <br>You make rain <br>But I'll make it I'll make it I'll make it shower <br>You should know I'm the one who's in control <br>I'll let you come take the wheel <br>as long as you don't forget <br><br>I got the I got the power <br>I got the I got the power <br>I got the I got the power <br>Cause I got I got I got the power <br>Oh yeah yeah yeah <br>I got the I got the power <br>I got the I got the power <br>I got the I got the power <br>Baby don't forget I got the power yeah <br>The power yeah yeah-eh <br><br>Motorbike motorbike motorbike motorbike <br>Bike bike bike bike <br>Bike bike bike bike bike bike whoop]]></content><category term="Little Mix" label="Little Mix"/><category term="Power" label="Power"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Toni_Braxton/He_Wasnt_Man_Enough/</id><title>Toni Braxton - He Wasn`t Man Enough - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:33:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:33:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Toni_Braxton/He_Wasnt_Man_Enough/" title="Toni Braxton - He Wasn`t Man Enough - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Darkchild, oh yeah <br>Toni Braxton, oh <br>Ha ha, uh huh <br>Yeah, uh, uh <br>Darkchild yeah <br><br>Listen girl <br>Who do you think I am <br>Don't you know that he was my man <br>But I chose to let him go <br>So why do you act like I still care about him <br>Looking at me like I'm hurt <br>When I'm the one who said I didn't want it to work <br>Don't you forget I had him first <br><br>What you thinkin' <br>Stop playing me <br>He wasn't man enough for me <br>If you don't know now here's your chance <br>I've already had your man <br>Do you wonder just where he's been, yeah <br>Not be worried about him <br>Now it's time you know the truth <br>I think he's just the man for you <br><br>What are you thinking <br>Did you know about us back them <br>Do you know I dumped your husband, girlfriend <br>I'm not thinking 'bout him <br>But you married him <br>Do you know I made him leave <br>Do you know he begged to stay with me <br>He wasn't man enough for me <br><br>Listen girl <br>Didn't he tell you the truth <br>If not then why don't you ask him <br>Then maybe you can be more into him <br>Instead of worrying about me <br>And hopefully you won't find <br>All the reasons why his love didn't count <br>And why we couldn't work it out <br><br>What you thinkin' <br>Stop playing me <br>He wasn't man enough for me <br>If you don't know now here's your chance <br>I've already had your man <br>Do you wonder just where he's been, yeah <br>Not be worried about him <br>Now it's time you know the truth <br>I think he's just the man for you <br><br>What are you thinking <br>Did you know about us back them <br>Do you know I dumped your husband, girlfriend <br>I'm not thinking 'bout him <br>But you married him <br>Do you know I made him leave <br>Do you know he begged to stay with me <br>He wasn't man enough for me <br><br>Oh yeah <br>So many reasons why our love is through, yeah <br>What makes you think he'll be good to you, no <br>It makes no sense cause he will never change <br>Girl you better recognize the game, oh yeah <br><br>What are you thinking <br>Did you know about us back them <br>Do you know I dumped your husband, girlfriend <br>I'm not thinking 'bout him <br>But you married him <br>Do you know I made him leave <br>Do you know he begged to stay with me <br>He wasn't man enough for me <br><br>What are you thinking <br>Did you know about us back them <br>Do you know I dumped your husband, girlfriend <br>I'm not thinking 'bout him <br>But you married him <br>Do you know I made him leave <br>Do you know he begged to stay with me <br>He wasn't man enough for me <br><br>What are you thinking <br>Did you know about us back them <br>Do you know I dumped your husband, girlfriend <br>I'm not thinking 'bout him <br>But you married him <br>Do you know I made him leave <br>Do you know he begged to stay with me <br>He wasn't man enough for me]]></content><category term="Toni Braxton" label="Toni Braxton"/><category term="He Wasn`t Man Enough" label="He Wasn`t Man Enough"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Usher/Good_Kisser/</id><title>Usher - Good Kisser - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:33:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:33:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Usher/Good_Kisser/" title="Usher - Good Kisser - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Make every minute worth it, baby <br>This for Usher, baby <br>Watch this <br><br>I done been around the world, I done kissed a lot of girls <br>So I'm guessin' that it's true <br>Make me holla and I bet a million dollars <br>Don't nobody kiss it like you <br>Don't nobody kiss it like you <br>Don't nobody kiss it like you, bang, bang, bang <br>Don't nobody kiss it like you, don't nobody kiss it like you <br><br>It's 5 in the mornin' <br>Kush is rollin' while she's makin' steak and eggs <br>At 5 in the mornin' <br>We can only be about to do one thing what <br><br>See, I told her, the devil is a lie <br>Them other girls can't compete with mine <br>You do it so good, you fuck my mind <br>You pull it out, then you open wide <br>You make me wanna tap out and retire <br>Your pretty lips leave me so inspired <br><br>I think that she's a winner <br>She could be a keeper <br><br>Cause she's such a good kisser <br>Got lipstick on my leg <br>Oh baby <br>She's such a good kisser <br>I'ma rain on this parade <br>Oh baby <br><br>I done been around the world, I done kissed a lot of girls <br>So I'm guessin' that it's true <br>Make me holla and I bet a million dollars <br>Don't nobody kiss it like you <br>Don't nobody kiss it like you <br>Don't nobody kiss it like you, bang, bang, bang <br>Don't nobody kiss it like you, don't nobody kiss it like you <br><br>This girl, she's my hero <br>Get dinero, euros, pesos, francs and yen <br>I ain't one to trick off either <br>I'm starin' at your barrel <br>Pull the trigger, chitty, chitty, bang, babe <br>What ever you want, I told her <br><br>See, I told her, the devil is a lie <br>Them other girls can't compete with mine <br>You do it so good, you fuck my mind <br>You pull it out, then you open wide <br>You make me wanna tap out and retire <br>Your pretty lips leave me so inspired <br><br>I think I got a winner <br>Could be a keeper <br><br>Cause she's such a good kisser <br>Got lipstick on my leg <br>Oh baby <br>She's such a good kisser <br>I'ma rain on this parade <br>Oh baby <br><br>Listen, the only thing I know <br>You give it to me, baby, with good flow <br>Don't ever run it back, come on, keep goin' <br>Just give it to me, give it up to me, give it up to me <br>I can't keep my control <br>Every time that I see you hit that floor <br>Just keep on givin' it to me, I want more <br>Just come on baby, just give it to me, give it up to me <br><br>Kiss it good, kiss it right <br>Keep it up, we be kissin' all night <br>Kiss it good, kiss it right <br>Keep it up, we be kissin' all night <br>Kiss it good, kiss it right <br>Keep it up, we be kissin' all night <br>Kiss it good, kiss it right <br>Keep it up, we be kissin' all night <br><br>Cause she's such a good kisser <br>Got lipstick on my leg <br>Oh baby <br>She's such a good kisser <br>I'ma rain on this parade <br>Oh baby <br><br>I done been around the world, I done kissed a lot of girls <br>So I'm guessin' that it's true <br>Make me holla and I bet a million dollars <br>Don't nobody kiss it like you <br>Don't nobody kiss it like you <br>Don't nobody kiss it like you, bang, bang, bang <br>Don't nobody kiss it like you, don't nobody kiss it like you]]></content><category term="Usher" label="Usher"/><category term="Good Kisser" label="Good Kisser"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Justin_Timberlake/Senorita/</id><title>Justin Timberlake - Senorita - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:33:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:33:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Justin_Timberlake/Senorita/" title="Justin Timberlake - Senorita - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlemen <br>It's my pleasure to introduce to you <br>He's a friend of mine <br><br>Yes, yes I am <br><br>And he goes by the name <br>Justin <br>Wowoowoooo <br><br>All the way <br>from Memphis, Tennessee <br>And he's got somethin' special for y'all tonight <br>He's gonna sing a song for y'all <br>About this girl <br><br>Come in right here <br><br>Yea, come on <br><br>On that sunny day <br>Didn't know I'd meet <br>Such a beautiful girl <br>Walking down the street <br>Seen those bright brown eyes <br>With tears coming down <br>She deserves a crown <br>But where is it now <br>Mamma listen <br><br>Senorita, I feel for you <br>You deal with things, that you don't have to <br>He doesn't love ya, I can tell by his charm <br>But you could feel this real love <br>If you just lay in my <br><br>Running fast in my mind <br>Girl don't you slow it down <br>If we carry on this way <br>This thing might leave the ground <br>How would you like to fly <br>That's how my queen should ride <br>But you still deserve the crown <br>or hasn't it been found <br>Mamma listen <br><br>Senorita, I feel for you <br>Feel for you <br>You deal with things, that you don't have to <br>No, no <br>He doesn't love ya, I can tell by his charm <br>He don't love ya baby <br>But you could feel this real love <br>Feel it <br>If you just lay in my <br><br>Ah, ah, arms <br>Won't you lay in my <br>Ah, ah, arms <br>Mama lay in my <br>Ah, ah, arms <br>Baby won't you lay in my <br>Ah, ah, arms <br><br>When I look into your eyes <br>I see something that money can't buy <br>And I know if you give us a try <br>I'll work hard for you girl <br>And no longer will you ever have to cry <br><br>Senorita, I feel for you <br>You deal with things, that you don't have to <br>Deal with things you don't have to <br>He doesn't love ya, I can tell by his charm <br>No, no <br>But you could feel this real love <br>Feel it <br>If you just lay in my <br><br>Ah, ah, arms <br>Whoa <br>Ah, ah, arms <br>My baby <br>Ah, ah, arms <br>Oooh, yea <br>Ah, ah, arms <br><br>When I look into your eyes <br>I see something that money can't buy <br>And I know if you give us a try <br>I'll work hard for you girl <br>You won't ever cry <br><br>Now listen <br>I wanna try somethin' right now <br>See they don't do this anymore <br>I'ma sing something <br>And I want the guys to sing wit' me <br>They go <br>It feels like something's heating up, can I leave with you <br>And then the ladies go <br>I don't know but I'm thinking bout, really leaving with you <br><br>Guys sing <br>It feels like something's heating up, can I leave with you <br>And ladies <br>I don't know but I'm thinking bout, really leaving with you <br>Feels good don't it, come on <br>It feels like something's heating up, can I leave with you <br>Yea, ladies <br>I don't know but I'm thinking bout, really leaving with you <br>Show the good to me <br><br>Sing it one more time <br>It feels like something's heating up, can I leave with you <br>Ladies <br>I don't know but I'm thinking bout, really leaving with you <br>Yea, yea <br>It feels like something's heating up, can I leave with you <br>Ladies <br>I don't know but I'm thinking bout, really leaving with you <br><br>Gentlemen, good night <br>Ladies, good morning <br>That's it]]></content><category term="Justin Timberlake" label="Justin Timberlake"/><category term="Senorita" label="Senorita"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jennifer_Lopez/Love_Dont_Cost_A_Thing/</id><title>Jennifer Lopez - Love Don`t Cost A Thing - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:33:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:33:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jennifer_Lopez/Love_Dont_Cost_A_Thing/" title="Jennifer Lopez - Love Don`t Cost A Thing - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You think you gotta keep me iced <br>You don't <br>You think I'm gonna spend your cash <br>I won't <br>Even if you were broke <br>My love don't cost a thing <br>Think I wanna drive your Benz <br>I don't <br>If I wanna floss I got my own <br>Even if you were broke <br>My love don't cost a thing <br><br>When you rolled up in the Escalade <br>Saw that truck you gave to the valet <br>Knew that it was game when you looked at me <br>Pulling up your sleeve so I could see the Rolley bling <br>Saw you later in the corner booth <br>Raising up a toast so I would notice you <br>But your heart's a mess <br>Think you outta know <br>Doesn't matter if you're balling out of control <br><br>All that matter's is <br>That you treat me right <br>Give me all the things I need <br>That money can't buy yeah <br><br>You think you gotta keep me iced <br>You don't <br>You think I'm gonna spend your cash <br>I won't <br>Even if you were broke <br>My love don't cost a thing <br>Think I wanna drive your Benz <br>I don't <br>If I wanna floss I got my own <br>Even if you were broke <br>My love don't cost a thing <br><br>When I took a chance <br>Thought you'd understand <br>Baby credit cards aren't romance <br>So you're tryna buy what's already yours <br>What I need from is not available in stores <br>Seen a side of you that I really feel <br>Doing way too much, never keep it real <br>If it doesn't change, gotta hit the road <br>Now I'm leaving, where's my keys <br>I've got to go <br><br>All that matter's is <br>That you treat me right <br>Give me all the things I need <br>That money can't buy yeah <br><br>You think you gotta keep me iced <br>You don't <br>You think I'm gonna spend your cash <br>I won't <br>Even if you were broke <br>My love don't cost a thing <br>Think I wanna drive your Benz <br>I don't <br>If I wanna floss I got my own <br>Even if you were broke <br>My love don't cost a thing <br><br>A thing, a thing, a thing <br>Yeah, yeah, yeah <br>You think the money that you make <br>Can substitute the time you take <br>Take the keys here to my heart <br>Then you can win my heart, and get what's in my heart <br>I think you need to take some time <br>To show me that your love is true <br>There's more than dollar signs in you <br>Then you can win my heart, and get what's in my heart <br><br>You think you gotta keep me iced <br>You don't <br>You think I'm gonna spend your cash <br>I won't <br>Even if you were broke <br>My love don't cost a thing <br>Think I wanna drive your Benz <br>I don't <br>If I wanna floss I got my own <br>Even if you were broke <br>My love don't cost a thing]]></content><category term="Jennifer Lopez" label="Jennifer Lopez"/><category term="Love Don`t Cost A Thing" label="Love Don`t Cost A Thing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pink/Blow_Me_One_Last_Kiss/</id><title>Pink - Blow Me (One Last Kiss) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:33:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:33:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pink/Blow_Me_One_Last_Kiss/" title="Pink - Blow Me (One Last Kiss) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[White knuckles <br>And sweaty palms from hanging on too tight <br>Clenched shut jaw <br>I've got another headache again tonight <br><br>Eyes on fire, eyes on fire <br>And they burn from all the tears <br>I've been crying, I've been crying <br>I've been dying over you <br><br>Tie a knot in the rope <br>Trying to hold, trying to hold <br>But there's nothing to grab <br>So I let go <br><br>I think I've finally had enough <br>I think I maybe think too much <br>I think this might be it for us <br>Blow me one last kiss <br><br>You think I'm just too serious <br>I think you're full of shit <br>My head is spinning, so <br>Blow me one last kiss <br><br>Just when it can't get worse <br>I've had a shit day <br>You've had a shit day <br>We've had a shit day <br><br>I think that life's too short for this <br>Want back my ignorance and bliss <br>I think I've had enough of this <br>Blow me one last kiss <br><br>I won't miss all of the fighting <br>That we always did <br>Take it in <br>I mean what I say when I say there is nothing left <br><br>No more sick whiskey dick <br>No more battles from me <br>You'll be calling a trick <br>'Cause you no longer sleep <br><br>I'll dress nice, I'll look good <br>I'll go dancing alone <br>I will laugh, I'll get drunk <br>I'll take somebody home <br><br>I think I've finally had enough <br>I think I maybe think too much <br>I think this might be it for us <br>Blow me one last kiss <br><br>You think I'm just too serious <br>I think you're full of shit <br>My head is spinning, so <br>Blow me one last kiss <br><br>Just when it can't get worse <br>I've had a shit day <br>You've had a shit day <br>We've had a shit day <br><br>I think that life's too short for this <br>Want back my ignorance and bliss <br>I think I've had enough of this <br>Blow me one last kiss <br><br>Blow me one last kiss <br>Blow me one last kiss <br><br>I will do what I please <br>Anything that I want <br>I will breathe, I will breathe <br>I won't worry at all <br><br>You will pay for your sins <br>You'll be sorry, my dear <br>All the lies, all the whys <br>Will all be crystal clear <br><br>I think I've finally had enough <br>I think I maybe think too much <br>I think this might be it for us <br>Blow me one last kiss <br><br>You think I'm just too serious <br>I think you're full of shit <br>My head is spinning, so <br>Blow me one last kiss <br><br>Just when it can't get worse <br>I've had a shit day <br>You've had a shit day <br>We've had a shit day <br><br>I think that life's too short for this <br>Want back my ignorance and bliss <br>I think I've had enough of this <br>Blow me one last kiss <br><br>Blow me one last kiss <br>Blow me one last kiss <br><br>Just when it can't get worse <br>I've had a shit day <br>You've had a shit day <br>We've had a shit day <br><br>I think that life's too short for this <br>Want back my ignorance and bliss <br>I think I've had enough of this <br>Blow me one last kiss]]></content><category term="Pink" label="Pink"/><category term="Blow Me (One Last Kiss)" label="Blow Me (One Last Kiss)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/Girl_On_Fire_Inferno_Ver_Feat_Nicki_Minaj/</id><title>Alicia Keys - Girl On Fire (Inferno Ver.) (Feat. Nicki Minaj) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:33:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:33:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alicia_Keys/Girl_On_Fire_Inferno_Ver_Feat_Nicki_Minaj/" title="Alicia Keys - Girl On Fire (Inferno Ver.) (Feat. Nicki Minaj) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Spirit of Marilyn <br>Callin' me, audibly, bawlin' she <br>Said that she would never leave <br>Continue to torture me <br>Tellin' me to come with her <br>Underneath my comforter <br>And she brought a gun with her <br>Pills and some rum with her <br>Took me on the balcony <br>Tellin' me to jump with her <br>Yeah I'm in the ghost but, I ain't doing stunts with her <br>I ain't tryna be that <br>Haters wanna see that <br>But I got 'em aggy <br>Cause I win the gold like Gabby <br><br>She's just a girl and she's on fire <br>Hotter than a fantasy, lonely like a highway <br>She's living in a world and it's on fire <br>Filled with catastrophe, but she knows she can fly away <br><br>Oh, oh oh oh oh <br>She got both feet on the ground <br>And she's burning it down <br>Oh oh oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh <br>She got her head in the clouds <br>And she's not backing down <br><br>This girl is on fire <br>This girl is on fire <br>She's walking on fire <br>This girl is on fire <br><br>Looks like a girl but she's a flame <br>So bright she can burn your eyes <br>Better look the other way <br>You can try but you'll never forget her name <br>She's on top of the world <br>Hottest of the hottest girls, say <br><br>Oh, oh oh oh oh <br>We got our feet on the ground <br>And we're burning it down <br>Oh oh oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh <br>Got our head in the clouds <br>And we're not coming down <br><br>This girl is on fire <br>This girl is on fire <br>She's walking on fire <br>This girl is on fire <br><br>Everybody stares as she goes by <br>Cause they can see the flame that's in her eyes <br>Watch her as she's lighting up the night <br>Nobody knows that she's a lonely girl <br>And it's a lonely world <br>But she gon' let it burn, baby, burn, baby <br><br>Dear God, if you're here God <br>Make the fire disappear when they stare God <br>Take away the fear when they interfere God <br>Do you fear God <br>Cause I fear God <br>And in my backyard, that's a deer, God <br>And that's a horse ranch <br>And to my core fans, keep reppin' me, do it to the death of me <br>X in the box, cause ain't nobody checking me <br><br>This girl is on fire <br>This girl is on fire <br>She's walking on fire <br>This girl is on fire <br><br>Oh, oh, oh <br><br>She's just a girl and she's on fire]]></content><category term="Alicia Keys" label="Alicia Keys"/><category term="Girl On Fire (Inferno Ver.) (Feat. Nicki Minaj)" label="Girl On Fire (Inferno Ver.) (Feat. Nicki Minaj)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beyonce/Single_Ladies_Put_A_Ring_On_It/</id><title>Beyonce - Single Ladies (Put A Ring On It) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:33:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:33:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Beyonce/Single_Ladies_Put_A_Ring_On_It/" title="Beyonce - Single Ladies (Put A Ring On It) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All the single ladies <br>All the single ladies <br>All the single ladies <br>All the single ladies <br>All the single ladies <br>All the single ladies <br>All the single ladies <br>Now put your hands up <br>Up in the club we just broke up <br>I'm doing my own little thing <br>You decided to dip <br>but now you wanna trip <br>Cause another brother noticed me <br>I'm up on him he up on me <br>don't pay him any attention <br>Cause I cried my tears <br>for three good years <br>Ya can't be mad at me <br>Cause if you liked it then you <br>should have put a ring on it <br>If you liked it then you <br>should've put a ring on it <br>Don't be mad once you <br>see that he want it <br>If you liked it then you <br>should've put a ring on it <br>Wuh uh oh uh uh <br>oh oh uh oh uh uh oh <br>Wuh uh oh uh uh <br>oh oh uh oh uh uh oh <br>Cause if you liked it then <br>you should have put a ring on it <br>If you liked it then you <br>should've put a ring on it <br>Don't be mad once you <br>see that he want it <br>If you liked it then you <br>should've put a ring on it <br>I got gloss on my lips <br>a man on my hips <br>Hold me tighter <br>than my Dereon jeans <br>Acting up drink in my cup <br>I could care less what you think <br>I need no permission <br>did I mention <br>Don't pay him any attention <br>Cause you had your turn <br>And now you gonna learn <br>What it really feels like to miss me <br>Cause if you liked it then <br>you should have put a ring on it <br>If you liked it then you <br>should've put a ring on it <br>Don't be mad once you <br>see that he want it <br>If you liked it then you <br>should've put a ring on it <br>Wuh uh oh uh uh <br>oh oh uh oh uh uh oh <br>Wuh uh oh uh uh <br>oh oh uh oh uh uh oh <br>If you liked it then you <br>should've put a ring on it <br>If you liked it then you <br>should've put a ring on it <br>Don't be mad once you <br>see that he want it <br>If you liked it then you <br>should've put a ring on it <br>Wuh uh oh uh uh <br>oh oh uh oh uh uh oh <br>Wuh uh oh uh uh <br>oh oh uh oh uh uh oh <br>Don't treat me to these <br>things of the world <br>I'm not that kind of girl <br>Your love is what I prefer <br>what I deserve <br>Is a man that makes me <br>then takes me <br>And delivers me to a destiny <br>to infinity and beyond <br>Pull me into your arms <br>Say I'm the one you want <br>If you don't you'll be alone <br>And like a ghost I'll be gone <br>All the single ladies <br>All the single ladies <br>All the single ladies <br>All the single ladies <br>All the single ladies <br>All the single ladies <br>All the single ladies <br>Now put your hands up <br>Wuh uh oh uh uh oh <br>oh uh oh uh uh oh <br>Wuh uh oh uh uh oh <br>oh uh oh uh uh oh <br>Cause if you liked it then you <br>should have put a ring on it <br>If you liked it then you <br>should've put a ring on it <br>Don't be mad once you <br>see that he want it <br>If you liked it then you <br>should've put a ring on it <br>Cause if you liked it then you <br>should have put a ring on it <br>If you liked it then you <br>should've put a ring on it <br>Don't be mad once you <br>see that he want it <br>If you liked it then you <br>should've put a ring on it <br>Wuh uh oh <br>]]></content><category term="Beyonce" label="Beyonce"/><category term="Single Ladies (Put A Ring On It)" label="Single Ladies (Put A Ring On It)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동요/안녕_어린이집필수동요/</id><title>동요 - 안녕 (어린이집필수동요) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:35:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:35:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/%EC%95%88%EB%85%95_%EC%96%B4%EB%A6%B0%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%91%ED%95%84%EC%88%98%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94/" title="동요 - 안녕 (어린이집필수동요) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[안녕 안녕 선생님 <br>안녕 안녕 친구들 <br>오늘 다시 만나 반갑습니다 <br>안녕 안녕 아안녕 <br><br>안녕 안녕 선생님 <br>안녕 안녕 친구들 <br>내일 다시 만나 재밌게 놀자 <br>안녕 안녕 아안녕]]></content><category term="동요" label="동요"/><category term="안녕 (어린이집필수동요)" label="안녕 (어린이집필수동요)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/After_Romeo/How_It_Happens_Inst/</id><title>After Romeo - How It Happens (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:36:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:36:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/After_Romeo/How_It_Happens_Inst/" title="After Romeo - How It Happens (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I see the perfect dream <br>A new reality <br>Where you and I are full of hope <br>I know you love to give <br>and keep your promises <br>When we’re together we just know <br>You see I haven’t met you yet <br>But I know you exist <br>I gotta remember that you’re coming <br>I hope that I get my wish <br>You’re the perfect gift <br>Think you should know <br>how bad I want it <br>If I could go the distance <br>My world would be different <br>I imagine <br>How it happens <br>You walk up and smile <br>We talk for awhile <br>I can imagine <br>That’s how it happens <br>Now I don’t know your name <br>and I won’t know the place <br>but I’ll keep you warm out in the snow <br>You’ll light the fireplace <br>and look at me that way <br>Until it happens I won’t know <br>You see I haven’t met you yet <br>But I know you exist <br>I gotta remember that you’re coming <br>I hope that I get my wish <br>You’re the perfect gift <br>Think you should know <br>how bad I want it <br>If I <br>I could go the distance <br>My world would be different <br>I imagine <br>How it happens <br>You walk up and smile <br>We talk for awhile <br>I can imagine <br>That’s how it happens <br>I know we’ll meet each other someday <br>Until that happens <br>I’m doing fine with just me <br>I’ve got a lot of love <br>that’s long over due <br>Coz I only see a future with you <br>If I could go the distance <br>My world would be different <br>I imagine <br>If I could go the distance <br>My world would be different <br>I imagine <br>How it happens <br>You walk up and smile <br>We talk for awhile <br>I can imagine <br>That’s how it happens <br>Until the day my wish comes true <br>I’ll be looking out for you <br>That’s how it happens <br>That’s how it happens <br>Until the day my wish comes true <br>I’ll be looking out for you <br>There ain’t nothing <br>I won’t do to make it happen <br>]]></content><category term="After Romeo" label="After Romeo"/><category term="How It Happens (Inst.)" label="How It Happens (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/After_Romeo/How_It_Happens/</id><title>After Romeo - How It Happens - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:36:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:36:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/After_Romeo/How_It_Happens/" title="After Romeo - How It Happens - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I see the perfect dream <br>A new reality <br>Where you and I are full of hope <br>I know you love to give <br>and keep your promises <br>When we’re together we just know <br>You see I haven’t met you yet <br>But I know you exist <br>I gotta remember that you’re coming <br>I hope that I get my wish <br>You’re the perfect gift <br>Think you should know <br>how bad I want it <br>If I could go the distance <br>My world would be different <br>I imagine <br>How it happens <br>You walk up and smile <br>We talk for awhile <br>I can imagine <br>That’s how it happens <br>Now I don’t know your name <br>and I won’t know the place <br>but I’ll keep you warm out in the snow <br>You’ll light the fireplace <br>and look at me that way <br>Until it happens I won’t know <br>You see I haven’t met you yet <br>But I know you exist <br>I gotta remember that you’re coming <br>I hope that I get my wish <br>You’re the perfect gift <br>Think you should know <br>how bad I want it <br>If I <br>I could go the distance <br>My world would be different <br>I imagine <br>How it happens <br>You walk up and smile <br>We talk for awhile <br>I can imagine <br>That’s how it happens <br>I know we’ll meet each other someday <br>Until that happens <br>I’m doing fine with just me <br>I’ve got a lot of love <br>that’s long over due <br>Coz I only see a future with you <br>If I could go the distance <br>My world would be different <br>I imagine <br>If I could go the distance <br>My world would be different <br>I imagine <br>How it happens <br>You walk up and smile <br>We talk for awhile <br>I can imagine <br>That’s how it happens <br>Until the day my wish comes true <br>I’ll be looking out for you <br>That’s how it happens <br>That’s how it happens <br>Until the day my wish comes true <br>I’ll be looking out for you <br>There ain’t nothing <br>I won’t do to make it happen <br>]]></content><category term="After Romeo" label="After Romeo"/><category term="How It Happens" label="How It Happens"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리노_쿠_Rino_Ku/넌_빛나는_별_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>리노 쿠 (Rino Ku) - 넌 빛나는 별 (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:36:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:36:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%85%B8_%EC%BF%A0_Rino_Ku/%EB%84%8C_%EB%B9%9B%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%B3%84_Acoustic_Ver/" title="리노 쿠 (Rino Ku) - 넌 빛나는 별 (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 마음 속에 남아 있는 <br>넌 빛나는 별 <br>저 넓은 우주 <br>너와 함께 지난 일들 <br>기억 나던 어느 날 <br>뚜렷하게 생각나는 <br>네 모습에 난 놀랬네 <br>내 마음 속에 남아 있는 <br>넌 빛나는 별 <br>저 넓은 우주 <br>우리 함께 걸었던 밤에 <br>도시 속의 빛 풍경들 <br>꿈만 같고 영화 같았던 <br>아름답던 첫사랑 <br>내 마음 속에 남아 있는 <br>넌 빛나는 별 <br>빛나는 우주 <br>언젠가는 이 기억들도 <br>저 모래처럼 흩어지고 <br>저 파도처럼 이 순간들도 <br>이 추억들도 눈물 짓겠지 <br>내 마음 속에 남아 있는 <br>넌 빛나는 별 <br>빛나는 우주 <br>내 마음 속에 남아 있는 <br>넌 빛나는 별 <br>저 넓은 우주 <br>내 마음 속에 남아 있는 <br>넌 빛나는 별 <br>저 넓은 우주 <br>빛나는 별 <br>저 넓은 우주 <br>빛나는 별 <br>저 넓은 너 <br>]]></content><category term="리노 쿠 (Rino Ku)" label="리노 쿠 (Rino Ku)"/><category term="넌 빛나는 별 (Acoustic Ver.)" label="넌 빛나는 별 (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ninho/Binks_To_Binks_4/</id><title>Ninho - Binks To Binks 4 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:36:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:36:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ninho/Binks_To_Binks_4/" title="Ninho - Binks To Binks 4 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nique la police nationale, nique le Mondeo noir <br>A 130 dans la ville donc la voiture vole, quand je prends les dos d'anes <br>Il n'y a rien de marrant, si tu cries pas t'es pas remunere <br>J'reviens plus chaud qu'avant, mais Boumara me dit qu'c'est mort pour eux <br>J'ai du papier a multiplier, pas l'temps pour les futilites <br>Je les baise dans tous les sens du terme, c'est une fatalite <br>J'ai remonte tes rimes et j'en ai des lo ki, j'entends beta omega dans le talkie walkie <br>Le petard est dans le smoking, j'suis chez Philipp je fais du shopping <br>Et les condes me veulent en shooting, ils me prennent pour Toto Rina ou John Gotti <br>La vie c'est dur j'vais pas t'faire un croquis, tout le monde voulait croquer mais l'gateau n'est pas assez gros <br>Quand j'avais soif, aucun d'entre vous m'a passe d'l'eau <br>J'suis passe devant, aujourd'hui tu vois qu'c'est chaud, et la tu voudrais ger man, mais la c'est mort <br>J'suis dans la turv' avec NICE, Quick et MOUSS, j'ai mis le succes dans le GPS <br>Nique la mere aux hesses nique, nique, nique, nique nique la mere aux hesses BIN BIN BINKS <br>Je n'oublierai pas les coups d'fouets, je n'oublierai pas le coton et les colonies <br>J'les entends rapper rapper rapper rapper rapper raconter que des calmonies <br>Bande de farceurs, vous n'avait jamais ete du cote des chasseurs <br>Nouvelles liasses, nouvelle yakhale, nouvelles paires de chaussures <br><br>J'finirai assassine comme ceux qui disent la verite <br>epargne moi tes bobards tes baratins, epargne moi tes bobards tes baratins <br>Si tu fais l'fou on revient pas a quinze, on revient a trois mais le chargeur est plein <br>Si tu fais l'fou on revient pas a quinze, on revient a trois mais le chargeur est plein salope <br>Recale par le videur, un an apres j'suis paye par l'patron de la boite <br>Tu veux rentrer avec NI aller va mettre ta schneck a la station d'lavage sale pute <br>Comment expliquer a son fils que je baise sa maman quand son papa travaille sale pute <br>J'ai gagne la guerre, pourtant je perdais la bataille <br>Il n'y a que les bonhommes qui montent a bord, ma generation me fait peur <br>Elle veut Louboutin et Chanel, mais elle ne sait meme pas faire des pates au beurre <br>Et si ca graille, moi j'veux ma part, c'est pas les miettes qui vont calmer ma faim <br>A l'ecole j'etais cale dans l'fond, quand y'avait les shmitts je la calais dans l'fion <br>Et tous ces vendus attendent la redemption, attendent la redemption <br>Charbon charbon detention, pour la reinsertion ce s'ra manutention <br><br>Heeee <br>J'en laisse un peu pour l'album <br>Bin binks]]></content><category term="Ninho" label="Ninho"/><category term="Binks To Binks 4" label="Binks To Binks 4"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김윤진/노래할_수_없는_곳이라_해도/</id><title>김윤진 - 노래할 수 없는 곳이라 해도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:36:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:36:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9C%A4%EC%A7%84/%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98%ED%95%A0_%EC%88%98_%EC%97%86%EB%8A%94_%EA%B3%B3%EC%9D%B4%EB%9D%BC_%ED%95%B4%EB%8F%84/" title="김윤진 - 노래할 수 없는 곳이라 해도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주님 사랑의 손길이 <br>나를 만들어 <br>내 모습 이대로 <br>사용하여 주시네 <br>흐트러진 마음을 만지시어 <br>이끄시는 곳 어디라도 <br>나는 노래하리 <br>노래할 수 없는 곳이라 해도 <br>난 노래하리 <br>기도할 수 없는 곳이라 해도 <br>난 기도하리 <br>노래할 수 없는 곳이라 해도 <br>난 노래하리 <br>기도할 수 없는 곳이라 해도 <br>난 기도하리 <br>주님 사랑의 손길이 <br>나를 만들어 <br>내 모습 이대로 <br>사용하여 주시네 <br>흐트러진 마음을 만지시어 <br>이끄시는 곳 어디라도 <br>나는 노래하리 <br>주님 사랑의 손길이 <br>나를 만들어 <br>내 모습 이대로 <br>사용하여 주시네 <br>흐트러진 마음을 만지시어 <br>이끄시는 곳 어디라도 <br>나는 노래하리 <br>주님 사랑의 손길이 <br>나를 만들어 <br>내 모습 이대로 <br>사용하여 주시네 <br>흐트러진 마음을 만지시어 <br>이끄시는 곳 어디라도 <br>나는 노래하리 <br>주님 사랑의 손길이 <br>나를 만들어 <br>내 모습 이대로 <br>사용하여 주시네 <br>흐트러진 마음을 만지시어 <br>이끄시는 곳 어디라도 <br>나는 노래하리 <br>주님 사랑의 손길이 <br>나를 만들어 <br>내 모습 이대로 <br>사용하여 주시네 <br>흐트러진 마음을 만지시어 <br>이끄시는 곳 어디라도 <br>나는 노래하리 <br>주님 사랑의 손길이 <br>나를 만들어 <br>내 모습 이대로 <br>사용하여 주시네 <br>흐트러진 마음을 만지시어 <br>이끄시는 곳 어디라도 <br>나는 노래하리 <br>]]></content><category term="김윤진" label="김윤진"/><category term="노래할 수 없는 곳이라 해도" label="노래할 수 없는 곳이라 해도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김윤진/나는_예배자입니다/</id><title>김윤진 - 나는 예배자입니다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:36:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:36:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%9C%A4%EC%A7%84/%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%98%88%EB%B0%B0%EC%9E%90%EC%9E%85%EB%8B%88%EB%8B%A4/" title="김윤진 - 나는 예배자입니다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 하나님을 <br>예배하는 예배자입니다 <br>내가 서 있는 곳 어디서나 <br>하나님을 예배합니다 <br>내 영혼 거룩한 <br>은혜를 향하여 <br>내 마음 완전한 <br>하나님 향하여 <br>이곳에서 바로 이 시간 <br>하나님을 예배합니다 <br>내 영혼 거룩한 <br>은혜를 향하여 <br>내 마음 완전한 <br>하나님 향하여 <br>이곳에서 바로 이 시간 <br>하나님을 예배합니다 <br>나는 하나님을 <br>예배하는 예배자입니다 <br>내가 서 있는 곳 어디서나 <br>하나님을 예배합니다 <br>내 영혼 거룩한 <br>은혜를 향하여 <br>내 마음 완전한 <br>하나님 향하여 <br>이곳에서 바로 이 시간 <br>하나님을 예배합니다 <br>나는 하나님을 <br>예배하는 예배자입니다 <br>내가 서 있는 곳 어디서나 <br>하나님을 예배합니다 <br>내 영혼 거룩한 <br>은혜를 향하여 <br>내 마음 완전한 <br>하나님 향하여 <br>이곳에서 바로 이 시간 <br>하나님을 예배합니다 <br>내 영혼 거룩한 <br>은혜를 향하여 <br>내 마음 완전한 <br>하나님 향하여 <br>이곳에서 바로 이 시간 <br>하나님을 예배합니다 <br>나는 하나님을 <br>예배하는 예배자입니다 <br>내가 서 있는 곳 어디서나 <br>하나님을 예배합니다 <br>내 영혼 거룩한 <br>은혜를 향하여 <br>내 마음 완전한 <br>하나님 향하여 <br>이곳에서 바로 이 시간 <br>하나님을 예배합니다 <br>내 영혼 거룩한 <br>은혜를 향하여 <br>내 마음 완전한 <br>하나님 향하여 <br>이곳에서 바로 이 시간 <br>하나님을 예배합니다 <br>이곳에서 바로 이 시간 <br>하나님을 예배합니다 <br>]]></content><category term="김윤진" label="김윤진"/><category term="나는 예배자입니다" label="나는 예배자입니다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/매드클라운/우리집을_못_찾겠군요_Feat_볼빨간사춘기/</id><title>매드클라운 - 우리집을 못 찾겠군요 (Feat. 볼빨간사춘기) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:36:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:36:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%A4%EB%93%9C%ED%81%B4%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EC%A7%91%EC%9D%84_%EB%AA%BB_%EC%B0%BE%EA%B2%A0%EA%B5%B0%EC%9A%94_Feat_%EB%B3%BC%EB%B9%A8%EA%B0%84%EC%82%AC%EC%B6%98%EA%B8%B0/" title="매드클라운 - 우리집을 못 찾겠군요 (Feat. 볼빨간사춘기) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[착해 빠진 게 독한 소리 할 때 <br>분명 지 속도 속 아니었겠죠 <br>잡는 목소리 머뭇거리지도 않고 <br>날 떠날 땐 분명 이 악물었겠죠 <br>상처받지 않은 듯 돌아섰지만 <br>애같이 눈물을 사탕처럼 <br>막 흘리면서 가 <br>다 흘리면서 가 <br>자기보다 큰 슬픔을 <br>쇠똥구리처럼 힘겹게 <br>굴리면서 가 <br>난 왜 그런 널 안지 못했을까 <br>그날 결판 짓던 순간에 <br>터널 같던 너의 눈가 <br>그 생각만 하면 자꾸 내 맘이 짠해 <br>저기요 좀 찾아주세요 <br>그 사람 나 아니면 갈 곳이 없어요 <br>마른 두 다리로 어딘가 헤맬 텐데 <br>내가 집이 돼주기로 했는데 <br>그리워서 그리워서 <br>밤하늘 바라봐요 <br>그대 알아 <br>나도 그대 마음과 같아 <br>시간 지나 사랑이면 <br>그래도 사랑이면 <br>Lonely you <br>돌아와 너의 집으로 <br>서로의 심술 맞은 자존심 <br>딱 그 정도 거리만큼 <br>우린 떨어져 걸었어 <br>뾰족한 맘 <br>괜히 툭 뱉은 말들에 비해 <br>진심은 항상 한 박자 느렸어 <br>그 한 발짝 물러서기가 <br>그렇게 힘들어 <br>이 꼴 저 꼴 다 본 끝에 <br>여기까지네 <br>30평 아파트가 돼주고 <br>싶었는데 <br>겨우 원룸밖에 못 돼 줘서 <br>미안해 <br>처음엔 시원했어 너 떠나간 후 <br>싹 지워냈어 그런 줄 알았어 <br>근데 아니더라고 나도 모르게 <br>익숙한 뒷모습을 몰래 <br>따라가더라 <br>넌 줄 알았어 <br>친구들은 다 나쁜 년이라고 <br>술자리서 욕하는데 <br>속으론 지들이 뭘 안다고 <br>니 편들게 되더라 <br>머리가 아프네 <br>집 가야지 지갑 어디다 뒀더라 <br>그리워서 그리워서 <br>밤하늘 바라봐요 <br>그대 알아 <br>나도 그대 마음과 같아 <br>시간 지나 사랑이면 <br>그래도 사랑이면 <br>Lonely you <br>돌아와 너의 집으로 <br>아저씨 사실 나 갈 곳 없어요 <br>그 사람 아니면 <br>내 마음 둘 곳 없어요 <br>어딜 가야 다시 볼 수 있을까요 <br>우리 집을 못 찾겠군요 <br>아저씨 그 사람 찾아주세요 <br>그 사람 나 아님 잠들 곳 없어요 <br>어딜 가야 다시 볼 수 있을까요 <br>우리 집을 못 찾겠군요 <br>그리워서 그리워서 <br>밤하늘 바라봐요 <br>그대 알아 <br>나도 그대 마음과 같아 <br>시간 지나 사랑이면 <br>그래도 사랑이면 <br>Lonely you <br>돌아와 너의 집으로 <br>저 골목길 돌면 자주 걷던 길과 <br>너가 마중 나왔던 버스 정류장 <br>미용실을 지나 <br>오르막길 올라서 <br>가다 보면 어느새 <br>불 꺼진 너의 집 앞 <br>난 믿어 <br>그리워하다 <br>언젠가 우연처럼 만나게 될 <br>만화 같은 기적 <br>그 사람 지금 어디 있을까요 <br>우리 집을 못 찾겠군요 <br>돌아봐도 사랑이면 <br>그래도 사랑이면 <br>그땐 울고 있는 <br>나를 찾아줄래 <br>]]></content><category term="매드클라운" label="매드클라운"/><category term="우리집을 못 찾겠군요 (Feat. 볼빨간사춘기)" label="우리집을 못 찾겠군요 (Feat. 볼빨간사춘기)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sade/The_Sweetest_Taboo_Remastered/</id><title>Sade - The Sweetest Taboo (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:38:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:38:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sade/The_Sweetest_Taboo_Remastered/" title="Sade - The Sweetest Taboo (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If I tell you <br>If I tell you now <br>Will you keep on <br>Will you keep on loving me <br>If I tell you <br>If I tell you how I feel <br>Will you keep bringing out the best in me <br><br>You give me, you give me the sweetest taboo <br>You give me, you're giving me the sweetest taboo <br>Too good for me <br><br>There's a quiet storm <br>And it never felt like this before <br>There's a quiet storm <br>That is you <br>There's a quiet storm <br>And it never felt this hot before <br>Giving me something that's taboo <br>Sometimes I think you're just too good for me <br><br>You give me the sweetest taboo <br>That's why I'm in love in with you with you <br>You give me the sweetest taboo <br>Too good for me <br>Sometimes I think you're just too good for me <br><br>I'd do anything for you, I'd stand out in the rain <br>Anything you want me to do, don't let it slip away <br>There's a quiet storm <br>And it never felt like this before <br>There's a quiet storm <br>I think it's you <br>There's a quiet storm <br>And I never felt this hot before <br>Giving me something that's taboo <br><br>You give me the you give me, you give me the sweetest taboo <br>That's why I'm in love with you with you <br>You give me, keep giving me the sweetest taboo <br>Too good for me <br><br>You've got the biggest heart <br>Sometimes I think you're just too good for me <br>Every day is Christmas, and every night is New Year's Eve <br>Will you keep on loving me <br>Will you keep on, will you keep on <br>Bringing out the best in me]]></content><category term="Sade" label="Sade"/><category term="The Sweetest Taboo (Remastered)" label="The Sweetest Taboo (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aaron_Espe/Making_All_Things_New/</id><title>Aaron Espe - Making All Things New - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:38:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:38:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Aaron_Espe/Making_All_Things_New/" title="Aaron Espe - Making All Things New - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I leave all the windows open <br>Let the light come thru <br>Sunshine warm and golden <br>Morning making all things new <br><br>Home, where my heart is <br>Home, where my love lives <br>Home, my beginning and end <br>Home <br><br>Look at all the colors <br>Wild, wonderful and true <br>Your breath light as a feather <br>Like little whispers in the room <br><br>Home, where my heart is <br>Home, where my love lives <br>Home, my beginning and end <br>Home <br>Home, where my heart is <br>Home, where my love lives <br>Home, my beginning and end <br>Home <br>Home, my beginning and end <br>Home]]></content><category term="Aaron Espe" label="Aaron Espe"/><category term="Making All Things New" label="Making All Things New"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로코베리/꿈속을_지나/</id><title>로코베리 - 꿈속을 지나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:39:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:39:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EC%BD%94%EB%B2%A0%EB%A6%AC/%EA%BF%88%EC%86%8D%EC%9D%84_%EC%A7%80%EB%82%98/" title="로코베리 - 꿈속을 지나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[별빛이 떨어지는 <br>창문 너머 넌 어딨을까 <br>아무도 없는 빈방 <br>i`m so blue <br>어쩌면 나 <br>이렇게 나의 맘은 <br>그립고 눈물이 나고 <br>밤은 외로워 <br>이 사랑이란 건 <br>아무렇지 않게 <br>할 순 없을 거야 <br>혼자라서 더 편한 게 <br>사람들은 더 많다고들 했지 <br>난 아닌데 난 아닌데 <br>아무 일도 없었단 듯이 <br>나타나줘 <br>우 꿈속을 지나 너에게로 <br>우 구름 위 별빛 내 곁으로 <br>우 오늘 밤 나를 찾아와 <br>침대에 누워 <br>잠시 네 얼굴을 <br>떠올려보면 <br>우스운 표정 짓던 <br>그 모습 <br>생각이 나 <br>날 웃게 하고 <br>날 바라보고 <br>거리를 걷고 <br>입을 맞추고 <br>널 생각하면 <br>난 어쩜 좋은 적이 <br>더 많은 것 같아 <br>혼자라서 더 편한 게 <br>사람들은 더 많다고들 했지 <br>난 아닌데 난 아닌데 <br>아무 일도 없었단 듯이 <br>나타나줘 <br>우 꿈속을 지나 너에게로 <br>우 구름 위 별빛 내 곁으로 <br>우 오늘 밤 나를 찾아와 <br>]]></content><category term="로코베리" label="로코베리"/><category term="꿈속을 지나" label="꿈속을 지나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/When_U_Need_Me/</id><title>Mura Masa - When U Need Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:39:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:39:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/When_U_Need_Me/" title="Mura Masa - When U Need Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ooohh <br><br>Aaahh <br><br>Promise <br>Ooohh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br>Ooohh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br>Aahhh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br>Aahhh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br>Ooohh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br>Ooohh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br>Ooohh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br>Ooohh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br>Ooohh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br>Ooohh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br><br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br><br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br>Aahhh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br>Aahhh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br>Ooohh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br>Ooohh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br>Ooohh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there <br><br>Promise <br>Ooohh <br>I'll get there <br>I'll get there]]></content><category term="Mura Masa" label="Mura Masa"/><category term="When U Need Me" label="When U Need Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Lovesick_Fuck/</id><title>Mura Masa - Lovesick Fuck - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:39:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:39:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Lovesick_Fuck/" title="Mura Masa - Lovesick Fuck - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I need you and I want you <br>Come over here <br>I need you and I want you <br>I need you and I want you <br>Come over here <br>I need you and I want you <br>I need you and I want you <br>Come over here <br>I need you and I want you <br>I need you and I want you <br>Come over here <br>I need you and I want you <br>I need you and I want you <br>Come over here <br>I need you and I want you <br>I need you and I want you <br>Come over here <br>I need you and I want you <br>I need you and I want you <br>Come over here <br>I need you and I want you <br>I need you and I want you <br>Come over here <br>I need you and I want you <br>I need you and I want you <br>Come over here <br>I need you and I want you <br>I need you and I want you <br>Come over here <br>I need you and I want you <br>I need you]]></content><category term="Mura Masa" label="Mura Masa"/><category term="Lovesick Fuck" label="Lovesick Fuck"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Low_Feat_Jay_Prince/</id><title>Mura Masa - Low (Feat. Jay Prince) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:39:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:39:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Low_Feat_Jay_Prince/" title="Mura Masa - Low (Feat. Jay Prince) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>Fall in place <br>This is amazing grace <br>Im 808 to change the game <br>amongst the greats <br>In favorite based upon the latest <br>Pages wrote in papers <br>Homies rolling papers <br>Toke it up and choke it out <br>The same way that it came <br>Up in the game for two days <br>ain't shit been the same <br>So today I'ma prove it <br>Oh God I'ma loose it <br>Truth is hard for the dick <br>that don't do shit <br>Hitting this get dismissed <br>with the business <br>Kick this peak this <br>I ain't lying <br>Speak my mind <br>Feed the lions <br>Keep them quiet <br>Moment of silence trying to keep me <br>behind closed doors <br>Though the truth that if I die though <br>I put up a fight for our lives <br>Put up a fight for my life <br>No more killin' my time my shines now <br>I pull up in the building like whoa <br>I told these other niggas I know <br>I'm from the city where the buddies might roll <br>to your mum's house <br>And tell her put your hands on the wall <br>How you doing my dude <br>That's the truth to the matter of the fact <br>Truth is cause I did them like that <br>Matter fact I'ma bring it right back <br>Playing games cause I did them like that <br>Plain game cause I did them like that <br>Shit great if you came from the trap <br>My nigga <br>All that I'm hearing is sounding retarded <br>Either pop mollies or getting this money <br>Either go beaches <br>and condos you fucking but airfare <br>I get it you get it that something you do <br>Or something you don't <br>I'm just out here trying <br>to give people hope <br>I'm just out here trying <br>to hold on the rope <br>I would never stoop that low]]></content><category term="Mura Masa" label="Mura Masa"/><category term="Low (Feat. Jay Prince)" label="Low (Feat. Jay Prince)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Your_Bones_Intermission/</id><title>Mura Masa - Your Bones (Intermission) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:39:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:39:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Your_Bones_Intermission/" title="Mura Masa - Your Bones (Intermission) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If I can be your clothes <br>I'll hang off all your bones <br>Every hour <br>Every day <br><br>If I can be your clothes <br>I'll hang off all your bones <br>Every hour <br>Every day <br><br>If I can be your clothes <br>I'll hang off all your bones <br>Every hour <br>Every day <br><br>If I can be your clothes <br>I'll hang off all your bones <br>Every hour <br>Every day <br><br>If I can be your clothes <br>I'll hang off all your bones <br>Every hour <br>Every day <br><br>If I can be your clothes <br>I'll hang off all your bones <br>Every hour <br>Every day <br><br>If I can be your clothes <br>I'll hang off all your bones <br>Every hour <br>Every day]]></content><category term="Mura Masa" label="Mura Masa"/><category term="Your Bones (Intermission)" label="Your Bones (Intermission)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Terrible_Love_Feat_Denai_Moore/</id><title>Mura Masa - Terrible Love (Feat. Denai Moore) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:39:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:39:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Terrible_Love_Feat_Denai_Moore/" title="Mura Masa - Terrible Love (Feat. Denai Moore) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Magic <br>Another carelessly off chord <br>And it's tragic <br>To lose control of my own heart <br>I know I'm not the only one <br>That you've held in your arms <br>I know I'm not the only one <br>I know I'm not the only one <br><br>Terrible <br>This is what terrible love feels like <br>Terrible <br>Am I breaking my own heart to fix this? <br><br>Magic <br>How I'm moved by the hate <br>But it's static <br>How I left in this state <br>I never thought that we'd become <br>So far apart and undone <br>I never thought that we'd become <br>I never thought that we'd become <br><br>Terrible <br>This is what terrible love feels like <br>Terrible <br>Am I breaking my own heart to fix this?]]></content><category term="Mura Masa" label="Mura Masa"/><category term="Terrible Love (Feat. Denai Moore)" label="Terrible Love (Feat. Denai Moore)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Firefly_Feat_Nao/</id><title>Mura Masa - Firefly (Feat. Nao) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:39:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:39:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Firefly_Feat_Nao/" title="Mura Masa - Firefly (Feat. Nao) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pavement's turning into gold <br>And it's risin' up into my eyes <br>Up on my back I feel the static more <br>Tripping the wire, surrounded in time <br><br>I see this as mystical <br>I'm sure that you know <br>I see this as mystical <br>I'm sure that you know <br><br>Just say <br>You'll be my firefly <br>Take everything or nothing at all <br>Just say <br>You'll be my firefly <br>Take everything or nothing at all <br><br>Just say "yes" <br>Just say "yes" <br>Just say <br>"I'd rather have everything than nothing at all" <br><br>Sorry I've got none to pose <br>Images I pictured inside <br>Everything I've tried to close <br>Carrying the weight on my back I feel the the static more <br>Tripping the wire, surrounded in time <br><br>I see this as mystical <br>I'm sure that you know <br>I see this as mystical <br>I'm sure that you know <br><br>Just say <br>You'll be my firefly <br>Take everything or nothing at all <br>Just say <br>You'll be my firefly <br>Take everything or nothing at all <br><br>Just say "yes" <br>Just say "yes" <br>Just say <br>"I'd rather have everything than nothing at all" <br>Just say "yes"]]></content><category term="Mura Masa" label="Mura Masa"/><category term="Firefly (Feat. Nao)" label="Firefly (Feat. Nao)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Are_U_There_/</id><title>Mura Masa - Are U There? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:39:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:39:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mura_Masa/Are_U_There_/" title="Mura Masa - Are U There? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I need to know <br>That you're here with me <br>I need to know <br>That you're here with me <br>I need to know <br>That you're here with me <br>I need to know <br>That you're here with me <br>Here with me <br>Here with me <br>Here with me <br>Here with me <br>Here with me <br>Here with me <br>Here with me <br>Here with me <br>Here with me <br>]]></content><category term="Mura Masa" label="Mura Masa"/><category term="Are U There?" label="Are U There?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Justin_Timberlake/Mirrors_Radio_Edit/</id><title>Justin Timberlake - Mirrors (Radio Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:40:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:40:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Justin_Timberlake/Mirrors_Radio_Edit/" title="Justin Timberlake - Mirrors (Radio Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Aren't you somethin' to admire <br>'Cause your shine is somethin' like a mirror <br>And I can't help but notice, <br>you reflect in this heart of mine <br>If you ever feel alone <br>and the glare makes me hard to find <br>Just know that I'm always parallel on the other side <br><br>'Cause with your hand in my hand <br>and a pocket full of soul <br>I can tell you there's no place we couldn't go <br>Just put your hand on the past <br>I'm here tryin' to pull you through <br>You just gotta be strong <br><br>'Cause I don't wanna lost you now <br>I'm lookin' right at the other half of me <br>The vacancy that sat in my heart <br>Is a space that now you hold <br>Show me how to fight for now <br>And I'll tell you, baby, it was easy <br>Comin' back into you once I figured it out <br>You were right here all along <br><br>It's like you're my mirror <br>My mirror staring back at me <br>I couldn't get any bigger <br>With anyone else beside me <br>And now it's clear as this promise <br>That we're making two reflections into one <br>'Cause it's like you're my mirror <br>My mirror staring back at me, staring back at me <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>Aren't you somethin', an original <br>'Cause it doesn't seem merely assembled <br>And I can't help but stare <br>'Cause I see truth somewhere in your eyes <br>I can't ever change without you <br>You reflect me <br>I love that about you <br>And if I could <br>I would look at us all the time <br><br>'Cause with your hand in my hand <br>and a pocket full of soul <br>I can tell you there's no place we couldn't go <br>Just put your hand on the past <br>I'm here tryin' to pull you through <br>You just gotta be strong <br><br>'Cause I don't wanna lost you now <br>I'm lookin' right at the other half of me <br>The vacancy that sat in my heart <br>Is a space that now you hold <br>Show me how to fight for now <br>And I'll tell you, baby, it was easy <br>Comin' back into you once I figured it out <br>You were right here all along <br><br>It's like you're my mirror <br>My mirror staring back at me <br>I couldn't get any bigger <br>With anyone else beside me <br>And now it's clear as this promise <br>That we're making two reflections into one <br>'Cause it's like you're my mirror <br>My mirror staring back at me, staring back at me <br><br><br>Yesterday is history <br>Tomorrow's a mystery <br>I can see you lookin' back at me <br>Keep your eyes on me <br>Baby, keep your eyes on me <br><br><br>'Cause I don't wanna lost you now <br>I'm lookin' right at the other half of me <br>The vacancy that sat in my heart <br>Is a space that now you hold <br>Show me how to fight for now <br>I'll tell you, baby, it was easy <br>Comin' back into you once I figured it out <br>You were right here all along <br><br>It's like you're my mirror <br>My mirror staring back at me <br>I couldn't get any bigger <br>With anyone else beside me <br>And now it's clear as this promise <br>That we're making two reflections into one <br>'Cause it's like you're my mirror <br>My mirror staring back at me, staring back at me <br><br>You are, you are the love of my life <br><br>Now, you're the inspiration for this precious song <br>And I just wanna see your face light up <br>Since you put me on <br>So now I say goodbye to the old me <br>It's already gone <br>And I can't wait wait wait wait wait to get you home <br>Just to let you know, you are <br><br>You are, you are the love of my life <br><br>Girl, you're my reflection <br>All I see is you <br>My reflection, in everything I do <br>You're my reflection and all I see is you <br>My reflection, in everything I do <br><br>You are, you are the love of my life]]></content><category term="Justin Timberlake" label="Justin Timberlake"/><category term="Mirrors (Radio Edit)" label="Mirrors (Radio Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Legend/All_Of_Me/</id><title>John Legend - All Of Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:40:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:40:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Legend/All_Of_Me/" title="John Legend - All Of Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What would I do without your smart mouth <br>Drawing me in, and you kicking me out <br>You've got my head spinning, no kidding, I can't pin you down <br>What's going on in that beautiful mind <br>I'm on your magical mystery ride <br>And I'm so dizzy, don't know what hit me, but I'll be alright <br><br>My head's under water <br>But I'm breathing fine <br>You're crazy and I'm out of my mind <br><br>'Cause all of me <br>Loves all of you <br>Love your curves and all your edges <br>All your perfect imperfections <br>Give your all to me <br>I'll give my all to you <br>You're my end and my beginning <br>Even when I lose I'm winning <br>'Cause I give you all of me <br>And you give me all of you, oh oh <br><br>How many times do I have to tell you <br>Even when you're crying you're beautiful too <br>The world is beating you down, I'm around through every mood <br>You're my downfall, you're my muse <br>My worst distraction, my rhythm and blues <br>I can't stop singing, it's ringing, in my head for you <br><br>My head's under water <br>But I'm breathing fine <br>You're crazy and I'm out of my mind <br><br>'Cause all of me <br>Loves all of you <br>Love your curves and all your edges <br>All your perfect imperfections <br>Give your all to me <br>I'll give my all to you <br>You're my end and my beginning <br>Even when I lose I'm winning <br>'Cause I give you all of me <br>And you give me all of you, oh oh <br><br>Give me all of you <br>Cards on the table, we're both showing hearts <br>Risking it all, though it's hard <br><br>'Cause all of me <br>Loves all of you <br>Love your curves and all your edges <br>All your perfect imperfections <br>Give your all to me <br>I'll give my all to you <br>You're my end and my beginning <br>Even when I lose I'm winning <br>'Cause I give you all of me <br>And you give me all of you <br><br>I give you all of me <br>And you give me all of you, oh oh]]></content><category term="John Legend" label="John Legend"/><category term="All Of Me" label="All Of Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도밍고/차가운_4월의_바다/</id><title>도밍고 - 차가운 4월의 바다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:40:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:40:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%EB%B0%8D%EA%B3%A0/%EC%B0%A8%EA%B0%80%EC%9A%B4_4%EC%9B%94%EC%9D%98_%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%A4/" title="도밍고 - 차가운 4월의 바다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지나가는 저 비바람처럼 <br>지나간다 말하지 말아요 <br>이해할 수 없는 당신이기에 <br>아무 말하지 말아요 <br>잊혀진다 말하지 말아요 <br>잊을 수 없는 사람이에요 <br>물로 적은 글씨가 아니기에 <br>맘에 새긴 슬픔이기에 <br>지나간다 지나간다 말하면서 <br>그럴 순 없잖아 <br>잊혀진다 잊혀진다 말하면서 <br>더 생각날 수 있잖아 <br>잊을 수 있는 방법이 있어도 <br>그렇게 잊지 않겠어 <br>잊지 않아 널 놓지 않아 그날의 <br>차가운 4월의 바다 <br>지나간다 지나간다 말하면서 <br>그럴 순 없잖아 <br>잊혀진다 잊혀진다 말하면서 <br>더 생각날 수 있잖아 <br>잊을 수 있는 방법이 있어도 <br>그렇게 잊지 않겠어 <br>잊지 않아 널 놓지 않아 그날의 <br>차가운 4월의 바다 <br>]]></content><category term="도밍고" label="도밍고"/><category term="차가운 4월의 바다" label="차가운 4월의 바다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/To_My_Mom/</id><title>ENM - To My Mom - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:40:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:40:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/To_My_Mom/" title="ENM - To My Mom - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어둔 밤 공기가 <br>다가와 나를 감싸고 <br>나는 두려움에 <br>눈물 흘릴 때 <br>항상 여린 나를 품으며 <br>따뜻한 손길로 <br>나를 지켜주신 <br>나의 어머니 <br>사랑했던 거겠죠 <br>너무나 소중했던 거겠죠 <br>나의 어머니 사랑인 걸요 <br>걱정됐던 거겠죠 <br>너무나 안쓰럽던 거겠죠 <br>나의 어머니 사랑을 <br>사랑해요 나의 어머니 <br>주름가득한 세월속에 <br>말못했죠 언제나 당신을 <br>사랑합니다 <br>My Mom <br>사랑했던 거겠죠 <br>너무나 소중했던 거겠죠 <br>나의 어머니 사랑인 걸요 <br>걱정됐던 거겠죠 <br>너무나 안쓰럽던 거겠죠 <br>나의 어머니 사랑을 <br>사랑해요 나의 어머니 <br>주름가득한 세월속에 <br>말못했죠 언제나 당신을 <br>사랑합니다 <br>My Mom <br>감사해요 나의 어머니 <br>주름가득한 세월속에 <br>말못했죠 언제나 당신을 <br>사랑합니다 <br>My Mom <br>감사합니다 <br>Thanks Mom <br>]]></content><category term="ENM" label="ENM"/><category term="To My Mom" label="To My Mom"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/데자뷰/</id><title>ENM - 데자뷰 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:41:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:41:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/%EB%8D%B0%EC%9E%90%EB%B7%B0/" title="ENM - 데자뷰 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[앙상한 나무위에 <br>새싹이 돋아나듯 <br>거칠은 내 모습도 <br>겨울을 깨워주는 <br>촉촉한 봄비들이 <br>내 작은 어깨위로 <br>떠나지말라고 해도 <br>잡힐듯 잡히지 않는 <br>나의 여린 꿈 <br>정신없이 달려봐도 <br>언제나 제자리인 듯 한데 <br>헤어지지말자 해도 <br>보일듯 보이지않는 <br>나의 첫사랑 <br>눈물속에 흐려지는 <br>다시 못볼 너의 저 뒷모습 <br>Hopefully just a dream <br>모두가 돌아가고 <br>어둠이 내려앉은 <br>흔들리는 창가에서 <br>매서워진 빗줄기에 <br>떨어지는 나를 봤지 <br>두눈을 감아보네 <br>떠나지말라고 해도 <br>잡힐듯 잡히지 않는 <br>나의 여린 꿈 <br>정신없이 달려봐도 <br>언제나 제자리인 듯 한데 <br>헤어지지말자 해도 <br>보일듯 보이지않는 <br>나의 첫사랑 <br>눈물속에 흐려지는 <br>다시 못볼 너의 저 뒷모습 <br>떠나지말라고 해도 <br>잡힐듯 잡히지 않는 <br>나의 여린 꿈 <br>정신없이 달려봐도 <br>언제나 제자리인 듯 한데 <br>헤어지지말자 해도 <br>보일듯 보이지않는 <br>나의 첫사랑 <br>눈물속에 흐려지는 <br>다시 못볼 너의 저 뒷모습 <br>Hopefully just a dream <br>]]></content><category term="ENM" label="ENM"/><category term="데자뷰" label="데자뷰"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/너를_위해/</id><title>ENM - 너를 위해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:41:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:41:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9C%84%ED%95%B4/" title="ENM - 너를 위해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나의 곁에서 <br>숨을 죽이며 <br>나를 살며시 <br>안아주던 그대 어디에 <br>사랑이 많아 <br>모든 슬픔을 <br>한눈에 간직하던 <br>너는 지금 어디에 <br>너를 내 품에 <br>안고 싶어 워 워 <br>우리 함께했던 <br>시간이 영원하도록 <br>떠나봐 너의 <br>자유로운 날개를 펴고 <br>멀리 멀리 날아봐 <br>날위해 널 슬프게 <br>할 순 없잖아 <br>더 이상 나로 인해 <br>너의 모든걸 포기하지마 <br>나보다 널 위한 <br>사랑 위하여 <br>너를 내품에 <br>안고 싶어 우 우 <br>우리 함께했던 <br>시간이 영원하도록 <br>떠나봐 너의 <br>자유로운 날개를 펴고 <br>멀리 멀리 날아봐 <br>날위해 널 슬프게 <br>할 순 없잖아 <br>더 이상 나로인해 <br>너의 모든걸 포기하지마 <br>나보다 널 위한 <br>사랑 위하여 <br>우리 함께 했던 <br>시간은 떠나가지만 <br>우리 사랑은 <br>언제나 영원하도록 <br>웃어봐 너의 <br>자유로운 날개를 펴고 <br>멀리 멀리 날아봐 <br>날위해 한번만 <br>밝게 웃어줘 <br>더 이상 나로인해 <br>너의 모든걸 포기하지마 <br>나보다 널 위한 <br>사랑 위하여 <br>]]></content><category term="ENM" label="ENM"/><category term="너를 위해" label="너를 위해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/한_남자_이야기/</id><title>ENM - 한 남자 이야기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:41:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:41:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/%ED%95%9C_%EB%82%A8%EC%9E%90_%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC%EA%B8%B0/" title="ENM - 한 남자 이야기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모든 게 끝난 것처럼 <br>너에게 말을 했지만 <br>모두가 널 위함인 걸 <br>내 맘 알 순 없겠죠 <br>함께 한 많은 날들이 <br>그댈 힘들게 한대도 <br>그대 조금만 참아줘요 <br>우연히 길을 걷다 <br>혹시 그댈 본다면 <br>지금처럼 한없이 <br>그저 눈물만 흘리겠죠 <br>그대 없는 나의 삶은 <br>말이 아니죠 <br>숨 쉬어도 산 게 아니죠 <br>평생을 못 잊겠죠 <br>그대 부디 행복하길 <br>기도 할게요 <br>내 삶을 포기한대도 <br>그대 행복만이 기쁨인 것을 <br>모두가 부정한대도 <br>너만을 놓지 않기를 <br>나에게 용길 주던 <br>널 외면했던 한 남자 <br>불안한 나의 일상과 <br>준비된 너의 행복을 <br>바꿀 순 없는 거잖아 <br>우연히 길을 걷다 <br>혹시 그댈 본다면 <br>지금처럼 한없이 <br>그저 눈물만 흘리겠죠 <br>그대 없는 나의 삶은 <br>말이 아니죠 <br>숨 쉬어도 산 게 아니죠 <br>평생을 못 잊겠죠 <br>그대 부디 행복하길 <br>기도 할게요 <br>내 삶을 포기한대도 <br>그대 행복만이 기쁨인 것을 <br>무료했던 나의 삶에 <br>빛을 안겨준 그대이기에 <br>그댈 잊을 순 없겠죠 <br>그대 없는 나의 삶은 <br>말이 아니죠 <br>숨 쉬어도 산 게 아니죠 <br>평생을 못 잊겠죠 <br>그대 부디 행복하길 <br>기도 할게요 <br>내 삶을 포기한대도 <br>그대 행복만이 기쁨인 것을 <br>]]></content><category term="ENM" label="ENM"/><category term="한 남자 이야기" label="한 남자 이야기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/소원/</id><title>ENM - 소원 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:41:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:41:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/%EC%86%8C%EC%9B%90/" title="ENM - 소원 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아침에 눈을 뜨면 <br>어느새 아른거리는 너 <br>나의 사랑이 널 힘들게 한다는 <br>그 말 난 슬픈데 <br>어쩌면 모르겠지 <br>널 위해 살아가는 모습 <br>세월이 지나 날 떠나간다는 <br>두려운 사랑을 <br>용서해줘 사랑이란 이름으로 <br>너의 순결함을 앗아갔지 <br>변해가는 세상 속에 닮아가는 <br>사랑이 두려웠기에 <br>너 없인 살아갈 수 <br>없다는 걸 알게 되었지 <br>아무 말없이 내 팔에 안기어 <br>힘없이 울던 너 <br>용서해줘 사랑이란 이름으로 <br>너의 순결함을 앗아갔지 <br>변해가는 세상 속에 닮아가는 <br>사랑이 두려웠기에 <br>울지는 마 울지는 마 그 무엇도 <br>너와 나를 헤어지게 만들지는 <br>못 할 것을 믿어 <br>힘들었지 우리사랑 간절했던 <br>그 날들을 이젠 우리 <br>영원히 함께 <br>널 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="ENM" label="ENM"/><category term="소원" label="소원"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/기도/</id><title>ENM - 기도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:41:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:41:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/%EA%B8%B0%EB%8F%84/" title="ENM - 기도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[힘들었죠 우리 사랑 <br>지켜간다는 게 <br>때론 너무나 슬퍼 <br>눈물도 많이 흘렸었죠 <br>행복했죠 지친 나의 <br>일상 속에서도 <br>항상 나의 곁에는 <br>그대가 있어 주었잖아요 <br>언제나 날 보며 웃어 주었죠 <br>아무것도 없는 날 위해 <br>기도를 했어 <br>너와 영원하도록 <br>함께 하고 팠던 마음을 <br>기억해줘 이 세상을 <br>눈감는 순간까지도 <br>함께 할 나란걸 <br>너의 두 눈에 고인 <br>그 눈물까지도 <br>함께 할 내 품 안으로 <br>기억하죠 초라해진 <br>나의 어깨에도 <br>그대 작은 손으로 <br>나를 조건 없이 잡아줬죠 <br>감사해요 어두웠던 <br>나의 생활에도 <br>그대 작은 빛으로 <br>밝은 세상을 내게 선물해줬죠 <br>언제나 날 보며 웃어 주었죠 <br>아무것도 없는 날 위해 <br>기도를 했어 <br>너와 영원하도록 <br>함께 하고 팠던 마음을 <br>기억해줘 이 세상을 <br>눈감는 순간까지도 <br>함께 할 나란걸 <br>너의 두 눈에 고인 <br>그 눈물까지도 <br>함께 할 내 품 안으로 <br>기억해줘 이 세상을 <br>눈감는 순간까지도 <br>함께 할 나란걸 <br>너의 두 눈에 고인 <br>그 눈물까지도 <br>함께 할 내 품 안으로 <br>기도를 했어 <br>가냘픈 너의 두 눈에 <br>미소가 가득하기를 <br>]]></content><category term="ENM" label="ENM"/><category term="기도" label="기도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/커피프린세스/</id><title>ENM - 커피프린세스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:41:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:41:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/%EC%BB%A4%ED%94%BC%ED%94%84%EB%A6%B0%EC%84%B8%EC%8A%A4/" title="ENM - 커피프린세스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[커피 향이 가득한 날에 <br>우연히 그대를 보았죠 <br>환한 미소에 단발머리 소녀 <br>나를 반겨주며 인사했죠 <br>손끝으로 주문만 하고 <br>눈은 그댈 향해 있네요 <br>나를 보는 그대 미소를 짓죠 <br>어색함에 눈 돌렸죠 <br>그대에게 단 한번만 <br>말 할 수 있다면 <br>신이 허락한다면 그저 <br>정신 없이 떠들겠죠 <br>그댈 향한 내 진심을 <br>이해할 수 없다 한대도 난 <br>행복함에 울겠죠 <br>매일 그댈 찾아 갔었죠 <br>때론 웃고 힘들어한 그대 <br>말없이 멀리서 바라만 보죠 <br>가끔 그댄 내게 미소 짓죠 <br>내게 말을 걸어 보아도 <br>말없이 손짓만 하지요 <br>하루라도 그댈 볼 수 없다면 <br>내겐 상상할 수 없죠 <br>그대에게 단 한번만 <br>말 할 수 있다면 <br>신이 허락한다면 그저 <br>정신 없이 떠들겠죠 <br>그댈 향한 내 진심을 <br>이해할 수 없다 한대도 난 <br>행복함에 울겠죠 <br>사랑한다는 것이 <br>때론 어렵겠지요 <br>평범한 것도 내겐 <br>쉽지가 않네요 <br>나에게도 사랑이 올 걸 <br>생각 못했죠 <br>그댈 생각만 해도 <br>그저 눈물이 나오는 걸요 <br>그댈 향한 내 사랑을 <br>말을 할 수 없다 하여도 난 <br>사랑함에 행복해 <br>사랑함에 소중해 <br>]]></content><category term="ENM" label="ENM"/><category term="커피프린세스" label="커피프린세스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/눈속에서/</id><title>ENM - 눈속에서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:41:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:41:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/%EB%88%88%EC%86%8D%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C/" title="ENM - 눈속에서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한밤에 내린 하얀 눈 속에 <br>그대 은빛 향기에 취해 난 잠들죠 <br>부드런 그대 숨결소리에 <br>머리 위에 내리는 눈을 녹이죠 <br>살며시 내게 다가와 <br>사랑을 속삭여주던 <br>그대 눈빛은 아직도 기억나는데 <br>새하얀 오늘 아침엔 그대 손길은 <br>누굴 위하여 보이질 않나요 <br>사랑에 지쳐 녹아버리는 <br>저 하얀 눈사람이 <br>나를 슬프게 해요 <br>이 밤이 모두 지나가기 전에 <br>모두가 녹기 전에 내게 돌아와요 <br>살며시 내게 다가와 <br>사랑을 속삭여주던 <br>그대 눈빛은 아직도 기억나는데 <br>새하얀 오늘 아침엔 그대 손길은 <br>누굴 위하여 보이질 않나요 <br>떠나간 많은 시간에 <br>그대 모습 그리워 잠 못 들었죠 <br>함께할 날을 약속해 <br>그대만을 사랑해 그대여 <br>그대 모습 그리워 잠 못 들었죠 <br>함께할 날을 약속해 <br>그대만을 사랑해 <br>그대여 <br>]]></content><category term="ENM" label="ENM"/><category term="눈속에서" label="눈속에서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/축복/</id><title>ENM - 축복 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:41:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:41:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/%EC%B6%95%EB%B3%B5/" title="ENM - 축복 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언젠가 흰 눈이 내리면 <br>우리의 따뜻한 사랑을 얘기해요 <br>눈 감은 그대 어깨에 기대어 <br>달빛보다 환한 그댈 보겠죠 <br>달빛에 은은히 빛나는 <br>저 하얀 세상에 사랑을 축복해요 <br>잠이든 그대 내 품에 안기어 <br>아침햇살 속에 눈을 뜨겠죠 <br>진한 꽃 향기와 수줍은 꽃잎에 <br>살며시 내려앉은 햇살 <br>fall in love <br>아침을 준비한 그대의 정성과 <br>소중한 사랑하는 가족들 <br>그대 내 품으로 오세요 <br>그대 사랑으로 오세요 <br>언젠가 떠나시던 그 밤이 <br>너무 두려웠죠 <br>하얀 눈송이가 날리며 <br>우리 사랑을 축복해요 <br>저 하늘 햇살 속으로 <br>비친 그대 모습 안으며 <br>나 죽는 날까지 사랑해요 <br>진한 꽃 향기와 수줍은 꽃잎에 <br>살며시 내려앉은 햇살 <br>fall in love <br>아침을 준비한 그대의 정성과 <br>소중한 사랑하는 가족들 <br>그대 내 품으로 오세요 <br>그대 사랑으로 오세요 <br>언젠가 떠나시던 그 밤이 <br>너무 두려웠죠 <br>하얀 눈송이가 날리며 <br>우리 사랑을 축복해요 <br>저 하늘 햇살 속으로 <br>비친 그대 모습 안으며 <br>나 죽는 날까지 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="ENM" label="ENM"/><category term="축복" label="축복"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/너의_하루/</id><title>ENM - 너의 하루 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:41:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:41:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ENM/%EB%84%88%EC%9D%98_%ED%95%98%EB%A3%A8/" title="ENM - 너의 하루 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[병들어 변해가는 세상들 <br>세상들 <br>웃음을 잃어가는 사람들 <br>사람들 <br>그대와 새하얗게 그려봐 <br>그려봐 <br>모두가 순수하기를 기도해 <br>구름처럼 흘러가는 <br>소리 없는 시간들 <br>바람결에 흩날리는 <br>낙엽 같은 추억들 <br>고요하게 숨을 쉬는 <br>꿈결같은 너에게 <br>이 모든걸 함께하며 <br>간직하고 싶은 걸 <br>my love <br>언제까지 너와 함께라면 <br>나는 웃을 수 있을 것 같아 <br>작은 행복의 순간까지라도 <br>모두 아름답도록 <br>잠든 너의 하루를 <br>I'm in your eyes <br>내가 깨우고 싶어 <br>이른 아침 이슬에 <br>I'm in your heart <br>너와 눈 뜨고 싶어 <br>예 <br>밤새워서 얘기했던 <br>우리만의 꿈들이 <br>웃음 짓는 별빛 속에 <br>사랑으로 변하네 <br>my love <br>언제까지 너와 함께라면 <br>나는 웃을 수 있을 것 같아 <br>작은 행복의 순간까지라도 <br>모두 아름답도록 <br>잠든 너의 하루를 <br>I'm in your eyes <br>내가 깨우고 싶어 <br>이른 아침 이슬에 <br>I'm in your heart <br>너와 눈 뜨고 싶어 <br>오 예 <br>]]></content><category term="ENM" label="ENM"/><category term="너의 하루" label="너의 하루"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이진호/문/</id><title>이진호 - 문 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:41:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:41:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%84%ED%98%B8/%EB%AC%B8/" title="이진호 - 문 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너의 집 문이 열리고 <br>따뜻한 조명이 비추고 <br>너는 조용한 <br>음악을 고르고 <br>나는 장을 봐온 <br>저녁거리를 나르네 <br>여기 가스렌즈에 <br>불을 조금만 <br>좀 올려줘 <br>니가 말하네 <br>저기 도마 위에 <br>양파와 파를 좀 썰어줘 <br>니가 말하네 <br>부엌엔 찌개 끊는 <br>냄새가 나고 <br>밥솥에 불은 초록색 <br>너는 조그만 <br>수저를 들고서 <br>내게 찌개의 간을 <br>맛보라 하네 <br>여기 냉장고 안에 <br>밑반찬 들을 <br>좀 꺼내줘 <br>니가 말하네 <br>저기 찬장 안에 <br>잔을 두 개만 <br>좀 꺼내줘 <br>니가 말하네 <br>그리고 너와 나는 <br>오늘 있었던 <br>일들을 나누네 <br>낮엔 누굴 만났어 <br>오전에 말한 <br>그 일은 잘 해결됐어 <br>찌게 맛있다 <br>많이 먹어 <br>물도 좀 마셔가면서 <br>그래 밥 좀 더있어 <br>그토록 바라던 일들이 <br>현실이 되었네 <br>그토록 바라던 일들이 <br>현실이 되었네 <br>]]></content><category term="이진호" label="이진호"/><category term="문" label="문"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임헌일/너무_아파/</id><title>임헌일 - 너무 아파 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:41:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:41:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%ED%97%8C%EC%9D%BC/%EB%84%88%EB%AC%B4_%EC%95%84%ED%8C%8C/" title="임헌일 - 너무 아파 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너와 헤어지고 <br>집으로 돌아오는 길에 <br>생각보다는 덤덤히 <br>아무 일도 없는 사람처럼 <br>버스에 올랐어 <br>지나치는 풍경 <br>늘 바래다주던 이 거리가 <br>마지막 인사를 건네던 <br>네 표정만큼 낯설어 보여 <br>그제서야 문득 <br>너를 보냈다는 게 <br>다시는 만날 수 없다는 게 <br>나는 솔직히 이해가 잘 안돼 <br>너무 사랑하는데 <br>그건 아무 의미가 없다는 게 <br>많이 힘들어 <br>너무 아파 <br>너무 아파 <br>횅한 방 한구석 침대 머리맡에 <br>네가 남겨둔 메시지들을 <br>정리하다 문득 <br>너를 보냈다는 게 <br>다시는 만날 수 없다는 게 <br>나는 솔직히 이해가 잘 안돼 <br>너무 사랑하는데 <br>그건 아무 의미가 없다는 게 <br>많이 힘들어 <br>너무 아파 <br>너무 아파 <br>]]></content><category term="임헌일" label="임헌일"/><category term="너무 아파" label="너무 아파"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임헌일/falling_in_love/</id><title>임헌일 - falling in love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:41:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:41:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%ED%97%8C%EC%9D%BC/falling_in_love/" title="임헌일 - falling in love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자꾸 고갤 돌린 건 <br>표정을 들킬 것 같아 그래 <br>요즘 잘 웃지 않는 건 <br>아직도 서툰 내 표현 때문에 <br>나를 걱정하는 듯 <br>멀뚱히 바라보는 <br>니 얼굴을 볼 자신이 없어 <br>난 너에게 빠진 것만 같아 <br>널 아는 건 꿈인 것만 같아 <br>I'm falling in love <br>깨어나고 싶지는 않아 <br>근데 가슴 한 켠이 아려와 <br>널 보면 눈물이 날 것 같아 <br>고개를 돌려 <br>cause I’m falling in love <br>tonight <br>너와 함께 있고 싶어 <br>너와 함께 <br>지나쳤어야 했어 <br>네가 아름답다는 걸 알기 전에 <br>몰랐어야 했어 <br>니 마음 속에 있는 그 사람을 <br>그게 왜 슬픈지 <br>사실 잘 모르겠어 <br>난 너에게 아무것도 아닌데 <br>난 너에게 빠진 것만 같아 <br>널 아는 건 꿈인 것만 같아 <br>I'm falling in love <br>깨어나고 싶지는 않아 <br>근데 가슴 한 켠이 아려와 <br>널 보면 눈물이 날 것 같아 <br>고개를 돌려 <br>cause I’m falling in love <br>tonight <br>아무리 노력해도 <br>널 지우려 해봐도 <br>내 마음은 더 깊어만 가고 <br>숨을 쉬기 힘들어 <br>난 견딜 수가 없어 <br>너에게 닿지도 않을 <br>노래를 부르고 있어 <br>넌 이런 내 마음을 아는지 <br>그저 우연인 건지 <br>눈을 맞추며 <br>그렇게 웃을 수 있는지 <br>그래서 난 더 마음이 아파 <br>멈출 수가 없을 것만 같아 <br>I’m falling in love <br>cause I’m falling in love <br>tonight <br>좋아해 널 사랑해 널 <br>falling in love <br>좋아해 널 사랑해 널 <br>cause I’m falling in love <br>]]></content><category term="임헌일" label="임헌일"/><category term="falling in love" label="falling in love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bracy/Lost/</id><title>Bracy - Lost - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:41:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:41:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bracy/Lost/" title="Bracy - Lost - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내겐 의미 없는 걸 <br>이제 재미없는 걸 이제 제 제 <br>이미 길이 아닌 길을 <br>가지 않으려 해 해 해 <br>한 눈에 봐도 저기 멀리 있어 <br>시간에 기대 흘러가려 해 <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>내가 할 수 있는 게 <br>내가 잘하던 것이 이제 제 제 <br>더는 생각이 나지 않아 <br>한 눈에 봐도 저기 멀리 있어 <br>시간에 기대 흘러가려 해 <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>희망은 부서졌어 <br>어디든 여기보다 나을 텐데 <br>나아가지도 못해 <br>다가가지도 못해 <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>Can’t Feel Can’t Feel <br>]]></content><category term="Bracy" label="Bracy"/><category term="Lost" label="Lost"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/B_Smyth/Might_Cuff_U/</id><title>B. Smyth - Might Cuff U - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:41:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:41:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/B_Smyth/Might_Cuff_U/" title="B. Smyth - Might Cuff U - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She let me touch her, so I ask her how it feel <br>She say she love it, but she wanna ride for real <br>So I let her ride for real <br>Goin' deep, givin' her chills <br>You can have whatever you want in this moment babe <br>I treat you right, yeah <br>Just bring that body to me 'cause I know you want it babe <br>I'ma take my time <br><br>Want you to remember that <br>So don't hold back, you feelin' that <br>When I put it in, you gon' want some more of that <br>When we fuck and we tryna get serious <br>Holdin' on tight like girl, get rid of it <br>Shawty so makes me so real of this <br>Call my line, you can't get enough, no <br>Just might cuff you, might cuff you <br><br>I don't wanna be the one to lead you on <br>But I might be the guy that's on your phone <br>Like, Baby, where you at What you doin' Can you come by <br>This money got me tunnel vision, I'm just out here tryna live life <br>I just might cuff you baby, love seems so overrated <br>I'll be the first to say it, I can't do no fakin' <br>I just might cuff you baby, love seems so overrated <br>I'll be the first to say it, I can't do no fakin' <br><br>Want you to remember that <br>So don't hold back, you feelin' that <br>When I put it in, you gon' want some more of that <br>When we fuck and we tryna get serious <br>Holdin' on tight like girl, get rid of it <br>Shawty so makes me so real of this <br>Call my line, you can't get enough, no <br>Just might cuff you, might cuff you <br><br>Baby girl, you can get cuffed by the Balmain dentals <br>Can't be sad when you dealin' with a Parkway nigga <br>Every nigga you see round me, I came a long way with 'em <br>I just gotta put a roll, I'ma pull up on you just because you full <br>Tryna lock you down like a jail, my bedroom is a cell <br>Feelin' on your booty like Kells, 500 dollars on smell <br>Fine as tonight in Chanel, nah nigga I don't resell <br>Kill the pussy, I'ma make bail, call me when your man ain't there, yeah <br><br>Want you to remember that <br>So don't hold back, you feelin' that <br>When I put it in, you gon' want some more of that <br>When we fuck and we tryna get serious <br>Holdin' on tight like girl, get rid of it <br>Shawty so makes me so real of this <br>Call my line, you can't get enough, no <br>Just might cuff you, might cuff you <br><br>Don't be actin' shy up in this room <br>Like I make you nervous, oh <br>I'ma take my time, do your body right <br>When I'm feelin' on your booty, yeah <br>I'ma take my time, do you right <br>Holdin' on tight like girl, get rid of it <br>I'ma take my time, do you right <br>Holdin' on tight like girl, get rid of it <br>Holdin' on tight like girl, get rid of it]]></content><category term="B. Smyth" label="B. Smyth"/><category term="Might Cuff U" label="Might Cuff U"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bipolar_Sunshine/The_Scientist/</id><title>Bipolar Sunshine - The Scientist - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:41:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:41:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bipolar_Sunshine/The_Scientist/" title="Bipolar Sunshine - The Scientist - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come up to meet you <br>tell you I'm sorry <br>You don't know <br>how lovely you are <br>I had to find you <br>tell you I need you <br>Tell you I set you apart <br>Tell me your secrets <br>and ask me your questions <br>Oh let's go back to the start <br>Running in circles <br>coming up tails <br>Heads on a science apart <br>Nobody said it was easy <br>It's such a shame for us to part <br>Nobody said it was easy <br>No one ever said <br>it would be this hard <br>Oh take me back to the start <br>I was just guessing <br>at numbers and figures <br>Pulling your puzzles apart <br>Questions of science <br>science and progress <br>Do not speak as loud as my heart <br>Tell me you love me <br>come back and haunt me <br>Oh and I rush to the start <br>Running in circles <br>chasing our tails <br>Coming back as we are <br>Nobody said it was easy <br>Oh It's such a shame for us to part <br>Nobody said it was easy <br>No one ever said <br>it would be so hard <br>I'm going back to the start <br>]]></content><category term="Bipolar Sunshine" label="Bipolar Sunshine"/><category term="The Scientist" label="The Scientist"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sky-Hi/クロノグラフ___Chronograph/</id><title>Sky-Hi - クロノグラフ / Chronograph - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:42:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:42:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sky-Hi/%E3%82%AF%E3%83%AD%E3%83%8E%E3%82%B0%E3%83%A9%E3%83%95___Chronograph/" title="Sky-Hi - クロノグラフ / Chronograph - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[치카즈이테 카사낫테 후레테 하나레테 <br>치카즈이테 카사낫테 유레테와 키에테 <br>아타타카이 카제가 후쿠 <br>이츠모노 미치토 하키나레타 쿠츠 <br>카와라나이 쿄우가 오와레바 <br>키미가 이나이 아시타가 쿠루 <br>난센카이메오 도지탓테 <br>짓토 시테테 쿠레나이 나미다 <br>칫테와 소라오 마우 하나비라니 <br>시센오 우츠시테 고마카시타 <br>돈나 코토바오 사가시테모 미츠카나이 <br>세메테 사이고쿠라이와토 무리니 <br>츠쿠루 에가오와 이비츠나 카타치 <br>이이나레타하즈노 아리가토우가 <br>이에즈니 이타 <br>쿠치카라 데타나라 가코니 나루카라 <br>이츠카 콘나 히가 쿠루난테 와캇테타 <br>다케도 소레와 다카라 소레가 <br>이타쿠테 이타쿠테 <br>이츠카 쟈나쿠 이마 키미가 미테루카라 <br>히토츠데모 오오쿠 와랏테 미세타 <br>오모에가 로쿠데모나이 코토노 가타가 도우모 <br>키미토 이루토 오오캇타 <br>안마리 키요우쟈나이노와 오타카이 사마다카라 <br>나오사라 코맛타몬닷타 <br>나니카토 미치니 마요우시 <br>와스레모노모 시테 키타 히토토우리 <br>도우니모 코우니모 이카나이 토키니와 <br>마카세테타나 아이쿄우니 <br>히토리데 야레루카 신빠이다요 <br>오마에모낫테 무키니 난나요 <br>쿠다라나이 코토바카리오 하나시테 <br>모우 히가 쿠레루 유우 사가리 <br>이이타쿠와 나이요 사요나라와 닷테 킷토 <br>쿠치카라 데타나라 모도레나이카라 <br>이츠카 오모이데와 투우자카루노나라 <br>세메테 이마와 다카라 이마와 <br>치카쿠데 미타쿠테 <br>이츠카 마타 이츠카 와라에루 히가 쿠루사 <br>소우 잇테 보쿠모 키미모 나이타 <br>아후레테쿠 지칸니 사카라우 사마니 <br>즛토 즛토 키미토 <br>카사낫테 하나레테 나이테 와랏테 <br>킷토 킷토 보쿠라 아스에 이쿤다 <br>이츠카 콘나 히가 쿠루난테 와캇테타 <br>다케도 소레와 다카라 소레가 <br>이타쿠테 이타쿠테 <br>이츠카 쟈나쿠 이마 키미가 미테루카라 <br>히토츠데모 오오쿠 와랏테 미세타 <br>이츠카 모우 이치도 마타 아우 히가 키타라 <br>이츠모 소코니 카와라나이 <br>보쿠데 이루카라 <br>이츠카 모우 이치도 마타 아우 소노 히마데 <br>사요나라 아리가토우 키미니 오쿠로우]]></content><category term="Sky-Hi" label="Sky-Hi"/><category term="クロノグラフ / Chronograph" label="クロノグラフ / Chronograph"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sky-Hi/Double_Down/</id><title>Sky-Hi - Double Down - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:42:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:42:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sky-Hi/Double_Down/" title="Sky-Hi - Double Down - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Play <br>싯빠이카 세이코오카 <br>소토시타라 Game Over <br>사아 하지메요우카 <br>Max Bet <br>호오카이카 에이코오카 <br>키오 누케바 Take Over <br>사아 하지메요우카 <br>Ladies and Gentlemen <br>히비쿠 카네노 오토 <br>핫테 소토시타라 스베테가 제로에 <br>가켓뿌치노 토키코소 카케노 메 <br>옷토, 후루에테루제 야메토케 <br>미히라이타 메 하이타 코토바니 <br>아마쿠 카라미츠쿠 우소노 미 <br>엔료난테 스루 코토모 나이 <br>스베테 이타다쿠제 사이오 코로가시 <br>운메이, 키보우, 세이코오스라 <br>테후다노 나카노 타다 히토츠노 슈단 <br>코오카 후코오카 고오루와 나이제 보오야 <br>It's Showtime 사아 쇼오부다 <br>잔넨, 스데니 오레노 페에스사 <br>스베테노 코에가 키에루 세츠나 <br>Ten, Jack, Queen, King <br>사이고와 모치론 Ace다 <br>카치호오나라 이마카라 레쿠챠아 <br>하시카라 아카레테 이쿠 테후다 <br>Ten, Jack, Queen, King <br>미나사마 오요샤 <br>It's my turn to fly <br>토메라레나이 <br>우소모 리아루모 요미 코무 세카이 <br>Double Down <br>토메야시나이 <br>제츠보오, 쿄오후, 콘톤, <br>마토메테 우케오우제 카키마제나 <br>Up and Down 테노히라노 우에사 <br>Let's Get Ready to Go <br>노코리 와즈카나 메이오 고탄노오 <br>테모토니 노코스 키리후다노 카아도 <br>I know 코코데 히쿠나도 고핫토 <br>기리기리데 이키루노가 스탄다아도 <br>High카 Low카 카케나 보오야 <br>도우시타? 야타라 하데나 몬스타아 <br>멧키가 하게타요오다 <br>스베테 마키아게니 키타제 Roll Up <br>타네카 시카케카 미타 메다케카 <br>쿠치비루 칸다 카코나라 시카바네사 <br>이마 카미사마스라 시타가에타 <br>오레가 스베테 테니 이레니 키타다케다 <br>노코리 와즈카나 메이오 고탄노오 <br>테모토니 노코스 키리후다노 카아도 <br>I know 코코데 히쿠나도 고핫토 <br>기리기리데 이키루노가 스탄다아도 <br>잔넨, 스데니 오레노 페에스사 <br>스베테노 코에가 키에루 세츠나 <br>Ten, Jack, Queen, King <br>사이고와 모치론 Ace다 <br>카치호오나라 이마카라 레쿠챠아 <br>하시카라 아카레테 이쿠 테후다 <br>Ten, Jack, Queen, King <br>미나사마 오요샤 <br>&gt;토메라레나이 <br>우소모 리아루모 요미 코무 세카이 <br>Double Down <br>토메야시나이 <br>이치방 타카이 옷즈카라 이츠닷테 <br>힛쿠리 카에시테키타 <br>카츠마데 야메나케레바 <br>마케시라즈노 후레에야아 <br>나미다니 키즈아토 소노 스베테 리시츠케테 <br>Ray Back <br>It's my turn to fly <br>토메라레나이 <br>우소모 리아루모 요미 코무 세카이 <br>Double Down <br>토메야시나이 <br>제츠보오, 쿄오후, 콘톤, <br>마토메테 우케오우제 카키마제나 <br>Up and Down 테노히라노 우에사 <br>Let's Get Ready to Play <br>싯빠이카 세이코오카 <br>소토시타라 Game Over <br>사아 하지메요우카 <br>Max Bet <br>호오카이카 에이코오카 <br>키오 누케바 Take Over <br>사아 하지메요우카 <br>Play <br>싯빠이카 세이코오카 <br>소토시타라 Game Over <br>사아 하지메요우카 <br>Max Bet <br>호오카이카 에이코오카 <br>키오 누케바 Take Over <br>사아 하지메요우카]]></content><category term="Sky-Hi" label="Sky-Hi"/><category term="Double Down" label="Double Down"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김수일/His_Loves_Never_Shaken_Feat_양효승_채수빈/</id><title>김수일 - His Love`s Never Shaken (Feat. 양효승, 채수빈) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:42:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:42:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%88%98%EC%9D%BC/His_Loves_Never_Shaken_Feat_%EC%96%91%ED%9A%A8%EC%8A%B9_%EC%B1%84%EC%88%98%EB%B9%88/" title="김수일 - His Love`s Never Shaken (Feat. 양효승, 채수빈) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어둔 내 삶에 찾아오셔서 <br>쓰러진 나를 일으켜 세워 <br>밝은 빛으로 나의 맘속을 <br>점점 환하게 비춰주신 <br>내 안의 상처뿐인 <br>모든 아픔 치유하시고 <br>모든 짐을 벗겨주시는 <br>내 안의 모든 과거 <br>모든 죄악 사해주시고 <br>회복의 기쁨을 주시는 <br>나를 향한 사랑 예수 <br>영원하신 사랑 예수 <br>His love's never shaken <br>His love's never failure <br>나를 향한 사랑 예수 <br>영원하신 사랑 예수 <br>His love's never shaken <br>His love's never failure <br>His love's never shaken <br>His love's never failure <br>His love's never shaken <br>His love's never shaken <br>His love's never failure <br>His love's never shaken <br>내 안의 상처뿐인 <br>모든 아픔 치유하시고 <br>모든 짐을 벗겨주시는 <br>내 안의 모든 과거 <br>모든 죄악 사해주시고 <br>회복의 기쁨을 주시는 <br>나를 향한 사랑 예수 <br>영원하신 사랑 예수 <br>His love's never shaken <br>His love's never failure <br>나를 향한 사랑 예수 <br>영원하신 사랑 예수 <br>His love's never shaken <br>His love's never failure <br>변하지 않는 주의 사랑을 <br>우리 같이 함께 노래해 <br>영원히 우리와 함께 계시는 <br>주의 사랑 함께 찬양해 <br>죄속에서 계속 <br>맛보는 실패도 <br>날 위해 뒤집으셨네 <br>속죄로 <br>그러니 어찌 <br>가만있을 수 있겠어 <br>그 사랑이 날 <br>향해 있어 매순간 <br>느끼며 살아 <br>사랑이 올 때 <br>느낌 오묘해 <br>내 삶에 유일한 <br>자랑인 사랑 <br>영원으로 이어질 <br>날까지 찬양해 <br>나를 향한 사랑 예수 <br>영원하신 사랑 예수 <br>His love's never shaken <br>His love's never failure <br>나를 향한 사랑 예수 <br>영원하신 사랑 예수 <br>His love's never shaken <br>His love's never failure <br>나를 향한 사랑 예수 <br>영원하신 사랑 예수 <br>His love's never shaken <br>His love's never failure <br>나를 향한 사랑 예수 <br>영원하신 사랑 예수 <br>His love's never shaken <br>His love's never failure <br>나를 향한 사랑 예수 <br>영원하신 사랑 예수 <br>His love's never shaken <br>His love's never failure <br>나를 향한 사랑 예수 <br>영원하신 사랑 예수 <br>His love's never shaken <br>His love's never failure <br>나를 향한 사랑 예수 <br>영원하신 사랑 예수 <br>His love's never shaken <br>His love's never failure <br>]]></content><category term="김수일" label="김수일"/><category term="His Love`s Never Shaken (Feat. 양효승, 채수빈)" label="His Love`s Never Shaken (Feat. 양효승, 채수빈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김수일/주를_위해/</id><title>김수일 - 주를 위해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:42:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:42:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%88%98%EC%9D%BC/%EC%A3%BC%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9C%84%ED%95%B4/" title="김수일 - 주를 위해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[무엇을 위한 <br>삶을 살아가는지 <br>무엇을 위한 <br>길을 걸어가는지 <br>무엇을 위한 <br>꿈을 꾸며 살아가는지 <br>아무것도 알지 못해 <br>울고 있을 때 <br>무엇을 위해 <br>바라봐야하는지 <br>무엇을 위해 <br>사랑해야하는지 <br>무엇을 위해 <br>노력해야하는지 <br>나를 위한 것이 아닌 <br>그 분의 영광 <br>주를 위해 내 삶 <br>드리기 원하네 <br>내 갈 길을 인도하시며 <br>함께 하시네 <br>주의 사랑 <br>항상 간직하며 <br>그의 사랑 세상에 <br>전하기를 원하네 <br>무엇을 위해 <br>바라봐야하는지 <br>무엇을 위해 <br>사랑해야하는지 <br>무엇을 위해 <br>노력해야하는지 <br>나를 위한 것이 아닌 <br>그 분의 영광 <br>주를 위해 내 삶 <br>드리기 원하네 <br>내 갈 길을 인도하시며 <br>함께 하시네 <br>주의 사랑 <br>항상 간직하며 <br>그의 사랑 세상에 <br>전하기를 원하네 <br>주를 위해 내 삶 <br>드리기 원하네 <br>내 갈 길을 인도하시며 <br>함께 하시네 <br>주의 사랑 <br>항상 간직하며 <br>그의 사랑 세상에 <br>전하기를 원하네 <br>무엇을 위해 <br>바라봐야하는지 <br>무엇을 위해 <br>걸어가야하는지 <br>]]></content><category term="김수일" label="김수일"/><category term="주를 위해" label="주를 위해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김수일/Joy_Feat_임아란/</id><title>김수일 - Joy (Feat. 임아란) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:42:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:42:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%88%98%EC%9D%BC/Joy_Feat_%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/" title="김수일 - Joy (Feat. 임아란) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘도 난 <br>난 당신을 만나러 갑니다 <br>당신을 만날 수 <br>있다는 설레임에 <br>내 맘은 너무 기쁘죠 <br>내일도 난 <br>난 당신을 만나러 갑니다 <br>당신이 있기에 <br>난 외롭지 않죠 <br>내 맘은 너무 평안해 <br>당신을 앎이 당신을 앎이 <br>내 삶에 참 큰 기쁨입니다 <br>당신과 함께 당신과 함께 <br>영원히 난 걷고 싶습니다 <br>내일도 난 <br>난 당신을 만나러 갑니다 <br>당신이 있기에 <br>난 외롭지 않죠 <br>내 맘은 너무 평안해 <br>당신을 앎이 당신을 앎이 <br>내 삶에 참 큰 기쁨입니다 <br>당신과 함께 당신과 함께 <br>영원히 난 걷고 싶습니다 <br>함께 있기에 기쁨이 <br>함께 있기에 평안이 <br>함께 있기에 <br>사랑이 넘쳐나네 <br>함께 있기에 기쁨이 <br>함께 있기에 평안이 <br>함께 있기에 <br>사랑이 넘쳐나네 <br>당신을 앎이 당신을 앎이 <br>내 삶에 참 큰 기쁨입니다 <br>당신과 함께 당신과 함께 <br>영원히 난 걷고 싶습니다 <br>함께 있기에 기쁨이 <br>함께 있기에 평안이 <br>함께 있기에 <br>사랑이 넘쳐나네 <br>함께 있기에 기쁨이 <br>함께 있기에 평안이 <br>함께 있기에 <br>사랑이 넘쳐나네 <br>함께 있기에 기쁨이 <br>함께 있기에 평안이 <br>함께 있기에 <br>사랑이 넘쳐나네 <br>함께 있기에 기쁨이 <br>함께 있기에 평안이 <br>함께 있기에 <br>사랑이 넘쳐나네 <br>함께 있기에 <br>사랑이 넘쳐나네 <br>]]></content><category term="김수일" label="김수일"/><category term="Joy (Feat. 임아란)" label="Joy (Feat. 임아란)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김수일/Come_Back_To_Jesus_Feat_김훈희/</id><title>김수일 - Come Back To Jesus (Feat. 김훈희) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:42:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:42:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%88%98%EC%9D%BC/Come_Back_To_Jesus_Feat_%EA%B9%80%ED%9B%88%ED%9D%AC/" title="김수일 - Come Back To Jesus (Feat. 김훈희) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 하루도 <br>이겨내지 못하고 <br>또 다시 넘어져 <br>고통스러운 나 <br>그 고통을 <br>세상의 물질과 <br>정욕으로 <br>이겨보려는 나 <br>만족하지 못해 <br>채우지 못해 <br>매일 하루하루 <br>똑같아지는 나 <br>죄 된 본성으로 <br>그 분으로부터 <br>멀리 떠나버린 나 <br>바벨탑을 쌓은 <br>어리석은 사람처럼 <br>홍해를 건너고도 <br>원망한 이스라엘 백성처럼 <br>자꾸만 높아지고 <br>더 가지고 싶은 <br>간사하고 교만한 내 모습 <br>겸손하지 못해 <br>정결치 못해 <br>매일 하루하루 <br>똑같아지는 나 <br>온갖 거짓과 부정으로 <br>가득해진 내 모습 <br>돌아가자 그 분의 <br>넓은 품으로 <br>돌아가자 나를 <br>기다리시는 그 분께로 <br>모든 걸 그 분께 <br>자백하고 용서를 구하며 <br>기쁨 평안 주시는 <br>그 분께로 <br>돌아온 탕자처럼 <br>돌아가려 삭개오처럼 <br>모든 걸 베풀려보려 <br>혼자의 힘으로 <br>이겨보려는 나 <br>간음한 여인처럼 <br>독주 즐긴 삼손처럼 <br>남들 앞에 잘 보였던 <br>바리새인 같던 나 <br>죄의 값은 받더라도 <br>고통의 지옥의 <br>굴레에서 벗어나 <br>그 분의 품으로 천국으로 <br>돌아가자 그 분의 <br>넓은 품으로 <br>돌아가자 나를 <br>기다리시는 그 분께로 <br>모든 걸 그 분께 <br>자백하고 용서를 구하며 <br>기쁨 평안 주시는 <br>그 분께로 <br>돌아가자 그 분의 <br>넓은 품으로 <br>돌아가자 나를 <br>기다리시는 그 분께로 <br>모든 걸 그 분께 <br>자백하고 용서를 구하며 <br>기쁨 평안 주시는 <br>그 분께로 <br>세상 그 어떤 것으로 <br>채울 수 없는 <br>그 분의 사랑 <br>날마다 느낄 수가 있잖아 <br>돌아가자 그 분의 <br>넓은 품으로 <br>돌아가자 나를 <br>기다리시는 그 분께로 <br>모든 걸 그 분께 <br>자백하고 용서를 구하며 <br>기쁨 평안 주시는 <br>그 분께로 <br>돌아가 돌아가 <br>영원하신 그 분께 <br>돌아가 돌아가 <br>용서하신 그 분께 <br>돌아가 돌아가 <br>기다리시는 그 분께 <br>돌아가 돌아가 <br>어서 돌아가 <br>모든 것을 고백해 <br>모든 것을 자백해 <br>솔직하게 털어놔 <br>용서하고 품어주시는 <br>그 분께 고백해 <br>그 분께로 돌아가 <br>]]></content><category term="김수일" label="김수일"/><category term="Come Back To Jesus (Feat. 김훈희)" label="Come Back To Jesus (Feat. 김훈희)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Betty_Who/Some_Kinda_Wonderful/</id><title>Betty Who - Some Kinda Wonderful - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:42:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:42:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Betty_Who/Some_Kinda_Wonderful/" title="Betty Who - Some Kinda Wonderful - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Clap your hands if it feels good <br>It does indeed, goddamnit <br>Laugh <br><br>I've been thinking we're meant to be <br>But I don't know how to show you the best of me <br>Yeah, I want you, do you want me, too <br>Yeah, I want you, do you want me, too <br>Showing up in your beat up truck <br>And now I'm sure it's more than a stroke of luck <br>Yeah, I love you, do you love me, too <br>Yeah, I love you, do you love me, too <br><br>Clap your hands if it feels good <br>Clap your hands, ohh <br>Clap your hands if it feels good <br>Clap your hands, ooh <br><br>Feeling tonight, some kinda wonderful <br>Feeling inside, some kinda wonderful <br>The rest of my life is some kinda wonderful <br>We will always be some kinda wonderful <br>Some kinda wonderful <br><br>I keep showing up in the nines <br>But you show me you know it's a waste of time <br>'Cause you want me and I want you, too <br>'Cause you want me and I want you, too <br>You've been loving me just for me <br>You don't care what I wear, and I can't believe <br>That you love me and I love you, too <br>Yeah, you love me and I love you, too <br><br>Clap your hands if it feels good <br>Clap your hands, ohh <br>Clap your hands if it feels good <br>Clap your hands, ooh <br><br>Feeling tonight, some kinda wonderful <br>Feeling inside, some kinda wonderful <br>The rest of my life is some kinda wonderful <br>We will always be some kinda wonderful <br>Some kinda wonderful <br>Some kinda wonderful <br><br>I feel you in my body, my soul <br>You're taking me to heaven, I'm whole <br>So go tell everybody we've got a sound <br>That's some kinda wonderful <br>I've been thinking we're meant to be <br>And I love that you love to be loving me <br><br>Feeling tonight, some kinda wonderful I feel you in my body <br>Feeling inside, some kinda wonderful you're taking me to heaven <br>The rest of my life is some kinda wonderful so please tell everybody <br>We will always be some kinda wonderful <br>Some kinda wonderful <br>Some kinda wonderful]]></content><category term="Betty Who" label="Betty Who"/><category term="Some Kinda Wonderful" label="Some Kinda Wonderful"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeremih/I_Think_Of_You_Feat_Chris_Brown__Big_Sean/</id><title>Jeremih - I Think Of You (Feat. Chris Brown &amp; Big Sean) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:43:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:43:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeremih/I_Think_Of_You_Feat_Chris_Brown__Big_Sean/" title="Jeremih - I Think Of You (Feat. Chris Brown &amp; Big Sean) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I give the best <br>that you ever had <br>Give you one dose <br>and got you addicted <br>I could own that <br>all night and all day <br>Say you on my plate girl <br>you so delicious <br>Last night we had <br>a good time gettin' faded <br>Wake up in the morn' <br>you was gone <br>It been on my brain <br>all day replayin' <br>Like we had it on record <br>I miss every minute <br>I take plenty chances <br>My love for you has been <br>a damn dimension <br>More than you imagine <br>I want all of them kisses <br>Mistletoe before Christmas <br>If you ain't got it don't get it <br>If you got time <br>it's no limit <br>Baby won't you <br>give me something <br>That I wanna do <br>When I see the sun set <br>Yeah I think of you <br>I think of you <br>You're all I want too <br>Left panties by my nightstand <br>Now I think of you <br>I think of you <br>Loving my baby <br>can you give to me the sweet talk <br>Love's up and down <br>it's like living on a see saw <br>Give me a favor baby <br>why you blaming me for <br>All I wanted was love babe <br>Last time we had a real good time <br>we was naked <br>Bumping and making love <br>Got me with all <br>these games you're playing <br>It's time for us to go <br>Don't care 'bout winning <br>Come on baby <br>I got the answers <br>You ain't gotta be a dancer <br>All I need is your love <br>Girl you obtain my mind <br>And I can see you hesitating <br>So baby <br>Baby won't you give me something <br>That I wanna do <br>When I see the sun set Oh girl <br>Yeah I think of you Baby <br>I think of you <br>You're all I want too <br>Left panties by my nightstand <br>Now I think of you <br>I think of you <br>I wish everyday was your day off <br>Goin' hard every night <br>like it's the play offs <br>You give me the energy <br>I like to play hard <br>Tell me is the feelin' mutual <br>around my way off <br>Be real be real stay real <br>Pull your heart out baby <br>I won't let it spill <br>I know the ones before me <br>probably said they never will <br>I'm breakin' promises <br>and break you down <br>'bout how you feel <br>Is that an illusion <br>I'm not tryna add <br>to the confusion <br>Break you all access <br>cause an abusion <br>You layin' all over me <br>'cause you wanna stab me <br>Swear I love you so much <br>I love your whole family <br>Bedroom dresser <br>full of your panties <br>We make the room feel <br>like summer Miami <br>No stressin' whenever you leave <br>'Cause ain't nobody <br>in the world fuck <br>you better than me <br>I think of you <br>]]></content><category term="Jeremih" label="Jeremih"/><category term="I Think Of You (Feat. Chris Brown &amp; Big Sean)" label="I Think Of You (Feat. Chris Brown &amp; Big Sean)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yuksek/Sweet_Addiction_Feat_Her/</id><title>Yuksek - Sweet Addiction (Feat. Her) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:44:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:44:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Yuksek/Sweet_Addiction_Feat_Her/" title="Yuksek - Sweet Addiction (Feat. Her) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't wanna be high then no more <br>I don't wanna be running no more <br>Just wanna be cruising <br><br>Oh, by the shore <br>Just wanna be holding hands <br>And more <br>And I just wanna be free to ignore <br>The hate you keep in store <br><br>Sweet addiction to you <br>Repetion feels new <br><br>You're upside down <br>Gotta throw the hatred <br>Yeah, yeah... <br>Have faith in your healing right <br>Showing you all out of sight <br>Cause I'm upside down <br><br>Sweet addiction to you <br>Repetion feels new <br><br>I don't wanna be running no more <br>I just wanna be cruisin' <br>Oh, by the shore <br>And I just wanna be free to ignore <br>The hate you keep in store. <br><br>Sweet addiction to you <br>Repetion feels new <br><br>You're upside down <br>We gotta be together <br>I want you now <br>Have faith in your healing right <br>Showing you all out of sight <br>Cause I'm upside down]]></content><category term="Yuksek" label="Yuksek"/><category term="Sweet Addiction (Feat. Her)" label="Sweet Addiction (Feat. Her)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박봄슬/사랑해_Wedding_Song/</id><title>박봄슬 - 사랑해 (Wedding Song) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:44:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:44:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EB%B4%84%EC%8A%AC/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4_Wedding_Song/" title="박봄슬 - 사랑해 (Wedding Song) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[많은 사람들 속에 서서 <br>얼굴이 발그레진 니 모습 <br>이제 내 사람이라는 게 <br>아직도 믿겨지지가 않아 <br>사랑한다는 말론 부족해 <br>천번해도 부족해 <br>나 이제 니 사람이 될게 <br>I want you 널 원해 <br>아침부터 아침까지 <br>I need you 필요해 <br>머리부터 발끝까지 <br>I love you 사랑해 <br>이세상 끝나도 <br>All my love to you <br>I love you with all my heart <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>너만을 사랑해 <br>i love you <br>많은 날들이 지나서도 <br>그 어떤 어려움이 있어도 <br>항상 곁에서서 있을게 <br>평생을 너 하나만 사랑해 <br>사랑한다는 말론 부족해 <br>만번해도 부족해 <br>너 이제 내 사람이 되줘 <br>i want you 널 원해 <br>꿈에서도 너를 원해 <br>i need you 필요해 <br>우주로 날아갈 만큼 <br>i love you 사랑해 <br>이세상 끝나도 <br>all my love to you <br>i love you with all my heart <br>dear my love 들어봐 <br>yes baby 말해봐 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑하고 또 사랑해 <br>고마워 고마워 <br>너의 모든것이 고마워 <br>one way one way <br>언제나 one way one way <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>너만을 사랑해 <br>i love you <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>너만을 사랑해 <br>i love you <br>]]></content><category term="박봄슬" label="박봄슬"/><category term="사랑해 (Wedding Song)" label="사랑해 (Wedding Song)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ansel_Elgort/Thief/</id><title>Ansel Elgort - Thief - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:44:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:44:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ansel_Elgort/Thief/" title="Ansel Elgort - Thief - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Call me a thief <br>There's been a robbery <br>I left with her heart <br>Tore it apart <br>Made no apologies <br>I've been living in the darkness <br>Shadows in my apartment heartless <br>Taking love just to spill it <br>on parchment <br>Next page and I'm out again <br>I've been living in the night life <br>Lips hit you like a drive by <br>frost bite <br>Ice cold I mean they cut you <br>like a sharp knife <br>Next page and I'm out again <br>Skin on my skin <br>what a wonderful sin <br>Take your breath <br>but you're asking for more <br>The tip of my finger is tracing <br>your figure <br>I say good night <br>and walk out the door <br>Call me a thief <br>There's been a robbery <br>I left with her heart <br>Tore it apart <br>Made no apologies <br>Just call me a thief <br>She was on top of me <br>Then I left with her heart <br>Broken and scarred <br>Made no apologies <br>We can be so hollow <br>Like my rib cage <br>the echoes follow <br>Follow me like the fears I swallow <br>And drown in all my mistakes <br>All I know is that your skin bled <br>Like the ink dripped from my pen <br>My bed will be drenched <br>in a scarlet rose red <br>And drown in all my mistakes <br>Skin on my skin <br>what a wonderful sin <br>Take your breath <br>but you're asking for more <br>The tip of my finger is tracing <br>your figure <br>I say good night <br>and walk out the door <br>Call me a thief <br>There's been a robbery <br>I left with her heart <br>Tore it apart <br>Made no apologies <br>Just call me a thief <br>She was on top of me <br>Then I left with her heart <br>Broken and scarred <br>Made no apologies <br>Girl you better just lock me up <br>Because I've never <br>been good enough <br>So you better just lock me up <br>lock me up <br>Girl you better just lock me up <br>Because I've never <br>been good enough <br>So you better just lock me up <br>lock me up <br>The tip of my finger <br>is tracing your figure <br>I say good night <br>and walk out the door <br>Call me a thief <br>There's been a robbery <br>I left with her heart <br>Tore it apart <br>Made no apologies <br>Just call me a thief <br>She was on top of me <br>Then I left with her heart <br>Broken and scarred <br>Made no apologies <br>Girl you better just lock me up <br>Because I've never <br>been good enough <br>So you better just lock me up <br>lock me up <br>Girl you better just lock me up <br>Because I've never <br>been good enough <br>So you better just lock me up <br>lock me up <br>]]></content><category term="Ansel Elgort" label="Ansel Elgort"/><category term="Thief" label="Thief"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나희경/끝_그_이후_Sorrow/</id><title>나희경 - 끝, 그 이후 (Sorrow) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:44:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:44:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%ED%9D%AC%EA%B2%BD/%EB%81%9D_%EA%B7%B8_%EC%9D%B4%ED%9B%84_Sorrow/" title="나희경 - 끝, 그 이후 (Sorrow) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어찌할 줄 모르겠는 <br>날들이 흘러간다 <br>돌이키기엔 너무 늦고 <br>잊기에는 강렬해 <br>새벽을 넘고 아침을 건너 <br>날이 가면 꽃이 떨어진다 <br>마른 꽃잎을 주워 모으면 <br>바스락대며 사라질까 <br>이불을 덮고 시간을 삼켜 <br>하얀 공백을 찾아 나선다 <br>눈을 아무리 감아보아도 <br>채워진 검정색뿐이지만 <br>어찌할 줄 모르겠던 <br>날들이 지나간다 <br>조금은 담담해졌고 <br>다시 난 살고 있어 <br>새벽을 넘고 아침을 건너 <br>날이 가면 꽃이 떨어진다 <br>이젠 향기도 나지 않지만 <br>앙상한 가지는 여전해 <br>방문을 열고 빛을 맞으며 <br>기억을 덮고 또 덮는다 <br>검게만 보이던 이 세계에 <br>푸른 빛이라도 스미도록 <br>]]></content><category term="나희경" label="나희경"/><category term="끝, 그 이후 (Sorrow)" label="끝, 그 이후 (Sorrow)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sia/Living_Out_Loud/</id><title>Sia - Living Out Loud - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:44:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:44:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sia/Living_Out_Loud/" title="Sia - Living Out Loud - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty five ounces <br>in a bottle of wine <br>Twenty four hours <br>it's a day at a time <br>Twenty three lived <br>a hell of a life <br>Twenty two such a blur <br>it's passing me by <br>Twenty one I caught <br>a glimpse of the light <br>Twenty drinks later <br>in the back of a ride <br>Nineteen momma <br>kicked me outta the house <br>Eighteen minutes <br>'till you bail me out <br>Seventeen magazine <br>was telling the truth <br>When they said <br>we all have issues <br>Just thinking out loud <br>Screaming so loud <br>Foolish and proud <br>Living out loud <br>Living out loud <br>Out loud <br>No nothing can stop me now <br>Gonna live out loud <br>And no one can break me down <br>Gonna live out loud <br>I'm screaming my demons out <br>Gonna live out loud <br>'Cause living out loud <br>is the only way I know how <br>'Cause living out loud <br>is the only way I know how <br>Living out loud <br>is the only way I know how <br>Sixteen candles yeah <br>I'm faking my age <br>Fifteen minutes <br>till they need me on stage <br>Fourteen K I would <br>have done it for free <br>Thirteen roses <br>and they bought them for me <br>Twelve step program <br>but I don't like to walk <br>Eleven wet kisses <br>just to get me to talk <br>Ten fingers <br>when you're holding my hand <br>Nine Eight Seven she lives <br>Just thinking out loud <br>Screaming so loud <br>Foolish and proud <br>Living out loud <br>Living out loud <br>Out loud <br>No nothing can stop me now <br>Gonna live out out loud <br>And no one can break me down <br>Gonna live out loud <br>I'm screaming my demons out <br>Gonna live out loud <br>'Cause living out loud <br>is the only way I know how <br>'Cause living out loud <br>is the only way I know how <br>I gotta live out loud out loud <br>Yeah living out loud <br>is the only way I know how <br>Cause living out loud <br>is the only way I know how <br>No nothing can stop me now <br>Gonna live out out loud <br>And no one can break me down <br>Gonna live out loud <br>I'm screaming my demons out <br>Gonna live out loud <br>'Cause living out loud <br>is the only way I know how <br>'Cause living out loud <br>is the only way I know how <br>Living out loud is <br>the only way I know how <br>]]></content><category term="Sia" label="Sia"/><category term="Living Out Loud" label="Living Out Loud"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박지연/특별한_여자/</id><title>박지연 - 특별한 여자 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:45:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:45:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A7%80%EC%97%B0/%ED%8A%B9%EB%B3%84%ED%95%9C_%EC%97%AC%EC%9E%90/" title="박지연 - 특별한 여자 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 나나나 우우우 <br>나 나나나 우우우 <br>난 특별한 여자가 되고 싶어요 <br>나 나나나 우우우 <br>나 나나나 우우우 <br>난 당신의 특별한 여자 <br>난 특별한 여자가 되고 싶어요 <br>당신 가슴에 영원히 새겨질 이름 <br>순간순간 생각나서 <br>부르고 그리는 <br>그 사람이 나였으면 해요 <br>특별한 사랑을 드리겠어요 <br>특별한 마음을 드리겠어요 <br>특별한 스페셜한 멋진 그 여자 <br>당신이 아껴주는 소중한 여자 <br>난 특별한 여자가 되고 싶어요 <br>당신 가슴에 새겨질 그 이름 <br>나 나나나 우우우 <br>나 나나나 우우우 <br>난 특별한 여자가 되고 싶어요 <br>나 나나나 우우우 <br>나 나나나 우우우 <br>난 당신의 특별한 여자 <br>난 특별한 여자가 되고 싶어요 <br>당신 가슴에 영원히 새겨질 이름 <br>순간순간 생각나서 <br>부르고 그리는 <br>그 사람이 나였으면 해요 <br>특별한 사랑을 드리겠어요 <br>특별한 마음을 드리겠어요 <br>특별한 스페셜한 멋진 그 여자 <br>당신이 아껴주는 소중한 여자 <br>난 특별한 여자가 되고 싶어요 <br>당신 가슴에 새겨질 그 이름 <br>당신 가슴에 새겨질 그 이름 <br>특별한 여자 <br>]]></content><category term="박지연" label="박지연"/><category term="특별한 여자" label="특별한 여자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/틱헤이_Tickhey/한_시절의_끝/</id><title>틱헤이 (Tickhey) - 한 시절의 끝 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:46:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:46:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8B%B1%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4_Tickhey/%ED%95%9C_%EC%8B%9C%EC%A0%88%EC%9D%98_%EB%81%9D/" title="틱헤이 (Tickhey) - 한 시절의 끝 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사람의 마음은 <br>머물지 못할까 <br>그토록 좋은 그대도 <br>결국 변해버리고 <br>그대의 마음을 <br>난 알 수가 없었네 <br>들여다 보면 볼수록 <br>멀어져만 갔네 <br>한 시절이 끝나 가네 <br>눈을 감았을 때 <br>성난 파도 밀려와 <br>우리의 모든 추억들이 <br>다 휩쓸려버려도 <br>나는 그대로 남아 <br>아무것도 모르는 <br>어린애처럼 <br>다시 사랑하고 싶어 <br>지난 날은 그저 <br>지나간 대로 <br>모든 만남에 끝이 <br>있음을 받아드리면 <br>지금 이 순간들이 <br>얼마나 큰 행운인지 <br>언젠가 알게 될까 <br>한 시절이 끝나 가네 <br>눈을 감았을 때 <br>성난 파도 밀려와 <br>우리의 모든 추억들이 <br>다 휩쓸려버려도 <br>나는 그대로 남아 <br>아무것도 모르는 <br>어린애처럼 <br>다시 사랑하고 싶어 <br>지난 날은 그저 <br>지나간 대로 <br>모든 만남에 끝이 <br>있음을 받아드리면 <br>지금 이 순간들이 <br>얼마나 큰 행운인지 <br>언젠가 알게 될까 <br>]]></content><category term="틱헤이 (Tickhey)" label="틱헤이 (Tickhey)"/><category term="한 시절의 끝" label="한 시절의 끝"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하엘비/잠/</id><title>하엘비 - 잠; - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:46:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:46:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%97%98%EB%B9%84/%EC%9E%A0/" title="하엘비 - 잠; - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 어떡하죠 주님 <br>난 어떡해요 <br>이 불쌍한 영혼 좀 <br>구원해주세요 <br>어떡하죠 주님 <br>난 어떡해요 <br>안 그럴려 했는데 <br>오늘도 잠들어 버렸어 <br>yeah <br>아침에 일어났는데 <br>오늘도 늦었어 <br>오전 열한시 <br>안 그럴려 주님께 <br>매일 고백했는데 <br>행동으로 안 따라지는 <br>내 몸뚱아리 <br>왜 그럴까 <br>왜 그럴까 <br>하고 생각을 해도 <br>답이 안 나오는게 <br>아닌데 <br>왜 그럴까 <br>왜 그럴까 <br>내 꿈이 사라져가네 <br>잠 때문에 <br>내 인생 망가져가네 <br>나 어떡하죠 주님 <br>난 어떡해요 <br>이 불쌍한 영혼 좀 <br>구원해주세요 <br>어떡하죠 주님 <br>난 어떡해요 <br>안 그럴려 했는데 <br>오늘도 잠들어 버렸어 <br>yeah <br>ha <br>이건 너무 얼척이 없어 <br>잠 때문에 <br>이런 모습보이는 것도 <br>내 자신이 <br>너무 넌더리가나 <br>자괴감에 <br>매일매일 시달리지 <br>날 보고 <br>사람들은 성인군자 <br>인사잘해 공손하데 <br>성격좋아 모범생 <br>이런 조건들로 <br>나를 평가해 <br>shut up 생까지마 <br>보이는게 다가 아냐 <br>이제 알아 이제 알아 <br>나의 약한 의지가 <br>날 그렇게 만들었단 걸 <br>이제 알아 이제 알아 <br>또 다시 마음잡았지 <br>잠 때문에 <br>내 인생 망칠 수 없어 <br>나 어떡하죠 주님 <br>난 어떡해요 <br>이 불쌍한 영혼 <br>좀 구원해주세요 <br>어떡하죠 주님 <br>난 어떡해요 <br>안그럴려 했는데 <br>오늘도 잠들어 버렸어 <br>지금까지의 <br>나는 모두 잊어 <br>주님의 은혜로 <br>다시 새롭게 <br>할렐루야 Lord <br>what can I do <br>할렐루야 Lord <br>what can I do <br>Please help <br>this poor soul <br>now I will not <br>oversleep <br>할렐루야 Lord <br>what can I do <br>surely I did not want <br>but to sleep in <br>my bed tonight <br>할렐루야 주님 <br>날 도우시네 <br>이 불쌍한 영혼을 <br>구원해 주셨네 <br>할렐루야 주님 <br>나 찬양하리 <br>나약한 어린양을 <br>구원한 주님을 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="하엘비" label="하엘비"/><category term="잠;" label="잠;"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/고리울초_락밴드반/사춘기/</id><title>고리울초 락밴드반 - 사춘기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:46:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:46:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%A0%EB%A6%AC%EC%9A%B8%EC%B4%88_%EB%9D%BD%EB%B0%B4%EB%93%9C%EB%B0%98/%EC%82%AC%EC%B6%98%EA%B8%B0/" title="고리울초 락밴드반 - 사춘기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[괜히 화가 나 요즘 <br>내 맘이 이상해 <br>반항하고 싶어 <br>시험지엔 비가 와 <br>엄마는 내 맘 몰라 <br>친구와 다투고 <br>마음이 복잡해 <br>누가 내 얘기 좀 들어줘 <br>말하지 못하는 <br>내 맘 좀 알아줘 <br>난 숨이 막힐 것 같아 <br>자꾸 변해만 가네 <br>몸과 마음이 달라 <br>풋사과 같은 내 입술은 <br>붉어져 가네 <br>진짜 짜증나 <br>아무도 믿어주지 않는 <br>이 시기가 난 너무 싫어 <br>누구도 날 이해해주지 않는 <br>이 시간이 넘 미워 <br>다시 시간을 되돌리고 싶어 <br>아무것도 몰랐던 <br>그 시간으로 돌려줘 <br>자꾸 변해만 가네 <br>몸과 마음이 달라 <br>풋사과 같은 내 입술은 <br>붉어져 가네 <br>누가 내 말 좀 들어줘 <br>아무도 믿어주지 않는 <br>이 시기가 난 너무 싫어 <br>누구도 날 이해해주지 않는 <br>이 시간이 넘 미워 <br>다시 시간을 되돌리고 싶어 <br>아무것도 몰랐던 <br>그 시간으로 돌려줘 <br>아무도 믿어주지 않는 <br>이 시기가 난 너무 싫어 <br>누구도 날 이해해주지 않는 <br>이 시간이 넘 미워 <br>다시 시간을 되돌리고 싶어 <br>아무것도 몰랐던 <br>그 시간으로 돌려줘 <br>괜히 화가 나 요즘 <br>내 맘이 이상해 <br>]]></content><category term="고리울초 락밴드반" label="고리울초 락밴드반"/><category term="사춘기" label="사춘기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lunatic/꿈에_Feat_용엽/</id><title>Lunatic - 꿈에 (Feat. 용엽) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:47:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:47:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lunatic/%EA%BF%88%EC%97%90_Feat_%EC%9A%A9%EC%97%BD/" title="Lunatic - 꿈에 (Feat. 용엽) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여전히 꿈에 나와 <br>이렇게 꿈에 나마 <br>또 한번의 일년이 지나가고 <br>내게는 좀 더 쌓인 <br>너에 대한 기억들 <br>더 이상 함께 할 수 <br>없다는 걸 알면서도 <br>꿈에서는 널 볼 수 <br>있다는 생각에 <br>계속 잠에 드나 봐 <br>오늘도 길고 긴 <br>밤을 보냈지 난 <br>너무도 길고 긴 <br>잠을 청했지 난 <br>행복한 장면이 <br>펼쳐지길 기대하지만 <br>꿈속에 조차 내 맘대로 안되 <br>가슴 아픈 악몽 에서 난 <br>계속 너를 찾아 헤메이고 <br>흐릿하게 널 가린 <br>안개 사이로 <br>조금 더 선명히 <br>너를 볼 수 있도록 <br>달려가 너의 어깨를 <br>감싸 안으면서 <br>난 또 꿈에서 깨 <br>이렇게 꿈에서라도 <br>널 보는 게 위로가 된다는 게 <br>마음 아프게 너무 아련해 <br>날 또 잠 못 들게 해 <br>여전히 꿈에 나와 <br>i will never forget you <br>i will never forget you <br>이렇게 꿈에 나마 <br>i will never forget you <br>i will never forget you <br>너의 손을 잡고 <br>함께 걷던 거리가 <br>내 팔짱 끼고 돌아다니던 <br>지하상가 <br>내 품에 안겨있어 따뜻하게 <br>더러워진 내 입을 치유해주던 <br>네 입술의 온기가 <br>가시를 다 발라 건네준 <br>생선을 먹는 모습이 <br>곤히 잠들어 살짝 <br>벌어지던 네 입술이 <br>틱틱 거리다 가도 한번씩 <br>보여주는 웃음이 <br>그리워져 또 혹시나 <br>하는 맘에 잠에 드는 난 <br>계속 너를 찾아 헤메이고 <br>흐릿하게 널 가린 안개 사이로 <br>조금 더 선명히 널 볼 수 있도록 <br>달려가 너의 어깨를 <br>감싸 안으면서 난 또 꿈에서 깨 <br>이렇게 꿈에서라도 <br>널 보는 게 위로가 된다는 게 <br>마음 아프게 너무 아련해 <br>날 또 잠 못 들게 해 <br>여전히 꿈에 나와 <br>i will never forget you <br>i will never forget you <br>이렇게 꿈에 나마 <br>i will never forget you <br>i will never forget you <br>지나간 기억들 속에서도 <br>널 마주보지 못하고 <br>무겁게 내려진 어둠 안에 난 <br>계속 너를 찾아 헤메이고 <br>흐릿하게 널 가린 안개 사이로 <br>달려갈 테니 조금만 기다려 <br>이 꿈에서만 이라도 잠시 널 <br>품에 안고 있을 수 있게 <br>이렇게 꿈에서라도 <br>널 보는 게 위로가 된다는 게 <br>마음 아프게 너무 아련해 <br>날 또 잠 못 들게 해 <br>여전히 꿈에 나와 <br>i will never forget you <br>i will never forget you <br>이렇게 꿈에 나마 <br>i will never forget you <br>i will never forget you <br>]]></content><category term="Lunatic" label="Lunatic"/><category term="꿈에 (Feat. 용엽)" label="꿈에 (Feat. 용엽)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Digital_Farm_Animals/Digital_Love_Feat_Hailee_Steinfeld/</id><title>Digital Farm Animals - Digital Love (Feat. Hailee Steinfeld) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:48:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:48:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Digital_Farm_Animals/Digital_Love_Feat_Hailee_Steinfeld/" title="Digital Farm Animals - Digital Love (Feat. Hailee Steinfeld) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey we got a good thing <br>Wish I had you right here with me <br>All day that I'm thinking <br>That it ain't gotta be that way <br>All that I'm seeing <br>Is your face on a phone screen <br>With a call and a message <br>Maybe we gon' be ok <br>Oh you gotta notice <br>I hear explosions <br>Whenever I see your face on my pillow <br>I swipe right <br>cause I see just what I like <br>Baby I tap twice for you <br>I swipe right <br>cause I see just what I like <br>Baby I tap twice for you <br>Cause we're living in a new age <br>It's called digital <br>It's called digital love love <br>It's called digital <br>it's called digital <br>It's called digital <br>it's called digital <br>It's late and I been drinking <br>So tired from working on the weekend <br>All day you had me wishing <br>That you would just show up my way <br>Gotta room and no it ain't much <br>But it's warm undercover <br>when it's just us <br>We could turn our phones off <br>Lie in bed and let the radio play <br>Oh you gotta notice <br>I hear explosions <br>Whenever I see your face on my pillow <br>I swipe right <br>cause I see just what I like <br>Baby I tap twice for you <br>I swipe right <br>cause I see just what I like <br>Baby I tap twice for you <br>Cause we're living in a new age <br>It's called digital <br>It's called digital love love <br>Cause we're living in a new age <br>It's called digital <br>It's called digital love love <br>It's called digital <br>it's called digital <br>It's called digital <br>Oh you gotta notice <br>I hear explosions <br>Whenever I see your face on my pillow <br>]]></content><category term="Digital Farm Animals" label="Digital Farm Animals"/><category term="Digital Love (Feat. Hailee Steinfeld)" label="Digital Love (Feat. Hailee Steinfeld)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lecrae/Blessings_Feat_Ty_Dolla_ign/</id><title>Lecrae - Blessings (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:48:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:48:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lecrae/Blessings_Feat_Ty_Dolla_ign/" title="Lecrae - Blessings (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If I ever took a loss, I learned a lesson <br>I won't ever think I'm better than the next man <br>I've been down before the come up, I ain't stressin' <br>Baby I'm too busy countin' all these blessings <br><br>Yah, yah, yah <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Line 'em up, line 'em up, line 'em up <br>Swear the sun shinin' on me in my huddle <br>No matter the trouble surroundin' us <br>They don't see that it's a lot of us <br>Everybody move anonymous <br>Won't take that credit, I know where we get it <br>Them blessings be comin' from God above <br>I was doin' all kinda bad <br>Where the choir at Tell 'em I need a verse <br>Hit the pew and tell God He's first <br>Hit the studio to body a verse <br>I remember pushin' mama's little white Hyundai with no gas money <br>I just bought a car, cash money <br>I ain't even tryna brag on it <br>I just tell it how it really is <br>I ain't trippin', they ain't feelin' this <br>I ain't sayin' I deserve nothin' <br>I'm just tryna talk about the benefits <br>I've been punchin' in the clock <br>Tryna keep the kitchen stocked <br>Man it's a blessin' 'cause we ain't ever had a lot <br>But all we need is all we got <br><br>If I ever took a loss, I learned a lesson <br>I won't ever think I'm better than the next man <br>I've been down before the come up, I ain't stressin' <br>Baby I'm too busy countin' all these blessings, blessings <br><br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Blessings <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Blessings <br><br>I put my mama in the crib, said, Stop stressin' <br>I put my girl in a brand new diamond necklace <br>She said she need more of my love and affection <br>'Cause lately I've been workin' harder than ever <br>She said, Baby, you a boss, baby, clear your schedule <br>Dolla you a boss, let's do somethin' special <br>Take me on a PJ, we should go to Mexico <br>I've been down for you, boy since when the money was low <br>Anything for my bae 'cause she a blessing <br>If you woke up this morning it's a blessing <br><br>If I ever took a loss, I learned a lesson <br>I won't ever think I'm better than the next man <br>I've been down before the come up, I ain't stressin' <br>Baby I'm too busy countin' all these blessings, blessings <br><br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Blessings <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Blessings <br><br>I took so many losses <br>Coulda lost it <br>Left 'em leakin' like a faucet <br>Almost cost me <br>Everything that I got, all of my fam <br>Part of the plan <br>I was eatin' fried bologna out of the pan <br>Y'all don't understand <br>I was tryna get it <br>I'm in that studio tryna keep it pushin' <br>Patty pies, boy I kept 'em cookin' <br>All I needed was the Mary Mary <br>But the God in me was havin' commentary, woo <br>I got angels all around like Anita Baker <br>Blessings fallin' in line, guess I need a taper <br>And every loss is a lesson <br>Tell my haters I confess <br>Treat 'em like the green bubbles on the iPhone <br>I probably never read the message <br><br>If I ever took a loss, I learned a lesson <br>I won't ever think I'm better than the next man <br>I've been down before the come up, I ain't stressin' <br>Baby I'm too busy countin' all these blessings, blessings <br><br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Blessings <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Count it up, count it up, count it up <br>Blessings]]></content><category term="Lecrae" label="Lecrae"/><category term="Blessings (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign)" label="Blessings (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비볼드_Be_Bold/Just/</id><title>비볼드 (Be Bold) - Just - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:48:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:48:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%EB%B3%BC%EB%93%9C_Be_Bold/Just/" title="비볼드 (Be Bold) - Just - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대만 보면 내 맘이 <br>왠지 모르게 <br>떨리는 맘을 좀처럼 <br>감출 수 없죠 <br>혹시 네게 다른 남자가 <br>있으면 어쩌나 걱정하고 있는 나 <br>눈 딱 감고 말해볼까 <br>널 좋아한다고 말야 <br>I’m gonna give you all my heart <br>내 모든걸 다 줄 거예요 <br>just say you love me now <br>날 사랑한다고 말해줘 <br>어서 내 맘 속에 들어와 <br>그대로 나를 채워줘요 <br>I can make you smile <br>언제나 그대에게 <br>행복만 줄 거에요 <br>그대 입술을 보면 나 <br>왠지 모르게 <br>입 맞추고 싶은 맘을 <br>꾹 참고 있어요 <br>혹시 네게 다른 남자가 <br>있으면 어쩌나 걱정하고 있는 나 <br>눈 딱 감고 말해볼까 <br>널 사랑한다고 말야 <br>I’m gonna give you all my heart <br>내 모든걸 다 줄 거예요 <br>just say you love me now <br>날 사랑한다고 말해줘 <br>어서 내 맘 속에 들어와 <br>그대로 나를 채워줘요 <br>I can make you smile <br>언제나 그대에게 <br>행복만 줄 거에요 <br>그대와 나 이렇게 손잡아요 <br>달콤하게 우리 둘 춤을 춰요 <br>그대와 나 이렇게 손잡아요 <br>달콤하게 우리 둘 <br>I’m gonna give you all my heart <br>내 모든걸 다 줄 거예요 <br>just say you love me now <br>날 사랑한다고 말해줘 <br>어서 내 맘 속에 들어와 <br>그대로 나를 채워줘요 <br>I can make you smile <br>언제나 그대에게 <br>행복만 줄 거에요 <br>]]></content><category term="비볼드 (Be Bold)" label="비볼드 (Be Bold)"/><category term="Just" label="Just"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비볼드_Be_Bold/I_Should_Be/</id><title>비볼드 (Be Bold) - I Should Be - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:48:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:48:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%EB%B3%BC%EB%93%9C_Be_Bold/I_Should_Be/" title="비볼드 (Be Bold) - I Should Be - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 처음 느낀 <br>느낌적인 느낌 <br>매일 마주치던 <br>널 보는 떨림 <br>대충 입은 옷에 <br>화장도 안한 네 얼굴이 <br>날이 갈수록 더 많아져 <br>너를 보는 시간들이 <br>어떻게 내 맘 흔들어 <br>놓을까 매일 밤 <br>고민하는 듯 해 <br>when i should be with you <br>오늘밤만은 집에 <br>가지 말아줘 <br>take all my heart <br>내 맘 이미 <br>니가 가져갔잖아 <br>when i should be with you <br>Oh 내 귓가에 <br>사랑을 속삭여요 <br>부드러운 너의 입술 <br>조심스레 다가가 <br>어색하게 변해가는 <br>너의 말투 <br>자연스레 너와 치던 장난이 <br>왠지 오늘은 조금 <br>어렵게 다가가게돼 <br>밤이 깊어지면 질수록 <br>짙어지는 내 마음이 <br>언제쯤 내게 가까이 <br>다가와 말할까 <br>기대하고있어 <br>when i should be with you <br>오늘밤만은 집에 <br>가지 말아줘 <br>take all my heart <br>내맘 이미 <br>니가 가져갔잖아 <br>when i should be with you <br>Oh 내 귓가에 <br>사랑을 속삭여요 <br>부드러운 너의 입술 <br>조심스레 다가가 <br>내 방안에 <br>온통 네 향기가 <br>널 내 품안에 <br>안고 깨고싶어 <br>조금만 더 너를 <br>가까이 보고싶어 <br>익숙한 니 모습 <br>여전히 아름다워 <br>when i should be with you <br>오늘밤만은 집에 <br>가지 말아줘 <br>take all my heart <br>내 맘 이미 <br>니가 가져갔잖아 <br>when i should be with you <br>Oh 내 귓가에 <br>사랑을 속삭여요 <br>부드러운 너의 입술 <br>조심스레 다가가 <br>when i should be with you <br>오늘밤만은 집에 <br>가지 말아줘 <br>take all my heart <br>내 맘 이미 <br>니가 가져갔잖아 <br>when i should be with you <br>Oh 내 귓가에 <br>사랑을 속삭여요 <br>부드러운 너의 입술 <br>조심스레 다가가 <br>]]></content><category term="비볼드 (Be Bold)" label="비볼드 (Be Bold)"/><category term="I Should Be" label="I Should Be"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비볼드_Be_Bold/Dont_Come_Too_Close/</id><title>비볼드 (Be Bold) - Don`t Come Too Close - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:48:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:48:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%EB%B3%BC%EB%93%9C_Be_Bold/Dont_Come_Too_Close/" title="비볼드 (Be Bold) - Don`t Come Too Close - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대는 나에게 <br>진한 향수보다 <br>더 나를 빠져들게 하네요 <br>Oh don’t come too close <br>너무 가까이 오진마 <br>떨리는 마음에 <br>숨을 쉴 수 없어요 <br>Wanna be love <br>네게 다가가 <br>Wanna be yours <br>넌 그 자리에서 <br>날 기다려 <br>you stay there for me babe <br>좁은 카페에 <br>익숙한 분위기 <br>오 그대도 나를 <br>바라보고 있나요 <br>i can’t stop loving you <br>난 멈출 수 없죠 <br>자꾸만 내 눈이 <br>그대에게 가네요 <br>좀처럼 그대 맘을 <br>알 수 없어요 <br>향기로운 그대 눈빛에 <br>빠져들어 내게로 <br>fall in love with you <br>for the first time in my life <br>falling in love with you <br>Wanna be love <br>네게 다가가 <br>Wanna be yours <br>넌 그 자리에서 <br>날 기다려 <br>You stay there for me babe <br>You stay there for me babe <br>]]></content><category term="비볼드 (Be Bold)" label="비볼드 (Be Bold)"/><category term="Don`t Come Too Close" label="Don`t Come Too Close"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비볼드_Be_Bold/Hold_On_With_Soul_Summit/</id><title>비볼드 (Be Bold) - Hold On (With Soul Summit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:48:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:48:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%EB%B3%BC%EB%93%9C_Be_Bold/Hold_On_With_Soul_Summit/" title="비볼드 (Be Bold) - Hold On (With Soul Summit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[몰래 지켜봤어 <br>니 화장하기 전 <br>잡티 하나 없는 니 얼굴을 <br>춤출 때 흔들리는 머릿결 <br>그 진한 향기가 <br>내 맘을 당겨 <br>나를 끌어당겨서 <br>every time i found you <br>난 너를 찾아 헤맸어 <br>눈부신 매력에 <br>눈이 멀어 버린걸 <br>기다리고 있어 baby <br>지나치게 들뜬 이 분위기 <br>적막하게 앉은 이 공기가 <br>맘에 들지 않아 널 데리고 <br>Hold on <br>붉어진 니 얼굴 <br>취기 어린 눈 <br>오늘 밤 너를 <br>내 품에 안고 싶어 <br>every time i need you <br>난 너만 갖고 싶은걸 <br>눈부신 매력에 <br>눈이 멀어 버린걸 <br>기다리고 있어 baby <br>지나치게 들뜬 이 분위기 <br>적막하게 앉은 이 공기가 <br>맘에 들지 않아 널 데리고 <br>Hold on <br>A-yo hold on yeah <br>난 너만 보고 있는데 <br>너와 눈이 마주치진 않을까 <br>괜히 기대하고 있잖아 <br>자꾸 헷갈리게 할거야 <br>애매하게 굴 거야 너 <br>머리부터 발끝까지 <br>너의 섹시한 그 눈빛까지 <br>my girl <br>you are my miss right <br>Lady <br>기다리고 있어 baby <br>지나치게 들뜬 이 분위기 <br>적막하게 앉은 이 공기가 <br>맘에 들지 않아 널 데리고 <br>Hold on <br>]]></content><category term="비볼드 (Be Bold)" label="비볼드 (Be Bold)"/><category term="Hold On (With Soul Summit)" label="Hold On (With Soul Summit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비볼드_Be_Bold/Memory/</id><title>비볼드 (Be Bold) - Memory - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:49:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:49:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%EB%B3%BC%EB%93%9C_Be_Bold/Memory/" title="비볼드 (Be Bold) - Memory - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보이지 않아 <br>닿을 듯 가까웠던 <br>너의 그 따뜻한 미소 <br>난 아직도 널 <br>꿈에 그리며 기다려 <br>이렇게 너와의 기억에 잠겨 <br>아무렇지 않은 듯 <br>널 지운 척 해봐도 <br>자꾸 생각나고 떠올라서 <br>잊을 수 없어 <br>떠나는 너의 뒷모습에 <br>한참을 그 자리에 <br>익숙했던 우리 추억 속에 <br>다른 누군가를 만나도 <br>나를 기억해줄래 <br>행복했던 우리 지난날을 <br>눈을 감으면 <br>내 앞에 네가 있어 <br>우리의 긴 시간들 속에 서서 <br>언제부턴가 내게 <br>익숙한 너인데 <br>자꾸 떠오르고 아른거려서 <br>지울 수 없어 <br>떠나는 너의 뒷모습에 <br>한참을 그 자리에 <br>익숙했던 우리 추억 속에 <br>다른 누군가를 만나도 <br>나를 기억해줄래 <br>행복했던 우리 지난날을 <br>I can see you in my eyes <br>기억 속에 <br>I can see you in my mind <br>떠나는 너 baby <br>I can see you in my eyes <br>miss you love you <br>I can see you in my mind <br>멀어져 가는 너를 보며 <br>아무 말도 못 하고 <br>뒤돌아서며 널 보냈을 때 <br>이젠 네게 닿을 수 없는 <br>나를 기억해줄래 <br>행복했던 우리 지난날을 <br>떠나는 너 모습 <br>한참을 그 자리에 <br>다른 누군가를 만나도 <br>나를 기억해줄래 <br>행복했던 지난 기억의 우리 <br>]]></content><category term="비볼드 (Be Bold)" label="비볼드 (Be Bold)"/><category term="Memory" label="Memory"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soen/Jinn/</id><title>Soen - Jinn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:49:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:49:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soen/Jinn/" title="Soen - Jinn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Forty days and forty nights <br>You were the drug that kept me alive <br>During weary times <br><br>Seemed so pure when wearing white <br>Within such a frail and immaculate mind <br>With those innocent eyes <br><br>We were young and full of life <br>You asked me to swear in a mirror confide <br>Underneath the stars <br><br>I should care to let you fly <br>A chance to retrieve what was left behind <br>To experience life <br><br>Staring at the sky <br>Staring at the sun <br>Waiting for a wonder <br>Within a forsaken land <br>The sparrow in my hand <br>Now buried in the sand <br>Leaving you dependent <br>Leaving you an open vein <br><br>Can't make you wait no more <br>Can't make you wait nowhere <br>It's hard to breathe <br>Everything's blackening <br><br>I am made of flesh and bone <br>Blood, sweat and tears are all you ever will find <br>Underneath the skin <br><br>You're affair, that I'm a stone <br>Falling from the depths into the grave <br>Where I'm destined to dwell <br><br>And we reach for mystery <br>At the edge of reason <br>Every path we take <br>We're wandering in blindness <br>In the end nothing is <br>Lonelier or so honorable <br>While we drown in doubt <br>We're drifting like strangers <br><br>Staring at the sky <br>Staring at the sun <br>Waiting for a wonder <br>Within a forsaken land <br>The sparrow in my hand <br>Now buried in the sand <br>Leaving you dependent <br>Leaving me with open veins <br><br>Forty days and forty nights <br>You were the drug that kept me alive <br>With those innocent eyes]]></content><category term="Soen" label="Soen"/><category term="Jinn" label="Jinn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soen/Lucidity/</id><title>Soen - Lucidity - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:49:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:49:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soen/Lucidity/" title="Soen - Lucidity - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In a purple room <br>Thrown <br>Sailing to the sun <br>Reaching higher <br>Sleeping on a bed <br><br>Passing night and day <br>wasting hours <br><br>Lying on the grass <br>By the river <br>Captured by the moon <br>Dreaming wide awake <br>Moving slowly <br>Waiting for a change <br>Never coming <br><br>Can't see the danger waving my eyes <br>Everyone's a stranger wearing disguise <br><br>Let the journey end and ties you to stay]]></content><category term="Soen" label="Soen"/><category term="Lucidity" label="Lucidity"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soen/Sectarian/</id><title>Soen - Sectarian - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:49:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:49:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soen/Sectarian/" title="Soen - Sectarian - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Eradicate all life <br>The ones I touch the earth will swallow <br>I bless them with demise <br>This burning field my ghost will hallow <br>Run away and leave it all <br>Run away and leave it all <br><br>Leave the trail for a moment <br>Change the course for a while <br>And give in to the presence <br>Conceding a severed utopia <br><br>Let me rest in your cradle <br>Suffocate by your hand <br>Be embraced by the rotten <br>Immoral perverted vile <br><br>Let the skies rain <br>On the weak and the fallen <br>Let them reach faith <br>And be saved by your glory <br>Tonight the wait will end signs left a trace <br>And you'll return unharmed <br>Free of all the pain <br><br>Keep me close to the marrow <br>Part my skin from the bone <br>Any thoughts of rebellion <br>Are captured and hooked up to a chain <br><br>When my spirit is broken <br>And my will disconnects <br>A mirage of existence <br>Will carry this life into the next <br><br>Let the skies rain <br>On the weak and the fallen <br>Let them reach faith <br>And be saved by your glory <br>Tonight the wait will end signs left a trace <br>And you'll return unharmed <br>Free of all the pain <br><br>Hollow, shadow guide me out of the shame <br>Faceless, tyrant let the fear be my fate?]]></content><category term="Soen" label="Soen"/><category term="Sectarian" label="Sectarian"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Manel_Navarro/Do_It_for_Your_Lover/</id><title>Manel Navarro - Do It for Your Lover - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:49:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:49:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Manel_Navarro/Do_It_for_Your_Lover/" title="Manel Navarro - Do It for Your Lover - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A veces cuesta decir todo lo que uno piensa <br>A veces la vida causa estragos sin te des cuenta <br>A veces parece que es como una melodia <br>Frustrada y perdida, no nos deja ver la luz del dia <br><br>Do it for your lover <br>Do it for your lover, baby <br>Clap your hands and do it for your lover <br>Do it for your lover <br>Do it for your lover, baby <br>Clap your hands and do it for your lover <br>Do it for your lover <br>Do it for your lover <br>Do it for those you ever care and love <br>And love <br><br>Coge mi mano, no cierres esa puerta <br>Deja que el dolor y la tristeza desaparezca <br>Asi que pega un grito y sal de ahi y vuela <br>Y veras que por los tuyos siempre vale la pena <br>Asi que <br><br>Do it for your lover <br>Do it for your lover baby <br>Clap your hands and do it for your lover <br>Do it for your lover <br>Do it for your lover baby <br>Clap your hands and do it for your lover <br>Do it for your lover <br>Do it for your lover <br>Do for those you ever care and love <br>And love <br><br>Just do it <br>Just do it <br>Just do it for your lover <br>Just do it <br>Just do it <br>Just do it for your lover <br>Just do it <br>Just do it <br>Just do it for your lover <br>Just do it <br>Just do it <br>Just do it for your lover <br><br>Do it for your lover <br>Do it for your lover, baby <br>Clap your hands and do it for your lover <br>Do it for your lover <br>Do it for your lover oh no, just do it for your lover <br>Do it for those you ever care and love <br>And love <br><br>Oh baby just do it <br>Oh baby just do it <br>Just do it, just do it <br>La la la la la la la la]]></content><category term="Manel Navarro" label="Manel Navarro"/><category term="Do It for Your Lover" label="Do It for Your Lover"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SEKAI_NO_OWARI/深い森___Hukai_Mori_깊은_숲/</id><title>SEKAI NO OWARI - 深い森 / Hukai Mori (깊은 숲) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:49:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:49:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SEKAI_NO_OWARI/%E6%B7%B1%E3%81%84%E6%A3%AE___Hukai_Mori_%EA%B9%8A%EC%9D%80_%EC%88%B2/" title="SEKAI NO OWARI - 深い森 / Hukai Mori (깊은 숲) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the birdcage freedom is sung <br>So loud that our freedom song can't be heard <br>All the lives lost make no difference to us <br>The prayers of beasts locked inside the camp <br>Are softly surrounded by the poison gas <br>It's just like what the world feared of all those years ago <br>The stories from 1940 to 1945 <br>End of the world <br>Inside the bug cage the butterfly prays of freedom <br>And our freedom prayers can't be heard <br>All the lives lost make no difference to us <br>In a pet shop where life has a price tag <br>We pick up and hold the lonely cat to our chests <br>It's like buying and selling a life for profit <br>Oh, what's it called again? <br>I'm too tired to remember the word <br>End of the world <br>Everybody has a different view of this world <br>I just want to live in harmony <br>There is no life that comes with a price into this world <br>I just want to treasure everything <br>End of the world <br>Ond day I began to feel that dogs weren't locked up in chains <br>So please let me ask you this <br>"what is the reason that you are free?"]]></content><category term="SEKAI NO OWARI" label="SEKAI NO OWARI"/><category term="深い森 / Hukai Mori (깊은 숲)" label="深い森 / Hukai Mori (깊은 숲)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SEKAI_NO_OWARI/眠り姬___Nemuri_Hime_잠자는_공주/</id><title>SEKAI NO OWARI - 眠り姬 / Nemuri Hime (잠자는 공주) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T16:49:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T16:49:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/SEKAI_NO_OWARI/%E7%9C%A0%E3%82%8A%E5%A7%AC___Nemuri_Hime_%EC%9E%A0%EC%9E%90%EB%8A%94_%EA%B3%B5%EC%A3%BC/" title="SEKAI NO OWARI - 眠り姬 / Nemuri Hime (잠자는 공주) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[키미토보쿠토데세카이오 <br>보우켄시타케도 <br>나이타리와랏타리시테 <br>보쿠라와돈나토키데모 <br>테오츠나이데키타케도 <br>이츠카와이츠노히카와 <br>아루아사보쿠가 <br>메오사마스토 <br>코노세카이니와 <br>키미와이나인다네 <br>오도로카소토시테 <br>카쿠레테미테모 <br>키미와사가시니코나인다 <br>Ah키미와이츠노히카 <br>후카이네무리니 <br>오치테시마운다네 <br>소시타라모우메오 <br>사마사나인다네 <br>보쿠라가이마마데 <br>보우켄시타세카이토 <br>보쿠와히토리데 <br>타타카와나캬이케나인다네 <br>봇토히오후쿠도라곤모 <br>보쿠라후타리데타타캇타네 <br>유우샤노츠루기모 <br>미츠케테키타요네 <br>Ah코노마마키미가 <br>오키나캇타라도우시요우 <br>손나코토오모이나가라 <br>키미노네가오오미테이탄다 <br>콘나아오조라노토키데모 <br>돈나아라시노토키데모 <br>테오츠나이데키타케도 <br>콘나니우레시이토키모 <br>돈나니카나시이토키모 <br>이츠카와이츠노히카와 <br>아루아사보쿠가 <br>메오사마스토 <br>코노세카이니와 <br>키미와이나인다네 <br>오코소우토시테유사부루케도 <br>키미와모우메오 <br>사마사나인다 <br>Ah 키미와이츠노히카 <br>후카이네무리니 <br>오치테시마운다네 <br>소시타라모우메오 <br>사마사나인다네 <br>보쿠라가이마마데 <br>보우켄시타세카이토 <br>보쿠와히토리데 <br>타타카와나캬이케나인다네 <br>Ah 마다미누타카라모 <br>보쿠라후타리데 <br>사가시니잇타네 <br>호시가후루요루니 <br>후네오다시테사 <br>Ah 코노마마키미가 <br>오키나캇타라도우시요우 <br>손나코토오모이나가라 <br>키미노네가오오미테이탄다 <br>Ah키미와이츠노히카 <br>후카이네무리니 <br>오치테시마운다네 <br>소시타라모우메오 <br>사마사나인다네 <br>보쿠라가이마마데 <br>보우켄시타세카이토 <br>보쿠와히토리데 <br>타타카와나캬이케나인다네 <br>봇토히오후쿠도라곤모 <br>보쿠라후타리데타타캇타네 <br>유우샤노츠루기모 <br>미츠케테키타요네 <br>Ah코노마마키미가 <br>오키나캇타라도우시요우 <br>손나코토오모이나가라 <br>키미노네가오오미테이탄다]]></content><category term="SEKAI NO OWARI" label="SEKAI NO OWARI"/><category term="眠り姬 / Nemuri Hime (잠자는 공주)" label="眠り姬 / Nemuri Hime (잠자는 공주)"/></entry></feed>