<feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:51:51+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강성호/디지몬_어드벤처_-_날_지켜줘/</id><title>강성호 - 디지몬 어드벤처 - 날 지켜줘 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:51:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:51:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%84%B1%ED%98%B8/%EB%94%94%EC%A7%80%EB%AA%AC_%EC%96%B4%EB%93%9C%EB%B2%A4%EC%B2%98_-_%EB%82%A0_%EC%A7%80%EC%BC%9C%EC%A4%98/" title="강성호 - 디지몬 어드벤처 - 날 지켜줘 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무것도 모르고 깊이 잠들어 있는 날 깨우는 너의 목소리 <br>짙은 어둠을 밝혀줄 한 줄기 빛 날 비춰줘 <br>내 맘 속에 자라는 꿈이라는 이름의 알 수 없는 나의 미래를 <br>이젠 깨워줘 어둠이 되가는 날 지켜봐줘 <br>내게 더 용기를 준다면 다시 시작할 수가 있어 당당하게 새로 태어날 내가있어 <br>잊지마 너와 나 이젠 할수있어 기회는 지금뿐이야 <br>언제나 기억해 기다리고 있어 끝까지 날 지켜봐줘 give me a way <br>내게 더 용기를 준다면 다시 시작할수가 있어 당당하게 새로 태어날 내가 있어 <br>잊지마 너와 나 이젠 할수있어 기회는 지금 뿐이야 <br>언제나 기억해 기다리고 있어 끝까지 날 지켜봐줘 give me a way <br>잊지마 너와 나 이젠 할수있어 기회는 지금 뿐이야 <br>언제나 기억해 기다리고 있어 끝까지 날 지켜봐줘 give me a way]]></content><category term="강성호" label="강성호"/><category term="디지몬 어드벤처 - 날 지켜줘" label="디지몬 어드벤처 - 날 지켜줘"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/장숙희/닥터_슬럼프/</id><title>장숙희 - 닥터 슬럼프 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:52:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:52:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%EC%88%99%ED%9D%AC/%EB%8B%A5%ED%84%B0_%EC%8A%AC%EB%9F%BC%ED%94%84/" title="장숙희 - 닥터 슬럼프 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아야 아야 <br>혹시 내가 내가 실수하더라도 <br>귀여우니 한 번 봐줘 <br>혹시 엉뚱하게 생각하더라도 <br>깜찍하니 이해해줘 <br>생긴 대로 사는 거지 (사는 거지) <br>화를 내도 소용없어 (소용없어) <br>월화수목금토일 뻔한 일주일은 싫잖아 (싫잖아 야야야) <br>오늘은 또 무슨 일이 생길까 <br>너무 너무 너무 궁금해 <br>내일은 또 누구를 만날까 <br>정말 정말 정말 궁금해 궁금해 <br>야야야야 신나는 세상 <br>너랑 나는 친구야 <br>야야야야 놀라운 세상 <br>이제부터 이제부터 이제부터 시작이야 <br><br>혹시 공부하다 머리 아파질 때 <br>언제라도 날 불러줘 <br>괜히 짜증나고 자꾸 심술날 때 <br>주저말고 날 불러줘 <br>천방지축 말썽쟁이 (말썽쟁이) <br>신기한 일 너무 많아 (너무 많아) <br>빨주노초파남보 무지개를 타고 놀 거야 (놀 거야 야야야) <br>오늘은 또 왜 이렇게 신날까 <br>너무 너무 너무 재밌어 <br>내일은 또 어디까지 달릴까 <br>정말 정말 정말 재밌어 재밌어 <br>야야야야 신나는 세상 <br>너랑 나는 친구야 <br>야야야야 놀라운 세상 <br>이제부터 이제부터 이제부터 시작이야]]></content><category term="장숙희" label="장숙희"/><category term="닥터 슬럼프" label="닥터 슬럼프"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김국환/검정고무신_오프닝/</id><title>김국환 - 검정고무신 오프닝 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:52:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:52:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EA%B5%AD%ED%99%98/%EA%B2%80%EC%A0%95%EA%B3%A0%EB%AC%B4%EC%8B%A0_%EC%98%A4%ED%94%84%EB%8B%9D/" title="김국환 - 검정고무신 오프닝 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[할아버지 할머니 어렸을 적에 신으셨던 추억의 검정고무신 <br>엄마 아빠도 어릴 적 신던 헐렁하고 못생긴 검정고무신 <br>지금 다시 생각해보면 웃지 못 할 이야기 정다운 얘기 검정고무신 <br><br>이제는 지나버린 꿈같은 이야기 <br>미워도 했고 사랑도 했고 원망도 했지만 워워워 <br><br>지난 시절 다시는 오지 않아도 <br>모두 다 아름답고 정다운 얘기 꿈같은 얘기 검정고무신 <br><br>할아버지 할머니 어렸을 적에 신으셨던 추억의 검정고무신 <br>엄마 아빠도 어릴 적 신던 헐렁하고 못생긴 검정고무신 <br>지금 다시 생각해보면 웃지 못 할 이야기 정다운 얘기 검정고무신 <br><br>이제는 지나버린 꿈같은 이야기 <br>미워도 했고 사랑도 했고 원망도 했지만 워워워 <br><br>지난 시절 다시는 오지 않아도 <br>모두 다 아름답고 정다운 얘기 꿈같은 얘기 검정고무신]]></content><category term="김국환" label="김국환"/><category term="검정고무신 오프닝" label="검정고무신 오프닝"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/예수전도단/주는_반석/</id><title>예수전도단 - 주는 반석 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:52:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:52:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%88%EC%88%98%EC%A0%84%EB%8F%84%EB%8B%A8/%EC%A3%BC%EB%8A%94_%EB%B0%98%EC%84%9D/" title="예수전도단 - 주는 반석 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주는 반석 내 구원자 <br>주는 소망 나의 피난처 <br>주 나의 모든 것 <br>주는 반석 내 구원자 <br>주는 소망 나의 피난처 <br>주 나의 모든 것 <br>길과 진리 생명 <br>내 삶에 빛 되신 주 <br>길과 진리 생명 <br>내 삶에 빛 되신 주 <br>나의 믿음 주께 있네 <br>나의 믿음 주께 있네 <br>주는 반석 내 구원자 <br>주는 소망 나의 피난처 <br>주 나의 모든 것 <br>길과 진리 생명 <br>내 삶에 빛 되신 주 <br>길과 진리 생명 <br>내 삶에 빛 되신 주 <br>나의 믿음 주께 있네 <br>나의 믿음 주께 있네 <br>주는 반석 내 구원자 <br>주는 소망 나의 피난처 <br>주 나의 모든 것 <br>주는 반석 내 구원자 <br>주는 소망 나의 피난처 <br>주 나의 모든 것 <br>나의 믿음 주께 있네 <br>나의 믿음 주께 있네 <br>나의 믿음 주께 있네 <br>나의 믿음 주께 있네 <br>주는 반석 내 구원자 <br>주는 소망 나의 피난처 <br>주 나의 모든 것 <br>주는 반석 내 구원자 <br>주는 소망 나의 피난처 <br>주 나의 모든 것 <br>주는 반석 내 구원자 <br>주는 소망 나의 피난처 <br>주 나의 모든 것 <br>]]></content><category term="예수전도단" label="예수전도단"/><category term="주는 반석" label="주는 반석"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Airflow/Night_Wave/</id><title>Airflow - Night Wave - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:57:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:57:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Airflow/Night_Wave/" title="Airflow - Night Wave - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어김없이 찾아 온 내 우주의 밤 <br>두렵기도 oh 설레기도한 <br>그런 이상한 <br>그리고 당연하다는 듯 내 우주엔 너 <br>어쩌면 즐기고 있는지도 몰라 <br>I'm surfing on my night wave <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>I'm surfing on my night wave <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>I'm surfing on my night wave <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>I'm surfing on my night wave <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>까만 공기 속 작은 조명을 밝히고 <br>꺼져가는 마음 속 불씨를 살려내 <br>조금씩 끄적이네 <br>내 기억 속에 사는 널 <br>어쩌면 꿈처럼 흐려진지 몰라 <br>I'm surfing on my night wave <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>I'm surfing on my night wave <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>I'm surfing on my night wave <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>I'm surfing on my night wave <br>Woo woo woo woo woo <br>]]></content><category term="Airflow" label="Airflow"/><category term="Night Wave" label="Night Wave"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Airflow/Midnight_Whisper/</id><title>Airflow - Midnight Whisper - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:57:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:57:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Airflow/Midnight_Whisper/" title="Airflow - Midnight Whisper - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Your whisper is like sugar <br>like candy like chocolate so sweet <br>Your whisper is like air <br>like shadow like fire so good <br>Your whisper is like star <br>like moon like dream so fantastic <br>Your whisper is like sugar <br>like candy like chocolate so sweet <br>Your whisper is like air <br>like shadow like fire so good <br>Your whisper is like star <br>like moon like dream so fantastic <br>]]></content><category term="Airflow" label="Airflow"/><category term="Midnight Whisper" label="Midnight Whisper"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백경희/당신하나뿐_Inst/</id><title>백경희 - 당신하나뿐 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:58:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:58:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%EA%B2%BD%ED%9D%AC/%EB%8B%B9%EC%8B%A0%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EB%BF%90_Inst/" title="백경희 - 당신하나뿐 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[좋아한다고 사랑한다고 <br>꽃보다 더 좋아한다고 <br>말해주고싶어 말해주고싶어 <br>당신 정말 사랑한다고 <br>바람에 갈대는 갈대는 흔들려도 <br>이 여자는 흔들리지 않아 <br>저 별을 준대도 저 달을 따준대도 <br>내 사랑은 당신 하나뿐 <br>사랑은 당신 하나뿐 <br>영원하다고 맹세한다고 <br>당신없인 살 수 없다고 <br>가슴속에 사랑 가슴속에 사랑 <br>타오르던 불꽃이라고 <br>바람에 갈대는 갈대는 흔들려도 <br>이 여자는 흔들리지 않아 <br>저 별을 준대도 저 달을 따준대도 <br>내 사랑은 당신 하나뿐 <br>사랑은 당신 하나뿐 <br>저 별을 준대도 저 달을 따준대도 <br>내 사랑은 당신 하나뿐 <br>사랑은 당신 하나뿐 <br>]]></content><category term="백경희" label="백경희"/><category term="당신하나뿐 (Inst.)" label="당신하나뿐 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백경희/당신하나뿐/</id><title>백경희 - 당신하나뿐 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:58:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:58:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%EA%B2%BD%ED%9D%AC/%EB%8B%B9%EC%8B%A0%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EB%BF%90/" title="백경희 - 당신하나뿐 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[좋아한다고 사랑한다고 <br>꽃보다 더 좋아한다고 <br>말해주고싶어 말해주고싶어 <br>당신 정말 사랑한다고 <br>바람에 갈대는 갈대는 흔들려도 <br>이 여자는 흔들리지 않아 <br>저 별을 준대도 저 달을 따준대도 <br>내 사랑은 당신 하나뿐 <br>사랑은 당신 하나뿐 <br>영원하다고 맹세한다고 <br>당신없인 살 수 없다고 <br>가슴속에 사랑 가슴속에 사랑 <br>타오르던 불꽃이라고 <br>바람에 갈대는 갈대는 흔들려도 <br>이 여자는 흔들리지 않아 <br>저 별을 준대도 저 달을 따준대도 <br>내 사랑은 당신 하나뿐 <br>사랑은 당신 하나뿐 <br>저 별을 준대도 저 달을 따준대도 <br>내 사랑은 당신 하나뿐 <br>사랑은 당신 하나뿐 <br>]]></content><category term="백경희" label="백경희"/><category term="당신하나뿐" label="당신하나뿐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박찬일/남아있어_Feat_옥성원/</id><title>박찬일 - 남아있어 (Feat. 옥성원) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:58:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:58:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%B0%AC%EC%9D%BC/%EB%82%A8%EC%95%84%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4_Feat_%EC%98%A5%EC%84%B1%EC%9B%90/" title="박찬일 - 남아있어 (Feat. 옥성원) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[차가운 방 창가에 앉아 <br>그대의 흔적에 잠겨 <br>온기가 사라진 <br>침대 한 켠에 누워봐 <br>남아있던 그대의 향기에 젖어 <br>참아왔던 눈물과 <br>차가운 이 밤이 흘러 <br>갈 곳을 잃은 <br>전화기를 붙잡고 <br>그대가 있는 하늘만 쳐다보네 <br>이 시간이 지난다면 <br>그대도 잊혀지겠죠 <br>꼭 붙잡고 있어봐도 잊혀져 <br>이젠 기다려도 오지 않겠죠 <br>같은 하늘 아래 함께 없다 해도 <br>시간 지나 그대 기억 잊혀진대도 <br>내 맘 깊은 곳에 남겨둔다면 <br>영원히 함께겠죠 <br>갈 곳을 잃은 <br>전화기를 붙잡고 <br>그대가 있는 하늘만 쳐다보네 <br>이 시간이 지난다면 <br>그대도 잊혀지겠죠 <br>꼭 붙잡고 있어봐도 잊혀져 <br>이젠 기다려도 오지 않겠죠 <br>같은 하늘 아래 함께 없다 해도 <br>시간 지나 그대 기억 잊혀진대도 <br>내 맘 깊은 곳에 남겨둔다면 <br>영원히 내겐 남아있어 <br>]]></content><category term="박찬일" label="박찬일"/><category term="남아있어 (Feat. 옥성원)" label="남아있어 (Feat. 옥성원)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tenere_티네어/Say_What_You_Want_Tenere_Remix_Feat_RPQ/</id><title>Tenere (티네어) - Say What You Want (Tenere Remix) (Feat. RPQ) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:58:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:58:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tenere_%ED%8B%B0%EB%84%A4%EC%96%B4/Say_What_You_Want_Tenere_Remix_Feat_RPQ/" title="Tenere (티네어) - Say What You Want (Tenere Remix) (Feat. RPQ) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey girl You make <br>my heart skip a beat <br>Every time you walk <br>across the room <br>You seem to have your way <br>with words <br>The things you say make <br>my mind go wild <br>Oh all the boys <br>try too hard to get you <br>They do the things <br>you want them to <br>You've got them by their necks <br>caught them by surprise <br>I'm pretty sure they don't know <br>what they're in for <br>Say what you want <br>Say what you will <br>Have you been thinking of me <br>You've got me barely breathing <br>I've been waiting for this <br>To see you to feel you <br>Your lips your skin <br>they send me to the moon <br>Your eyes your smile <br>everything about you girl <br>I've been crazy for you <br>I've been Say what you want <br>Say what you want <br>Say what you want <br>all the boys wanna <br>know what u really like <br>but they don't know <br>cuz I'm what u really like <br>I know you'r thinking of <br>me day and night <br>I do the same thing <br>about you all the time <br>everything your lips your skin <br>and eyes your smile <br>they send me to the moon <br>달을 걷는 기분 <br>다른 놈들은 너를 원해 <br>안달이 났지만 <br>이미 알 수 있어 <br>너도 내게 빠졌단걸 <br>everyday I'm thinking <br>about you 기다려 <br>너도 아닌 척할 필요 없어 다 알어 <br>Just tell me what you <br>wanna do where do you wanna go <br>I'll go with you <br>너와 함께라면 어디든지 paradise <br>Say what you want <br>Say what you will <br>Have you been thinking of me <br>You've got me barely breathing <br>I've been waiting for this <br>To see you to feel you <br>Your lips your skin <br>they send me to the moon <br>Your eyes your smile <br>everything about you girl <br>I've been crazy for you <br>I've been Say what you want <br>Say what you want <br>Say what you want <br>Say what you want <br>Say what you want <br>]]></content><category term="Tenere (티네어)" label="Tenere (티네어)"/><category term="Say What You Want (Tenere Remix) (Feat. RPQ)" label="Say What You Want (Tenere Remix) (Feat. RPQ)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/남태현_South_Club/LIAR/</id><title>남태현 (South Club) - LIAR - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:59:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:59:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%A8%ED%83%9C%ED%98%84_South_Club/LIAR/" title="남태현 (South Club) - LIAR - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 앞에 앉아서 신나게 <br>자기 얘기를 떠드는데 <br>못 알아 듣겠어 <br>자기는 이런 사람이라고 <br>열의에 차서 침을 튀기는데 <br>미안해요 미안해요 <br>관심이 없어요 그대에게 <br>그대는 너무나 예뻐요 <br>나같은 사람과 시간 보내지 마요 <br>그렇게 잘나신 그대가 <br>나와 한 공간에 있긴 아까워요 <br>Liar 입만 열면 거짓말이 입에 뱄어 <br>Liar 머리가 아파 오네요 <br>그만해요 Liar <br>You Are Liar <br>그대는 내가 멍청해 보이나 봐요 <br>어쩜 그리 뻔뻔할까 <br>혹시 날 좋아하나요 <br>그렇다면 방법이 잘못 됐어 그만해요 <br>추해보여 말을 아껴봐요 거봐 <br>얼마나 예뻐요 <br>그래도 난 관심 없어요 <br>Liar 입만 열면 거짓말이 입에 뱄어 <br>Liar 머리가 아파 오네요 <br>그만해요 Liar <br>You Are Liar You Are Liar <br>You Are Liar <br>You Are Liar You Are Liar <br>Yeah <br>You Are Liar <br>]]></content><category term="남태현 (South Club)" label="남태현 (South Club)"/><category term="LIAR" label="LIAR"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/남태현_South_Club/IDS/</id><title>남태현 (South Club) - I.D.S - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:59:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:59:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%A8%ED%83%9C%ED%98%84_South_Club/IDS/" title="남태현 (South Club) - I.D.S - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[외로운 내 마음은 채워지지 않아 <br>어차피 내 말은 들어주지 않아 <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit Anymore <br>말 많이 해 봤자 입만 아프더라 <br>약속을 해 봤자 순간 뿐이더라 <br>난 사람이 싫어요 <br>아니 무서운 걸요 이젠 <br>신경 안 쓸라고 <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit Anymore <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit Anymore <br>싸늘한 눈빛과 달콤한 거짓말 <br>입 발린 친절과 뜻 모를 비웃음 <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit Anymore <br>난 사람이 싫어요 <br>아니 무서운 걸요 <br>이젠 신경 안 쓸라고 <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit Anymore <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit <br>But I Don’t Give A Shit Anymore <br>난 사람이 싫어요 <br>아니 무서운 걸요 이젠 <br>]]></content><category term="남태현 (South Club)" label="남태현 (South Club)"/><category term="I.D.S" label="I.D.S"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/남태현_South_Club/Hug_Me/</id><title>남태현 (South Club) - Hug Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:59:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:59:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%A8%ED%83%9C%ED%98%84_South_Club/Hug_Me/" title="남태현 (South Club) - Hug Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[매일 누군가 만나고 <br>같이 밤을 지새우고 <br>늦은 담배를 물어 <br>너도 나처럼 외롭고 <br>뭔가 채워지지 않는 <br>빈 공간이 있겠지 <br>우린 너무 멀리 온 거야 <br>되돌아갈 순 없을 것 같아 <br>그게 무서워 <br>안아줘 안아줘 <br>하루가 가고 누군갈 <br>만나 자고 일어나면 <br>아무 기억이 없어 <br>내가 죄를 지은 건가요 <br>너무 아픈 벌을 받나요 <br>그만 그만 데려가 줘요 <br>우린 너무 멀리 온 거야 <br>되돌아갈 순 없을 것 같아 <br>안아줘 안아줘 <br>나도 웃고 싶어요 <br>이제 그만하고 싶어 <br>나도 힘들어 <br>안아줘 <br>안아줘 안아줘 <br>매일 누군가 만나고 <br>같이 밤을 지새우고 <br>늦은 담배를 물어 <br>]]></content><category term="남태현 (South Club)" label="남태현 (South Club)"/><category term="Hug Me" label="Hug Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/남태현_South_Club/Believe_U/</id><title>남태현 (South Club) - Believe U - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:59:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:59:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%A8%ED%83%9C%ED%98%84_South_Club/Believe_U/" title="남태현 (South Club) - Believe U - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever 바라는 대로 해요 <br>넌 뭘 해도 예뻐요 <br>난 그댈 믿어요 <br>무엇이든 하고 싶은 거 하세요 <br>자꾸 눈치 보지 말고 <br>편하게 생각해요 <br>I Believe You Believe You <br>I Believe You Oh I Love You <br>Believe You Believe You <br>I Believe You Oh I Like You <br>Believe You Believe You <br>I Believe You Oh I Miss You <br>Believe You Believe You <br>I Love You <br>Whatever 원하는 대로 해요 <br>넌 어차피 잘 될 거야 <br>난 그댈 믿어요 <br>무엇이든 하고 싶은 거 하세요 <br>자꾸 눈치 보지 말고 <br>편하게 생각해요 <br>I Believe You Believe You <br>I Believe You Oh I Love You <br>Believe You Believe You <br>I Believe You Oh I Like You <br>Believe You Believe You <br>I Believe You Oh I Miss You <br>Believe You Believe You <br>I Love You <br>]]></content><category term="남태현 (South Club)" label="남태현 (South Club)"/><category term="Believe U" label="Believe U"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/남태현_South_Club/I_Got_The_Blues/</id><title>남태현 (South Club) - I Got The Blues - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:59:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:59:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%A8%ED%83%9C%ED%98%84_South_Club/I_Got_The_Blues/" title="남태현 (South Club) - I Got The Blues - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한껏 취해 보이는 여자가 내게 다가와 <br>이상하게 머리를 흔들어 대며 <br>나에게 할 말이라도 있었는지 <br>내 귓가에 입술을 대고 속삭이네 <br>I Got The Blues <br>I Got The Blues <br>I Got The Blues <br>I Got The Blues <br>어젯밤에 술을 너무 많이 마셨나 봐 <br>눈을 뜨니 목이 마르고 <br>배가 너무 고파서 <br>온 집을 다 뒤져봐도 먹을 게 없어 <br>친구에게 전화를 거니 한마디 하네 <br>I Got The Blues <br>I Got The Blues <br>I Got The Blues <br>I Got The Blues Baby <br>오늘 따라 춤이 너무 추고 싶어서 <br>밖으로 나가 노래를 정말 크게 트니까 <br>모두들 저게 뭔가 싶어 하더니 <br>어느새 내 옆에 와서 춤을 추고 있네 <br>I Got The Blues <br>I Got The Blues <br>I Got The Blues Baby <br>I Got The Blues <br>I Got The Blues Blues Baby No No <br>I Got The Blues Blues Baby No <br>I Got The Blues Blues Baby No No <br>I Got The Blues <br>I Got The Blues Huh <br>I Got The Baby No <br>I Got The Blues Huh <br>I Got The Baby No <br>I Got The Blues Huh <br>Oh My Baby No <br>I Got The Blues <br>]]></content><category term="남태현 (South Club)" label="남태현 (South Club)"/><category term="I Got The Blues" label="I Got The Blues"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/남태현_South_Club/더러운_집/</id><title>남태현 (South Club) - 더러운 집 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T17:59:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T17:59:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%A8%ED%83%9C%ED%98%84_South_Club/%EB%8D%94%EB%9F%AC%EC%9A%B4_%EC%A7%91/" title="남태현 (South Club) - 더러운 집 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뭐 그리 안 되는 게 많아 <br>튕기지 좀 마 <br>난 세 번 이상 참지 못해 <br>그만 항복하거라 <br>이 만큼 만나보고 <br>대화 나눴음 됐지 <br>도대체 뭘 더 알고 싶은 거야 <br>이만하면 충분해 <br>집이 대체 뭐 어떻길래 <br>난 깔끔한 집이 너무 싫어 Baby <br>어차피 나와 함께 가면 <br>아주 수십 배는 더러워져 <br>Oh Dirty House <br>Dirty House <br>Dirty House <br>Dirty House <br>I Don't Care <br>Dirty House <br>Dirty House <br>Dirty House <br>Dirty House <br>I Don't Care <br>집이 대체 뭐 어떻길래 <br>난 깔끔한 집이 너무 싫어 Baby <br>어차피 나와 함께 가면 <br>아주 수십 배는 더러워져 <br>Oh Dirty House <br>Dirty House <br>Dirty House <br>Dirty House <br>I Don't Care <br>Dirty House <br>Dirty House <br>Dirty House <br>Dirty House <br>I Don't Care <br>뭐 그리 안 되는 게 많아 <br>튕기지 좀 마 <br>난 세 번 이상 참지 못해 <br>그만 항복하거라 <br>이 만큼 만나보고 <br>대화 나눴음 됐지 <br>도대체 뭘 더 알고 싶은 거야 <br>이만하면 충분해 <br>]]></content><category term="남태현 (South Club)" label="남태현 (South Club)"/><category term="더러운 집" label="더러운 집"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/넉살/Nuckle_Flow__Inst/</id><title>넉살 - Nuckle Flow (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:04:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:04:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%84%89%EC%82%B4/Nuckle_Flow__Inst/" title="넉살 - Nuckle Flow (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주먹을 쥔다고 다 깡패는 아냐 <br>악수를 한다고 다 짝패는 아냐 <br>신문을 본 다고 다 똥싸진 않아 <br>MIC를 잡는다고 다 MC는 아냐 <br>소문이 돈다고 다 진실은 아니고 <br>술을 먹는다고 꼭 솔직하진 않지 <br>rhyme을 짠다고 <br>rap이 아닐 수도 있어 <br>제대로 된 boss는 없고 <br>다 사장 옆에 비서 <br>fisher man 우린 사람 낚는 어부 <br>언어를 가려서 해 <br>네게 재능이 있다면 <br>이건 선택하는 것이 아닌 <br>선택 받은 것 <br>책임감을 가져 벗겨버려 <br>세상 위의 가면 <br>I feel the fire I feel the fire <br>프로메테우스의 불을 줄게 <br>내 rap을 받어 <br>비춰봐 넌 본적이 없지 <br>이 바닥의 내면 <br>플라톤 shit 걍 웃겨 존박의 냉면 <br>겉치레 코스프레 나 보다 <br>머리 짧은 계집애들 <br>내가 시를 쓸 때 <br>딴 테이블에서 씹얘기나 해 <br>그러니 니넨 hip hop bitch들의 <br>가십 거리 밖엔 안돼 <br>이 거리 밖엔 악마들이 <br>춤을 추는 댄스홀 같애 <br>지붕 위에서 하이네켄을 <br>마시는 진짜 악마들은 <br>우릴 비웃을 수밖에 <br>rap 다운 rap hip hop 다운 hip hop <br>난 그 이상을 봐 내 이름을 건 음악 <br>내가 대표하는 얼굴이 하나 더 늘고 <br>내가 대표하는 이들에겐 미소를 선사 <br>Yo 별말씀을 하셔 yes I'm 넉살 <br>RHYD YO GUERILLAZ <br>2개의 체인에 롤렉스는 없지만 <br>내가 뱉는 rap은 <br>최소한 3개의 금메달 <br>을 걸어 임마 넌 이 게임에 <br>뭘 걸었냐 임마 <br>냄새 나는 니 부랄 <br>두 쪽이랑 인생 얘긴 <br>닥치고 그만 꺼져 이 게임에 부랑자들 <br>불안 종자들 말도 섞기 싫어 <br>그래서 로디형은 자켓 뒤에 숨어 <br>우탄이는 여전히 show and prove <br>그리고 저기 양화대교를 <br>건너오는 639 <br>그리고 나 VMC <br>The god of small things <br>]]></content><category term="넉살" label="넉살"/><category term="Nuckle Flow (Inst.)" label="Nuckle Flow (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/넉살/Nuckle_Flow/</id><title>넉살 - Nuckle Flow - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:04:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:04:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%84%89%EC%82%B4/Nuckle_Flow/" title="넉살 - Nuckle Flow - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주먹을 쥔다고 다 깡패는 아냐 <br>악수를 한다고 다 짝패는 아냐 <br>신문을 본 다고 다 똥싸진 않아 <br>MIC를 잡는다고 다 MC는 아냐 <br>소문이 돈다고 다 진실은 아니고 <br>술을 먹는다고 꼭 솔직하진 않지 <br>rhyme을 짠다고 <br>rap이 아닐 수도 있어 <br>제대로 된 boss는 없고 <br>다 사장 옆에 비서 <br>fisher man 우린 사람 낚는 어부 <br>언어를 가려서 해 <br>네게 재능이 있다면 <br>이건 선택하는 것이 아닌 <br>선택 받은 것 <br>책임감을 가져 벗겨버려 <br>세상 위의 가면 <br>I feel the fire I feel the fire <br>프로메테우스의 불을 줄게 <br>내 rap을 받어 <br>비춰봐 넌 본적이 없지 <br>이 바닥의 내면 <br>플라톤 shit 걍 웃겨 존박의 냉면 <br>겉치레 코스프레 나 보다 <br>머리 짧은 계집애들 <br>내가 시를 쓸 때 <br>딴 테이블에서 씹얘기나 해 <br>그러니 니넨 hip hop bitch들의 <br>가십 거리 밖엔 안돼 <br>이 거리 밖엔 악마들이 <br>춤을 추는 댄스홀 같애 <br>지붕 위에서 하이네켄을 <br>마시는 진짜 악마들은 <br>우릴 비웃을 수밖에 <br>rap 다운 rap hip hop 다운 hip hop <br>난 그 이상을 봐 내 이름을 건 음악 <br>내가 대표하는 얼굴이 하나 더 늘고 <br>내가 대표하는 이들에겐 미소를 선사 <br>Yo 별말씀을 하셔 yes I'm 넉살 <br>RHYD YO GUERILLAZ <br>2개의 체인에 롤렉스는 없지만 <br>내가 뱉는 rap은 <br>최소한 3개의 금메달 <br>을 걸어 임마 넌 이 게임에 <br>뭘 걸었냐 임마 <br>냄새 나는 니 부랄 <br>두 쪽이랑 인생 얘긴 <br>닥치고 그만 꺼져 이 게임에 부랑자들 <br>불안 종자들 말도 섞기 싫어 <br>그래서 로디형은 자켓 뒤에 숨어 <br>우탄이는 여전히 show and prove <br>그리고 저기 양화대교를 <br>건너오는 639 <br>그리고 나 VMC <br>The god of small things <br>]]></content><category term="넉살" label="넉살"/><category term="Nuckle Flow" label="Nuckle Flow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스텔라장_Stella_Jang/Alright_Inst/</id><title>스텔라장 (Stella Jang) - Alright (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:04:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:04:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%94%EB%9D%BC%EC%9E%A5_Stella_Jang/Alright_Inst/" title="스텔라장 (Stella Jang) - Alright (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Gimme gimme <br>Gimme gimme give me back <br>너에게 속한 금쪽같은 시간 <br>짐이 짐이 <br>짐이 짐이 짐이 돼 <br>내 좁은 어깨 위에 자리를 잡아 <br>하나 둘 툭 털어내고 나면 <br>어느새 꿈처럼 다시 <br>제자리로 훅 돌아와 버리면 <br>심장이 쿵 떨어져 <br>But little by little <br>And day by day <br>널 지워가는 <br>내가 기특해 <br>So let me say without hesitation <br>That I'm alright <br>Ye I'm alright <br>Yes I am <br>Cuz I don't mind <br>No I don't mind <br>No I don't <br>과거는 과거에 묻기로 해 <br>너도 나의 과거에만 두기로 해 <br>너로 인한 <br>stress and tears and time wasting <br>내겐 다 불필요해 <br>네게 붓기로 했던 시간 돈과 마음 <br>지나고 보니 다 부질없네 <br>네 마지막 조각까지 모두 털어낸 다음 <br>이젠 전부 내게 쓰기로 해 <br>하나 둘 툭 털어내고 나면 <br>어느새 꿈처럼 다시 <br>제자리로 훅 돌아와 버리면 <br>심장이 쿵 떨어져 <br>But little by little <br>And day by day <br>널 지워가는 <br>내가 기특해 <br>So let me say without hesitation <br>That I'm alright <br>Ye I'm alright <br>Yes I am <br>Cuz I don't mind <br>No I don't mind <br>No I don't <br>시간이 지나서 언젠가 <br>너의 이름조차도 다 잊게 되면 <br>그땐 이 노래도 <br>부르지 않겠지 <br>There'll be no need to say <br>That I'm alright <br>Ye I'm alright <br>Yes I am <br>Cuz I don't mind <br>No I don't mind <br>No I don't <br>That I'm alright <br>Ye I'm alright <br>Yes I am <br>Cuz I don't mind <br>No I don't mind <br>No I don't <br>]]></content><category term="스텔라장 (Stella Jang)" label="스텔라장 (Stella Jang)"/><category term="Alright (Inst.)" label="Alright (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스텔라장_Stella_Jang/Alright/</id><title>스텔라장 (Stella Jang) - Alright - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:04:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:04:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%94%EB%9D%BC%EC%9E%A5_Stella_Jang/Alright/" title="스텔라장 (Stella Jang) - Alright - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Gimme gimme <br>Gimme gimme give me back <br>너에게 속한 금쪽같은 시간 <br>짐이 짐이 <br>짐이 짐이 짐이 돼 <br>내 좁은 어깨 위에 자리를 잡아 <br>하나 둘 툭 털어내고 나면 <br>어느새 꿈처럼 다시 <br>제자리로 훅 돌아와 버리면 <br>심장이 쿵 떨어져 <br>But little by little <br>And day by day <br>널 지워가는 <br>내가 기특해 <br>So let me say without hesitation <br>That I'm alright <br>Ye I'm alright <br>Yes I am <br>Cuz I don't mind <br>No I don't mind <br>No I don't <br>과거는 과거에 묻기로 해 <br>너도 나의 과거에만 두기로 해 <br>너로 인한 <br>stress and tears and time wasting <br>내겐 다 불필요해 <br>네게 붓기로 했던 시간 돈과 마음 <br>지나고 보니 다 부질없네 <br>네 마지막 조각까지 모두 털어낸 다음 <br>이젠 전부 내게 쓰기로 해 <br>하나 둘 툭 털어내고 나면 <br>어느새 꿈처럼 다시 <br>제자리로 훅 돌아와 버리면 <br>심장이 쿵 떨어져 <br>But little by little <br>And day by day <br>널 지워가는 <br>내가 기특해 <br>So let me say without hesitation <br>That I'm alright <br>Ye I'm alright <br>Yes I am <br>Cuz I don't mind <br>No I don't mind <br>No I don't <br>시간이 지나서 언젠가 <br>너의 이름조차도 다 잊게 되면 <br>그땐 이 노래도 <br>부르지 않겠지 <br>There'll be no need to say <br>That I'm alright <br>Ye I'm alright <br>Yes I am <br>Cuz I don't mind <br>No I don't mind <br>No I don't <br>That I'm alright <br>Ye I'm alright <br>Yes I am <br>Cuz I don't mind <br>No I don't mind <br>No I don't <br>]]></content><category term="스텔라장 (Stella Jang)" label="스텔라장 (Stella Jang)"/><category term="Alright" label="Alright"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이설아/넌_새로워_Inst/</id><title>이설아 - 넌 새로워 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:04:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:04:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%A4%EC%95%84/%EB%84%8C_%EC%83%88%EB%A1%9C%EC%9B%8C_Inst/" title="이설아 - 넌 새로워 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[폭풍우가 몰아치던 어느 날 <br>개인 후의 무지개 같아 <br>삐져나온 코털을 볼 때면 <br>뽑아주고 파 손이 먼저 가 <br>어릴 적 꿈속에서 보았던 <br>백마 탄 왕자님보다 더 <br>신선한 네 입술에 뽀뽀하고 파 <br>넌 새로워 <br>활짝 지어 보이는 미소가 <br>너무 간지러워 <br>오 놀라워 <br>새콤달콤한 너의 향기에 <br>흠뻑 빠져들어 <br>헤어 나올 수 없어 <br>너의 코 고는 소리는 <br>나에겐 나긋한 속삭임 <br>목 늘어난 흰 티조차도 <br>내가 보기엔 브랜드야 <br>운동 후의 땀 냄새까지도 <br>라일락 꽃향기 같은 걸 <br>무인도에 홀로 떨어졌을 때 <br>나타난 구조원보다 더 <br>반가운 네 입술에 뽀뽀하고 파 <br>넌 새로워 <br>활짝 지어 보이는 미소가 <br>너무 간지러워 <br>오 놀라워 <br>새콤달콤한 너의 향기에 <br>흠뻑 빠져들어 <br>헤어 나올 수 없어 <br>너의 코 고는 소리는 <br>나에겐 나긋한 속삭임 <br>너의 코 고는 소리는 <br>나에겐 나긋한 속삭임 <br>너무나 새로운걸 <br>나에겐 따뜻한 설레임 <br>]]></content><category term="이설아" label="이설아"/><category term="넌 새로워 (Inst.)" label="넌 새로워 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이설아/넌_새로워/</id><title>이설아 - 넌 새로워 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:04:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:04:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%A4%EC%95%84/%EB%84%8C_%EC%83%88%EB%A1%9C%EC%9B%8C/" title="이설아 - 넌 새로워 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[폭풍우가 몰아치던 어느 날 <br>개인 후의 무지개 같아 <br>삐져나온 코털을 볼 때면 <br>뽑아주고 파 손이 먼저 가 <br>어릴 적 꿈속에서 보았던 <br>백마 탄 왕자님보다 더 <br>신선한 네 입술에 뽀뽀하고 파 <br>넌 새로워 <br>활짝 지어 보이는 미소가 <br>너무 간지러워 <br>오 놀라워 <br>새콤달콤한 너의 향기에 <br>흠뻑 빠져들어 <br>헤어 나올 수 없어 <br>너의 코 고는 소리는 <br>나에겐 나긋한 속삭임 <br>목 늘어난 흰 티조차도 <br>내가 보기엔 브랜드야 <br>운동 후의 땀 냄새까지도 <br>라일락 꽃향기 같은 걸 <br>무인도에 홀로 떨어졌을 때 <br>나타난 구조원보다 더 <br>반가운 네 입술에 뽀뽀하고 파 <br>넌 새로워 <br>활짝 지어 보이는 미소가 <br>너무 간지러워 <br>오 놀라워 <br>새콤달콤한 너의 향기에 <br>흠뻑 빠져들어 <br>헤어 나올 수 없어 <br>너의 코 고는 소리는 <br>나에겐 나긋한 속삭임 <br>너의 코 고는 소리는 <br>나에겐 나긋한 속삭임 <br>너무나 새로운걸 <br>나에겐 따뜻한 설레임 <br>]]></content><category term="이설아" label="이설아"/><category term="넌 새로워" label="넌 새로워"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/우효/소나기/</id><title>우효 - 소나기 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:04:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:04:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9A%B0%ED%9A%A8/%EC%86%8C%EB%82%98%EA%B8%B0/" title="우효 - 소나기 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대 슬픈 눈을 바라볼 때면 <br>나는 할 말을 잃고 <br>어루만질 수도 없는 걸 <br>그저 내 마음에 묻고서 <br>소리 없이 오는 소낙비처럼 <br>내 가슴에 퍼지는 <br>그대 웃음 뒤에 쓸쓸함 <br>애써 잊어 보려 하네요 <br>시린 가을바람 사이로 <br>그대 흔들리던 <br>혼자 헤매이던 <br>그 모든 날들 <br>어떡해야 내가 <br>함께 걸어갈 수 있을까요 <br>꽃같이 여린 그대를 내가 어떡하죠 <br>내 사랑은 안돼요 <br>이것만으로는 <br>잠깐의 햇살로는 채울 수 없어 <br>내 사랑은 안돼요 <br>어림없어요 <br>그대의 눈물 <br>닦아줄 수 없어 <br>닦아줄 수 없어 <br>내 사랑은 안돼요 <br>이것만으로는 <br>잠깐의 햇살로는 <br>채울 수 없어 <br>내 사랑은 안돼요 <br>어림없어요 <br>그대의 눈물 닦아줄 수 없어 <br>닦아줄 수 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="우효" label="우효"/><category term="소나기" label="소나기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강민희/널_보낸_적_없어_Inst/</id><title>강민희 - 널 보낸 적 없어 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:04:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:04:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EB%AF%BC%ED%9D%AC/%EB%84%90_%EB%B3%B4%EB%82%B8_%EC%A0%81_%EC%97%86%EC%96%B4_Inst/" title="강민희 - 널 보낸 적 없어 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가만히 길을 걷다 이쯤이었나 <br>살아난 기억에 발걸음을 세워 <br>네가 가장 예뻤던 바람이 불던 그날 <br>또다시 그 계절이 왔나 봐 <br>네가 떠난 그날 <br>난 단 한 번도 널 보낸 적 없어 <br>여전히 난 이 자리에 서있어 <br>서로가 머물렀던 자리 <br>누군가 머물게 된다면 <br>행복했던 우리가 있었다 말해주리 <br>가만히 길을 걷다 이쯤이었나 <br>살아난 추억에 발걸음을 돌려 <br>말없이 날 감싸준 그 시간 속으로 <br>아직도 널 놓지 못하나 봐 <br>우리 그날 <br>난 단 한 번도 널 보낸 적 없어 <br>여전히 난 이 자리에 서있어 <br>서로가 머물렀던 자리 <br>누군가 머물게 된다면 <br>행복했던 우리가 있었다 말해주리 <br>난 여기 서있어 기억에 머물러 <br>같은 꿈 서로 다른 곳에서 <br>너를 단 한 번도 잊어본 적 없어 <br>돌아섰던 마지막까지 한 번도 <br>한 순간도 널 잊은 적 없어 <br>여전히 널 기다리고 있어 <br>바람이 불어오는 자리 <br>그 길 위에 우리 있을까 봐 <br>그럴까 봐 추억의 앞에 마중 나와 <br>지난날 널 그려보고 있어 <br>그 기억을 따라 걷고 있어 <br>아픔이 머물렀던 자리 <br>네가 다시 돌아와 준다면 <br>아름답던 우리의 기억이 피어나리 <br>]]></content><category term="강민희" label="강민희"/><category term="널 보낸 적 없어 (Inst.)" label="널 보낸 적 없어 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강민희/널_보낸_적_없어_Feat_한동근/</id><title>강민희 - 널 보낸 적 없어 (Feat. 한동근) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:04:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:04:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EB%AF%BC%ED%9D%AC/%EB%84%90_%EB%B3%B4%EB%82%B8_%EC%A0%81_%EC%97%86%EC%96%B4_Feat_%ED%95%9C%EB%8F%99%EA%B7%BC/" title="강민희 - 널 보낸 적 없어 (Feat. 한동근) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 보낸 적 없어 (Feat. 한동근) <br><br>가만히 길을 걷다 이쯤이었나 <br>살아난 기억에 발걸음을 세워 <br>네가 가장 예뻤던 바람이 불던 그날 <br>또다시 그 계절이 왔나 봐 <br>네가 떠난 그날 <br>난 단 한 번도 널 보낸 적 없어 <br>여전히 난 이 자리에 서있어 <br>서로가 머물렀던 자리 <br>누군가 머물게 된다면 <br>행복했던 우리가 있었다 말해주리 <br>가만히 길을 걷다 이쯤이었나 <br>살아난 추억에 발걸음을 돌려 <br>말없이 날 감싸준 그 시간 속으로 <br>아직도 널 놓지 못하나 봐 <br>우리 그날 <br>난 단 한 번도 널 보낸 적 없어 <br>여전히 난 이 자리에 서있어 <br>서로가 머물렀던 자리 <br>누군가 머물게 된다면 <br>행복했던 우리가 있었다 말해주리 <br>난 여기 서있어 기억에 머물러 <br>같은 꿈 서로 다른 곳에서 <br>너를 단 한 번도 잊어본 적 없어 <br>돌아섰던 마지막까지 한 번도 <br>한 순간도 널 잊은 적 없어 <br>여전히 널 기다리고 있어 <br>바람이 불어오는 자리 <br>그 길 위에 우리 있을까 봐 <br>그럴까 봐 추억의 앞에 마중 나와 <br>지난날 널 그려보고 있어 <br>그 기억을 따라 걷고 있어 <br>아픔이 머물렀던 자리 <br>네가 다시 돌아와 준다면 <br>아름답던 우리의 기억이 피어나리 <br>]]></content><category term="강민희" label="강민희"/><category term="널 보낸 적 없어 (Feat. 한동근)" label="널 보낸 적 없어 (Feat. 한동근)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헨리_HENRY/끌리는_대로_Im_good_Feat_nafla/</id><title>헨리 (HENRY) - 끌리는 대로 (I`m good) (Feat. nafla) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:05:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:05:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A8%EB%A6%AC_HENRY/%EB%81%8C%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_%EB%8C%80%EB%A1%9C_Im_good_Feat_nafla/" title="헨리 (HENRY) - 끌리는 대로 (I`m good) (Feat. nafla) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Everything is better <br>끌리는 대로 끌리는 대로 <br>It’s alright alright <br>I don’t even need you <br>끌리는 대로 끌리는 대로 <br>It’s alright alright <br>I don’t even need you <br>지내는 곳이 많아 요즘엔 <br>신경 써야 할 게 줄었어 <br>And I don’t need your love <br>내겐 사랑은 하나의 Game <br>모든 게 다 새로워 Now I know it <br>같이 보낸 곳에서 딴 생각해 <br>다른 여자들을 보며 웃어 해맑게 <br>잘 지내지 뭐 어떡해 <br>Now you wanna comeback <br>But I ain't got no time for that <br>Cuz everything is better <br>끌리는 대로 끌리는 대로 <br>It’s alright alright <br>I don’t even need you <br>끌리는 대로 끌리는 대로 <br>It’s alright alright <br>다 지나가니 <br>I’m all good without you <br>I’m all good without you <br>I’m all good without you <br>I’m all good <br>I don’t even need you <br>알 수 없지 내일은 <br>Miss calls and girls waiting <br>혼자여서 더 즐거워 <br>예전처럼 될 수가 없어 너와 난 <br>I can’t stand another day <br>이젠 같이 보낸 곳에서 딴 생각해 <br>다른 여자들을 보며 웃어 해맑게 <br>잘 지내지 뭐 어떡해 <br>Now you wanna comeback <br>But I ain’t got no time for that <br>Cuz everything is better <br>끌리는 대로 끌리는 대로 <br>It’s alright alright <br>I don’t even need you <br>끌리는 대로 끌리는 대로 <br>It’s alright alright <br>다 지나가니 <br>I’m all good without you <br>I’m all good without you <br>I’m all good without you <br>I’m all good <br>I don’t even need you <br>I’m all good 벗어나 감옥 <br>Without you 즐기지 환호 <br>I’m all good 벗어나 감옥 <br>Without you I ain’t got no <br>problems <br>나는 괜찮아 시간 지나니 <br>불필요해 너와의 Time <br>I don’t need no apology <br>다른 품으로 떠나 <br>부재중인 나의 Phone Phone Phone <br>원위치 된 나의 Home Home Home <br>Cuz everything is better <br>끌리는 대로 끌리는 대로 <br>It’s alright alright <br>I don’t even need you <br>끌리는 대로 끌리는 대로 <br>It’s alright alright <br>다 지나가니 <br>I’m all good without you <br>I’m all good without you <br>I’m all good without you <br>I’m all good <br>I don’t even need you <br>It’s alright <br>Cuz I don’t even need you <br>It’s alright It’s alright <br>Know that I don’t even need you <br>]]></content><category term="헨리 (HENRY)" label="헨리 (HENRY)"/><category term="끌리는 대로 (I`m good) (Feat. nafla)" label="끌리는 대로 (I`m good) (Feat. nafla)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sheppard/Edge_Of_The_Night/</id><title>Sheppard - Edge Of The Night - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:07:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:07:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sheppard/Edge_Of_The_Night/" title="Sheppard - Edge Of The Night - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1] <br>Fifteen to five, another Friday afternoon <br>Watching the weekend creeping closer into view <br>Eye of the Tiger on the highway home to you <br>Home to you, home to you, home to you <br>[Pre-Chorus] <br>Don't tell me you can't find time to party <br>I don't wanna hear that damn excuse <br>Baby if we can't go find a party <br>Guess we'll have to make one here for two <br>[Chorus] <br>Milk and Honey, sunny delight <br>I wanna take you on a <br>Street safari party alright <br>Into the wild jungle <br>Ooh-ooh if you ain't scared of the fall <br>We'll be hanging off the edge of the night, alright <br>Supernova galaxy kiss <br>I wanna take you on a <br>Street safari party like this <br>Into the wild jungle <br>Ooh-ooh if you ain't scared of the fall <br>We'll be hanging off the edge of the night, alright <br>[Verse 2] <br>Fifteen to five, another sunrise next to you <br>I spent my pay check now there's nothing left to lose <br>Watching the ocean from a blanket on the roof <br>On the roof, on the roof, on the roof <br>[Pre-Chorus] <br>Don't tell me you can't find time to party <br>I don't wanna hear that damn excuse <br>Baby if we can't go find a party <br>Guess we'll have to make one here for two <br>[Chorus] <br>Milk and Honey, sunny delight <br>I wanna take you on a <br>Street safari party alright <br>Into the wild jungle <br>Ooh-ooh if you ain't scared of the fall <br>We'll be hanging off the edge of the night, alright <br>Supernova galaxy kiss <br>I wanna take you on a <br>Street safari party like this <br>Into the wild jungle <br>Ooh-ooh if you ain't scared of the fall <br>We'll be hanging off the edge of the night, alright <br>[Bridge] <br>So wake up the neighbors <br>Sleep is overrated <br>Jump on it and shake it <br>Baby you're my favorite <br>Go wake up on the neighbors <br>Sleep is overrated <br>Jump on it and shake it <br>Baby you're my favorite <br>[Chorus] <br>Milk and Honey, sunny delight <br>I wanna take you on a <br>Street safari party alright <br>Into the wild jungle <br>Ooh-ooh if you ain't scared of the fall <br>We'll be hanging off the edge of the night, alright <br>Supernova galaxy kiss <br>I wanna take you on a <br>Street safari party like this <br>Into the wild jungle <br>Ooh-ooh if you ain't scared of the fall <br>We'll be hanging off the edge of the night, alright]]></content><category term="Sheppard" label="Sheppard"/><category term="Edge Of The Night" label="Edge Of The Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비프리_B-Free/Final_Destination/</id><title>비프리 (B-Free) - Final Destination - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:09:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:09:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC_B-Free/Final_Destination/" title="비프리 (B-Free) - Final Destination - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[feel like can't no body stop me <br>마치 자동 조종 장치 <br>고장 난 것처럼 돌진 <br>그냥 난 계속해 돌진 <br>가끔은 피가 좀 말러 <br>가끔은 기가 좀 빨려 <br>근데 난 멈출 수 없어 <br>계속 또 달려 달려 <br>원하면 무조건 모두다 담아놔 <br>통장 또 비우고 다시 또 쌓아놔 <br>넌 집에서 시청해 드라마 <br>I gotta stack it up get up my <br>commas <br>지금 내 기분은 1등 <br>모두 내 뒤를 또 쫓지 <br>이걸 또 들으며 질투하는 <br>너네의 꼴은 또 꼴찌 <br>I've been up grinding <br>the whole week <br>I've been up grinding <br>the year <br>I've been up grinding <br>my whole life Keith처럼 찍어내 <br>공장 <br>내 앞에 덫을 나봐도 <br>날 잡을 수 없어 I'm free <br>내 기분 Keanu reeves <br>멈출 수 없어 like speed <br>all about my won's dollar's <br>난 게으른 애들관 달러 <br>we ain't got nothing in common <br>오늘도 달려 또 달려 <br>feel like i'm on autopilot <br>뛰다가 지치면 날어 <br>on my mufucking high horse <br>아무도 나를 못 말려 <br>racing racing racing <br>to my final destination <br>racing racing racing <br>to my final destination <br>racing racing racing <br>to my final destination <br>racing racing racing <br>to my final destination <br>feel like can't no body stop me <br>너무 빨라 마치 like sonic <br>too hot yeah like a comat <br>fuck your 2 cents fuck <br>and all your comments <br>멈출 수 없어 고장났지 <br>break break <br>yeah you know the name <br>free <br>yeah you know the name free <br>몰라도 아는척해 <br>fuck your respect i need the check <br>난 그냥 달리고 땡기고 <br>챙길거 챙기고 jet <br>난 영원한 유망주 <br>불타 마치 휘발유 <br>내 손목과 목에는 은하수 <br>항상 난 물속에 지하수 <br>아무리 내욕을 해도 <br>지옥에 도착할 때까지 <br>못 끄지 시동 <br>부산 공연 늦었어 밟어 <br>시속 240 킬로 <br>rocking that off white vlone <br>난 절대로 못 느껴 피로 <br>실패를 해도 또 시도 <br>위로 또 위로 또 위로 <br>what the fuck is a rafe <br>I just wanna by bapes <br>I got a iphone 6 <br>i don't need no i8 <br>bitch this race you runnin <br>in place <br>This aint no game <br>i dont play <br>all about my won's dollar's <br>난 게으른 애들관 달러 <br>we ain't got nothing in common <br>오늘도 달려 또 달려 <br>feel like i'm on autopilot <br>뛰다가 지치면 날어 <br>on my mufucking high horse <br>아무도 나를 못 말려 <br>racing racing racing <br>to my final destination <br>racing racing racing <br>to my final destination <br>racing racing racing <br>to my final destination <br>racing racing racing <br>to my final <br>]]></content><category term="비프리 (B-Free)" label="비프리 (B-Free)"/><category term="Final Destination" label="Final Destination"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코난_로코베리/여름비/</id><title>코난 (로코베리) - 여름비 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:09:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:09:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%82%9C_%EB%A1%9C%EC%BD%94%EB%B2%A0%EB%A6%AC/%EC%97%AC%EB%A6%84%EB%B9%84/" title="코난 (로코베리) - 여름비 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여름비가 또 내리네 흩어지네 <br>외로운 이날 <br>우산 그 끝에 <br>빗방울이 맺혀지던 추억 <br>비가 내리면 <br>그대에게 전화를 또 걸겠어요 <br>그대 나에게 어떤 말이라도 해줘요 <br>지금 이 비가 또 그치면 사라질까요 <br>내게 돌아와줘요 <br>창문 밖에 쏟아지는 비를 보면 <br>거리에 나가 <br>사람들은 어디로 <br>향해 가는지 모르지만 <br>비가 내리면 <br>그대에게 전화를 또 걸겠어요 <br>그대 나에게 어떤 말이라도 해줘요 <br>지금 이 비가 또 그치면 사라질까요 <br>내게 돌아와줘요 <br>오늘밤 비가 내리네 <br>그대는 오지 않고 <br>빗물이 나를 적시네 <br>슬프도록 우우우 그대여 <br>내게 돌아와줘요 <br>그댄 나만의 사랑 <br>이 비가 그치는 날엔 <br>]]></content><category term="코난 (로코베리)" label="코난 (로코베리)"/><category term="여름비" label="여름비"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Club_8/Lost/</id><title>Club 8 - Lost - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:09:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:09:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Club_8/Lost/" title="Club 8 - Lost - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We wait a long time <br>We wait a long time <br>We wait a long time <br>It’s been a long time <br>Feelings can get lost <br>while we are waiting <br>Feelings can get lost <br>while we are waiting <br>Feelings can get lost <br>while we are waiting <br>Feelings can get lost <br>We wait a long time <br>A love forsaken <br>We wait a long time <br>My love forsaken heart <br>We wait a long time <br>A love forsaken <br>It’s been a long time <br>]]></content><category term="Club 8" label="Club 8"/><category term="Lost" label="Lost"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조수진/다함없는_그_사랑/</id><title>조수진 - 다함없는 그 사랑 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:10:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:10:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%88%98%EC%A7%84/%EB%8B%A4%ED%95%A8%EC%97%86%EB%8A%94_%EA%B7%B8_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="조수진 - 다함없는 그 사랑 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[4시 40분 첫 차의 눈을 감으면 <br>내 영혼의 흘리는 핏방울 <br>무감각을 배워가는 내 영혼 <br>떨어지는 내 영혼 <br>눈을 감아야 주의 영광 <br>귀를 닫아야 그 음성이 <br>그 끝에 들리네 <br>주님 계시네 영광의 길 <br>그 길 끝에 내가 있네 <br>깨닫기를 원해 그 사랑 예수 <br>의와 승리의 주님 <br>깨닫기를 원해 그 사랑 예수 <br>다함 없는 그 사랑 <br>4시 40분 첫 차의 눈을 감으면 <br>내 영혼의 흘리는 핏방울 <br>무감각을 배워가는 내 영혼 <br>떨어지는 내 영혼 <br>눈을 감아야 주의 영광 <br>귀를 닫아야 그 음성이 <br>그 끝에 들리네 <br>주님 계시네 영광의 길 <br>그 길 끝에 내가 있네 <br>깨닫기를 원해 그 사랑 예수 <br>의와 승리의 주님 <br>깨닫기를 원해 그 사랑 예수 <br>다함 없는 그 사랑 <br>깨닫기를 원해 그 사랑 예수 <br>의와 승리의 주님 <br>깨닫기를 원해 그 사랑 예수 <br>다함 없는 그 사랑 <br>깨닫기를 원해 그 사랑 예수 <br>의와 승리의 주님 <br>깨닫기를 원해 그 사랑 예수 <br>다함 없는 그 사랑 <br>다함 없는 그 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="조수진" label="조수진"/><category term="다함없는 그 사랑" label="다함없는 그 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로니_추_Ronny_Chu/Be_The_One_Inst/</id><title>로니 추 (Ronny Chu) - Be The One (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:11:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:11:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%8B%88_%EC%B6%94_Ronny_Chu/Be_The_One_Inst/" title="로니 추 (Ronny Chu) - Be The One (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[담담한 척 괜찮다 했어 <br>어쩔 수 없잖아 위로했지 <br>지쳐버린 내 하루는 <br>쉽게 잠에 못 들어 <br>꿈뻑꿈뻑 오늘 밤도 I say <br>Be the one that you wanted to be <br>Don't be the one that you're told to be <br>오늘도 내일도 그 모레도 <br>Don't waste it but face it <br>Never hesitate <br>몇 번이고 일어서기엔 <br>오늘의 나는 겁쟁이인가 봐 <br>고꾸라질 때의 쓰라림 오 눈물이 뚝 <br>아물지 않은 어제의 나는 어떡해 <br>굳은 살이 생겼음 해 I say <br>Be the one that you wanted to be <br>Don't be the one that you're told to be <br>오늘도 내일도 그 모레도 <br>Don't waste it but face it <br>Never hesitate <br>꾸불꾸불하기만 한 나의 삶 <br>한숨 또 두 숨 땅이 꺼져라 쉬지만 <br>울퉁불퉁 넘어져도 괜찮아 <br>Cause life is a journey <br>go surf 'round the world <br>비록 상처투성이지만 <br>오르막길 비탈길 상관없어 <br>오늘도 내일도 그 모레도 <br>누가 뭐래도 난 나 하고픈 대로 <br>Be the one that you wanted to be <br>Don't be the one that you're told to be <br>오늘도 내일도 그 모레도 <br>Don't waste it but face it <br>Never hesitate <br>나나나나나 나나나나나 <br>나나나나나 나나나나 <br>나나나나나 나나나나나 <br>나나나나나 나나나나 <br>오오 <br>나나나나나 나나나나나 <br>나나나나나 나나나나 <br>나나나나나 나나나나나 <br>나나나나나 나나나나 나 <br>]]></content><category term="로니 추 (Ronny Chu)" label="로니 추 (Ronny Chu)"/><category term="Be The One (Inst.)" label="Be The One (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/로니_추_Ronny_Chu/Be_The_One/</id><title>로니 추 (Ronny Chu) - Be The One - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:11:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:11:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A1%9C%EB%8B%88_%EC%B6%94_Ronny_Chu/Be_The_One/" title="로니 추 (Ronny Chu) - Be The One - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[담담한 척 괜찮다 했어 <br>어쩔 수 없잖아 위로했지 <br>지쳐버린 내 하루는 <br>쉽게 잠에 못 들어 <br>꿈뻑꿈뻑 오늘 밤도 I say <br>Be the one that you wanted to be <br>Don't be the one that you're told to be <br>오늘도 내일도 그 모레도 <br>Don't waste it but face it <br>Never hesitate <br>몇 번이고 일어서기엔 <br>오늘의 나는 겁쟁이인가 봐 <br>고꾸라질 때의 쓰라림 오 눈물이 뚝 <br>아물지 않은 어제의 나는 어떡해 <br>굳은 살이 생겼음 해 I say <br>Be the one that you wanted to be <br>Don't be the one that you're told to be <br>오늘도 내일도 그 모레도 <br>Don't waste it but face it <br>Never hesitate <br>꾸불꾸불하기만 한 나의 삶 <br>한숨 또 두 숨 땅이 꺼져라 쉬지만 <br>울퉁불퉁 넘어져도 괜찮아 <br>Cause life is a journey <br>go surf 'round the world <br>비록 상처투성이지만 <br>오르막길 비탈길 상관없어 <br>오늘도 내일도 그 모레도 <br>누가 뭐래도 난 나 하고픈 대로 <br>Be the one that you wanted to be <br>Don't be the one that you're told to be <br>오늘도 내일도 그 모레도 <br>Don't waste it but face it <br>Never hesitate <br>나나나나나 나나나나나 <br>나나나나나 나나나나 <br>나나나나나 나나나나나 <br>나나나나나 나나나나 <br>오오 <br>나나나나나 나나나나나 <br>나나나나나 나나나나 <br>나나나나나 나나나나나 <br>나나나나나 나나나나 나 <br>]]></content><category term="로니 추 (Ronny Chu)" label="로니 추 (Ronny Chu)"/><category term="Be The One" label="Be The One"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피망씨/사랑_배우기_Inst/</id><title>피망씨 - 사랑 배우기 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:11:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:11:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EB%A7%9D%EC%94%A8/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_%EB%B0%B0%EC%9A%B0%EA%B8%B0_Inst/" title="피망씨 - 사랑 배우기 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 느낌 무얼까 <br>코끝이 짜릿짜릿 <br>애꿎은 입술은 바짝 <br>이 기분 무얼까 <br>심장이 콩닥콩닥 <br>가슴은 두근 두근 두근 <br>야릇한 느낌 무얼까 <br>조금씩 조금씩 네게로 다가가는 <br>닿을 듯 닿을 듯 내게로 다가오는 <br>나 낯설기만 해 <br>수줍기만 해 <br>더 서툴기만 해 <br>한 걸음 한 걸음 천천히 다가갈게 <br>아직은 아직은 사랑에 배울 게 많아 <br>좋아한달 말 <br>사랑한단 말 <br>늘 혼잣말처럼 되뇌이곤 해 <br>내가 왜 이럴까 <br>행여나 마주치면 <br>모른 척 피하는 난 바보 <br>괜스레 머리만 긁적 <br>조금씩 조금씩 네게로 다가가는 <br>닿을 듯 닿을 듯 내게로 다가오는 <br>나 낯설기만 해 <br>수줍기만 해 <br>더 서툴기만 해 <br>한 걸음 한 걸음 천천히 다가갈게 <br>아직은 아직은 사랑에 배울 게 많아 <br>좋아한단 말 <br>사랑한단 말 <br>늘 혼잣말처럼 <br>조금씩 조금씩 내게로 다가와 줘 <br>닿을 듯 닿을 듯 내게로 다가와줘 제발 <br>좋아한단 말 <br>사랑한단 말 <br>늘 혼잣말처럼 되뇌이곤 해 <br>나 아직 사랑을 몰라 <br>]]></content><category term="피망씨" label="피망씨"/><category term="사랑 배우기 (Inst.)" label="사랑 배우기 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/피망씨/사랑_배우기/</id><title>피망씨 - 사랑 배우기 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:11:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:11:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%BC%EB%A7%9D%EC%94%A8/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_%EB%B0%B0%EC%9A%B0%EA%B8%B0/" title="피망씨 - 사랑 배우기 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 느낌 무얼까 <br>코끝이 짜릿짜릿 <br>애꿎은 입술은 바짝 <br>이 기분 무얼까 <br>심장이 콩닥콩닥 <br>가슴은 두근 두근 두근 <br>야릇한 느낌 무얼까 <br>조금씩 조금씩 네게로 다가가는 <br>닿을 듯 닿을 듯 내게로 다가오는 <br>나 낯설기만 해 <br>수줍기만 해 <br>더 서툴기만 해 <br>한 걸음 한 걸음 천천히 다가갈게 <br>아직은 아직은 사랑에 배울 게 많아 <br>좋아한달 말 <br>사랑한단 말 <br>늘 혼잣말처럼 되뇌이곤 해 <br>내가 왜 이럴까 <br>행여나 마주치면 <br>모른 척 피하는 난 바보 <br>괜스레 머리만 긁적 <br>조금씩 조금씩 네게로 다가가는 <br>닿을 듯 닿을 듯 내게로 다가오는 <br>나 낯설기만 해 <br>수줍기만 해 <br>더 서툴기만 해 <br>한 걸음 한 걸음 천천히 다가갈게 <br>아직은 아직은 사랑에 배울 게 많아 <br>좋아한단 말 <br>사랑한단 말 <br>늘 혼잣말처럼 <br>조금씩 조금씩 내게로 다가와 줘 <br>닿을 듯 닿을 듯 내게로 다가와줘 제발 <br>좋아한단 말 <br>사랑한단 말 <br>늘 혼잣말처럼 되뇌이곤 해 <br>나 아직 사랑을 몰라 <br>]]></content><category term="피망씨" label="피망씨"/><category term="사랑 배우기" label="사랑 배우기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastille/Glory/</id><title>Bastille - Glory - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:13:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:13:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bastille/Glory/" title="Bastille - Glory - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Deep in a corner <br>of the night <br>We were lying <br>in the middle of the road <br>Counting the planes <br>as they flew by <br>Inconceivable imagining them go <br>And drunk we set the world to rights <br>As we fell and hit our heads <br>upon the curb <br>You make me laugh <br>until I die <br>Can you think <br>of any better way to choke <br>Stories told to me <br>and stories told to you <br>And did you ever feel <br>like they were ringing true <br>And all their words for glory <br>Well they always sounded empty <br>When we're looking up for heaven <br>Looking up for heaven <br>And way down here <br>upon the ground <br>When we're lying in the dirt <br>There's no looking up for heaven <br>Looking up for heaven <br>Not everything had gone to plan <br>But we made the best <br>of what we had <br>you know <br>Passing the drink <br>from hand to hand <br>We admit we really know <br>nothing at all <br>Stories told to me <br>and stories told to you <br>And was it feeling real <br>and were they ringing true <br>And all their words for glory <br>Well they always sounded empty <br>When we're looking up for heaven <br>Looking up for heaven <br>And way down here <br>upon the ground <br>When we're lying in the dirt <br>There's no looking up for heaven <br>Looking up for heaven <br>I'll take my chances <br>on the curb here with you <br>We watched the planes <br>leave us behind <br>On the curb here with you <br>We watched the planes <br>leave us behind <br>And then you put your <br>hand in mine <br>And pulled me back <br>from things divine <br>Stop looking up for heaven <br>waiting to be buried <br>And all their words for glory <br>Well they always sounded empty <br>When we're looking up for heaven <br>Looking up for heaven <br>And way down here <br>upon the ground <br>When we're lying in the dirt <br>There's no looking up for heaven <br>Looking up <br>]]></content><category term="Bastille" label="Bastille"/><category term="Glory" label="Glory"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/와인루프_Wine_Loop/로맨스_시즌_Inst/</id><title>와인루프 (Wine Loop) - 로맨스 시즌 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:14:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:14:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%80%EC%9D%B8%EB%A3%A8%ED%94%84_Wine_Loop/%EB%A1%9C%EB%A7%A8%EC%8A%A4_%EC%8B%9C%EC%A6%8C_Inst/" title="와인루프 (Wine Loop) - 로맨스 시즌 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘따라 왠지 기분이 좋아 <br>무슨 일이 생길까 <br>매일 걷던 이 거리가 설레이는 건 <br>단지 너 때문인 걸까 <br>날 바라봤을 때 <br>네가 날 바라볼 땐 <br>아무 생각 없이 그냥 멍해져 <br>내게 눈웃음칠 때 <br>웃으며 얘길 할 땐 <br>시간이 멈춘 것 같아 <br>사실은 나 <br>너 땜에 그래 적응이 안 돼 <br>별다를 것 없던 나의 하루가 <br>난 special 해 넌 fresh 해 <br>그저 그런 설렘이라는 단어에 <br>흘러가는 romance <br>이젠 없을 줄 알았던 감정에 <br>다시 봄이 온 걸까 <br>상처받은 기억이 희미해지는 건 <br>왠지 너 때문인 걸까 <br>내 옆에 있을 때 <br>네가 옆에 있을 땐 <br>마냥 웃게 되는 내가 신기해 <br>너와 길을 걸을 때 <br>네 손을 잡고 걸을 땐 <br>세상이 멈춘 것 같아 <br>사실은 나 <br>너 땜에 그래 적응이 안 돼 <br>별다를 것 없던 나의 하루가 <br>난 special 해 넌 fresh 해 <br>그저 그런 설렘이라는 단어에 <br>흘러가는 romance <br>이제는 나 <br>우리의 계절을 기억할래 <br>별다를 것 없던 나의 계절이 <br>넌 special 해 난 fresh 해 <br>보고 싶은 설렘이라는 단어에 <br>기다려온 romance <br>]]></content><category term="와인루프 (Wine Loop)" label="와인루프 (Wine Loop)"/><category term="로맨스 시즌 (Inst.)" label="로맨스 시즌 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/와인루프_Wine_Loop/로맨스_시즌/</id><title>와인루프 (Wine Loop) - 로맨스 시즌 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:14:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:14:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%80%EC%9D%B8%EB%A3%A8%ED%94%84_Wine_Loop/%EB%A1%9C%EB%A7%A8%EC%8A%A4_%EC%8B%9C%EC%A6%8C/" title="와인루프 (Wine Loop) - 로맨스 시즌 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘따라 왠지 기분이 좋아 <br>무슨 일이 생길까 <br>매일 걷던 이 거리가 설레이는 건 <br>단지 너 때문인 걸까 <br>날 바라봤을 때 <br>네가 날 바라볼 땐 <br>아무 생각 없이 그냥 멍해져 <br>내게 눈웃음칠 때 <br>웃으며 얘길 할 땐 <br>시간이 멈춘 것 같아 <br>사실은 나 <br>너 땜에 그래 적응이 안 돼 <br>별다를 것 없던 나의 하루가 <br>난 special 해 넌 fresh 해 <br>그저 그런 설렘이라는 단어에 <br>흘러가는 romance <br>이젠 없을 줄 알았던 감정에 <br>다시 봄이 온 걸까 <br>상처받은 기억이 희미해지는 건 <br>왠지 너 때문인 걸까 <br>내 옆에 있을 때 <br>네가 옆에 있을 땐 <br>마냥 웃게 되는 내가 신기해 <br>너와 길을 걸을 때 <br>네 손을 잡고 걸을 땐 <br>세상이 멈춘 것 같아 <br>사실은 나 <br>너 땜에 그래 적응이 안 돼 <br>별다를 것 없던 나의 하루가 <br>난 special 해 넌 fresh 해 <br>그저 그런 설렘이라는 단어에 <br>흘러가는 romance <br>이제는 나 <br>우리의 계절을 기억할래 <br>별다를 것 없던 나의 계절이 <br>넌 special 해 난 fresh 해 <br>보고 싶은 설렘이라는 단어에 <br>기다려온 romance <br>]]></content><category term="와인루프 (Wine Loop)" label="와인루프 (Wine Loop)"/><category term="로맨스 시즌" label="로맨스 시즌"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pharrell_Williams/Despicable_Me/</id><title>Pharrell Williams - Despicable Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:14:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:14:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pharrell_Williams/Despicable_Me/" title="Pharrell Williams - Despicable Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm having a bad bad day <br>Its about time that I get my way <br>Steam rolling whatever I see, huh <br>Despicable me <br>I’m having a bad bad day <br>If you take it personal thats ok <br>Watch this is so fun to see, huh <br>Despicable me <br><br>Why ask why better yet why not <br>Why are you marking x on that spot <br>Why use a blow torch isn’t that hot <br>Why use a chainsaw is that all you got <br>Why do you like seeing people in shock <br>But my question to you is why not <br>Why go to the bank and stand in line <br>Just use a freeze gun it saves me time <br><br>Im having a bad bad day <br>Its about time that I get my way <br>Steam rolling whatever I see, huh <br>Despicable me <br>I’m having a bad bad day <br>If you take it personal thats ok <br>Watch this is so fun to see, huh <br>Despicable me <br><br>Why ask why when this is art <br>Why parallel when I can just park <br>Why does Vector think that he’s smart <br>And does his dad know I know his part <br>Why did I have to live with my mom <br>Why do you think that I should be calm <br>Why want the moon, the World's in my palm <br><br>Is it crazy you think I’ve gone <br><br>Im having a bad bad day <br>Its about time that I get my way <br>Steam rolling whatever I see, huh <br>Despicable me <br>I’m having a bad bad day <br>If you take it personal thats ok <br>Watch this is so fun to see, huh <br>Despicable me <br><br>Excuse me if you will <br>You look like you have time to kill <br>Can you chill <br>Cause Gru Got the speakers and the trunk to make you <br>Bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce <br>To make you bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce <br><br>Im having a bad bad day <br>Its about time that I get my way <br>Steam rolling whatever I see, huh <br>Despicable me <br>I’m having a bad bad day <br>If you take it personal thats ok <br>Watch this is so fun to see, huh <br>Despicable me <br><br>Despicable me, despicable me <br>Despicable me, despicable me <br>Despicable me, despicable me <br>Despicable me, despicable me <br><br>Im having a bad bad day <br>Its about time that I get my way <br>Steam rolling whatever I see, huh <br>Despicable me <br>I’m having a bad bad day <br>If you take it personal thats ok <br>Watch this is so fun to see, huh <br>Despicable me]]></content><category term="Pharrell Williams" label="Pharrell Williams"/><category term="Despicable Me" label="Despicable Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/UseMind/Wonderful_Life/</id><title>UseMind - Wonderful Life - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:14:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:14:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/UseMind/Wonderful_Life/" title="UseMind - Wonderful Life - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[발길 닿는 대로 <br>너와 내가 움직여 <br>숨막히는 이곳을 떠나 <br>그대를 향해서 <br>아직 깨지 못한 <br>내 안에 틀을 <br>모두 깨부셔 <br>나를 깨부셔 <br>내 손끝발끝털끝 <br>내 몸과 맘과 내 눈끝 <br>내 낮과 밤은 <br>저 땅끝을 향해 걸어 <br>문을 열어 <br>날 막으려는 것들 <br>날 방어하는 것들 <br>모두 방해 방해 방해 <br>wonderful life <br>baby <br>open your eyes <br>wonderful life <br>baby <br>i'm dreamer <br>dream <br>발길 닿는 대로 <br>너와 내가 움직여 <br>사람들 모두 향해가는 길 <br>반대로 <br>아직 깨지 못한 <br>내 안에 틀을 <br>모두 깨부셔 <br>나를 깨부셔 <br>눈을 감고 떠오르는 모든 것들을 <br>꺼내볼 수 있게 <br>표현할 수 있게 <br>눈을 감고 떠오르는 모든 것들을 <br>너에게 전해 <br>너에게 전해 <br>wonderful life <br>baby <br>open your eyes <br>wonderful life <br>baby <br>i'm dreamer <br>dream <br>i love my self <br>i love my self <br>i love my self <br>i love my self <br>]]></content><category term="UseMind" label="UseMind"/><category term="Wonderful Life" label="Wonderful Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/5T/Thats_Dope_Inst/</id><title>5T - That`s Dope (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:14:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:14:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/5T/Thats_Dope_Inst/" title="5T - That`s Dope (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>that's dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>that's dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope <br>나를 보고 말해 솔직하게 나를 봐바 <br>그게 아냐 내 느낌을 느껴 봐바 <br>먼저 다가가지 않아 <br>모두 먼저 나를 따라 <br>ya 그래 난 class 가 달라 <br>또 어김없이 이른아침 담밸 물어 yo <br>또 매일 몰고 다녀 <br>my car name 트랜스 포머 yo <br>남들 하기 힘든 일을 <br>내가 대신하지 아바타 <br>그 말은 즉 누구도 안되 나와 비교가 <br>가치를 따지자면 가장 높은 순위야 <br>dope 이 노래 딱 네 스타일이야 <br>이 곡이 끝난 이후 기대 <br>다음 나의 level <br>거리를 다녀봐 <br>아무도 나를 모름 shit <br>낡은 조낄 입고 <br>매일 매일 돌아다녀 wide <br>날 애타게 기다리는 <br>전화가 울려 fire <br>가진거 하나 없어도 <br>버텼어 가오하나로 <br>택시를 잡아도 당연히 난 뒷자리로 <br>5T가 제네시스 타면 그거 cut it <br>바빠도 챙겨먹어 밥은 3분 커리 <br>거릴 걸어갈땐 비비크림 gold chain <br>내 목에 하나 없어 <br>그게 바로 나의 옥의티 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>that's dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>that's dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope <br>내가 어제 밤에 꾼 꿈속에도 <br>다른건 없어 또 시궁 창이었고 <br>그래서 랩을 하는중 나는 고민중 <br>어떻게 니들 머리속에 <br>날 알릴까 고민중 <br>준비했던 mixtape 반응 좃망 <br>듣는 새끼는 날 알아보는 친구만 <br>내 친구 모두 흙수저들 뿐이지만 <br>그새끼들 위해라도 <br>올라간다 저 위 정상 으로 <br>내 동네 용산 굳이 <br>알릴 필요따윈 없어 <br>재벌이 많이 살어 <br>정원이 딸린 집에서 <br>그들은 먼미래를 바라보며 살아 wa <br>난 또 하루만을 보며 살아 wa <br>상상하고 기대하고 기다리는 야망 <br>아마 내앞의 현실과는 너무나도 달라 <br>내일만 보고 계속가 달려 <br>여기까지 왔던 나 <br>이제 나 더 한날을 위해 <br>계속 가 멈추지 마 <br>이 노래 들어봐 솔직히 말해봐 <br>한방에 날수 있는 실력 가진 airline <br>누가 뭐래도 절반은 먹지 자신감 <br>난 나를 믿어 나만 믿어 <br>나는 나를 알어 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>that's dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>that's dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope <br>]]></content><category term="5T" label="5T"/><category term="That`s Dope (Inst.)" label="That`s Dope (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/5T/Tevolution/</id><title>5T - Tevolution - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:14:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:14:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/5T/Tevolution/" title="5T - Tevolution - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>now 나 오늘도 출근 돈 벌러 <br>어제 늦게까지 가사쓰니 좀 졸려 <br>그래서 먹어 피곤은 간땜에 우루 <br>덩치는 곰탱이다 손만들면 다 쫄려 <br>What I want to say <br>아이폰 안에 적어내 <br>서본론 건너뛰고 결관 상댈 폐기해 <br>내기해 내 승리에 <br>핸승에 돈을 걸어내 <br>타짜가 아니라면 뻔한 결과 <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>17년 첫 mixtape talking about me <br>싸클 파도타고 듣고 느낌점 <br>you got a bitch <br>소개해 내 이 존재감이 이바닥에 <br>가뭄에 콩나게 내리는 단비 <br>매일밤 그녈 침대위에서 다 처벌 <br>바위에 붙은 전복 <br>내 몽둥이로 따 먹어 <br>버릇없는 급식충 그들의 컨셉 <br>함부로 깝쳤다가 좃됨 <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>fuck that 쉴드를 제대로 쳐 막아내 <br>뭐든지 꺽어버려 <br>실리콘 넣은 니 콧대 <br>마저 누르진 않을께 <br>긴장해 늘 all day <br>새벽 6시 너 출근해 봐야지 군대 <br>억대 이게 울 엄마 빚 단위 <br>심장 따윈 못 팔아 <br>내 심정을 써 담으니 <br>그래 나는 없이 살아 왔어 <br>Half of my life 아직 18년 남았어 <br>클럽 아직 나도 입장 가능 내 나이 <br>쿨하게 주문 하고 돈은 각자 뿜빠이 <br>잘익은 김치년을 찾아보니 <br>웬 girl 이거 <br>죽순이만 피해 run away <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>fucking hater i'll be back <br>터미네이터 <br>날 보면 손을 올려 <br>내가 원하는 건 famous <br>살기위해 매일 일을 하고 돈을 벌어 <br>지원지진 않어 <br>가슴으로 때려 맞은 counter <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>Tevolution <br>]]></content><category term="5T" label="5T"/><category term="Tevolution" label="Tevolution"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/5T/Thats_Dope/</id><title>5T - That`s Dope - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:14:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:14:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/5T/Thats_Dope/" title="5T - That`s Dope - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>that's dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>that's dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope <br>나를 보고 말해 솔직하게 나를 봐바 <br>그게 아냐 내 느낌을 느껴 봐바 <br>먼저 다가가지 않아 <br>모두 먼저 나를 따라 <br>ya 그래 난 class 가 달라 <br>또 어김없이 이른아침 담밸 물어 yo <br>또 매일 몰고 다녀 <br>my car name 트랜스 포머 yo <br>남들 하기 힘든 일을 <br>내가 대신하지 아바타 <br>그 말은 즉 누구도 안되 나와 비교가 <br>가치를 따지자면 가장 높은 순위야 <br>dope 이 노래 딱 네 스타일이야 <br>이 곡이 끝난 이후 기대 <br>다음 나의 level <br>거리를 다녀봐 <br>아무도 나를 모름 shit <br>낡은 조낄 입고 <br>매일 매일 돌아다녀 wide <br>날 애타게 기다리는 <br>전화가 울려 fire <br>가진거 하나 없어도 <br>버텼어 가오하나로 <br>택시를 잡아도 당연히 난 뒷자리로 <br>5T가 제네시스 타면 그거 cut it <br>바빠도 챙겨먹어 밥은 3분 커리 <br>거릴 걸어갈땐 비비크림 gold chain <br>내 목에 하나 없어 <br>그게 바로 나의 옥의티 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>that's dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>that's dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope <br>내가 어제 밤에 꾼 꿈속에도 <br>다른건 없어 또 시궁 창이었고 <br>그래서 랩을 하는중 나는 고민중 <br>어떻게 니들 머리속에 <br>날 알릴까 고민중 <br>준비했던 mixtape 반응 좃망 <br>듣는 새끼는 날 알아보는 친구만 <br>내 친구 모두 흙수저들 뿐이지만 <br>그새끼들 위해라도 <br>올라간다 저 위 정상 으로 <br>내 동네 용산 굳이 <br>알릴 필요따윈 없어 <br>재벌이 많이 살어 <br>정원이 딸린 집에서 <br>그들은 먼미래를 바라보며 살아 wa <br>난 또 하루만을 보며 살아 wa <br>상상하고 기대하고 기다리는 야망 <br>아마 내앞의 현실과는 너무나도 달라 <br>내일만 보고 계속가 달려 <br>여기까지 왔던 나 <br>이제 나 더 한날을 위해 <br>계속 가 멈추지 마 <br>이 노래 들어봐 솔직히 말해봐 <br>한방에 날수 있는 실력 가진 airline <br>누가 뭐래도 절반은 먹지 자신감 <br>난 나를 믿어 나만 믿어 <br>나는 나를 알어 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>that's dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 말해 솔직하게 <br>말해 솔직하게 <br>that's dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope dope <br>dope <br>]]></content><category term="5T" label="5T"/><category term="That`s Dope" label="That`s Dope"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billion/파워_피플송_Power_People_Song_Inst/</id><title>Billion - 파워 피플송 (Power People Song) (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:14:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:14:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billion/%ED%8C%8C%EC%9B%8C_%ED%94%BC%ED%94%8C%EC%86%A1_Power_People_Song_Inst/" title="Billion - 파워 피플송 (Power People Song) (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Attention <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>세상을 바꾼 파워 피플 스토리 <br>에이브러햄 링컨 <br>흑인 노예를 해방시킨 <br>노예 해방의 아버지 <br>세종대왕 <br>나랃말싸미 <br>훈민정음을 창제한 <br>백성의 왕 <br>오프라 윈프리 <br>헬로우 에브리 원 <br>토크쇼의 여왕 <br>워런버핏 <br>20세기 가장 성공한 <br>현명한 가치 투자자 <br>이태석 신부 <br>아프리카 톤즈 브라스 밴드 <br>빠라 빠빠빠밤 <br>스티븐 호킹 <br>우주 물리학 위해 <br>루게릭병 물러가라 <br>마에스트로 정명훈 <br>클래식 음악 위의 한국인 <br>스티브 잡스 <br>Think Different <br>혁신의 아이콘 와이 피플 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>세상을 바꾼 파워 피플 스토리 <br>손정의 가난해도 꿈이 있어 <br>제인 구달 야생 침팬지는 내 친구 <br>리처드 파인만 <br>파인만 다이어그램 <br>철의 여인 마거릿 대처 <br>파스퇴르는 우유가 아냐 <br>미생물학 창시자 <br>위대한 영혼 마하트마 간디 <br>오드리 헵번 만인의 연인 <br>선행의 천사 <br>안토니오 가우디 천재 건축가 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>세상을 바꾼 파워 피플 스토리 <br>콧수염 찰리 채플린 무성 영화 <br>슬랩스틱 코미디는 내가 최고 <br>강철 왕 앤드루 카네기 <br>위대한 기부 왕 <br>코코 샤넬 20세기 패션 <br>해방 디자이너 <br>체 게바라 긴 머리칼 <br>검은 베레모 텁수룩한 턱수염 <br>혁명의 아이콘 <br>칭기즈 칸 몽골을 통일하고 <br>대정복의 시대를 열었어 <br>알버트 아인슈타인 <br>가장 영향력 있는 과학자 <br>하얀 머리 과학자 <br>안중근 만주 하얼빈 역 <br>이토 히로부미 <br>우리나라 침략하지마 <br>이순신 1592 임진왜란 <br>명량해전 노량해전 <br>모두모두 승리해 <br>와이 피플 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>세상을 바꾼 파워 피플 스토리 <br>신사임당 오만원권 초상화 <br>율곡 이이 어머니 <br>대한민국 임시 정부의 주석 김구 <br>이중섭 한국적인 세계의 화가 <br>흑인 인권 운동 넬슨 만델라 <br>마리 퀴리 여성 최초 노벨상 <br>도산 안창호 독립운동가 <br>정약용 발명의 천재 <br>윈스턴 처칠 <br>2차 세계대전 승리 <br>마더 테레사 <br>아름다운 봉사의 상징 <br>와이 피플 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>세상을 바꾼 파워 피플 스토리 <br>와이 피플 <br>]]></content><category term="Billion" label="Billion"/><category term="파워 피플송 (Power People Song) (Inst.)" label="파워 피플송 (Power People Song) (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billion/파워_피플송_Power_People_Song/</id><title>Billion - 파워 피플송 (Power People Song) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:14:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:14:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billion/%ED%8C%8C%EC%9B%8C_%ED%94%BC%ED%94%8C%EC%86%A1_Power_People_Song/" title="Billion - 파워 피플송 (Power People Song) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Attention <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>세상을 바꾼 파워 피플 스토리 <br>에이브러햄 링컨 <br>흑인 노예를 해방시킨 <br>노예 해방의 아버지 <br>세종대왕 <br>나랃말싸미 <br>훈민정음을 창제한 <br>백성의 왕 <br>오프라 윈프리 <br>헬로우 에브리 원 <br>토크쇼의 여왕 <br>워런버핏 <br>20세기 가장 성공한 <br>현명한 가치 투자자 <br>이태석 신부 <br>아프리카 톤즈 브라스 밴드 <br>빠라 빠빠빠밤 <br>스티븐 호킹 <br>우주 물리학 위해 <br>루게릭병 물러가라 <br>마에스트로 정명훈 <br>클래식 음악 위의 한국인 <br>스티브 잡스 <br>Think Different <br>혁신의 아이콘 와이 피플 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>세상을 바꾼 파워 피플 스토리 <br>손정의 가난해도 꿈이 있어 <br>제인 구달 야생 침팬지는 내 친구 <br>리처드 파인만 <br>파인만 다이어그램 <br>철의 여인 마거릿 대처 <br>파스퇴르는 우유가 아냐 <br>미생물학 창시자 <br>위대한 영혼 마하트마 간디 <br>오드리 헵번 만인의 연인 <br>선행의 천사 <br>안토니오 가우디 천재 건축가 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>세상을 바꾼 파워 피플 스토리 <br>콧수염 찰리 채플린 무성 영화 <br>슬랩스틱 코미디는 내가 최고 <br>강철 왕 앤드루 카네기 <br>위대한 기부 왕 <br>코코 샤넬 20세기 패션 <br>해방 디자이너 <br>체 게바라 긴 머리칼 <br>검은 베레모 텁수룩한 턱수염 <br>혁명의 아이콘 <br>칭기즈 칸 몽골을 통일하고 <br>대정복의 시대를 열었어 <br>알버트 아인슈타인 <br>가장 영향력 있는 과학자 <br>하얀 머리 과학자 <br>안중근 만주 하얼빈 역 <br>이토 히로부미 <br>우리나라 침략하지마 <br>이순신 1592 임진왜란 <br>명량해전 노량해전 <br>모두모두 승리해 <br>와이 피플 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>세상을 바꾼 파워 피플 스토리 <br>신사임당 오만원권 초상화 <br>율곡 이이 어머니 <br>대한민국 임시 정부의 주석 김구 <br>이중섭 한국적인 세계의 화가 <br>흑인 인권 운동 넬슨 만델라 <br>마리 퀴리 여성 최초 노벨상 <br>도산 안창호 독립운동가 <br>정약용 발명의 천재 <br>윈스턴 처칠 <br>2차 세계대전 승리 <br>마더 테레사 <br>아름다운 봉사의 상징 <br>와이 피플 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>피플 피플 피이오피엘이 <br>세상을 바꾼 파워 피플 스토리 <br>와이 피플 <br>]]></content><category term="Billion" label="Billion"/><category term="파워 피플송 (Power People Song)" label="파워 피플송 (Power People Song)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TENGGER/Breathe_In_Breathe_Out/</id><title>TENGGER - Breathe In, Breathe Out - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:14:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:14:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TENGGER/Breathe_In_Breathe_Out/" title="TENGGER - Breathe In, Breathe Out - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe in Breathe out <br>Breathe in Breathe out <br>Breathe in Breathe out <br>Breathe in Breathe out <br>Breathe in Breathe out <br>오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>]]></content><category term="TENGGER" label="TENGGER"/><category term="Breathe In, Breathe Out" label="Breathe In, Breathe Out"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TENGGER/Oneul/</id><title>TENGGER - Oneul - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:14:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:14:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TENGGER/Oneul/" title="TENGGER - Oneul - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>]]></content><category term="TENGGER" label="TENGGER"/><category term="Oneul" label="Oneul"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TENGGER/Kkum/</id><title>TENGGER - Kkum - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:14:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:14:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TENGGER/Kkum/" title="TENGGER - Kkum - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>]]></content><category term="TENGGER" label="TENGGER"/><category term="Kkum" label="Kkum"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TENGGER/Sora/</id><title>TENGGER - Sora - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TENGGER/Sora/" title="TENGGER - Sora - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>오늘이 오고 <br>숲이 눈앞에 <br>바다가 들려오고 <br>숨도 따라오고 <br>]]></content><category term="TENGGER" label="TENGGER"/><category term="Sora" label="Sora"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Madonna/Into_the_Groove/</id><title>Madonna - Into the Groove - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Madonna/Into_the_Groove/" title="Madonna - Into the Groove - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And you can dance for inspiration <br>Come on, I'm waiting <br><br>Get into the groove <br>Boy, you've got to prove <br>Your love to me, yeah <br>Get up on your feet <br>Yeah, step to the beat <br>Boy, what will it be <br><br>Music can be such a revelation <br>Dancing around, you feel the sweet sensation <br>We might be lovers if the rhythms right <br>I hope this feeling never ends tonight <br><br>Only when I'm dancing can I feel this free <br>At night, I lock the doors, where no one else can see <br>I'm tired of dancing here all by myself <br>Tonight, I want to dance with someone else <br><br>Get into the groove <br>Boy, you've got to prove <br>Your love to me, yeah <br>Get up on your feet <br>Yeah, step to the beat <br>Boy, what will it be <br><br>Gonna get to know you in a special way <br>This doesn't happen to me every day <br>Don't try to hide it, love wears no disguise <br>I see the fire burning in your eyes <br><br>Only when I'm dancing can I feel this free <br>At night I lock the doors, where no one else can see <br>I'm tired of dancing here all by myself <br>Tonight I want to dance with someone else <br><br>Get into the groove <br>Boy, you've got to prove <br>Your love to me, yeah <br>Get up on your feet <br>Yeah, step to the beat <br>Boy, what will it be <br><br>Live out your fantasy here with me <br>Just let the music set you free <br>Touch my body, and move in time <br>Now I now you're mine <br>Now I know you're mine, now I know you're mine <br>Now I know you're mine, now I know you're mine <br>You've got to <br><br>Get into the groove <br>Boy, you've got to prove <br>Your love to me, yeah <br>Get up on your feet <br>Yeah, step to the beat <br>Boy, what will it be <br><br>Only when I'm dancing can I feel this free <br>At night I lock the doors, where no one else can see <br>I'm tired of dancing here all by myself <br>Tonight I want to dance with someone else <br><br>Live out your fantasy here with me <br>Just let the music set you free <br>Touch my body, and move in time <br>Now I now you're mine <br><br>Get into the groove <br>Boy, you've got to prove <br>Your love to me, yeah <br>Get up on your feet <br>Yeah, step to the beat <br>Boy, what will it be <br>Get into the groove <br>Boy, you've got to prove <br>Your love to me, yeah <br>Get up on your feet <br>Yeah, step to the beat <br>Boy, what will it be]]></content><category term="Madonna" label="Madonna"/><category term="Into the Groove" label="Into the Groove"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nena/99_Luftballons/</id><title>Nena - 99 Luftballons - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nena/99_Luftballons/" title="Nena - 99 Luftballons - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hast Du etwas Zeit fur mich <br>Dann singe ich ein Lied fur Dich <br>Von 99 Luftballons <br>Auf ihrem Weg zum Horizont <br><br>Denkst Du vielleicht g'rad an mich <br>Dann singe ich einen Lied fur Dich <br>Von 99 Luftballons <br>Und dass so was von so was kommt <br><br>99 Luftballons <br>Auf ihrem Weg zum Horizont <br>Hielt man fur UFOs aus dem All <br>Darum schickte eine General <br><br>'Ne Fliegerstaffel hinterher <br>Alarm zu geben, wenn es so war <br>Dabei war'n da am Horizont <br>Nur 99 Luftballons <br><br>99 Dusenflieger <br>Jeder war ein grosser Krieger <br>Hielten sich fur Captain Kirk <br>Es gab ein grosses Feuerwerk <br><br>Die Nachbarn haben nichts gerafft <br>Und fuhlten sich gleich angemacht <br>Dabei schoss man am Horizont <br>Auf 99 Luftballons <br><br>99 Kriegsminister <br>Streichholz und Benzinkanister <br>Hielten sich fur schlaue Leute <br>Witterten schon fette Beute <br><br>Riefen, Krieg und wollten Macht <br>Mann, wer hatte das gedacht <br>Dass es einmal soweit kommt <br>Wegen 99 Luftballons <br><br>Wegen 99 Luftballons <br>99 Luftballons <br><br>99 Jahre Krieg <br>Liessen keinen Platz fur Sieger <br>Kriegsminister gibt's nicht mehr <br>Und auch keine Dusenflieger <br><br>Heute zieh' ich meine Runden <br>Seh die Welt in Trummern liegen <br>Hab 'n Luftballon gefunden <br>Denk' an Dich und lass' ihn fliegen]]></content><category term="Nena" label="Nena"/><category term="99 Luftballons" label="99 Luftballons"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박민주/나는_나비_Inst/</id><title>박민주 - 나는 나비 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EB%AF%BC%EC%A3%BC/%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84_Inst/" title="박민주 - 나는 나비 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 모습이 보이지 않아 <br>앞길도 보이지 않아 <br>나는 아주 작은 애벌레 <br>살이 터져 허물벗어 <br>한번 두번 다시 <br>나는 상처 많은 번데기 <br>추운 겨울이 다가와 <br>힘겨울지도 몰라 <br>봄바람이 불어오면 <br>이젠 나의 꿈을 찾아 날아 <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 <br>세상을 자유롭게 날꺼야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 <br>나는 아름다운 나비 <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 <br>세상을 자유롭게 날꺼야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 <br>나는 아름다운 나비 <br>거미줄을 피해 날아 <br>꽃을 찾아 날아 <br>사마귀를 피해 날아 <br>꽃을 찾아 날아 <br>꽃들의 사랑을 전하는 나비 <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 <br>세상을 자유롭게 날꺼야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 <br>나는 아름다운 나비 <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 <br>세상을 자유롭게 날꺼야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 <br>나는 아름다운 나비 <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 <br>세상을 자유롭게 날꺼야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 <br>나는 아름다운 나비 <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 <br>세상을 자유롭게 날꺼야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 <br>나는 아름다운 나비 <br>Spread my wings and fly away <br>Ride the wind sailing <br>on the world today <br>Sing a song reach for the sky <br>Flying butterfly God save me <br>I want to fly away <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 <br>세상을 자유롭게 날거야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 <br>나는 아름다운 나비 <br>]]></content><category term="박민주" label="박민주"/><category term="나는 나비 (Inst.)" label="나는 나비 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박민주/나는_나비/</id><title>박민주 - 나는 나비 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EB%AF%BC%EC%A3%BC/%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84/" title="박민주 - 나는 나비 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 모습이 보이지 않아 <br>앞길도 보이지 않아 <br>나는 아주 작은 애벌레 <br>살이 터져 허물벗어 <br>한번 두번 다시 <br>나는 상처 많은 번데기 <br>추운 겨울이 다가와 <br>힘겨울지도 몰라 <br>봄바람이 불어오면 <br>이젠 나의 꿈을 찾아 날아 <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 <br>세상을 자유롭게 날꺼야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 <br>나는 아름다운 나비 <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 <br>세상을 자유롭게 날꺼야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 <br>나는 아름다운 나비 <br>거미줄을 피해 날아 <br>꽃을 찾아 날아 <br>사마귀를 피해 날아 <br>꽃을 찾아 날아 <br>꽃들의 사랑을 전하는 나비 <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 <br>세상을 자유롭게 날꺼야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 <br>나는 아름다운 나비 <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 <br>세상을 자유롭게 날꺼야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 <br>나는 아름다운 나비 <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 <br>세상을 자유롭게 날꺼야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 <br>나는 아름다운 나비 <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 <br>세상을 자유롭게 날꺼야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 <br>나는 아름다운 나비 <br>Spread my wings and fly away <br>Ride the wind sailing <br>on the world today <br>Sing a song reach for the sky <br>Flying butterfly God save me <br>I want to fly away <br>날개를 활짝 펴고 <br>세상을 자유롭게 날거야 <br>노래하며 춤추는 <br>나는 아름다운 나비 <br>]]></content><category term="박민주" label="박민주"/><category term="나는 나비" label="나는 나비"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pharrell_Williams/Doowit/</id><title>Pharrell Williams - Doowit - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pharrell_Williams/Doowit/" title="Pharrell Williams - Doowit - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One more time, I gotta tell you now <br>One more time, tell you <br><br>We've been down together for so long <br>Solid and strong <br>The lights went on <br>Wasn't your memory you forgot about <br>When you were down and out <br>You left dirt in my mouth <br><br>I know you're probably saying "G" <br>I know you said it but woah, woah, woah <br>'Cause you really didn't believe <br>You didn't think that we would go, go, go <br><br>Well, don't you know what they say about the show <br>Well, even if you don't play, it must go on <br>You have decided to stay, you wanna be home <br>But don't take it no way, me and my bros <br>We just got to do it do it <br>Do it do it do it do it do it he-ya <br>One more time, we just got to do it do it <br>Do it do it do it do it do it he-ya <br>One more time, gotta tell you now <br><br>If I gotta do it alone, I will <br>Roll this boulder up this hill <br>Roll up my sleeves, no chill <br>Be rolling, you can sit still <br>More like family there were no bounds <br>We used to ride towns <br>And burn them all down <br><br>I know you're probably saying "G" <br>I know you said it but woah, woah, woah <br>'Cause you really didn't believe <br>You didn't think that we would go, go, go <br><br>Well, don't you know what they say about the show <br>Well, even if you don't play, it must go on <br>You have decided to stay, you wanna be home <br>But don't take it no way, me and my bros <br>We just got to do it do it <br>Do it do it do it do it do it he-ya <br>One more time, we just got to do it do it <br>Do it do it do it do it do it he-ya <br><br>Like most [] snowglobe <br>Distracted and confused <br>Gotta make yo' mind up <br>This is yours to lose <br>Things will always pop up <br>Like snowflakes they will move <br>I know that sounds real cold, but <br>What you gonna do <br>What you gonna do <br><br>Can't tell what two dudes not allow <br>You don't like crowds <br>But you gotta get out <br>You could change the world if you change your route <br>You gotta leave your house <br>Go outside out <br><br>I know you're probably saying "G" <br>I know you said it but woah, woah, woah <br>'Cause you really didn't believe <br>You didn't think that we would go, go, go <br><br>Well, don't you know what they say about the show <br>Well, even if you don't play, it must go on <br>You have decided to stay, you wanna be home <br>But don't take it no way, me and my bros <br>We just got to do it do it <br>Do it do it do it do it do it he-ya <br>One more time, we just got to do it do it <br>Do it do it do it do it do it he-ya <br>One more time, gotta tell you now]]></content><category term="Pharrell Williams" label="Pharrell Williams"/><category term="Doowit" label="Doowit"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Minions/Papa_Mama_Loca_Pipa/</id><title>The Minions - Papa Mama Loca Pipa - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Minions/Papa_Mama_Loca_Pipa/" title="The Minions - Papa Mama Loca Pipa - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pito pato milo mila taka tiki poulet tika <br>Cepa lajoi demitoka lana moule macarena <br>Pao lettus pabo pati mele cepa maka gusta <br>Mami lebel mela moustache ella pika muchaaa <br>Moka coca pila caca fissa bella lamassala <br>Papa mama loca pita pola gusta la rumbada <br>Chaipa koda mila toka bocca pis-sa la lasagnaaa <br>Kika la po maka bomba bella mira la bologna <br>Kika la po maka bomba bella mira la bologna <br>Kika la po maka bomba bella mira la bologna <br>Kika la po maka bomba bella mira la bolognaaaaa <br>Pito pato milo mila taka tiki poulet tika <br>Cepa lajoi demitoka lana moule macarena <br>Moka coca pila caca fissa bella lamassala <br>Papa mama loca pita pola gusta la rumbadaaa <br>Moka coca pila caca fissa bella lamassala <br>Papa mama loca pita pola gusta la rumbadaaa <br>Chaipa koda mila toka bocca pis-sa la lasagna <br>Chaipa koda mila toka bocca pis-sa la lasagna <br>Chaipa koda mila toka bocca pis-sa la lasagnaaa <br>Moka coca pila caca fissa bella lamassala <br>Papa mama loca pita pola gusta la rumbadaaa]]></content><category term="The Minions" label="The Minions"/><category term="Papa Mama Loca Pipa" label="Papa Mama Loca Pipa"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/A-ha/Take_On_Me/</id><title>A-ha - Take On Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/A-ha/Take_On_Me/" title="A-ha - Take On Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We're talking away <br>I don't know what <br>I'm to say I'll say it anyway <br>Today's another day to find you <br>Shying away <br>I'll be coming for your love, okay <br><br>Take on me, take on me <br>Take me on, take on me <br>I'll be gone <br>In a day or two <br><br>So needless to say <br>I'm odds and ends <br>I'll be stumbling away <br>Slowly learning that life is OK <br>Say after me <br>It's no better to be safe than sorry <br><br>Take on me, take on me <br>Take me on, take on me <br>I'll be gone <br>In a day or two <br><br>Oh the things that you say <br>Is it live or <br>Just to play my worries away <br>You're all the things I've got to remember <br>You're shying away <br>I'll be coming for you anyway <br><br>Take on me, take on me <br>Take me on, take on me <br>I'll be gone <br>In a day <br><br>I'll be gone take on me <br>In a day]]></content><category term="A-ha" label="A-ha"/><category term="Take On Me" label="Take On Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Jackson/Bad/</id><title>Michael Jackson - Bad - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Michael_Jackson/Bad/" title="Michael Jackson - Bad - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Your butt is mine <br>Gonna tell you right <br>Just show your face <br>In broad daylight <br>I'm telling you <br>On how I feel <br>Gonna hurt your mind <br>Don't shoot to kill <br>Come on <br><br>Come on <br>Lay it on me <br>All right <br><br>I'm giving you <br>On count of three <br>To show your stuff <br>Or let it be <br>I'm telling you <br>Just watch your mouth <br>I know your game <br>What you're about <br><br>Well they say the sky's the limit <br>And to me that's really true <br>But my friend you have seen nothin' <br>Just wait 'til I get through <br><br>Because I'm bad, I'm bad come on <br>You know I'm bad, I'm bad come on, you know <br>You know I'm bad, I'm bad come on, you know <br>And the whole world has to <br>Answer right now <br>Just to tell you once again <br>Who's bad <br><br>The word is out <br>You're doin' wrong <br>Gonna lock you up <br>Before too long <br>Your lyin' eyes <br>Gonna tell you right <br>So listen up <br>Don't make a fight <br>Your talk is cheap <br>You're not a man <br>You're throwin' stones <br>To hide your hands <br><br>But they say the sky's the limit <br>And to me that's really true <br>And my friends you have seen nothin' <br>Just wait 'til I get through <br><br>Because I'm bad, I'm bad come on <br>You know I'm bad, I'm bad come on, you know <br>You know I'm bad, I'm bad come on, you know <br>And the whole world has to <br>Answer right now <br>Just to tell you once again <br>Who's bad <br><br>We can change the world tomorrow <br>This could be a better place <br>If you don't like what I'm sayin' <br>Then won't you slap my face <br><br>Because I'm bad, I'm bad come on <br>You know I'm bad, I'm bad come on, you know <br>You know I'm bad, I'm bad come on, you know <br>And the whole world has to <br>Answer right now <br>Just to tell you once again <br>Who's bad <br><br>Because I'm bad, I'm bad come on <br>You know I'm bad, I'm bad come on, you know <br>You know I'm bad, I'm bad come on, you know <br>And the whole world has to <br>Answer right now <br>Just to tell you once again <br>Who's bad <br><br>Who's bad]]></content><category term="Michael Jackson" label="Michael Jackson"/><category term="Bad" label="Bad"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pharrell_Williams/Hug_Me/</id><title>Pharrell Williams - Hug Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pharrell_Williams/Hug_Me/" title="Pharrell Williams - Hug Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Why do you insist on trying to give me away <br>When they were too good and you wanted to shake them, who came <br><br>I was your dirty boy, your good, new secret toy <br>Show me how they get you joy who stayed in trouble with you <br>Oh, don't you want some more Come on, I think they're gone <br>Our part is coming on you're either with me or <br><br>Hug me bring it in <br>Won't you loosen up, won't ya <br>Hug me bring it in <br>I think they wanna take a picture <br><br>Wake up, you're sleeping on me, playing this stupid game <br>Why can't we flex on the world and make them say our name <br><br>Our favorite color's purple, we stay out past the curfew <br>My kung-fu grip will hurt you who stayed in trouble with you <br>You dyed your hair like me, black so everyone can see <br>Your parents couldn't believe you're either with me or <br><br>Hug me bring it in <br>Would ya loosen up Would ya <br>Hug me bring it in <br>I think they wanna take a picture <br><br>Oh would ya, would ya, would ya, would ya <br>Oh would ya, would ya, would ya <br>Oh would ya <br>Oh would ya, would ya loosen up, would ya <br>Oh would ya, would ya <br>Oh would ya, would ya <br>Oh would ya, would ya <br>Would ya wanna take a picture <br><br>Hug me bring it in <br>Would ya loosen up Would ya <br>Hug me bring it in <br>I think they wanna take a picture <br>Hug me bring it in <br>Would ya loosen up Would ya <br>Hug me bring it in <br>I think they wanna take a picture]]></content><category term="Pharrell Williams" label="Pharrell Williams"/><category term="Hug Me" label="Hug Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/해변의_파프리카/밥_Song/</id><title>해변의 파프리카 - 밥 Song - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%B4%EB%B3%80%EC%9D%98_%ED%8C%8C%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC%EC%B9%B4/%EB%B0%A5_Song/" title="해변의 파프리카 - 밥 Song - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[연두부 비빔밥 오징어 해물 밥 <br>곤드레 나물 재첩 비빔밥 <br>아보카도 초밥 양념치킨 볶음밥 <br>칠리소스 오징어 볶음밥 <br>멍게 비빔밥 연어 비빔밥 <br>두부 주먹밥 곤드레 밥 <br>김밥 김치볶음밥 짬뽕밥 <br>참치 양파 볶음밥 <br>장어덮밥 김치말이 주먹밥 <br>바지락 비빔밥 <br>굴 국밥 연어구이 덮밥 <br>참치 마파두부밥 <br>돼지 국밥 충무김밥 <br>열무 보리 비빔밥 <br>현미 콩나물밥 취나물 두부밥 <br>두부 소보로 땡초 주먹밥 <br>베이컨 볶음밥 참치 미역 볶음밥 <br>닭 가슴살 청국장 덮밥 <br>도토리 묵밥 돌솥비빔밥 <br>참치 회덮밥 제육덮밥 <br>김밥 김치볶음밥 짬뽕밥 <br>참치 양파 볶음밥 <br>장어덮밥 김치말이 주먹밥 <br>바지락 비빔밥 <br>굴 국밥 연어구이 덮밥 <br>참치 마파두부밥 <br>돼지 국밥 충무김밥 <br>열무 보리 비빔밥 <br>]]></content><category term="해변의 파프리카" label="해변의 파프리카"/><category term="밥 Song" label="밥 Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KayH/기억/</id><title>Kay.H - 기억 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/KayH/%EA%B8%B0%EC%96%B5/" title="Kay.H - 기억 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잊었던 추억 다시 돌아오고 있어 <br>이번엔 처음보단 조금 익숙해 <br>지키지 못한 많은 우리 약속들이 <br>아직도 날 아프게 하네 <br>별거 아닌 우리 사소한 <br>약속들이 내겐 <br>그렇게 작았었을까 <br>우리의 기억 다가오는 그날들이 <br>모두 흩어져 가고 있잖아 <br>혼자만 추억하긴 이제 힘들어 <br>우리 다시 해보면 어떨까 제발 <br>돌아오는 시간 속에 <br>갇힌 내 모습을 <br>너는 알고 있을까 <br>우리의 기억 다가오는 그날들이 <br>모두 흩어져 가고 있잖아 <br>혼자만 추억하긴 이제 힘들어 <br>우리 다시 해보면 어떨까 제발 <br>]]></content><category term="Kay.H" label="Kay.H"/><category term="기억" label="기억"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코드코즈_Chord_Coze/The_Best_Days/</id><title>코드코즈 (Chord Coze) - The Best Days - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%93%9C%EC%BD%94%EC%A6%88_Chord_Coze/The_Best_Days/" title="코드코즈 (Chord Coze) - The Best Days - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We don't have to cry <br>Never mind <br>We don't have to cry <br>We even have tomorrow <br>So I say <br>It'll be all right <br>Sometimes so cold <br>But I'm on your side <br>Forever forever and so <br>I believe that someday <br>all the way we got through <br>would be the best days in life <br>In our mind forever I know <br>We just have to try <br>to keep alive <br>We just have to try <br>Never let you down <br>So why don't <br>give yourself some smile <br>Sometimes so tired <br>But I will be right <br>behinds you forever and so <br>I believe in our life somehow <br>all the ways we got through <br>I believe <br>Would be the best days in life <br>In our mind oh best days in life <br>In life <br>Even if we can't make <br>do again just I'm on your side <br>I believe <br>In our life <br>I believe alright <br>So you never lose yourself <br>for that's what I love I love <br>And I know forever <br>]]></content><category term="코드코즈 (Chord Coze)" label="코드코즈 (Chord Coze)"/><category term="The Best Days" label="The Best Days"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엄국화/In_My_Heart_MR/</id><title>엄국화 - In My Heart (MR) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%84%EA%B5%AD%ED%99%94/In_My_Heart_MR/" title="엄국화 - In My Heart (MR) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무도 가지 않는 그 길에 <br>홀로 가시네 <br>아무도 듣지 않는 곳에서 <br>말씀 하시네 <br>누구도 알 수 없는 진실을 <br>짊어 지고 가시네 <br>모든 걸 바꿔 놓는 시간 <br>절대 놓칠 수 없어 <br>내 안에 끝없이 부르고 있어 <br>내 맘을 두드리고 있어 <br>날 부르고 있어 <br>홀로 남겨진 곳에서 <br>외롭다 느낄 때 <br>쓰리도록 아픈 상처로 <br>눈물 흘릴 때 <br>그 누가 알아 주지 않는 <br>나의 맘을 아시네 <br>상처뿐인 나의 마음을 <br>그가 치유 하시네 <br>내 안에 끝없이 부르고 있어 <br>내 맘을 두드리고 있어 <br>날 부르고 있어 <br>사랑의 언약으로 <br>끝없이 들려오는 <br>위대한 그 목소리 <br>내 맘에 울려 퍼져 <br>상처뿐인 내 눈물을 <br>은혜로 인도 하시네 <br>내 안에 끝없이 부르고 있어 <br>내 맘을 두드리고 있어 <br>날 부르고 있어 <br>내 안에 끝없이 부르고 있어 <br>내 맘을 두드리고 있어 <br>날 부르고 있어 <br>사랑의 언약으로 <br>끝없이 들려오는 <br>위대한 그 목소리 <br>내 맘에 울려 퍼져 <br>상처뿐인 내 눈물을 <br>은혜로 인도 하시네 <br>내 안에 끝없이 부르고 있어 <br>내 맘을 두드리고 있어 <br>날 부르고 있어 <br>]]></content><category term="엄국화" label="엄국화"/><category term="In My Heart (MR)" label="In My Heart (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엄국화/In_My_Heart/</id><title>엄국화 - In My Heart - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%84%EA%B5%AD%ED%99%94/In_My_Heart/" title="엄국화 - In My Heart - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무도 가지 않는 그 길에 <br>홀로 가시네 <br>아무도 듣지 않는 곳에서 <br>말씀 하시네 <br>누구도 알 수 없는 진실을 <br>짊어 지고 가시네 <br>모든 걸 바꿔 놓는 시간 <br>절대 놓칠 수 없어 <br>내 안에 끝없이 부르고 있어 <br>내 맘을 두드리고 있어 <br>날 부르고 있어 <br>홀로 남겨진 곳에서 <br>외롭다 느낄 때 <br>쓰리도록 아픈 상처로 <br>눈물 흘릴 때 <br>그 누가 알아 주지 않는 <br>나의 맘을 아시네 <br>상처뿐인 나의 마음을 <br>그가 치유 하시네 <br>내 안에 끝없이 부르고 있어 <br>내 맘을 두드리고 있어 <br>날 부르고 있어 <br>사랑의 언약으로 <br>끝없이 들려오는 <br>위대한 그 목소리 <br>내 맘에 울려 퍼져 <br>상처뿐인 내 눈물을 <br>은혜로 인도 하시네 <br>내 안에 끝없이 부르고 있어 <br>내 맘을 두드리고 있어 <br>날 부르고 있어 <br>내 안에 끝없이 부르고 있어 <br>내 맘을 두드리고 있어 <br>날 부르고 있어 <br>사랑의 언약으로 <br>끝없이 들려오는 <br>위대한 그 목소리 <br>내 맘에 울려 퍼져 <br>상처뿐인 내 눈물을 <br>은혜로 인도 하시네 <br>내 안에 끝없이 부르고 있어 <br>내 맘을 두드리고 있어 <br>날 부르고 있어 <br>]]></content><category term="엄국화" label="엄국화"/><category term="In My Heart" label="In My Heart"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이미향/즐거운_마음/</id><title>이미향 - 즐거운 마음 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%AF%B8%ED%96%A5/%EC%A6%90%EA%B1%B0%EC%9A%B4_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C/" title="이미향 - 즐거운 마음 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[즐거운 마음은 좋은 약이 되고 <br>마음의 근심은 뼈를 마르게 하니 <br>항상 기뻐하라 기뻐하라 <br>주 안에서 기뻐하라 기뻐하라 <br>즐거운 마음은 주님께로 오고 <br>모든 유혹을 이기게 하시니 <br>항상 기뻐하라 기뻐하라 <br>주 안에서 기뻐하라 기뻐하라 <br>믿음의 나무에서 열리는 과실같이 <br>즐거운 마음을 주시는 주님 <br>근심하는 자 같으나 <br>항상 기뻐하는 믿음의 삶 살게 하소서 <br>항상 기뻐하라 기뻐하라 <br>주 안에서 기뻐하라 기뻐하라 <br>항상 기뻐하라 기뻐하라 <br>주 안에서 기뻐하라 기뻐하라 <br>항상 기뻐하라 기뻐하라 <br>주 안에서 기뻐하라 기뻐하라 <br>항상 기뻐하라 기뻐하라 <br>주 안에서 기뻐하라 기뻐하라 <br>항상 기뻐하라 기뻐하라 <br>주 안에서 기뻐하라 기뻐하라 <br>즐거운 마음으로 기뻐하라 <br>]]></content><category term="이미향" label="이미향"/><category term="즐거운 마음" label="즐거운 마음"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박웅/냉수_한_그릇/</id><title>박웅 - 냉수 한 그릇 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9B%85/%EB%83%89%EC%88%98_%ED%95%9C_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%87/" title="박웅 - 냉수 한 그릇 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[목마르고 지친 자들아 모두 나오라 <br>주님께서 그들에게 주시네 <br>냉수 한 그릇 <br>가난하고 외로운 자들아 모두 나오라 <br>주님께서 그들에게 주시네 <br>냉수 한 그릇 <br>주께서 주시는 냉수 한 그릇 <br>냉수 한 그릇 <br>영원한 생명수 냉수 한 그릇 <br>주가 주신 사랑 나도 따라 전하리라 <br>손 내밀어 전해주리라 냉수 한 그릇 <br>수고하고 짐진 자들아 모두 나오라 <br>손 내밀어 전해주리라 냉수 한 그릇 <br>주께서 주시는 냉수 한 그릇 <br>냉수 한 그릇 <br>영원한 생명수 냉수 한 그릇 <br>주가 주신 사랑 나도 따라 전하리라 <br>우리의 작은 손길 주님은 기억하시네 <br>냉수 한 그릇 냉수 한 그릇 <br>냉수 한 그릇 냉수 한 그릇 <br>냉수 한 그릇 냉수 한 그릇 <br>주님 주시는 영원한 생명수 <br>냉수 한 그릇 <br>영원한 주님의 큰 사랑 <br>]]></content><category term="박웅" label="박웅"/><category term="냉수 한 그릇" label="냉수 한 그릇"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최상규/회복/</id><title>최상규 - 회복 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%83%81%EA%B7%9C/%ED%9A%8C%EB%B3%B5/" title="최상규 - 회복 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주여 나의 마음이 <br>심히 곤고합니다 <br>내 영혼 붙들어 주소서 <br>죄로 가득한 내 맘 <br>더러운 내 영혼을 <br>주여 돌아보소서 <br>내가 종일 눈물로 밤을 지새며 <br>주의 은혜와 긍휼 기다립니다 <br>주의 얼굴 내게로 돌이키소서 <br>나를 돌아보소서 <br>나의 하나님이여 내 속에 <br>정직한 영혼을 창조하소서 <br>나를 주님 앞에서 멀리 <br>멀리하지 마시고 <br>구원의 그 기쁨 다시 내 안에 <br>회복시켜 주소서 <br>하나님 원하시는 제사 <br>상한 심령이라 <br>하나님 원하시는 제물 <br>찢겨진 심령이라 <br>나의 하나님이여 내 속에 <br>정직한 영혼을 창조하소서 <br>나를 주님 앞에서 멀리 <br>멀리하지 마시고 <br>구원의 그 기쁨 다시 내 안에 <br>회복시켜 주소서 <br>구원의 그 기쁨 다시 내안에 <br>회복 시켜 주소서 <br>회복 시켜 주소서 <br>]]></content><category term="최상규" label="최상규"/><category term="회복" label="회복"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박하나/놀라우신_은혜/</id><title>박하나 - 놀라우신 은혜 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%95%98%EB%82%98/%EB%86%80%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B0%EC%8B%A0_%EC%9D%80%ED%98%9C/" title="박하나 - 놀라우신 은혜 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 같은 죄인 살리신 주 하나님 <br>주 은혜 놀라워 기쁨이 됩니다 <br>잃었던 생명 나 찾고 광명을 얻었네 <br>큰 죄악에서 나를 건지신 주님 <br>나 처음 믿은 그 시간 귀하고 놀랍네 <br>거기서 영원히 주 은혜로 <br>내가 산 것도 주님의 은혜 <br>나를 장차 본향으로 인도해 주심 믿네 <br>나 영원히 주를 찬양하길 원하네 <br>나 처음 믿은 그 시간 귀하고 놀랍네 <br>거기서 영원히 주 은혜로 <br>내가 산 것도 주님의 은혜 <br>나를 장차 본향으로 인도해 주심 믿네 <br>나 영원히 주를 찬양하길 원하네 <br>찬양하기 원하네 <br>찬양하기 원하네 <br>]]></content><category term="박하나" label="박하나"/><category term="놀라우신 은혜" label="놀라우신 은혜"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정규환/모두_나를_위함이라/</id><title>정규환 - 모두 나를 위함이라 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B7%9C%ED%99%98/%EB%AA%A8%EB%91%90_%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9C%84%ED%95%A8%EC%9D%B4%EB%9D%BC/" title="정규환 - 모두 나를 위함이라 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[겟세마네 동산에서 <br>피땀 흘린 주의 기도 <br>십자가에 죽음도 <br>모두 나를 위함이라 <br>모두 나를 위함이라 <br>주옥 같은 붉은 죄를 <br>흰 눈 같이 씻기시고 <br>하나님의 자녀로 <br>영원한 삶 주시었네 <br>모두 나를 위함이라 <br>내게 주신 크신 사랑 <br>무엇으로 보답할까 <br>내게 주신 모든 은혜 <br>무엇으로 보답할까 <br>겟세마네 동산에서 <br>피땀 흘린 주의 기도 <br>십자가에 죽음도 <br>모두 나를 위함이라 <br>모두 나를 위함이라 <br>모두 나를 위함이라 <br>]]></content><category term="정규환" label="정규환"/><category term="모두 나를 위함이라" label="모두 나를 위함이라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이미향/새_힘_얻으리라/</id><title>이미향 - 새 힘 얻으리라 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:15:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:15:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%AF%B8%ED%96%A5/%EC%83%88_%ED%9E%98_%EC%96%BB%EC%9C%BC%EB%A6%AC%EB%9D%BC/" title="이미향 - 새 힘 얻으리라 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[봄동산의 풀들이 <br>하늘을 바라보듯 <br>꽃이 태양을 바라볼 때 <br>아름다워진다 <br>우리 영혼 주 볼 때 <br>새 힘 얻으리라 <br>주 바라볼 때 <br>새 힘 얻으리 <br>새 힘 얻으리라 <br>오직 여호와를 앙망하는 자 <br>새 힘 얻으리라 <br>독수리 날개 치며 올라감 같이 <br>새 힘 얻으리라 <br>달음질하여도 곤비치 않고 <br>새 힘 얻으리라 <br>걸어도 피곤치 아니함 같이 <br>새 힘 얻으리라 <br>새 힘 얻으리라 <br>]]></content><category term="이미향" label="이미향"/><category term="새 힘 얻으리라" label="새 힘 얻으리라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백승헌/항상_기뻐하라/</id><title>백승헌 - 항상 기뻐하라 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:16:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:16:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%EC%8A%B9%ED%97%8C/%ED%95%AD%EC%83%81_%EA%B8%B0%EB%BB%90%ED%95%98%EB%9D%BC/" title="백승헌 - 항상 기뻐하라 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[항상 기뻐 기뻐하라 <br>주 안에서 기뻐하라 <br>주님께서 말하기를 <br>항상 기뻐하라 <br>마음의 근심 걱정 <br>모두 다 떨쳐 버리고 <br>시기 질투 미움도 <br>모두 버려라 <br>항상 기뻐 기뻐하라 <br>주 안에서 기뻐하라 <br>말씀과 기도로 은혜 받고 <br>항상 기뻐하라 <br>항상 기뻐 기뻐하라 <br>주 안에서 기뻐하라 <br>내가 다시 말하노니 <br>항상 기뻐하라 <br>마음의 즐거움은 <br>양약이지만 <br>심령의 근심은 <br>뼈를 마르게 하네 <br>하나님 믿으며 <br>모든 것 맡기면 <br>충만한 성령 채워주시네 <br>항상 기뻐 기뻐하라 <br>주 안에서 기뻐하라 <br>주님만 믿고서 의지하며 <br>항상 기뻐하라 <br>항상 기뻐하라 <br>]]></content><category term="백승헌" label="백승헌"/><category term="항상 기뻐하라" label="항상 기뻐하라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이미향/참_믿음/</id><title>이미향 - 참 믿음 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:16:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:16:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%AF%B8%ED%96%A5/%EC%B0%B8_%EB%AF%BF%EC%9D%8C/" title="이미향 - 참 믿음 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세상에 있지만 <br>세상에 속하지 않는 <br>믿음 주소서 <br>세상을 살지만 <br>세상에 물들지 않는 <br>믿음 주소서 <br>아직 이루어지진 않았지만 <br>이루어진 것처럼 <br>아무것도 보이진 않지만 <br>보이는 것처럼 <br>믿음의 눈으로 <br>바라보게 하소서 <br>영혼의 눈으로 <br>바라보게 하소서 <br>이것이 참 믿음이라 <br>주님 기뻐하시네 <br>아직 이루어지진 않았지만 <br>이루어진 것처럼 <br>아무것도 보이진 않지만 <br>보이는 것처럼 <br>믿음의 눈으로 <br>바라보게 하소서 <br>영혼의 눈으로 <br>바라보게 하소서 <br>이것이 참 믿음이라 <br>주님 기뻐하시네 <br>이것이 참 믿음이라 <br>주님 기뻐하시네 <br>]]></content><category term="이미향" label="이미향"/><category term="참 믿음" label="참 믿음"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김소영/예배/</id><title>김소영 - 예배 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:16:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:16:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%86%8C%EC%98%81/%EC%98%88%EB%B0%B0/" title="김소영 - 예배 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나님은 영이시니 <br>예배하는 자는 <br>신령과 진정으로 예배 할 지라 <br>하나님은 영이시니 <br>예배하는 자는 <br>신령과 진정으로 예배 할 지라 <br>너희 몸을 하나님 <br>기뻐하시는 거룩한 <br>산제사로 드리라 <br>오직 마음을 새롭게 <br>함으로 변화를 받으라 <br>이는 너희의 드릴 영적 예배라 <br>신령과 진정으로 예배 할 지라 <br>너희 몸을 하나님 <br>기뻐하시는 거룩한 <br>산제사로 드리라 <br>오직 마음을 새롭게 <br>함으로 변화를 받으라 <br>이는 너희의 드릴 영적 예배라 <br>신령과 진정으로 예배 할 지라 <br>이는 너희의 드릴 영적 예배라 <br>신령과 진정으로 예배 할 지라 <br>]]></content><category term="김소영" label="김소영"/><category term="예배" label="예배"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박하나/할렐루야_주의_성소에서/</id><title>박하나 - 할렐루야 주의 성소에서 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:16:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:16:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%95%98%EB%82%98/%ED%95%A0%EB%A0%90%EB%A3%A8%EC%95%BC_%EC%A3%BC%EC%9D%98_%EC%84%B1%EC%86%8C%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C/" title="박하나 - 할렐루야 주의 성소에서 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[할렐루야 그의 성소에서 <br>하나님을 찬양하며 <br>할렐루야 그의 권능의 궁창에서 <br>주를 찬양할지라 <br>할렐루야 그의 성소에서 <br>하나님을 찬양하며 <br>할렐루야 그의 권능의 궁창에서 <br>주를 찬양할지라 <br>그의 능하신 행동을 찬양하며 <br>그의 지극히 위대하심을 <br>따라 찬양하라 <br>나팔소리로 찬양하며 <br>비파와 수금으로 <br>찬양 소고치며 춤추며 <br>현악과 퉁소로 찬양 할 지어다 <br>큰소리 나는 제금으로 <br>호흡있는 자마다 <br>여호와를 찬양 할 지어다 <br>할렐루야 그의 성소에서 <br>하나님을 찬양하며 <br>할렐루야 그의 권능의 궁창에서 <br>주를 찬양할지라 <br>할렐루야 그의 성소에서 <br>하나님을 찬양하며 <br>할렐루야 그의 권능의 궁창에서 <br>주를 찬양할지라 <br>그의 능하신 행동을 찬양하며 <br>그의 지극히 위대하심을 <br>따라 찬양하라 <br>나팔소리로 찬양하며 <br>비파와 수금으로 <br>찬양 소고치며 춤추며 <br>현악과 퉁소로 찬양 할 지어다 <br>큰소리 나는 제금으로 <br>호흡있는 자마다 <br>여호와를 찬양 할 지어다 <br>호흡있는 자마다 <br>여호와를 찬양 할 지어다 <br>찬양 할 지어다 <br>찬양 할 지어다 <br>호흡있는 자마다 <br>여호와를 찬양 할 지어다 <br>할렐루야 <br>]]></content><category term="박하나" label="박하나"/><category term="할렐루야 주의 성소에서" label="할렐루야 주의 성소에서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최재도/내게_오라/</id><title>최재도 - 내게 오라 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:16:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:16:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9E%AC%EB%8F%84/%EB%82%B4%EA%B2%8C_%EC%98%A4%EB%9D%BC/" title="최재도 - 내게 오라 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[부드러운 주 음성 내게 들리니 <br>내게 오라 내게 오라 <br>주 말씀하시네 내게로 오라 <br>온유하신 주 음성 내게 들리니 <br>내게 오라 내게 오라 <br>쉼을 주리라 다 내게로 오라 <br>수고하고 무거운 짐 진 자들아 <br>내게 오라 내가 너희를 <br>쉬게 하리라 다 내게로 오라 <br>수고하고 무거운 짐 진 자들아 <br>내게 오라 내가 너희를 <br>쉬게 하리라 다 내게로 오라 <br>내게 오라 다 내게로 오라 <br>]]></content><category term="최재도" label="최재도"/><category term="내게 오라" label="내게 오라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최상규/네가_어디_있느냐/</id><title>최상규 - 네가 어디 있느냐 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:16:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:16:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%83%81%EA%B7%9C/%EB%84%A4%EA%B0%80_%EC%96%B4%EB%94%94_%EC%9E%88%EB%8A%90%EB%83%90/" title="최상규 - 네가 어디 있느냐 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[네가 어디 있느냐 <br>사무치게 부르시는 하나님 <br>그 애절한 음성 들리는가 <br>너는 하나님께로 돌아오라 <br>네가 어디 있느냐 <br>먼저 우릴 부르시는 하나님 <br>그 사랑의 음성 피하지 말라 <br>너는 하나님께로 돌아오라 <br>너는 여호와를 찾으라 <br>가까이 계실 때 부르라 <br>불의한 자 그 생각 버리고 <br>여호와께 돌아오라 <br>그가 긍휼히 여기시리라 <br>하나님께 돌아오라 <br>네가 어디 있느냐 <br>네가 어디 있느냐 <br>너희는 여호와를 찾으라 <br>가까이 계실 때에 부르라 <br>돌아오라 돌아오라 <br>널리 용서하시리라 <br>하나님께 돌아오라 <br>하나님께 돌아오라 <br>네가 어디 있느냐 <br>]]></content><category term="최상규" label="최상규"/><category term="네가 어디 있느냐" label="네가 어디 있느냐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레니/대학_일기/</id><title>레니 - 대학 일기 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:16:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:16:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EB%8B%88/%EB%8C%80%ED%95%99_%EC%9D%BC%EA%B8%B0/" title="레니 - 대학 일기 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다들 봄이 왔다고 말해 <br>근데 나는 아직도 <br>패딩 입고 다니는데 <br>잠이 쏟아지는 걸 보니 <br>봄이 오긴 왔나 보네 <br>또 잠이 오네 <br>나 빼고 다들 가벼운 걸음 <br>연애한다는 친구들까지 <br>왜 내게도 꽃 피는 봄이 올까 <br>살도 빼고 알바에 공부도 하면 <br>이번 생엔 틀린 것 같아 <br>가끔 들려줘라 너의 연애 얘기로 <br>대리만족하게 <br>나 빼고 다들 가벼운 걸음 <br>연애한다는 친구들까지 <br>왜 내게도 꽃 피는 봄이 올까 <br>살도 빼고 알바에 공부도 하면 <br>이번 생엔 틀린 것 같아 <br>가끔 들려줘라 너의 연애 얘기로 <br>대리만족하게 <br>]]></content><category term="레니" label="레니"/><category term="대학 일기" label="대학 일기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imagine_Dragons/Dancing_In_The_Dark/</id><title>Imagine Dragons - Dancing In The Dark - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:16:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:16:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imagine_Dragons/Dancing_In_The_Dark/" title="Imagine Dragons - Dancing In The Dark - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't throw my name 'round here like that <br>You could get us in some trouble <br>Talking that way and <br>Monday you got me, that's a fact <br>You could get me in some trouble <br>Talking that way and <br>I don't need nobody <br>If you ever want to join me <br>Baby, I'll be dancing in the dark <br>If you ever want to join me <br>Baby, I'll be dancing in the dark <br>Dancing in the <br>Join me <br>Dancing in the <br>Join me baby <br>Dancing in the <br>Join me baby <br>Most days I'm keeping to myself, living in my little bubble <br>Pushing my weight and moving my body through the sea <br>You could come join with me <br>Moving like the weekend <br>I don't need nobody <br>If you ever want to join me <br>Baby, I'll be dancing in the dark <br>If you ever want to join me <br>Baby, I'll be dancing in the dark <br>Dancing in the <br>Join me <br>Dancing in the <br>Join me baby <br>Dancing in the <br>Join me baby <br>Dancing in the <br>Join me baby <br>If you ever want to join me <br>Baby, I'll be dancing in the dark <br>If you ever want to join me <br>Baby, I'll be dancing in the dark <br>Dancing in the, join me baby <br>If you ever want to join me <br>Baby, I'll be dancing in the dark <br>If you ever want to join me <br>Baby, I'll be dancing in the dark <br>Dancing in the]]></content><category term="Imagine Dragons" label="Imagine Dragons"/><category term="Dancing In The Dark" label="Dancing In The Dark"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imagine_Dragons/Start_Over/</id><title>Imagine Dragons - Start Over - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:16:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:16:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imagine_Dragons/Start_Over/" title="Imagine Dragons - Start Over - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Clenched teeth, no words <br>All this distance taking is a toll <br>Speaking volumes, silence screaming over your words <br>I never did you right, I know that <br>Too many sleepless nights, I own that <br>I said it time and time, I know that <br>I wanna try again <br>Can we start over? <br>Can we start over? <br>Can we start over? <br>Before it's over, over <br>Cold nights, cold sheets <br>One more lonely empty hotel room <br>What I'd give to find my way back into you <br>I never did you right, I know that <br>Too many sleepless nights, I own that <br>I said it time and time, I know that <br>I wanna try again <br>Can we start over? <br>Can we start over? <br>Can we start over? <br>Before it's over, over <br>Can we start over? <br>Can we start over? <br>Can we start over? <br>Before it's over, over <br>Come alive, come alive, come alive again <br>Come alive, come alive, come alive again <br>Come alive, come alive, come alive again <br>Come alive, come alive, come alive again <br>Can we start over? <br>Can we start over? <br>Can we start over? <br>Before it's over, over <br>Can we start over? <br>Come alive, come alive, come alive again <br>Can we get closer? <br>Come alive, come alive, come alive again <br>Can we start over? <br>Come alive, come alive, come alive again <br>Before it's over, over]]></content><category term="Imagine Dragons" label="Imagine Dragons"/><category term="Start Over" label="Start Over"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imagine_Dragons/Mouth_Of_The_River/</id><title>Imagine Dragons - Mouth Of The River - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:17:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:17:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imagine_Dragons/Mouth_Of_The_River/" title="Imagine Dragons - Mouth Of The River - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh the mouth of the river <br>Oh the mouth of the river <br>Oh the mouth of the river <br><br><br>I wanna live a life like that <br>Live the life of the faithful one <br>Wanna bow to the floor <br>With everybody else wanna be someone <br>I wanna make some love <br>I don't want no enemies <br>Oh it's the curse of the man <br>Always living life living life living just to please <br><br><br>Oh the mouth of the river <br>And the wrath of the giver <br>With the hands of a sinner <br>Oh the mouth of the river <br>Oh the mouth of the river <br>And the wrath of the giver <br>With the hands of a sinner <br>Oh the mouth of the river <br><br><br>Oh I'm alkaline <br>I'm always keeping to the basics <br>I'm overboard <br>I'm self-destructive <br>And self-important <br>And I'm anxious <br>Oh I'm self-assured <br>I'm nervous <br>And I'm pacing oh I'm pacing <br><br><br>Oh the mouth of the river <br>And the wrath of the giver <br>With the hands of a sinner <br>Oh the mouth of the river <br>Oh the mouth of the river <br>And the wrath of the giver <br>With the hands of a sinner <br>Oh the mouth of the river <br>Oh the mouth of the river <br>Oh the mouth of the river <br><br><br>And I am going under <br>Oh I am going under <br>I am going under <br>Oh I am going under <br>I am going under <br><br>Oh the mouth of the river <br>And the wrath of the giver <br>With the hands of a sinner <br>Oh the mouth of the river <br>Oh the mouth of the river <br>And the wrath of the giver <br>With the hands of a sinner <br>Oh the mouth of the river <br>Oh the mouth of the river <br>Oh the mouth of the river]]></content><category term="Imagine Dragons" label="Imagine Dragons"/><category term="Mouth Of The River" label="Mouth Of The River"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imagine_Dragons/Yesterday/</id><title>Imagine Dragons - Yesterday - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:17:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:17:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imagine_Dragons/Yesterday/" title="Imagine Dragons - Yesterday - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here's to my future <br>Here's to my yesterday <br>Here's to change <br>Oh, here's to my yesterday <br>No tomorrow without a yesterday <br>Here's to my future <br>Goodbye to yesterday <br>All these years I've been searching <br>For who I'm supposed to be <br>All this time I've been wasting <br>'Cause I was right in front of me <br>Oh, it's a crooked old tradition <br>By a masterful magician <br>But in all this trouble I've met <br>I haven't got one single regret, no <br>Here's to my future <br>Here's to my yesterday <br>Here's to change <br>Oh, here's to my yesterday <br>No tomorrow without a yesterday <br>Here's to my future <br>Goodbye to yesterday <br>Yesterday <br>Oh, I'm a hopeless crash collision <br>'Cause I'm a hostage to my pride <br>By my own volition <br>I've been a saint, i've been the truth, I've been the lie <br>Oh, it's a crooked old tradition <br>By a masterful magician <br>But in this all this trouble I've met <br>I haven't got one single regret, no <br>Here's to my future <br>Here's to my yesterday <br>Here's to change <br>Oh, here's to my yesterday <br>No tomorrow without a yesterday <br>Here's to my future <br>Goodbye to yesterday <br>Yesterday <br>A new day you can go, you can do anything you wanna <br>It's your play, swing low, go high <br>Anywhere you wanna <br>You can reach for the moon <br>Anywhere your dreams can take you <br>Go astray, fade away <br>Just leave it to yesterday <br>Here's to my future <br>Here's to my yesterday <br>Here's to change <br>Oh, here's to my yesterday <br>No tomorrow without a yesterday <br>Here's to my future <br>Goodbye to yesterday <br>Yesterday]]></content><category term="Imagine Dragons" label="Imagine Dragons"/><category term="Yesterday" label="Yesterday"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imagine_Dragons/Ill_Make_It_Up_To_You/</id><title>Imagine Dragons - I`ll Make It Up To You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:17:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:17:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imagine_Dragons/Ill_Make_It_Up_To_You/" title="Imagine Dragons - I`ll Make It Up To You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Took your heart, took your hand <br>Promise you all that I have <br>Hoping that you understand <br>I'm far from a perfect man <br><br>'Cause honey it's been a hard year <br>It seemed like we're going nowhere <br>You're crying inside your bedroom <br>Baby I know it's not fair <br><br>Lay with me, for one more night <br>I promise you, I'll make it right <br><br>I'll make it up to you (you, you) <br>Every night <br>I'll make it up to you (you, you) <br>Every night <br>I'll make it up to you <br><br>I know you don't understand <br>The vices that follow a man <br>And in your eyes I can see <br>The places that you'd rather be <br><br>'Cause honey it's been a hard year <br>It seemed like we're going nowhere <br>You're crying inside your bedroom <br>Baby I know it's not fair <br><br>I'll make it up to you (you, you) <br>Every night <br>I'll make it up to you (you, you) <br>Every night <br>I'll make it up to you <br><br>In our darkest hour, in the dead of the night <br>I'll make it up to you <br>Your hands in mine <br>I'll make it up to you <br>Promises are nothing more than fleeting thoughts <br>But you, you are my lifeblood <br><br>I'll make it up to you <br>Every night <br>I'll make it up to you <br>Every night <br>I'll make it up to you (you, you) <br>Every night <br>I'll make it up to you (you, you) <br>Every night <br>I'll make it up to you (you, you) <br>Every night <br>I'll make it up to you]]></content><category term="Imagine Dragons" label="Imagine Dragons"/><category term="I`ll Make It Up To You" label="I`ll Make It Up To You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imagine_Dragons/Rise_Up/</id><title>Imagine Dragons - Rise Up - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:17:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:17:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imagine_Dragons/Rise_Up/" title="Imagine Dragons - Rise Up - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was hoping for an indication <br>I was seeking higher elevation <br>I've been shaken <br>waking in the night light <br>I've been breaking <br>hiding from the spotlight <br>The more I stray the less I fear <br>And the more I reach <br>the more I fade away <br>The darkness right in front of me <br>Oh it's calling out and <br>I won't walk away <br>I would always open up the door <br>Always looking up at higher floors <br>Wanna see it all give me more <br>I was always up for making changes <br>Walking down the streets <br>meeting strangers <br>Flipping through my life <br>turning pages <br>Like a prayer that only <br>needs a reason <br>Like a hunter waiting for the season <br>I was there but <br>I was always leaving <br>I was living but <br>I was never breathing <br>The more I stray the less I fear <br>And the more I reach <br>the more I fade away <br>Darkness right in front of me <br>Oh it's calling out and <br>I won't walk away <br>I would always open up the door <br>Always looking up at higher floors <br>Wanna see it all give me more <br>I was always up for making changes <br>Walking down the streets <br>meeting strangers <br>Flipping through my life <br>turning pages <br>I'm bursting like the fourth of July <br>So color me and blow me away <br>I'm broken in the prime of my life <br>So embrace it and leave me to stray <br>I would always open up the door <br>Always looking up at higher floors <br>Wanna see it all give me more <br>I was always up for making changes <br>Walking down the streets <br>meeting strangers <br>Flipping through my life <br>turning pages <br>I would always open up the door <br>Always looking up at higher floors <br>Wanna see it all give me more <br>I was always up for making changes <br>Walking down the streets <br>meeting strangers <br>Flipping through my life <br>turning pages <br>]]></content><category term="Imagine Dragons" label="Imagine Dragons"/><category term="Rise Up" label="Rise Up"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imagine_Dragons/I_Dont_Know_Why/</id><title>Imagine Dragons - I Don`t Know Why - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:17:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:17:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Imagine_Dragons/I_Dont_Know_Why/" title="Imagine Dragons - I Don`t Know Why - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We could be strangers in the night <br>We could be passing in the shadows <br>We couldn't be closer if we tried <br>When we're caught in the headlights <br>We could be faces in the crowd <br>We could be passing in the shadows <br>Upping the risk of being found <br>When we're caught in the headlights <br>Dangerous <br>Your love is always dangerous <br>And now I'm lost in us <br>We're livin' in a lying trust <br>I don't know why but I guess it's got something to do with you <br>To do with you <br>I don't know why but I guess it's got something to do with you <br>To do with you <br>I was a fakeing alibi <br>Trading the truth in for a lie, oh <br>We were the essence of desire <br>And we're caught in the headlights <br>Dangerous <br>Your love is always dangerous <br>And now I'm lost in us <br>We're livin' in a lying trust <br>I don't know why but I guess it's got something to do with you <br>To do with you <br>I don't know why but I guess it's got something to do with you <br>To do with you (I don't know why) <br>I don't know why but I guess <br>it's got something to do with you (I don't know) <br>To do with you (I don't know why) <br>I don't know why but I guess it's got something to do with you <br>To do with you <br>Tell me that you love me <br>Tell me that you love me <br>Tell me that you love me <br>Tell me that you love me <br>Tell me that you love me (dangerous} <br>Tell me that you love me <br>Tell me that you love me (your love is always dangerous} <br>Tell me that you love me <br>I don't know why but I guess it's got something to do with you (I don't know) <br>To do with you (I don't know why) <br>I don't know why (I don't know why) <br>But I guess it's got something to do with you (do with, do with, do with) <br>To do with you (I don't know why) <br>I don't know why but I guess it's got something to do with you (I don't know) <br>To do with you (I don't know why) <br>I don't know why but I guess it's got something to do with you <br>To do with you]]></content><category term="Imagine Dragons" label="Imagine Dragons"/><category term="I Don`t Know Why" label="I Don`t Know Why"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/철희/군산항아_2017_Ver_MR/</id><title>철희 - 군산항아 (2017 Ver.) (MR) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:17:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:17:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%A0%ED%9D%AC/%EA%B5%B0%EC%82%B0%ED%95%AD%EC%95%84_2017_Ver_MR/" title="철희 - 군산항아 (2017 Ver.) (MR) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람에 날리는 눈꽃처럼 <br>내 사랑 당신은 날아가 버렸어요 <br>군산항에 울려 퍼지는 <br>뱃고동 소리는 <br>내 마음을 슬프게 하네요 <br>어제도 오늘도 군산항 부둣가에 <br>떠나간 그 님을 기다린다 <br>군산항아 갈매기야 <br>이 내 마음 들리거든 그 님에게 <br>소식 좀 전해 전해다오 <br>바람에 날리는 눈꽃처럼 <br>내 사랑 당신은 날아가 버렸어요 <br>군산항에 울려 퍼지는 <br>뱃고동 소리는 <br>내 마음을 슬프게 하네요 <br>어제도 오늘도 군산항 부둣가에 <br>떠나간 그 님을 기다린다 <br>군산항아 갈매기야 <br>이 내 마음 들리거든 그 님에게 <br>소식 좀 전해 전해다오 <br>어제도 오늘도 군산항 부둣가에 <br>떠나간 그 님을 기다린다 <br>군산항아 갈매기야 <br>이 내 마음 들리거든 그 님에게 <br>소식 좀 전해 전해다오 <br>소식 좀 전해 전해다오 <br>]]></content><category term="철희" label="철희"/><category term="군산항아 (2017 Ver.) (MR)" label="군산항아 (2017 Ver.) (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/철희/군산항아_2017_Ver/</id><title>철희 - 군산항아 (2017 Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:17:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:17:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%A0%ED%9D%AC/%EA%B5%B0%EC%82%B0%ED%95%AD%EC%95%84_2017_Ver/" title="철희 - 군산항아 (2017 Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람에 날리는 눈꽃처럼 <br>내 사랑 당신은 날아가 버렸어요 <br>군산항에 울려 퍼지는 <br>뱃고동 소리는 <br>내 마음을 슬프게 하네요 <br>어제도 오늘도 군산항 부둣가에 <br>떠나간 그 님을 기다린다 <br>군산항아 갈매기야 <br>이 내 마음 들리거든 그 님에게 <br>소식 좀 전해 전해다오 <br>바람에 날리는 눈꽃처럼 <br>내 사랑 당신은 날아가 버렸어요 <br>군산항에 울려 퍼지는 <br>뱃고동 소리는 <br>내 마음을 슬프게 하네요 <br>어제도 오늘도 군산항 부둣가에 <br>떠나간 그 님을 기다린다 <br>군산항아 갈매기야 <br>이 내 마음 들리거든 그 님에게 <br>소식 좀 전해 전해다오 <br>어제도 오늘도 군산항 부둣가에 <br>떠나간 그 님을 기다린다 <br>군산항아 갈매기야 <br>이 내 마음 들리거든 그 님에게 <br>소식 좀 전해 전해다오 <br>소식 좀 전해 전해다오 <br>]]></content><category term="철희" label="철희"/><category term="군산항아 (2017 Ver.)" label="군산항아 (2017 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유명진/내고향_함평천지/</id><title>유명진 - 내고향 함평천지 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:18:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:18:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EB%AA%85%EC%A7%84/%EB%82%B4%EA%B3%A0%ED%96%A5_%ED%95%A8%ED%8F%89%EC%B2%9C%EC%A7%80/" title="유명진 - 내고향 함평천지 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1절 <br>내 고향 함평천지야 <br>우리 함께 손에 손 잡고 <br>나비처럼 훨훨 날아서 <br>덩실덩실 춤을 춥시다 <br>지상낙원 따로 있나 <br>천국이 따로 있나요 <br>내 고향 함평천지 나비천지가 <br>어쩔시구 지상낙원이야 <br>2절 <br>내 고향 나비천지야 <br>우리 함께 손에 손 잡고 <br>벌 나비 춤을 추듯이 <br>덩실덩실 춤을 춰보자 <br>지상낙원 따로 있나 <br>천국이 따로 있나요 <br>내 고향 함평천지 나비천지가 <br>어쩔시구 지상낙원이야 <br>후렴: <br>내 고향 함평천지 나비천지가 <br>어쩔시구 지상낙원이야]]></content><category term="유명진" label="유명진"/><category term="내고향 함평천지" label="내고향 함평천지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마마무/다라다_휘인_Jeff_Bernat_BO/</id><title>마마무 - 다라다 (휘인, Jeff Bernat, B.O.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:18:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:18:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%A7%88%EB%AC%B4/%EB%8B%A4%EB%9D%BC%EB%8B%A4_%ED%9C%98%EC%9D%B8_Jeff_Bernat_BO/" title="마마무 - 다라다 (휘인, Jeff Bernat, B.O.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[매일 너만 바라보다가 <br>이젠 눈을 감아도 네가 보여 <br>100미터를 달린 것처럼 <br>내 맘은 뛰어 이미 <br>너를 만나러 가는 길은 <br>Singing like <br>다 다 다라다 다다 다라다 <br>다 다 다라다 다다 다라다 <br>Sing a song on and on <br>다 다 다라다 on and on <br>Maybe I fall in love with you oh <br>Sunshine gentle breeze you and I <br>내게 와줘요 어서 안아줘요 <br>꽃이 비처럼 내리는 길을 같이 걸어요 <br>아무 말 않고 보아도 좋아요 <br>그대와 함께라면 <br>잠이 오질 않네요 <br>이 밤이 지나가면 그대를 만나겠죠 <br>달빛도 따뜻해요 그대만 생각하면 <br>내 피아노만 켜면 <br>다 다 다라다 다다 다라다 <br>다 다 다라다 다다 다라다 <br>Sing a song on and on <br>다 다 다라다 on and on <br>You’re the one and only <br>that I give my everything <br>I feel you every moment <br>that I breathe <br>내게 와줘요 어서 안아줘요 <br>꽃이 비처럼 내리는 길을 같이 걸어요 <br>아무 말 않고 보아도 좋아요 <br>그대와 함께라면 <br>이 밤이 지나면 <br>When the morning comes <br>그댈 만나겠죠 <br>I want to hold you baby <br>그대만 생각하면 달빛도 따뜻해요 <br>I never felt like this before <br>I feel you every night and morn <br>Now we walk along this road together <br>내게 와줘요 어서 안아줘요 <br>꽃이 비처럼 내리는 길을 같이 걸어요 <br>아무 말 않고 보아도 좋아요 <br>그대와 함께라면 <br>다라 다다 다라 다다다 <br>다라 다다 다라 다다다 <br>아무 말 않고 보아도 좋아요 <br>그대와 함께 라면 <br>]]></content><category term="마마무" label="마마무"/><category term="다라다 (휘인, Jeff Bernat, B.O.)" label="다라다 (휘인, Jeff Bernat, B.O.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마마무/아재개그_Narr_김대희_김준호/</id><title>마마무 - 아재개그 (Narr. 김대희, 김준호) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:18:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:18:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%A7%88%EB%AC%B4/%EC%95%84%EC%9E%AC%EA%B0%9C%EA%B7%B8_Narr_%EA%B9%80%EB%8C%80%ED%9D%AC_%EA%B9%80%EC%A4%80%ED%98%B8/" title="마마무 - 아재개그 (Narr. 김대희, 김준호) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어떡해 오늘 나 또 지각이야 <br>아 미치겠네 미치지 말고 솔을 쳐봐 <br>뭔 소리야 이게 웃긴 얘기야 <br>참 어이없게 집 갈 때 생각나 <br>바나나 먹으면 나한테 반하나 <br>지금 너 불만 있냐 아니 물도 있어 <br>너 어디야 지금 제주도야 <br>내 맘을 흔든 너 재주도 좋아 <br>Yo A.Z.E <br>아재의 꿈은 커다래 <br>너의 센스 존중해 Respect <br>아주 어마 무시 무시 무시무시해 <br>천방지축 어린 아이 같아 후 <br>I think 말장난 신선한 발상 <br>척척박사 아무도 못 말려 <br>크게 웃어 줘요 활짝 <br>아재개그 아저씨군 <br>삐뚤빼뚤 지그재그 <br>쟤쟤쟤 쟤 봐라 <br>엄머머 쟤 좀 봐라 <br>아 아저씨 아저씨 아저씨군 <br>아재개그 아저씨군 <br>삐뚤빼뚤 다같이 Stop <br>왼손은 허리위로 <br>오른손은 머리위로 <br>잘생긴 부처님 <br>다같이 부처핸섬 <br>오 아재 소금이 죽었소 맞춰봐 <br>소금이 죽으면 죽염이 되오 죽염 <br>엊그제 어떤 아재한테 <br>이 가사 쓰려고 <br>몇 개 좀 배워왔소 Let’s Go <br>결혼한 복숭아는 웨딩 피치 <br>만인의 파이는 Wifi <br>소시는 옷 가게에서 티파니 <br>소가 위로 올라간다 소오오름 <br>너무해 너무해 그래 너는 무해 <br>잘못 봤다간 멘탈 다 나갈 수 있어 <br>아재개그 아저씨군 <br>삐뚤빼뚤 지그재그 <br>쟤쟤쟤 쟤 봐라 <br>엄머머 쟤 좀 봐라 <br>아 아저씨 아저씨 아저씨군 <br>아재개그 아저씨군 <br>삐뚤빼뚤 다같이 얼음 땡 <br>왼손은 허리위로 <br>오른손은 머리위로 <br>잘생긴 부처님 <br>다같이 부처핸섬 뛰어 <br>아재개그 Oh 지끈지끈 <br>아 죄송 <br>아재개그 아저씨군 <br>삐뚤빼뚤 지그재그 <br>쟤쟤쟤 쟤 봐라 <br>엄머머 쟤 좀 봐라 <br>아 아저씨 아저씨 아저씨군 <br>아재개그 아저씨군 <br>삐뚤빼뚤 열중 쉬어 <br>왼손은 허리위로 <br>오른손은 머리위로 <br>잘생긴 부처님 <br>다같이 부처핸섬 뛰어 <br>아재개그 Oh 지끈지끈 <br>AZE 쉿 <br>]]></content><category term="마마무" label="마마무"/><category term="아재개그 (Narr. 김대희, 김준호)" label="아재개그 (Narr. 김대희, 김준호)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마마무/구차해_Solo_문별/</id><title>마마무 - 구차해 (Solo. 문별) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:18:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:18:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%A7%88%EB%AC%B4/%EA%B5%AC%EC%B0%A8%ED%95%B4_Solo_%EB%AC%B8%EB%B3%84/" title="마마무 - 구차해 (Solo. 문별) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 왜 널 좋아했을까 <br>생각보다 안 맞는 우리 둘 Uh <br>친구를 붙잡고 욕하지만 <br>너의 연락 한 통에 Only you Uh <br>지쳐갈 때쯤이면 넌 꼭 <br>다정해 따뜻해 기대를 주네 <br>내가 필요할 때면 넌 꼭 <br>바쁘대 안돼 혼자가 된 나 <br>네가 있어도 난 아파 <br>보고 싶은데 내가 뭘 어쩌겠어 <br>티 내고 싶지 않아 <br>날 안타깝게 볼까 봐 Yeah <br>아무래도 난 구차해 구차해 Yeah <br>Uh 멈출 수가 없어 I found you <br>나만 그런 것 같아 화가나 <br>I don't understand <br>이 정도 속앓이는 익숙해 <br>동정은 No 하던 대로 해 <br>그게 너다우니깐 <br>맘을 쿡쿡 쑤셔도 <br>말을 툭툭 뱉어도 <br>나 너 하나니깐 <br>이 밤에 맥주 한잔 들고 <br>여전히 신세한탄 중 <br>네가 있어도 난 아파 <br>보고 싶은데 내가 뭘 어쩌겠어 <br>티 내고 싶지 않아 <br>날 안타깝게 볼까 봐 Yeah <br>아무래도 난 구차해 구차해 Yeah <br>I recognize 한쪽으로 치우친 사이 <br>못 미뤄놔 정리하고 싶어 빨리 <br>짜증나는 밤이네 Love and hate <br>한 두 번도 아닌데 예민해 <br>Everyday I falling love again <br>애써 태연하게 구는 내가 싫어 <br>You made it <br>네가 있어도 난 아파 <br>보고 싶은데 내가 뭘 어쩌겠어 <br>티 내고 싶지 않아 <br>날 안타깝게 볼까 봐 Yeah <br>아무래도 난 구차해 구차해 Yeah <br>Call me call me <br>everyday everynight <br>Hug me hug me <br>everywhere everytime <br>Love me love me <br>everyday everynight <br>But I'm lonely so lonely <br>구차해 매일 난 <br>]]></content><category term="마마무" label="마마무"/><category term="구차해 (Solo. 문별)" label="구차해 (Solo. 문별)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마마무/Finally/</id><title>마마무 - Finally - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:18:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:18:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%A7%88%EB%AC%B4/Finally/" title="마마무 - Finally - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Finally Finally <br>Finally Finally <br>이제야 알았어 Baby <br>널 만난 이후로 왜이리 <br>모든 게 특별해 Always <br>드디어 만났어 Baby <br>이번이 마지막 Maybe <br>이 느낌 모든 게 완벽한 걸 <br>꼭 맘에 들어 <br>마냥 어린애처럼 한 순간인 것처럼 <br>그냥 하는 말이 아냐 Oh <br>너는 마치 내게 와서 <br>내 세상을 바꿔 준 Hero <br>걱정은 하고 싶지 않아 No way <br>너랑 간다면 지구 끝까지 On &amp; On <br>잠들었던 내 안에 다른 날 깨워 <br>기다렸던 네가 온 거야 <br>Oh 짜릿한 느낌이야 너너너 너 <br>아무런 생각 안나 네 눈을 바라보면 <br>Oh 이런 맘 처음이야 나나나 나 <br>하루가 일분 같아 너와 함께 있으면 <br>Finally Finally Finally Finally <br>너는 내 운명 Actually <br>누가 뭐라 해도 Love me <br>내 곁에 있어줘 Baby <br>이대로 행복해 Really <br>자꾸만 생각나 Day Day <br>아껴온 내 맘을 숨김없이 <br>다 주고 싶어 <br>Blow your mind 이젠 부러워 마 <br>내가 채워줄게 혼자인 밤 <br>안달 난 사람처럼 보여도 <br>난 괜찮아 Oh 괜찮아 <br>솔직하고 싶어 조금 더 가까이와 <br>궁금해서 잠이 안 와 <br>How do you feel now <br>미치겠어 <br>구름 위를 걷는 기분 <br>나긋한 목소리로 불러줘 <br>내 이름 <br>Oh 짜릿한 느낌이야 너너너 너 <br>아무런 생각 안나 네 눈을 바라보면 <br>Oh 이런 맘 처음이야 나나나 나 <br>하루가 일분 같아 너와 함께 있으면 <br>마치 꿈인 것 같아 <br>널 처음 만난 그때 <br>상상만했던 미래 <br>나 정말 빠진 것 같아 <br>딴생각 할 수 없게 <br>너만 담아 둘게 <br>Oh 짜릿한 느낌이야 너너너 너 <br>아무런 생각 안나 네 눈을 바라보면 <br>Oh 이런 맘 처음이야 나나나 나 <br>하루가 일분 같아 너와 함께 있으면 <br>Finally Finally Finally Finally <br>Finally Finally Finally Finally <br>]]></content><category term="마마무" label="마마무"/><category term="Finally" label="Finally"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/마마무/나로_말할_것_같으면_Yes_I_am/</id><title>마마무 - 나로 말할 것 같으면 (Yes I am) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:18:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:18:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%88%EB%A7%88%EB%AC%B4/%EB%82%98%EB%A1%9C_%EB%A7%90%ED%95%A0_%EA%B2%83_%EA%B0%99%EC%9C%BC%EB%A9%B4_Yes_I_am/" title="마마무 - 나로 말할 것 같으면 (Yes I am) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나로 말할 것 <br>같으면 자신감 있는 여자 <br>말하자면 느낌 있는 여자 <br>자신 있으면 나를 따라 해도 돼 <br>뒤따라와 뒤따라와 <br>Follow me E Ae Ae <br>화장은 옅게 귀찮으니까 <br>노출은 안 해 그럴 필요 없어 <br>이상해 좀 특이해 평범한 게 더 싫어 <br>이런 내 모습 부모님께 감사해 <br>Me Me 4 with Sun <br>생각 말어 정신은 High Class <br>눈치 보지마 네가 바로 Vogue <br>Hello Bonjour nihao 안녕 <br>세계각국마다 매력이 있듯이 <br>나로 말할 것 같으면 <br>겨울에 민소매 입으면 <br>여름이 되는 거야 I love Ya <br>Introduce My Self <br>나로 말할 것 <br>같으면 자신감 있는 여자 <br>말하자면 느낌 있는 여자 <br>자신 있으면 나를 따라 해도 돼 <br>뒤따라와 뒤따라와 <br>Follow me E Ae Ae <br>Yes I am 나로 말할 것 같으면 <br>Yes I am 아주 건방져 <br>편한 게 좋아 그게 나니까 <br>돌려 말 안 해 숨기지 못해 <br>건방져 신경 안 써 나를 모르는 소리 <br>그냥 내 멋대로 내 식대로 해 <br>My name is 문스타 <br>어디까지나 그냥 <br>내 취향이니까 예민하지마 <br>컴플렉스 Nothing 슬렉스 셔츠 로퍼 <br>클래식한 스타일로 <br>난 나를 표현해 My Baby <br>아직까지 말꼬리 잡는 너 <br>Take off the blind <br>Drive 내 차에 타 <br>자 자 나로 말할 것 <br>같으면 자신감 있는 여자 <br>말하자면 느낌 있는 여자 <br>자신 있으면 나를 <br>따라 해도 돼 해도 돼 <br>뒤따라와 뒤따라와 <br>Follow me E Ae Ae <br>Yes I am 나로 말할 것 같으면 <br>Yes I am Follow me E Ae Ae <br>Yes I am 나로 말할 것 같으면 <br>Yes I am 볼이 뚠뚠해 <br>V라인보다 동그란 내 얼굴이 좋아 <br>나만의 Some special thing <br>쌍꺼풀 있는 눈매 보단 <br>나는 내 눈 무쌍이 좋아 <br>웃을 땐 인디언 보조개와 코 찡긋 <br>아주 칭찬해 <br>나로 말할 것 같으면 말할 것 같으면 <br>아주 시크해 <br>나로 말할 것 같으면 말할 것 같으면 <br>Introduce My Self <br>쟤 쟤 쟤 <br>나로 말할 것 같으면 <br>자신감 있는 여자 <br>말하자면 느낌 있는 여자 <br>자신 있으면 나를 따라 해도 돼 <br>뒤따라와 뒤따라와 <br>Follow me E Ae Ae <br>Yes I am 나로 말할 것 같으면 <br>Yes I am Follow me E Ae Ae <br>Yes I am 나로 말할 것 같으면 <br>Yes I am <br>아주 건방져 <br>]]></content><category term="마마무" label="마마무"/><category term="나로 말할 것 같으면 (Yes I am)" label="나로 말할 것 같으면 (Yes I am)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/장지우/다_드릴께요/</id><title>장지우 - 다 드릴께요 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:19:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:19:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%EC%A7%80%EC%9A%B0/%EB%8B%A4_%EB%93%9C%EB%A6%B4%EA%BB%98%EC%9A%94/" title="장지우 - 다 드릴께요 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1절 <br>눈감으면 어디선가 <br>당신모습 눈에 보여요 <br>오늘따라 유난히도 <br>당신이 그립습니다 <br>당신만 생각하면 <br>눈앞에 물결이 <br>두 눈에 눈물 되어 <br>찰랑 찰랑 거려요 <br>사랑을 하고 싶어요 <br>어서어서 내게 오세요 <br>(오세요 어서 오세요) <br>(내 모든걸 다 드릴께요) <br>2절 <br>눈감으면 떠오로는 <br>잊지 못할 당신의 모습 <br>어젯밤도 꿈속에서 <br>당신 숨결 느껴 봅니다 <br>당신만 생각하면 가슴이 메어와 <br>두 눈에 눈물이 찰랑찰랑 거려요 <br>사랑을 하고 싶어요 <br>어서어서 내게 오세요 <br>(오세요 어서 오세요) <br>(내 모든걸 다 드릴께요)]]></content><category term="장지우" label="장지우"/><category term="다 드릴께요" label="다 드릴께요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이진아/양평에서_만나요_MR/</id><title>이진아 - 양평에서 만나요 (MR) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:19:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:19:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%84%EC%95%84/%EC%96%91%ED%8F%89%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C_%EB%A7%8C%EB%82%98%EC%9A%94_MR/" title="이진아 - 양평에서 만나요 (MR) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[정다운 양평 그곳 <br>정든 고향 양평 그곳 <br>맑은 물이 흘러 넘치고 <br>우리들의 꿈이 펼쳐지는 그곳 <br>산새들 지저귀고 <br>종달새 울어대는 <br>아름다운 양평 바로 그곳 <br>양평으로 오세요 기다릴께요 <br>양평으로 오세요 <br>양평에서 만나요 <br>꽃피는 양평 그곳 <br>용문산이 있는 양평 그곳 <br>두물 머리 아침 햇살이 <br>영롱하게 피어 오르는 그곳 <br>산새들 지저귀고 <br>종달새 울어대는 <br>아름다운 양평 바로 그곳 <br>양평으로 오세요 기다릴께요 <br>양평으로 오세요 <br>양평에서 만나요 <br>양평으로 오세요 기다릴께요 <br>양평으로 오세요 <br>양평에서 만나요 <br>양평에서 만나요 <br>]]></content><category term="이진아" label="이진아"/><category term="양평에서 만나요 (MR)" label="양평에서 만나요 (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이진아/양평에서_만나요/</id><title>이진아 - 양평에서 만나요 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:19:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:19:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%84%EC%95%84/%EC%96%91%ED%8F%89%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C_%EB%A7%8C%EB%82%98%EC%9A%94/" title="이진아 - 양평에서 만나요 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[정다운 양평 그곳 <br>정든 고향 양평 그곳 <br>맑은 물이 흘러 넘치고 <br>우리들의 꿈이 펼쳐지는 그곳 <br>산새들 지저귀고 <br>종달새 울어대는 <br>아름다운 양평 바로 그곳 <br>양평으로 오세요 기다릴께요 <br>양평으로 오세요 <br>양평에서 만나요 <br>꽃피는 양평 그곳 <br>용문산이 있는 양평 그곳 <br>두물 머리 아침 햇살이 <br>영롱하게 피어 오르는 그곳 <br>산새들 지저귀고 <br>종달새 울어대는 <br>아름다운 양평 바로 그곳 <br>양평으로 오세요 기다릴께요 <br>양평으로 오세요 <br>양평에서 만나요 <br>양평으로 오세요 기다릴께요 <br>양평으로 오세요 <br>양평에서 만나요 <br>양평에서 만나요 <br>]]></content><category term="이진아" label="이진아"/><category term="양평에서 만나요" label="양평에서 만나요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김종환/그대가_있어/</id><title>김종환 - 그대가 있어 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:20:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:20:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A2%85%ED%99%98/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EA%B0%80_%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4/" title="김종환 - 그대가 있어 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대가 있어 나는 행복해 <br>오늘도 이렇게 함께 있으니 <br>비록 지금 캄캄한 어둠일지라도 <br>난 참 행복해 <br>힘들 땐 언제든지 연락해 <br>혼자서 그렇게 아파 울지 마 <br>나도 아플 땐 네게 연락할 테니까 <br>꼭 연락해 <br>내일의 꿈도 물론 소중하지만 <br>지금 이 순간 우리 <br>다시 올 수 없는 시간들 <br>우리 함께 즐기는 거야 <br>그렇게 싸우는 거야 <br>마침내 붉은 태양 솟아오르는 <br>그날 그 순간까지 <br>그대가 있어 나는 행복해 <br>오늘도 이렇게 함께 있으니 <br>비록 지금 캄캄한 어둠일지라도 <br>난 참 행복해 <br>내일의 꿈도 물론 소중하지만 <br>지금 이 순간 우리 <br>다시 올 수 없는 시간들 <br>우리 함께 즐기는 거야 <br>그렇게 싸우는 거야 <br>마침내 붉은 태양 솟아오르는 <br>그날 그 순간까지 <br>마침내 붉은 태양 솟아오르는 <br>그날 그 순간까지 <br>]]></content><category term="김종환" label="김종환"/><category term="그대가 있어" label="그대가 있어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김종환/함안/</id><title>김종환 - 함안 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:20:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:20:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A2%85%ED%99%98/%ED%95%A8%EC%95%88/" title="김종환 - 함안 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[거동이 불편한 장애인이 <br>혼자 생활하다 <br>방안에서 숨진 채 <br>발견되었습니다 <br>강추위로 수도꼭지가 터지면서 <br>동사한 것으로 <br>추정되고 있습니다 <br>지난 2005년 12월 18일 <br>영하 10도의 강추위 속에 <br>팔다리를 잘 움직이지 못하는 <br>근육장애인 조 아무개 씨가 <br>숨진 채 발견되었다 <br>발견 당시 조 씨는 <br>동파한 수도관에서 <br>흘러 들어온 물에 <br>온몸이 얼어 있었다 <br>현장에는 흘러 들어오는 <br>물을 막아보려고 <br>토씨로 수도꼭지를 <br>감싼 흔적이 남아 있었다 <br>9년 전 어머니를 여의고 <br>한 달에 기초수급비와 <br>장애수당 20여 만원으로 <br>생활해온 조 씨는 <br>기름값을 아끼려고 <br>평소 보일러도 <br>거의 틀지 않은 채 생활했다 <br>조 씨는 1994년 <br>5급 장애로 판정 받았으나 <br>재판정을 받지 못한 채 <br>동사하기 전까지 <br>근육장애가 계속 <br>심해진 상태였다 <br>조 씨의 죽음 이후에도 <br>활동보조인이 없는 상황에서 <br>집에서 일어난 화재로 <br>김주영 송국현 <br>박지우 지훈 남매 등 <br>중증장애인들이 <br>연이어 목숨을 잃었다 <br>사회적 타살은 <br>아직도 계속되고 있다 <br>난 어쩔 수 없었어 <br>어쩔 수 없었어 <br>수도관이 터져 <br>차가운 물이 방바닥으로 <br>스멀스멀 흐르고 <br>내 몸을 감싸고 차츰 얼어붙어 <br>혈관을 굳게 만들고 <br>얼음처럼 딱딱해진 손가락으로 <br>일일구 누르지도 못하고 <br>마네킹처럼 말라가고 있었지 <br>그렇게 살과 피와 마음이 <br>차갑게 딱딱해져 가고 <br>세상아 세상아 <br>함께 살자고 <br>이 절망을 조금이라도 <br>함께 나누자고 <br>죽게 내버려 두지 말라고 <br>세상아 세상아 <br>난 어쩔 수 없었어 <br>어쩔 수 없었어 <br>그렇게 살과 피와 마음이 <br>차갑게 딱딱해져 가고 <br>세상아 세상아 <br>함께 살자고 <br>이 절망을 조금이라도 <br>함께 나누자고 <br>죽게 내버려 두지 말라고 <br>세상아 세상아 <br>난 어쩔 수 없었어 <br>어쩔 수 없었어 <br>어쩔 수 없었어 <br>]]></content><category term="김종환" label="김종환"/><category term="함안" label="함안"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김종환/마중물/</id><title>김종환 - 마중물 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:20:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:20:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A2%85%ED%99%98/%EB%A7%88%EC%A4%91%EB%AC%BC/" title="김종환 - 마중물 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[힘든가요 그대 오늘도 <br>거리에 시간들이 아플까 봐 <br>우리가 건네는 말들이 <br>그냥 흩어져 버릴까 봐 <br>두려운가요 그대 거리에서 <br>낯선 눈빛의 수많은 사람들과 <br>그 시간들이 우리를 <br>더 외롭게 만들까 봐 <br>하지만 그대 외로워 말아요 <br>그대는 다가올 참세상 마중물 <br>그대가 있어 힘든 세상에서도 <br>버티며 숨 쉬고 있는 걸 음 <br>미안해요 그대 지금껏 <br>한번도 말하진 못했지만 <br>이제는 말할게요 <br>그대 정말 고마워요 <br>하지만 그대 외로워 말아요 <br>그대는 다가올 참세상 마중물 <br>어두운 길도 우리 환한 빛으로 <br>세상을 물들여 가리니 음 <br>미안해요 그대 지금껏 <br>한번도 말하진 못했지만 <br>이제는 말할게요 <br>그대 정말 고마워요 <br>이제는 말할게요 <br>그대 정말 고마워요 <br>]]></content><category term="김종환" label="김종환"/><category term="마중물" label="마중물"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김종환/꽃다지2/</id><title>김종환 - 꽃다지2 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:20:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:20:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A2%85%ED%99%98/%EA%BD%83%EB%8B%A4%EC%A7%802/" title="김종환 - 꽃다지2 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쓰라린 기억을 지우며 가자 <br>창살 밖 그리운 하늘을 보면 <br>다시 서는 사람들 눈에 보이고 <br>투쟁의 그 모습 선연하여라 <br>부끄런 기억을 곱씹어 가자 <br>쓰러져 잠든 가슴 모두 일으켜 <br>녹슨 철문 부수고 기쁘게 맞을 <br>동지의 그 모습 선연하여라 <br>차가운 창살 안에 <br>내 비록 갇혔어도 <br>내 온몸의 핏줄을 주마 <br>붉은 핏줄 너에게 주마 <br>아아 거대하게 넘실거리는 <br>민중연대 전선에서 <br>손에 손 엮을 단결의 핏줄 <br>너에게 주마 <br>차가운 창살 안에 <br>내 비록 갇혔어도 <br>내 온몸의 기름을 주마 <br>적을 태울 기름을 주마 <br>아아 투쟁으로 끝내 승리할 <br>노동해방 전선에서 <br>굳게 움켜쥘 꽃병의 기름 <br>너에게 주마 <br>굳게 움켜쥘 꽃병의 기름 <br>너에게 주마 <br>]]></content><category term="김종환" label="김종환"/><category term="꽃다지2" label="꽃다지2"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김종환/점거하라/</id><title>김종환 - 점거하라 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:20:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:20:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A2%85%ED%99%98/%EC%A0%90%EA%B1%B0%ED%95%98%EB%9D%BC/" title="김종환 - 점거하라 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[온몸을 무쇠사슬로 칭칭 휘감고 <br>팔차선 피에 젖은 대로를 점거하리라 <br>이것이 우리의 파업 우리의 무기 <br>빼앗긴 권리 찾는 날까지 투쟁하리라 <br>방패에 찍히고 찍혀 나뒹굴어도 <br>찢겨진 천막 위에 해방의 깃발 세우니 <br>이것이 우리의 파업 우리의 무기 <br>마침내 장애해방 새 세상 쟁취하리라 <br>마침내 장애해방 새 세상 쟁취하리라 <br>]]></content><category term="김종환" label="김종환"/><category term="점거하라" label="점거하라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김종환/후회하지_마라/</id><title>김종환 - 후회하지 마라 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-05T18:20:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-05T18:20:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A2%85%ED%99%98/%ED%9B%84%ED%9A%8C%ED%95%98%EC%A7%80_%EB%A7%88%EB%9D%BC/" title="김종환 - 후회하지 마라 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[후회하지 마라 뒤돌아보지도 마 <br>비바람에 눈보라에 온몸 적셔도 <br>따스한 봄날에 태양이 함께 있는 한 <br>너와 나의 시간들은 더 아름다워라 <br>무너진 싸움터의 흔적들 <br>눈물 모아 삼켜버리고 <br>이제는 처음부터 다시 <br>시작해보는 거야 <br>가다가 가다가 다시 쓰러진대도 <br>되돌아올 수 없는 길 <br>살아서 살아서 끝내 이루고야 말 <br>노동해방의 나라 <br>무너진 싸움터의 흔적들 <br>눈물 모아 삼켜버리고 <br>이제는 처음부터 다시 <br>시작해보는 거야 <br>가다가 가다가 다시 쓰러진대도 <br>되돌아올 수 없는 길 <br>살아서 살아서 끝내 이루고야 말 <br>노동해방의 나라 <br>가다가 가다가 다시 쓰러진대도 <br>되돌아올 수 없는 길 <br>살아서 살아서 끝내 이루고야 말 <br>노동해방의 나라 <br>]]></content><category term="김종환" label="김종환"/><category term="후회하지 마라" label="후회하지 마라"/></entry></feed>