<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:42:24+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/빅스/늪_Six_Feet_Under/</id><title>빅스 - 늪 (Six Feet Under) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:32:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:32:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%85%EC%8A%A4/%EB%8A%AA_Six_Feet_Under/" title="빅스 - 늪 (Six Feet Under) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA['cause you got me going crazy <br>왜 미친 가슴이 널 보고 뛰는지 <br>늪에 빠진 것 같아 <br>점점 나를 조여 와 <br>Hey Psst 눈을 떠 <br>정신 차려봐 <br>시간 없어 당장 벗어나 <br>get out now oh 도망쳐 <br>Six feet under that's enough <br>그녀는 마치 달콤한 caffeine <br>날뛰는 심장이 널 갈구하잖아 <br>왜 나를 버려 왜 <br>가질 수 없는 Destiny <br>긴 꿈같이 홀린 뒤 <br>웃으며 넌 말하지 <br>Bye bye baby now <br>'cause you got me going crazy <br>왜 미친 가슴이 널 보고 뛰는지 <br>늪에 빠진 것 같아 <br>점점 나를 조여 와 <br>더는 답 없지 마치 <br>넌 내 머리 위로 <br>난 네 포로인 채 <br>벗어나려 해봐도 <br>결국 다시 너잖아 <br>넌 가끔씩 날 찾아와 <br>아름다운 순진한 얼굴로 날 <br>또다시 집어삼켜 <br>이미 사랑은 DOA <br>내 몫의 넌 fade away <br>길들지도 않는 pain <br>숨이 막혀와 <br>'cause you got me going crazy <br>왜 미친 가슴이 널 보고 뛰는지 <br>늪에 빠진 것 같아 <br>점점 나를 조여 와 <br>더는 답 없지 마치 <br>넌 내 머리 위로 <br>난 네 포로인 채 <br>벗어나려 해봐도 <br>결국 다시 너잖아 <br>Six feet under that's enough <br>그녀는 마치 투명한 coffin <br>Six feet under that's enough <br>Six feet under <br>악어떼가 나온다 도망가 <br>도망가도 더 빠져드는 <br>너란 늪에 놀아나 <br>네 오만한 자신감이 <br>분명 얄미운데 <br>망부석이야 내 발이 <br>내 예감이 틀리지 않은듯해 <br>넌 내 맘을 날려서 공중분해 <br>무덤덤하게 내 심장을 <br>또 드리블해 <br>미치겠네 넌 가만있어도 <br>날 미치게 해 <br>'cause you got me going crazy <br>니 말에 베어 난 또다시 <br>going insane <br>버틸 수가 없어 난 <br>버틸 수가 없어 난 <br>너 때문에 미쳐가 미쳐가 <br>한 치도 볼 수 없게 <br>넌 나를 가둔 채로 <br>내 두 귀를 막아 <br>두 귀를 막아 <br>끝내 무릎 꿇어도 <br>돌아보지 않는 너 <br>'cause you got me going crazy <br>전부를 다 바쳐도 <br>날 보지 않는 너 <br>이제 그만 꺼내줘 <br>벗어나고 싶어 널 <br>너라는 덫에 갇혀 <br>미쳐 지쳐도 또 <br>난 그저 one of your men <br>갖지 못할 신기루 <br>제발 나를 구해줘 <br>]]></content><category term="빅스" label="빅스"/><category term="늪 (Six Feet Under)" label="늪 (Six Feet Under)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/빅스/다이너마이트/</id><title>빅스 - 다이너마이트 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:32:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:32:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%85%EC%8A%A4/%EB%8B%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%84%88%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B4%ED%8A%B8/" title="빅스 - 다이너마이트 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's too late girl <br>All mine her mind <br>All mine her mind <br>All mine her mind <br>Maybe I'm jealous <br>뭘 봐 이거 놔 <br>진정하라 하지 마 <br>무슨 소용이야 다 <br>이미 뻔히 저기 끝이 보여 <br>바텐더 한 잔 더 <br>I need more one shot <br>one more two shot <br>흐트러지게 내버려 둬 let go <br>놔둬 gonna shake it down <br>ooh 너는 저기 기우는 moon <br>까맣게 사라져갈 뿐 <br>늦어버린 time <br>시곌 돌리고 되돌려봐도 <br>I got one night <br>세상을 다 뒤집어 <br>come on girl <br>Dynamite <br>오늘만 나 조금 욱할게 oh <br>Dynamite <br>미쳐 날뛰어 어질러 <br>Shake it down <br>Dynamite <br>온 세상을 엎어서라도 girl <br>제발 오늘 넌 나를 떠나가지 마 <br>수리수리 이뤄져라 All mine <br>수리수리 돌아서라 Her mind <br>안 믿어 난 뭔가 잘못된 거야 <br>넌 아무것도 몰라 <br>그녀는 내 거일 운명이었어 <br>ooh 이건 악몽 같은 꿈 <br>누군가 장난친 것뿐 <br>어긋난 만남 <br>시곌 돌리고 되돌려봐도 <br>I got one night <br>세상을 다 뒤집어 <br>come on girl <br>Dynamite <br>오늘만 나 삐뚤어질게 oh <br>Dynamite <br>밀쳐 던져 흔들어 <br>Shake it down <br>Dynamite <br>온 세상을 바꿔서라도 girl <br>어떻게든 넌 나를 떠나가지 마 <br>이건 다 꿈이야 맞아 yes right <br>악몽 속의 악몽 같아 <br>내가 반항해도 <br>누가 날 자꾸 잠들게 마성의 <br>자장가를 불러 주나 봐 <br>온 세상 악당이 모여도 <br>이런 나쁜 장난은 안 해 Oh No <br>난 하루아침에 마녀가 된 백설 <br>분명히 뭔가 잘못됐어 <br>내일이면 삼켜야만 할 현실인 걸 <br>씁쓸하지만 알고 있지만 다 <br>I got one night <br>너를 보낼 수가 없어 <br>끝나지 않은 story <br>Dynamite <br>원래 주인공은 나인데 oh <br>Dynamite <br>악역이 돼버렸어 어쩌다 <br>Dynamite <br>못된 맘을 먹어서라도 girl <br>뺏고 싶은 너 나를 떠나가지 마 <br>Dynamite <br>오늘만 나 조금 욱할게 oh <br>Dynamite <br>미쳐 날뛰어 어질러 <br>Shake it down <br>Dynamite <br>온 세상을 엎어서라도 girl <br>제발 오늘 넌 나를 떠나가지 마 <br>수리수리 이뤄져라 All mine <br>수리수리 수리수리 <br>수리수리 돌아서라 Her mind <br>]]></content><category term="빅스" label="빅스"/><category term="다이너마이트" label="다이너마이트"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/빅스/Milky_Way/</id><title>빅스 - Milky Way - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:32:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:32:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%85%EC%8A%A4/Milky_Way/" title="빅스 - Milky Way - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah you're my bright light <br>We're walking on the milky way <br>너와 발을 맞춰 걷기 시작한 <br>그날 후로 Everyday <br>괜히 어깨가 으쓱해지고 <br>뭘 해도 자신 있게 돼 <br>혹시 내 머리에 들어와 <br>나를 간지럽히고 있니 <br>자꾸 입꼬리가 올라가 <br>내려오질 않잖아 <br>girl you are my bright light <br>빛나도 너를 더 빛나게 할래 tonight <br>girl I am your bright light <br>넌 그저 빛나기만 해줘 girl <br>no more question answer <br>서로에게 정답이야 <br>Yeah <br>우리들의 관계를 의심하지 마 <br>난 네 앞에선 절대 돌아서지 않아 <br>새까만 밤하늘의 별을 <br>모두 모아 모아 <br>너를 더 눈 부시게 할래 <br>baby you're my you're my <br>네 눈 속에 비친 내 얼굴 <br>그 속엔 반짝이는 미소 뿐 <br>세상에 빛나는 무엇보다 <br>난 너야 너야 <br>네 매력은 끝도 없이 몰아쳐 <br>러블리한 허리케인 <br>쉽게 널 벗어날 수가 없어 <br>자꾸 빠져들게 돼 <br>넌 또 내 가슴에 들어와 <br>내 온도를 높이고 있어 <br>자꾸 내 심장이 요동쳐 <br>진정을 못 하잖아 <br>girl you are my starlight <br>세상을 전부 다 푸른 빛으로 tonight <br>girl I am your star right <br>영원히 빛나게 해 줄게 girl <br>no more question answer <br>서로에게 정답이야 <br>내가 받은 감동보다 <br>커다란 감동으로 보답할 거야 <br>새까만 밤하늘의 별을 <br>모두 모아 모아 <br>너를 더 눈 부시게 할래 <br>baby you're my you're my <br>네 눈 속에 비친 내 얼굴 <br>그 속엔 반짝이는 미소 뿐 <br>세상에 빛나는 무엇보다 <br>난 너야 너야 <br>아 네가 좋아서 주체가 잘 안돼 <br>맘이 너무 예쁜 너 애기 누나 해 <br>아 너무 너무 너무 좋아 <br>부숴버려 아파트 <br>너무 너무 좋아 부숴버려 지구 <br>말했잖아 이 바닥을 갤럭시로 <br>만들 거야 난 너 아니면 싫어 <br>오늘도 밤하늘에다 빌어 <br>지나온 시간보다 <br>지나갈 시간이 길어 <br>매번 상상하지 못한 선물처럼 <br>다가가지 my girl <br>별을 향한 설레는 걸음 <br>빛나는 Highway <br>You're my milky way <br>이런 기분일까 <br>넌 마치 아이처럼 <br>내게 미소 짓는 걸 <br>그런 너를 담은 맘이 <br>녹아버릴 것 같아 <br>Whenever 너를 바라보며 <br>빛나 줄게 so bright <br>Wherever 함께라는 그거 <br>하나면 돼 so bright <br>슬픔보다 행복할 날이 <br>지금보다 앞으로가 더 <br>우리에게는 웃을 일이 <br>더 많잖아 so right <br>새까만 밤하늘의 별을 <br>모두 모아 모아 <br>너를 더 눈 부시게 할래 <br>baby you're my you're my <br>네 눈 속에 비친 내 얼굴 <br>그 속엔 반짝이는 미소 뿐 <br>세상에 빛나는 무엇보다 <br>난 너야 너야 <br>]]></content><category term="빅스" label="빅스"/><category term="Milky Way" label="Milky Way"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/알리_ALi/Chitty_Chitty_Bang_Bang_주문하시겠습니까_팝콘_소녀/</id><title>알리_ALi - Chitty Chitty Bang Bang (주문하시겠습니까 팝콘 소녀) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:32:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:32:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%8C%EB%A6%AC_ALi/Chitty_Chitty_Bang_Bang_%EC%A3%BC%EB%AC%B8%ED%95%98%EC%8B%9C%EA%B2%A0%EC%8A%B5%EB%8B%88%EA%B9%8C_%ED%8C%9D%EC%BD%98_%EC%86%8C%EB%85%80/" title="알리_ALi - Chitty Chitty Bang Bang (주문하시겠습니까 팝콘 소녀) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너의 말이 그냥 나는 웃긴다 <br>너의 말이 그냥 나는 웃긴다 <br>너의 말이 그냥 나는 웃긴다 <br>그냥 그냥 나는 나는 웃긴다 <br>그 누구도 내게 간섭마 <br>다 똑같은 말도 하지마 <br>여기 나만의 것 It's my world <br>더 이상 이젠 나를 찾지마 <br>안간힘을 쓰고 있잖아 <br>걱정 따윈 필요 없어 난 <br>어차피 나는 혼자 <br>떠드는 니 숨만 차 <br>그냥 모른척 지나가줘 <br>쉬지 않고 난 계속 달려가 <br>겁내지 말고 나를 따라와 <br>조금 더 높이 날아가 <br>I can make you want me so what <br>누구보다 나를 더 믿는걸 <br>못이기는 척 나를 따라와 <br>gonna be the one that I want <br>Chitty Chitty Bang Bang <br>Chitty Chitty Bang Bang <br>너의 말이 그냥 나는 웃긴다 <br>너의 말이 그냥 나는 웃긴다 <br>너의 말이 그냥 나는 웃긴다 <br>그냥 그냥 나는 나는 웃긴다 <br>여기까지 혼자 왔어 나 <br>손 내밀때 어디 있었나 <br>여기 나만의 것 It's my world <br>그냥 나를 지켜봐 <br>사실 너도 나를 알잖아 <br>나의 무대가 두렵잖아 <br>퍽이나 위하는 척 <br>내 걱정 해주는 척 <br>차라리 그냥 지나가줘 <br>쉬지 않고 난 계속 달려가 <br>겁내지 말고 나를 따라와 <br>조금 더 높이 날아가 <br>I can make you want me so what <br>누구보다 나를 더 믿는걸 <br>못 이기는 척 나를 따라와 <br>gonna be the one that I want <br>Chitty Chitty Bang Bang <br>Chitty Chitty Bang Bang <br>Chitty Chitty Bang Bang <br>넌 상대가 안돼 <br>쓸데없는 참견말고 가던 길 갈래 <br>내 무대는 포-폭발해 <br>널 미치게 만들어 <br>더 큰일이 나기 전에 <br>그냥 내 말 들어 <br>너의 말이 그냥 나는 웃긴다 <br>어디서 감히 그러다가 맞는다 <br>내가 등장하면 <br>All my lady is going down <br>You better know my Name <br>너만 모르고 있잖아 <br>나를 조정하길 바랐니 <br>원하는걸 또 또 telling me <br>제발 정신차려 그대로 다 차렷 <br>거기 까지 I can make it right <br>쉬지 않고 난 계속 달려가 <br>겁내지 말고 나를 따라와 <br>조금 더 높이 날아가 <br>I can make you want me so what <br>누구보다 나를 더 믿는걸 <br>못 이기는 척 나를 따라와 <br>gonna be the one that I want <br>Chitty Chitty Bang Bang <br>Chitty Chitty Bang Bang <br>너의 말이 그냥 나는 웃긴다 <br>너의 말이 그냥 나는 웃긴다 <br>너의 말이 그냥 나는 웃긴다 <br>그냥 그냥 나는 나는 웃긴다 <br>]]></content><category term="알리 (ALi)" label="알리 (ALi)"/><category term="Chitty Chitty Bang Bang (주문하시겠습니까 팝콘 소녀)" label="Chitty Chitty Bang Bang (주문하시겠습니까 팝콘 소녀)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신용재_포맨/가끔_뜨거운_심장_양철로봇/</id><title>신용재_포맨 - 가끔 (뜨거운 심장 양철로봇) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:32:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:32:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9A%A9%EC%9E%AC_%ED%8F%AC%EB%A7%A8/%EA%B0%80%EB%81%94_%EB%9C%A8%EA%B1%B0%EC%9A%B4_%EC%8B%AC%EC%9E%A5_%EC%96%91%EC%B2%A0%EB%A1%9C%EB%B4%87/" title="신용재_포맨 - 가끔 (뜨거운 심장 양철로봇) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘밤은 유난히 추워 <br>가만히 밤 하늘을 또 다시 보고 있어 <br>벌써 1년이 지나 <br>아련하게 다가와 추억 <br>널 집에 데려다 줬던 그 기억들이 다 <br>너무 소중해 <br>언젠가 널 내 옆에 두고 <br>그땐 그랬었지 <br>라며 추억들을 <br>나눌 거라고 생각했었지 <br>넌 나와 같을까 되뇌어보지만 <br>감이 오질 않아 <br>그냥 가끔 그리울 뿐인데 <br>너와 입을 맞추고 널 감싸 안았던 <br>아주 가끔 보고플 뿐인데 <br>오늘은 왜 이렇게 눈물이 나는지 <br>오랜만에 열어본 서랍 속엔 <br>환하게 웃고 있는 네 사진들 <br>버리게 되면 영영 <br>널 잊게 될까 봐 두려워져 <br>언젠가 널 내 옆에 두고 <br>그땐 그랬었지 <br>라며 추억들을 <br>나눌 거라고 생각했었지 <br>넌 나와 같을까 나만 아는 걸까 <br>이미 넌 무감각해졌으니까 <br>그냥 가끔 그리울 뿐인데 <br>너와 입을 맞추고 널 감싸 안았던 <br>아주 가끔 보고플 뿐인데 <br>오늘은 왜 이렇게 눈물이 나는지 <br>있을 때 잘할걸 후회 하면서도 <br>돌이킬 자신이 없는걸 <br>이렇게 나만 바보처럼 <br>내 맘 가두고서 살아 <br>my baby <br>I miss you I miss you baby <br>I miss you 자꾸 왜 눈물이 나는지 <br>my baby 눈물이 나는지 <br>그냥 가끔 그리울 뿐인데 <br>너와 입을 맞추고 널 감싸 안았던 <br>아주 가끔 보고플 뿐인데 <br>오늘은 왜 이렇게 눈물이 나는지 <br>]]></content><category term="신용재 (포맨)" label="신용재 (포맨)"/><category term="가끔 (뜨거운 심장 양철로봇)" label="가끔 (뜨거운 심장 양철로봇)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/모니카/기억상실_오즈의_마법사_도로시/</id><title>모니카 - 기억상실 (오즈의 마법사 도로시) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:32:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:32:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AA%A8%EB%8B%88%EC%B9%B4/%EA%B8%B0%EC%96%B5%EC%83%81%EC%8B%A4_%EC%98%A4%EC%A6%88%EC%9D%98_%EB%A7%88%EB%B2%95%EC%82%AC_%EB%8F%84%EB%A1%9C%EC%8B%9C/" title="모니카 - 기억상실 (오즈의 마법사 도로시) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[떠난다고 그래서 <br>떠나라고 말했어 <br>사랑하다 한번쯤 하는 말이라서 <br>올 거라고 다 안다고 <br>거울에 비친 나를 달래고 <br>벌써 손가락 열개를 다 접고 <br>애써 하루를 또 세어도 <br>보이지 않아 아직도 <br>내 사랑 하나 못찾고 <br>더듬거리는 손으로 <br>네 사진을 찾다가 <br>자꾸 멀어버리는 내 눈은 <br>한참 눈물 쏟아내고 <br>내 맘은 지독한 멍이 생기고 <br>잊으라고 그래서 <br>안된다고 말했어 <br>살아가다 한번쯤 만날 것 같아서 <br>나 운다고 아프다고 <br>어느새 지친 소릴 내보고 <br>네가 걸어오던 길에서 멈춰서 <br>안아주던 곳에서 <br>난 눈물을 닦아봐도 <br>보이지 않아 아직도 <br>내 사랑 하나 못찾고 <br>더듬거리는 손으로 <br>네 사진을 찾다가 <br>자꾸 멀어버리는 내 눈은 <br>한참 눈물 쏟아내고 <br>내 맘은 지독한 멍이 생기고 <br>사랑에 부딪혀 헐어버리고 <br>네가 깊게 새긴 네가 소리없이 남긴 <br>너란 상처들로 덮힌 나를 <br>불쌍하다고 느낀다면 <br>다시 날 사랑할까 <br>화장을 하고 지우고 <br>옷을 꺼내고 입어도 <br>아무리 해도 하나도 <br>기억할 수 없나봐 <br>사랑한다는 말도 들었던 <br>웃는 내 모습을 찾고 돌아올 널 위해 <br>내가 같아야만 하는데 <br>조금도 기억이 나지를 않아 <br>]]></content><category term="모니카" label="모니카"/><category term="기억상실 (오즈의 마법사 도로시)" label="기억상실 (오즈의 마법사 도로시)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/희철_HEECHUL/나비잠_Sweet_Dream_Inst/</id><title>희철_HEECHUL - 나비잠 (Sweet Dream) (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:34:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:34:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9D%AC%EC%B2%A0_HEECHUL/%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84%EC%9E%A0_Sweet_Dream_Inst/" title="희철_HEECHUL - 나비잠 (Sweet Dream) (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어느덧 흘러간 <br>시간을 수놓을 수 있는 밤 <br>짧지 않던 세월 <br>서로가 가까워진 지금을 <br>웃으며 기억하고 싶어 <br>끝이 온다 말을 해도 <br>언젠가 헤어진다 해도 <br>내일 당장 사라져도 <br>잊어버리게 하지 않도록 <br>기억하도록 <br>오래 지나도 잊을 수 없게 <br>기억하도록 <br>오늘을 되돌아보며 <br>감은 두 눈에 머금고 <br>꿈 속까지 미뤄 잠이 들 테죠 <br>마지막 바람이 불며 <br>끝나는 날을 알려도 <br>함께 했던 추억 사진의 <br>빛이 바래진대도 <br>웃으며 기억하고 싶어 <br>끝이 온다 말을 해도 <br>언젠가 헤어진다 해도 <br>내일 당장 사라져도 <br>잊어버리게 하지 않도록 <br>기억하도록 <br>오래 지나도 잊을 수 없게 <br>기억하도록 <br>오늘을 되돌아보며 <br>감은 두 눈에 머금고 <br>꿈 속에 담아내려 잠이 들 테죠 <br>봄의 꽃 여름의 나비 <br>가을의 낙엽 <br>그 겨울의 달빛 펼쳐진다면 <br>우리의 추억 또한 <br>영원히 곁에 떠오르니까 <br>시들 수 없어 <br>인연의 꽃을 마음에 피워 <br>망각의 낙엽이 져도 <br>하늘 달을 보며 그 땔 <br>떠올릴 테니 편히 잠을 청해요]]></content><category term="희철 (HEECHUL)" label="희철 (HEECHUL)"/><category term="나비잠 (Sweet Dream) (Inst.)" label="나비잠 (Sweet Dream) (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/희철_HEECHUL/나비잠_Sweet_Dream/</id><title>희철_HEECHUL - 나비잠 (Sweet Dream) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:34:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:34:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%9D%AC%EC%B2%A0_HEECHUL/%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84%EC%9E%A0_Sweet_Dream/" title="희철_HEECHUL - 나비잠 (Sweet Dream) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어느덧 흘러간 <br>시간을 수놓을 수 있는 밤 <br>짧지 않던 세월 <br>서로가 가까워진 지금을 <br>웃으며 기억하고 싶어 <br>끝이 온다 말을 해도 <br>언젠가 헤어진다 해도 <br>내일 당장 사라져도 <br>잊어버리게 하지 않도록 <br>기억하도록 <br>오래 지나도 잊을 수 없게 <br>기억하도록 <br>오늘을 되돌아보며 <br>감은 두 눈에 머금고 <br>꿈 속까지 미뤄 잠이 들 테죠 <br>마지막 바람이 불며 <br>끝나는 날을 알려도 <br>함께 했던 추억 사진의 <br>빛이 바래진대도 <br>웃으며 기억하고 싶어 <br>끝이 온다 말을 해도 <br>언젠가 헤어진다 해도 <br>내일 당장 사라져도 <br>잊어버리게 하지 않도록 <br>기억하도록 <br>오래 지나도 잊을 수 없게 <br>기억하도록 <br>오늘을 되돌아보며 <br>감은 두 눈에 머금고 <br>꿈 속에 담아내려 잠이 들 테죠 <br>봄의 꽃 여름의 나비 <br>가을의 낙엽 <br>그 겨울의 달빛 펼쳐진다면 <br>우리의 추억 또한 <br>영원히 곁에 떠오르니까 <br>시들 수 없어 <br>인연의 꽃을 마음에 피워 <br>망각의 낙엽이 져도 <br>하늘 달을 보며 그 땔 <br>떠올릴 테니 편히 잠을 청해요 <br>]]></content><category term="희철 (HEECHUL)" label="희철 (HEECHUL)"/><category term="나비잠 (Sweet Dream)" label="나비잠 (Sweet Dream)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레디_Reddy/너라도_Feat_김보아_of_SPICA_Inst/</id><title>레디_Reddy - 너라도 (Feat. 김보아 of SPICA) (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:34:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:34:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EB%94%94_Reddy/%EB%84%88%EB%9D%BC%EB%8F%84_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EB%B3%B4%EC%95%84_of_SPICA_Inst/" title="레디_Reddy - 너라도 (Feat. 김보아 of SPICA) (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그게 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 나는 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 <br>난 젊고 능력 있어 <br>아직까지 ya <br>영원하길 바래 이 <br>모든 것들이 ya <br>묶이는 게 싫어 나는 그게 너라도 <br>어젯밤에 만난 여자들의 전화도 <br>오늘이 지나면 안 받을 거야 <br>니가 보고 싶은데 그냥 참을 거야 <br>깊어지기 싫어 그게 너라도 <br>아프기는 싫어 그게 너라도 <br>헤어지고 또 누군가를 만나도 <br>다시 또 아파질 걸 다들 알아도 <br>깨져버릴 사랑 같은 걸 <br>다시 말하고 <br>아무렇지 않게 웃잖아 <br>내일 보자고 <br>시간이 지나면 괜찮을 걸 알아도 <br>나는 못하겠어 너랑 깊어지는 거 <br>가벼운 게 낫지 그러면 아마도 <br>나중에 내가 너를 <br>놓아주기 쉬울걸 <br>그게 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 나는 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 <br>니가 나를 바라볼 때 <br>모든 것이 선명해져 <br>내게서 돌아설 때면 <br>그대 온기가 흩어져 <br>나를 바라보는 너의 눈빛은 날 <br>외롭게 하지 <br>어서 나를 안아줘 <br>아무도 모르게 <br>시간이 가 tic toc tic toc <br>흘러가 도망가듯이 <br>모두 잊어버려 <br>한 번만 더 날 안아줘 <br>모두 잊을 수 있게 <br>Baby 너는 <br>영원히 내 손 꼭 잡아줘 <br>그게 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 나는 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 <br>시간이 지나면 괜찮을 걸 알아도 <br>나는 못하겠어 너랑 깊어지는 거 <br>가벼운 게 낫지 그러면 아마도 <br>나중에 내가 너를 <br>놓아주기 쉬울걸 <br>그게 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 나는 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 <br>]]></content><category term="레디 (Reddy)" label="레디 (Reddy)"/><category term="너라도 (Feat. 김보아 of SPICA) (Inst.)" label="너라도 (Feat. 김보아 of SPICA) (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레디_Reddy/너라도_Feat_김보아_of_SPICA/</id><title>레디_Reddy - 너라도 (Feat. 김보아 of SPICA) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:34:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:34:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EB%94%94_Reddy/%EB%84%88%EB%9D%BC%EB%8F%84_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EB%B3%B4%EC%95%84_of_SPICA/" title="레디_Reddy - 너라도 (Feat. 김보아 of SPICA) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그게 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 나는 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 <br>난 젊고 능력 있어 <br>아직까지 ya <br>영원하길 바래 이 <br>모든 것들이 ya <br>묶이는 게 싫어 나는 그게 너라도 <br>어젯밤에 만난 여자들의 전화도 <br>오늘이 지나면 안 받을 거야 <br>니가 보고 싶은데 그냥 참을 거야 <br>깊어지기 싫어 그게 너라도 <br>아프기는 싫어 그게 너라도 <br>헤어지고 또 누군가를 만나도 <br>다시 또 아파질 걸 다들 알아도 <br>깨져버릴 사랑 같은 걸 <br>다시 말하고 <br>아무렇지 않게 웃잖아 <br>내일 보자고 <br>시간이 지나면 괜찮을 걸 알아도 <br>나는 못하겠어 너랑 깊어지는 거 <br>가벼운 게 낫지 그러면 아마도 <br>나중에 내가 너를 <br>놓아주기 쉬울걸 <br>그게 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 나는 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 <br>니가 나를 바라볼 때 <br>모든 것이 선명해져 <br>내게서 돌아설 때면 <br>그대 온기가 흩어져 <br>나를 바라보는 너의 눈빛은 날 <br>외롭게 하지 <br>어서 나를 안아줘 <br>아무도 모르게 <br>시간이 가 tic toc tic toc <br>흘러가 도망가듯이 <br>모두 잊어버려 <br>한 번만 더 날 안아줘 <br>모두 잊을 수 있게 <br>Baby 너는 <br>영원히 내 손 꼭 잡아줘 <br>그게 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 나는 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 <br>시간이 지나면 괜찮을 걸 알아도 <br>나는 못하겠어 너랑 깊어지는 거 <br>가벼운 게 낫지 그러면 아마도 <br>나중에 내가 너를 <br>놓아주기 쉬울걸 <br>그게 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 나는 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 이건 안돼 <br>아무리 너라도 너라도 <br>]]></content><category term="레디 (Reddy)" label="레디 (Reddy)"/><category term="너라도 (Feat. 김보아 of SPICA)" label="너라도 (Feat. 김보아 of SPICA)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Weeknd/I_Feel_It_Coming_Feat_Daft_Punk/</id><title>The_Weeknd - I Feel It Coming (Feat. Daft Punk) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:34:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:34:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Weeknd/I_Feel_It_Coming_Feat_Daft_Punk/" title="The_Weeknd - I Feel It Coming (Feat. Daft Punk) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tell me what you really like <br>Baby I can take my time <br>We don't ever have to fight <br>Just take it step-by-step <br>I can see it in your eyes <br>Cause they never tell me lies <br>I can feel that body shake <br>And the heat between your legs <br>You've been scared of love <br>and what it did to you <br>You don't have to run <br>I know what you've been through <br>Just a simple touch <br>and it can set you free <br>We don't have to rush <br>when you're alone with me <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>You are not the single type <br>So baby this the perfect time <br>I'm just trying to get you high <br>And faded off this touch <br>You don't need a lonely night <br>So baby I can make it right <br>You just got to let me try <br>To give you what you want <br>You've been scared of love <br>and what it did to you <br>You don't have to run <br>I know what you've been through <br>Just a simple touch <br>and it can set you free <br>We don't have to rush <br>when you're alone with me <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>You've been scared of love <br>And what it did to you <br>You don't have to run <br>I know what you've been through <br>Just a simple touch <br>And it can set you free <br>We don't have to rush <br>When you're alone with me <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I know what you feel right now <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I know what you say right now babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming babe <br>I feel it coming babe <br>]]></content><category term="The Weeknd" label="The Weeknd"/><category term="I Feel It Coming (Feat. Daft Punk)" label="I Feel It Coming (Feat. Daft Punk)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Trials/</id><title>Speak - Trials - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:34:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:34:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Trials/" title="Speak - Trials - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Calling in sick <br>Static on the other line <br>He'll be just fine <br><br>By the time you're rich enough to pay <br>For every ritual you crave <br>You struggle just to stay awake <br><br>And I think I've earned a clearer head <br>But I'd settle for a face instead <br>Or lips that shred like yours do <br><br>And I look out on fire in the sky <br>To imagine it a healthy start <br>And I shook your hand <br>And pulled the card away <br><br>It's alright <br>It's alright <br>It's alright <br>It's alright <br>It's alright <br><br>Standing in line for a trial by fire <br>Standing in line for a trial by fire by fire <br>Standing in line for a trial by fire <br>Standing in line for a trial by fire by fire <br><br>Skip to the end <br>You wander this enchanted rock <br>And burn your skin <br><br>By the time you're rich enough to pay <br>Pay for every ritual you've made <br>You struggle just to stay away <br><br>And for the moment I can't breathe <br>But that's just the way you'll always be <br>And the odyssey is above you <br><br>And I look out on fire <br>And a healthy star <br><br>Father I am young but I'm not afraid <br>No I'm not afraid of this <br>And father I am young but I'm not afraid <br>No I won't be afraid of this <br>But it's all that's left <br>To wonder why <br>Sunburned skin has to feel like <br>Sunburned skin has to feel like <br>Sunburned skin has to feel like <br>Sunburned skin has to feel like fire <br><br>Now father I am young but I'm not afraid <br>I'm young but I'm not afraid]]></content><category term="Speak" label="Speak"/><category term="Trials" label="Trials"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/The_Meantime/</id><title>Speak - The Meantime - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:34:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:34:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/The_Meantime/" title="Speak - The Meantime - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In the meantime <br>While the dust sets <br>And we've said it all <br>Just remember <br>What we promised <br>When the gloves were off <br><br>In the daylight <br>When we notice <br>There's no cover <br>Just remember <br>What it feels like <br>When the clothes are off <br><br>You're right <br>You're right <br>You're right <br>You're right <br><br>When the wall breaks <br>And the old dream <br>Is a dirty word <br>Can you promise <br>Not to turn out <br>All the will we've earned <br><br>In the fallout <br>When we fall away <br>And the tides have turned <br>Will the white wash <br>Cover everything <br>Or do cracks emerge <br><br>You're right <br>You're right <br>You're right <br>You're right <br><br>After nine lives <br>That I sweat for you <br>Is it so hard <br>To remember <br>That I'm human too <br><br>In the firelight <br>When the bonds break <br>Do we hold them up <br>With a blank slate <br>And the hindsight <br>That we're dangerous <br><br>You're right <br>You're right <br>You're right <br>You're right <br><br>Every fight you ever knew <br>You could have someone to fight for you <br>And every fight you lose <br>You could have known someone who's fighting too <br>And I can't know and I can't know and I can't know what the edge is like <br>Every time the center falls away from you I'm on your side]]></content><category term="Speak" label="Speak"/><category term="The Meantime" label="The Meantime"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/11_12_13/</id><title>Speak - 11/12/13 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:34:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:34:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/11_12_13/" title="Speak - 11/12/13 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Why is eleven not enough <br>Why don't we ever toughen up <br>Where do we finally find the nerve <br>I've denied it all I can, but no is just a word <br><br>Why doesn't twelve mean something more <br>I could insist but I'm not sure <br>There's nothing wrong with moving slow <br>But I never would have gone if I never said I'd go <br><br>Why don't we gamble on thirteen <br>There's knowing at the end but there's wisdom in between <br>You can trade the end or the ire in your eyes <br>Cause they might enjoy the game, but you'll win it every time <br><br>Why don't we give fourteen the floor <br>Let's see what he says, he's been here before <br>They they ain't always on the team <br>But he'll give you what you want and he'll say just what he means]]></content><category term="Speak" label="Speak"/><category term="11/12/13" label="11/12/13"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Heavy_Metal_War/</id><title>Speak - Heavy Metal War - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:34:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:34:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Heavy_Metal_War/" title="Speak - Heavy Metal War - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How long ago <br>Heavy metal wars <br>Oh, and you, you've been faithful too <br>But they don't wanna know <br>Every time you try <br><br>Snow, spire aisles outlined <br>Red white and gold <br>Fire on your mind <br>Oh and you, you can swan dive too <br>But it's so far below <br>And you'd rather burn inside <br><br>Just behave yourself <br>Stay silent if nothing else <br><br>And you, you've been saddled too <br>But they don't want to know <br>Every time I try <br><br>Some other mind <br>Says be brave all your life <br>But they're all alive <br>Just behave]]></content><category term="Speak" label="Speak"/><category term="Heavy Metal War" label="Heavy Metal War"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Congo/</id><title>Speak - Congo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Congo/" title="Speak - Congo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know we're safe for now <br>But I believe you have something to talk about <br>And as the nights grow long <br>It feels like I've been on my own <br><br>You can pretend alright <br>But they can't help but notice it every night <br>And if they could eat they would <br>Cause hunger's all they've understood <br><br>So why don't you tell us what it is what it is what it is <br>You know they don't need to know you <br>But they're here if you forget you forget you forget <br>Or you lose art to darkness <br><br>Well I've been wrecked before <br>But I don't really dwell on it anymore <br>And I know you've been wrecked too <br>The records of it work for you <br><br>So why don't you tell us what it is what it is what it is <br>You know they don't need to know you <br>But they're here if you forget you forget you forget <br>And you lose art to darkness <br><br>Winter night, realize you won't <br>Even if it feels right you won't <br>If it sounds like insight, you won't <br>Ivory from the insides and you won't]]></content><category term="Speak" label="Speak"/><category term="Congo" label="Congo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Be_Reasonable_Diane/</id><title>Speak - Be Reasonable, Diane - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Be_Reasonable_Diane/" title="Speak - Be Reasonable, Diane - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's nothing wrong with a holiday <br>There's something wrong with a telephone <br>It doesn't bother me anyway <br>It's not the first time I'm on my own <br><br>Oh get it off enough's enough's enough <br>Oh I'll go on and on and on and on <br><br>I know it feels like we always fight <br>I know it feels like I'm always wrong <br>But I get the feeling I'm always right <br>And even more as the fights go on <br><br>Oh get it off enough's enough's enough <br>Oh I'll go on and on and on and on <br><br>WAIT <br>You might get lost in that mysterious state <br>And maybe I won't really know what to say <br>Cause maybe I don't wanna stand at the gate <br>And E E E <br><br>Every time that you fall asleep <br>Well you're distractingly close to me <br>And how we work is a mystery <br>So maybe work is the thing we need <br><br>Oh get it off <br>Oh I'll go on <br><br>WAIT <br>You might get lost in that mysterious state <br>And maybe I won't really know what to say <br>Cause maybe I don't wanna stand at the gate <br>And I I I <br><br>I'm hoping girl that I'll meet you in a world <br>That I'm working for, I'm working for you know <br>If you work too well then the faster we're through <br>So be reasonable, Diane <br><br>I might hold onto that mysterious state <br>Between dream and awake, between dream and awake you know <br>If you work too well then the faster we're through <br>So be reasonable, be reasonable Diane <br><br>Tonight I need a holiday <br>If I could have one cigarette <br>To hide me in a cloud of smoke <br>I'd disappear <br><br>WAIT <br>You might get lost in that mysterious state <br>And maybe I won't really know what to say <br>Cause maybe I don't wanna stand at the gate <br>And I I I <br><br>I'm hoping girl that I'll meet you in a world <br>That I'm working for, I'm working for you know <br>If you work too well then the faster we're through <br>So be reasonable, Diane <br><br>I might hold onto that mysterious state <br>Between dream and awake, between dream and awake you know <br>If you work too well then the faster we're through <br>So be reasonable, be reasonable Diane]]></content><category term="Speak" label="Speak"/><category term="Be Reasonable, Diane" label="Be Reasonable, Diane"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Modern_Art/</id><title>Speak - Modern Art - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Modern_Art/" title="Speak - Modern Art - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't even know how to feel anymore <br>Tastes like pride, satisfied, on a roll <br>And you could sell them anyone dead or alive <br>Anyone who's anyone can't wait to die <br><br>Ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh <br>Ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh <br><br>If you're feeling trivial while you wait for the proof <br>Cause everybody's critical when they've got nothing to lose <br>Beat me like a brother would with a wink and smile <br>Cause you believe in everything but just for a while <br><br>Ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh <br>Ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh <br><br>If I could only get my image straight <br>Then maybe they'd believe that I'm tough <br>But now I'm fretting like a light weight <br><br>And if you come at it a another way <br>Then suddenly I'm heavy enough <br>And all the fretting was a mistake <br><br>Ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh <br>Ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh <br>Ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh <br>Ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh <br>Ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh <br>Ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh <br>Ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh <br>Ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh ahhhhh]]></content><category term="Speak" label="Speak"/><category term="Modern Art" label="Modern Art"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Oh_Lord/</id><title>Speak - Oh Lord - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Oh_Lord/" title="Speak - Oh Lord - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh lord, it's another one <br>It's nothing to be scared of <br>As long as you're prepared, oh <br><br>Tell me that you're lonely <br>You won't control me <br>I've been a possession <br>You must respect them <br><br>Take whatever meaning <br>This is believing <br>Tell me that we're lonely <br>Come on control me, yeah <br><br>Oh lord, it's another one <br><br>Oh lord, it's another one <br>It's nothing to be scared of <br>As long as you're prepared, oh <br><br>Tell me that you own me <br>But you don't know me <br>You would leave a light on <br>So I could find home <br><br>Maybe I'd believe you <br>If I could see you <br>But every time I look close <br>I hear an old ghost <br><br>Cause I can see the way that you look at me <br>Like you don't believe we can still be free <br>But I can promise that it's over <br><br>And I can feel you turning your cheek at me <br>Like you've never seen love without the ring <br>But I can promise that it's over <br><br>Oh lord, it's another one <br>It's nothing to be scared of <br>As long as you're prepared, oh <br><br>Oh lord, it's another one]]></content><category term="Speak" label="Speak"/><category term="Oh Lord" label="Oh Lord"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Peaks/</id><title>Speak - Peaks - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Peaks/" title="Speak - Peaks - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[That's as high as it goes <br>That's as loud as it gets <br>Take a minute to breathe <br>Smoke your first cigarette <br>Scream as loud as you want <br>Scream as loud as you need <br>That's what the 90's were for <br>May they never recede <br>You could take me with you <br>I could take you with me <br>Though we're better off here <br>I mean ultimately <br><br>We don't need cheering up <br>We don't need any more <br>We don't need what we want <br>That's what the 80's were for <br><br>If you think you're alive <br>If you think you're a man <br>You were already dead <br>Oh before it began <br>Searching for rock <br>In a pile of sand <br>All the kind that you want <br>'Till it's all in your hands <br><br>I know, I know it's not the easiest thing <br>To decide to let the easy things go <br>Cause it's hard enough without <br>Another sign that you've slowed down <br><br>An emotion is a terrible thing <br>But emotion is a terrible thing to waste <br>I've been over it again and again <br>And the only thing I'm over's the time it takes <br><br>Any motion is a hell of a thing <br>Knowing emotion is a hell of a thing to face <br>You can do it with your back on the wall <br>But the oldest ones are always the backs that break <br><br>And if you fight with fire <br>If you wrestle to sleep <br>May the wrestling end <br>Now you find what you need <br>And you fill it with lead <br>And it fills you with ink <br>Always less than you want <br>Always more than you think <br>You know, you know it's not the easiest thing <br>To decide to keep the easy things close <br>Cause it's hard enough without <br>An open mind to weigh you down <br><br>An emotion is a terrible thing <br>But emotion is a terrible thing to waste <br>I've been over it again and again <br>And the only thing I'm over's the time it takes <br><br>And emotion is a terrible thing <br>Any motion is a terrible thing <br><br>And emotion is a terrible thing]]></content><category term="Speak" label="Speak"/><category term="Peaks" label="Peaks"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/This_Much_I_Know/</id><title>Speak - This Much I Know - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/This_Much_I_Know/" title="Speak - This Much I Know - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This windowsill is a place to start <br>Or the end, I can't tell the two apart <br>Little ghost, you grow, we still see past you <br>This much I know <br><br>I can't decide if I'm in the fog <br>Or I'm close, and I've been here all along <br>I'd fill my lungs just to clear the air <br>This much I know <br>This much I know <br><br>This road is enough for me <br>Because I can't, I can't seem to find a thing <br>It's not that hard, I'm just not trying <br>This much I know <br>This much I know <br>This much I know]]></content><category term="Speak" label="Speak"/><category term="This Much I Know" label="This Much I Know"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Weiss/</id><title>Speak - Weiss - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Weiss/" title="Speak - Weiss - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[this window ceil is a place to start <br>in the end i can't tell the truth quiet <br>little girls to worried stand still, i still <br>this much i know <br><br>i can't decide if i'm in the fall <br>or i'm close, i bet you wanna know <br>i feel my lungs, used to clear air <br>this much i know, this much i know <br><br>this role is not for me <br>cause i can't, i can't seem to find the thing <br>it's not that hard, just not trying <br>this much i know <br>this much i know]]></content><category term="Speak" label="Speak"/><category term="Weiss" label="Weiss"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Nightlight/</id><title>Speak - Nightlight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Nightlight/" title="Speak - Nightlight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If this cell is beginning to serve you well <br>Feel my face, is it you there or somewhere else <br>Cause everyone needs my help <br>But I'm tired and I need theirs as well <br><br>And if every day is an eye for an eye <br>Well then I won't lose sight <br>Cause if I never get any closer in <br>Then they won't know I tried <br>And the better way's looking up all night <br>So I don't lose my mind <br>Cause I see the same light as you <br>Just not the same signs <br><br>Every word is a whisper of someone's hell <br>Every name is a number to someone else <br>And everyone counts themselves <br>Till they break and the words slip out <br><br>And if every day is an eye for an eye <br>Well then I won't lose sight <br>Cause if I never get any closer in <br>Then they won't know I tried <br>And the better way's looking up all night <br>So I don't lose my mind <br>Cause I see the same light as you <br>Just not the same signs]]></content><category term="Speak" label="Speak"/><category term="Nightlight" label="Nightlight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Mystery_Lights/</id><title>Speak - Mystery Lights - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Mystery_Lights/" title="Speak - Mystery Lights - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And it feels like <br>Something's over <br>If it's real life <br>I don't notice <br><br>And I know everything about you <br>Whether or not you wanted me to <br>Cause it feels like I'm an alright polygraph <br><br>You know everything about me <br>I mean at least that's how it should be <br>But I just seem to hang between the hours <br><br>And it feels like <br>Something's over <br>If it's real life <br>I don't notice <br><br>They know everything about us <br>And the more that they know the more they're in love <br>And you know everyone <br><br>Little flickers and they light up <br>But all that they want is someone to touch <br>And I've been hiding lately <br>Cause I don't know how to give them enough <br><br>But I know I wanna get out <br>Of these mystery lights <br>Cause there's nowhere to hide <br>And I don't feel anyone else <br>But I guess that's alright <br>Cause there's no one in sight <br><br>And it feels like <br>Something's over <br>If it's real life <br>I don't notice]]></content><category term="Speak" label="Speak"/><category term="Mystery Lights" label="Mystery Lights"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Gates/</id><title>Speak - Gates - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Speak/Gates/" title="Speak - Gates - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This is my second life <br>And it's hell or paradise <br>Those circles in your eyes <br><br>But I won't let you die twice <br>Cause if this is what it takes <br>To make us feel ashamed <br><br>I won't live my life again <br>Cause I've got the only heaven I want <br>I'm not fighting for the end <br>Cause right now we're better lost than we're found <br><br>Maybe we'll get it all <br>If we choose one night <br>And we both choose right <br><br>But it's hazy before the dawn <br>When it's so hard to know <br>It's so hard to know <br><br>So no I won't <br><br>I won't live my life again <br>Cause I've got the only heaven I want <br>I'm not fighting for the end <br>Cause right now we're better lost than we're found <br><br>I won't, I won't <br><br>Then no I won't <br><br>I won't live my life again <br>Cause I've got the only heaven I want <br>I'm not fighting for the end <br>Cause right now we're better lost than we're found]]></content><category term="Speak" label="Speak"/><category term="Gates" label="Gates"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/세정_구구단/꽃길_Prod_By_ZICO/</id><title>세정_구구단 - 꽃길 (Prod. By ZICO) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%B8%EC%A0%95_%EA%B5%AC%EA%B5%AC%EB%8B%A8/%EA%BD%83%EA%B8%B8_Prod_By_ZICO/" title="세정_구구단 - 꽃길 (Prod. By ZICO) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세상이란 게 제법 춥네요 <br>당신의 안에서 살던 때 보다 <br>모자람 없이 주신 사랑이 <br>과분하다 느낄 때쯤 <br>난 어른이 됐죠 <br>한 송이 꽃을 피우려 <br>작은 두 눈에 <br>얼마나 많은 비가 내렸을까 <br>Oh rewind <br>돌이킬수록 더 미안 <br>포기 안 하려 포기해버린 <br>젊고 아름다운 당신의 계절 <br>여길 봐 예쁘게 피었으니까 <br>바닥에 떨어지더라도 <br>꽃길만 걷게 해줄게요 <br>문득 쳐다본 그 입가에는 <br>미소가 폈지만 주름이 졌죠 <br>내게 인생을 선물해주고 <br>사랑해란 말이 <br>그리도 고마운가요 <br>한 송이 꽃을 피우려 <br>작은 두 눈에 <br>얼마나 많은 비가 내렸을까 <br>oh rewind <br>돌이킬수록 더 미안 <br>포기 안 하려 포기해버린 <br>젊고 아름다운 당신의 계절 <br>여길 봐 예쁘게 피었으니까 <br>바닥에 떨어지더라도 <br>꽃길만 걷게 해줄게요 <br>겨울이 와도 마음속에 <br>봄 향기가 가득한 건 <br>한결같이 시들지 않는 <br>사랑 때문이죠 <br>oh rewind <br>짧은 바람 같던 시간 <br>날 품에 안고 흔들림 없는 <br>화분이 되어준 당신의 세월 <br>여길 봐 행복만 남았으니까 <br>다 내려놓고 이 손잡아요 <br>꽃길만 걷게 해줄게요 <br>]]></content><category term="세정 (구구단)" label="세정 (구구단)"/><category term="꽃길 (Prod. By ZICO)" label="꽃길 (Prod. By ZICO)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/업텐션_UP10TION/Just_Like_That/</id><title>업텐션_UP10TION - Just Like That - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%85%ED%85%90%EC%85%98_UP10TION/Just_Like_That/" title="업텐션_UP10TION - Just Like That - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Just like that <br>내 맘을 훔치기 전에 <br>다가와 그래 그렇게 <br>네 맘의 비밀을 원해 <br>나만 알 수 있게 <br>단 한 번도 느끼지 못한 <br>감정이 날 감싸 안아 피어나 <br>애써 나를 감추려 해도 <br>네가 가득 찬 내 맘이 <br>널 찾아가는 걸 <br>반짝이는 별처럼 내 안에 <br>빛이 되어 나를 비춰줘 <br>내 마음은 투명한 달빛처럼 <br>네 안에 아무도 모르게 <br>Just like that <br>나를 바라보는 모습도 <br>아름다운 너의 미소도 <br>나도 모르게 날 이끌어 <br>점점 더 널 따라가는 걸 <br>네 맘에 흩어져 <br>꽃잎처럼 나만의 향기를 <br>네 안에 선물해 <br>아무도 없는 곳으로 너와 날 <br>단 한 번도 느끼지 못한 <br>감정이 날 감싸 안아 피어나 <br>애써 나를 감추려 해도 <br>네가 가득 찬 내 맘이 <br>널 찾아가는 걸 <br>반짝이는 별처럼 내 안에 <br>빛이 되어 나를 비춰줘 <br>내 마음은 투명한 달빛처럼 <br>네 안에 아무도 모르게 <br>Just like that <br>내 모든 시선 속에 널 <br>놓치고 싶지 않아 <br>숨기고 싶지 않아 <br>같은 공간 속에 더 <br>우리 둘만 이대로 <br>너에게 물드는 이 밤 <br>반짝이는 별처럼 내 안에 <br>빛이 되어 나를 비춰줘 <br>내 마음은 투명한 달빛처럼 <br>네 안에 아무도 모르게 <br>Just like that <br>]]></content><category term="업텐션 (UP10TION)" label="업텐션 (UP10TION)"/><category term="Just Like That" label="Just Like That"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/업텐션_UP10TION/빠져가지고/</id><title>업텐션_UP10TION - 빠져가지고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%85%ED%85%90%EC%85%98_UP10TION/%EB%B9%A0%EC%A0%B8%EA%B0%80%EC%A7%80%EA%B3%A0/" title="업텐션_UP10TION - 빠져가지고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너와 함께하는 시간이 <br>나에겐 대신할 순간이 없어 <br>오로지 너 oh <br>AY <br>너와 같은 시간 <br>같은 공간에 있을 때 <br>비교 따윈 절대로 <br>안 될 거예요 <br>쉬운 여잔 아닌 걸 <br>그 뒤태가 말해줘 <br>이미 난 너한테 <br> 넘어간 것 같애 <br>오 넘어선 안될 선을 Yeah <br>Leggo Leggo Leggo <br>오 넘어야 할 것 같애 <br>어때 Be true <br>빠 빠 빠 빠져가지고 <br>나 진짜 미쳐가지고 <br>지금 이 순간에 또 파고들어 <br>허 허 허우적대 <br>근데 기분은 Not so bad <br>빠 빠 빠 빠져가지고 <br>나 진짜 미쳐가지고 <br>멘탈은 놓치고 <br>다린 후달리고 <br>허 허 허우적대 <br>근데 헤매는 기분도 <br>Not so bad <br>눈 떴을 때와 감았을 때가 둘 다 <br>아무것도 보이지 않는 건 다 똑같아 <br>또 다른 감각 손가락 끝자락에서 <br>느껴지는 너의 부드러운 따뜻함 <br>그 다음엔 naughty time <br>F class this ain't no tea time <br>AY <br>너와 같은 시간 <br>같은 공간에 있을 때 <br>비교 따윈 절대로 <br>안 될 거예요 <br>쉬운 여잔 아닌 걸 <br>그 뒤태가 말해줘 <br>이미 난 너한테 <br>넘어간 것 같애 <br>오 넘어선 안될 선을 Yeah <br>Leggo Leggo Leggo <br>오 넘어야 할 것 같애 <br>어때 Be true <br>빠 빠 빠 빠져가지고 <br>나 진짜 미쳐가지고 <br>지금 이 순간에 또 파고들어 <br>허 허 허우적대 <br>근데 기분은 <br>Not so bad <br>빠 빠 빠 빠져가지고 <br>나 진짜 미쳐가지고 <br>멘탈은 놓치고 <br>다린 후달리고 <br>허 허 허우적대 <br>근데 헤매는 기분도 <br>Not so bad <br>Ya 풍덩 <br>Dive in it into 너란 ocean <br>You get hotter and colder <br>요염하게 밀고 당기며 꼬셔 <br>느려지는 내 모션 <br>숨은 벅차올라 <br>You rock my world <br>Coachella <br>오늘밤 난 Hero 보단 Villain <br>내가 보기엔 백퍼 큰일 저질러 <br>빠 빠 빠 빠져가지고 <br>나 진짜 미쳐가지고 <br>지금 이 순간에 또 파고들어 <br>허 허 허우적대 <br>근데 기분은 <br>Not so bad <br>빠 빠 빠 빠져가지고 <br>나 진짜 미쳐가지고 <br>멘탈은 놓치고 <br>다린 후달리고 <br>허 허 허우적대 <br>근데 헤매는 기분도 <br>Not so bad <br>]]></content><category term="업텐션 (UP10TION)" label="업텐션 (UP10TION)"/><category term="빠져가지고" label="빠져가지고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/업텐션_UP10TION/왜냐하면/</id><title>업텐션_UP10TION - 왜냐하면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%85%ED%85%90%EC%85%98_UP10TION/%EC%99%9C%EB%83%90%ED%95%98%EB%A9%B4/" title="업텐션_UP10TION - 왜냐하면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한동안 나 꿈인 줄 알았어 <br>끝인 줄 몰랐어 우리 둘 사이 <br>친구들은 다 괜찮다고 해도 <br>예전과 다른 너를 쳐다보면 <br>난 실감이 나질 않나 봐 <br>Tell me why <br>어쩌다 우린 이렇게 <br>어색하게 돼버린 걸까 <br>믿기지가 않아 <br>너무나 행복했던 우리 <br>만날 수 있다고 <br>시간을 넘어 너를 다시 <br>되찾고 싶다고 <br>기억해 I'll be there <br>여기서 있을게 <br>아파도 참을래 왜냐하면 <br>너 없인 난 안돼 <br>You are You are <br>My everything <br>You are You are <br>My everything <br>You are You are <br>My everything <br>너 없인 난 안돼 <br>이제는 널 다시 <br>부를 수가 없는 걸까 <br>이대로 우린 평행선을 <br>계속 걷는 건가 <br>차갑게 떠나가 버린 <br>너 엇갈려버린 걸 <br>한 번쯤 여기서 <br>날 찾을 것 같아 <br>여전히 서있어 <br>이대로 <br>멀어져 가는 널 보며 <br>다시 웃을 수 없을까 봐 <br>사실 두렵지만 <br>너무나 행복했던 우리 <br>만날 수 있다고 <br>시간을 넘어 너를 다시 <br>되찾고 싶다고 <br>기억해 I'll be there <br>여기서 있을게 <br>아파도 참을래 왜냐하면 <br>너 없인 난 안돼 <br>아파도 참을래 <br>널 향한 맘을 왜 <br>접어야만 하는데 <br>네 맘 깊숙이 남을게 <br>I will stay <br>여기서 있을게 <br>혹시나 길을 잃을 때 <br>두 팔을 벌리고 <br>모두 던지고 <br>환하게 비출게 <br>아닌 척하고 남자답게 널 <br>잊어버리고 싶지만 <br>자꾸 가슴이 막 무너져 <br>견디기 힘들어 <br>제발 <br>너무나 행복했던 우리 <br>만날 수 있다고 <br>시간을 넘어 너를 다시 <br>되찾고 싶다고 <br>잊지마 I'll be there <br>여기서 있을게 <br>아파도 괜찮아 왜냐하면 <br>널 사랑하니까 <br>You are You are <br>My everything <br>You are You are <br>My everything <br>You are You are <br>My everything <br>]]></content><category term="업텐션 (UP10TION)" label="업텐션 (UP10TION)"/><category term="왜냐하면" label="왜냐하면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/업텐션_UP10TION/전력질주/</id><title>업텐션_UP10TION - 전력질주 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%85%ED%85%90%EC%85%98_UP10TION/%EC%A0%84%EB%A0%A5%EC%A7%88%EC%A3%BC/" title="업텐션_UP10TION - 전력질주 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 꺼라Go 세상에 외칠게 <br>백 번 양보해도 너만은 <br>절대 포기할 수 없어 <br>미치겠어 터질 것만 같은 <br>가슴으로 전력질주 할게 <br>나만이 널 가질 수 있어 <br>거친 숨이 차올라도 막을 수 없어 <br>거기 딱 서있어 <br>네게 전력질주 할게 <br>한번 더 말하지만 <br>그만 좀 하라는 말 <br>더 이상 꺼내지마 <br>널 포기하라는 건 <br>있을 수 없다는 것 <br>아직도 모르니 왜 <br>대충 흘려 들을 만한 이야긴 아냐 <br>넌 지금 만화 속에 들어와 있고 <br>난 행운의 남자 주인공 let's go <br>내가 할 수 있는 건 <br>오직 널 바라보며 <br>네게 달려가는 것 <br>내 꺼라Go 세상에 외칠게 <br>백 번 양보해도 너만은 <br>절대 포기할 수 없어 <br>미치겠어 터질 것만 같은 <br>가슴으로 전력질주 할게 <br>나만이 널 가질 수 있어 <br>거친 숨이 차올라도 막을 수 없어 <br>거기 딱 서있어 <br>네게 전력질주 할게 <br>더워 난 너만 보면 <br>like hot hot hot hot <br>날아갈 것만 같아 <br>feel so high high high high <br>난 아냐 거짓말쟁이 <br>But I addicted 그건 너의 책임 <br>SNS에는 내 이름을 꼭 <br>해시태그 해 매일매일 babe <br>서툴고 어색해서 <br>표현하지 못했어 <br>이젠 오해하지 마 <br>내 맘은 진짜라고 <br>말로 표현 안 해도 <br>전해질 거라 믿어 <br>전해질 거라 믿어 <br>그렇다면 망가질 일 없지 <br>해가 뜰 때부터 질 때까지 <br>Good energy Did you get it <br>하늘에 약속할게 <br>오직 널 바라보며 <br>변하지 않을 거야 <br>내 꺼라Go 세상에 외칠게 <br>백 번 양보해도 너만은 <br>절대 포기할 수 없어 <br>미치겠어 터질 것만 같은 <br>가슴으로 전력질주 할게 <br>나만이 널 가질 수 있어 <br>거친 숨이 차올라도 막을 수 없어 <br>거기 딱 서있어 <br>네게 전력질주 할게 <br>비 오는 날 umbrella <br>꼭 약속해줘 제발 <br>난 너만의 비스킷이 되고 <br>넌 달콤한 누텔라 alright <br>솔직하게 말해 흔들리는 거 알아 <br>어쩌라고 마음이 가는데 <br>백 번 천 번을 생각해도 <br>절대로 놓칠 수 없어 <br>달려갈게 칠전팔기 <br>포기란 없어 전력질주 할게 <br>나만이 널 가질 수 있어 <br>거친 숨이 차올라도 막을 수 없어 <br>거기 딱 서있어 <br>네게 전력질주 할게 <br>]]></content><category term="업텐션 (UP10TION)" label="업텐션 (UP10TION)"/><category term="전력질주" label="전력질주"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/업텐션_UP10TION/하얗게_불태웠어/</id><title>업텐션_UP10TION - 하얗게 불태웠어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%85%ED%85%90%EC%85%98_UP10TION/%ED%95%98%EC%96%97%EA%B2%8C_%EB%B6%88%ED%83%9C%EC%9B%A0%EC%96%B4/" title="업텐션_UP10TION - 하얗게 불태웠어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A-Yo UP10TION Let me hear say <br>Hey attention Leggo <br>Burning out Burning out Burning out <br>Burning out Burning out Burning out <br>넌 불을 지핀다 in my heart <br>시간이 멈추다 흐른다 <br>아름다운 네 모습에 <br>모든 신경들이 곤두서게 돼 <br>너로 가득 찬 눈빛에 <br>뜨거운 기름을 붓는다 <br>너에게 타오르게 <br>어지러워 끝까지 완전 연소해 <br>난 자신해 내 모든 걸 걸어 <br>겁이 없어 내일이 없는 것처럼 <br>뒤돌아 보지 마 내게 걸어 <br>어차피 난 끝인 걸 Baby <br>너 없이는 끝인 걸 Baby <br>말하지 못한 내 맘을 전해 <br>의심까지도 지워줄게 <br>하얗게 불타버렸어 <br>아무것도 없어 다 버렸어요 <br>남은 건 하나 오직 너뿐이야 <br>넌 나의 마지막 <br>새까맣게 불타버렸어 <br>남은 것도 없이 다 버렸어요 <br>이 맘 멈추려 하지 마 <br>Can't stop plz 더 이상 <br>나를 슬프게 하지 마 <br>Don't stop me now <br>이제 네게 달려갈 거니까 <br>가까이 가거든 손을 내밀어 잡어 <br>네 맘에 닿거든 거부하지는 말어 <br>모든 걸 매번 또 제껴 <br>널 잡으려 애써도 <br>누가 널 뺏어 널 갖고 말겠어 <br>쉽지 않아 이런 게 사랑이라면은 <br>너 말고는 꿈도 못 꾸게 <br>식지 않아 거짓말 같던 세상에서 <br>꺼내줘 네 빛으로 baby <br>아무 말도 하지 마 baby <br>그냥 내게 오면 돼 baby <br>다 끝나도 난 아직도 애가 타 <br>네게 빠진 내 맘은 <br>하얗게 불타버렸어 <br>아무것도 없어 다 버렸어요 <br>남은 건 하나 오직 너뿐이야 <br>넌 나의 마지막 <br>새까맣게 불타버렸어 <br>남은 것도 없이 다 버렸어요 <br>이 맘 멈추려 하지 마 <br>간절한 내 맘 불완전하니까 <br>이건 쓰러지기 직전의 jenga <br>젠장 그녈 사랑하는 것도 죄인가 <br>인정해 넌 이겼어 <br>나의 모든 걸 사로잡았어 <br>이글거리는 내 심장 네 거니까 <br>하얗게 불타버렸어 <br>아무것도 없어 다 버렸어요 <br>남은 건 하나 오직 너뿐이야 <br>너는 나의 마지막 떠나지 마 <br>끝까지 난 더 Burning out <br>결국 너니까 <br>이 맘 멈추려 하지 마 <br>]]></content><category term="업텐션 (UP10TION)" label="업텐션 (UP10TION)"/><category term="하얗게 불태웠어" label="하얗게 불태웠어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Genevieve/Authority/</id><title>Genevieve - Authority - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Genevieve/Authority/" title="Genevieve - Authority - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you were young <br>You were gold, you were innocent <br>And you had dreams that you dreamt <br>But you wouldn't tell <br>'Cause you were told you were born in a deficit <br>And you should hide all the feelings that you felt <br><br>No need to fear just breathe <br>The coast is clear just breathe <br>I can't sleep either just breathe <br>Look in the mirror <br><br>Who I want to be, it's my authority <br>Who I want to be, it's my authority <br>Just keep your head up x 8 <br><br>Just breathe <br>Just breathe <br><br>And now you're grown to the bone, you've been workin' it <br>You've spent your life in the line, and the third degree <br>But deep inside there's a power you can't resist <br>And it's your right to define who you wanna be <br><br>No need to fear just breathe <br>The coast is clear just breathe <br>I can't sleep either just breathe <br>Look in the mirror <br><br>Who I want to be, it's my authority <br>Who I want to be, it's my authority <br>Just keep your head up x 8 <br><br>Who I want to be, it's my authority <br>Who I want to be, it's my authority <br>Just keep your head up x 8]]></content><category term="Genevieve" label="Genevieve"/><category term="Authority" label="Authority"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Genevieve/For_You/</id><title>Genevieve - For You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Genevieve/For_You/" title="Genevieve - For You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll try not to hide from you <br>After all we've been through <br>You ask me to tell the truth <br><br>And I wouldn't lie to you <br><br>For you, I would stand in the line of fire <br>For you, I would wait 'til the end of time <br>For you, I would sail through the darkest water <br>I'm comin' around for you <br>I'm comin' around <br><br>There was a time, we were young <br>Reckless and wild, we would run <br>Each day was a war to be won <br>And I was a loaded gun <br><br>For you, I would stand in the line of fire <br>For you, I would wait 'til the end of time <br>For you, I would sail through the darkest waters <br>I'm comin' around for you <br>I'm comin' around <br><br>I don't wanna lose you now <br>I won't let you lose the fight <br>I don't want to let you down <br>I won't let you lose your light <br><br>For you, I would stand in the line of fire <br>For you, I would wait 'til the end of time <br>For you, I would sail through darkest waters <br>I'm comin' around for you <br>I'm comin' around <br><br>For you, I would stand in the line of fire <br>For you, I would wait 'til the end of time <br>For you, I would sail through the darkest water <br>I'm comin' around for you <br>I'm comin' around]]></content><category term="Genevieve" label="Genevieve"/><category term="For You" label="For You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Genevieve/Human_Again/</id><title>Genevieve - Human Again - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Genevieve/Human_Again/" title="Genevieve - Human Again - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sugar and spice and everything nice <br>Sugar and spice and everything nice <br>Sugar and spice and everything nice <br>Sugar and spice and everything nice <br><br>I used to be a yes girl, yes girl <br>Dress me up in white, I'll sign the papers <br>I used to be a promise maker <br>Leaving trails of endless empty favors <br>I used to be my father's daughter <br>Everything I did was for attention <br>Like an undercover soldier <br>Posing for a picture of perfection <br><br>Sleeping in so late that by the time I woke up <br>The day had turned to night <br><br>It feels like I'm almost human, human <br>It feels like I'm almost back in my skin <br>It feels like I'm almost human <br>It feels like I'm almost human again <br><br>I used to be a power play, power play <br>Pushing me from one place to another <br>I used to be a runaway, runaway <br>I was only looking for my mother <br><br>Staying out so late that by the time I woke up <br>The day had turned to night <br><br>It feels like I'm almost human, human <br>It feels like I'm almost back in my skin <br>It feels like I'm almost human <br>It feels like I'm almost human again <br><br>I'm still running in my dreams <br>But not a way more towards my life <br>I'm no longer a machine <br>I'll leave the nightmares behind me <br><br>It feels like I'm almost human, human <br>It feels like I'm almost back in my skin <br>It feels like I'm almost human <br>It feels like I'm almost human again]]></content><category term="Genevieve" label="Genevieve"/><category term="Human Again" label="Human Again"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Genevieve/My_Real_Name/</id><title>Genevieve - My Real Name - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:35:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:35:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Genevieve/My_Real_Name/" title="Genevieve - My Real Name - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Before you go <br>I just want you to hear this <br>I never told you <br><br>what my real name is <br>When I was young <br>I would play defense <br>'cause in my home <br>love was a contest <br>But, when you're looking <br>deep in my eyes <br>all of the nightmares <br>turn into light <br>You help me <br>let go <br>Maybe I can make it <br>Maybe I can make it <br>You push me <br>to grow <br>Maybe I can make it <br>Maybe I can make it <br>Traded my sword <br>in for my spirit <br>I'd rather die than <br>give up my freedom <br>One of these days <br>I will have children <br>I'll teach them to question <br>and to be fearless <br>And when I look in <br>deep in their eyes <br>Won't need to hide <br>behind my disguise <br>You help me <br>let go <br>Maybe I can make it <br>Maybe I can make it <br>You push me <br>to grow <br>Maybe I can make it <br>Maybe I can make it <br>When on a losing streak <br>and I'm feeling blue <br>I can read this letter <br>think of you <br>think of you <br>You help me <br>let go <br>Maybe I can make it <br>Maybe I can make it <br>You help me <br>let go <br>Maybe I can make it <br>Maybe I can make it <br>You push me <br>to grow <br>Maybe I can make it <br>Maybe I can make it]]></content><category term="Genevieve" label="Genevieve"/><category term="My Real Name" label="My Real Name"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/키디비_KittiB/음성메모_Feat_QM/</id><title>키디비_KittiB - 음성메모 (Feat. QM) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:36:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:36:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%82%A4%EB%94%94%EB%B9%84_KittiB/%EC%9D%8C%EC%84%B1%EB%A9%94%EB%AA%A8_Feat_QM/" title="키디비_KittiB - 음성메모 (Feat. QM) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 내 폰 음성메모엔 <br>음기 가득한 가사와 노래 <br>그 어느 때보다 더 짙게 베인 상처 <br>티비를 틀면 으슬으슬해 <br>성공이란 코트를 걸쳐 입고 <br>먼저 저 앞을 걷는 <br>이들의 발자취를 멈춰 <br>하늘을 우러러 한점 부끄럼 없기를 <br>바라면 하는 말은 나를 숨겨줘 <br>그래 싹 다 모아 <br>탈탈 털어보면 먼지 <br>실오라기 하나 <br>안 나오는 사람이 어딨겠냐만 <br>너의 먼지 스케일은 <br>대륙의 황사 수준이니까 <br>Uh 피해 주지마 <br>사람들 앞길에 먼지를 휘날리지마 <br>Uh 또 팔짱 끼지마 <br>성난 개돼지의 눈빛으로 보지마 <br>시간은 흐르고 모든 것은 잊혀지고 <br>천사 같던 애들의 미소는 <br>다 꿈인가 싶어 <br>동화 속에 마녀는 <br>TV 속에 늘 있지만 <br>우릴 구해줄 누군가를 <br>기다리긴 넘 지겨워 <br>난 내 자리에서 <br>내 생각을 녹음하고 <br>넌 네 자리에서 힘을 보태줘 <br>검은 종이에 너네 이름이 <br>적힌대도 겁먹지마 <br>작은 불씨가 쓰레기 더미를 태워 <br>Sos oh sos <br>손 내밀어 네게 닿을 수 있게 <br>Sos oh sos <br>내가 예쁜 노래를 만들 수 있게 <br>Stress stress stress <br>머리 빠지겠네 <br>Stress stress stress <br>술이 더 늘겠네 <br>가사를 다 쓰고 놨더니 <br>또 하나가 터져 <br>Stress stress stress <br>Stress stress stress <br>머리 빠지겠네 <br>Stress stress stress <br>담배 더 피겠네 <br>가사를 다 쓰고 놨더니 <br>또 하나가 터져 <br>Stress stress stress <br>내 선택지가 하나씩 줄어드는 <br>이 기분은 아마 뷔페 <br>접시 다섯 개에 내가 먹고 싶은 걸 <br>가득 담아왔을 때 <br>옆에 놈이 맛있겠다 하며 <br>하나씩 가져갈 때 같아 God damn <br>뭔갈 바라봐도 곧이곧대로 <br>받아들일 수가 없다는 말이지 한땐 <br>승마를 동경해서 <br>티비를 돌리다가도 저건 동물이랑 <br>노는 직업 꽤나 짜릿하겠지라 <br>생각하고 각설탕이란 <br>영화를 보며 설마 실화 <br>그러다 그녀가 2등 하니까 <br>심판을 다 잡아갔다데 <br>새로 고침 여러 번 해 이게 실화 <br>나는 승마 볼 때 <br>이제 그녀 생각에 잠긴 채로 <br>티비를 껐네 <br>얼마 전엔 항공사 하나를 빼 <br>냈고 예전엔 내가 먹던 우유를 빼 <br>난 바꿔버렸네 몇 년째 피던 담배 <br>근데 빼버리고 나니까 내 몸 같아 <br>그래 좋은 건 나눠먹어야지 <br>너네는 뭣하러 <br>주는 대로 받아먹고 <br>손가락은 못 막어 <br>난 못 빨아 잘못된 거는 <br>이제 안 볼 때도 됐네 이런거 더는 <br>Sos oh sos <br>손 내밀어 네게 닿을 수 있게 <br>Sos oh sos <br>내가 예쁜 노래를 만들 수 있게 <br>Stress stress stress <br>머리 빠지겠네 <br>Stress stress stress <br>술이 더 늘겠네 <br>가사를 다 쓰고 놨더니 <br>또 하나가 터져 <br>Stress stress stress <br>Stress stress stress <br>머리 빠지겠네 <br>Stress stress stress <br>담배 더 피겠네 <br>가사를 다 쓰고 놨더니 <br>또 하나가 터져 <br>Stress stress stress <br>요즘 기분 뭐 같아 <br>So stressed out <br>구린 노래만 나와 <br>So stressed out <br>할부금 5년 남은 엄마 차 <br>So stressed out <br>작은 원룸 월세와 나 몰래 <br>오르는 가스비까지 다 <br>So stressed out <br>나 같은 삶들이 대부분인데 <br>어찌 삶이 나아지는 건 걔들뿐 <br>내 지갑은 없을 무 <br>걔 지갑은 있을 유라 <br>별명을 붙어준다면 재무부 <br>순순히 말 잘 듣는 <br>우리 집 개 미르는 <br>오늘도 누워서 그냥 쉬네 <br>그래도 간식은 따박따박 <br>들어가 미르 입에 <br>이건 상실의 시대 <br>Sos oh sos <br>손 내밀어 네게 닿을 수 있게 <br>Sos oh sos <br>내가 예쁜 노래를 만들 수 있게 <br>Stress stress stress <br>머리 빠지겠네 <br>Stress stress stress <br>술이 더 늘겠네 <br>가사를 다 쓰고 놨더니 <br>또 하나가 터져 <br>Stress stress stress <br>Stress stress stress <br>머리 빠지겠네 <br>Stress stress stress <br>담배 더 피겠네 <br>가사를 다 쓰고 놨더니 <br>또 하나가 터져 <br>Bang bang bang <br>]]></content><category term="키디비 (KittiB)" label="키디비 (KittiB)"/><category term="음성메모 (Feat. QM)" label="음성메모 (Feat. QM)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/키디비_KittiB/Nobodys_Perfect/</id><title>키디비_KittiB - Nobody`s Perfect - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:36:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:36:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%82%A4%EB%94%94%EB%B9%84_KittiB/Nobodys_Perfect/" title="키디비_KittiB - Nobody`s Perfect - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[외출을 할 때 거울 앞의 난 <br>미간에 주름 한 번은 잡고 <br>관리 태만 빨간 불이 들어오네 자꾸 <br>어떤 재난 영화보다 무서운 노화를 <br>막을 수는 없네 <br>점점 짙어지는 메이크업과의 사투 <br>수많은 사람들 중 <br>여자의 고충은 비슷해 <br>내가 좀 괜찮은 여자가 되려면 <br>꾹 참아야만 하는 비스켓 <br>티비에는 마른 몸을 강요하면서 <br>잘 먹는 여자가 이쁘대 <br>원치 않아도 시작된 <br>이 게임은 여자라는 이름에 <br>그 참가 자격이 주어지지 <br>예쁜 애는 돈을 움켜쥐지 <br>소개남은 주선자에게 첫 질문을 해 <br>Hey is she pretty <br>백치는 괜찮아도 돼지는 안돼 <br>정돈 안된 손톱 털도 안돼 <br>완벽한 Bitch들에게 <br>깔아주는 레드 카펫 <br>누굴 만나고 누구와 자고 <br>엿 같은 소문 들어야 하고 <br>그 새낀 잘도 살아가도 <br>난 여자니까 감당해야 한다고 <br>알아 난 매일 밤 <br>다독이며 이겨내니까 <br>여자로 살아가는 이 시간 <br>지친 그녀들에게 해주고픈 말 <br>Oh baby please stop <br>남들과 비교하지마 <br>까만 터널 속에 널 <br>밀어 넣는 생각은 하지마 <br>Cause nobody's perfect <br>흐릿해진 나를 볼 때 <br>Nobody's perfect <br>타인인 듯 나를 볼 때 <br>Nobody's perfect <br>미워하는 마음 들 때 <br>No no nobody no <br>어린 소녀들이 떼로 <br>짧은 치마를 입었지 경쟁 속 <br>적은 투표율을 받은 그녀에겐 <br>밋밋한 몸 못난 얼굴이 error <br>메쓰거운 속을 달래며 돌린 채널 <br>요즘 핫하다는 노래 가사에선 <br>아름다운 여잔 받아야 한대 대접 <br>아름다운 여신한텐 호구가 되도 <br>괜찮대 듣는 나의 모습은 <br>계속 작아지는 걸까 왜 <br>열등감에 둘러싸일 땐 <br>켄드릭의 I 들어 I love my self <br>그래도 맘 속에 <br>악마가 떠나질 않네 <br>더 낮게 파고들어 숨을 참네 <br>세상의 기준과 날 비교하기엔 <br>너무 괴로워 오늘도 <br>엄마의 품을 찾네 <br>Young &amp; Beautiful <br>울 엄만 이제 이 말에 <br>해당되지 않아 <br>지금의 엄만 귀찮다며 <br>화장도 잘 안 하고 <br>드레스와 타이트한 스커트는 <br>옷장에서 사라져 <br>역시 영원한 건 없지 <br>모두 변해 덧없이 <br>엄마를 떠난 아빠처럼 <br>언젠간 내 남자도 역시 <br>내 겉모습이 망가지면 올리겠지 <br>우리 사랑의 졸업식 <br>거짓말이라도 절대 넌 <br>변치 않을 거라 속삭여줘 <br>Please <br>난 나이를 먹어도 <br>엄마처럼 되긴 싫어 <br>그런 못된 말을 막 지껄인 적 있어 <br>딸이라고는 딱 하나 뿐인데 고작 <br>이거밖에 안돼 <br>한때는 엄마를 남들 앞에 <br>창피해한 적도 있어 <br>그땐 왜 그랬는지 <br>I don't know I don't know <br>그때도 지금도 엄만 <br>아름답단 걸 잘 알아둬 <br>Oh baby please stop <br>남들과 비교하지마 <br>까만 터널 속에 널 <br>밀어 넣는 생각은 하지마 <br>Cause nobody's perfect <br>흐릿해진 나를 볼 때 <br>Nobody's perfect <br>타인인 듯 나를 볼 때 <br>Nobody's perfect <br>미워하는 마음 들 때 <br>No no nobody no <br>]]></content><category term="키디비 (KittiB)" label="키디비 (KittiB)"/><category term="Nobody`s Perfect" label="Nobody`s Perfect"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/My_Only_Regret_Bonus_Track/</id><title>James_Durbin - My Only Regret (Bonus Track) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:39:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:39:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/My_Only_Regret_Bonus_Track/" title="James_Durbin - My Only Regret (Bonus Track) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My only one regret, is I didn't know you when we were kids <br>Hid behind the bleachers and kiss your lips, and after we stop act like we never met <br>My only one regret is I didn't ask you to be my homecoming date <br><br>Buy you a corsage <br>and putting it on <br>Shake your dad's hand and started talking to your mom <br>But if i could turn back time now, and find out where you live <br>Where you live and i'll knock on your door <br>Cause if I knew then what I know now there's no doubt I would made you my girl long before we met <br>That's my only regret <br>That's my only <br>regret <br>Ooooh yeah <br>My only one regret is I didn't know you over a summer <br>No school just one party after another <br>Knowing only three months is all we get to get to know eachother <br>My only one regret is I over estimeated my ability to win, I was a jerk, selfish and conceited <br>It's taken years to find out what I needed <br>But if I could turn back time now and find out where you live, where you live and knock on your door <br>Cause if I knew then what I know now, there's no doubt, I would've made you my girl long before we met <br>Thats my only regret <br>My only one regret that the pictures of you and me don't exist from when we were little kids, but that was then and now this is this, and the future for us is where it is <br>But if I could turn back time now and find out where you live, where you live and I'll knock on your door <br>Cause if I knew then what I know now, there's no doubt, I would've made you my girl long before we met <br>If I could turn back time now and find out where you live, where you live and I'd knock on your door <br>Cause if I knew then what I know now, there's no doubt, I would've made you my girl long before we met <br>That's my only regret <br>Thats my only regret <br>Ooooh]]></content><category term="James Durbin" label="James Durbin"/><category term="My Only Regret (Bonus Track)" label="My Only Regret (Bonus Track)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Get_Over_Yourself_Bonus_Track/</id><title>James_Durbin - Get Over Yourself (Bonus Track) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:39:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:39:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Get_Over_Yourself_Bonus_Track/" title="James_Durbin - Get Over Yourself (Bonus Track) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Started out I couldn't look away <br>From your silhouette to the curve of your shape <br>You kiss so good <br>So good that it hurt <br>But then it all turned from bad to worse <br>Cuz something in your eyes just wasn't right <br>Untouchable when you said stay the night <br>You called me crazy cuz I made you mad <br>And the kiss that we had <br>Well I take it back <br>Cuz you're not all that <br><br>So girl get over yourself <br>Like I got over you <br>And your cheap perfume and your bad tattoos <br>Get over yourself, your Gucci and prada shoes <br>That runway walk and that dumb girl talk <br>Cuz you try and you try <br>But you just can't hide the truth about you <br>So girl get over yourself <br>Like I got over you <br><br>Now you're stalking my house <br>I saw you round there at night <br>Thought this girls bark was worse than her bark <br>Throwing rocks at my window, bricks at my car <br>Just can't believe how crazy you really are <br>You're hardly an angel, you're more like a freak <br>You blame it on me and then you called the police <br>Being chained to you is like a living hell <br>A one night stand was a night in jail <br>But I made bail <br><br>So girl get over yourself <br>Like I got over you <br>And your cheap perfume and your bad tattoos <br>Get over yourself, your Gucci and Prada shoes <br>That runway walk and that dumb girl talk <br>Cuz you try and you try <br>But you just can't hide the truth about you <br>So girl get over yourself <br>Like I got over you <br><br>Now it's been three months since the fight that we had <br>I changed all the locks after you called your dad <br>Heard about somebody new <br>Good riddance to you <br><br>So girl get over yourself <br>Like I got over you <br>And your cheap perfume and your bad tattoos <br>Get over yourself, your Gucci and Prada shoes <br>That runway walk and that dumb girl talk <br>Cuz you try and you try <br>But you just can't hide the truth about you <br>So girl get over yourself <br>Like I got over you]]></content><category term="James Durbin" label="James Durbin"/><category term="Get Over Yourself (Bonus Track)" label="Get Over Yourself (Bonus Track)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Real_Love/</id><title>James_Durbin - Real Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:39:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:39:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Real_Love/" title="James_Durbin - Real Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Feeling older, fighting like a soldier <br>Floating on the sea of gold <br>Lightning striking, fires a blazing frightening <br>Hoping for nothing more <br><br>We'll face the weather, we'll sail away together <br>We can make it, mi amore <br>Astounding you found me, the light of love surrounds me <br>There's no way I could ask for more <br><br>When you say, what I said <br>That's not the way I meant to say <br>I'm sorry, guess I chose the wrong way <br>To let you know <br>I miss and need to feel your arms around <br>I swear that this is real love <br>Real, my love <br><br>Forever lovers, we'll never lose each other <br>We'll ride into the sun <br>The stars will follow, don't worry about tomorrow <br>We'll all keep shining on <br><br>So when you say, what I said <br>That's not the way I meant to say <br>I'm sorry, guess I chose the wrong way <br>To let you know <br>I miss and need to feel your arms around <br>I swear that this is real love <br>Real, my love <br><br>Sometimes we drift apart <br>But that ain't who we are <br>We just need some kerosene to feed the fire <br>Slow down, let's take it easy <br>Sometimes I can't believe it <br>It feels like fantasy that you are mine, yeah <br>You are mine, yeah <br><br>So when you say, what I said <br>That's not the way I meant to say <br>I'm sorry, guess I chose the wrong way <br>To let you know <br>I miss and need to feel your arms around <br>I swear that this is real love <br>Real, my love <br><br>I swear that this is real love <br>Real, my love]]></content><category term="James Durbin" label="James Durbin"/><category term="Real Love" label="Real Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Celebrate/</id><title>James_Durbin - Celebrate - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:39:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:39:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Celebrate/" title="James_Durbin - Celebrate - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Some say that love is just a matter of time <br>You've gotta search high and low, or you can never find <br>It took some time to fix that piece of my mind <br>But I'm thankful everyday for the love of my life <br><br>I wanna celebrate, celebrate my life with you <br>Celebrate, Ooh baby <br>I just gotta celebrate, climb a little higher with you <br>Fly a little higher with you, Baby <br><br>You use to be lonely, well girl so was I <br>We can take it slowly, if you give it a try <br>At the edge of the earth with my arms open wide <br>We can keep on turning like the wheel in the sky <br><br>I wanna celebrate, celebrate my life with you <br>Celebrate, Ooh baby <br>I just gotta celebrate, climb a little higher with you <br>Fly a little higher with you, Baby <br><br>Ooh, the stars in my eyes <br>Sun shinin' too, I wanna waste my time with you <br><br>I wanna celebrate, celebrate my life with you <br>Celebrate, Ooh baby <br>I just gotta celebrate, climb a little higher with you <br>Fly a little higher with you, Baby <br><br>I wanna celebrate, celebrate my life with you <br>Celebrate, Ooh baby <br>I just gotta celebrate, climb a little higher with you <br>Fly a little higher with you, Baby <br><br>I wanna celebrate, celebrate my life with you <br>Celebrate, Ooh baby <br>I just gotta celebrate, climb a little higher with you <br>Fly a little higher with you, Baby]]></content><category term="James Durbin" label="James Durbin"/><category term="Celebrate" label="Celebrate"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Forget_It/</id><title>James_Durbin - Forget It - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:39:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:39:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Forget_It/" title="James_Durbin - Forget It - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Waking up just to feel comatose <br>Walking alone along an endless road <br>Sometimes the meanings re misunderstood <br>Always doing the opposite of what you should <br><br>Everyday gets you further from the truth <br>It's not what you give, it's what you lose <br>The world will turn you sick and crazy <br>Until all you feel is one shade of grey <br>But can you, can you <br><br>Just forget it, forget it <br>Let it go and watch it burn <br>Forget it, forget it <br>And bury it with all that hurts <br>You don't have to fake it <br>How long have you waited <br><br>Forget it, forget it <br>And wipe the tears from your eyes <br>Forget it, forget it <br>Learn to live before you die <br>You don't have to fake it <br>How long have you waited <br>How long have you waited <br><br>Life's too short to just wish away <br>Praying good fortune always comes your way <br>There's no time to run and push it down <br>Cause everything that matters is right here and now <br>But will you, will you <br><br>Just forget it, forget it <br>Let it go and watch it burn <br>Forget it, forget it <br>And bury it with all that hurts <br>You don't have to fake it <br>How long have you waited <br><br>Forget it, forget it <br>And wipe the tears from your eyes <br>Forget it, forget it <br>Learn to live before you die <br>You don't have to fake it <br>How long have you waited <br><br>And now that it seems <br>It seems we've never hurt so much <br>You know we've never hurt this much <br>I know you're scared of this <br>I know you're scared to death <br><br>Forget it, forget it <br>Let it go and watch it burn <br>Forget it, forget it <br>And bury it with all that hurts <br>You don't have to fake it <br>How long have you waited <br><br>Just forget it, forget it <br>Let it go and watch it burn <br>Forget it, forget it <br>And bury it with all that hurts <br>You don't have to fake it <br>How long have you waited <br><br>Forget it, forget it <br>And wipe the tears from your eyes <br>Forget it, forget it <br>Learn to live before you die <br>You don't have to fake it <br>How long have you waited <br><br>Forget it, forget it <br>How long have you waited <br>Forget it, forget it <br>How long have you waited]]></content><category term="James Durbin" label="James Durbin"/><category term="Forget It" label="Forget It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Youre_Not_Alone/</id><title>James_Durbin - You`re Not Alone - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:39:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:39:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Youre_Not_Alone/" title="James_Durbin - You`re Not Alone - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know your story far too well <br>And I've been inside your burning hell <br>Where love is nowhere close to you <br>And you don't even know yourself <br><br>I'll see you inside your fractured heart <br>And I'll piece together broken parts <br>Cause love was always meant for you <br>And now it's time to start <br><br>You're not alone <br>Cause where you are <br>Is where I'll be <br>You're not alone <br>Though you're finally free <br><br>Take these arms, they're open wide <br>Take the wrong and make it right <br>Cause love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you <br><br>Let the weight fall from your wings <br>And leave behind those painful things <br>Cause love was always meant for you <br>Can't you see <br><br>You're not alone <br>Cause where you are <br>Is where I'll be <br>You're not alone <br>Though you're finally free <br><br>Take these arms, they're open wide <br>Take the wrong and make it right <br>Cause love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you <br><br>Forget all that you think you've seen <br>With us there ain't no in between <br>Cause love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you <br><br>Take these arms, they're open wide <br>Take the wrong and make it right <br>Cause love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have <br><br>Forget all that you think you've seen <br>With us there ain't no in between <br>Cause love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you <br>Love is all I have for you]]></content><category term="James Durbin" label="James Durbin"/><category term="You`re Not Alone" label="You`re Not Alone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Live_Right_Now/</id><title>James_Durbin - Live Right Now - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:39:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:39:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Live_Right_Now/" title="James_Durbin - Live Right Now - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Go out swinging <br>All in or nothing <br>Believe in something <br>Impossible <br><br>Burn out brighter <br>Dream in colour <br>Feeding the fire <br>Heart and soul <br><br>These are the days <br>When we all stop running <br>These are the days <br>When we face what's coming <br>Take on today like there's no tomorrow <br>No tomorrow <br>Don't wanna live forever ever ever <br>Don't wanna live forever ever ever <br>Don't wanna live forever ever ever <br>I wanna live right now now now now, yeah <br><br>Kicking, screaming <br>Smiling, bleeding <br>Finally feeling <br>Something real <br><br>Over faster <br>To the moment you're after <br>Chasing shadows <br>Endlessly <br><br>These are the days <br>When we all stop running <br>These are the days <br>When we face what's coming <br>Take on today like there's no tomorrow <br>No tomorrow <br>Don't wanna live forever ever ever <br>Don't wanna live forever ever ever <br>Don't wanna live forever ever ever <br>I wanna live right now now now now yeah <br><br>Don't wanna live forever ever ever <br>Don't wanna live forever ever ever <br>Don't wanna live forever ever ever <br>I wanna live right now now now now yeah <br><br>These are the days <br>When we all stop running <br>These are the days <br>When we face what's coming <br>Take on today like there's no tomorrow <br>No tomorrow <br>Don't wanna live forever <br><br>Don't wanna live forever ever ever <br>Don't wanna live forever ever ever <br>Don't wanna live forever ever ever <br>I wanna live right now now now now yeah <br><br>Don't wanna live forever ever ever <br>Don't wanna live forever ever ever <br>Don't wanna live forever ever ever <br>I wanna live right now now now now yeah]]></content><category term="James Durbin" label="James Durbin"/><category term="Live Right Now" label="Live Right Now"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Louder_Than_A_Loaded_Gun/</id><title>James_Durbin - Louder Than A Loaded Gun - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:39:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:39:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Louder_Than_A_Loaded_Gun/" title="James_Durbin - Louder Than A Loaded Gun - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You left that key <br>You left that key on the table <br>You left my heart <br>You left my heart on the floor <br>I battle on <br>With my battle scars still open <br>What is it good for <br>Tell me, what is it good for <br><br>If an apology's all that you needed <br>It was right on the tip of my tongue <br>And I'm finding it hard to believe that <br>It was easier to run <br>Was it easier to run <br><br>So say, say, say <br>Just can say what you want to <br>But hey hey hey <br>Just don't give me up <br>I can scream scream scream <br>As loud as I want to <br>But silence has become <br>Louder than a loaded gun <br><br>Would you walk with me <br>Walk with me to the ocean <br>Just to write goodbye <br>To write goodbye in the sand <br>Well there's nothing here <br>And nothing left to be broken <br>Maybe that's part of the plan <br>To shatter everything I am <br><br>If an apology's all that you needed <br>It was right on the tip of my tongue <br>And I'm finding it hard to believe that <br>It was easier to run <br>Was it easier to run <br><br>So say, say, say <br>Just say what you want to <br>But hey hey hey <br>Just don't give me up <br>I can scream scream scream <br>As loud as I want to <br>But silence has become <br>Louder than a loaded gun <br><br>Pick up the pieces <br>That fell in between us <br>Take it or leave it <br><br>You can say, say, say <br>Just say what you want to <br>But hey hey hey <br>I don't give a damn <br>I can scream scream scream <br>Just as loud as I want to <br>Your silence has become <br>Louder than a loaded gun <br><br>Say, say, say <br>Just say what you want to <br>But hey hey hey <br>Just don't give me up <br>I can scream scream scream <br>As loud as I want to <br>But silence has become <br>Louder than a loaded gun <br>Louder than a loaded gun <br>Louder than a loaded gun <br><br>Say, say, say <br>Just say what you want to <br>But silence has become <br>Louder than a loaded gun]]></content><category term="James Durbin" label="James Durbin"/><category term="Louder Than A Loaded Gun" label="Louder Than A Loaded Gun"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Fool_For_You/</id><title>James_Durbin - Fool For You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:39:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:39:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Fool_For_You/" title="James_Durbin - Fool For You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She floats like a butterfly, stings like a bee <br>Notorious just like BIG <br>She's got me lookin' over my shoulder, ugh <br>Short red dress with Vanna White thighs <br>Bubblegum lips with starry blue eyes <br>She's building me up an American dream <br><br>She flirts with all my best friends <br>And screams out, I never listen <br>So tell me what's a, what's a boy to do a boy to do <br>She'll go down for no reason <br>And steal from me when I'm sleeping <br>She's holding back her, her I love you's her I love you's <br>So tell me why, well me why <br><br>You're always building me up up, to bring me down <br>Look at you, look at you baby <br>Calling me king just to steal my crown <br>Well didn't you, didn't you make me <br>Fall for the games that you played with my head, girl <br>I let you get away with murder <br>I guess I'm just a fool for you <br><br>People ask if I'm okay <br>I got scratches on my back and face <br>She really likes to leave her mark leave her mark <br>She comes home drunk at 4 am <br>With whipped cream, strawberries in her hand <br>She's keeping me up like I got a choice, yeah yeah <br><br>She makes cruel seem like sexy <br>Gets off when she hears McCartney <br>She'd like me better if I was Bruno Mars Bruno Mars <br>So tell me why, tell me why <br><br>You're always building me up up, to bring me down <br>Look at you, look at you baby <br>Calling me king just to steal my crown <br>Well didn't you, didn't you make me <br>Fall for the games that you played with my head, girl <br>I let you get away with murder <br>I guess I'm just a fool for you <br><br>No matter what we hear, we'll turn the world away <br>Cause honestly it's you and me and nothing's gonna change <br>I guess what I'm trying to say, is it's enough for me <br>Oh, it's enough for me, it's enough for me <br><br>But you're building me up, you're building me up <br><br>You're always building me up up, to bring me down <br>Look at you, look at you baby <br>Calling me king just to steal my crown <br>Well didn't you, didn't you make me <br>Fall for the games that you played with my head, girl <br>I let you get away with murder <br><br>You're always building me up up, to bring me down <br>Look at you, look at you baby <br>Calling me king just to steal my crown <br>Well didn't you, didn't you make me <br>Fall for the games that you played with my head, girl <br>I let you get away with murder <br>I let you get away with murder <br>I guess I'm just a fool for you, oh yeah <br>I guess I'm just a fool for you, I'm a fool for you]]></content><category term="James Durbin" label="James Durbin"/><category term="Fool For You" label="Fool For You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Issues/</id><title>James_Durbin - Issues - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:39:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:39:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Issues/" title="James_Durbin - Issues - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If you were to say to me <br>If you ask what's wrong with me <br>Well I would tell you it's everything <br>When I'm tired and feeling sick <br>When it's nothing you can fix <br>I want you to know it's not you <br><br>Cause I will never be OK, this I know, but that's OK <br>Cause my eyes are never shut, while my heart is wide awake <br>And it's all that I can do <br>Tell me, what else should I do <br>Cause <br><br>I've got issues, I've got scars <br>And the color is just like yours <br>I was broken right from the start <br>I'm no different than you are <br>I'm not perfect, I'm perfectly flawed <br>And my scratches don't hurt much at all <br>But just like you, I've got issues <br><br>There are smiles, there are tears <br>There are times through the years <br>Where I cannot remember yesterday <br>And everything is like a blur <br>It loses me around a curve <br>I'm always in a high speed chase <br><br>And I'm trying to gain control using everything I know <br>But nothing seems to work, I'll never catch at this I'm sure <br>But I will not forget <br>You've been with me step by step <br><br>I've got issues, I've got scars <br>And the color is just like yours <br>I was broken right from the start <br>I'm no different than you are <br>I'm not perfect, I'm perfectly flawed <br>And my scratches don't hurt much at all <br>But just like you, I've got issues <br><br>Am I unwell, cause I don't understand <br>Is this what they say it is, to be human <br>And these bandages I wear to keep out the cold <br>They keep me from something that I'll never know, know <br><br>I've got issues, I've got scars <br>And the color is just like yours <br>I was broken right from the start <br>I'm no different than you are <br>I'm not perfect, I'm perfectly flawed <br>And my scratches don't hurt much at all <br>But just like you <br>You know I'm just like you <br>I've got issues]]></content><category term="James Durbin" label="James Durbin"/><category term="Issues" label="Issues"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/You_Cant_Believe/</id><title>James_Durbin - You Can`t Believe - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:39:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:39:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/You_Cant_Believe/" title="James_Durbin - You Can`t Believe - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Too black, too white, too left, too right <br>Too thin, too wide, don't waste your time <br>That's what they say, no other way <br>Don't buy it all, don't buy it all <br><br>Too rich, too poor, too prude, too bored <br>Too mental and too obscene <br>What's ugliness to some <br>Is so beautiful to me <br><br>Don't hesitate, don't wait <br>It's always wrong to play it safe <br>What you've become is never wrong <br>You're always in the right place <br><br>Some things are so hard to be <br>Some things are just meant to be <br>I'm here to tell ya <br><br>You can't believe <br>What people say about you <br>You've gotta be <br>Yourself in your own virtue <br>You can't believe can't believe <br>What people think about you <br>You've gotta live gotta live <br>The life that you were born to <br>Woah woah <br>You can't believe you can't believe <br>What people say about you, you <br><br>Too straight, too gay, too bi, too strange <br>Everyone's got their own way <br>The world is cruel, they ridicule <br>What they're too afraid to face <br><br>Don't play the game, make it change <br>Just right the wrong and fight the hate <br>What you've become is never wrong <br>You're always in the right place <br><br>Some things are so hard to be <br>Some things are just meant to be <br>I'm here to tell ya <br><br>You can't believe <br>What people say about you <br>You've gotta be <br>Yourself in your own virtue <br>You can't believe can't believe <br>What people think about you <br>You've gotta live gotta live <br>The life that you were born to <br>Woah woah <br>You can't believe you can't believe <br>What people say about you, you <br><br>I'm here to tell ya <br><br>You can't believe <br>What people say about you <br>You've gotta be <br>Yourself in your own virtue <br>You can't believe can't believe <br>What people think about you <br>You've gotta live gotta live <br>The life that you were born to <br>Woah woah <br>You can't believe you can't believe <br>You can't believe you can't believe <br>What people say about you <br>You can't believe you can't believe <br>You can't believe you can't believe <br>What people say about you <br>What people say about you <br>What people say about you]]></content><category term="James Durbin" label="James Durbin"/><category term="You Can`t Believe" label="You Can`t Believe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Parachute/</id><title>James_Durbin - Parachute - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:39:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:39:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Parachute/" title="James_Durbin - Parachute - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hangin like a broken star in the sky <br>No reason to shine <br>Thinkin I could never be <br>Someone's wish on <br>The first star at night <br><br>And I believed there was nothing left <br>Left in my chest <br>Then I lost my grip <br>When you made a wish <br>I could never have guessed <br><br>I'm in a free fall <br>But I won't crash <br>Hit the ground <br>And I bounce right back <br>I'm not comin down no more <br>Not comin down no more <br><br>I've lost all gravity now <br>Like walking on the moon <br>Feels like I'm floating away <br>Without a parachute <br><br>I've lost my fear of flying <br>I'm falling hard for you <br>Not scared of anything <br>So I think I think I'll just <br><br>Jump jump jump jump <br>Without my parachute <br>Jump jump jump jump <br>Straight into you <br><br>I was torn I was left with a permanent scar <br>I'd been there before <br>But you saw through every flaw <br>Found what was lost <br>So I pulled the rip cord <br><br>I'm lettin go <br>I'm gonna jump this time <br>Into the blue <br>Now I won't look back <br>No I won't look back <br>With someone like you <br><br>I'm in a free fall <br>But I won't crash <br>Hit the ground <br>And I bounce right back <br>I'm not comin down no more <br>Not comin down no more <br><br>I've lost all gravity now <br>Like walking on the moon <br>Feels like I'm floating away <br>Without a parachute <br><br>I've lost my fear of flying <br>I'm falling hard for you <br>Not scared of anything <br>So I think I think I'll just <br><br>Jump jump jump jump <br>Without my parachute <br>Jump jump jump jump <br>Without my parachute <br>Jump jump jump jump <br>Without my parachute <br>Jump jump jump jump <br>Straight into you <br>Straight into you <br><br>Straight into youuuuuu <br><br>No I won't look back <br>No I won't look back <br><br>Cuz I've lost all gravity now <br>Like walking on the moon <br>Feels like I'm floating away <br>Without a parachute <br><br>I've lost my fear of flying <br>I'm falling hard for you <br>Not scared of anything <br>So I think I think I'll just <br><br>Jump jump jump jump <br>Without my parachute <br>Jump jump jump jump <br>Without my parachute <br>Jump jump jump jump <br>Without my parachute <br>Jump jump jump jump <br>Straight into you]]></content><category term="James Durbin" label="James Durbin"/><category term="Parachute" label="Parachute"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Children_Under_The_Sun/</id><title>James_Durbin - Children Under The Sun - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:39:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:39:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/James_Durbin/Children_Under_The_Sun/" title="James_Durbin - Children Under The Sun - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Taking a bus to the boardwalk <br>Flying higher than the North Star <br>Lifting the veil above my eyes <br>Drawing spirals in the sky <br><br>Along the way I stopped at the ocean <br>To swim with the dragons in the concrete waters <br>Surrounding myself with no one <br>In beautiful masks they came in numbers <br><br>Wasted <br>We fade into the sun <br><br>We are one <br>Let the rollercoaster <br>Take us over the edge <br>On the run <br>We're children under the sun <br><br>Raise your hands <br>Let the rollercoaster <br>Take you over the edge <br>While we're young <br>We're children under the sun <br><br>Looking at life through a keyhole <br>It's hitting me harder than sledgehammers on a kick drum <br>Surrounded by millions of people <br>Silhouetted dancers in the freak show <br><br>Wasted <br>We fade into the sun <br><br>We are one <br>Let the rollercoaster <br>Take us over the edge <br>On the run <br>We're children under the sun <br><br>Raise your hands <br>Let the rollercoaster <br>Take you over the edge <br>While we're young <br>We're children under the sun <br><br>We're children under the sun <br>We're children under the sun <br>We're children under the sun <br><br>Wasted <br>We fade into the sun <br><br>Let the rollercoaster <br>Take us over the edge <br>Let the rollercoaster <br>Fade into the sun]]></content><category term="James Durbin" label="James Durbin"/><category term="Children Under The Sun" label="Children Under The Sun"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/One_Kiss/</id><title>Eddie_Cochran - One Kiss - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/One_Kiss/" title="Eddie_Cochran - One Kiss - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Give me one kiss, one kiss, that's what I want from you <br>I just want to kiss your lips, that's what I want to do <br>Eleven thirty, the lights are low <br>Just one more kiss dear, before I go <br>Give me one kiss, one kiss, that's what I want from you <br><br>I'll hold you closer at your front door <br>We may have time left for three or four <br>Give me one kiss, one kiss, that's what I want from you <br>Ah, come on, just one little kiss]]></content><category term="Eddie Cochran" label="Eddie Cochran"/><category term="One Kiss" label="One Kiss"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Cradle_Baby/</id><title>Eddie_Cochran - Cradle Baby - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Cradle_Baby/" title="Eddie_Cochran - Cradle Baby - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, they call you cradle baby <br>They say you're too young <br>Oh, that yours is not real love <br>You're just havin' fun <br><br>'Cause you're only sixteen <br>And your life is not free <br>Well, they call you cradle baby <br>But you're just right for me <br><br>So when I need a lovin' <br>And all of us do <br>L know that I'm a cookin' <br>Well, I'm a lookin' for you <br><br>Right back in the cradle <br>They say you should be <br>Well, they call you cradle baby <br>But you're just right for me <br><br>Well, they call you cradle baby <br>Why don't they leave you alone <br>They say your mama will worry <br>If you don't hurry home <br><br>Just a pay no attention <br>'Cause it's all there to see <br>Well, they call you cradle baby <br>But you're just right for me]]></content><category term="Eddie Cochran" label="Eddie Cochran"/><category term="Cradle Baby" label="Cradle Baby"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Have_I_Told_You_Lately_That_I_Love_You/</id><title>Eddie_Cochran - Have I Told You Lately That I Love You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Have_I_Told_You_Lately_That_I_Love_You/" title="Eddie_Cochran - Have I Told You Lately That I Love You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Have I told you lately that I love you <br>Could I tell you once again somehow <br>Have I told you with all my heart and soul, how I adore you <br>Well darling, I'm telling you now <br>This heart would break in two if you'd refuse me <br>I'm no good without you anyhow <br>Have I told you lately that I love you <br>Well darling, I'm telling you now]]></content><category term="Eddie Cochran" label="Eddie Cochran"/><category term="Have I Told You Lately That I Love You" label="Have I Told You Lately That I Love You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Tell_Me_Why/</id><title>Eddie_Cochran - Tell Me Why - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Tell_Me_Why/" title="Eddie_Cochran - Tell Me Why - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tell me why the ivy twines <br>Tell me why the stars do shine <br>Tell me why the ocean's blue <br>And I will tell you just why I love you <br><br>Because God made the ivy twine <br>Because God made the stars to shine <br>Because God made the ocean blue <br>Because God made you, that's why I love you]]></content><category term="Eddie Cochran" label="Eddie Cochran"/><category term="Tell Me Why" label="Tell Me Why"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Stockings_And_Shoes/</id><title>Eddie_Cochran - Stockings And Shoes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Stockings_And_Shoes/" title="Eddie_Cochran - Stockings And Shoes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, my baby goes rockin', ooh, rockin' all night <br>No shoes no stockin's, but that's all right <br>Well she don't need stockin's and shoes to rock all night <br>Ooh, stockin's and shoes, stockin's and shoes <br>Well you don't need stockin's and shoes to dance the blues <br>Well I love a my baby, indeed I do <br>Well I love a my baby, she loves me too <br>You oughta see us rock without stockin's and shoes <br>Ooh, stockin's and shoes, stockin's and shoes <br>Well you don't need stockin's and shoes to dance the blues <br>Well the bare feet slappin' on the hardwood floor <br>These crazy things a happen, along about four <br>And the very next night my baby's a back for more <br>Ooh, stockin's and shoes, stockin's and shoes <br>Well you don't need stockin's and shoes to dance the blues <br>Well I bought my baby some crazy socks <br>I love my baby, but she don't wear socks <br>Yeah she kicks her shoes right off and man she rocks <br>Ooh, stockin's and shoes, stockin's and shoes <br>Well you don't need stockin's and shoes to dance the blues <br>Ooh, stockin's and shoes, stockin's and shoes <br>Stockin's and shoes]]></content><category term="Eddie Cochran" label="Eddie Cochran"/><category term="Stockings And Shoes" label="Stockings And Shoes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Mean_When_Im_Mad/</id><title>Eddie_Cochran - Mean When I`m Mad - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Mean_When_Im_Mad/" title="Eddie_Cochran - Mean When I`m Mad - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You petrify me, a baby, ooh, satisfy me, a baby <br>But don't defy me, a baby <br>'Cause I'm mighty, mighty mean when I'm mad <br>You tantalize me, a baby, you hypnotize me, a baby <br>But don't surprise me, a baby <br>'Cause I'm mighty, mighty mean when I'm mad <br>Don't want my lovin' from another girl <br>'Cause you mean more to me than this whole wide world <br>I need your lovin' and I need it bad <br>Watch out a baby if you make me mad <br>So hug and kiss a me, a baby <br>Act like you missed me, a baby <br>But don't resist me, a baby <br>'Cause I'm mighty, mighty mean when I'm mad]]></content><category term="Eddie Cochran" label="Eddie Cochran"/><category term="Mean When I`m Mad" label="Mean When I`m Mad"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Proud_Of_You/</id><title>Eddie_Cochran - Proud Of You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Proud_Of_You/" title="Eddie_Cochran - Proud Of You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm just as proud as I can be <br>And everytime you're out with me <br>I'm hopin' everyone will see <br>'Cause I'm so proud of you <br>When we go walkin' down the street <br>I show you off to all we meet <br>You roll your eyes and look so sweet <br>I'm just so proud of you <br>When we go home together after school each night <br>I don't want no other, you're a doll all right <br>I'm just so proud when I'm with you <br>The way you wear that cute hair do <br>And when you blush, I love that too <br>I'm just so proud of you]]></content><category term="Eddie Cochran" label="Eddie Cochran"/><category term="Proud Of You" label="Proud Of You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Lovin_Time/</id><title>Eddie_Cochran - Lovin` Time - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Lovin_Time/" title="Eddie_Cochran - Lovin` Time - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The breeze will tease the trees <br>And whistle by the brook, we'll take a look <br>And ripple by your ear, to clew you in <br>It's lovin' time again <br>For you and I will find a hideaway for love <br>Will always have the right of way <br>No need to tell us two, it's lovin' time again <br>Lovin' time again <br><br>Now if the girl for you can't see your point of view <br>Lovin' time will leave a spell <br>The first thing that you know, you'll have a heart in tow <br>The rest is up to you <br>The moon will be discreet <br>It won't repaet the things you say to me <br>It's time we meet, so let romance begin <br>It's lovin' time again lovin' time again]]></content><category term="Eddie Cochran" label="Eddie Cochran"/><category term="Lovin` Time" label="Lovin` Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Im_Alone_Because_I_Love_You/</id><title>Eddie_Cochran - I`m Alone Because I Love You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Im_Alone_Because_I_Love_You/" title="Eddie_Cochran - I`m Alone Because I Love You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm alone because I love you <br>Love you with all my heart <br>Oh, I'm alone because I had to be true <br>Sorry, I can't say the same about you <br>Yesterday's kisses are bringing me pain <br>Yesterday's sunshine has turned into rain <br>I'm alone because I love you <br>Love you with all my heart]]></content><category term="Eddie Cochran" label="Eddie Cochran"/><category term="I`m Alone Because I Love You" label="I`m Alone Because I Love You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Undying_Love/</id><title>Eddie_Cochran - Undying Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Undying_Love/" title="Eddie_Cochran - Undying Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're the world to me, until eternity <br>It will always be, undying love <br>As long as stars will shine, I will call you mine <br>Till the end of time, undying love <br>Please don't ever leave me, grieve me, deceive me <br>Never let me go never let me go <br>Try to understand me, commend me, demand me <br>I'll always love you so <br>You're the world to me, until eternity <br>It will always be, undying love]]></content><category term="Eddie Cochran" label="Eddie Cochran"/><category term="Undying Love" label="Undying Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Completely_Sweet/</id><title>Eddie_Cochran - Completely Sweet - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Completely_Sweet/" title="Eddie_Cochran - Completely Sweet - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well completely sweet that's my baby <br>Completely sweet, I don't mean maybe <br>Well completely sweet that's my baby <br>Completely sweet, I don't mean maybe <br>And I love her more 'n' more each day <br>She's so completely sweet <br><br>Well a just like a honey, that the bees bring in <br>Mmm, a just like a honey, that the bees bring in <br>Mmm, I get my sugar, when I kiss her on the chin <br><br>Well the sugar in my coffee, well the sugar in my tea <br>Well the sugar in my coffee, mmmm the sugar in my tea <br>Mmm, they both taste better, with a sugar on my knee]]></content><category term="Eddie Cochran" label="Eddie Cochran"/><category term="Completely Sweet" label="Completely Sweet"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Sittin_In_The_Balcony/</id><title>Eddie_Cochran - Sittin` In The Balcony - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Cochran/Sittin_In_The_Balcony/" title="Eddie_Cochran - Sittin` In The Balcony - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm just a sittin' in the balcony <br>Just a watchin' the movie <br>Or maybe it's a symphony, I wouldn't know <br>I don't care about the symphonies <br>Just a cymballs and a timpanies <br>I'm just a sittin' in the balcony, on the very last row <br>I'll hold your hand and I'll kiss you too <br>The feature's over, but we're not through <br>Just a sittin' in the balcony <br>Holdin' hands in the balcony <br>Just a sittin' in the balcony, on the very last row <br><br>We may stop lovin' to watch Bugs Bunny <br>But he can't take the place of my honey <br>Just a sittin' in the balcony <br>Just a snootchin' in the balcony <br>Just a sittin' in the balcony, on the very last row <br>Just a huggin' and a kissin' <br>With my baby in the very last row]]></content><category term="Eddie Cochran" label="Eddie Cochran"/><category term="Sittin` In The Balcony" label="Sittin` In The Balcony"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Day_Of_Rain/</id><title>Thriving_Ivory - Day Of Rain - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Day_Of_Rain/" title="Thriving_Ivory - Day Of Rain - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Late again <br>Guilt free in the middle of the pouring rain <br>Hair's a mess she said <br>Would you mind if I spent the night alone <br><br>3am she's up said <br>It's not you and it never was <br>Packs her things she's gone where <br>That place I'll never know <br>Somewhere in the middle of the pouring rain <br><br>I wake up late <br>Sometimes I wish I never woke up at all <br>And I contemplate <br>I guess maybe I'm better off alone <br><br>I'm gonna leave this place <br>I guess winter got the best of us this year <br>And the sky's a mess <br>I'll run out in the middle of the pouring rain <br><br>When the day is done and you're not here again <br>When the day is done and you're not here again <br>When the day is done and you're not here again <br><br>I'll run out in the middle of the pouring rain <br>God speed in the middle of the pouring rain <br>I'll find love in the middle of the pouring rain]]></content><category term="Thriving Ivory" label="Thriving Ivory"/><category term="Day Of Rain" label="Day Of Rain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Light_Up_Mississippi/</id><title>Thriving_Ivory - Light Up Mississippi - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Light_Up_Mississippi/" title="Thriving_Ivory - Light Up Mississippi - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The silence never changes <br>In the city with no name <br>Would you come down after midnight <br>Leave the rest of us to shame <br>Why don't we talk to the dead <br>When the living's all the same <br>Why do we crawl like babies <br>Why don't we light up anyway <br><br>Come down Mississippi tonight <br>As we all watch under big lights <br><br>You grow up fast and lonely <br>With the lines to mark your face <br>Bet you never felt so empty <br>Have you wasted all your days <br><br>We're you born from the seed of disguise <br>Do you pray to become undone <br>You're the best of all that you know <br>So uncover me in the big lights <br><br>Come down Mississippi tonight <br>As we all watch under big lights <br>Why don't you come down Mississippi tonight <br>As we all watch under big lights <br><br>Why don't we talk to the dead <br>When the living's all the same <br>Why do we crawl like babies, baby <br>Why don't we light up anyway <br><br>Come down Mississippi tonight <br>As we all watch under big lights <br><br>Come down Mississippi tonight <br>As we all watch under big lights]]></content><category term="Thriving Ivory" label="Thriving Ivory"/><category term="Light Up Mississippi" label="Light Up Mississippi"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Unhappy/</id><title>Thriving_Ivory - Unhappy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Unhappy/" title="Thriving_Ivory - Unhappy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She takes her clothes off and she says <br>Is it alright if I stay the night <br>I don't remember what I said, is it alright <br><br>Well she's gone when I awake <br>Left a letter, saying everything was a mistake <br>And I'm alone, but it's alright <br>'Cause I understand, I could tell everything's not fine <br>It's never alright to push away, I'm not as blind as you may think <br>And I'm tired of all that is <br>And I know that this time it's not all in my head <br><br>You look a little unhappy, 'bout the way the world is turning <br>Is there anything I could do to take your mind off <br>Your troubled hearted kind And she said maybe, just maybe <br>You won't end up like him <br><br>It's just another day it's cold <br>And I'm losin' myself inside <br>The colors on the wall, are all fading <br>And all that's left is a hope for another day <br>That's not cold again, and it's a shame <br><br>You look a little unhappy, 'bout the way the world is turning <br>Is there anything I could do to take your mind off <br>Your troubled hearted kind And she said maybe, just maybe <br>You won't end up like him <br><br>Must have been around midnight, There's a ghost at the door <br>She said please go slowly, cause we've all been here before <br>She takes her clothes off and she says <br>Is it alright if I stay the night <br>I don't remember what I said, is it alright <br>And I know that this time it's not all in my head <br><br>You look a little unhappy, 'bout the way the world is turning <br>Is there anything I could do to take your mind off <br>Your troubled hearted kind And she said maybe, just maybe <br>You won't end up like him]]></content><category term="Thriving Ivory" label="Thriving Ivory"/><category term="Unhappy" label="Unhappy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/For_Heavens_Sake/</id><title>Thriving_Ivory - For Heavens Sake - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/For_Heavens_Sake/" title="Thriving_Ivory - For Heavens Sake - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pull yourself together <br>Before you set yourself apart <br>Make every door you walk through <br>A living work of art <br>For Heaven's Sake <br><br>For heaven's sake there's more at stake <br>Than we may ever learn <br>More footsteps to hold onto and corners to be turned <br>Like weeping violins, you tremble and you shake <br>Don't you dwell on the future for it's miles away <br>For Heaven's Sake <br><br>Your talkin' in your sleep <br>Like there's nothing more to lose <br>Well hey you know you're not alone <br>Cause honey I get lonely too <br>And it feels so familiar, must have been here before <br>Singin' I don't wanna go but I don't wanna hurt anymore <br>For Heaven's Sake <br><br>And I know and I know and I know <br>That it ain't always fair <br>You're gonna have to let it go <br>No you're not moving anywhere <br><br>Pull yourself together <br>Before you set yourself apart <br>Make every door you walk through <br>A living work of art <br>For Heaven's Sake <br><br>And I know and I know and I know <br>That you've had more than you can bare <br>But you're gonna have to let it go <br>No you're not moving anywhere <br>For Heaven's Sake]]></content><category term="Thriving Ivory" label="Thriving Ivory"/><category term="For Heavens Sake" label="For Heavens Sake"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Overrated/</id><title>Thriving_Ivory - Overrated - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Overrated/" title="Thriving_Ivory - Overrated - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She makes herself at home <br>God it's better than her place <br>She loves the little things <br>God we all need something <br><br>She swears this life is often overrated <br><br>Wont see her in the movies <br>Ain't no Marilyn Monroe <br>She calls herself Maria <br>Because she likes the name <br><br>She swears this life is often overrated <br>She can't relate to a world that only knows her by her face <br>Is here anyone still breathing <br>And she thinks that I'm the one that makes it rain <br><br>She never cared for reason <br>And no religion at all <br>She said it makes her feel unsteady <br>Without a god to blame <br><br>She swears this life is often overrated <br>She can't relate to a world that only knows her by her face <br>Is there anyone still breathing <br>And she thinks that I'm the one that makes it rain]]></content><category term="Thriving Ivory" label="Thriving Ivory"/><category term="Overrated" label="Overrated"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Long_Hallway_With_A_Broken_Light/</id><title>Thriving_Ivory - Long Hallway With A Broken Light - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Long_Hallway_With_A_Broken_Light/" title="Thriving_Ivory - Long Hallway With A Broken Light - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[White lines that never fade <br>Burn deep with everyday <br>And I need to know <br>You live here in a photograph <br>No sound and no regrets <br>And I need to know <br>Heart stained but never weak <br>You lay down alone but you don't mind <br>Questions that never breathe <br>Your face on a wall that I can't shake <br><br>I'm walking on air <br>Close to you <br>Through a long hallway with a broken light <br>And I, I need to know <br>If you're still alive <br><br>You hold me like a bag of bones <br>Wrapped up and underground <br>Pull me out so I can feel <br>Make me believe that one more night's not a minute too long <br>When a moment's all I need <br><br>I'm walking on air <br>Close to you <br>Through a long hallway with a broken light <br>And I, I need to know <br>If you're still alive <br><br>You'll marry the night <br>Dance with the pain <br>But you don't mind <br>See the city burn tonight <br>Hearts up in flames <br>Would you carry me away <br><br>I'm walking on air <br>Close to you <br>Through a long hallway with a broken light <br>And I, I need to know <br>If you're still alive]]></content><category term="Thriving Ivory" label="Thriving Ivory"/><category term="Long Hallway With A Broken Light" label="Long Hallway With A Broken Light"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Secret_Life/</id><title>Thriving_Ivory - Secret Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Secret_Life/" title="Thriving_Ivory - Secret Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hangs up her coat like always <br>Wouldn't have it any other way <br>The TV glows in her apartment <br>Much better than most company <br>Is something on your mind <br>Hands are cold as ice <br><br>You dance like a queen <br>In spite of all the things you never wanted <br>When you're left out in the cold <br>You dance like a queen <br>Your silhouette is still my reflection <br>You speak to me in riddles <br>You speak to me in riddles <br><br>Puts on her face like breathing <br>Another day in black and red <br>Coat is old <br>Car seat's freezing <br>And a radio that just wont play <br><br>You dance like a queen <br>In spite of all the things you never wanted <br>When you're left out in the cold <br>You dance like a queen <br>Your silhouette is still my reflection <br>You speak to me in riddles <br>You speak to me in riddles <br><br>Is something on your mind <br>Hands are cold as ice she says <br>Tell me about your secreat life <br>And all the things you've seen <br>Tell me what you think of me <br><br>You dance like a queen <br>In spite of all the things you never wanted <br>When you're left out in the cold <br>You dance like a queen <br>Your silhouette is still my reflection <br>You speak to me in riddles <br>You speak to me in riddles]]></content><category term="Thriving Ivory" label="Thriving Ivory"/><category term="Secret Life" label="Secret Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Twilight/</id><title>Thriving_Ivory - Twilight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Twilight/" title="Thriving_Ivory - Twilight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I recall a long farewell <br>And a time to choose <br>So we part like rivers baby <br>Yeah like rivers do <br>But I still talk about you though <br>And wonder how it is you life will unfold <br><br>Show me what it looks like <br>Outside your window at twilight <br>Show me what it looks like <br><br>I recall drivin' home <br>This ain't gonna hit me till god knows when <br>You know I feel it in my bones <br>And I wear it on my skin <br>But there ain't no use in right or wrong <br>A heart must go where it belongs <br><br>Show me what it looks like <br>Outside your window at Twilight <br><br>It is me that you see <br>Dancing on a line <br>Singin' I could be yours <br>If you would be mine <br><br>C'mon grow old with me <br>And surely you will see <br><br>I remember thinking <br>Boy you must be dreaming <br>So hold on <br>Hold on <br>Before it's all gone <br>And I do remember thinking <br>That your world will go on spinning <br>Without me now <br>So c'mon <br>C'mon please <br><br>Show me what it looks like <br>Outside your window at twilight <br>Show me what it looks like <br>Outside your window at twilight <br>Is it me that you see <br>Dancing on a line <br>Singin' I could be yours if you would be mine <br><br>C'mon grow old with me <br>And surely you will see <br><br>I recall a long farewell <br>And a time to choose <br>So we part like rivers baby <br>Yeah like rivers do]]></content><category term="Thriving Ivory" label="Thriving Ivory"/><category term="Twilight" label="Twilight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Hey_Lady/</id><title>Thriving_Ivory - Hey Lady - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Hey_Lady/" title="Thriving_Ivory - Hey Lady - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She checks her pulse <br>Gotta know if her heart's still beating <br>And the hospital's <br>Not far if anything should happen here <br>She's bored in a week <br>Big dreams but nothing material <br>And I refuse to believe <br>That love is for the weak <br>I'm not vulnerable <br><br>Hey lady <br>Don't give up on me <br>Don't burn your heart out love <br>Till we're ash over seas <br>Hey lady <br>Said I don't wanna fight <br>Like pretty girls need cowboys <br>I need you here tonight <br><br>She screams for more <br>More than just some blue eyed metaphor <br>And the trouble is <br>The trouble is she's always searching <br>The hour's late <br>Don't wanna hear that it's all gonna end soon <br>Not I'm not crazy <br>I'm in control <br>And all of my friends still know <br><br>Hey lady <br>Don't give up on me <br>Don't burn your heart out love <br>Till we're ash over seas <br>Hey lady <br>Said I don't wanna fight <br>Like pretty girls need cowboys <br>I need you here tonight <br><br>I'm on one knee <br>Lover please <br>How can I put it more simply <br>And I wait for your invitation <br>And I'm so so so so over waiting <br>I'm on one knee <br>Lover please <br>How can I put it more simply <br><br>Hey lady <br>Don't give up on me <br>Dont' burn your heart out love <br>Till we're ash over seas <br>Hey lady <br>Said I don't wanna fight <br>Like pretty girls need cowboys <br>I need you here tonight]]></content><category term="Thriving Ivory" label="Thriving Ivory"/><category term="Hey Lady" label="Hey Lady"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Alien/</id><title>Thriving_Ivory - Alien - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Alien/" title="Thriving_Ivory - Alien - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No need to be here <br>No card to clock in <br>And I could swear somebody's watchin' <br>Where I go and where I've been <br>Brother I could see Moses <br>And all the things he did for you <br>Oh brother I've been hearin' voices <br>That I'm probably not supposed to <br>How will I walk steady <br>If the ground should come alive <br>And how will I be ready <br>For the world another time <br><br>Oh alien <br>You'll be just fine <br>You've always been beautiful to me <br>Oh alien <br>Pay us no mind <br>We haven't the light you hold to see <br><br>So am I another slave now <br>To the screamin' in my head <br>Or is it a little strange now <br>How the moment's gone and fled <br>Bother I gotta tell you <br>That something here is wrong <br>Oh brother I gotta tell ya <br>This place ain't what I thought <br><br>Oh alien <br>You'll be just fine <br>You've always been beautiful to me <br>Oh alien <br>Pay us no mind <br>We haven't the light you hold to see <br><br>I know I ain't gonna live forever <br>And I know you feel the same <br>You'll see it when you're older <br>No love is not a game anymore <br>So thank god we're together <br><br>Oh alien <br>You'll be jsut fine <br>You've always been beautiful to me <br>Oh alien <br>Pay us no mind <br>We haven't the light you hold to see <br>Oh alien]]></content><category term="Thriving Ivory" label="Thriving Ivory"/><category term="Alien" label="Alien"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Angels_On_The_Moon/</id><title>Thriving_Ivory - Angels On The Moon - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Angels_On_The_Moon/" title="Thriving_Ivory - Angels On The Moon - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do you dream that the world will know your name <br>So tell me your name <br>Do you care about all the little things <br>or anything at all <br>I wanna feel, all the chemicals inside <br>I wanna feel <br>I wanna sunburn, just to know that I'm alive <br>To know I'm alive <br><br>Don't tell me if I'm dying <br>'Cause I don't wanna know <br>If I can't see the sun, maybe I should go <br>Don't wake me 'cause I'm dreaming <br>Of angels on the moon <br>Where everyone you know <br>Never leaves too soon <br><br>Do you believe, in the day that you were born <br>Tell me do you believe <br>Do you know, that every day's the first <br>Of the rest of your life <br><br>Don't tell me if I'm dying <br>'Cause I don't wanna know <br>If I can't see the sun <br>Maybe I should go <br>Don't wake me 'cause I'm dreaming <br>Of angels on the moon <br>Where everyone you know <br>Never leaves too soon <br><br>This is to one last day in the shadows <br>And to know a brother's love <br>This is to New York City angels <br>And the rivers of our blood <br>This is to all of us <br>To all of us <br><br>Don't tell me if I'm dying <br>'Cause I don't wanna know <br>If I can't see the sun <br>Maybe I should go <br>Don't wake me 'cause I'm dreaming <br>Of angels on the moon <br>Where everyone you know never leaves too soon <br><br>You can tell me all your thoughts <br>About the stars that fill polluted skies <br>And show me where you run to <br>When no one's left to take your side <br>But don't tell me where the road ends <br>'Cause I just don't wanna know <br>No I don't wanna know <br><br>Don't tell me if I'm dying <br>Don't tell me if I'm dying]]></content><category term="Thriving Ivory" label="Thriving Ivory"/><category term="Angels On The Moon" label="Angels On The Moon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Runaway/</id><title>Thriving_Ivory - Runaway - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thriving_Ivory/Runaway/" title="Thriving_Ivory - Runaway - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I am more than you know <br>Street lights and open roads <br>I am more than a face <br>Stuck living in one place <br>So call me California <br>Call me what you will <br>'Cause I am bigger than this place <br>And so far from alone <br><br>I don't believe in your hate <br>Cause these scars are gonna fade <br>So pour me out like water <br>And soak me up like rain <br><br>Like a runaway <br>Spend these nights counting stars <br>Like a runaway <br>And maybe I could call this home tonight <br><br>I whisper all these secrets <br>To a blank page on a line <br>Said we don't speak like lovers <br>And my words are dripping with wine <br>So call me California <br>Call me what you will <br>Cause I am bigger than this place <br>And so far from alone <br><br>Like a runaway <br>Spend these nights counting stars <br>Like a runaway <br>And maybe I could call this home tonight <br>Like a runaway <br><br>When burning bridgs wont come down <br>Like symphonies without a sound <br>I spend these nights counting stars <br>And wonder if there's hope for me out there <br><br>Like a runaway <br>Spend these nights counting stars <br>Like a runaway <br>And maybe I could call this home tonight]]></content><category term="Thriving Ivory" label="Thriving Ivory"/><category term="Runaway" label="Runaway"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이루/못_Inst/</id><title>이루 - 못 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%A3%A8/%EB%AA%BB_Inst/" title="이루 - 못 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아파 너무 아파 <br>그대가 못처럼 박혀서 <br>빼내려해도 버리려해도 <br>손댈 수 없을 만큼 아파 <br>my pain my heart <br>조금씩 파고드는 그대 <br>찾으려해도 지우려해도 <br>보이지 않아요 그대 <br>그대를 잊을 수 있나요 <br>그대를 지울 수 있나요 <br>하루하루 내 가슴에 그대 <br>아파오네요 <br>그대를 빼낼 수 없다면 <br>그대를 간직하려 해요 <br>하루하루 지날수록 너무 <br>보고싶어요 <br>my pain my heart <br>조금씩 파고드는 그대 <br>찾으려해도 찾고싶어도 <br>보이지 않아요 그대 <br>그대를 잊을 수 있나요 <br>그대를 지울 수 있나요 <br>하루하루 내 가슴에 그대 <br>아파오네요 <br>그대를 빼낼 수 없다면 <br>그대를 간직하려 해요 <br>하루하루 지날수록 너무 <br>보고싶어요 <br>사랑이 흘러서 <br>가슴을 적셔서 <br>번져가는데 어떡하나요 <br>그대를 잊을 수 없다면 <br>그대를 사랑하려 해요 <br>지금처럼 이대로만 <br>그대 있어주세요 <br>그대 있어주세요 <br>]]></content><category term="이루" label="이루"/><category term="못 (Inst.)" label="못 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이루/못/</id><title>이루 - 못 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%A3%A8/%EB%AA%BB/" title="이루 - 못 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아파 너무 아파 <br>그대가 못처럼 박혀서 <br>빼내려해도 버리려해도 <br>손댈 수 없을 만큼 아파 <br>my pain my heart <br>조금씩 파고드는 그대 <br>찾으려해도 지우려해도 <br>보이지 않아요 그대 <br>그대를 잊을 수 있나요 <br>그대를 지울 수 있나요 <br>하루하루 내 가슴에 그대 <br>아파오네요 <br>그대를 빼낼 수 없다면 <br>그대를 간직하려 해요 <br>하루하루 지날수록 너무 <br>보고싶어요 <br>my pain my heart <br>조금씩 파고드는 그대 <br>찾으려해도 찾고싶어도 <br>보이지 않아요 그대 <br>그대를 잊을 수 있나요 <br>그대를 지울 수 있나요 <br>하루하루 내 가슴에 그대 <br>아파오네요 <br>그대를 빼낼 수 없다면 <br>그대를 간직하려 해요 <br>하루하루 지날수록 너무 <br>보고싶어요 <br>사랑이 흘러서 <br>가슴을 적셔서 <br>번져가는데 어떡하나요 <br>그대를 잊을 수 없다면 <br>그대를 사랑하려 해요 <br>지금처럼 이대로만 <br>그대 있어주세요 <br>그대 있어주세요 <br>]]></content><category term="이루" label="이루"/><category term="못" label="못"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Civil_Twilight/Teardrop/</id><title>Civil_Twilight - Teardrop - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:40:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:40:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Civil_Twilight/Teardrop/" title="Civil_Twilight - Teardrop - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love, love is a verb <br>Love is a doing word <br>I feel like the sun might give way <br>Gentle implosions <br>Wakes and makes me tired <br>Fearless on my breath <br><br>Teardrops on your fire <br>Burning in my heart, today <br>Teardrops on your fire <br>Burning away <br><br>Teardrops on your fire <br>Black flowers blossom <br>I feel like the sun might give way <br>Oceans in my head <br>Crash against my lonely bed <br>I feel like the sun might give way <br><br>Teardrops on your fire <br>Burning in my heart, today <br>Teardrops on your fire <br>Burning away <br><br>Teardrops on your fire 4x <br><br>I feel them burning 3x <br><br>Burning 2x <br><br>Teardrops on your fire <br>Burning on your fire <br>Oh, teardrops on your fire <br>Burning on your fire <br><br>I feel them burning]]></content><category term="Civil Twilight" label="Civil Twilight"/><category term="Teardrop" label="Teardrop"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/테이크_TAKE/향수/</id><title>테이크_TAKE - 향수 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%85%8C%EC%9D%B4%ED%81%AC_TAKE/%ED%96%A5%EC%88%98/" title="테이크_TAKE - 향수 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그 곳이 차마 <br>꿈엔들 잊힐리야 <br>넓은 벌 동쪽 끝으로 <br>옛 이야기 지줄대는 <br>실개천이 휘돌아 나가고 <br>얼룩백이 황소가 <br>해설피 금빛 게으른 <br>울음을 우는 곳 <br>그 곳이 차마 꿈엔들 잊힐리야 <br>질화로에 재가 식어지면 <br>빈 밭에 밤바람 소리 <br>말을 달리고 <br>엷은 졸음에 겨운 <br>늙으신 아버지가 <br>짚 베개를 돋아 고이시는 곳 <br>그 곳이 차마 꿈엔들 잊힐리야 <br>함부로 쏜 화살을 찾으려 <br>풀섶 이슬에 함초롬 휘적시던 곳 <br>그 곳이 차마 꿈엔들 잊힐리야 <br>전설 바다에 춤추는 <br>밤물결 같은 <br>검은 귀밑머리 날리는 <br>어린 누이와 <br>아무렇지도 않고 <br>예쁠 것도 없는 <br>사철 발 벗은 아내가 <br>따가운 햇살을 등에 지고 <br>이삭 줍던 곳 <br>그 곳이 차마 꿈엔들 <br>꿈엔들 잊힐리야 <br>하늘에는 성근 별 <br>알 수도 없는 <br>모래성으로 발을 옮기고 <br>서리 까마귀 우지 <br>짖고 지나가는 초라한 지붕 <br>그 끝에 도란도란 거리는 곳 <br>그 곳이 차마 그 곳이 차마 <br>전설 바다에 춤추는 <br>밤물결 같은 <br>검은 귀밑머리 날리는 <br>어린 누이와 <br>아무렇지도 않고 <br>예쁠 것도 없는 <br>사철 발 벗은 아내가 <br>따가운 햇살을 등에 지고 <br>이삭 줍던 곳 <br>그 곳이 차마 잊힐리야 <br>꿈엔들 잊을까 <br>그 시절 그날의 기억에 <br>그 곳에 <br>]]></content><category term="테이크 (TAKE)" label="테이크 (TAKE)"/><category term="향수" label="향수"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김현성/푸르른_날/</id><title>김현성 - 푸르른 날 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%98%84%EC%84%B1/%ED%91%B8%EB%A5%B4%EB%A5%B8_%EB%82%A0/" title="김현성 - 푸르른 날 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈이 부시게 푸르른 날은 <br>그리운 사람을 그리워하자 <br>저기 저기 저 가을 꽃자리 <br>초록이 지쳐 단풍 드는데 <br>눈이 내리면 어이하리요 <br>봄이 또 오면 어이하리요 <br>내가 죽고서 네가 산다면 <br>네가 죽고서 내가 산다면 <br>눈이 부시게 푸르른 날은 <br>그리운 사람을 그리워하자 <br>저기 저기 저 가을 꽃자리 <br>초록이 지쳐 단풍 드는데 <br>눈이 내리면 어이하리요 <br>봄이 또 오면 어이하리요 <br>내가 죽고서 네가 산다면 <br>네가 죽고서 내가 산다면 <br>눈이 부시게 <br>눈이 부시게 푸르른 날은 <br>그리운 사람을 그리워하자 <br>저기 저기 저기 <br>저 가을 꽃자리 꽃자리 <br>초록이 지쳐 단풍 드는데 <br>]]></content><category term="김현성" label="김현성"/><category term="푸르른 날" label="푸르른 날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/왁스/이별_노래/</id><title>왁스 - 이별 노래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%81%EC%8A%A4/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="왁스 - 이별 노래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[떠나는 그대 <br>조금만 더 늦게 떠나준다면 <br>그대 떠난 뒤에도 <br>내 그대를 사랑하기에 <br>아직 늦지 않으리 <br>그대 떠나는 곳 <br>내 먼저 떠나가서 <br>그대의 뒷모습에 깔리는 <br>노을이 되리니 <br>옷깃을 여미고 어둠 속에서 <br>사람의 집들이 어두워지면 <br>나 그대 위해 <br>노래하는 별이 되리니 <br>떠나는 그대 <br>조금만 더 늦게 떠나준다면 <br>그대 떠난 뒤에도 <br>내 그대를 사랑하기에 <br>아직 늦지 않으리 <br>그대 떠나는 곳 <br>내 먼저 떠나가서 <br>그대의 뒷모습에 깔리는 <br>노을이 되리니 <br>옷깃을 여미고 어둠 속에서 <br>사람의 집들이 어두워지면 <br>나 그대 위해 <br>나 그대 위해 <br>노래하는 별이 되리니 <br>그대 조금만 <br>더 늦게 떠나준다면 <br>그대 떠난 뒤에도 <br>내 그대를 사랑하기에 <br>아직 늦지 않으리 <br>]]></content><category term="왁스" label="왁스"/><category term="이별 노래" label="이별 노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Civil_Twilight/The_Courage_Or_The_Fall/</id><title>Civil_Twilight - The Courage Or The Fall - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Civil_Twilight/The_Courage_Or_The_Fall/" title="Civil_Twilight - The Courage Or The Fall - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Man wasn't made to live alone <br>That's why I have my enemies <br>Whenever I close my eyes <br>They're all I can see <br>Every man needs his saviour <br>Every saviour needs his task <br>But which one am I, the man or the one behind the mask <br>What comes first, the courage or the fall <br><br>Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh <br><br>Is that a saviour outside my window <br>Or is that a reflection of me]]></content><category term="Civil Twilight" label="Civil Twilight"/><category term="The Courage Or The Fall" label="The Courage Or The Fall"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/챈슬러_Chancellor/MURDA_Feat_Dok2/</id><title>챈슬러_Chancellor - MURDA (Feat. Dok2) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B1%88%EC%8A%AC%EB%9F%AC_Chancellor/MURDA_Feat_Dok2/" title="챈슬러_Chancellor - MURDA (Feat. Dok2) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She's working over <br>time she working <br>Working over time <br>she working <br>시험에 들고 있어 <br>너의 아름다움 속에 <br>Hold up hold up <br>비 내려 Money shower <br>Pour up pour up <br>느리게 She grinding <br>매일 밤 매일 밤 <br>Every night <br>She kill me like it's murda <br>Murda murda murda <br>She dancing like its murda <br>Murda murda <br>She give love to the strangers <br>아무도 널 가질 수 없어 <br>너란 여잔 Danger <br>They call you murda murda <br>Ooooh she killin it <br>straight murder scene <br>I can't breath emergency <br>No mercy no courtesy <br>네 말이라면 다 뭐든지 <br>다 해야만 할 것만 같아 <br>네께 난 돼야만 할 것만 같아 <br>시간이 얼마가 지났든 <br>다시 널 봬야 좀 살 것만 같아 <br>Baby just hol up hol up <br>girl where u goin <br>다 완벽한데 좀 외로워 보여 <br>다 필요 없어 그대로만 <br>옆자리만 빼고 그대로 와 <br>Come get this love from me <br>It's yours bae you deserve it <br>You and me 그래 너와 나 <br>남잔 똑같대지 But no I'm not <br>She kill me like it's murda <br>Murda murda murda <br>She dancing like its murda <br>Murda murda <br>She give love to the strangers <br>아무도 널 가질 수 없어 <br>너란 여잔 Danger <br>They call you murda murda <br>Murda murda she dancing <br>in money shower <br>그 모습이 아름다워 날 죽여 <br>Water water you thirsty <br>and now you want her <br>난 너에게 목이 말라 시들어 <br>눈을 감아 <br>넌 다른 세상을 열어 <br>꿈처럼 <br>Working every night <br>밤에 달처럼 <br>All the time all the time <br>Every night <br>She kill me like it's murda <br>Murda murda murda <br>She dancing like its murda <br>Murda murda <br>She give love to the strangers <br>아무도 널 가질 수 없어 <br>너란 여잔 Danger <br>They call you murda murda <br>난 네 아름다움에 노예 너의 <br>난 헤어 나올 수 없어 없어 <br>헤어 나올 수 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="챈슬러 (Chancellor)" label="챈슬러 (Chancellor)"/><category term="MURDA (Feat. Dok2)" label="MURDA (Feat. Dok2)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/장희영/공항에서_Inst/</id><title>장희영 - 공항에서 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%ED%9D%AC%EC%98%81/%EA%B3%B5%ED%95%AD%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C_Inst/" title="장희영 - 공항에서 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이별하는 연인처럼 우리 <br>돌아서도 울지 말자 <br>다시 만날 연인처럼 우리 <br>힘 나게 그렇게 웃자 <br>바쁘다고 밥 거르지 말고 <br>아픈데도 참지 말고 <br>보고 싶어 전화할 때마다 <br>눈물 꾹 사랑해 하자 <br>you’re always on my mind <br>다른 시간에 살아가도 <br>only you and I <br>우리 그날까지 say goodbye <br>함께하던 매번 너의 생일 <br>나 없다고 서럽지 마 <br>너무 외로워도 멀리 있어도 <br>눈물 꾹 사랑해 하자 <br>you’re always on my mind <br>다른 시간에 살아가도 <br>only you and I <br>우리 그날까지 say goodbye <br>오래 걸리진 않을 거야 <br>건강히 잘 지낼게 <br>다시 만날 그때까지만 <br>조금만 기다려 줄래 <br>Because you're my life <br>걱정하지마 함께잖아 <br>Oh You make me smile <br>너를 사랑해서 고마워 <br>you’re always on my mind <br>다른 시간에 살아가도 <br>only you and I <br>우리 그날까지 say goodbye <br>우리 그날까지 say goodbye <br>]]></content><category term="장희영" label="장희영"/><category term="공항에서 (Inst.)" label="공항에서 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/장희영/공항에서/</id><title>장희영 - 공항에서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%ED%9D%AC%EC%98%81/%EA%B3%B5%ED%95%AD%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C/" title="장희영 - 공항에서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이별하는 연인처럼 우리 <br>돌아서도 울지 말자 <br>다시 만날 연인처럼 우리 <br>힘 나게 그렇게 웃자 <br>바쁘다고 밥 거르지 말고 <br>아픈데도 참지 말고 <br>보고 싶어 전화할 때마다 <br>눈물 꾹 사랑해 하자 <br>you’re always on my mind <br>다른 시간에 살아가도 <br>only you and I <br>우리 그날까지 say goodbye <br>함께하던 매번 너의 생일 <br>나 없다고 서럽지 마 <br>너무 외로워도 멀리 있어도 <br>눈물 꾹 사랑해 하자 <br>you’re always on my mind <br>다른 시간에 살아가도 <br>only you and I <br>우리 그날까지 say goodbye <br>오래 걸리진 않을 거야 <br>건강히 잘 지낼게 <br>다시 만날 그때까지만 <br>조금만 기다려 줄래 <br>Because you're my life <br>걱정하지마 함께잖아 <br>Oh You make me smile <br>너를 사랑해서 고마워 <br>you’re always on my mind <br>다른 시간에 살아가도 <br>only you and I <br>우리 그날까지 say goodbye <br>우리 그날까지 say goodbye <br>]]></content><category term="장희영" label="장희영"/><category term="공항에서" label="공항에서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/달총_Cheeze/사랑이라오_Inst/</id><title>달총_Cheeze - 사랑이라오 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%AC%EC%B4%9D_Cheeze/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4%EB%9D%BC%EC%98%A4_Inst/" title="달총_Cheeze - 사랑이라오 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대 오늘 밤 <br>할 일이 많은가요 <br>혹시 이 연락이 <br>그댈 방해할까 봐 <br>한참을 고민하다 <br>전화했어요 <br>혹시 자고 있던 건가요 <br>지금 그대의 집 <br>앞으로 갈게요 <br>혹시 괜찮다면 <br>만나줄 수 있나요 <br>오늘은 이상하게 <br>용기가 생겨서 <br>괜찮을 것 같아 <br>사랑을 아냐고 <br>물었던 그날 밤 <br>난 말없이 웃어 <br>넘겨 버렸죠 <br>곰곰이 생각을 <br>하다 보니까 <br>조금은 알 것 같아 <br>난 그댈 위해 <br>이 밤을 밤새 걸어 <br>저 달을 따겠소 <br>그대 닮은 예쁜 꽃 <br>한 송이와 <br>그대의 집 앞에서 <br>이 노랠 부르겠소 <br>이게 내 사랑이라오 <br>그대가 내 사랑이라오 <br>사랑을 아냐고 <br>물었던 그날 밤 <br>난 말없이 웃어 <br>넘겨 버렸죠 <br>곰곰이 생각을 <br>하다 보니까 <br>조금은 알 것 같아 <br>난 그댈 위해 <br>이 밤을 밤새 걸어 <br>저 달을 따겠소 <br>그대 닮은 예쁜 꽃 <br>한 송이와 <br>그대의 집 앞에서 <br>이 노랠 부르겠소 <br>이게 내 사랑이라오 <br>그대가 내 사랑이라오 <br>이 밤을 밤새 걸어 <br>저 달을 따겠소 <br>그대 닮은 예쁜 꽃 <br>한 송이와 <br>그대의 집 앞에서 <br>이 노랠 부르겠소 <br>이게 내 사랑이라오 <br>그대만 내 사랑이라오 <br>]]></content><category term="달총 (Cheeze)" label="달총 (Cheeze)"/><category term="사랑이라오 (Inst.)" label="사랑이라오 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/달총_Cheeze/사랑이라오/</id><title>달총_Cheeze - 사랑이라오 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%AC%EC%B4%9D_Cheeze/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4%EB%9D%BC%EC%98%A4/" title="달총_Cheeze - 사랑이라오 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대 오늘 밤 <br>할 일이 많은가요 <br>혹시 이 연락이 <br>그댈 방해할까 봐 <br>한참을 고민하다 <br>전화했어요 <br>혹시 자고 있던 건가요 <br>지금 그대의 집 <br>앞으로 갈게요 <br>혹시 괜찮다면 <br>만나줄 수 있나요 <br>오늘은 이상하게 <br>용기가 생겨서 <br>괜찮을 것 같아 <br>사랑을 아냐고 <br>물었던 그날 밤 <br>난 말없이 웃어 <br>넘겨 버렸죠 <br>곰곰이 생각을 <br>하다 보니까 <br>조금은 알 것 같아 <br>난 그댈 위해 <br>이 밤을 밤새 걸어 <br>저 달을 따겠소 <br>그대 닮은 예쁜 꽃 <br>한 송이와 <br>그대의 집 앞에서 <br>이 노랠 부르겠소 <br>이게 내 사랑이라오 <br>그대가 내 사랑이라오 <br>사랑을 아냐고 <br>물었던 그날 밤 <br>난 말없이 웃어 <br>넘겨 버렸죠 <br>곰곰이 생각을 <br>하다 보니까 <br>조금은 알 것 같아 <br>난 그댈 위해 <br>이 밤을 밤새 걸어 <br>저 달을 따겠소 <br>그대 닮은 예쁜 꽃 <br>한 송이와 <br>그대의 집 앞에서 <br>이 노랠 부르겠소 <br>이게 내 사랑이라오 <br>그대가 내 사랑이라오 <br>이 밤을 밤새 걸어 <br>저 달을 따겠소 <br>그대 닮은 예쁜 꽃 <br>한 송이와 <br>그대의 집 앞에서 <br>이 노랠 부르겠소 <br>이게 내 사랑이라오 <br>그대만 내 사랑이라오 <br>]]></content><category term="달총 (Cheeze)" label="달총 (Cheeze)"/><category term="사랑이라오" label="사랑이라오"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Box_Of_Crayons_B-Side/</id><title>Jillette_Johnson - Box Of Crayons (B-Side) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Box_Of_Crayons_B-Side/" title="Jillette_Johnson - Box Of Crayons (B-Side) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My bed is white <br>My floor is blue <br>My walls are red <br>My door is too <br>My eyes are brown <br>My skin is tan <br>I am the colors of a woman <br><br>And every night inside my room <br>I lie awake and think of you <br>And though I'll never play that part <br>You are the color of my heart <br><br>Dadadadadadadadadadada da da da <br><br>And when I wake I look outside <br>I watch the buildings multiply <br>My walls are red <br>My beds still white <br>Just as empty as last night <br><br>Dadadadadadadadadadada da da da <br><br>Your eyes are green <br>Your hair is black <br>You are the colors that I lack <br>Your hands are strong <br>Your skin is tan <br>You are the colors of a man <br><br>Dadadadadadadadadadada da da da <br><br>My box of crayons <br>My box of crayons <br>My box of crayons <br><br>Color me outside my lines <br>Color me outside my lines <br>Color me outside my lines <br><br>My bed is white <br>My floor is blue <br>My walls are red <br>My door is too <br>My eyes are brown <br>Your eyes are green <br>They are the only color <br>They are the only color <br><br>Dadadadadadadadadadada da da da <br><br>The only <br>The only <br>The only color <br><br>Yeah Yeah <br><br>You are the only color I can see]]></content><category term="Jillette Johnson" label="Jillette Johnson"/><category term="Box Of Crayons (B-Side)" label="Box Of Crayons (B-Side)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/170/</id><title>Jillette_Johnson - 17.0 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/170/" title="Jillette_Johnson - 17.0 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Kiss the nape, of my back <br>And lay me down in the silence <br>I like the way you take me out <br>Half my end turns to violence <br>I love you <br>Young blind and dumb <br>And you love me <br>Upside and down <br>Still darling, still we can be 17 <br>Feels like the day, that we met <br>The bite of frost, on the sidewalk <br>The morning glare, the nervous calm <br>The need to touch, the fear to talk <br>Oh I love you <br>Young blind and dumb <br>And you love me <br>Upside and down <br>Love you, young blind and dumb <br>Love me, upside and down <br>Still darling, still we can be 17 <br>Grandfather talks, fire pops <br>The floor creaks, in a chorus <br>How was your day I missed your face <br>But I light up when that door opens <br>I hate Wisconsin, the heaters broken <br>I miss my home on the pacific <br>But ill push through it, we all get homesick <br>But this is home now, cause you're in it <br>And in love you <br>You love me <br>I love you, young blind and dumb <br>And you love me upside and down <br>Love you, young blind and dumb <br>And you love me, upside and down <br>Still darling, we can be <br>Still darling, we can be seventeen]]></content><category term="Jillette Johnson" label="Jillette Johnson"/><category term="17.0" label="17.0"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/True_North/</id><title>Jillette_Johnson - True North - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/True_North/" title="Jillette_Johnson - True North - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The enemy is in my mind <br>But the little belly aches give it, light <br>If I could be inside my body while I move my mouth, then, I <br>Could better swallow what I feel <br>And it would only be like water in a, whale <br>I could release you to the ocean with a mighty sound <br><br>I'll find true north, somewhere, somehow <br>When the road ends, and spits me out <br>I'll call my friends, and wipe my nose <br>Ill find true north, and stumble out <br><br>C'mon be a comedian <br>Got to admit there's something funny in the <br>fall to ruin <br>You're broken, hungover, and living in your parent's house <br><br>You'll find true north, somewhere, somehow <br>When the road ends, and spits you out <br>You'll call your friends, and wipe your nose <br>You'll find true north, and stumble out <br><br>I'm <br>I'm <br>Stumbling <br>Home <br><br>I'm <br>Stumbling <br>Home <br><br>Am I air or am I water will I dry or will I drown <br>I built everything I wanted then I tore it, down <br><br>I am sure <br>As hot as cold <br>The more I learn <br>The less I know <br>I'll find true north, and settle down <br>Release the lowness of my doubt <br>I'll call my friends, and wipe my nose <br>I'll find true north, and stumble home]]></content><category term="Jillette Johnson" label="Jillette Johnson"/><category term="True North" label="True North"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Heathen/</id><title>Jillette_Johnson - Heathen - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Heathen/" title="Jillette_Johnson - Heathen - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cinder blocks around my brain <br>Came to mock but I remain to <br><br>Pray, oh, pray <br>Am I talking to myself <br>Talking to myself <br>Or brother are you with me <br><br>The muscle of a temperate breeze <br>Could KO my philosophy <br><br>And I feel it shake <br>I feel it shake <br>I'm at the belly of a well <br>Talking to myself <br><br>Lover can you lift me <br>Baby, are you still awake, hey, hey <br>Can I tell you about my night screams <br>Would you teach a heathen how to pray <br><br>Cinder blocks around my brain <br>Came to mock but I remain to <br><br>Pray, oh, pray <br>Axion shake, but I came to pray <br>I'm at the belly of a well <br>Talking to myself <br><br>Lover can you lift me <br>Baby, are you still awake, hey, hey <br>Can I tell you about the night screams <br>Would you teach a heathen how to pray <br><br>Oh, brother are you with me <br>Baby, are you still awake, hey, hey <br>Can I tell you about the night screams <br>Would you teach a heathen how to pray <br>Would you teach a heathen how to pray <br>Can I tell you about the lightning <br>Can I muster up a little faith]]></content><category term="Jillette Johnson" label="Jillette Johnson"/><category term="Heathen" label="Heathen"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Basset_Hound/</id><title>Jillette_Johnson - Basset Hound - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Basset_Hound/" title="Jillette_Johnson - Basset Hound - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wanna follow you around <br>Like a dog, like a dog, like a basset hound <br>I wanna feel you everywhere <br>Like the wind, like the wind, and away you spin <br><br>I got my tongue in a knot <br>I got a paper cut heart <br>And it stings, baby, stings <br>From your lemonade love <br>Love me or love me not <br>I am under the wheels of your juggernaut <br><br>I wanna follow you around <br>Like a dog, like a dog, like a basset hound <br>I wanna feel you, sticks and stones <br>In my lungs, in my veins, in my splintered bones <br><br>I got my tongue in a knot <br>I got a paper cut heart <br>And it stings, baby, stings <br>From your lemonade love <br>Love me or love me not <br>I'm an innocent soul in your witching pot <br><br>While you play games, I'll be at your game, baby <br>Watching from a stone's throw away <br>I can wait, I can wait <br><br>I wanna follow you around <br>Like a dog, like a dog, like a basset hound <br>I wanna come in from the cold <br>I'm a stray running 'way, I'm in starving mode <br><br>I got my tongue in a knot <br>I got a paper cut heart <br>And it stings, baby, stings <br>From your lemonade love <br>Love me or love me not <br>You're my great white hope and you're all I've got <br><br>While you play games, I'll be at your game, baby <br>Watching from a stone's throw away, baby <br>Wondering how long it's gonna take <br>I can wait, I can wait <br><br>I wanna follow you around <br>Like a dog, like a dog, like a basset hound <br>Til they bury me in hallowed ground]]></content><category term="Jillette Johnson" label="Jillette Johnson"/><category term="Basset Hound" label="Basset Hound"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Peter_Pan/</id><title>Jillette_Johnson - Peter Pan - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Peter_Pan/" title="Jillette_Johnson - Peter Pan - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We don't get drunk on Tuesday nights anymore <br>We don't don't have the stink from the weed <br>With the towel on the bathroom floor anymore <br><br>Everyone's got something to wake up for <br>Doubling, coupling, only doing couple things <br>We don't get drunk on Tuesday nights anymore <br><br>Well I guess I'm the only one <br>I'm the only one <br>I'm the only one left in Neverland <br><br>Hey where ya going <br>Aren't you sick of growing <br>I'm the only one left in Neverland <br><br>We don't take trips no little white tricks anymore <br>We don't fade away <br>let the world decay on the bathroom floor anymore <br><br>Everyone does what they can get paid for <br>Puppet strings, puppet strings, money moves everything <br><br>We don't take trips for the shit of it anymore <br><br>Well I guess I'm the only one <br>I'm the only one <br>I'm the only one left in Neverland <br><br>Hey where ya going <br>Aren't you sick of growing <br>I'm the only one left in Neverland <br><br>Me and Peter Pan <br><br>We don't wanna ever leave <br><br>Oh oh oh <br>All I need is my shadow <br>Oh oh oh <br>And all the rest is hollow <br>oh oh oh <br>And all the rest is hollow <br><br>Well I guess I'm the only one <br>I'm the only one <br>I'm the only one left in Neverland <br><br>Hey where ya going <br>Aren't you sick of growing <br>I'm the only one left in Neverland <br><br>Me and Peter Pan <br><br>We don't wanna ever leave <br><br>Don't even think I can <br><br>Our never Neverland]]></content><category term="Jillette Johnson" label="Jillette Johnson"/><category term="Peter Pan" label="Peter Pan"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Pauvre_Coeur/</id><title>Jillette_Johnson - Pauvre Coeur - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Pauvre_Coeur/" title="Jillette_Johnson - Pauvre Coeur - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If I recall it was a Friday <br>Gentle hum before the war <br>You were high and watching poker <br>And I had just walked in the door <br>You started screaming at the TV <br>Saying, make a play you filthy whore <br>And I was trying to make you see me <br>Like the way you did before <br><br>So I took off my clothes and I opened a bottle <br>And told you I'd do whatever you wanted <br>Naked on the floor, crying I'm too beautiful <br><br>Oh my poor, poor, pauvre coeur <br>Beats no more <br><br>Dare I say I was enamored <br>By the stories of your pain <br>You were darkened in the wild fight <br>And I was tangled in your mane <br>But God forbid you would get angry <br>I had to dive out of the way <br>You'd be gunning for me blindly <br>And there was nothing I could say <br><br>But I love you, don't do this, is it it really worth it <br>That's not very Buddhist and I don't deserve it <br>I'm naked on the floor, crying I'm too beautiful <br><br>Oh my poor, poor, pauvre coeur <br>Beats no more <br>Poor, pauvre coeur <br>Beats no more <br><br>Making me nauseous, open elevator <br>I'm stuck in the middle, there's nobody out there <br>To pull me off my sword <br>I am far too beautiful <br>To be yours]]></content><category term="Jillette Johnson" label="Jillette Johnson"/><category term="Pauvre Coeur" label="Pauvre Coeur"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Last_Bus_Out/</id><title>Jillette_Johnson - Last Bus Out - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Last_Bus_Out/" title="Jillette_Johnson - Last Bus Out - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What if I never make it to the bus stop <br>Never get on <br>What if I never take you to the west coast <br>Move back the clock <br>What if I stay in these sheets <br>And keep your hands on my knees <br>What if I want want to stay <br>And keep my clothes at your place <br>What if I belong in this battle <br>This side with this pillow <br>Sleeping in your sweater <br>Your skin and your smile <br>Maybe I don't in California weather <br>What if I miss the last bus out <br><br>My life is waiting for me at a rental <br>Right on this street <br>They tell me this is where it all happens <br>Where the money is <br>What if I hate the machine <br>And get chewed up by the dream <br>What if I want want to stay <br>And keep my clothes at your place <br>What If I belong in this battle <br>This side with this pillow <br>Sleeping in your sweater <br>Your skin and your smile <br>Maybe I don't in California weather <br>This battle <br>This side with this pillow <br>Sleeping in your sweater <br>Your skin and your smile <br>Maybe I don't in California weather <br>What if I miss the last bus out <br><br>And we stay right here in this garden of skin <br>And bones comatose <br>Ivy's crawling up the bed <br>Tangling our legs <br>Forever till we're dead <br>Baby I belong <br>In this battle <br>This side with this pillow <br>Sleeping in your sweater <br>Your skin and your smile <br>Maybe I don't in California weather <br>This battle <br>This side with this pillow <br>Sleeping in your sweater <br>Your skin and your smile <br>Maybe I don't in California weather <br>What if I miss the last bus <br>What if I miss the last bus <br>What if I miss the last bus out]]></content><category term="Jillette Johnson" label="Jillette Johnson"/><category term="Last Bus Out" label="Last Bus Out"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/When_The_Ship_Goes_Down/</id><title>Jillette_Johnson - When The Ship Goes Down - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/When_The_Ship_Goes_Down/" title="Jillette_Johnson - When The Ship Goes Down - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wanna live in a better part of town <br>Over the park in a bed of garlands <br>With an ivory banister I can slide down <br>And a man outside that I call Simon <br>I wanna fall asleep in a cashmere nightgown <br>When the ship goes down <br><br>I wanna live in a better part of town <br>Where I don't have to hide my diamonds <br>The bourgeois are bubbling around <br>But they can't touch my sweet asylum <br>They'll put me on the first lifeboat out <br>When the ship goes down <br>When the ship goes down <br><br>We deserve a chauffeur in our car <br>Black truffle loaded with caviar <br>White gloves to open up every door <br>Life is short, let's get what we came for <br>Ah, ah, I want more <br>La, la and I'll get what I came for <br>La, la, I want more <br><br>I wanna get high and never come down <br>Mountains of white and music so loud <br>I want to die with jewels in my crown <br>When the ship goes down <br>When the ship goes down <br>When the ship goes down]]></content><category term="Jillette Johnson" label="Jillette Johnson"/><category term="When The Ship Goes Down" label="When The Ship Goes Down"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Flood_The_Ocean/</id><title>Jillette_Johnson - Flood The Ocean - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Flood_The_Ocean/" title="Jillette_Johnson - Flood The Ocean - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come, come, come along <br>Everybody hit their party drum <br>And sit next to your friends <br>Namaste and amen <br><br>Roll off of your tongue <br>Whatever which way you get it done <br>Good grace, god bless <br>Love will fill the emptiness <br><br>Aren't we just <br>The luckiest kids east of the river <br>Plucked out of nowhere, brought together by <br>A greater motion <br>C'mon, c'mon, let's paint the town redder <br>Tie our shoelaces together <br>And unhinge the dam <br>And let flood the ocean <br><br>Fishbowl, rabbit hole <br>Hunkering down to hide the <br>Romance of a hopeless heart <br>But you can't help who you really are <br><br>Learned it from your mum and dad <br>They try to cover you up with elbow pads <br>But you still catch in electric wire <br>Whatever it is that started the fire <br><br>Aren't we just <br>The luckiest kids east of the river <br>Plucked out of nowhere, brought together by <br>A greater motion <br>C'mon, c'mon, let's paint the town redder <br>Tie our shoelaces together <br>And unhinge the dam <br>And let flood the ocean <br><br>Come, come, come along <br>Everybody hit their party drum <br>And sit next to your friends <br>Namaste and amen <br><br>Aren't we just <br>The luckiest kids east of the river <br>Plucked out of nowhere, brought together by <br>A greater motion <br>C'mon, c'mon, let's paint the town redder <br>Tie our shoelaces together <br>And let flood the ocean <br><br>I gotta know, do you remember <br>First thing you said to me was the weather <br>Is breaking open <br>You are the sun, you'll make it better <br>Let's tie our shoelaces together and <br>Unhinge the dam <br>And let flood the ocean]]></content><category term="Jillette Johnson" label="Jillette Johnson"/><category term="Flood The Ocean" label="Flood The Ocean"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Cameron/</id><title>Jillette_Johnson - Cameron - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Cameron/" title="Jillette_Johnson - Cameron - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron's in drag, makes his father mad <br>Since he was a little boy he always felt more comfortable in lipstick <br>People call him fag, teachers turn their backs <br>Off the bus he runs and runs to get home before anyone can catch him <br><br>These days the world is full of aliens <br>The world is full of aliens <br>But you are a real, live human <br>Aren't you, Cameron <br><br>Powder and a brush can cover any cuts <br>And quickly running cotton under cold water rinses out the blood marks <br>Cameron, you're a star <br>A light where there is dark <br>And you're a hundred times a woman <br>A hundred times the man that they are <br><br>These days the world is full of aliens <br>The world is full of aliens, but you are a human <br>A real, live human <br>Aren't you, Cameron <br><br>You're not an alien <br>You're not an alien <br>You're not an alien <br>Cameron <br><br>You're not an alien <br>You're not an alien <br>You're not an alien <br>Cameron <br><br>Cameron's in drag, makes his father mad <br>Since he was a little boy he always felt more comfortable in lipstick <br><br>These days the world is full of aliens <br>The world is full of aliens, but you are a human <br>You're not an alien <br>You are a real, live human <br>Aren't you, Cameron]]></content><category term="Jillette Johnson" label="Jillette Johnson"/><category term="Cameron" label="Cameron"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Torpedo/</id><title>Jillette_Johnson - Torpedo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:41:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:41:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jillette_Johnson/Torpedo/" title="Jillette_Johnson - Torpedo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So come on torpedo <br>So come on torpedo <br><br>I know how to take a right hook <br>I know how to put a shot back <br>I know how to fake a hard look <br>When I just about done lost everything that I had <br>They've been hunting me for decades <br>Barracudas on a warpath <br>But they'll never get me <br>I will not idly go, I got too much to fight for <br><br>So come on torpedo do your worst <br>Get me right in the heart, blow me up 'til you see my ghost <br>But I will not lay down in the road <br>I will not make it easy <br>I ain't got no saints or saviors <br>This is guerrilla and I will fight this war <br>So come on torpedo <br><br>Just a little more morphine <br>A little peace while I writhe <br>I'll get back into it easy <br>Saddle up my horse and ride like a wildfire <br>There's no water so wicked <br>No rapid so ruthless <br>This may be the way I die <br>But I gotta try for the other side <br><br>So come on torpedo do your worst <br>Get me right in the heart, blow me up 'til you see my ghost <br>But I will not lay down in the road <br>I will not make it easy <br>I ain't got no saints or saviors <br>This is guerrilla and I will fight this war <br>So come on torpedo <br><br>Heart in my throat, dirt on my nose <br>Dark diamond in my eyes, will my demons ever die <br>Heart in my throat, dirt on my nose <br>Dark diamond in my eyes, will my demons ever die <br><br>So come on torpedo do your worst <br>Get me right in the heart, blow me up 'til you see my ghost <br>But I will not lay down in the road <br>I will not make it easy <br>I ain't got no saints or saviors <br>This is guerrilla and I will fight this war <br>So come on torpedo <br><br>I will fight this war, so come on torpedo]]></content><category term="Jillette Johnson" label="Jillette Johnson"/><category term="Torpedo" label="Torpedo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Spirit_Animal/World_War_IV_To_The_Floor/</id><title>Spirit_Animal - World War IV (To The Floor) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:42:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:42:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Spirit_Animal/World_War_IV_To_The_Floor/" title="Spirit_Animal - World War IV (To The Floor) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I could be your sugar daddy <br>You could be my sugar mama <br>Without a dollar <br>No water <br><br>We'd have everything we wanted <br>E e e e everything we needed <br>Ready or not <br>honey i'm comin' <br>ready or not <br>better get runnin' <br><br>Know what I want]]></content><category term="Spirit Animal" label="Spirit Animal"/><category term="World War IV (To The Floor)" label="World War IV (To The Floor)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Spirit_Animal/True_Believer/</id><title>Spirit_Animal - True Believer - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-20T23:42:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-20T23:42:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Spirit_Animal/True_Believer/" title="Spirit_Animal - True Believer - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We walked the days, we talk for miles <br>We shared the story, it made us smile <br>But the world is going, it can all be wrong <br><br>Something sweet <br>Someone nice <br>It's all I wanted all my life <br>But I heard you talking <br>Sounds like trouble <br>All you ever say is you need a change <br>True believer <br>Darling, am I right if you stay the same <br>You make me wanna say <br><br>Uh uuh uh uh uh, oh <br>Uh uuh uh uh uh, oh <br><br>You can't lose faith <br>You can't lose sight <br>Just say you want me one more night <br>'Cause heard the talking, all that trouble <br><br>If you go alone <br>If you go alone <br>If you go alone <br>If you go alone <br>If you go alone <br>There's no going back <br><br>All you ever say is you need a change <br>True believer <br>Darling, am I right if you stay the same <br>You make me wanna say <br><br>Uh uuh uh uh uh, oh <br>Uh uuh uh uh uh, oh <br><br>If you go alone <br>There's no going back <br>No going back <br>No going back <br><br>All you ever say is you need a change <br>True believer <br>Darling, am I right if you stay the same <br>You make me wanna say <br>Uh uuh uh uh uh, oh <br>Uh uuh uh uh uh, oh <br><br>All you ever say you need a change <br>True believer <br>Darling, am I right if you stay the same <br>You make me wanna say]]></content><category term="Spirit Animal" label="Spirit Animal"/><category term="True Believer" label="True Believer"/></entry></feed>